911. What's your emergency?
Ma'am, you need to calm down.
Yes, sir, we have units on the way.
There's a dead body
in the warehouse.
Excuse me, sir?
There's a dead body in the warehouse
in Crawfordville.
Can you be more specific
about the location of that warehouse?
West of Crawfordville highway,
South of woodland.
A dirt road.
Do you have an address?
No.
Charlie 44, role to location
of possible dead body.
Is someone on the way?
Yes, but I need you to stay
on the line with me.
Are you sure the victim is dead?
He will be in a second.
Excuse me?
Sir?
Charlie 44, we have shots fired now.
I repeat, shots fired.
I'm not sure what's going on in there,
but I no longer have contact
with the complainant.
Advise and use extreme caution.
This is Charlie 44.
We're on scene.
It's quiet out front.
We're moving in.
10-4. Use caution.
Ems is on the way, too.
Eyes open, Ray.
State police!
State police! Open the door!
You, in the chair!
Stand up and let me see your hands.
Last chance, man!
Stand up!
Lord have mercy.
Do not blow dinner, Ray.
I'm OK.
I mean it.
You need to outside, you go.
I said I'm fine.
This is Charlie 44. You can cancel
that EMS out here, dispatch.
Are you sure, 44?
Oh, yeah, I'm sure.
This looks to be
a successful suicide.
10-4.
What the hell...
Got a light.
Take a look at this, Tommy.
These women all dead?
Doesn't say this one's
every been found.
I recognize that name.
She only went missing 3 weeks ago.
This is 44 again.
We're gonna need bosses,
, detectives,
crime scene out here on the double.
Hell, just...
Send everybody.
Have a good weekend, JJ.
Sorry.
There goes my beach house rental.
And my non-refundable sin
to win weekend
- in Atlantic city.
- Sin to win?
And I always win big.
I didn't have any plans.
These were just faxed to me.
I talked to a Tallahassee Detective
who's been working a missing coed.
Rebecca Daniels- she went missing while
jogging Near the FSU campus 3 weeks ago.
Who's this?
Florida state police responded to an
apparent suicide an hour and a half ago.
Middle-aged male.
Those are photos of him postmortem.
- What's with the tattoos?
- He's covered in them,
almost completely.
That's why they requested our presence.
The tattoos are portraits
of previously missing women,
with the years of death or the years
the remains were recovered, anyway.
The tattoos correlate to faces
on a wall next to the body,
with information on
the women going back 10 years.
Rebecca is also shown on that wall,
but there's no image
of her on the body.
The Detective thinks that that may
mean that she's alive somewhere.
He called in his own suicide,
didn't he?
- Yeah. How did you...
- He staged all this.
No reason to put on a show
without an audience.
Tell them to leave the body where it is.
We need to see it how he wanted it seen.
If this girl's still out there, the only
one who knows where she is may be dead.
"A sincere artist
"tries to create something
which is in itself
"a living thing."
Painter William Dobell.
This heat is brutal.
It isn't so much the heat
as it is the humidity.
At some point it doesn't matter
how you look at it. It all sucks.
- FBI?
- Yes, sir.
John Barton, Tallahassee pd.
I'm the primary on the missing girl,
Rebecca Daniels.
I got my files in
the car if you need them.
I'm Agent Hotchner.
This is Agent Rossi,
Agent Prentiss, Dr. Reid,
Agent Morgan, Agent Jareau.
- We spoke on the phone.
- Thanks for coming out so quickly.
I appreciate that. I've also confirmed
that all the women Are victims
from around the southeast,
Florida, Louisiana, Georgia, Alabama.
Rebecca's the only woman on the wall
Who's not represented on his body?
Yeah, she's the only one.
Hope you have a strong stomach.
The chair was turned like that?
This is exactly where you found him?
Yeah.
Talk about staging.
- Talk about ego.
- There's also
a couple boxes with journal, composition
books. They're filled with writing.
We haven't been through them yet
other than to dust them for prints.
- Have you identified him?
- We're working on it.
We got a rush on the DNA and the prints.
He's cleared locally,
but it's gonna take some time
to get the national records.
- What about property records?
- Talked to the owner.
She said she rented it
a couple weeks ago to a quiet,
normal-looking guy named Bob.
He said he wanted to store some
equipment, and he paid in cash.
They're always normal.
- No lease?
- Month to month, no.
Out here in the boonies you don't
get a lot of, record-keeping types.
Especially when it comes to
cash transactions, I'll bet.
He's no kid,
yet the missings go
back Only 10 years?
- As far as I could tell.
- Late bloomer.
You see this a lot,
these guys killing themselves?
Most serial killers who commit suicide
Do it in prison after they're caught.
JJ, gather as much information
about the prior victims as you can.
Morgan and Prentiss,
take the journals.
Dave, you and Reid, the tattoos.
See if he left any clues about
where miss Daniels might be.
You think there's a chance
she might still be alive?
It's probably better
not to speculate.
May I take a look at the case
files you have on miss Daniels?
He was on the phone
with dispatch and then.
Must be what, 15 feet?
Consummate overachiever.
Right.
Why is it when men kill themselves,
It gets everywhere, but women don't
leave a mess, Like they were never there?
Women worry about
who has to clean up.
Men don't give a damn.
JJ, what have you found?
The earliest clipping
is from 10 years ago,
and they're in order, oldest to newest.
Brenda Carlyle first,
- Rebecca Daniels last.
- That was thoughtful of him.
One victim a year
for 10 years straight.
Each girl's remains were recovered
In a well-traveled wooded area.
Strangled,
repeatedly sexually assaulted,
and then about a week later,
another woman goes missing.
Did the new abductions happen before
the previous body's been found?
- No, never.
- So he has a year-long cycle.
He uses them up
and he gets a newer model.
But he won't take another girl
until the last body's been found.
He's telling a story and he can't start
a new one Until the old one's over.
Look at that. At the turn of
the 16th century, Rose tattoos
were put on men
who were sentenced to death.
Really?
Yeah. If they escaped, it served
to identify them. But now roses
pretty much symbolize pure love.
Pure love.
Right before he kills them.
- Have you read "the illustrated man"?
- Nope.
It's amazing. It's a collection
of short stories By Ray Bradbury,
based on the metafictive device
of a man who's covered in tattoos
drawn by a woman from the future.
At nighttime, the tattoos come to life
and tell a story. It's pretty awesome.
These do tell a story.
You want to see something?
A space in the tree.
And there's no date on that one.
Why would he leave
that space blank?
Maybe this guy's just a psycho.
If it were that simple,
we'd all be out of a job.
Hey, Reid.
What's up?
Our man here was a
prolific journaler.
With teeny tiny handwriting.
He probably had counseling at some point
when journaling was part of his therapy.
That's what we were thinking.
And?
And, uh, Well, you know,
the two of us,
it would take us like 3 days
to read all of this stuff.
You guys owe me.
It's no wonder no one has
ever connected these cases.
They're from different states,
different jurisdictions.
It's probably no accident.
He knows the system.
Why kill himself now?
He wasn't on anyone's radar.
Something changed.
Let's gather everyone.
So what do we know so far?
He wanted the police here.
He wanted us to see all this.
He was definitely a sadist.
From what we saw, his journals
were graphic and meticulous.
Covering himself with
his victims' likeness
is methodical, possessive.
He'll always own them.
And the suicide shows commitment.
He's organized and compulsive.
The crimes are on an annual cycle.
Computer printouts on the board,
they were all printed
on the same day, 2 weeks ago.
That's when he
rented this building.
And proceeded to move everything
into it. It's a history of his crimes.
So he did all of this in 2 weeks.
He got away with it for 10 years.
He could have kept going.
But he decides to end it all
and hand everything to us.
That's it...everything.
- Everything.
- Reid?
Everything. His body,
the tattoos, the clippings,
The printout, the journals.
He moved it all into one room.
He wanted us to see all of it.
See all of him--
his work... the women,
he put them in chronological order.
He's screaming, "look at me."
- We all got that.
- No, but think about it.
If you take a step back,
it sort of makes sense.
It's just a confession.
A giant, flashy confession.
What would we say
if an unsub turned himself in to the police
before they were even onto him?
That he was trying
to hide something.
Or someone.
He made a mistake-
in his third book.
I almost missed it,
but then I caught it.
"I thought it would take longer,
"but today was the lucky day.
"she almost walked right by,
"almost missed her completely,
"but at the last moment,
We found our latest guest."
We.
He has a partner.
He put everything in this room
So we wouldn't look further,
wouldn't dig even deeper.
If he has a partner, he's still out
there, and he's got Rebecca Daniels.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I was calling out, but I guess
your music was too loud.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine. It's all right.
Juliet Monroe?
- That's me.
- That's for you.
If I can get you to sign here.
- Thank you very much. Sorry about that.
- It's fine.
- Have a great day, now.
- You, too.
Ma'am.
My dearest love,
by the time you read this,
I will have gone.
Our life together has
brought me more joy
than a man like me thought
he could ever know.
My first wish would be
to take you with me,
but since you are in our
home readying yourself
with the next chapter
of our life...
to care for and raise
our beautiful child,
My last hope is that you finish...
what we started.
Please...
Just let me go home.
This is your fault.
Please...
What's she doing down there?
She's trying to keep the media
from running the story right now.
But wouldn't that help
us get it out there,
put some pressure on the partner?
But if the partner didn't
know about the suicide,
He might dispose
of miss Daniels and disappear.
If anyone can stop the media
from running something, it's JJ.
So let's profile the partner.
We know that the unsub was
a dominant personality, an Alpha.
Can any of you guys think of a case
where a dominant unsub
committed suicide
- to protect a submissive partner?
- No.
So the partner must be
an equal in some way,
or at least not a competitor,
not somebody that he needed
to feel dominance over.
Maybe it was someone
he cared about?
It would be hard for a sadistic
psychopath to care about anybody.
Which would make the partner all
that much more important to him.
What about the tattoo artist?
He couldn't have done
those by himself.
- Maybe that's the role for the partner.
- It would certainly make him important.
What the hell does any of
this have to do with Becky?
I mean, isn't there something
we should be doing, damn it?
Detective, may I speak
with you for a moment?
So we have until the
evening news--6 P.M.
How much do they know?
Oh, the troopers
told them everything.
Agent Rossi,
please tell me you called
because the case is over
and I can erase this freakity-freak
off my otherwise
uber-delicious desktops.
Long way to go, kid.
I am into epidermartistry
as much as the next gen xer,
but this guy...Eesh, I'm just glad
He's not breathing the same air as you,
my fine furry friends.
Agreed. What have you found out
about tattoo artists down here?
That the state of Florida requires
licensing for all skin illustrators, but
and I am not going to
elaborate on how I know this
not everyone in the body art lifestyle
goes through official channels.
All right, we'll start
with the legit ones
and see if anyone
recognizes the work.
- I shall send the list to your PDA.
- Thanks.
Epidermartistry?
...What is happening.
She will get...
Only a girl can fill
that empty energy.
Starting to get angry.
I approach her door...
Look, I'm sorry I popped off.
I'm just a little worked up.
I've been over the Rebecca
Daniels case file, your reports.
- Do you know her?
- What?
Is there a personal relationship?
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
You've referred to
her twice as Becky.
I did?
And nowhere else is she referred
to that way. It's always Rebecca.
Now, if there's something that's
gonna cloud your judgment,
I need to know about it.
No. I don't know her.
Then what is it?
Look, I've...
I've been doing this
a long time, and...
it usually just washes right over me,
you know, people...
killing people, depravity, you know?
As long as you make it
home at night, right?
But this one...
her parents...
they're just such good,
decent people. She seems
like an amazing girl, and...
it's all...
Sometimes it's just too much.
You take it personal.
Stupid, right?
Caring about a victim,
personalizing them,
can only be stupid
if it's reckless.
Don't worry about me.
I'm good.
All right. Let's go and
try to bring her home.
It's like 110 out here
and it feels like a refrigerator
compared to their warehouse.
How's Reid doing?
It doesn't even seem to faze him.
He's just sitting there
in a corner turning pages.
Yeah, he goes to another
place when he reads.
I've got the addresses of the major
tattoo parlors in Tallahassee.
That work is pretty detailed.
Someone might recognize it.
You want to go check
these out with me?
Sounds fun.
Hey, so, uh, I got a few
more hours out of the media.
Well, we'll take what we can get.
Prentiss and Rossi are going to
check out some tattoo parlors.
Is he OK?
Yeah.
Did you ask him about
calling her Becky?
He'll be all right.
Well, I hope so.
Because we still have no indication
that this girl's even alive.
I wasn't able To tie
up all the loose ends.
You would have known
what was happening.
So now it's left for you.
Wait for night
and take it to the water.
The animals will do the rest.
This guy killed all those women?
Looks like it.
And there's another one missing.
Then he killed himself?
Yeah, he did.
Good. Sort of a public service.
I guess that's a good way
of looking at it.
We send it to
the m.E. 's office in Tallahassee.
You sign it?
I'll take care of that,
later. Thanks.
Thanks a lot.
You sure it's OK to move the body?
Well, there's no reason not to anymore.
We've seen this guy's show.
Have you ever seen
anything like this before?
Like what?
Everything. The suicide,
The clippings, the journal.
I think it's pretty safe to say that no
one's ever seen anything like this.
Man, this is beautiful work.
It's a body suit?
He's completely covered?
Pretty much.
"the illustrated man."
Second time I've heard that today.
The book?
Reid mentioned it.
Everybody in the body art
world knows that story.
You said this dude killed himself?
Did he, like, gash his
wrists open or something?
The tattoos, could you
recognize who did this?
I wish. I'd hire this
dude in a heartbeat.
This looks free-hand.
Trust me, free-hand portraiture
is pretty gnarly to do on skin, man.
Did he shoot himself?
Because none of these
pictures have a head.
Can you tell if the
same artist did these?
It looks like it.
But they weren't all done at the same
time. Some of the inks are newer.
You know, if I saw the body,
I'd probably be able to tell you more.
How about these?
These are a lot of portraits.
What do they mean?
That's what we're
trying to figure out.
Wait.
That doesn't fit.
What doesn't?
There's something
under the rose there.
Looks like...A cross?
A big one.
Where?
Inside the rose.
And the work is sloppy.
See that? They put the rose
over it to cover it up.
Yeah, I see that.
Yeah, that wasn't
done professionally.
More like it was done in jail.
If he did time,
That would explain how
a 50-year-old unsub
- Doesn't start killing until he's 40.
- This dude's a killer?
And why rapists become killers
after they've been in prison.
They learn not to leave a witness.
Garcia can track this through the
biometric recognition program.
So, there's, like, no chance of
me seeing the dead dude, right?
None.
Hey, p.G., I'm gonna send you
a photograph Of a tattoo.
You know, that empty space
On his back makes him exactly like
"the illustrated man."
I thought he was
covered completely.
In the book.
In the movie, there's an
open spot On his back,
so you can see the future.
Rossi and Prentiss think
he may have done time
And that one of the tattoos
may have been done in prison.
That's a good bet.
I've got Garcia running everything
Through the biometrics database.
Biometrics?
Yeah, it catalogues all the
prison inmates and their tattoos.
They have detailed photos of
every one on every inmate.
What happened?
Shut up.
Please, sit down.
You can tell me.
We can sit down and
We can talk about this. We could
Wait! Please...
Can we please talk?
My dad has to be so
worried about me.
Don't you have a father?
I don't have anyone anymore.
Please...
Just
let me go before he comes back.
He's not coming back.
What?
Wait.
You can let me go.
What?
It's just
I won't tell anyone what happened.
I promise I won't tell anyone.
You won't tell anyone?
I know you're afraid of him, too.
You're not going to tell anyone
Because you're never
leaving this room alive.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry...
I was never afraid of him.
I loved him.
I would do anything,
I did anything for him.
He was my masterpiece.
You're bleeding!
I'll be able to fill in the
last space in my art collection.
The last space... Last space...
Last space...
No, no, no, that's not right.
Hey, guys, it isn't
the only blank space.
What do you mean?
The spot on his chest
where we assumed
Rebecca's
portrait would go
In the journal he talks about
filling in the last space,
How once he does that the
artwork will be complete.
And?
It isn't the only blank space.
In his back, in the middle of
that tree Is a giant open spot.
Why would he talk about completing
the artwork when he hasn't?
I need to see the body again.
I'll go with you.
I'll call the M.E. and let him
know You're on your way.
I ran the covered tattoo through
the morpho tracking system.
Tell me you got something, babe.
Emily, don't get ahead
of my dramatic telling.
I analyzed color,
design, and texture.
There's a 95% chance it is from
one of 4 major institutions
In the northeastern prison system.
The string of missings
began unbroken from 2000,
So I went back from that year,
Found 53 similar
tattoos on forearms.
Of those 53, 10 were released Prior
to 2000. Thank you and good night.
You are amazing.
Of the 10, any convicted rapists?
4.
Do any of them trace
back To Tallahassee?
None.
So ultimately I have Nada.
Bob.
Oh, the guy, his name,
the guy who rented the property,
Just Bob.
Ok, OK.
I have a Robert Matthew Burke,
Convicted in 1991, 8 years for rape,
Released October of '99.
And the missings began in 2000.
Garcia, remind me never
to try to hide from you.
perish the thought, Mon Ami.
Hotch, we got the name.
The unsub's name is
Robert Matthew Burke.
Burke?
You know him?
Burke. Yeah.
I know the name.
Damn it!
He's a registered sex offender.
He's an ex-con out of Virginia.
He got a traffic ticket near FSU
the night Rebecca disappeared.
He's one of my suspects.
I--I went to his apartment,
I don't know, a couple times
In the past 3 weeks to try to interview
him, But I could never catch up with him
Did he know you were
looking for him?
Well, yeah, I talked
to him on the phone.
He's scheduled to come down for an
interview and a DNA swab on Monday.
That's what changed.
He knew it was only a matter of
time before you caught up to him.
And he wasn't about
to go back to prison.
Do you have his address?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Something's wrong.
Unchain me.
Unchain me and I will help you.
I am not stupid.
Your baby needs help.
Wait! You can't--
The collar.
You help me and I'll let you go.
Ok.
Ok. Ok.
FBI!
Damn it.
If these tattoos are a fetish,
What enjoyment does he get
out of the ones on his back?
He can't even see them.
You know what? There's something here.
I can feel the raised ink.
Do you have a black light scanner?
Thanks.
Right there. Feel that.
Yeah, what is that?
Thanks.
I've read about this.
Tattoos put on with invisible ink
So that no one can see them.
Oh, man.
Can you, uh, turn the
lights down? Thanks.
Look, there's one over here, too.
They're all connected
to the faces.
They lead to the blank spot.
Ow, wow. What is that?
It's an embryo in a womb.
The partner's a woman,
and they're having a baby.
Oh, my God!
There's more blood.
I don't know what I'm doing.
It...It won't stop.
It won't stop.
I don't know what to do!
It won't stop. I don't--
Help me.
Do we know if she
had the baby yet?
The tattoos have dates,
the embryo doesn't.
Dating is prominent in the
tattoos and the journals
And they're calendrical in their abductions.
It's hard to believe their baby's birthdate
Wouldn't be exceedingly
important to them.
Then she's probably
still pregnant.
Well, he didn't live here with a pregnant
woman. This is a males-only SRO.
No, she has to have
a house, anyway.
How do you know that?
They kept these women
for a year each.
It wasn't in a one-room apartment.
Everyone get back here. We need to
update the profile and narrow the search.
push. Push.
Push! Push!
It's almost--
It's almost there.
Just keep pushing.
I see the head! I can't.
One more time, that's it!
Hi.
Please...
Tell me it's a girl.
What?
It can't be a boy.
Please.
It--
You have a son.
It can't be a boy.
Get it away from me.
You need to take him.
I don't want it.
He'll hurt me like they all do.
I felt for sure I
was having a girl.
You gotta get me out of here.
You have to get me out of here!
Help us!
I know.
You're a sweetheart.
it's OK.
The partner being
pregnant can help us.
We should have Garcia try and find
her through doctor visits or medical records.
He basically lived off the grid,
Which means she did, too.
Judging by the photographs of
what they did to the victims,
It's safe to say they
live in isolation.
We've seen his hatred for women,
and yet he teams up with her.
What kind of woman
could change him?
You think they met in prison?
Garcia already went
through all of that.
He had no female visitors.
What about prison staff,
doctors, religious volunteers?
We went through a long
list of all the vendors
Who were there during
his incarceration.
None of them resurfaced
in Tallahassee.
What kind of a woman would go to
a prison to fall in love with a rapist?
Someone vulnerable, emotionally fragile,
drawn to violent men.
Someone in her life made her that way.
Classic abuse cycle.
What if that's who she
was there to visit?
It's worth a try.
my sweet.
Hey, you know the visitor logs
From the prison we looked at?
Uh-huh. Still have
them at the ready.
Ok, great. I need you
to check dates for me.
Were there any women who visited
another inmate while Burke was there
But then suddenly stopped
visiting when Burke was released?
Huh. Ok, let me hit you back.
It's OK. It's OK.
I can't help you!
it's OK...
Rev your engines, guys.
Juliet Monroe went to
visit her father in prison
Once or twice a year
from '92 to '95.
What was he in for?
Rape. And she was
his primary victim.
He raped her and she still
went to visit him every year?
She's repeating the
cycle she grew up with.
Yeah. And she went from visiting
him once or twice a year
To once a month from '95 to '97.
When Burke was serving
his time for rape.
Yeah. And then she increased
her visits to once a week
All through '98 and '99,
until they stopped completely
In October of that year.
That's when he was released.
And if you want me to
slip you some convincers,
She owns a house in
Northern Florida.
Garcia, get us the address.
Rossi and I will take the front.
Take the side.
Go.
In here!
Please help. In here!
In here.
The baby. The baby.
She's--she's--she's--
She's dead.
All right, give me the baby.
Give me the baby. I got him.
You're gonna be all right.
Help me.
Becky, are you OK?
I just want to go home.
Yeah, you're going home, honey.
You're going home. It's OK.
So, I talked to your parents.
They're gonna meet you
at the hospital, OK?
Is the baby OK?
Oh, yeah, he's-
he's in another ambulance.
What's gonna happen to him?
Hey, don't you worry. We're gonna
take real good care of him, OK?
Ma'am, we should get going.
Ok. Take care.
It'll be OK.
She gonna be OK?
I wouldn't bet against anybody
who survived what she did.
How about you?
Oh, yeah, you know,
nothing's gonna affect me.
You know, we wouldn't be here if you
hadn't worked the case as hard as you did.
How's that?
It would have been an easy thing
To miss a routine traffic ticket
In the area she disappeared.
You kept the pressure on.
You cleared 9 homicides and
you brought Becky home.
It's impressive work, Detective.
Thanks.
3 cards, please.
3 cards for the lady.
And I'm gonna take one card.
One card.
A straight or a flush, Dr.
Reid, what are you trying to fill in?
Well, considering the odds of
filling in an open-ended straight
with one card Are 5-to-1 against,
while a one-card flush draw
Is more like 4.5-to-1,
I guess you'd say if I was smart,
I'm drawing to a flush.
I think I'm gonna
go all in on this.
So, are you?
Am I drawing to a flush,
or am I smart?
Either. Well,
I'm-- I'm provably a genius,
But, uh, actually,
I was drawing to a full house.
8s over 6s.
I always forget you're from Vegas.
Yup.
Ooh, I'm sorry, not so fast.
I, too, have a boat.
Jacks over 3s.
You drew 3 cards to a full house?
That's like 100-to-1 against.
97-to-1.
Looks like you're out.
Hey, Prentiss.
Sin to win.
I'm sorry, what?
Come on, now, I gotta know.
What the hell is a sin to win
weekend in Atlantic city?
Derek, I have a tremendous
amount of respect for you,
But there's some questions
that if you have to ask them,
It means you probably
couldn't handle the answer.
There is a whole other
side to that woman.
I never lose.
A whole other side.
I know environment plays a
bigger role than genetics
When it comes to determining
a child's future,
But that baby, I mean,
both the parents.
How many other serial
killers had kids?
A lot. Manson has like
10 or 11 children.
Albert fish had 6.
Gary Ridgeway had a son.
Fred and Rosemary West Had 7
children living in the home
Where they killed 10 women.
Including one of the children.
Ok, so, the baby's gonna be OK?
Most likely. If he grows
up in a good home.
Loved, cared for.
Good.
Gandhi said,
"I have seen children
successfully surmount the effects
"of an evil inheritance.
"that is due to purity
being an inherent attribute
Of the soul."