Rtraffic's looking pretty good this
afternoon for your evening commute.
This is john brown with
your kmpa traffic report.
Stay tuned for southland
sports,coming up after this.
Can't be late for my own party, norman.
I gotta go. You're gonna
have to meet me there.
Ok.
You're not gonna wear that tie, are you?
Not one of my favorites.
Don't forget to put the seat down.
Jeez,lady!
- Excuse me,miss?
- Yes?
Excuse me.
Oh,wait. Hold on one second.
All right,i'm back.
No,go on. And as i was saying...
The principal's office
called. Yeah--plagiarism.
Yeah,well,i was in the middle of
closing on the ocean park 5-bedroom...
And i'm telling you, if i lose that commission,
it is coming out of his college fund.
«˙√˚:A Well Respected Man
∏Ë ÷:The Kinks
* and he comes back
home at five-thirty,*
* gets the same train every time.*
* and he's, oh, so good,*
* and he's, oh, so fine,*
* and he's, oh, so healthy,*
* in his body and his mind.*
* he's a well respected man about town,*
* doin' the best things
so conservatively.*
* and his mother goes to meetings, *
* while his father pulls the maid, *
* and she stirs the
tea with councilors, *
* while discussin' foreign trade, *
* and she passes looks,
as well as bills *
* at every suave young man *
What's gotten into you tonight?
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Criminal Minds
Season04 Episode11 Normal
"every normal man must
be tempted at times
"to spit on his hands,
hoist the black flag,
"and begin to slit throats."
H.l.mencken.
This is orange county, california.
10 days ago,judy hannity, a
real estate broker and a mother,
Was shotgunned on the 91 freeway.
- She survived this?
- Barely.
She's paralyzed from the waist down.
The second and third
victims were both d.o.a.
There were different
vehicles for each shooting.
A small black suv, a black sedan,a
white sedan, no makes,no plates.
No solid witnesses?
The first victim described the shooter as
a normal,middle-aged white guy in an suv.
She gave that description but
she couldn't rember anything else?
Isn't that consistent with trauma?
Uh,actually,no.
Trauma victims either
remember everything or nothing.
So wait--the third victim was shot last
week, we just got the phone call today?
Until the third shooting, the locals
weren't convinced it was a serial shooter.
There were different cars, and the first
shooting there was a different weapon.
It's the same weapon.
The shot pattern on the second and
third one are much wider,though.
He sawed off the shotgun.
It's the same shooter.
He's evolving,and quickly.
The media has already
dubbed him the road warrior.
That explains why they
wanted us there so quickly.
What do you mean?
This type of unsub is
the hardest to catch.
Totally impersonal victims.
A third of the crime scene
flees with him and his vehicle.
The victim's car's a wreck.
And the last third, the road, it's contaminated
by all the other cars that drive over it.
So how do we get him?
We build a solid profile.
We release it to the public
with an appeal for help.
Somebody knows this guy.
And it's my job to make them realize.
Sheriff's.....
Thea salinas, sheriff's county homicide.
I'm running the taskforce.
I'm special agent jordan todd, special
agents rossi, hotchner, prentiss...
Morgan... And that's dr. Spencer reid.
- Are these the vehicles from the shootings?
- Yes.
Did you set up the hotline?
Like you asked.
We have the local stations
putting the number out there.
We're getting about
a dozen calls an hour.
I'll alert the media to stand by
for our press conference. Excuse me.
The sheriff's department
and the chp are on tac alert.
We've got choppers on
round-the-clock freeway patrol.
The victims' vehicles,with
maps,csps,and bullet points.
Everything we got on
the case is in this room.
Anything solid on the tip line?
Usual nutjobs, crime buffs,
bored senior citizens.
You might have got
everything squared away.
It's not me. It's the shooter.
The o.c.has an endless
supply of 3 things--
Freeways,news coverage, and
blond female luxury car owners.
People are pretty scared?
I could ask for a submarine and get it.
The first m.o.in the first shooting
differs dramatically from the other two.
Daylight on a crowded freeway.
That's dozens of potential witnesses.
It's high-risk. He got lucky.
Well,then, he's a fast study.
Sawed off his shotgun and lowered his risk
by switching to nights and changing vehicles.
What if he wasn't planning
on murder the first time?
You think the first
shooting was spontaneous?
Well,we know what he's
capable of when he plans ahead.
If i'm not planning to commit a
crime, why not drive my own vehicle?
So the suv is his actual car.
But then,why did he have a gun in the suv
if he wasn't planning to commit murder?
And what happened to make
him pull that first trigger?
We need to re-interview
the first victim.
Ms.hannity, i'm agent aaron hotchner.
This is agent emily
prentiss. We're from the fbi.
She already told the police
everything she can remember.
Rick... It's ok.
Please.
It's just the two of us.
He feels like it's
his job to protect me.
I understand you've
spoken to the police.
I just need to go back
through the shooting with you.
It only comes back in pieces.
We can take it slowly.
Just try to piece together
your day,if you can.
Have you seen accidents
like this before?
A few.
Do people recover?
The doctor said she has a good chance.
- It's my fault.
- No.
This is no one's fault but
the man who shot your mother.
I got in trouble at school.
She was on her way there.
She shouldn't have even been in her car.
So you were angry?
I don't know. I suppose.
I know this is difficult, but every
detail helps us understand who this man is.
Come on. Come on,move!
I was impatient.
And you cut him off?
Was there anything else?
Did he swear? Did he honk?
Did he threaten you in any way?
Excuse me.
Oh,wait. Hold on one second.
He tried to speak to me.
What did he say?
He couldn't say anything.
I wouldn't give him a chance.
What? Now you want to talk about
your feelings like you're some chick?
You drive like an old lady.
All right,i'm back.
No,go on. And as i was saying...
If he hadn't seemed so normal...
I wouldn't have said anything.
I...
I usually don't even use my
horn, because on the road...
You never know.
I'll ask your son to come back in.
Is she ok?
She says you've been taking
very good care of her.
I guess so.
She's lucky to have you.
So... What happened?
She made it personal.
When the victimology's this specific, we know
the victims represent a specific person to him.
Who?
Given the fact that he's the
same age and race as the victims,
Likely a current or
former wife or girlfriend.
So why not just kill the actual person?
She's just a scapegoat for
his own personal failings.
He knows if he kills her,
he loses that scapegoat.
So he just goes around
blowing away any women?
No,just women that
remind him of his wife.
When this type of killer is triggered,
they need to release the resentment quickly.
Subsequently,they tend to strike
close to the focus of that resentment.
So if the focus is his wife,
then that focus is his home.
Yeah. He almost certainly
lives in this area.
This is his kill zone.
Uh,what are these various
markers everywhere?
Uh,roadwork.
Judith hannity said that he shot her
after she challenged him personally.
Before that, he was almost apologetic.
What's going on?
Out of the 30 roadwork sites in the
kill zone, only 2 were alternate merges,
Both less than 3 miles
from the crime scenes.
Alternate merges?
Multiple lanes funneled down to one.
One car per lane, alternating
at the drivers' discretion.
These sites allow him to
set up the confrontation.
A guy who follows the
rules may lash out once,
but to do it again, he'd
need similar provocation.
So he seeks out alternate merge sites, then
he goes through them over and over again
Until he finds a woman that fits
his victim type and who cuts him off.
So,we have to shut down every alternate
merge in the county immediately.
And we need to talk to the
crews that work these sites.
So what does all this tell you?
Impersonal killers
are like drug addicts.
The first time gives them the ultimate
high, and after that, no high is as good.
Unfortunately,the
addict doesn't know that.
He will chase that high to the
gates of insanity and death.
By now,killing is all
our unsub things about.
He's set up the exact same situation again
and again, hoping to get the same result.
He begins to think he's doing it wrong.
He becomes obsessed with improving
his skills, honing his m.o.
And tailoring his weapon
to his deadly purpose.
He figures if he gets
them all just right,
if he can get his technique
and his tools perfected,
He'll feel that first high again.
He's becoming a more lethal addict.
And he'll never accept that the
high is gone and it won't come back.
He'll never stop. Never.
You know how many cars i see
drive through my work site here?
Your boss said you were the
safety officer that night?
So?
So that means you would have been
holding the sign to slow cars down.
We're looking for a man in a white sedan, and
he would have come through over and over again.
The driver would have been going extra slow,
like he was daring anyone to cut him off.
Son of a bitch.
You remember someone?
Yeah. I thought the guy was lost.
I mean, i even talked to tony about
this guy dressing like a hard-ass,
but he drove like a chick.
- No offense.
- None taken.
What do you mean,
dressed like a hard-ass?
This jackass was wearing a leather
jacket, he's got sunglasses on,
They're mirrored, you
know, like the cops use.
But it was dark out.
He's starting to role-play.
He's breaking from reality.
Do you remember anything
else about this man?
A car cut him off, and he stuck
his arm out across the front seat.
But after that i didn't
see him come through again.
Show me what he did with his arm.
Like this.
Like he was keeping a passenger
from hitting the dashboard?
Yeah,but the dude was alone.
- Thanks for your time.
- Sure.
What's wrong?
A small suv is a family vehicle.
Between that and the hand gesture, i'm
afraid that our unsub's married with children.
Why does that matter?
Well,if he's breaking from reality and
he's lashing out at surrogates for his life,
Then it's only a matter of time before
he tries to wipe out the real thing.
Are you saying this guy's
gonna kill his wife and kids?
Call your people.
We need to get a profile
out as soon as possible.
The hyper-masculine
disguise, victim preference,
And the emasculating
trigger of the first attack
All tell us this is an unsub
suffering a masculine identity crisis.
A masculine identity crisis?
That's why he's driving
around blowing women away?
No. Judy hannity was just the trigger.
We need to identify the
precipitating trauma.
Something happened in the unsub's
life, something so traumatic,
It turned a normal man
into a serial killer.
So he's suffering from some
kind of psychotic break.
Which means the world he sees around him
has changed,and so has his role in it.
And that of his family.
His perception of his home life
is the key to his pathology.
At home this unsub feels less than a man,
a failure as a father and as a husband.
He feels his children
don't need or respect him.
And that he's unwanted and
obsolete in their lives.
As a husband he feels emasculated
and humiliated by his wife.
Yeah,right, that'd be good.
Now,these beliefs and
perceptions, real or imagined,
Have destroyed this individual's
masculine self-image.
This unsub is delusional.
He's now dressing in
this road warrior persona.
It gives him feelings of power
and purpose that he craves.
It is now the single most
important thing in his life.
And he will die before giving it up.
His new fantasy persona can't co-exist
with the everyday reality of his home life.
Which means sooner or later he's
going to kill his entire family.
So what do we do?
Our strategy's three-fold.
First we find every small-model blue
suv owner in the estimated kill zone.
2--we set up a single alternate merge scenario
in that zone, and we man it with our people.
And 3--we release our
profile to the public.
Somebody out there knows this
man. They just don't realize it.
Hey,norman.
Can you put this on my account?
I'll need mr. Manning's approval.
Whenever you get around to it.
I'm still waiting for last
month's expense summary,norman.
I'm sorry.
The guys on the sixth floor
are asking for my quarterly.
I need that summary.
I got--i know i got--
i got it here somewhere.
You're an old,bald loser
and everyone laughs at you.
What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
Look,norman, the sixth floor doesn't
care what's going on in your life
or how long you've been with the firm.
They're all about the numbers,
and the numbers tell them that younger
workers cost less and produce more.
I like you,norman.
I know how hard things have been
for you these past few months.
Don't give those bastards on the sixth
floor an excuse, you know what i mean?
Yeah. Yeah.
Here it is.
Thanks.
We ask the public to listen very
carefully to the following description.
Anyone who believes they recognize this
individual should call our tip line immediately.
We are looking for a white,
middle-aged,married father.
We believe his wife is blond,
approximately 40 years old,
Resembles the victims,
and drives a luxury sedan.
This individual drives
a blue small-model suv
and most likely lives in this area.
It is also very possible this
individual recently suffered
a personal trauma in his life.
All points bulletin: be on the lookout
for a worthless loser named norman,
Who resents anyone with a life and kills
just to prove he's not an emasculated loser.
It's very possible this individual has
suffered a personal trauma in his life.
Again,a white,middle-aged,
married father.
We believe his wife is
blond,approximately 40 years old,
Resembles the victims, and
drives a luxury sedan. This...
They do it to me, they do it to me,
they do it to me, they do it to me!
Why do they always do that to me?
Makes you... Damn...
Hey,buddy. Are you all right?
Joe karem and timothy calvert.
D.o.a.no wants,no warrants.
They work in the area, and detectives
are notifying their families.
Sawed-off 12-gauge, close range, shot out of the
driver's side window, driving a small blue suv.
That's our guy, but
he went way off script.
Multiple male victims, surface street,
daytime attack, and he drove his own vehicle.
Something triggered
him and pissed him off.
What time did this happen?
Approximately 2:20.
Single witness says the shooter
was driving a small blue suv.
Didn't get a plate.
Middle-aged white guy, wearing a tie.
Suit jacket hanging in the back.
- Press conference?
- 2:20.
Jordan went on the air at
2:00. He was watching the news.
You said the unsub was going
to be watching the coverage.
20 minutes from wherever he was watching
the press conference to this intersection.
He drives the speed limit, taking into
account red lights and mid-day traffic...
No more than 10 miles.
So he lives within 10 miles of here?
- I don't think so.
- I don't understand.
We were wrong.
He was wearing a tie, suit
jacket hanging in the back.
And considering the time of day...
He works in the area.
I'm gonna call garcia.
Give it to me.
Hey,baby. Can you pull up a map
of the crime scene area for me?
Sugar,i could shut down the power grid
to the whole city if you told me to.
Yeah,i'm sure you can.
Right now i just need you to highlight
a 10-mile radius around this point.
Track any calls coming in
from this area to the tip line.
Coordinate with prentiss
and reid,would you?
I'm all over it. Mwah.
Thanks,baby girl.
You think he's gonna
kill again soon,don't you?
And he's done killing surrogates.
Did you know?
Excuse me. This is not
the time or the place.
You gonna do this in front of the press?
He killed those people
because of something i said.
No. Whenwetalk to the public,
it's always a possibility.
That is part of the job. Tell
me now if you can do it or not.
Damn right. I can do the shop.
Good. You're about to give
another press conference.
We're on the air in 3,2,1...
We are prepared to release to
the public additional information
About the individual responsible
for the freeway shooting.
The individual is a white, 45- to
55-year-old male of average build.
He works in this area.
He wears a suit and tie to work and left
work very abruptly shortly after 2:00,
immediately after watching our
earlier statement about him.
If anyone has any additional information,
please call our anonymous tip line immediately.
Thank you.
One last thing.
This individual has committed horrible
crimes and must be held to account,
but he is a husband and a father.
He's violent and he's troubled,
but he must be capable of some
degree of mercy and compassion.
And so... We appeal to him...
Do not hurt any more people.
Please turn yourself in.
Norman? Is something wrong?
I'm the road warrior.
What?
I'm the road warrior,
the freeway shooter.
I thought i should tell you.
Of course you are,dear.
And i'm the zodiac killer.
We should compare notes at dinner.
What's so funny?
Dad confessed. He's the road warrior.
You're such a dork.
Yeah.
What is the exact address?
What do we got?
You have no idea how many middle-aged
white men there are out there
Who have someone close to them
that think they're a serial killer.
And you said that he saw
the press conference,right?
Ok,thank you.
Guys,i think we might have something.
That's funny,when i heard the description in
the first press conference, i thought of norman.
Then i just thought,
it couldn't be,you know?
He's so quiet.
What is it that mr. Hill does for you?
He's in charge of the company's
travel expenses. This is his desk.
Does he have access to the company cars?
Yeah,the whole fleet.
What about the first press
conference made you think of norman?
The woman mentioned something
about him suffering a tragedy.
Daddy, what's taking so long?
Daddy will be done in a minute.
Just stay in the car,baby.
I want to help.
Jenny,get back in the car!
Get back in the car! No!
How long ago did his daughter die?
6 months.
I really should have
done more to help him.
Thank you.
Norman's personnel file.
This address current?
It should be.
Why does he have 2 files?
Uh,we cross-reference married couples.
I don't understand.
Norman's wife vanessa works here,too.
We need to speak to her.
Uh,she's not here.
She just got a promotion, so
she took a couple of weeks off.
Get in the car.
- I just got home from school.
- Don't talk back to me!
Norman,what's going on?
You'll see. Everybody,now. I'm driving.
Norman,what are you doing?
- Norman,slow down!
- No!
What do you mean,no?
We have to get out of here.
Dad,let us out of the car!
Damn it.
- Please.
- Ok,norman, the police are behind us.
- Shut up!
- Shut up?
- The police should stay out of this.
- Stay out of it?
You ran a stop sign and you're
going like 100 miles an hour.
- This is family business!
- Family?
- You have to stop this.
- No.
What we have to do is we
have to get out of here.
Please,dad,this is crazy!
Norman,stop this car right now!
Shut up! All of you shut up!
Salinas. Where?
We have a chase. Small model suv,blue.
Driving recklessly. 117th and pacific.
Morgan,we have a high-speed chase, 117
and pacific. It sounds like our guy.
All right,listen, we're closer
to 117, so we're on our way now.
We'll head over to the hill house.
If he's having a break, he could
be on his way there to finish it.
- We're on our way. Be careful.
- Ok.
Norman,please stop.
We should have done
this a long time ago.
Done what?
We can't move on living in
that house. I can't do it.
- Move on?
- I don't know how you could.
How you could-- you keep looking
at those same walls, the same...
The same pictures.
Norman,what are you talking about?
It's my job to make
everything right again.
- Turn right here.
- Where,here?
Right--right-- turn right
here! Turn right here!
I'm gonna need a little
more notice than that,kid.
Sorry. Sorry.
Norman,please just tell
me what's happening.
Why are you doing this?
Because i know that you blame me.
Blame you?
I see the way you all
look at me. I see it.
- All right,left.
- Where?
Uh,next light.
Norman,please,just stop.
Oh,my god. Where did you get that?
I tried to tell you,
but you wouldn't listen.
You just wouldn't listen!
Repeat,shots fired! On the chase now.
He's losin' it.
Reid,does it look like the chase
could be headed to his house?
Uh,yeah,i think so.
It almost looks like he's starting to go
in a wide circle toward that direction.
Ok,emily, we're right outside it now.
All units, pursuit now
headed over memorial bridge.
We're almost there. Turn
right at the next light.
Norman,where did you get that gun?
- How could you forget her so fast?
- What?
- You think i forgot?
- You moved on!
I cry every day!
Don't lie to me! Don't lie to me!
Memorial bridge is
around the next corner.
Hold on! Hold on!
- You good!
- We're good,go,go!
Vanessa hill! Fbi!
Are you inside?
Maybe they went somewhere safe.
Let's check around back.
We can never be a family
again in that house.
We can never be a family anywhere!
No. No,don't say that.
- You let her die,daddy!
- No,no,no, it wasn't my fault.
Of course it was your fault!
Please don't say it!
Just stop saying that!
I wasn't there. Sasha wasn't there.
You had her and you let her die!
Just shut up! Just shut up!
A '63 astin martin db-5.
James bond. Goldfinger.
Guys.
Reid,get on the radio and
tell them we're in the chase.
This is the fbi
behavioral analysis unit.
We caught up to the chase
and are now monitoring.
We ask if you're able
to stop the vehicle,
You allow us to take the
lead in contacting the driver.
We believe him to be a
severely deranged suspect.
Copy.
Let's split up.
It was your fault.
I'm sorry.
You let my baby girl die.
And you think i forgot?!
It was your fault.
No. No,no,no, no,no!
Norman!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
- Don't move!
- My family's inside!
- Stop and listen to me!
Listen to me! - No,my family's--
- nobody is in that car.
- Nobody...
- Your family's gone,norman.
- No,they're in there.
They're gone,norman!
Look inside. Look in
the car. Look in the car.
They were never there.
It's over.
They were never with you.
No,but they were. They were...
Your family's gone,norman.
Oh,god,what did i do?
Oh,what did i do to my family?
My family! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry! My family...
It's over,norman.
We're gonna get you some help.
It's over. Let's go. Get up.
Jordan?
Did i do that?
Is this my fault?
No,kiddo. No way.
They were gone before
we even got the case.
We knew he would hurt his family.
We just didn't know that he already had.
I don't...
I'm not sure i can do this job.
That's ok.
There's nothing wrong with that.
"there's no tragedy in life
"like the death of a child.
Things never get back
to the way they were."
President dwight eisenhower.
You all right?
I will be.
Hey,you guys ever notice how the trip
home always seems to go so much faster?
That's because the
tailwinds are in our favor.
No,i meant 'cause-- anybody
want to get something to eat?
- Not really.
- You?
No,not really.
There's someone in the b.a.u.room,guys.
- What are you doing here?
- JJ.
Garcia said you guys were
on your way back tonight.
I thought you could use a surprise.
I thought i gave you strict orders to get
this place out of your head for a while.
My bad. I couldn't help myself.
Here. I heated it up. Room temp. Right?
I just realized, with all that we do
and see in this room, it never smiles.
I wanted at least one
good memory to hold on to.
Excuse me,kid.
Um,jj,uh... Can i?
Of course.
Ok,you gotta hold his
head up. Careful,careful.
- I got it,i got it.I got it.
- No,you don't got it. You're smothering him.
Look,what's he doing? What's he doing?
He is smiling at derek morgan.
- Gas.
Give me that.
Hey,little man.
You're smiling.
Yes.
We miss you.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚