Best show ever, Dante!
Great show!
Nice job!
Beautiful.
Just let me...
Hey, look, you're not
allowed to be over there, all right?
Stay there.
Here he comes.
I know. I know.
I know.
He looked right at me.
Did you see that?
I saw it. I saw him
look right at you.
- We had a connection.
- *******
When he sang "resurrection"
it was like everyone
in the theater just disappeared.
He is so beautiful.
- So beautiful.
- Totally, man.
So beautiful.
This is us.
Both of you?
Yeah.
We live on the same block, dummy.
I could, uh, walk you
to your building.
What?
I mean, it's... it's dark.
So?
We gotta go.
I'm just saying, it's dark.
I could walk you...
I'm pretty sure
I'm tougher than you are, Ted.
Thank you for taking us
to the concert, though, Ted.
- Yeah.
- Bye!
Bye-bye.
It's Ed, not Ted.
The latest victim
is Tara Farris, 20.
She's the third victim in 2 weeks.
All found on freeway
off-ramps by commuters.
Well, he's not hiding them.
An l.A. Freeway
during morning rush hour?
He wants them found.
Quickly.
Well, they're still dressed.
That minimizes the shock value.
Maybe he's concerned for them.
Think he wants them taken care of?
No signs of sexual assault
on any of the victims.
Look how pale she is.
All of them were severely
hypovolemic.
Tara had less than a pint
of blood in her.
Look at this. The first 2 had
more than 3 pints each.
If exsanguination is the goal,
the unsub is definitely
becoming more proficient.
This is new. Tara's the only victim
to have a written message.
"The liar."
"The" liar.
That's strange, isn't it?
Not a liar or just liar.
So what did you lie about, Tara?
All of the victims appear
to have been strangled
and then bled out through
identical wounds in the throat.
Wait seriously, are those supposed
to be fang marks?
All of the wounds on the victims
were covered in saliva.
Human saliva, as though...
Someone drank their blood.
Team Criminal Minds
http://experts.heberg-forum.net/
In the darkest pages
of the malign supernatural,
there is no more terrible
tradition than that of the vampire.
A pariah even among demons.
Writer montague summers.
Ok. Thanks.
So they've already set up
a task force in Los Angeles.
This isn't their first serial case.
You remember detective owen kim?
From the stalker case.
You remember that case,
don't you, Spence?
I do remember that case.
Yeah, you ever talk to,
Lila anymore?
You know, I think we should
probably focus on this case right now.
It's a little more pertinent.
All right, so tell us about
blood-drinkers, reid.
Human blood consumption,
or clinical vampirism,
is known as renfield's syndrome,
named after the insect-eating character
in bram stoker's novel "dracula."
Are they sadists?
Not necessarily. Pain to the victim
is usually only a byproduct.
Blood is the focus.
Renfield's syndrome is usually
accompanied by
varying levels of schizophrenia
and occasionally
more classic cannibalism
if the condition evolves.
Classic cannibalism.
Lovely job we have.
I will say this...
true cases are exceedingly rare.
That's comforting.
Sort of.
Renfield's may be rare,
but vampires are anything but.
And there's a huge
subculture in Los Angeles
Of the red-drinking undead.
Why is that not a surprise?
Garcia, all these people
drink blood?
Au contraire. They mostly just dress up
like Prentiss did in high school
and they make believe.
It's all kinds of delicious.
It's not the same thing
at all. As a matter of fact,
we should refer to this unsub
as a vampirist, not a vampire.
And they would be attracted
to the subculture
merely for its professed
worship of blood.
Ok, I'm going to continue spelunking
through the various online sites,
see if anything jumps up
and bites me.
Thanks, baby g...
Thanks, Penelope.
Stay close.
Yes, sir.
Garcia out.
You guys, one more thing...
vampirists are coveters.
They most generally always
have some sort of relationship
with the victim,
even if it's tangential.
And they're likely
to become obsessed.
They've almost certainly
crossed paths in some way.
It's ok. It's just me.
It's ray.
You still in bed?
I'm sick.
Look, Dante, you're already late.
Don't call me that.
Sorry, but, man,
you gotta get going, ok?
I said no.
The record company is gonna
be pissed again if you're not.
Get out!
I know you hate these parties,
but you've got to sell the record.
You can't blow this off.
It's your job, man.
And it's my job to make you go.
Do I have to be him?
You know that you do.
I'll be down in 20 minutes.
Great. I'll make you
something to eat.
I'm not hungry.
What happened to you last night?
What do you mean?
After the show.
You just kind of disappeared.
I don't remember.
Hi, lieutenant Kim.
Agent Jareau.
JJ, of course.
I remember most of you.
Agent Hotchner.
Reid.
Morgan.
Welcome back to the left coast.
These are agents Prentiss and Rossi.
I believe they're new to you.
Hi. Pleasure.
We already have
a room set up full of
glass boards, case files,
and extremely bad coffee.
We've worked with a lot less.
Agent Morgan's in charge now.
It's his show.
Long story.
I know you like to start
with the freshest information
and work your way back.
So Tara's apartment has been
processed and sealed
in case you want to go there.
And her body, along with
that of the first 2 girls,
is at the morgue with an M.E.
Waiting there for your call.
All right.
JJ, get set up here,
and then hook up with Garcia.
Send her the witness information
so she can start cross-referencing
with the first 2 victims.
Reid, I want you to go
through all the case files,
set up a preliminary
profile based on
what you already know about the
psychopathology. And the rest of us,
let's find out what we can on Tara.
So we're looking for a connection
between the witnesses.
When vampirists become obsessed,
they aren't likely to find
a random victim.
If we can find a cross-relationship,
someone in all the victims' lives,
that'll be incredibly helpful.
Gina king knew Tara the longest.
They apparently had
some classes together.
Let's get all the information
we can on that relationship.
As a matter of fact, get me everything
you can on all of Tara's friends.
All right. In the morning I'll track
them down and do some follow-up.
That's fine.
Dante.
This is Jeff
from "metal life" magazine.
He's writing a story
on artists who cross over...
Cross over.
Is that what I do,
Jeff from "metal life"?
I guess, kind of.
You're not totally goth, right?
That whole vampire thing
you do is...
Ah, the vampire thing?
Yeah, your act.
****
it appeals to certain people.
It appeals to desperate,
sad people with, at best,
a tenuous hold on reality.
Can I quote you on that?
Sure. Knock yourself out.
No, don't use that quote.
'cause I can just get him back,
get another...
You know what, don't even bother, man.
He was old news 5 years ago.
Where's the scotch?
Over here.
Listen, here's the thing,
He's not on his game lately.
This is almost exactly like
my first apartment in Georgetown.
My mom wanted me to stay on campus,
but I was determined
to make it, so...
I waitressed on
the weekends to swing it.
You must have been
a hell of a waitress
to swing an apartment in georgetown.
No, I sucked.
I only got by 'cause my mom
put money in my account every week
and we both pretended I didn't know.
Looks like she was
studying to make movies.
Rossi.
Who is this guy?
Well, if you want to look into
a young girl's life today,
you have to access her myspace,
facebook, and twitter accounts.
I'll call the sexiest
hacker on the planet.
I don't think he's going
to print that quote.
Who cares?
You shouldn't say stuff like that
about your fans.
Maybe I'll just jump off.
I mean, I'm a vampire.
Maybe I could just fly away.
I don't like that kind of talk.
What's wrong, Ray,
afraid you're gonna lose
your cash cow?
What's happened to you?
It doesn't matter.
Come on.
We used to have fun, remember?
I don't make music anymore.
I make events.
- I play a character.
- You sell records.
It's...
It's not as if I exactly light up
the sales charts anymore, anyway.
You'll sell again.
Ray, you may be the only
friend I have left, but...
you're a pretty crappy liar.
- I'm so sorry!
- ************
It's my fault. It's my fault.
Let me help you.
Interesting hand.
Do you know who I am?
Yeah. I mean, you're the music guy.
This is your party, right?
Yes. This is...
this is for me, but...
I have a pocket full
of what will make us both
feel so much happier.
You do?
So let's get out of here.
Really?
Yeah. Come on, let's go.
You won't be sorry.
The saliva hasn't been DNA I.D.'D,
But we have it
going through the lab.
You can have the samples sent over
to the local bureau lab
and have them rush it.
You should have something
by sometime tomorrow.
I'll have it sent right over.
They're not bites.
Look at the edges.
They're razor sharp.
A tooth would leave
a ragged, torn edge.
I have some photos of animal
bites on the table for comparison.
Some sort of boring
instrument, then?
Very sharp and very efficient.
Well, if it isn't a bite,
then the saliva,
is it from licking, afterwards?
Maybe. I haven't seen
anything like it.
Once an unsub like this
gets started...
it only gets worse.
This is chase manning,
news chopper 12,
over the 101 freeway
in the san fernando valley.
Apparently a second body
in as many days
has been found near an off-ramp.
So much for keeping the media out.
Penelope?
Are we in yet?
All yours.
I always feel skeevy going
through someone's life like this.
Ok, so everything
looks like it's password protected,
so you might not even be able to...
- You're in already, aren't you?
- The password was cullen.
Of course.
Colon?
Cullen.
The vampire family from "Twilight."
What's "Twilight"?
Do you ever read anything
other than technical books?
Not much in english.
Ok, I'll see what I can dredge.
My love is strong.
Ok, thanks.
How's the profile coming?
I don't know.
I never really feel ready, you know?
It'll be fine. I am gonna
go talk to Tara's BFF
Before the media requests come
in and it gets too crazy.
What's a BFF?
Best Friend Forever.
Should I go with you?
No. You have a profile to deliver.
I should really work
on it a little more.
Reid.
What are you doing with my phone?
Derek, hey, um,
Spence is ready for the profile.
Why, yes, he is, right here.
- *****
- I'll be back.
Hey.
All right, Reid.
We'll be right in.
Hotch, Reid's ready
with the profile.
Good.
Highway crew found her
just as the sun was coming up.
How long's she been here?
Barely even cold yet.
- Hour, maybe.
- The liar.
The same message.
Apparently it wasn't Tara-specific.
I wonder what it means, then.
The first victim
on a consecutive day.
Detective Kim, can you have
your crime scene techs
keep us apprised of the processing?
We're ready with
a preliminary profile.
That's quick.
So's this unsub.
We aren't looking for a vampire
in the supernatural sense,
only in the sense
that this unsub
has a very strong desire,
a need, for human blood.
Now, fortunately, vampirists
display several characteristics
which will be helpful
in finding him.
He will have cut himself repeatedly.
It's called auto-vampirism,
essentially becoming
his own first victim.
It's the way by which
he first tasted human blood.
Most vampirists are
incredibly ashamed of this
and will wear long-sleeved
shirts in order to conceal it.
Secondly, there will be
a long history of animal abuse,
starting with smaller animals
such as insects and rodents
and then working his way up
to larger things...
dogs and cats.
Though this is
a well-recognized component
of the homicidal triad
seen in other serial killers,
in the case of the vampirist,
it's more pronounced.
There will, interestingly enough,
not be any animal torture,
as with other psychopathologies.
The killing isn't the point, it's merely
a means by which to obtain the blood.
Look hard at your animal
control sections records,
as far back as you can.
They will probably have some record
of this unsub as an adolescent.
This guy also most likely lives
in a poorly kept older home.
He needs a house for the privacy,
not an apartment.
It takes some time to drain
a body completely of blood.
Uninterrupted time.
This unsub also most likely
lives with an elderly woman,
a grandmother, a mother,
even an aunt.
How could you know that?
This type of mental illness,
accompanied by extreme
schizophrenia,
dominates a family's
entire existence.
It often leads to a broken home,
and a woman ends up
as primary caregiver.
The men generally leave.
And one more thing.
This type of disorder
cannot be hidden for long.
I guarantee you someone out there
already knows this unsub
is very, very sick.
You ok?
You all right?
Should I...should I call somebody?
Tell me what's happening.
Talk to me.
Oh, my god.
I can't stop it.
- I want to.
- Yeah.
- But I can't stop it.
- *************
You gotta help me.
I know. I will.
I will.
Are you all right?
Talk to me.
I can't stop it.
Come here.
We're gonna fix this, ok?
I'm gonna fix this.
Agent Morgan, we've identified
this morning's victim.
Erin Hickman.
She worked for a caterer
at an event last night.
They're still there cleaning up.
Where can I find Ms. Masters?
She's right there.
Thank you.
Excuse me. Ms. Masters?
I'm lieutenant Kim, LAPD.
Is this about Erin?
Yes, ma'am.
Is she really dead?
I'm sorry.
These are FBI agents
Morgan and Prentiss.
- FBI?
- Erin Hickman work for you?
Well, till last night. She walked out
on me In the middle of the party.
Walked out?
All I know
Is she was here one minute
and gone the next.
Was it uncommon for her
to be irresponsible?
Look, I don't want to
speak ill of the...
She had a problem with drugs.
Excuse me.
Morgan.
We saw a poster of him
in tara's house.
Speak to me, vision.
Garcia, give me everything
you've got
On a singer named Dante.
Dante, the vampire guy?
I was just about to call you.
You know him?
Uh, he's the one thing that all
of our victims have in common.
What do you mean?
They have cyber shrines
set up for this guy.
They worship him.
They're obsessed with his music.
Well, his new album comes out
today and it's called "The Liar."
"The Liar," I know. And isn't that
what was written on them?
Ok, uh, all of our victims,
including the first two,
were diehard fans.
Tara and Gina...
that's Tara's friend...
They were practically
running his fan club.
What about Erin Hickman,
our latest victim?
Erin Hickman,
I haven't run across that name.
Ok, we need to talk
to this dante guy.
Garcia, can you get us an address?
That's gonna take a little while.
These celebrities are protected
by layers of privacy.
It's like finding
information on a deeply
22423 Greenvale Circle,
Holmby Hills. GPS coordinates
are uploading to you now.
And his name is
Paul Davies, by the way.
Run him for a criminal record, too.
You got it.
Thanks, P.G.
I'd hate to think
what she could find out about me.
Oh, I prefer
not even to consider it.
It doesn't look like
a lot of poorly maintained
- single-family homes.
- No.
I hate to ask this,
but are your profiles
this far off sometimes?
They haven't been yet.
This probably isn't our unsub,
just a piece of the puzzle.
I could get used to this.
This is definitely
not poorly maintained.
One of these things does not belong.
Hey, Garcia, can you
run a plate for me?
This isn't our guy, is it?
I highly doubt it.
May I help you guys?
Dante?
No.
You're not the singer?
Dante's not my name.
He's a character I play.
So who are you guys?
- We're investigating a murder...
- Sir!
Would you mind coming in
to answer a few questions?
- Prentiss, what are you doing?
- That car is Erin Hickman's car.
The victim's car.
Would you mind coming in, sir?
This is Elizabeth chambers outside
the Los Angeles police department
with a story we're still developing.
The singer-songwriter known as Dante
has been taken into custody
by the FBI
as a suspect in a recent string
of murders in the Los Angeles area.
- Dante!
What's it been, 30 minutes?
What about your music?
Welcome to the media
capital of the world.
Oh, god.
How the hell did they
get here so fast?
Who knows?
They always do.
Now listen up.
We're gonna have to push through.
Can you at least put a jacket
over me or something?
Do you have anything
you want to say?!
If we're gonna go we gotta go now.
Back off! Back off!
Everyone back off!
Back off!
Back up, please! Back up!
Back up!
I'm with the FBI!
I have an official statement
if you'll just come over here, please.
Is he gonna be ok?
He's got a gun.
Keep moving.
Right in here.
Thank you very much.
Ok, this is just a preliminary
investigation right now.
A lot of this doesn't add up.
We've been wrong before.
Not this much.
The plot thickens.
He was arrested for domestic
violence 10 years ago.
How bad?
Well, Garcia was able
to find the battery charge,
but it was expunged, so who knows?
Again, welcome to celebrity justice.
He's pretty agitated.
I wonder why.
Celebrities out here aren't used
to being put in the box.
This seems more than that, though.
I don't know.
These are people everyone falls
down around, defers to.
Adulation is their norm.
You know, Prentiss, that may be
a good way for you to play him.
Me?
You were the one who pointed at him.
He may see you as an adversary.
Have him off-guard.
So, what did you tell the press?
My official statement was
that I hate Los Angeles.
What's happening?
Prentiss is gonna take the lead.
Good choice.
Remember, if he is the unsub,
he's ashamed of the disorder,
- so use that to your advantage.
- Tell him you can't believe
that someone like him could do this.
Throw him a lifeline.
Right.
Ask him for his autograph.
Oh. Right. Right.
Adulation.
Mr. Davies.
Have a seat, relax.
Relax?
How the hell am I supposed to relax?
Please sit.
I've been trying to call my manager,
but I can't get a signal.
These interrogation rooms don't
usually have cell service.
Is there another phone
that I can use? I...
I think there's been
a really big mistake.
There's been no mistake.
I'm sure that you couldn't have had
anything to do with what's happened.
Really?
I mean, you're the one
that brought me in here.
The police gave me
some bad information.
You're not the police?
Good, she's confusing him.
Schizophrenics can't follow that.
Neither one of us
is the type of person
who belongs in
a police interrogation room.
Supervisory special agent
Emily Prentiss,
Federal Bureau of Investigation.
FBI?
And, of course, I know who you are.
I'm a big fan.
Really?
Does that surprise you?
Yeah. Yeah, that's a surprise.
Ok. Well,...
before we get started...
would you mind?
Would I mind what?
Well, I hate to ask,
but I don't usually get
opportunities like this.
What the hell is this?
You're no fan of mine.
You people think I'm stupid.
That kind of contradiction should
completely confuse a schizophrenic.
They can't make sense of it.
Am I suspected of something?
What's the name of your new album,
the one that comes out today?
- Is she...
- Dead? Yes.
With the name of your new
album written on her.
It's a common phrase.
Is it?
It seems a little odd to me.
The instead of a.
And this girl went home
with you last night.
She's dead?
Can you explain that?
I... I don't...
- I don't remember.
- You don't remember hurting her?
No.
Their blood was drained.
From holes in their throats.
What?
Are you a vampire, Mr. Davies?
You can't be serious.
It's a character I play,
a stage act.
You know, sometimes
things get out of hand.
No, no.
This is... this is crazy.
I don't know how that girl
ended up like that.
I think I need my manager here.
You're gonna do this all on your own,
just like a big boy.
But I have the right to a lawyer.
Are you asking for an attorney?
No. I'm asking to speak
to my manager
so he can find one.
I need a phone.
I need to make a call.
There's nothing you can do
when they lawyer up, Prentiss.
Dr. Reid here.
Spence, what's going on?
The possible suspect's
some sort of rock and roll star.
Seriously?
A lot of it doesn't fit
the profile, though.
- Anything I can do?
- There's a lot of media attention.
All right.
Well, I'm already here at Gina's house,
so let me get some info
and I'll be back.
Great. Thank you so much.
- None of this makes any sense.
- No.
Television is saying his new record
is selling through the roof.
All of his stuff is.
As soon as his being questioned in an
actual string of murders became public.
What do they say?
Any publicity's good publicity.
What are we gonna do with him?
Hotchner.
Well, he wants to talk
to his manager, so...
maybe we let him make that call
and find out what that guy knows.
It's worth a try.
You sure?
Ok, thanks.
- Something?
- That's the lab.
The saliva samples
from the victims' throats...
the DNA's from a woman.
Stop. Don't to that.
Grandma's asleep.
She's gonna wake up.
So you have to stop it.
I need to go to the yard.
Gina.
- Gina.
- I'm with the...
FBI.
A woman?
That's incredibly rare.
But not impossible.
No, but renfield's with
this type of aggression...
- it almost never presents this way.
- We knew something was wrong.
Our profiles have never
been this far off, Reid.
Go back and work it with a woman.
See if there's anything
we may have missed.
You wanted to call your manager.
Can I have some privacy?
That's not how it works.
Ray.
Holy hell, man,
the record's gone through the roof.
What do you mean?
It's flying off the shelves.
I told you I'd fix it.
I told you.
Yeah, everything's good.
You're gonna be back on top,
everything's gonna
go right back to normal,
- you can stop doing the drugs.
- Ray,...
I'm at the police station
with the FBI.
I know, I know, I know.
Don't worry about it.
- Don't worry?
- No, don't... don't worry about it.
Look, there's nothing that
could be tied to you,
absolutely nothing.
It's all good, man.
Come on, let's go.
Yes.
What did you do, Ray?
The less you know
about it the better.
Look, I gotta take care
of this thing,
and then I'll be right back.
I'll be down there.
Let me just fix this.
- Ray...
- Hey, relax, would ya?
It's gonna be all right.
Did he do something?
I don't know.
What did he say?
He said he'd be down to fix it.
Fix what?
Fix this, I suppose.
But he didn't ask you
what "this" was.
No.
Gina.
My name is Jennifer Jareau.
Gina, where'd you go?
Gina...
Who the hell is that?
What kind of fan mail
do you get, Mr. Vampire?
A woman... what changes,
what doesn't?
Older female...
Oh, no.
Yeah.
Uh, Reid,
I found fan mail to Dante.
Vampire fan mail.
It's bananas.
- Obsessional?
- Ad infinitum and beyond.
Tara's friend Gina...
the stuff she writes...
she...
he's her god.
A vampire god.
She lives for him.
She said she'll kill for him.
And she fits every other
piece of the profile.
Guys!
The girl Tara was with before
she died Gina... it's her.
- Do you have an address?
- Yeah. I think JJ is there right now.
Let's go.
Who the hell is she?
I'm so upset.
It's all going to go bad.
Forget that. You've got...
you've got to kill her.
It's all going bad.
Listen to me,
we've got to help Dante.
You gotta help Dante again.
- Dante?
- Yeah.
He's... he's... he's gonna be angry.
No, no, no, no.
I promise.
He'll only be angry
if you don't kill this woman.
Listen,
you gotta hurt one more girl
and then you'll be able
to join him in the undead. Ok?
- She isn't answering.
- Keep trying.
You don't understand!
I do. I do understand.
You just have to do one more
and Dante will be able to live then.
Just one?
Just this one more girl
and then you can join the undead,
just like we promised.
You said that Tara was the last one.
That's what you said. You said.
Now it's the other girl...
This is the last one.
The last one that you have to do,
and then you can join Dante
and be the undead.
Just like we talked about, remember?
Remember?
Just one more?
- Just one...
- Just one more.
And then yourself.
Just like he promised.
Just one... ok.
Just one.
- Last one.
Take it.
Go on, take it.
Beautiful.
Where did she...
Don't move.
Hey!
JJ?
In the back!
Mine. This is mine.
It's mine. You can't...
You can't have it.
Go away.
JJ.
Show me your hands!
Let me see your hands!
It's ok. It's ok.
Get your hands clear!
No, no, please, you have to...
No, no, no, no! No, no, no!
The blood is going bad!
Please!
Please don't do this!
- Are you armed?
- No, no, no.
- No.
- Go, go!
Hey, I got nothing to do with this.
Hey, it's not me.
It's the chick.
It's got nothing to do with me.
Has something happened?
It was your manager.
He used a fan of yours.
What?
A young girl.
She'd been writing you letters
about wanting to kill someone
for their blood.
I never...
I never received anything.
No, he did.
And I guess he thought
he could use it for publicity.
He was right.
Your new album is selling very well.
I never asked for that.
Well...
Where is he?
Your manager?
He's in custody.
Is he ok?
Is there anything I can do for him?
He's gonna need a good lawyer.
What about the girl?
I don't know where she'll end up.
She's pretty sick.
I'd like to help her, too, if I can.
That's all?
I can go now?
That's all.
You know,...
all I really ever wanted to do
was make music.
And I'm not sure when
that stopped being enough.
Hey, do you guys think Davies will
continues to perform as Dante?
The character's probably responsible
for the murder of 4 women.
If he has any conscience at all,
Dante died with them.
- Thanks.
- Are you ok?
Yeah. Doctor said
it'll be sore for a while, but...
I'm fine, really.
I feel so bad I didn't go
with you to interview Gina.
Spence, stop, all right?
We had no way of knowing
she was gonna be dangerous.
She was just the friend of a victim.
Granted, a schizophrenic friend
with a sociopathic partner.
And a shovel.
Seriously, Reid,
we had no way of knowing
that Gina had that type
of anger inside of her.
Yeah, but she was
obsessed with Dante.
I should have known that that level
of fixation can lead to manipulation.
But only when the fixation's
coupled with schizophrenia,
which we had no way of knowing.
Still it never ceases to amaze me
how dark obsession can get.
And with a pop star?
I mean,
I was obsessed with the rat pack,
but I wouldn't have
killed for Frank or Dean.
No, you just drank
whiskey and smoked cigars.
This from the man who's favorite
record is the Beatles' white album.
Just because manson hijacked it
doesn't have to ruin it
for the rest of us.
That's why I stick to Beethoven.
There's no chance
of guilt by association.
Well, yeah.
Have you ever seen a movie
called "a clockwork orange"?
Writer Cyril Connolly said,
"better to write for yourself
and have no public
than to write for the public
and have no self."