there's a basement.
damn.
you sure it's him?
who else could it be?
i just want
to make sure.
male. approximately
6 years old. i'm sorry.
there's something in here.
what's that baby doing here?
j.j. can't let her baby
be at a crime scene.
reid.
j.j.
sorry, i was dreaming.
ha, no kidding.
we found a 6-year-old
boy who had been abused and stabbed.
your baby was
at the crime scene.
i was trying to get him
out of there.
sorry.
it's ok.
you know, reid,
simple dream analysis--
if there's a baby in your dreams,
that baby's actually you.
i don't believe in
dream analysis.
i don't know.
it makes sense.
the case we're working on and the case in your dream
both involve children.
maybe your subconscious is
telling you you want to sit this one out.
i don't.
well, maybe you're just stressed out
about going home to las vegas.
did you tell your mom
you're coming?
why aren't we reviewing
the case file?
i don't know. maybe because
someone fell asleep on the jet.
all right, let's start
from the beginning one more time.
this is ethan hayes.
he was 5.
2 weeks ago he was abducted
out of his own front yard.
where were the parents?
his mom just ran inside
to grab her purse.
when she came back,
he was gone.
she wasn't away for more
than a minute or 2.
police found his body
exactly one week later in the desert.
he was in a new change
of clothes.
his nails clipped.
his hair was combed.
that's a lot of remorse.
no sign of sexual assault.
the medical report suggests
he was smothered.
unsub could see this death
as merciful.
who's the new boy?
michael bridges.
yesterday, he set out to walk by himself
to a friend's house a block away
and he never showed up.
are we sure these cases are
even connected?
the unsub called
each of the families.
but no ransom demand.
it was more like taunts.
he's telling them
it's their fault that their child was taken.
ok. so, we have an unsub who shows remorse
and then projects his own guilt onto the victims' parents.
and if we're lucky, 6 days to find the boy
before he is killed.
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
CRIMINAL MINDS 406
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译: 校对:
时间轴:我爱狮心小s
SUBURBS, LAS VEGAS, NEVADA
amos bronson alcott said,
"who speaks to the instincts speaks to the deepest in mankind
and finds ???
det. ashby?
jennifer jareau.
this is aaron hotchner.
thanks for getting here
so quick.
morning.
what can you tell us?
we've got an amber alert
in effect.
tip line's being run through
the precinct.
his photo's on the wire.
has the phone company been
served with a caller subscription subpoena?
yeah. we'll get a name and location
if he's calling from a land line.
we'll also run the calls
through our analyst at quantico.
she can triangulate
cell calls.
we need to clear the area
of official vehicles.
if the unsub happens to drive by,
i don't want him to panic ???
ok. i'll clear 'em out after
we make introductions.
how are they
handling it?
separate.
craig, amy bridges,
these are agents jareau and hotchner from the fbi.
we just want to say how sorry we are
for what you're going through
but we're here to do whatever we can
to try and get michael home.
i'm going to tell you
what i told the police.
i don't want to know
what happened to that other boy.
i just want to hear how you're going to find michael.
we understand.
no, you don't.
you're right.
i don't know exactly
what you're going through.
but i do know these cases.
and we're gonna need your help.
of course. we know that.
was it normal for michael
to walk to a friend's house by himself?
what are you saying?
it's just a question.
no it's not.
do you think we had
something to do with this?
no. i don't.
if this was his routine, someone could have
been watching him for some time now.
he'd only done it
a couple times.
amy and i had
a fight about it.
i thought
we were babying him.
i don't want him
crawling into bed with us anymore.
and i thought he should be able to walk
to a friend's house by himself, alone.
he was really proud
of himself the first time he did it.
excuse me.
i'm sorry.
it's like she can't engage
in what's going on.
it's all right.
everybody deals with it differently.
i need to know what happened
to that other boy.
there was no bruising
around his neck or face.
i'm guessing
he used a pillow.
was there any sign
of a struggle?
no, but he would have
been extremely weak.
why's that?
this is where it gets weird.
he was noticeably thin.
and both his stomach and intestines were
completely empty.
he was being starved?
it seems that way.
ok. so,
what's the weird part?
i wanted to determine
if malnutrition played a part in his death.
so, i looked for evidence
of starvation ketosis
by analyzing some vitreous humor--
the squishy part OF THE EYEBALL
and i couldn't find
any ketone bodies there.
meaning?
he was getting
nutrients somehow.
through an i.v.?
there were no marks
to indicate that.
any idea
what else could it be?
honestly, i have no idea.
CRIME SCENE DO NOT CROSS
not exactly
a well-preserved scene.
it's the crime scene
investigators.
they all want to play cop instead of just being
scientists--
and they end up trampling
on everything.
so, he suffocates the boy at another location,
prepares the body,
takes him out to the middle
of nowhere and dumps him.
except there were no traces of the unsub's sweat
on the boy's clothing.
what are you getting at?
well, it's like 1,000 degrees
out here.
if he carried the body,
then he would have gotten
traces of sweat on the clothes.
so, he wraps him
in something.
no fibers.
so, he took the time to change the boy's clothing
and groom him ONCE HE GOT HERE.
if he took that much time,
he'd have to do it at night.
but you still run the risk of someone recalling your
car once the body's found.
not if you didn't have
to park it by the road.
well, you'd want to park a distance away from the dump site
just in case someone saw the car
and came to see what you were up to.
now, tell me this.
if you can drive out
into the desert to dump a body,
why not go in deeper, where you
won't be seen from the road?
because he wanted to be able to drive by and see the body.
that's why he groomed him.
it's like he was preparing him
for a funeral.
yeah. i got it.
thank you.
detective, the funeral for the first victim is tomorrow.
do you feel comfortable asking the family
if they'd be willing to open THE SERVICE UP TO THE PUBLIC?
- why's that? - we feel if they do,
there's a good chance the unsub will come.
i'll go speak to them.
craig, we'd like you and your wife to consider
being there as well.
good. anything.
i think you should talk
to amy about it.
if it might help,
there's nothing to discuss.
i understand. but, please,
just...discuss it with her.
when the police asked
for a picture of michael,
i couldn't decide
what to give them.
i didn't know if it was
right for him to be smiling.
any choice you made
would have been right.
my husband doesn't know
what to do with himself.
he thinks we should be
out there looking for him.
the best thing for you right now
is to just let us guide you through this.
he thinks i blame him.
i'm sure that's not true.
he's right.
my son's been taken.
i'm completely frozen.
and now i'm blaming
my husband.
i feel like a monster.
when they need you,
you'll come through.
you don't even know me.
call it intuition.
i found it when i came into his room,
after he'd been taken.
we don't let him eat in bed.
i haven't moved it
because...
i don't want him to think he's in trouble
for breaking the rules.
you know what you're having?
it's--it's a boy.
congratulations.
- garcia, you ready?
- ready.
mr. bridges, let's go back
over what we discussed.
- he's got my son.
- exactly.
just stay positive.
i've written down some important phrases--
we need to answer the phone.
mr. bridges, please.
i think amy should do this.
she doesn't want to do this.
no. i don't.
it's our experience that the parent that's
least emotional is best.
amy, you'll be great.
just try to humanize michael
at every opportunity.
he needs to see him
as a person.
try to keep him on the line as long
as you possibly can.
the more he talks,
the more he'll reveal about himself.
hello.
are you alone?
um, my husband is with me.
why are you just sitting at home
when you should be out looking for your boy?
you're right.
we need to do that.
he's better off with me.
thank you for calling us
to let us know michael's all right.
i didn't say
he was all right.
i know. i'm--i'm just
trusting that he's ok.
he's in a better place now.
may i speak with michael?
he doesn't want
to talk to you.
he knows what a bad mother
you are.
your 3 minutes are up.
garcia, anything?
it looks to be
a disposable cell phone.
i couldn't triangulate the call.
but it did bounce off not one but 2 towers.
- meaning?
- i know he's mobile.
and i know he's moving
within the las vegas limits.
he didn't travel
outside the city.
it's just a start.
like i said, the more he talks,
the more we'll learn about him.
these are agents
morgan and reid.
they'll be here all night
just in case he calls back.
i need to lie down.
of course.
you should go with her.
yeah.
what'd you find out
from the medical examiner?
we think that
he's starving them.
but that doesn't fit with the care he takes
with the bodies.
starvation would be
a form of torture.
there's no sexual assault.
the torture could be
a substitute for the sex act.
i'll coordinate
with rossi and prentiss.
we'll call you
if there's anything new.
couldn't find any evidence
of forced entry.
why would that matter?
'cause it means he most likely knew
his attacker.
reid?
get 'em off. morgan!
get 'em off! get 'em off!
morgan, get 'em off me!
get 'em off me!
get 'em--
morgan, get 'em off me!
reid. reid. wake up.
it's morgan.
what the hell's going on?
sir, ma'am.
everything's ok.
you wake us up screaming,
you think everything's ok?
i understand we startled you.
and i'm sorry for that.
you're the f.b.i.
you're right.
i'm really sorry.
sir, please, go back upstairs
and try to get some rest.
it was just
a misunderstanding.
everything is fine,
i promise you that.
are you ok?
it was a dream.
i'm really sorry.
was it about michael?
no.
i've been afraid
to close my eyes.
i'm scared i'll see him die.
ma'am, i know it's hard.
but i need you to go upstairs
and try to get some sleep.
please.
i am sorry
for the disturbance.
i'm making everything worse.
reid...
these cases get to all of us.
i'm losing it
in their living room.
and i'm dreaming--
i'm dreaming about dead kids
and covered in leeches.
what the hell is scaring you?
this boy's gonna die
and there's nothing i can do to stop it.
i can't do this.
i'm sorry.
what are you doing?
i'm not going to the funeral.
we talked about this.
no, you talked. i listened.
please, tell her
this is our only chance.
we feel like
it's a viable plan.
you're asking us to go to
the funeral of a 5-year-old boy.
we're going to watch them
lower his body into the ground.
and the same man
who killed him has our son.
if the man who took michael is there,
your presence MIGHT JUST STARTLE HIM.
we're looking for anything that
might draw him out.
i can't watch them bury
a child knowing that we're next.
we feel like this plan
has a reasonable chance SUCCESS.
what do you consider a reasonable chance
that i will ever see my son again? 10%? 20?
i can't give you numbers.
you could.
i understand
if you can't do this.
but if you can, we need to talk about
who we're looking for.
we believe the man
we're looking for is white.
he's probably in his
late 20s to mid-30s.
judging by the quality of the clothing he put
his first victim in,
we believe he comes from
a middle-class background.
this is not someone who is going to be
at the funeral in a high-end or well tailored suit.
he also might be paying
a lot of attention
to the parents of the most
recent boy to be abducted.
watch for anyone whose focus
is on them instead of the service itself.
we also believe he may drive
a 4-wheel-drive vehicle.
pay extra attention
to those mourners.
and memorize license plates.
this unsub dumped his last
body far from the city.
and yet,
he didn't try to hide it.
in fact, it was close enough
to be seen from the road.
that tells us he's trying
to separate his actions from himself.
yet, he wanted to be able
to drive out and visit the body.
this is about remorse.
which is why we believe
there's a good chance he'll be there today.
ok. if you sense someone looking
at you you need to tell us.
we're conditioned
to feel fear.
the little hairs
on the back of your neck?
they tell us the truth.
j.j. will stay here.
if the phone rings,
she'll say she's a family friend and
that you're at a funeral.
you can do this.
hey, kid,
we're almost ready to go.
you know, they're right.
odds are we'll catch the unsub when he dumps the body
or when he tries to snatch another kid.
i know the odds, reid.
it's weird.
some things never go away.
when i was a kid,
every boy i knew had piles of dinosaur toys.
not you?
i had books and notebooks.
my mom filled hundreds of them
with poems by w.s. merwin,
BY BOB DYLAN.
she liked it
when i memorized them.
she was convinced that they were watching us
and writing songs ABOUT THEIR WIVES.
basements are the first part
of a house to be built, right?
so if you're having recurring dream
about a basement,
kinda speaks to the core
fundamentals of who you are as a person.
i thought you didn't believe
in dream analysis.
freud's been discredited
but jung still has his merits.
my dream. the dead boy.
i've been having different versions of it
since i was a little kid.
hey.
you know, nobody would think less of you
if you took a little time off ???
i just want
to find this boy.
there's a very full
crowd here today,
which i believe is part of the natural outpouring of grief
over losing someone so innocent.
it is also a reminder that there
is another boy out there
who is in danger
AND HIM NEED OF OUR PRAYERS.
let's take a moment
and pray for that boy.
for his safe return.
he's here.
why aren't you helping me?
spencer, pay attention.
reid.
what's going on?
i've been here before.
in the name
of the father, son,
holy ghost. amen.
let us take comfort in the gospel
according to matthew.
chapter 18.
"at that time, the disciples
came to jesus and asked,
"who is the greatest
in the kingdom of heaven?
"he called a child,
whom he put among them and said,
"'truly i tell you,
"'unless you change
and become like children,
"'you will never enter
the kingdom of heaven.
whoever becomes humble...'"
are you a friend
of the family?
uh, no.
i just read about it IN THE PAPER.
and you decided
to come to the funeral?
yeah. it was sad.
i love kids.
i wanted the family
to know that people care.
and videotaping it?
who's that for?
we're gonna take a walk.
and we're gonna do it
very quietly so as not
to disturb these people.
where were you on the days ethan hayes and
michael bridges were abducted?
i was home.
don't you need to ask
what days those were?
am i under arrest?
no. you love kids.
you're just helping us
with an investigation.
so, you have no right
to search me.
why? what would we find?
oh, do you like videotaping other things
besides funerals?
how's it going?
he's nervous.
they're trying
to pin him down.
what's that?
you mind giving us a minute?
no, sure.
i had one of the detectives
pull it.
the name riley jenkins
mean anything to you?
no.
think.
back to when
you were a little boy.
i had an imaginary friend
named riley when i was little.
riley jenkins.
he was murdered right here in las vegas
when he was 6 years old.
my math says that you would have been
around 4 at the time.
he was found him in the basement of his own house,
behind the dryer.
he'd been sexually abused
and stabbed.
where can we find
michael bridges?
you are trying to frame me.
you killed ethan hayes,
and you're holding michael bridges.
no.
then why were you
videotaping a funeral?
does death excite you?
oh, wait. that's it.
death gets you off.
i told you, i don't touch.
no. you just kill 'em and find new ways
to watch him afterwards.
i am not sick.
i think you are.
and i think you
desperately want to tell us
exactly how sick
you really are, walter? don't you?
you want us to search
your computer and your home
because this is eating
you up inside
and you know you need
to be stopped.
i never would have
molested that boy!
which boy?
the one from the funeral.
hotchner.
he doesn't know details
of the murder.
you sure?
he assumes the boy was
molested.
all right. thanks.
he's not the one.
i'm sorry.
you said it looked good.
i was hopeful. i'm sorry.
but he was videotaping
that funeral.
we believe he's
a preferential sex offender.
but he doesn't have michael.
how many of these people
are out there?
more than you want to know.
hello.
put the fbi on.
i don't know
what you're talking about.
i saw them there
at the funeral.
put them on!
this is special agent
aaron hotchner.
you were trying to trick me.
you were trying to lock me down
but you arrested the wrong person.
why don't we just
slow down and talk.
we only have 3 minutes.
no. we have
as long as we want.
that's not the rules.
ok. you're right.
your rules.
it was good of you to go
to the funeral today.
you must have really
cared about ethan.
i loved him.
his parents didn't deserve him.
i took good care of him.
is that why you bought
him the new clothes?
they put him in those silly blue sneakers
and lime green oxford.
he hated those!
well, maybe when you're
good enough to bring michael home,
you can tell his parents
what he really likes.
no. he's never coming home.
i saw that so-called mother.
she looked right at me.
she knows he sleeps
better with me.
i don't know who you are.
but please give me back
my son! please.
i'm begging you.
i'll do anything.
just don't hurt my baby.
please!
your time is up.
you were trying to trick me.
no one was trying
to trick you.
you were trying to lock me down
but you arrested the wrong person.
would it be possible for us
to work in private for a while?
he was at the funeral.
i told you.
he was at the funeral,
and you arrested the wrong man.
i don't think
it is a man.
did you hear the way
she described the clothing?
she said the blue shoes.
lime green oxford.
a male wouldn't reference
specific details like that.
i think reid's right.
she talked about
what the child wanted.
how he slept.
how she took care of him.
she said, "i loved him."
a male unsub would have
emphasized the competition, not the care giving.
he would have talked
about how he was smarter than the f.b.i.
bragged about not being caught.
- we could have been looking at both men and women--
- the statistics are overwhelming.
women abduct newborns.
men take children.
garcia.
i'm right here, sir.
will you run the license plates
the police gave you
and find any that might be
registered to a woman.
that would be...
PARAMETERS:REGISTRANT = FEMALE
MATCHING RESULTS: 0
zero.
how's that possible?
transcript almost reads like she's been
institutionalized.
you mean she's crazy.
she described herself
as being "locked down"
not "arrested"
or "put away."
plus, most mental facilities
are very rigid about the amount of phone ???
i think her talking about only having 3 minutes
isn't her rule to us.
it's what she's been institutionalized
to think of as normal.
garcia, can you get records of women released
from mental institutions this past month?
she most likely has some
trauma in her case file--
possibly the death of a child.
i'm sorry. i can't do that.
to protect patient privilege
there's no central database.
i could hack
each hospital individually,
but even then,
most diagnoses are kept separately BY THE DIFFERENT DOCTORS.
i think
i might have a way.
dr. reid.
your mom didn't tell me
you were in town.
she doesn't know i'm here.
i'm working on a case.
and i actually thought
you might be able to help us.
of course.
you've read about the recent
child murder and second abduction?
yes.
we think the person
responsible is a woman.
she would have been
institutionalized.
but we believe she may have been released
within the past few weeks,
just before the first abduction.
what can i do?
i'm assuming you have a good working relationship
with the administrators at other hospitals.
i know no one can open their files.
but if you wouldn't mind
just giving them the profile,
that would be a tremendous help.
she's delusional.
fueled by grief.
very well might have lost a child of her own,
probably around the age of 5.
i'll see what i can do.
spencer?
what are you doing here?
i'm here for work.
we're investigating the murder and abduction
of two 5-year-old boys.
i don't like the idea of you working on things
that are so sad.
i know.
you're so thin.
i was going to come see you the second
we solved the case.
what else is going on
in there?
nothing.
don't lie to your mother,
spencer.
we know.
we feel things.
try to remember the moment when
you felt someone's eyes on you.
i don't know.
yes, you do.
at one point you said,
"he's here."
when was that?
it's her.
garcia, the blonde in the middle.
do you have her?
got her.
isolate the image.
run it through vicap.
see if we get a hit.
on it.
did i know a boy
named riley jenkins?
riley jenkins...
he was a story you made up.
no. no. he was a real kid who was murdered
when i was 4 years old.
oh, i think you're mistaken.
i've been seeing things.
don't say that.
i've been having dreams about his death
since i was little, mom.
you were always a reader.
it affected your dreams.
i remember, when i was 4,
we went to a funeral.
your uncle daniel's, maybe?
i also remember
we moved houses.
and you and dad
argued about it.
and you told dad
that i was in danger.
because you were.
why--why did you think that?
i don't know. i just knew.
i told you. a mother knows.
we're animals, spencer.
we feel things.
i'm sorry. i talked to the heads of
9 different hospitals.
there's no one who matches
your description.
thank you for trying.
you know, if this person has
an axis-1 condition,
her release wouldn't be as important as
whether or not she keeps to her medications.
all right. thank you.
again, thank you very much.
i went off my medication
when i was pregnant with you.
i spent every day in terror,
but i made it.
and it was beautiful.
i had you.
oh, god.
what is it, baby?
women abduct newborns.
excuse me.
i don't understand.
doctor, would it be possible for a woman to convince herself
that a random 5-year-old child's actually her own newborn?
if her psychosis is strong enough.
and, again, if they'd stopped
taking their medication, absolutely.
thank you. thanks.
hotch, i'm pretty sure i know why
the medical examiner was so confused.
i think she's
breastfeeding them.
mommy's here.
there we go.
there ya go.
mommy's here.
get some sleep now, ok?
i got a hit off the woman
on the video.
i ran it through vicap.
her name's claire bates.
she was institutionalized 3 years ago
after she assaulted a fellow
secretary at a law firm.
by that i mean,
she bit off part of her ear.
do we have an address?
there's no last known.
try running
the license plates again.
STATE OF NEVADA
DEPARTMENT OF MOTOR VEHICLES
PARAMETERS: REGISTRANT LAST NAME = BATES
MATCHING RESULTS:
1) HERBERT BATES, RENO, NV
GOT IT
- NO WAY. THAT'S NO GOOD.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
CERTIFICATE OF DEATH
CASUE OF DEATH, DETAILS: MYOCARDIAL INFARCTION
IT'S REGISTERED TO THE FATHER.
he lived in reno, but he died 2 years ago.
GARCIA, PULL HER BIRTH RECORDS.
IF SHE'S REALLY BREASTFEEDING THEM,
then she must
have just given birth.
here we go.
claire bates...
gave birth to a son 3 weeks ago.
BIRTH RECORDS.
OFFICIAL NOTIFICATION :CHILD PROTECTIVE SERVICES
INTERVENED WITH A COURT-ORDERED
SEVEN-DAY EVALUATION,
RESULTING IN THE INFANT BEING REMOVED
FROM THE BIRTH MOTHER PERMANENTLY. (MORE INFO)
oh...
what is it, garcia?
social services removed the baby
from her care after a 7-day evaluation.
that's why she holds
the boys for 7 days.
she's recreating
the loss of her baby.
but she's taking
5-year-olds.
her psychosis must be projecting her baby
onto any children she can get access to.
garcia, can you read us
the social services report?
"while it is admirable that patient stayed off
anti-psychotic medication
"for the health of her fetus,
"we strongly believe that due to a history
of violent and delusional behavior,
"there is a significant risk to the child
if she is granted guardianship.
"therefore, the child shall be a ward of the state
until such time a full-time guardian can be established."
is there an address?
2509 brookside avenue.
j.j. will stay here with you.
we'll call with any updates.
tell reid where we're going.
watch yourselves.
if she's truly delusional,
she'll have moments of clarity
where she realizes what she's done.
morgan and i'll go
around back.
prentiss and i'll
take these doors.
claire!
stop, claire!
she's going out the back.
careful. she's got the boy!
hotch, we got her!
she's going to the garage!
claire, back away from the fire
and put him down.
my baby's dead.
no, he isn't.
he's being taken really good
care of by someone else.
just like you need to take
care of this boy.
i kept healthy.
i did good.
we know you did.
we just need you to step away
and put the boy down.
my baby's dead.
no. he isn't, claire.
let us prove it to you.
do you have
a clean shot of her?
she's not armed, rossi.
if he's still alive
and she drops him in the fire,
we may not be able to save him.
do you have a shot?
yes. i got one.
i've got michael!
i got ya.
no, don't do it!
a doctor has to check him out,
but you can be with him
the whole time.
he should be able to be back
in his bed by tonight.
thank you.
you're gonna be great.
i know.
you know, this is about as good a day
as we're gonna get on this job.
i know.
and yet you're still thinking about a boy
you're not even sure if you really knew.
when i was 4, my mother had a sense
that i was in danger.
reid,
your mother wasn't well.
i know facts about the case.
reid, you've got a photographic memory.
odds are, you saw the story.
he was just a kid like you.
and it caught your imagination.
i don't really think that you believe that.
you wanna know what i really believe?
i believe you could have done anything
in the world with your life
and you chose
to do this job.
your man carl jung says our unconscious
is the key to our life's pursuits.
yeah. yeah.
so, for whatever reason,
that case was stuck in your
brain all these years
and it not only led you
to this career choice
but to the same city
where your mother lives
and for us to have the opportunity to save this child.
yeah.
like i said, this is about as good a day
as we're gonna get, man.
enjoy your moment.
hotch, do you think it would be possible
to wait until tomorrow to return home?
do you think you could find something to do
in las vegas for the night?
bob dylan once said,
"i think the truly natural things are dreams,
which nature can't touch with decay."
i'm proud of you, spencer.
for what?
saving that boy.
how'd you know?
i told you. a mother knows.
dr. norman gave me permission
to sleep on the couch in your room tonight
if it's all right with you.
if anyone tries to keep him
in here any longer,
i'll scratch your eyes out.
one night only.
it helps if they think
you're crazy.
they don't argue.
Bob Dylan "Shelter From the Storm"
* 'twas in another lifetime *
* one of toil and blood *
* when blackness was a virtue,
the road was full of mud *
* i came in from the wilderness,
a creature void of form *
* "come in," she said, "i'll give you shelter from the storm." *
* and if i pass this way again *
* you can rest assured *
* i'll always do my best
for her *
* on that i give my word *
* in a world of steel-eyed
death and men *
* who are fighting to be warm *
* "come in," she said, "i'll give you shelter from the storm." *
* not a word was spoke
between us *
* there was little risk
involved *
* everything up to that point
had been left unresolved *
* try imagining a place *
* where it's always
safe and warm *
* "come in," she said, "i'll give you shelter from the storm." *
fbi.
put your hands in the air.
show me your face.
dad?
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入