Previously on The O.C.:
Do you think that Marissa would mind
if I invited Johnny?
She seemed a little weird
when she saw us together last night.
But they're just friends,
so why would it matter?
I love Ryan.
- It doesn't mean you don't like Johnny.
- I don't.
Then you wouldn't mind
that I just made out with him upstairs.
We both have very complex lives...
...and maybe we should consider
all the implications before going further.
Are we building a hospital?
- Is it too late for a new approach?
- Let's do it your way.
You're trying to take care of me.
The least I can do is take care of you.
- Caleb would've been proud.
- We got it.
Sandy, that's wonderful.
And you did it your way.
Yeah.
Cohen! I got one.
An interview with the Brown guy.
Rushfield told me, and you got one too.
Please tell me it went okay.
It went great. We totally bonded.
Are you high?
Am I high?
Ryan. Ryan. Come on, wake up.
- Hi. What's wrong?
- Seth is gone.
- What? He's gone?
- Yeah.
His alarm went off, I went into
his room, his bed is empty.
- Calc exam.
- Calc exam?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. He probably just
went in early to school, cram for it.
- I'm gonna drive there to make sure.
- No, no, I'll go. I'll go.
I gotta get to school early anyway.
If there was anything going on
with Seth, anything I should know...
...you would tell me, right?
Yeah. I'll call you when I find him.
Hey, man.
So Sandy noticed you're gone.
He's worried.
- Just taking in the sunrise, Ryan.
- That's what they got windows for.
So I wanted to be alone. Are you
the only one that's allowed to brood?
Man, whatever it is, you can tell me.
My Brown interview did not go so well.
Actually, it didn't go at all.
- You blew it off?
- Yep.
Then to put the cherry on top, I went
ahead and lied to Summer about it.
Right.
Well, I don't know, talk to her.
Yeah, it's just, Summer was
over pot by the 10th grade.
She thinks it's juvenile. It's like
telling her I'm into Beanie Babies.
At least tell her
you missed the interview.
You do that, and I'll keep quiet
about the rest.
We're getting dangerously close
to an after-school special.
It's marijuana, I did it twice.
So you're telling me you didn't
come down here to buy a bag?
Fine, I wasn't gonna
smoke anymore anyways.
- What are you doing?
- Trying to decide on a bathing suit.
- Do you think tankinis are over?
- You're going swimming?
No. Johnny's taking me
for a surf lesson.
Says the waves are best
in the morning.
That's what I hear.
Look, I know that you're mad
about me and Johnny.
I'm not mad. Do I look mad?
Okay, we may not be BFFs...
...but you're my sister,
and I can tell when you're mad.
Kaitlin, look in my eyes.
I don't care about you and Johnny.
You have a boyfriend.
So Johnny Harper's fair game, right?
I'm not talking about this.
Can you honestly tell me
you have no feelings for him?
That's what I thought.
Hey. You're right on time.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to walk in on anything.
- No problem. You ready to surf?
- I gotta go. Enjoy the beach.
Katie Rubel, 39, single.
Loves tennis, loves working out.
- Do we have anyone for her?
- I say she dies alone.
- Julie.
- I'm sorry.
I just can't focus on fixing other people's
love lives when my own is such a mess.
Dr. Roberts will call you.
Or if you want, you could call him.
I know you've been married
for 200 years...
...but you must remember
something about dating.
Well, I hope so,
or I'm in the wrong business.
Maybe that's the answer.
Pitch Dr. Roberts the dating service,
set him up.
- Set him up? Are you high?
- No, I'm serious.
Then you'll be back on his radar, and
it won't seem like you're pursuing him.
I like it. I'm aloof, but thoughtful.
When he confronts the idea
of dating these Newpsies...
Half of whom he's botoxed himself.
- he will realize that the only woman
he wants is you.
- And he will call you for dinner.
- I'll suggest Al Forno's.
A table by the window.
I'm impressed. You're sneakier
than I thought, Kirsten Cohen.
Well, being around you
all these years, it's rubbed off.
- Hey.
- Hey, Cohen.
Hey, did you write your thank-you note
yet to the Brown interviewer?
No, actually, that's something
I wanted to talk to you about.
You came to the right person, because
I am master of the thank-you note.
Listen to this.
"Thank you so much
for the resplendent interview."
- Resplendent?
- Yeah. I bought a thesaurus.
Shelley loves SAT words.
I didn't know you two
were on a first-name basis.
Oh, yeah, we totally power-bonded.
Which means I may have
a chance of getting into Brown.
You know what that means?
No calling, texting, e-mailing.
- Just us together. Isn't that great?
- Yeah.
So tell me, how did your interview
really go? Do you think you aced it?
- I knocked it out of the park.
- Really?
Yeah, yeah, and it wasn't easy,
believe me.
But, you know, I turned on
the Cohen charm, as usual...
...and the lady swooned.
- Cohen.
- Yeah.
Shelley's a guy.
Is it because...? Yes, yes.
You're... I'm sorry. Correct.
But with a feminine energy.
I got a gay vibe.
I'm gender-blind, that's the thing.
That's something that I'm gonna
have to work on...
...at Brown, next year,
when we go together.
When we go together.
- I'm gonna see you later. I gotta go.
- Cohen.
We'll talk after school.
Wow, somebody was
really craving caffeine.
Yeah. I can barely keep my eyes open.
Early-morning wake-up call,
courtesy of Seth.
- Oh, has he told Summer yet?
- No, and he's not going to.
By the way, I promised that
we'd keep quiet about it...
...as long as he told her
about the interview.
I was looking forward to Summer
bitch-slapping Kaitlin for giving Seth pot.
- Gonna get away with it, like always.
- Maybe that's best.
I mean, she screwed up,
but she's still pretty much a kid.
Yeah, but with my mom's DNA.
Which means she's capable
of more than you think.
- Are we still talking about Seth?
- This is just sister stuff.
You know, I should probably
get to class. See you later.
Okay.
It's just sister stuff?
Okay, let's practice your pop-up
one more time.
When you told me you were
gonna give me a surfing lesson...
...I kind of imagined us in the water.
No, no. First lesson's
always on the sand.
As long as we're skipping the water
part, let's do this back at your place.
Or we could just blow the whole thing
off. Rent a movie, order in pancakes.
You said you wanted
to learn how to surf.
I'm not training
for the Olympics, okay?
I'm sorry. I'm just distracted.
Thinking about Marissa.
Story of my life.
I like a guy, he's in love
with my older sister.
Look, Marissa and I have
a history together, all right?
- It's just complicated.
- Uncomplicate it.
- Do something.
- I can't do anything. It's not my place.
If you're too lame to do something,
I'll just find somebody who will.
I thought this was a done deal.
Merriam gave us the contract.
He did. Now he has to present it
to the board of physicians.
Can't have a hospital without doctors.
Like it or not, they got a say.
Oh, great. Now we have to ply
more people with women and liquor.
I don't think that's gonna work.
They're doctors, not businessmen.
Then we got that in common.
Call it willful naiveté,
call it bleary-eyed optimism.
- You think we've got a shot?
- Yeah.
There's over 100,000 uninsured
that live in Orange County.
There's got to be some angle we can
find to make that land on these guys.
Well, there is.
The head of the board, Henry Griffin...
Turns out we have
a personal connection.
Well, now, there's a shocking
turn of events.
- It's his daughter, Maya.
- She's a stripper too?
No, she was a year
ahead of me at Kellogg.
Now she's his most trusted adviser.
She used to have a thing for me.
Well, who could blame her?
So now you wanna wine and dine her.
Use her affection for you
to manipulate her father.
Listen, it's no worse than the strippers
we got for Bill Merriam.
Oh, I don't know.
I draw the line at family, Matt.
How about this?
How about we find a strategy that
doesn't involve liquor or sexual favors?
Thank you. I mean, gracias.
- Julie.
- Hi.
Your receptionist told me
you'd be home today...
...so I thought I'd come by
and personally thank you...
...for hosting Kaitlin's birthday party.
And as a token of my appreciation:
"Bachelorettes of Newport"?
- You wanna set me up?
- Well, unless you don't wanna be set up.
Well, I hadn't really thought about it.
Because I can totally understand
if a blind date seems like too much.
Let's see what you have there.
- NewMatch. Wow, she's pretty.
- Pear-shaped, but pretty.
- Look at her. Nice smile.
- Yeah. Adult braces.
And her.
Julie, all of these women
look fantastic.
It's gonna take me a while to choose
one. Mind if I get back to you?
Finally. You're home.
What'd you do, take the scenic route?
I'm sorry. I didn't know
you were waiting for me.
Well, I just get kind of Ionely
while you guys are all at school.
Speaking of school, shouldn't you be
going back to yours soon?
How many times do I have to tell you?
It's called mid-winter break. It's long.
- Apparently.
- Look, I wanna talk to you about Marissa.
This whole Johnny triangle
we're all trapped in.
Triangle?
Now that I'm here,
it's more like a square.
Well, anyway, see, I like him.
And I'm not getting anywhere because
he thinks he's got a chance with Marissa.
Well, not that that's any of your
business, but it's not the case.
I don't know. See, today I asked her
if she had feelings for him, point-blank.
She didn't deny it.
Thanks for the heads-up.
Marissa and I can handle it ourselves.
So if you just wanna...
Ryan, I want you
to do something about it.
I mean, you're a man of action.
You throw punches, set fires.
That's the guy I remember
from two years ago.
- We've all grown up since then.
- You're reformed now. Congratulations.
- Doesn't mean you still can't talk to her.
- So you can hook up with Johnny?
You get something out of it too.
You get to find out where you stand.
Once and for all.
Ryan, hey. Is everything okay?
You sounded really weird
on the phone.
I need to know how you feel
about Johnny.
- So I take it Kaitlin paid you a visit.
- This isn't about Kaitlin.
We both knew this was an issue
long before she showed up.
- I'm with you.
- But that's not the whole story, is it?
Look, maybe you just
feel sorry for him.
Or maybe sometimes you didn't think
you could talk to me...
...or I wasn't listening.
Or maybe you're in love with him.
Either way, you gotta figure it out.
Until then, I don't wanna see you.
Look, I know things
have been confusing...
Hey. Morning.
Oh, no, the Atwood grunt.
That's never a good sign.
What's the matter?
Let me guess, Marissa or Johnny.
Maybe Kaitlin. I'm gonna say
probably a combo platter.
- I think Marissa and I are on thin ice.
- No.
She needs to figure out her
relationship with Johnny, pronto.
She's got good taste in people.
I'm sure she'll do the right thing.
Speaking of the right thing...
- I tried to talk to Summer.
- And?
I chickened out. Which is kind of
my go-to move these days.
But I'm gonna take care of it,
I'm rescheduling the interview.
Think they'll let you
after you blew the first one off?
Well, for the first one,
I had an epileptic fit.
There was a three-car pileup on the
freeway with a jackknifed truck, so...
- All right, I'll work on my excuse.
- That's a good idea.
And, Rita, when did you first find out
that he was cheating on you?
- You mean, the first time?
- Oh, Kaitlin, you're up.
I was just making some grits.
Okay, Mom, we get it.
We live in a trailer park.
- There's no need to go overboard.
- Marissa, you want some?
- I'm not hungry.
- Fine.
I'll go see if Gus likes these.
I mean, he does eat pigeons after all.
Be right back.
I'd kill for some Apple Jacks.
Do you think we have any?
Kaitlin, you had no right to talk to Ryan
about my relationship with Johnny.
- It's none of your business.
- I was sharing my opinion.
What did I ever do to you? I mean,
I know Mom ignores you and Dad left...
- Let's not turn this into family therapy.
- Let's not pretend it's all about Johnny.
- What else would this be about?
- You're doing this to punish me.
You know, I was happy
when you came home.
I thought we were gonna be friends. But
now I just can't wait for you to leave.
Summer. I just got off the phone
with Mr. Spivey from Brown.
- Looks like you've got a fan.
- Oh, great.
I was just curious, did he mention
how it went with Seth?
Seth Cohen?
Yeah. Gangly, mop head,
barely has an ass.
Right. Unfortunately,
Seth missed his interview.
- What?
- He was a no-show.
He was just here
explaining the situation.
Something about a
tractor-trailer accident.
- Oh, my God, that little bitch.
- Excuse me?
I'm sorry. Thank you for your help.
- Well, I finally heard from Dr. Roberts.
- That's great.
- Or not.
- He had me set him up with Laura Cross.
They'll be eating at Al Forno's.
Table by the window.
- Oh, Julie, I'm sorry.
- Oh, no, it's my own fault.
I let you do the scheming.
Clearly, not your wheelhouse.
From now on, if someone
needs to be manipulated...
...we put me in charge.
- Fair enough.
Laura Cross, I don't know her.
Well, she'll probably marry him
and enjoy a life of free browlifts.
Anyway, I am going to get to know her
and find out what I'm up against.
Don't tell me you're
gonna spy on them.
I tried taking your advice, Kiki,
and quite frankly, it sucked.
From now on, we do things
the Julie Cooper way.
Julie Cooper, be careful.
- I see we have a problem.
- Chili, man, I'm fine, all right?
- I'm just...
- In love with Marissa Cooper.
In all my years of loving ladies
and getting nothing in return...
...I have never been as bad off as you.
Thanks. It makes me feel a lot better.
Normally, I would advise you
to go cold turkey.
Delete her number from your cell,
spam-block her e-mails...
...and hope the obsession passes, but
I see that you are in deeper than this.
- So, what do I do?
- Take a shot.
That way, even if she rejects you,
at least you know you tried.
Yeah, and there's always the chance
that she feels the same way, right?
Reasons abound.
The point is, you owe it to yourself to at
least know whether or not she likes you.
- You could have a drink tonight.
- You sure?
Well, you've had a tough day.
So has Matt. Looks like he's
come here to drown his sorrows.
Oh, well, you should ask him
to join us if he's all by himself.
Or not.
Oh, that's Maya Griffin.
OC Weekly did a profile on her.
Apparently,
she's an up-and-coming Newpsie.
Wow, I have too much time
on my hands.
If she's the new queen,
she's got a lot to learn.
Well, why wouldn't she date him?
He's young and attractive.
He's using her.
Her father's the head of the board.
Are you gonna talk to him?
Tomorrow.
Tonight, I'm out with my lovely,
beautiful, morally uncompromised wife.
We could go to the Crab Shack.
Pick up something to go?
Sand dabs are in season. Genius.
- Hey.
- Hey. Thanks for meeting me.
Yeah, I wanted to talk to you too.
- Things have been really...
- Really weird between us. I know.
That's why I wanted
to get everything out.
Johnny, I don't know
if now's the time...
I love you.
And I think you love me too.
- Johnny.
- Look what's happened between us.
I mean, I got hurt, and you took care
of me, even when I begged you not to.
I know. That's true, but...
I told you to stay away from me,
and you showed up at my house.
I'm not imagining this, okay?
There's something real between us.
That's why neither of us can walk away.
Look, you don't have to say anything
right now, okay?
Just, you know, think about it.
- Morning.
- Hi, Ryan. Feel like a bagel?
- I do. Thank you.
- There's my son. How are you?
- Good. Do we have poppy? Oh, great.
- How are you, really?
- I'm really fine, Dad. How are you?
Good. Just making sure you're staying
afloat. I know you got lots of stress.
Exams, college applications.
- Yeah, not to worry.
It's all under control.
- Oh, hey, Summer.
- Hi.
- Just in time for breakfast.
- Oh, thanks, Mr. C.
Actually, I was wondering if I could
talk to Seth upstairs?
- Possibly alone.
- Okay.
All right, so... What the hell?
You lied about your college interview,
and I don't like liars.
- I can explain.
- Explain what? That you're pathological?
That you invent stories about interviews
that never even happened?
You make it sound so bad.
Cohen, you are in a deceit spiral.
If you don't stop, you'll turn into
one of those creepy men...
...with secret attics where they hide
stolen money and porn.
First of all, that sounds awesome.
Second of all, could be worse.
- I got scared.
- Scared?
Yeah.
Tongue-tied, dizzy,
my bladder felt weak.
I just wanna know
why you didn't tell me.
Because I was embarrassed.
You've got this natural confidence.
You're small and you're cute.
People like you.
I'm a social outcast
with a mumbling problem.
- You're just realizing this now?
- lf we go to college together...
...everybody's gonna love you,
and I'm gonna be your nerdy boyfriend.
I'm gonna be your not-so-bright
girlfriend that can't keep up...
...when everyone's talking about
yakuza films and Proust.
- It's Proust.
- See?
Look, we have to be honest with
each other, or this is never gonna work.
- No, you're right.
- Anything else you need to tell me?
Because now's your chance.
Just put it out on the table.
No.
Okay.
Then you are officially exonerated.
Thesaurus again.
You wanna get down?
Hey, I didn't know
we were working this weekend.
Thought maybe you
and I'd go hit the links.
And ruin a sport I love?
It's the weekend,
so I'm gonna make this brief.
I was at dinner last night
with Kirsten at the yacht club.
I saw you there.
With Maya.
Griffin told Maya about meeting me,
so she decided to get in touch.
- She asked you to dinner?
- She did.
Why, is it illegal
to take a girl out to dinner?
You know, when Kirsten
used to run this place...
...I saw a lot of creeps in nice suits
that tried to use her to get to her father.
I didn't like it then,
and I don't like it now.
We're trying to build a hospital
that could service 100,000 uninsured.
You're trying to use a daughter
to manipulate her father.
And you're comfortable with that.
Sandy, you're a great guy, but maybe
you don't have the stomach for this.
We have to bend the rules
if we wanna win the game.
That'd look great on a bumper sticker.
I wanna see you on Monday
with a real game plan.
All right.
Hey.
- Kirsten let me in. She seems really nice.
- What do you want?
Look, you've always been
a really good guy to me.
You know, you've helped me
with Volchok.
- Trusted me with Marissa...
- Now you're in love with her.
I told her.
I promised myself I would just
live with these feelings, you know.
I wouldn't do anything about them.
But I just can't do that anymore.
What do you want, my blessing?
I guess, I just...
Just wanted to say I'm sorry.
Thanks for that.
Leave. Now.
I'm passionately devoted to my work
on the board of the Children's Museum.
Children are so important,
don't you think?
She's so phony.
Well, of course she is.
She lives in Newport.
Oh, God, mayday.
Taryn Baker just walked in.
Get out of there before she sees you.
Oh, too late. Hi, Taryn.
Why are you all bundled up like that?
Has Newport been taken over
by the Taliban?
I'd love to stay and chat,
but I have to be going.
Oh, my goodness, it's Laura Cross.
Laura. Hi.
- It's me, Taryn, from Orchid Club.
- Oh, Taryn, of course.
- Do you know Julie?
- I have to go.
- We haven't met. Julie?
- Julie?
Oh, my. What a coincidence.
Have you been sitting
at the next table this whole time?
Are you spying on me?
I...
I'm sorry.
Hey.
There's a sale at Paul Frank
if you wanna go.
Probably can't afford anything.
- But we could try stuff on.
- No, thanks.
I'm guessing you're still mad at me.
I know you may not believe this,
but I'm trying to do you a favor.
Oh, yeah? Well, thanks.
So far it's been a real blast.
Remember when we were little, and
Dad used to take us to Baskin-Robbins?
You'd have to sample every flavor before
you could decide what you wanted.
And then once you did, you'd realize
you didn't like it, so you'd cry.
Dad would take you back
to get another.
Another story about how growing up,
it was always about me?
No. It's about you
not trusting your instincts.
- Maybe I'm not built that way.
- So?
It's a skill. Learn it.
Make a decision and stick with it.
- Remember what I used to always get?
- Gold Medal Ribbon.
Every time.
I figured, I loved it,
why question it?
Honey, you just missed Marissa.
- Marissa?
- Yeah.
She left this for you.
I'm sorry.
You wanna be with Johnny.
No. I'm sorry I ever made you wonder.
You two have a connection.
I get that. It's not about him.
No, it's about me.
It was just...
...not being able
to talk to you about Trey.
And then with Kaitlin coming back,
her hooking up with Johnny...
...it threw me for a loop.
- I think we can get past that.
- It's not that easy.
You can't just snap your fingers
and make everything the way it was.
Well, we can try.
Maybe start with dinner?
Oh, no.
This is KRKR TV.
And now for the latest news.
Early tonight, the captain of a
Swedish icebreaker in the Barents Sea...
... reported seeing a strange
red fireball come out of the sky.
Says the captain, "It hovered
above my ship for about a minute"...
Johnny.
Which Coop are you here to see?
I'm here to see you.
I thought maybe
we could go to the beach.
For a night surfing lesson?
I was thinking more like
bonfire and tequila.
Even better. I know
where my mom keeps the stash.
So, what's the occasion?
Just feel like you and I
never got a chance to party.
- What do you say?
- Okay.
- Hungry?
- Oh, I'm sorry, baby.
- I should have called.
- Oh, that's okay.
I figured you were here.
Who would've thought
the Newport Group...
...would be where I go
for a moment of Zen?
Sometimes this job makes
you do a lot of hard thinking.
I want this hospital more than
I've wanted anything in a long time.
Then you can't let Matt's relationship
with Maya Griffin stand in your way.
She could be using him too.
Or they could live happily ever after.
The point is, if you want this
as bad as I think you do...
...you have to go for it.
So where's the line?
I'm not worried about you
knowing where the line is.
You always do. It's who you are.
Coming.
- Cohen?
- Hang on.
Cohen, why is the door locked?
Cohen. I brought some DVDs.
Save the Last Dance and She's All That.
I know you're not interested...
...but I can't watch another movie
with Japanese people flying.
That's fine. Let's go downstairs.
- That's fine? Are you okay?
- Yeah. I'm great. Come on.
- What's that smell?
- It is incense.
- I was doing yoga, plus I had bad gas.
- Gross.
Wish we brought
something to mix it with.
Couple more sips,
you won't even notice.
Okay, alky.
Can we just hook up already?
Before you pass out on me.
You don't waste any time, do you?
Well, it's just the fire,
it's so romantic.
And the fire is actually kind of dying.
Well, okay then.
I'll just go find some driftwood.
Heat things up a bit.
What's that?
Nothing I wanna remember.
Where you going?
- Climb up there.
- Okay.
Tequila and rock climbing.
I'm not exactly sure
that's the best combination.
So don't come.
Johnny, wait.
Go away, Gus.
I told you, I don't wanna
play strip pinochle.
You play strip pinochle?
Long story. What...?
What are you doing here?
I stopped by to thank you
for fixing me up with Laura.
She's a wonderful woman.
Well, good. I'm glad it worked
out with the two of you.
If you'll excuse me, I have
a Hot Pocket in the microwave...
...and a wine cooler with
my name on it, so good luck.
What? What do you want?
You.
Excuse me?
You can be manipulative.
You can be aggressive.
I've known you to stretch
the truth on occasion.
But the fact is...
...when I'm not around you,
I miss you.
You do?
What can I say?
I've fallen for you.
Well, this just may be
your lucky night.
I have an extra Hot Pocket.
I'm almost to the top.
Johnny, would you just
come down already?
- You're wasted.
- I'm not wasted.
Johnny, just come down.
- Stop it, that's high enough.
- I'm not gonna fall.
You're scaring me.
I get it. You're awesome.
Just stop.
- Johnny! Oh, my God.
- It's okay!
Johnny!
- You see?
- Johnny, just come down.
I almost dropped it.
It's okay, I got it.
Johnny, please, just come down!
Seth is really into that movie.
Yeah, I know.
And he ate all of our dumplings.
I know it's gonna take more than Thai
food and teen movies to sort this out...
...but if you wanna talk...
Talking's the last thing
I feel like doing.
I figured, since you gave me the silent
treatment the whole way in the car.
What do you want from me?
I want you.
- You wanna answer that?
- Not really.
- It's Kaitlin.
- She's setting the mood.
All right. Let me just get rid of her.
Setting the mood. I'm telling you.
Wait. Kaitlin, let me call you back.
Can you come and get me?
- I'm at Westwood Cove with Johnny.
- No, I'm busy.
Yeah, you're getting busy.
No, but you don't understand.
I'm scared.
He's drunk and
acting like a crazy person.
Come up here!
You gotta see this view!
- Johnny, just come down!
- What's that?
Marissa, it's him. I'm telling you.
Johnny's in trouble,
and I don 't know what to do.
Hold on. She sounds really upset.
- It's Johnny?
- Yeah, he's in trouble.
- Kaitlin?
- Ryan, you have to help me.
- He's drunk and he's gonna get hurt.
- He's really in trouble?
- Yes, come now.
- Be right there.
So that was...?
That was Save the Last Dance, huh?
Okay, I know there weren't
any subtitles or kung fu or whatever.
- But I thought it was good.
- I thought it was amazing.
That dance number at the end
was so inspiring.
And, Summer, I'm so glad...
...I'm so, so glad...
...that she got into
Juilliard in the end.
And she did it for her mom.
For her mom, Summer.
Yeah, it wasn't that good.
This is pretty amazing too.
- It's just a blue screen, Cohen.
- I know, but it's so blue.
I never realized how blue
it was before.
I kind of like... I wanna
go swimming in it or something.
- Yeah.
- For a little dippy-dip.
- Okay. It's pretty blue.
- Yeah.
- Excuse me. I gotta go to the bathroom.
- Yeah, I'm not going anywhere.
I'm not going anywhere.
We should...
We should take our pants off.
Come on, Captain Oats.
We both know something's up.
Over there. You go to Kaitlin.
I'll find another way up there.
- Keep him talking.
- Okay. Be careful.
- Johnny, just come down!
- Kaitlin.
- Are you all right?
- Oh, I'm so happy that you're here.
Marissa.
Johnny, look,
you have to get down from there.
Go home. I don't have
anything to say to you.
We can get through this.
You're one of my best friends.
After all we've been through,
I get to be your best friend.
Go away! Leave me alone!
Come on, just let me explain it to you.
Just come down, Johnny.
Dude, you are the last person
I wanna see now.
Let's get you down from there.
We can talk about it later, okay?
Right, right.
Right, so you can save me
one more time in front of Marissa.
Hey, Marissa! Marissa!
You wanna watch Ryan
save me again?
- Just come down, Johnny, please?
- So she'll love you even more.
- Get back from the edge.
- Listen to her!
- Just be careful.
- Or what, I might fall?
You get to come in
and grab me at the last second?
Ryan Atwood saves the...
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group