Nice job on the grill, Seth.
Those swordfish look perfect.
Wow, the student becomes the master.
There's a new king of the BBQ.
I cede you my oven mitts.
I thought I was destined to live
in your shadow. See, buddy?
- No need to become a fisherman.
- Yeah. That was a bad idea.
- We all have our moments.
- You mean like lying to Summer...
...and breaking up with her?
- I think that was a great idea.
What was your other option?
Telling the truth?
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
- What are you guys talking about?
- Nothing.
I don't know if you saw,
but your graduation tickets came.
Aisle seats, nice.
You'd think after sending two kids
to Harbor...
...they could cough up more tickets.
He's just worried about the Nana.
- She's an excellent clapper.
- She can do the two-finger whistle.
And she's never taken a picture
out of focus.
- She was born for graduations.
- Let her take my tickets.
You know, I mean, Seth's got you guys
covered. Hate to see mine go to waste.
Why don't you invite family?
Your mom would love it.
I'm gonna go wash up.
Sink's right here. Oh.
I don't think it's a good idea.
I tried this already.
She signed up for AA,
she's starting her life again.
After writing bad checks
and getting arrested and disappearing.
- She doesn't have the greatest record.
- Think I'm gonna wash up too.
- It's important to him.
- I don't wanna see him get hurt again.
- It's his decision.
- Well, he's still a kid.
Right. Because when we get older,
we make much better decisions.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to upset...
It's fine. It's something
I've been thinking about.
Haven't seen her in so long...
...if I don't invite her to graduation,
will I ever see her again?
I know the last time she was here
it was difficult.
- When Sandy saw her, how was she?
- Honestly, not good.
But she's trying.
Maybe seeing you again will be
just the thing.
For both of you.
- What if she's worse?
- There's only one way to find out.
And if you want me to fly
to Albuquerque with you...
If I do this, I need to do it alone.
But you're right.
You're right, she's my mom.
I owe her a chance.
How bad can it be, right?
Right.
What are you doing in here?
I just got back from my little trip
down Mexico way.
I bribed your maid with local speak.
Really? Mima's from the Philippines.
Must have said something right.
- Hope you weren't Ionely without me.
- I survived.
Okay. We can't do this. Okay?
What're you talking about? I go away
and you get over me?
- No, it's not that, it's just...
- Her mother might find out.
I told Neil this house had rats.
How you doing?
It's nice to meet you.
Keep that grimy paw away from me.
Unless you wanna see what 10 years
of Cardio Barre can do to your face.
I was just leaving anyways.
Yeah, I think your daughter's over me.
I guess I was just a phase.
- Spare me the lecture.
- No lecture. I get it. He's cool.
He's got great abs...
...and personifies everything
that's bad for you.
So you wanna sleep with him instead?
Choices you make
are going to affect your future.
He's not that bad.
Look, you were wrong about Ryan...
...maybe you're wrong now.
- We're not gonna test that theory.
Because I'm not gonna allow it.
I went completely overboard...
...and made you a gigantic sandwich
for the flight.
Thanks. Looking forward to it.
I booked you a car to go anywhere.
- I can take a cab.
- Just humor me. I worry enough.
All right.
Actually, I'm a little worried too.
- I didn't get a lot of sleep.
- Do you have a game plan?
Yeah. I guess.
She mentioned some diner
she's working at.
I figure I show up...
...and say hi,
and wait for the fireworks.
Whatever happens, you have
at least one proud mother...
...watching you when you graduate.
- Yeah, thanks.
Hey, Sum.
If it makes you feel any better...
...I saw Seth and he looks
as miserable as you do.
The thing that would make me better
would be seeing that assless wuss...
...skinned, flayed, and served
as assless wuss tartar.
- That's very descriptive, Summer.
- Look, "T-to-the-T"...
...I know you're up on life,
down with God...
...and you have a very positive,
optimistic view on the world.
- But I ain't having it.
- I'm not trying to offer you anything...
...other than my friendship.
But, you know, if you wanna be alone
that's okay with me.
How could he lead me on and agree...
...that we should plan
our futures together...
...and then decide,
"You know what? Maybe we shouldn't.
We're not destined for each other."
I should just go ship off to Rhode Island?
I'm going to be deserted on an island.
Technically, Rhode Island is only
bordered on three sides by water, so...
- It was an awful thing to do.
- And to think...
...just two years ago
he stood up on that cart...
...and declared his love for me.
- Oh, that was so sweet.
You didn't see me, but I was there.
And I remember,
that geek was in love with you.
And I have only gotten hotter since then.
Something is up.
A guy like Cohen is incapable
of walking away from a girl like me.
Unless he is hiding something.
And no one hides anything from me.
I'm gonna get to the bottom of this.
Thank you so much for our pep talk.
- Another Starr and Ginger.
- Why don't you get it in a to-go cup.
What's the matter?
You're not happy to see me?
You don't know when to quit, do you?
What's this?
A projection of what my future earnings
would've been.
Plus pain and suffering.
Which were considerable.
- You want me to pay you?
- Actually, Griffin.
He's the one I've got evidence on.
Otherwise I think the DA would be very
interested in the documents I've got.
You're talking blackmail,
it's not even noon yet.
Tell your boy Griffin to pay up in cash
tomorrow. Or I start spreading the news.
Put it on his tab.
You're getting yourself in
pretty deep here.
No deeper than you.
Yeah?
- Did you forget your watch again?
- No, I came to see you.
Look, I get it.
Your mom doesn't like me.
I'm a bad influence, blah, blah.
See you around.
Actually, I was thinking
maybe you'd wanna hang out.
- And what about school?
- It's second semester, senior year.
Unless you don't want to.
Well, if you're gonna stay, then stay.
Wherever you want. Place is all yours.
I'm looking for someone.
Dawn Atwood?
Her shift doesn't start
for a couple hours.
- Who should I say is looking for her?
- A friend.
- I'm staying at La Crescenta.
- Nice hotel.
Dawn doesn't have friends
that stay at nice hotels.
I got a good rate.
She does, however, have a son.
Lives with some pretty wealthy people.
Supposed to be cute.
- Ryan.
- Chloe.
Your mom is gonna lose it
when she finds out you're here.
I hope not.
Couple hours, you said?
Great. I'll be back.
I'll be here.
Okay.
All right.
Let's review factoring a polynomial.
This is good stuff, you guys.
All right, what we have
is an expression...
...in which constants and variables
are combined using only addition...
...subtraction and multiplication.
Seth, you are so funny. I'm sorry,
that was just such a knee-slapper.
Is there a problem, Miss Roberts?
No, no. Well, not unless you're insulted
by Seth's impersonation of you...
...behind your back involving penguin
walking, buckteeth, and cross-eyes.
You do an impression of me?
No, no, I don't do any impressions.
I don't use props.
I don't like jokes in general.
Why don't you work on some
one-liners in Dr. Kim's office.
And why don't you join him since
you're such a receptive audience.
Should be a hilarious
weekend detention.
What is your deal, woman?
I've never been thrown out of a class.
Sorry to tarnish your perfect record...
...but how else
was I going to talk to you?
The breakup is off.
I broke up with you...
...and it's in my power
to un-break us up.
- You can do that?
- Technically, I just did.
Unless you can explain
what your deal is...
...and why you don't want
to be together, we're back on.
Technically, officially, completely.
- Okay, now...
- Wait. Here we are.
Dr. Kim's office. You know what?
I'll go first.
You just plead temporary insanity.
It's good to have you back, babe.
Are you not coming in?
- Don't think so.
- Wanna go somewhere...
...and talk or something?
Sounds good.
Hold that position.
It's probably my supply drop.
- I'm having some people over tomorrow.
- Marissa!
- Oh, my God, it's my mom.
- I'll handle it.
Good, because I'm gonna hide.
Where is my daughter?
Is she in here?
Hey, I thought you were my dealer.
Kind of disappointed.
Don't get smart.
You don't have the equipment.
Her school called.
She didn't show up.
- She already got into college.
- Listen up, Tommy Lee.
You're the latest in a series
of experiments my daughter makes...
...when acting out. So enjoy it.
Because right here, right now,
is as good as it gets for you.
Soon Marissa's gonna wake up and
realize she is so much better than you.
You think she's gonna come
back to you?
Marissa knows that I will be there
for her...
...whenever she decides to come home,
because I am her family.
Not some punk with a smirk, three
brain cells and a good coke connection.
You tell her that.
That's my mom.
I'm gonna get some beer.
- Best not to tell my mom about the beer.
- Also won't tell the guys you're not 21.
Good idea. Cheers.
- You traveled pretty far to avoid her.
- Yeah, well, I'm working up to it.
My mom and I haven't had
the easiest relationship.
Knowing Dawn a little, I figured.
But if it makes you feel better,
she's doing well.
Yeah, I saw that. She seemed happy.
There was a guy that made me
nervous, but...
Oh, that's just Ron.
Her new boyfriend.
- That's what I was afraid of.
- He looks hardcore.
And, yeah, he does own a rather
large snake. But he's got a good heart.
Yeah. They all do at first.
I love this song. Do you wanna?
Come on.
I don't really dance so much. I...
- This is not what I expected.
- Yeah? Well, maybe it's what you need.
Boy, you've got a way with people.
Urban Planning Committee
has signed off.
What can I say? I'm very charming.
Close the door.
Your message was cryptic.
Do we have a problem?
Matt's not giving up. Since you had
nothing to do with the ass-kicking...
...that shouldn't get your blood up.
- What's he want?
Money. In exchange
for the incriminating files...
...which you claim couldn't be
incriminating. You know what?
I'm gonna let the cops deal with it.
And destroy all your hopes and dreams?
Watch all of this disappear?
We have done such good work so far.
I'll deal with Ramsey.
Explain to him the importance
of the hospital.
No. I'm making Matt my problem.
Well, then, good luck.
For both of you.
- Not gonna say anything to your mom.
- Yeah, good plan.
Oh, so that's why you came
looking for her.
- Invite her to graduation?
- Yeah, something like that.
Oh, your mom and Ron should blend
right in at your school.
You've gotta send me a photo.
Thanks for the company.
- Hello?
- Hey, man.
- How's Albuquerque?
- I just hooked up with a waitress.
That would never happen to me,
you stallion.
Doesn't know I'm here.
I'm thinking about taking
an early flight back.
You can't just fly to New Mexico
and not say hi.
You wanna meet her trucker
boyfriend and his python at graduation?
So don't invite anyone.
Just do a quick pop in, say hello.
- What can happen?
- Not a question I want answered.
Just be a man.
Someone around here ought to.
You still lying to everyone?
I'm trying to speak as little as possible.
Less I say, the fewer lies I have to track,
but Summer wants answers.
If I tell her the truth, she'll throw away
her future over me.
Yeah, well, sounds like we both have
women to face.
Each who suffers blackouts
of their own kind.
- Well, good luck.
- You too.
My baby.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
What are we doing tonight? Since we're
dating again we should go on a date.
Except since you un-broke up with me,
you sort of put the ball back in my court.
And now I break up with you.
Which means only I have the power
to un-break us up.
- You're breaking up with me?
- Yes. I'm sorry, I really am...
...but I feel it's for the best.
- What? l...
I un-broke up with you
so I could find out...
...why you broke up with me.
I guess you'll never know.
- You look so good, sweetie.
- So do you, Mom.
When Chloe told me,
I couldn't believe it.
- She told you?
- And my answer's yes.
A hundred percent. I wouldn't miss
your graduation for anything.
She told you about
the graduation too?
She just called.
Let's go, Dawn. Food's getting cold.
Yeah. I hear you, Nick.
Hey, Nick. That's my baby.
This is my meatloaf. Get it out there.
You know what? You're busy.
Let's talk tomorrow.
- All right? Okay.
- You bet.
- It's so good to see you.
- It's good to see you too.
Thanks for asking me, Ry.
Light it up, light it up.
You still sleeping?
- Party's starting early.
- You need to call your mom?
So the princess fell off her throne
and landed on Volchok's mattress.
Heather. It's good to see you too.
Who said it was good to see you?
You know, the dress you wore to PJ's
going-away party was pretty cute.
Kind of plain, don't you think?
You should see how the women dress
in Newport.
Like in the magazines.
You should treat yourself.
Chloe, you got a customer.
Dawn, your boy's here.
- Morning, hon.
- Morning.
I'll get some coffee.
Chloe's been trying
to talk me into a new dress.
- You don't have to buy anything.
- No, I want it to be perfect.
And I was thinking,
after the ceremony...
...I'd like to take everyone to dinner.
I mean, nothing fancy
if I'm footing the bill, but...
Hang on.
Hey, baby. Staying out of trouble?
I was sorry you had to go
on the road last night.
I really want Ryan to meet you.
Yeah. No, I checked on the flights
to Orange County and...
Hang on a sec.
It's okay if I bring a friend, right?
- Yeah, yeah. Sure.
- Let me get my calendar.
- She on cloud nine or what?
- She's very excited.
Sorry I ruined your surprise.
I mentioned I ran into you
and it just kind of slipped out.
You were gonna invite her, right?
- Yeah, totally.
- Okay.
No way. No scheming,
no plan B's, no wacky high jinks.
Cohen broke up with me. Only he
has the power to un-break us up.
There's no way I'm gonna go
groveling back to him...
...like some pathetic,
brokenhearted little bitch.
- Do you still love him?
- Yeah.
- There's something wrong with me.
- Did he say that he doesn't love you?
Now that you mention it, no.
He did not.
You see? He's acting out of fear.
He's trapped in an anxiety spiral.
And in the rock-paper-scissors
of romance, love trumps fear.
Actually, loves trumps everything.
So let's just say for conversation's sake
I was open to a little scheming.
Well, I have an idea.
You didn't get into Brown too,
did you?
- Hey, Taylor. What's up?
- I wanted to let you know...
...that detention today
is in the student lounge.
And you're telling me this because...?
Because it's my job
as a Harbor Student Proctor.
I'm supervising detention this week.
How is that better than
having actual detention?
Seth, student lounge.
And don't be late or I will have to
give you a tardy.
Hey, honey.
You left early without saying goodbye.
- I didn't want to wake you.
- Last night, when you came in?
It was late.
I need you home tonight, Sandy.
We have to talk.
I just feel like
we're so disconnected right now.
You're right.
Well, I think I can be home by 7.
Thanks. I'll see you then.
I'll see you.
You buying again?
You should stop celebrating
and start packing.
I spoke to Griffin.
He's not interested in your deal.
- That's not what he said.
- You called him?
He called me, actually.
Said that you two talked.
He understands what he has to do,
and he's willing.
He's willing to
go round two on your skull.
He's meeting me tonight
with the money.
If I give him what he wants, this time
next week I'll be on a beach in Cabo...
...getting some well-earned R and R.
I'm gonna start
my own business in Chicago.
He can't be trusted, Matt.
If anybody should know that,
you should.
- I hold all the cards here.
- You willing to bet on that?
Yeah. Take it off.
Yeah, Heather, come on, baby.
Hey. She's having fun.
More than you.
Yeah, well, I'm not wasted.
- That's not bad.
- Yeah.
Yeah, Heather, you need another beer.
Hey, let me get you a refill, baby.
Hey, Heather. Drink it, baby.
Drink it up.
There you go, come on.
Little bit more.
Oh, yeah, I like that.
Hey.
Got ten bucks?
- What are you doing?
- I know you're afraid, Cohen.
Yeah, that you're gonna fall.
Don't go up there.
Your breakup...
...was missing a key ingredient.
The only ingredient, really.
- Which is?
- That you don't love me anymore.
- Summer...
- Look, I love you this much.
And I wanna be with you now and next
year and whatever comes after that.
So I'm asking, in the presence
of this coffee cart...
...and the sacred moment
that it represents...
...if you can honestly tell me that
you don't love me anymore?
- Summer, I...
- Just say it.
Cohen, if you don't love me,
I promise I will go to Brown by myself...
...and I will be cold and miserable
and alone.
And I will never bother you again.
I don't love you anymore.
Oh, my God.
- Summer...
- Just get away from me.
Okay? Just get out of here, Cohen!
- I'm so sorry...
- I gotta go to detention.
- Where are we going?
- Oh, don't worry about it.
Hey, Heather?
Hey, I'm glad I found you guys.
I left my jacket in the van.
Volchok said you have the keys?
- But it's not that cold.
- True, but it's my favorite jacket, so...
Hey! Get off of me. Heather!
- Shut up, bitch!
- Heather!
Dude, wait your turn!
- Get off of her!
- What the hell?
Get off of her! Oh, God.
- Get out!
- Hey, come on, dude.
It's cool.
We were just having a little fun.
Yeah? One sec.
Hey, Mom, I was gonna go
look for you at the diner.
She wouldn't have been there. The girls
have been on a serious shopping spree.
Okay, I know this isn't like
what Kirsten wears.
It's kind of low-cut, a little sparkly.
- It's a special occasion.
- You gotta see it on her.
- Go put it on.
- Oh, okay.
You know what?
I don't have the time right now.
Yeah, yeah, I got an earlier flight.
And Mom...
...I was talking to Seth,
and graduation's just a ceremony.
I mean, everybody in those
funny hats...
...bunch of boring speeches...
- It wouldn't be boring to me.
Well, we were thinking about
just blowing it off...
...getting out of town that weekend.
- Out of town?
Yeah, but I mean, you could come in
later in the summer and visit me...
...or I could come up here.
But no graduation.
No, no, I guess not.
You don't have to lie to me, Ryan.
Don't have to worry about me
embarrassing you at graduation.
- Mom...
- I may not have been the best mother...
...but I have never been
ashamed of my family.
You don't know her the way I do.
- I never said I did.
- Been the same my whole life.
She gets clean for a little while,
promises she's changed.
Then she meets some lowlife,
he moves in with her, she bottoms out.
How many of these lowlifes
does she meet in rehab?
Hasn't had a drink in 12 years.
Pays for their apartment,
even fixed up one of his old cars for her.
- Yeah, well, I didn't know that.
- Didn't want to.
Maybe you already
made up your mind about him.
And about your mom too.
- I gotta get to the airport. Car's waiting.
- I'll drive you.
After the trouble I caused,
it's the least I can do.
And there's a stop
I wanna make on the way.
Hi, this is Sandy Cohen.
I can 't get to the phone right now...
- I see you brought your nurse.
- And your money.
Files are in the back seat of my car.
The door's unlocked.
- Not gonna send your guy to get them?
- Well, he's not here for the files, Matt.
Just as well, since there are no files.
The only evidence Matt has
is of his own bad judgment.
You expect me to believe
this is a bluff?
Oh, go check the car yourself.
After we spoke,
I had your hard drive searched...
...checked your e-mail.
You never had evidence.
Whatever you think Griffin was up to
is based purely on gossip and hearsay.
Yeah, well, I figure if he was guilty,
he'd pay up...
...just to be safe.
- Wasting my time, Ramsey.
- Yeah.
Think about all the sick people
you could be healing.
- What's this?
- It's your severance.
Might not buy that beach in Cabo,
but it'll get you on your feet in Chicago.
- I can't take this, not after...
- I put you on this path.
Take it and go.
Sandy.
- I'm sorry.
- Me too.
- Hey, Mom.
- Hey.
Where have you been? It's late.
Full Metal Yakuza
and 99 Cycling Swords.
- Those are movies?
- A few hours...
...of bloodshed and violence
might help kill the pain.
- You wanna talk?
- I was gonna ask you if you'd seen Ryan.
- Not yet.
- Okay.
- Everything okay?
- Everything's okay.
- Okay. Good night.
- Night.
Before you leave, I just want you
to know something.
You're her whole life, Ryan.
Kirsten sent that stuff.
She's a real nice lady.
Oh, don't worry, my eyes are red
from crying, not from drinking.
I'll be out there.
I'm sorry.
You know, when Sandy came to
invite me to your birthday party...
...I really wanted to go.
- But you didn't.
I wasn't ready.
I guess I know the feeling.
But I've been showing up at my
meetings and showing up for work...
...and finally picked a decent guy.
You probably don't understand how
hard it is to hold it together every day.
I don't know about that.
I live in Newport,
but I'm still your kid, after all.
- So I'm still your mom.
- Yeah.
If there's a little bit of me in you,
then I can't be all bad, right?
- Promise me you'll remember that.
- I promise.
- So I'm sorry if...
- It's okay.
Your little family intervention
seems to have worked.
Then I'm not sorry.
For anything that may have happened.
Me either.
Well, my ride's here, flight to catch.
Well, if everything works out
at graduation...
...maybe we'll see some more of you.
- All right. Yeah. Sounds good.
Okay.
Mom?
Marissa, honey.
You want me to whip up
another round of Frappuccinos?
They say chocolate and sugar
send endorphins to your brain.
Come on, tell me you feel better.
He doesn't love me.
Welcome back, buddy.
How was your mom?
Coming to graduation.
You really waiting here
to ask about my mom?
I made the worst mistake of my life.
Now I need to get Summer back
and get into Brown.
- Great. How?
- That's where you come in.
- We need a plan?
- It's gonna be a long night, Ryan.
Lot of whining, lot of pining...
...some brainstorming.
You don't mind?
It's good to be home.
All right. How are we gonna
get Summer back?
Plan A: I fake my own death.
You never wanna underestimate
the power of the sympathy vote.
- Is there a Plan B?
- Yeah, yeah.
I could hack in through
the Brown firewall...
...into the Admissions Office mainframe
and reverse my acceptance.
That's actually a good idea.
You know how?
I had an uncle who went to De Vry.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group