Previously on The O.C.:
- What do I do to get you to stay?
- I think you're doing it.
- You know this engagement is a trial.
- What?
- Griffin will not move unless you're gone.
- He's taking kickbacks from vendors.
Totally and completely untrue.
Give me your word,
I'll give you the benefit of the doubt.
What happened?
I know about Volchok.
What's gotten into you?
- You're being so lame.
- Not as lame as you.
I'm hoping that you both
will apply to Berkeley.
The guy from Brown didn't say they
couldn't take more students from Harbor.
- This might be the year.
- That's right.
- Cohen, come out. I wanna see!
- All right!
I feel like Pa Kettle.
Not bad. Try this on.
Oh, wow, you got us
matching parkas.
And matching hats
and matching scarves.
We're going to be the warmest,
most coordinated couple at Brown.
Think you're jumping the gun?
We don't get our letters till tomorrow.
Oh, please. With your dorked-out grades
and my NASA-level SATs...
...we are so getting in.
- It's Brown.
Everyone's got good grades
and SATs.
It's very possible that neither of us
could get in. Or one of us could.
- Which one of us would that be?
- Just as likely you'll get in and I won't.
- You really believe that?
- Where would you be?
Stuck in Providence, with one half
of a his-and-hers parka set.
Yeah, like I'd go if you didn't.
- What?
- Cohen.
I applied to Brown so we could be
together. I'm not going without you.
Brown's one of the top
universities in the world.
People dream about going there.
No, you dream about going there.
I dream about
being with the one I love.
Even all padded up,
you still look scrawny.
I need to get some water. I'm sweating
so much, I'm getting dehydrated.
- I thought you were making me dinner.
- I did.
Yeah?
- You didn't let me eat it.
- No one's stopping you.
Really? Okay.
- Well, in that case...
- Nope!
No. No.
What?
So with a 90-day escrow...
...that means you'll be in town for...
- Ninety more days, Einstein.
- Right. That makes sense.
Or till you get accepted
to whatever college you applied to.
Yeah.
Okay.
Should I not have mentioned it?
No, no, it's fine. You're right.
Your letter should be
arriving tomorrow, right?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, but I've found ignoring
the future never makes it go away.
Well, whatever happens,
we'll make it work.
We should eat before the burgers
get cold. I'll grab some water.
- Hi.
- Hey. You want a water?
Sure.
I was just
cooling myself off.
All this time, I thought getting into
college would make everything easier.
Yeah.
Not gonna happen.
There's a cold front coming through.
Pass the milk.
That's cream. I said milk.
Eating breakfast, are we?
Does this mean
we're going to school?
Or you need strength for the children
you and Volchok plan to mug?
Big day, girls. College letters arriving.
- Are you excited?
- Yeah, delirious.
Don't be nervous. You're getting
into Berkeley. I feel it in my bones.
- I gotta get to school.
- Oh, Marissa.
Your friend, his motorcycle woke up
Neil. You might wanna apologize.
Why? In case he changes his mind about
marrying into our trailer-park family?
- That's not really my problem.
- Marissa.
She's really outdone herself again.
Summer, how worried
do I need to be about her?
I don't know. She's not exactly
confiding in me right now.
- Morning, everybody. Hey, sweetheart.
- Hey, Dad.
- Feeling lucky?
- Yes. My aura is green.
Oh, that has to be good.
- Where's Marissa?
- She...
Went to school early because she's
nervous with all the college stuff.
Berkeley would be lucky to have her.
Just think:
It's just a short
motorcycle ride away.
Well, that's a hell of a forehand.
Imagine that
connecting with somebody.
I didn't know you were coming.
The gate was unlocked. You should
be more conscious of security.
I'm assuming these are some references
to what happened to Matt.
- Hope he's okay.
- Let's skip to the part...
...where you tell me you had
nothing to do with it.
- Is he implying that I did?
- Matt hasn't said anything.
This is me talking. I want this
hospital built more than anything.
But if you haven't resigned
within 48 hours...
...I'm gonna do everything in my power
to take you down.
And I was lying.
Your forehand sucks.
I don't know about that. That just
doesn't look right to me. You guys.
- I'm so glad to see you.
- Hey. What's up?
- Have you spoken to Marissa lately?
- lf you count, "Pass the milk."
I need to talk to her about the sweatshirt
bonfire. You guys are coming?
Where the seniors wear sweatshirts
of the colleges they're going to?
Because that always struck me
as incredibly lame.
- Oh, and I need your help.
- I gotta get to class.
- I gotta too.
- I know you're just making an excuse...
...to get away from me.
It's okay. It's cute.
- Anyway, about Marissa.
- I wouldn't count on her.
That's great.
She's supposed to get the food.
This is so typical. You know?
People join Social Committee,
they think it's fun and games.
Who ends up doing work when someone
decides to go Last Exit to Brooklyn?
- Taylor. That's who.
- I think she's just...
...going through something right now.
- Seung Ho, it's Taylor. Hi.
Listen, how much kimchi
can you get me by tomorrow night?
You are saving my ass, Seung Ho.
You are really saving my ass.
Hey, I'm glad you called.
That's the first time
anyone's ever said that.
- What's up?
- Nothing.
Well, college letters are arriving today.
My mom's been pressuring me about it.
And Summer and I are fighting.
So I guess, maybe everything.
Well...
...the guys are gonna party
on the beach.
Maybe you should come, you know?
Take the edge off.
- Can you pick me up?
- Be there in a half-hour.
- Hey, you.
- Hey.
- Thought I'd stop by.
- Well, I'm flattered.
Taking time out of your day to see me
when you have a letter waiting for you.
What can I say?
Couldn't help myself.
I could probably tell if you got in.
- Yeah?
- I never mentioned I could read palms?
- Must have slipped your mind.
- Must have.
- You're gonna be rich.
- That's nice to know.
Oh, sorry.
- I read it upside down, so flip that.
- Well, easy come.
This is important. It's warning against
dark-haired beauties...
...who walk into your life.
Really? And what does it say?
It says if you're not very,
very careful...
...they'll steal your heart.
In all that, there's...
There's nothing about college?
Oh, yeah. You got in.
All right, I just need to grab a jacket.
Any chance you can get
some beer money?
I'm a little short.
Sure. I'll be right back.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
- Hello?
- Summer?
- Hey!
- I got in!
What? Yeah! All right!
Congratulations. Amazing.
- Thanks. Did you?
- Yeah.
- Really?! Oh, congratulations.
Where's Cohen?
- I don't...
- Hey.
Hey. So you guys both got in?
Yeah. Are you...?
Oh, my God.
Pack your muffler.
We're going to Brown.
Yeah!
- Oh, man. That's awesome, dude.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I'm so happy.
- I'm proud of you.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hello? Hi.
I've been on hold since 5 in the morning,
so here's my question:
Is there some sort of a possibility
that a mistake was made?
Because I mean, mistakes can happen.
Right? Even at Brown.
No, no. I'm not trying
to be sarcastic at all.
Let me ask you this: Is there
some sort of appeals process or...?
Next year?
Lady, my girlfriend is... Is... Is... Is...
Hello?
Sandy?
- Oh, hey.
- Good morning.
Whatever problems you're thinking
about right now, let them go.
Our kids got into college.
It's a big day.
- You're right. We did it.
- We did it.
- I see the self-congratulation...
...has begun.
We are so proud of you.
A Cohen in the Ivy Leagues.
You did the work. But I think our genes
deserve some of the credit.
- Thanks.
- We knew you could do it.
Oh, hey. There's Ryan.
He got into college too.
- Give him some hugs.
- Congratulations.
Our next generation Berkeley man.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- We're so proud of both of you.
You know, we should have
a celebration dinner tonight.
- Invite your ladies.
- Yeah.
- You think you're making too big a deal?
- Your father's right.
- Seven-thirty.
- Sure, sure. Thanks.
No more hugging.
Physical contact freaks me out.
- Feeling better?
- Yeah.
I don't know where you were
or what you think you're doing...
...but call me as soon as you get this.
I've had it, young lady.
Neil, you're up.
Can I get you some coffee?
Yeah.
Summer just left.
She's excited about Brown. Wanted
to stop by REl on the way to school.
Something about a subzero
sleeping bag.
Marissa must have left
super early this morning.
I'm worried she didn't get in...
...and maybe is embarrassed to tell me.
- She got in.
- Excuse me?
I found this in the trash
when I got home last night.
- Oh, my God.
- Julie...
...we both know she didn't
spend the night here.
I don't know what's going on.
But we have to stop pretending
that it's not happening.
You've gotta talk to her.
You late for something?
I figured I'd make an appearance
at Harbor. It's fourth period.
So, what are you doing
tomorrow?
My school's having this party thing
I have to go to.
All the seniors wear the sweatshirt
to the college they got into. It's...
Gayest thing I've ever heard.
So you're really thinking
about going to college?
Why? You don't see it?
So me and some of the guys
are going to Baja for the weekend.
You know, surf.
Smoke some Mexican green.
Wanna come?
Or can't you miss
your gay sweatshirt party?
Hey. Atwood,
have you seen Skeletor?
- No, why?
- Well, I bought us thermal facemasks.
I wanted him to try his on.
Oh, well, why don't you just
bring them to dinner tonight?
Sandy and Kirsten? The celebration
thing? I'm sure he meant to tell you.
- Oh, well, yeah. Probably.
- Probably.
When you see him,
will you give him this?
Hey, man.
Summer was looking for you.
I invited her for tonight.
Cool. Good.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah, no.
It's just, if she sees me,
she'll dress me like a Timberland Barbie.
Did you invite Sadie?
- I'm going over to her place.
- You tell her you got in?
No. No, that's kind of difficult.
We haven't been
going out long...
...but what do you do when only
one of you is going to college?
Man, I wish I knew.
- Hi.
- Hey!
Perfect timing.
I just finished working.
So, congratulations.
Psychic, remember?
- And when you didn't call last night...
- Yeah.
Well...
Yeah.
- I'm happy for you.
- Thank you.
You wanna mention the elephant
in the room or should I?
I've been thinking, I don't
have to go till August.
We could have the summer.
Not so into relationships
with an egg timer on them.
Sadie, the last few months...
Okay, Ryan. Pet peeve:
Having a guy tell me how amazing I am
while dumping me. Rings kind of false.
I was gonna say I've been happier than
I've ever been with anyone I've dated.
I'm in Newport
because of you.
Making jewelry.
Very portable business.
You see where I'm going with this?
You would move to Berkeley?
Yeah, I would. If you want me to.
Yeah, I do.
Hello, Mr. and Mrs. Cohen.
- Well, hello, Summer!
- Hi, Summer.
- My dad just dropped me off.
- Hey, is dinner ready?
Oh, my God.
Get used to it. This is what you're gonna
be looking at for the next four years.
Hey, we're not late, are we?
Not at all. We're glad you're here.
Now, everybody, outside.
Dinner is served.
All right.
So Ryan told me that you guys
actually went to Berkeley.
- Yes.
- Don't have him tell the Halloween story.
Let's just say we met
under unusual circumstances.
It's a beautiful place.
You should try and visit.
Sadie's gonna be coming up
to Berkeley with me.
When you go look at the school?
- No, to live.
- What?
I don't understand.
Did you apply to Berkeley?
No, no. It's just... My business
can kind of go anywhere...
...and Ryan's gonna be up there.
So we figured, why not?
So when did you decide this?
- This afternoon.
- It was my suggestion.
No, actually. I think I asked you.
Well, I think it's great.
Finding the right person...
...and then deciding to be with them.
That's what life's about, right?
- You know, I'm actually kind of tired.
- Sadie.
- I'm gonna go home.
- Oh, no, no.
Thank you both for dinner.
- Oh, wait.
- I'll walk you out.
You've been, like, so quiet tonight.
Is anything wrong?
- No, I'm fine.
- I can't believe...
...that Ryan and Sadie
are moving to Berkeley.
- That is so romantic.
- I don't know what Ryan's thinking.
- What are you talking about?
- He's 18. College should come first.
Not if you're with the one you think
you should be with. Forever be with.
Well, who really knows that at 18?
I do.
Oh, my God.
- You don't.
- Summer.
- That's not what I mean.
- You know what? I have to go.
If you're here about the sweatshirt party,
I'm not going.
So if you wanna yell, yell.
Actually, I was hoping
that we could just talk.
Marissa, I don't know what's going
on with you or what I did wrong...
Although, I'm sure we could come up
with a few things.
- but I just can't bear to see you
doing this to yourself.
Mom, this isn't about you.
I just keep trying to picture
myself at Berkeley and I can't.
That... That just means you're scared,
honey, and that's fine.
Look, Marissa,
I've been in that place before...
...where you lose faith in yourself.
But, honey, I believe in you
and you deserve this.
I don't know, Mom.
Marissa, please don't
give up on yourself.
You've no idea
how much I want this for you.
I'll think about it.
That's all I want.
Hey.
- Thanks, man.
- Sure.
- Did you talk to the parents?
- You know what? In hindsight...
...breaking the news to them that way?
Probably not a very good plan.
At least my dad didn't have an actual
heart attack at the table. That's a plus.
True. Anything happen after I left?
Summer and I got into a soul-crushing
fight about Brown.
- I'm sorry. Have you talked to her?
- No.
But even if I did, man, and she forgave
me, it's, like, then what? You know?
It's just... I don't know.
It's complicated.
Seth, I gotta ask.
Did you really get into Brown?
Did I get in...?
Ryan, now who's smoking pot?
Listen to me.
The only class that I've ever
gotten less than an A in was gym.
My essay on the Ioneliness
of being Superman...
...made Mrs. Rushfield cry.
So, you know, of course...
Oh, God, how did I not get in?
- Why are you lying about it?
- For Summer.
Think she's gonna notice
you're not there?
Well, she said if I didn't get in
and she did, she wouldn't go to Brown.
I'm not gonna let her do that.
- It's the opportunity of a lifetime.
- Well, I think that's up to her.
Sorry, man, I think
you gotta tell her the truth.
Hey, sorry I'm late.
No, it's fine. I just got here myself.
So Harbor's having this party tonight.
Everyone wears
their college sweatshirt.
- lf you wanna go.
- Sure. Yeah. That will be fun.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
And I'm sorry about last night.
That was not the way
it should've happened.
- Or maybe it was.
- What do you mean?
In the heat of the moment,
we decide to go to Berkeley together?
- Maybe we need to think about it.
- You don't want to?
Make sure we're doing this
for the right reasons.
We are.
Because we wanna stay together.
Right?
I just feel like a lot of people
go to college to find themselves.
And maybe you're
one of those people.
I wouldn't wanna get in the way.
I feel more myself with you...
...than anyone.
Those are some
pretty big words, mister.
I am going to Berkeley.
Seung Ho, you dog.
Oh, let me give you my credit card.
Summer. Come on, cheer up.
It's gonna be fine.
You and Seth will work it out.
I know, I just don't get it.
We had a dream.
The dream comes true.
Suddenly he's, like,
"What a crappy dream."
- I mean, who does that?
- Summer...
...getting a man is like capturing...
...a wily, silverback gorilla
in the Ugandan highlands.
You see, nature is telling that gorilla
to stay in the wild.
But both you and I know
that gorilla would be much happier...
...back in the zoo,
on a normal feeding schedule.
But sometimes he's just gotta roar
and beat his chest...
...before he'll let you shoot him
with a tranq.
So, what you're saying is, he's trying
to exert his gorilla independence?
Yes. That is exactly
what I'm saying, Summer.
Now come help me set up the bonfire.
Seung Ho...
- Yeah. What she said.
- Oh. Bye, guys.
- Hey.
- Got a sec?
- Yeah.
I was about to head to the bonfire.
I found this in the closet.
- It's a little worn, but...
- Wow. Wow, that's great, thanks.
And Kirsten was wondering
if maybe Sadie could use this.
Yeah.
Sorry about last night.
We both think she's a great girl.
She is. She is.
And, you know,
I know it seems kind of fast...
...but I really care about her.
- I'm sure you do.
It's funny.
Before you sprung your news...
...I was about to tell you I'd spoken
to Paul Glass at Berkeley.
He told me that he could
get you into my old dorm.
Of course, living with Sadie, you're
gonna have to find off-campus housing.
She's not gonna be
part of the meal plan.
So between food and rent
you're both gonna have to have jobs.
Now, Kirsten and I,
we're gonna cover your costs.
- But now with Sadie in the mix...
- I would never ask that.
I guess we just haven't had time
to really figure everything out.
No, of course not.
How could you?
It all happened so fast.
I ever tell you I almost
didn't make it to Berkeley?
I was driving across the country
that first summer.
I spent the night in this little town
1000 miles from home.
And I was terrified.
I'm not doing this
with Sadie because I'm scared.
Okay.
- Hey.
- Where are you? I'm ready to go.
I can't go to Baja tonight.
- All right.
- But call me when you get back.
Yeah, sure, whatever.
Sadie?
Glad you're here.
I've something huge to tell you.
- Yeah, so do I.
- Oh, okay, you wanna go first?
No, no, no, that's fine.
Go ahead.
I called the guy who sells
my jewelry in the Bay area.
It turns out he runs
an artists' co-op in Berkeley.
So I could live there.
Or we could live there. Together.
- Isn't that awesome?
- Yeah, that's amazing.
See, I told you I was psychic.
Okay, what was your news?
I talked to Sandy.
He and Kirsten are fine about us.
That's awesome.
Okay, we gotta leave
for your party, right?
Yeah.
Gonna be weird
that I'm not wearing a sweatshirt?
No, no, you'll be fine.
- Okay. I'm gonna go grab my purse.
- All right.
Summer?
Hey.
Hey. Where have you been?
Oh, I had to help Taylor
set up for the bonfire.
That girl can handle a chainsaw.
Hey, Seth hasn't called, has he?
No, I don't think so.
Everything okay with you guys?
Don't worry about it.
Look, Summer, I'm sorry
about the way I've been acting.
Just give me a chance.
Remember the boys made us watch that
movie about gay guys on the mountain?
- Lord of the Rings.
- Yeah.
And you remember that Gollum guy...
...how he got more evil
the closer he got to that fiery thing?
That's kind of how Seth is
about Brown.
Hey, you guys will work it out.
You love each other.
Thanks.
So no offense, but what
has been going on with you?
I don't know.
I keep trying to get back
to the life I remember, but I just...
I can't. It never seems to work.
You couldn't talk to me about this?
I've been your best friend
since the first grade.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I forgive you.
But you have to come with me
to the sweatshirt party as penance.
Oh, I would,
but I don't have a sweatshirt.
Oh, yeah.
What are we gonna do about that?
I bought this a few months ago.
Looks like somebody believed in you.
Hey.
You okay?
- Please, I just... I can't do this right now.
- Do what?
Be tested as wife-mother material
while I'm worried about my daughter.
I get it, okay? It's not
what you expected. I failed, fine.
But right now,
I need to think about Marissa.
Julie, I'm sorry if I...
If I made you feel
like you were being tested.
I was wrong.
And you've hardly failed. I think
Marissa's lucky to have you for a mom.
Hey. Guys, we're going to the party.
Bye, Mom. Bye, Dr. Roberts.
What I tell you?
- Hey.
- Hey, guys.
- Congratulations.
- Yeah, you too. Hi, Sadie.
Hey.
- Has anyone seen Cohen?
- Someone say my name?
Hey. You're not wearing
your sweatshirt.
You guys are all here.
The core four.
I need a picture. Go.
Go.
- Sorry. Do you mind?
- No, no, it's fine.
Everybody say,
"Higher earning potential."
- So cute.
- All right.
- Can I talk to you a second?
- Yeah.
I'm hungry. Do you want anything?
- No, I'm good.
- I will show you where the food is.
Hi, I'm Taylor. I used to be
total enemies with those guys.
But I'm pretty much
second-circle core now.
- Like your sweatshirt.
- Thanks. Yours isn't so bad either.
You doing okay?
Besides this thing choking me?
No, honestly I'm beginning to think
all of this is a bad idea.
- What's that?
- The sweatshirt. The party.
You know, even though
we're not together...
...I'm here if you ever wanna talk.
Thanks.
Means a lot.
So this is my friend Seung Ho.
And this is Sadie.
You could have told me
your answer on the phone.
Well, I wanted us to talk.
So you're not pulling out? Fine.
The DA's office
are gonna find who attacked Matt.
They're not gonna keep it quiet.
Look, I had nothing to do
with what happened to Matt.
I can't offer you
anything but my word.
Which doesn't carry weight with me.
- How about $ 700 million?
- Excuse me?
With the hospital going up, the city's
interested in revitalizing the entire area.
Parks, affordable housing, restaurants.
Head of the Appropriations Committee
is a friend.
- He's asked about your firm.
- Wow.
So now you're trying to bribe me?
The face of this city's
changing, Sandy.
You can be a part of that.
- Oh, my God. What...? Come inside.
- No, that's all right.
- Sandy here?
- No, he's out. What happened to you?
Some guys
broke into my apartment.
- Tell him I stopped by with a proposal.
- No, Matt. Wait.
Wait, did you call the police?
- They have to find out who did this.
- I know who.
What are you talking about?
Look, I really like Sandy.
But you just gotta...
You gotta get him to quit this.
Because pretty soon
it's gonna be too late.
- So are you gonna talk or what?
- Yeah.
It's just not easy.
Then I'll go.
Look, I get that you're a guy, okay?
And I know you have
that whole simian brain thing.
If we're gonna
go to college together...
...you can't keep
freaking out on me all the time.
- Yeah, Summer, that's just it.
- What is?
I'm not sure I wanna
go to Brown next year.
- What?
- I've just been thinking a lot about it.
And I'm not sure that Brown
is the right choice for me.
For you, I think it's great.
We applied to Brown
so that we could be together.
Yeah, I know. I just...
I guess I just changed my mind.
So we just suddenly
apply somewhere else?
No, I think you
should still go to Brown.
You should.
I'll just go somewhere else.
Do you really mean this?
I'm sorry. I think it's for the best.
Okay.
Well, I guess,
if this is how you feel, fine.
We're over.
Hey, been looking for you.
Yeah, Taylor went off
with that food guy.
I'm sure they were
talking dirty to each other in Korean.
Do you wanna leave?
Know it's kind of hard on you
not knowing anyone.
You're a nice guy, Ryan.
But I'm not coming
to Berkeley with you.
Don't you see? This is what
it would be like next year.
You'll have this other world
and I'll be pulling you away from it.
You won't get to experience college
the way you should.
- I'm not gonna do that to you.
- Sadie, come on.
You know I'm right.
I'm gonna go home.
I have to start packing in the morning.
- I'll drive you.
- I wanna walk.
And I'd rather say goodbye here.
Keep in touch, Ryan.
I'm gonna miss you.
Sandy.
What are you doing
sitting in the dark?
- Matt came by.
- What did he say? Because you know...
Promise me you're gonna
quit this thing.
Oh, honey. It's complicated.
- It's not.
- It's about more than the hospital.
Do you forget that I worked
at that company for 15 years...
...and I saw what happened
to my father?
I'm not gonna become your father.
But I can't just quit.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group