Previously on The O.C.:
If you ever wanna kick it or hang out
or something, I'm around.
Would you maybe wanna
go to prom with me?
All right.
Oh, my God.
- Let's go! Come on!
- Get in.
Don't be a little bitch.
Will you stop by the Newport Group?
There's a concept drawing
your father needs for his presentation.
There was a fire at the Newport Group.
They think Seth did it.
- Thirty-one cents a share. Also to recap
what I told you earlier coming out...
Hey, man. So how'd it go?
He denied everything. Stopped by,
picked up the drawing, left.
Well, that's a good thing.
Except you don't believe him.
I didn't know what to say.
- It was an accident. I swear.
- All right, so tell your dad.
Ordinarily, I'd believe him.
You know that.
In light of revelations about
his behavior, I don't know.
He's hiding something.
Dad, remember when I called you
the worst father ever?
Right after,
I swung by your place of work...
...I smoked a joint,
I forgot to put it out...
...and now your office
fits into an ashtray.
Security camera in the garage has him
as the last person to leave.
If he's telling the truth
and you accuse him of lying...
I've disappointed him enough already.
I don't need to give him any more ammo.
This is shaping up to be
a hell of a graduation.
I can't do hard time, Ryan.
Well, lying to Sandy Cohen,
what's harder than that?
I'm gonna go to the car, get my iPod,
listen to sad music for a change.
- Which car?
- My mom's.
You know what? I'll get it.
- It's okay. It's just in the garage.
- No, it's not.
I parked it on the street.
I've been meaning to move it. I'll get it.
Yo, yo, yo.
- What are you doing here?
- I bailed out and ran.
- Yeah? What about the cops?
- They got a good look at me.
I can't go home.
I gotta get out of town.
- Yeah, well, have a nice trip.
- I need your help! I need your help.
- I'm not gonna help you. I'm done.
- I need money.
- I've got graduation, family.
- You don't get it.
If I go down,
you are going down with me.
You know?
And not on some assault charge.
That was a $ 120,000 car we stole.
You stole.
Yeah, tell it to the cops.
Or your mom when she gets here.
I'm sure she'll be real proud.
I can't believe we're gonna be
on that stage in our cap and gowns.
Except for Seth,
who may be in an orange jumpsuit.
- Taylor!
- Sorry, Summer.
I'm just really nervous
about my valedictorian speech.
Well, it's not like Cohen got charged.
He didn't burn the entire building.
- He just damaged a couple of offices.
- It sounds like Ryan.
Sounds like the smoldering passion
we unleashed in Seth needed an outlet.
Think again, Taylor. I don't think
Cohen's the one that needs to get laid.
Have I told you about my after
after-prom party...
...with Seung Ho and Young Nam?
It was hot and spicy...
...and let's just say I had my very own
Korean barbecue.
I am so off kimchi.
- Marissa.
- Hey, Mom.
- Isn't it a bit early to be saving seats?
- I brought you something.
It's from Dad. A gift maybe.
He wanted you to have it for graduation.
I thought you'd want it right away.
- Yeah. Yeah, thanks.
- Okay.
- I'll see you in a bit. Bye, girls.
- Bye.
- That was nice of him to think of you.
- Yeah. I'm gonna...
- Dawn.
- Kirsten.
- Come on in.
- Oh, thank you. Thanks.
Wow, it seems like forever
since I was last here.
- Give me your bags.
- Thank you.
Of course, maybe
I was too drunk to remember.
Kidding. I'm doing good.
It seems that way.
- Hey, Mom.
- Graduate.
How you doing?
I'm glad you could make it.
- Well, Kaitlin, hello.
- Dr. Roberts.
- We weren't expecting you.
- Well, you know...
...since my grades went
from B's to A's...
...I was actually wondering
if you could change me A's to B's.
Well, Kaitlin,
I think that augmentation...
...is something to be discussed
with your mother when you're older.
Dude, I'm totally kidding.
I just love graduations.
I thought I might stop by.
- Kaitlin? Sweetie, hi. What...?
- Hi.
- Is everything okay?
- Totally.
I figured it was a safe bet, you know,
Dad wouldn't come here.
So I thought maybe
you'd have an extra seat.
Yeah, great, okay.
All right, well, I'm just gonna go to the
hot tub because I am so stressed out.
Finals, you know.
Okay.
That's very nice of her
to come home to support her sister.
Yeah, really nice.
- Father.
- Son.
I just wanted to make sure
you had the camera charged.
I do. Although you'll have to explain
to your nana the whole Ofoto concept.
- She's not good with the Internet.
- Sure.
And when they announce my name...
...could you not do that cheer
you did for me...
...when I won Capture the Flag
at Parents' Weekend?
Which cheer was that?
Check out my boy, Cohen
Can you believe how he's grown?
The competition, away he's blown
That's the one.
Please, don't do that ever.
Despite everything,
I'm still very proud of you.
Yeah. Damn it, why does Sandy Cohen
have to be the best father ever?
This is too hard.
Dad, I smoked a joint,
I forgot to put it out.
That's what started the fire.
I appreciate you coming clean.
- What I can't forgive is all the lying.
- Yeah, I know.
You smoke dope, you didn't tell me
the truth about Brown...
...and that you couldn't come to me.
Well, I was embarrassed.
What? We're your parents.
- We specialize in embarrassing you.
- Yeah, I know.
But I felt like
I couldn't really talk to you.
I tried a couple of times,
but you were busy with work...
...and I was afraid of upsetting Mom.
I understand that.
And I'm sorry.
- Well, we both screwed up.
- We're both usually so awesome.
Well, this is still very serious, isn't it?
Couple of hundred of thousands
of dollars in damages...
...offices that have to be rebuilt,
and I need to speak to the police.
Yeah. Yeah, I figured.
But you know what?
I don't want any of that
standing in the way of today.
Your mother and I have been looking
forward to this moment for forever.
No cheer.
No cheer. How about a hug?
Sure.
- Thanks, Dad.
- I love you, kid.
I can't say "I love you"
to another man.
But I have much affection
for you as well.
- Hey!
- Is everything okay?
- Can you sit?
Oh, okay.
- Well, how's your dad?
- Really good, actually.
He's not getting beat up
by anyone...
...and he's not in charge
of anyone's money.
That's good.
He's actually sailing
really nice boats for rich people.
- Sounds like fun.
- I know. That's what I thought.
Oh, you wanna, like, rent a yacht?
We totally should.
More like work on one.
See my dad's captain of a yacht
that's sailing to the Greek islands...
...and he says they need
extra crew members.
So he asked me if I wanted to go.
- You don't know how to sail boats.
- This would be more like, you know...
...peeling potatoes, washing dishes.
Oh, yes, much more
in your area of expertise.
But it's just for a year.
- What about college?
I'm not meant for college.
Not now, anyway.
You guys are all leaving.
I'm gonna be stuck here alone.
I need a new life. I need a change.
Well, scrubbing decks
would definitely be a change.
But it's kind of
the perfect graduation present.
And you know, this way
I can hang out with my dad.
He seems to have turned it around.
- When would you leave?
- Well, that's the only thing.
The boat's leaving Hawaii
in the middle of the week...
...so I'd have to fly out
tomorrow night.
My dad also kind of included
the plane ticket.
If you promise to sail up
to Rhode Island, I'm in.
- I love you.
- Me too.
Wherever you're going,
hopefully they have a Laundromat.
- What about the cops?
- I didn't see them.
- Maybe you're just being paranoid.
- No, no. I just...
I gotta get out of here.
I'm waiting for some cash.
You can make that money in no time.
If you want to go, go.
Unless it's not money
you're waiting for.
Get in. Let's go.
You're still thinking about Marissa,
aren't you?
I mean, you cheated on her and now
you can't stop thinking about her.
I asked you for clothes, okay,
not opinions.
God, you chicks
and your opinions, man.
So this girl's the best thing
that ever happened to you.
You freaked out, ruined it...
...and now you regret it.
- You could walk.
And now what? You think that you're
gonna convince her to go to Mexico?
This is it. Never gonna have
to step foot in this stupid school...
...this stupid student lounge again.
- Nostalgic already, huh?
Never gonna have to see any
of these shoe-peeing, shallow...
...water-polo playing...
Get out of my way, geek.
What is that? A dress?
It's a graduation gown.
You're wearing one too.
Queer admitted to wearing a gown.
Hey!
Hey, you guys look so cute.
Is everything okay at home?
Sandy and I got
a little man-boy love going.
- Hey.
Graduates, let's step outside
for the processional.
- Ryan, can I talk to you for a sec?
- Sure, yeah.
So, what do you think?
You think it's
the stupidest idea ever, right?
No, it sounds great.
It's what you need.
That means a lot to me.
You know, who would've thought
you'd be going to college?
And you'd be doing manual labor?
Well, everyone's doing exactly
what they need to.
Yeah.
Hey, this is gonna sound weird,
but can I drive you to the airport?
You're the first person I met here.
I'd kind of like to be
the last person to say goodbye.
You know, it's funny,
I was gonna ask you the same thing.
Hey!
Let's go graduate. Come on!
They say there's no one older
than a high school senior.
But no one younger
than a college freshman.
Well, I guess now we'll find out
as we begin our journey.
Daniel Aaron.
Ryan Atwood.
But as Cicero said:
"I hope the memory of our friendship
will be everlasting."
Seth Cohen.
All right, Sethy! All right!
- Marissa Cooper.
- Yeah!
And just because we're leaving Harbor,
does not mean that our learning is done.
We must learn as long as we may live.
Alex Petsovich.
Summer Roberts.
But if I can leave you all
with one final word of advice:
Don't let the bastards get you down.
Thank you.
And it has been my pleasure
to teach you, to watch you grow...
...and now enter the world.
Good luck.
It is my honor to present to you...
...the Harbor School class of 2006.
There's no such thing as a little racist.
- Okay.
- Come on. You're kidding!
Excuse me. Forgive me,
but I'm a very proud father...
...and I wanna say a few words.
I think I can speak for Kirsten
and the other parents here tonight...
...when I tell you
how thrilled we are...
...to share this wonderful
touchstone with you.
We love you guys.
I know the last few years
have been a roller coaster...
There's been tragedy and comedy...
...and first loves and broken hearts.
Family members lost and found.
It hasn't all been perfect,
but we're all family here.
So cheers.
Cheers.
His speech wasn't that moving.
No, it's just so sad, you know?
I mean, it's all over. No more Harbor...
...Atwood's going to Berkeley...
...Marissa's sailing around the world,
I'm going to Rhode Island.
- I'll be there.
- We don't know yet.
- We haven't heard form RISD.
- Well, whatever happens you know...
...we'll make it work.
- We will?
- Yeah, of course.
That's sweet.
Are you gonna do this all summer?
Hey, can I talk to you?
Yes, of course. Oh, I have
to give you your graduation gift.
Honey, what's wrong?
I kind of have some big news.
- Sweetie, I know.
- You know?
Your father called me last week.
Ran the idea by me,
wanted to know what I thought.
And what do you think?
I think that I will miss you terribly...
...and that if you really want to leave,
I need to let you go.
I knew about it too.
- You did?
Dad, he called me. Threw the idea
by me, asked my opinion...
...and also told me that you might need
another daughter to worry about.
So that's why I decided
to come home.
For good.
Oh, my God.
Cooper family hug. Come on.
- Mom, okay.
Oh, your gift. Here.
I don't know how much good
it'll be on a boat.
Oh, Mom, it's beautiful.
Maybe you'll get attacked by pirates.
You can barter it.
- So where are we going, huh?
- Just trust me.
I trust you but...
What?
You got me a car?
You got me a car?!
- Do you like it?
- I love it.
I love it. Are you kidding?
How did you...?
I've been saving up for a little while.
And Ron, my boyfriend, he knows
this guy who restores old cars...
...so that helped pay for the parts.
But I got the bow.
Car and bow. Amazing.
I don't know what to say.
Come here. Come here.
You wanna drive me home
in your new ride?
- Sure. Yeah.
- Okay. I'll get my purse.
Okay.
And here.
- Hi, guys.
- Hi.
I stopped by to say farewell.
You're leaving for the Sorbonne?
Not quite. Seung Ho and I decided to
spend the summer in his family's village.
We're diffusing land mines
in the DMZ.
That's a way to spend
your summer vacation.
What about the after-grad party?
As a gift to the class of 2006.
So my work here is done. It has been
a pleasure being second-circle core.
- I think you can join the inner circle.
- I can?
Oh, my God! The fab five.
- I'm so happy and so sad.
- I know. Me too.
This is awkward. I was sort of kidding
about the inner circle thing.
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
- Why are you calling me?
- Look, I'm really sorry, okay?
And I wanna make it up to you.
So I got a plan.
Oh, yeah? Well, I've got a plan too.
It's called never seeing you again.
If I don't get a chance to see you...
...then I'm gonna make life real bad
for your friend Ryan.
Don't threaten me or Ryan.
No, no, no. It's not a threat.
Ask him about the car that we stole.
- This is cool.
- Yeah, yeah. It's a gift from my mom.
Oh, yeah?
So it's not the one you stole.
Volchok called me.
- Look, the whole thing is...
- Complicated?
- What does he want?
- Money to get out of town.
- And you have this money?
- Not yet, but...
- Let me help you.
- It's all right. I got it.
Ryan, I brought Volchok on us.
It's only fair I help get rid of him.
Come on.
We're in this together, okay?
- One last time.
Thanks so much. I mean it.
- You're welcome.
- For everything.
- For the cab.
- Oh, God, no.
- Oh, come on.
- No, I got it.
- All right. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- Good to see you.
My turn.
Okay, I'm gonna try and say goodbye
without losing it.
Mom, why don't we just not say
goodbye. How about see you soon?
- See you soon.
- See you soon?
- See you soon, babe.
- All right.
- Love you.
- Love you too.
Hey, Seth.
- Good to see you again.
- Good to see you too.
It means a lot that you made it down.
I was being sincere.
- Okay, so...
- And thanks again for the car.
- You bet.
- Ryan got a car?
Really? I've been waiting three years
for a car.
I'm supposed to be the spoiled one.
- See you, kid.
- All right. Bye.
Hey. Marissa, easy on the bass.
Oh, Kaitlin. What are you doing?
Where's your sister?
Oh, Marissa went to go
rendezvous with Ryan.
And you thought you'd do
some renovations for her?
Well, yeah, she said
I could have her room.
I left some paint chips in the kitchen,
if you wanna go look.
Oh, is this going to be
a permanent picture?
Well, I worked really hard on that.
Seems like you and Marissa
are on good terms now.
Yeah, figures.
Just as she's about to set sail.
Pretty cool that you're letting her go.
Pretty cool that you came back
so she can leave.
Well, I don't love Marissa that much.
Just, all the older kids, they just
see me as Marissa's little sister.
They've graduated,
and now I can rule Harbor.
Hey. Your mom left, huh?
- It went well.
- Yeah, really well.
We get this out of the way,
we'll have nothing left to worry about.
- I don't know what I'll do with myself.
- Oh, I'm sure you'll figure it out.
Your mom won't be offended?
Well, I feel bad, but she did say
I could use it to barter with pirates.
- This seems to fit the bill.
- Yeah, definitely.
So, I'll navigate us to the pawn shop.
No, I'll go. Give me the directions.
- I thought we decided I was coming.
- I'm gonna handle this myself.
Okay, if you come, you stay in the car.
- You know what?
- What?
I'm really gonna miss you
bossing me around.
- You'll get used to it.
- Nope, nope.
- Yes.
- The rest of my life...
...I'm gonna be sad about it.
- Hey. Yeah.
- Oh, excuse me. Sorry.
If you came to haggle me
on the Ramirez plea, forget it.
- I'm up to my ass in unhappy ADAs.
- No, no, I'm just passing through.
What, did you come to
admire the wainscoting?
- This is my old office.
- You're Sandy Cohen?
My reputation precedes me?
- Self-righteous, arrogant, a little nutso?
- I see that it does.
- Jason Spitz.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. You're a legend.
Not to mention, I heard about your
post-victory karaoke bar performances.
Defend the poor, sing the classics.
I had a reputation and a routine.
You went to some
high-powered private firm?
Oh, for a minute. Then I went into
the private sector, into big business.
Why did you want to leave this dump?
Long hours, no pay.
Not to mention, the worst coffee
in Southern California.
Believe it or not, working here
were the best days of my life.
Yeah, right.
Grass is always greener.
- Coffee's always fresher.
- Sandy Cohen.
- Greg.
- Back at the PD's office, huh?
- Thanks for meeting on neutral ground.
- Ready to talk?
Yeah. Spitz.
- Nice meeting you.
- Hey, what are they asking for?
With a B and E with no priors?
You gotta be kidding.
Come in.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm in my third month on this book.
I'm hoping to have it finished by fall.
Hard to believe you're done with school.
You're not a kid anymore.
Let's be honest.
I was never very kid-like.
You always were an old soul.
- Mom, I want you to know...
- You don't have to apologize.
That fire was the best thing
that could have happened.
Well, then I did it on purpose.
Your father's talking to the lawyers,
and hopefully, you'll be free and clear.
Okay, good. Just have to wait and
hear from RISD.
Speaking of which, I think there's
some mail you might be interested in.
The pearls would have
looked good on you.
- Hey, funny kid. You got the money?
- Yup.
- Can use it to start over.
- Thanks, Ranger Rick.
- Save your speeches for the Boy Scouts.
- Ranger Rick. That hurts.
- Whatever, man, we're done.
- Not yet.
- I wanna talk.
- Send her a postcard.
- Marissa?
- Come on, let's go.
I just want to talk to you, okay?
Wait. Wait!
I just want to talk to you. Don't...
Wait!
Hey, honey.
So, I guess this is it, huh?
Yeah. I guess so.
Marissa, I just want you
to know that...
...everything I ever did,
good, bad, or otherwise...
...I did it for you.
So you could have
a better life than I had.
And I know I wasn't perfect.
I mean, the thing with Luke...
...and trying to frame Ryan...
...for attempted homicide...
- Mom.
I love you. Okay? Just know that.
Oh, sweetheart, that's all I wanted.
I love you too.
Besides, you know the strength it takes
to start over, to go out on my own?
That has to come from being
Julie Cooper's daughter.
- I am spirited, aren't I?
- Yeah.
Hey, Ryan and Seth are here.
All right. I guess I better go.
You gotta promise to keep things
interesting for Mom next year, okay?
- Oh, that won't be a problem.
- Wait.
One more Cooper family hug.
Do you know where this party is?
I think it's in the flower streets.
It could be in the number streets.
- I'll check the Evite.
- Can I ask a question?
Why are we going to
a lame Harbor party?
Yeah, it's Marissa's last night.
Well, we always wind up just
talking to each other.
- All right, so Bait Shop? Diner?
- Yeah.
Wait, I know somewhere
where we could go.
You're gonna have to follow
in your car.
It's a little something,
just because I love you.
- Flowers usually means bad news.
- Oh, ye of little faith.
No, I spoke to the DA,
came clean about the accident.
Since we're not gonna press charges,
the whole thing will blow over.
Then it's back to the Newport Group?
Business as usual?
Well, how about not?
Went back to my old office.
The place looked worse than ever.
The guy in there was beaten down,
exhausted.
It was a thing of beauty.
You wanna go back.
- Where are the kids?
- At some party.
And then Ryan's taking Marissa
to the airport.
So this is what it'll be like
all next year, huh?
Empty nest.
What does one do in an empty nest?
Oh, I have a few ideas.
- Okay, this looks familiar.
- Yeah, well, it shouldn't.
They rebuilt it completely
after you burned it down.
- Model home.
- Yup.
It's for sale and
it's completely deserted.
Ever wonder what life would
be like if Atwood never came?
- I never would have talked to Seth.
- Hell no, me either.
See, you owe me one, buddy.
Me? She'd still be dating the dude
who shaves his chest.
I can't believe it for a minute
I was actually interested in Atwood.
Wait, no offense.
- None taken.
- It was only until...
...you found out he was from Chino.
- Exactly.
You actually invited me to
Holly's beach house.
- Oh, my God.
- You said she invited me.
I'm not fairing well in
this trip down memory lane.
Well, as fun as it usually is
making fun of Seth...
...I think it's time I should go.
Here come the waterworks.
I can't believe
I'm saying goodbye to you.
I know.
- I love you so much.
- I love you too.
You're my best friend forever, okay?
If you hook up with
some hot, Greek shipping heir...
...I'm so your maid of honor.
- I know.
- See you.
- All right. See you later.
Guys, hug!
All right.
Bye. I'm gonna go get changed.
- All right. See you in a while.
- Okay.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
So weird talking about that night.
Last time we were here,
I was leaving, and now you are.
That night, did you ever think
we'd end up together?
You saying it's over?
You never know, right?
I'm sorry for all the craziness.
I wouldn't have done it
any differently.
Except maybe Oliver.
Me too.
Okay. Showing me a fun time,
stalking rich kids.
Maybe I should drive.
No.
- Whoa, what is this?
- Your graduation present.
Oh, my God, it's a 60-inch,
high-def flat screen.
Maybe.
- It's empty.
- No, it's not.
What is this?
"Dear Mr. Cohen, while your application
arrived too late for our fall semester...
...we are happy to announce that
your application has been approved."
- You got in!
- Yeah.
I start in January.
Let me just say again how sorry I am
for messing up the college thing...
...and lying to you and hurting you...
- Hey.
It's okay. Everything happened
the way it was supposed to.
Well, then I did it on purpose.
Okay, so, I'll go to Rhode Island and
I'll get the lay of the land.
Thanksgiving, Christmas,
then we'll be together.
- I think I might cry again.
- Tears of joy?
- Come on. Come into the box.
- This is so romantic.
What are we doing?
So are you okay?
Are you ready for this?
I have no idea.
I mean, what about you?
You're leaving the Cohens,
doing the college thing.
- I'm terrified.
- Me too.
So if you ever wanna talk or e-mail,
if they have that...
- I don't know how boats work...
- I'll find a way to stay in touch.
- What's that?
- This guy's following me. Go ahead!
Go ahead, pass.
What is he doing?
- What the hell?
- All right, hold on, hold on.
Oh, my God. It's him.
What are you doing?
- Okay, pull over.
- Where?
Stop! What the hell are you doing?
I'm gonna get him to pull the car over
so I can finally finish this.
- Get away, okay...
- Pull over!
Stop it!
Ryan! Look out!
Hold on!
Marissa.
Marissa. Marissa. Marissa.
Ryan. Ryan. Ryan.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm gonna go get help, okay?
- Gotta get help.
- Don't leave.
- Yeah, I gotta get help.
- No. No.
No. Stay.
Don't leave.
Okay.
Hold on. Hold on, okay? Okay?
Hold on, hold on.
You're gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Marissa.
Marissa!
No. No.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group