- Previously on The O.C.:
- I was with Johnny.
He went through something.
Something like I went through.
Even if Marissa was accused...
...she wouldn't go to jail.
- She also wouldn't be going to college.
- Look, can we talk?
- Before you say anything...
- I like you.
- Boy.
Seth, I mean, it's obvious
that we are soul mates.
What were you doing talking to her?
You were gonna scam me
into throwing a fake charity...
...and leave me to pick up
the pieces so you could skip town.
- You don't have any friends here.
- Wrong.
I have Kirsten.
And I won't do this to her.
Okay, picture me in college.
Big fish in a small pond
or small fish in a big pond?
I don't know. I never really
pictured you in a pond.
Me neither. Finding the right college
ought to be more soulful.
- You gotta fill it out. They're due today.
- What's due today?
- Hey. What's up?
- Hey.
- "Picking the Perfect College."
- I totally spaced that.
- Does anyone have an extra?
- There you go. Remember...
...meeting the college counselor today.
- That can be so stressful.
I can't even pick out my shoes,
let alone plan my life.
It's okay, it's only four years.
And according to this...
...it's the high point
of an otherwise miserable existence.
These kids look pretty happy.
Look, Coop, two girls looking in a
microscope and smiling. That could be us.
- Yeah, I don't think so.
- Coop, are you okay?
She's okay. She gets to leave Newport.
We all do. Think about this.
Soon we're gonna be living in real cities
with real, non-Botox, non-plastic people.
- Cohen, shut up.
- And weather.
How about a little weather
for a change, you know?
I'm not talking about
"it's cloudy with drizzle" weather.
I'm talking about snowstorm...
...seal-your-windows-with-duct-tape
weather.
- That's what I want.
- You know...
...it's getting late.
I'm gonna go.
- Are you all right?
- I'd get to wear wool.
- I'd get to wear a real wool sweater.
- Shut up.
- Sorry.
- Coop, what's wrong?
Nothing. I mean, this whole college thing,
it's great for you guys.
I'm just not gonna get to be
a part of it.
- What are you talking about?
- Look, I've done the research.
With my background, my history,
I don't have a chance of getting in.
I'm just not going to college,
that's all.
And there's a different approach.
- So, what's on the agenda today?
- Oh, it's packed.
- You don't wanna know.
- Sure I do.
Okay, conference call with the zoning
board, lunch with a couple of investors.
I've gotta oversee Ramsey's presentation
for tomorrow. You want me to go on?
I do. Believe it or not,
it sounds exciting.
What, more so than perfecting
the art of soufflé?
Speaking of, that one you made
last night, it was topnotch.
- Sandy, I'm going crazy.
- What?
It's the sifting, the kneading,
the measuring.
I can't take it.
I need to get out of the kitchen.
- Honey...
- It's not the cooking I hate. It's the quiet.
Well, we have to get used to
a quiet house.
I know. The boys started filling out
college forms today.
Well, look on the upside.
Seth will be right up the road at Berkeley.
Oh, I wouldn't be so sure.
Remember before Ryan came...
...Seth was dead set on going
to school on the East Coast.
- He wants out of California.
- That was years ago. He was a kid.
Sandy, Seth has never said
that he wants to go to Berkeley.
But he never said he didn't.
- Try not to go too stir-crazy.
- I'll try.
Marissa.
Brace yourself. You, my friend,
are in the presence of a celebrity.
- I am?
- Harper here is moments away...
...from being a surfing legend.
- I have to make it through this weekend.
Assuming that you shred it, you're gonna
be picked for PacWest's 2006 team.
Oh, well, that's great. Congratulations.
Cooper! A little enthusiasm, buddy,
this is a banner day for Dennis Childress.
It's a banner day for you?
Yeah. You might get to be the star,
but I get to be the entourage...
...which is a way better deal anyways.
We're talking free swag, VIP parties...
...crashing your world tour.
- I had no idea.
- Someone's gotta carry your surfboard.
- Well, I'll be there to watch you...
...in your moment of glory.
- You all right?
- You seem a little...
- I'm fine.
Promise. Look, I'll see you guys later.
- Something's wrong with her.
- Poor kid's probably starstruck.
Get used to it.
So we'll deal with grades
and boards later.
But for now I just wanna get a feel
for what you want.
- Where you imagine yourself.
- Somewhere cold.
- Or brisk. I would settle for brisk.
- I want 365 sun days.
And don't mean the day after Saturday.
Not someplace too big,
but not a lot of sports.
- Not a lot of big guys playing sports.
- I definitely wanna join a sorority.
Oh, but I don't wanna learn Greek.
- Where are you thinking?
- I don't know. I've only lived in California.
Hawaii. Arizona.
Boston, Connecticut, Vermont,
Maine, Rhode Island or New Hampshire.
- Do they have a college in Cabo?
- I'm not sure.
I guess this sounds like
I haven't given it a lot of thought.
But the truth of the matter is, I have.
I'll be the first in my family to graduate
from high school, let alone go to college.
So I mean, this whole...
It's a lot.
It's just so odd that Charlotte just up
and left without so much as a phone call.
Well, you know, her father called,
he said it was an emergency.
- That's all she needed to hear.
- She hasn't spoken to her father in years.
You know how it is with family.
One day...
...you're estranged,
next you're bugs in a rug.
But enough about Charlotte.
How are you?
It's just, I'm...
I'm losing my mind at home.
I feel like...
Julie, are you even listening to this?
Yes. Of course.
Is there something you need to tell me?
Excuse me.
Ms. Cooper, this is the last time I'm going
to warn you. I need that rent check.
Ten thousand, or this could get
very ugly.
Is everything okay?
I don't need any, thanks.
Hello, I don't need any steak knives.
You want some coffeecake?
- Hey, man.
- What's up?
You gonna visit me
in Providence next year?
- You're going to Rhode Island?
- Brown University.
The counselor said I had a very good shot
at getting in because I'm awesome.
- This your first choice?
- My only choice. It's liberal.
It's turtleneck weather. Most importantly,
it's 3000 miles away from here.
It's safe to say you're not applying
to Berkeley. Have you told your dad?
Sandy Cohen's a perceptive guy.
He'll figure it out.
Seth, you gotta tell him.
"Dad, I'm not applying to Berkeley.
Where'd you get a gun?
Why do you have this gun?"
That doesn't have a good ring to it.
It doesn't have a good ring. Fine.
I'll stop by after school
and break it to him.
- At least you're going to college.
- Unlike a lady friend of yours?
Yeah. I don't get it. I mean, it's...
She's always...
...wanted to go to college, you know?
- Well, you could talk to her.
- Use your powers of persuasion.
- I don't have any.
Ever since I got back to Harbor,
I don't have a leg to stand on.
Well, you need to find somebody
who does.
- You need to get yourself an ally.
- Why are you doing that?
I don't give a crap about this school.
I'm out of here.
Summer. Feel my forehead.
- What? Why?
- I have college fever.
- Don't you?
- Maybe.
What are the symptoms,
you become incredibly annoying?
Summer, cheer up.
You're just gonna love Arizona.
How do you know
that I'm applying there?
I work in the college counseling office.
- I do a lot of filing.
- Oh, and snooping.
Well, I did notice that you and Seth are
headed to opposite ends of the country.
- Well, we have different tastes.
- Yeah, apparently.
He wants to go to Brown,
and you wanna go someplace sunny...
...where kids drink till they vomit.
- Do you have a point?
I'm just sad for you, is all.
You know, I mean, the long-distance
thing can be such a grind.
What am I talking about? I'm sure you
and Seth have a whole plan worked out.
- A plan?
- Yeah.
Seth wouldn't just skedaddle
off to the East Coast...
...without so much as a thought
to your relationship, would he?
No one is skedaddling
anywhere yet, okay?
If you two haven't even
talked about this yet...
...my guess is there's
stormy weather ahead.
Intimacy, it's a tricky business.
Dad.
I didn't know
you'd be dropping by today.
Yeah, well, you know,
I had kind of a big day at school.
I know. You had a meeting
with your college counselor.
I'm dying to hear about it.
You know, she said
that I actually have a lot of options.
Well, of course you do.
And whatever you decide, I'll respect.
- Good.
- I'm just happy...
...you're considering Berkeley.
- You are. Well, aren't you?
- Yeah, considering?
- Sure.
- Great.
- Yeah.
- As long as it's still on the table...
...I'm happy.
Yes, Berkeley. Okay. Well, I'm glad
we got this all cleared up.
I'm gonna see you back at the house.
Oh, okay. All right. You got it.
- Dad, good talk.
- You... Yep.
Hey, Cheryl. Yeah, will you get Paul Glass
at Berkeley on the line for me?
Hey. Thanks for coming to get me.
Not a problem. Hey, whoa,
you wanna hang out for a minute?
- What, you just wanna enjoy the scenery?
- I wanted to talk to you about college.
- I told you, I'm not going.
- I know, you made up your mind.
You could talk to somebody.
Sorry, I sort of overheard what you were
talking about. What are you doing here?
I was trying to convince Marissa
to see your guidance counselor.
- Oh, Mitchell Davidson. He's a great guy.
- That's what I hear.
That's what you hear?
From who?
Oh, my God, you guys planned this,
didn't you?
Look, we just... We didn't want you
to do something you might regret.
So you conspired to get me here? To
lecture me on what to do with my life?
- It's not like that.
- I thought I could talk to you.
- I thought you were on my side.
- I'm on your side. Trust me.
Just leave me alone.
Oh, man, it'll be great to see you.
Yeah, that's right, tomorrow night.
I'll see you then. All right, Paul. Bye.
- Who's that?
- Our old friend Paul Glass.
Paul Glass,
as in Paul Glass from Berkeley?
Well, not from anymore. At.
He's working there now.
What? He called me. Besides, Seth came
by the office yesterday to talk colleges.
- He seems interested in Cal.
- As long as you don't pressure him.
No. No pressure.
A nudge. A father's allowed to nudge.
Nudging's allowed.
But any more than that...
...and I'll confiscate your
Cal sweatshirt.
- You wouldn't dare.
- Try me.
I gotta go. I'm gonna try
to make a Cardio Barre class.
Cardio Barre is crawling with Newpsies.
How bored are you?
I thought I'd go because Julie loves it.
And I thought it might cheer her up.
Lately she seems not herself.
- Is that a bad thing?
- I'm serious, Sandy.
- She's keeping something from me.
- When it comes to Julie...
...sometimes it's better not knowing.
- Yeah.
Yes. Yeah. Whatever. Let's go.
- You look very sporty.
- Thank you.
So how did it go with Marissa?
She accused me and Johnny
of ganging up on her.
- Oh, so it went well.
- I don't know. I guess it's to be expected.
We'll be splitting up.
It makes people tense.
Okay, but why focus on the negative?
This is a cause for celebration.
We get to finally leave Newport.
Not everybody sees that
as something to celebrate.
You wanna stay in Orange County?
Grow old playing golf,
chatting about the NASDAQ?
No, I'm just saying, you know,
maybe Newport isn't all evil.
Name one thing about Newport
that isn't evil.
- I will name you two.
- Cohen, hi. You, me, upstairs now.
Tell my parents I love them.
- How are you?
- Better, thanks.
- Look, I'm sorry about yesterday.
- I didn't mean to pressure you.
You know, I realized after,
you're probably just trying to help.
I made an appointment
with the college counselor.
- All right, you did?
- I mean, I can't promise anything...
...but I'm gonna try.
These are our college lists.
Do you see a difference?
Yeah, the font. Looks like you went
with the Times New Roman.
The schools, doofus.
None of them are the same.
None of them are
in the same time zone.
Okay, so you want West Coast,
I want East Coast. It's not a hip-hop war.
We are gonna be separated
by like a zillion-billion miles.
I was up all last night thinking
about that.
You were?
You haven't even given this
a second thought, have you?
- Summer, wait a second.
- No. Too late, Cohen.
Julie, you're leaving us already?
Well, you know, I was only
staying here temporarily.
I'm renovating my place
in Balboa Estates.
- Couldn't stand the racket.
- You live in the Balboa Estates...
...and you drive your own U-Haul?
- I'm just keeping it real.
Well, gotta go. See you around.
Three-F.
Mrs. Rushfield? Hi.
I wanted to read up on a school. Brown.
I know, it's a major reach.
But it doesn't hurt to look, right?
Of course. Let me just
get the file for you.
Thanks.
That's been checked out.
Here you go.
This is just what we were looking for.
Thank you, Taylor.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
- You're applying to Brown?
- Maybe.
I'm sure they'd just love to have you.
I hear the Ivies often recruit
from Fred Segal.
- I can get into Brown if I want to.
- Of course you can.
And on the off chance that you don't,
you can always come and visit.
Seth and I will show you around.
You have the grades. Lots of activities.
My guess is you'll be fine.
Except I'm not sure I wanna go.
I'm sorry, Marissa. I'm a little confused.
What are we doing here?
Does this have anything to do with
what happened to you over the summer?
I read about it in your file.
It's just, I'd have to explain it,
wouldn't I?
Well, on the applications, yes.
You will have to say
why you were expelled.
But if it means getting into college,
it seems like a small price to pay.
I've just spent all this time
trying to forget about it.
And, you know, if I had
to dredge it up again...
...I don't know if I could handle it.
- I get it.
That's a tough skeleton
to have in your closet.
But if you want my advice...
...write about it.
- See what comes out.
- That's exactly what I don't wanna do.
Marissa, you can't run away
from your past.
So before you let it ruin your future...
...you might try learning to live with it.
Oh, excuse me.
Could I get a little help over here?
- I ain't no bellman, lady.
- How charming.
- I take it you're my landlord?
- Yup.
I'm Gus. Welcome to the Taj Mahal.
- I can't believe I'm back here.
- You've lived here before?
I'm speaking figuratively.
Truth is, I moved out of
a place like this when I was 18.
I never thought I'd be back.
Yeah, well, when I was a kid, I wanted
to be wide receiver for the Chargers.
Sometimes life don't work out.
Everyone's here. Perfect.
A college buddy of mine, Paul Glass,
is in town.
I invited him over for dinner tonight.
And what brings Paul to town?
- Oh, something to do with work.
- Something for Berkeley?
- Your friend works at Berkeley?
- It's not what you think.
- You mean, an ambush?
- A resource.
- You guys might enjoy talking to him.
- Sounds like an ambush.
It's dinner. They have to eat.
- Hey, what are you guys doing here?
- PacWest Surf Contest.
- Today's the day, remember?
- Oh, you know, that's okay.
- I don't wanna be a downer.
- Why, what's up?
I tried to write this essay for school...
If I can't write the essay, you know,
I may as well forget about college.
So forget it. Come on tour with us.
- What?
- It's not a bad idea.
Travel the world,
give yourself some time to think.
- Are you serious?
- Look...
...maybe you just need
to take the pressure off.
You know, give yourself some time.
Why not do it in Fiji?
Just come to the contest today,
see what you think.
All right. Give me five minutes.
- Hey.
Was that Johnny and Dogboy
downstairs?
Yeah, Johnny's got this
big surf contest today.
I'm gonna go support him.
What about your essay?
You know, you can use my computer.
Just be gentle with it.
Yeah, that might be put off
for a while.
What are you talking about?
Hello.
- Hey, Julie. Glad you were free.
- Well, I can't stay long.
Did I tell you I'm moving?
It's such a hassle, but the
new place, it's beautiful.
Well, then I'll get right to it.
How'd you like to go
into business together?
- What?
- Well, think about it.
The magazine, the fundraiser.
- We make a good team.
- Kirsten, I don't need your charity.
Then why are you living in a trailer?
I'm sorry. I followed you yesterday.
Well, then I certainly hope
you're opening a detective agency.
It's not charity.
I'm going crazy doing nothing.
I need this.
Well...
...if you need it, I guess.
Just one thing. If we're partners, I need
to know what happened to Charlotte.
She can't be with her dad.
She hates her dad.
Oh, God, she didn't relapse, did she?
No, she couldn't,
because she's not an alcoholic.
What are you talking about?
Oh, Kirsten, I never wanted
to tell you this.
Charlotte went to rehab to find...
...a rich, vulnerable woman
she could exploit.
She's a con artist. I'm so sorry.
- But the fundraiser...
- A scam.
She was planning on taking
that money with her...
...but I stopped her at the last minute.
Oh, my God.
- You were in on it?
- Kirsten...
Kirsten, let me explain.
- What is it, Cohen?
- We need to talk.
I brought visual aids.
Boarding-school stuff?
My entire life, I have wanted to get
as far away from Newport as possible...
...and the only reason
I didn't is because...
...Ryan came and you
started talking to me...
...and I'm very glad I stayed,
but now I have to go.
Fine. I get it.
What's your plan for us?
E-mails? Phone calls?
- See each other once every two months?
- Or...
Or you could come with me.
No. You've always wanted to go east.
- I've always wanted to stay west.
- But don't you think...?
But what? My dreams are
not as important as yours?
Summer, I'm trying to make this work.
I feel like you're just writing us off.
You don't see Ryan
and Marissa giving up.
Not yet anyway.
What does that mean?
Get ready for our surfers
to hit the water.
We're about to start the competition.
And the first surfer in the water...
You don't have to go
trying to be a bitch here.
I'm telling you, there is no shame
in playing it safe. Tell him.
- Tell him what?
- Our lives. Costa Rica, Fiji, Hawaii.
- It all rides on today.
- Way to take the pressure off, man.
- Hey, you're gonna be great out there.
- Thanks.
I gotta get to the staging area.
See you guys later.
Bye.
So is this what next year's
gonna be like?
Just hanging out on the beach,
watching Johnny surf?
That and scoring hot foreign babes.
Great.
By the way,
I talked to some people that I know.
They think they can get you a job
as a label rep for the tour.
Yeah. So if you're serious about it,
let me know. I'll make it happen.
- Hi, man.
- Hi.
What's up? Everything all right?
You would think that
we could deal with next year...
...I don't know, next year. But no.
It's gotta screw up this year too.
Yeah. Marissa and I have
some of that too.
By the way, have you spoken
to her today?
No, I was on my way to see
if she wanted to grab lunch. Why?
Have a seat. I don't wanna
tell you this standing up.
- Thanks for coming, Taylor.
- Well, it was no problem at all, Summer.
I wanna talk about next year.
First, let me just say that where
I apply to college...
...is frankly none of your business.
And if some of those schools
happen to cross with Seth's, well...
Taylor. Shut up, okay?
You can have him. Go to Brown
or wherever you smart people go.
He's yours.
- This is a ploy, isn't it?
- No, it's life.
He's going to Rhode Island
and I'm going to Arizona.
I thought you would do
the long-distance thing.
And struggle along, break up at
Thanksgiving and hook up at Christmas.
Then break up in January
when we're both back at school?
- You could apply to a school near him.
- Imagine me on the East Coast.
I'd be like those animals ripped
from their habitat and put in the zoo.
My fur would get all mangy.
I'd throw dung at people. It'd be awful.
You know, I'm almost offended...
...that you think I would believe
that sort of idiotic lie.
You want the truth, Taylor?
What if he goes to college
and meets a bunch of really smart...
...and interesting girls and realizes that
that's who he's supposed to be with?
And that you're
just his high school girlfriend.
Cute, you're fun to be with...
...but doesn't want his kids
to have your DNA?
Yeah.
Maybe we should just end it,
you know.
- Summer.
- You be nice to him, okay?
- That was so awesome.
- Yeah, you were amazing.
- Well, I caught some good waves.
- And modest.
I'm gonna go see
when they're announcing the teams.
I'm gonna call my mom,
let her know how I did.
She's working up in San Jose
this weekend.
- Hey.
- Hey. Heard you were here.
- Yeah, Johnny was competing.
- What's going on?
Last night you say you wanna go
to college and now you're doing this?
Ryan, I tried to write the essay.
- I couldn't.
- Okay, I'll help you.
No, I really don't think you can.
Hey, Ryan. Thanks for coming, man.
- What's up?
- Did you tell Marissa to blow off college?
- Of course not.
- Then explain why you're here.
Dude, no offense, but maybe
you just don't understand...
...what she's going through.
- Is that what you think?
- No. Okay, I think it's complicated.
What's up, everybody?
Yeah!
We're about to announce
this year's PacWest Surf Team.
But before we do that, let's give it up
for those surfers out there, huh?
Johnny! Johnny!
- Look, can we talk about this later?
- You know what, you two talk. I'm done.
Johnny!
- No, wait.
- Johnny!
- I'll get him.
Ryan.
Johnny!
Our first member of this year's team
is Johnny Harper.
Johnny Harper, where are you?
Somebody call an ambulance!
- Were you all with Johnny Harper?
- Yeah.
- He's gonna be okay, right?
- Does he have a parent here?
His mom's flying in from San Jose.
How is he?
Lucky. The only real damage
is to his knee.
There's been a clean tear of the ACL,
some bone damage.
- He'll require surgery.
- When can he surf again?
I'm less worried about him surfing
than when he's gonna walk again.
He'll be awake in an hour
if you wanna see him.
I can't deal with this.
It's my fault. He was coming after me
when he got hit.
Ryan, let's not do this now, okay?
You should probably go.
Sandy will be wondering
where you are.
I think I should go find Chili.
I'll call you.
Kirsten, look who I found.
I heard this is where
Newport's newest culinary talent lives.
- Paul, it's good to see you.
- And you remember Seth.
Sure, last time I saw you,
you were in a Berkeley onesie.
- Thank you for that.
- Why don't you run upstairs, put it on.
- And... Oh, here's Ryan. Paul Glass.
- Nice to meet you.
Seth, grab the bread
and we can go outside.
Sure. After you.
- Paul...
- How's your friend?
He's gonna be okay. At least I hope.
What do you say
we get something to eat.
Yeah.
What is it with people
showing up with bags?
I brought you something.
Providence College?
It has good Catholic values...
...admission standards a little
more in your wheelhouse...
...and, best of all,
it's 20 minutes from Brown.
- Taylor...
- Look, Summer...
...who knows what will happen in the
future? But right now, Seth loves you.
And you're not even giving him
a chance.
Why are you doing this?
I figured Brown was
a little Vanity Fair for my taste.
- And now I'm considering the Sorbonne.
- No, I mean, why are you being so nice?
Well, pathetic as it sounds, you and Seth
are pretty much my best friends.
And, let's face it, I never really had
a shot with him.
- Taylor, we are your friends.
- Really?
Because I just got Kieslowski's
Decalogue on DVD.
And I don't know if you're
into Polish cinema...
...but maybe you could come over. We
could have a sleepover marathon and...
No. Sorry. Okay.
Keep in touch, Summer.
So anyway, it was Halloween...
...and I set Sandy up with a roommate
of this girl that I was dating.
I didn't have a costume, so when I went
to pick her up, I put a bag over my head.
I felt like I was dating
the Elephant Man.
You know, supposedly something
like 50 percent of people...
...meet their future mates in college.
You two have girlfriends?
Yes.
- I'm gonna get that.
- Sure.
- I don't know anymore.
- Yeah.
All right, so, what do you call
a black guy who flies a plane?
A pilot, you freaking racist.
It's the Cohens. We can 't come
to the phone, so leave us a message.
- Thanks.
- Kirsten, it's me.
Look, I know you probably
never wanna see me again.
I just wanted to say I'm sorry, again.
After everything you've done, you...
You deserve a better friend than me.
You know?
I'm sorry. I have to run.
- It was good to see you, Paul.
- It was great to see you too.
- Is everything okay?
- Oh, it's fine.
I'll be back in a half an hour.
- Oh, Summer.
- Hi.
- I was hoping that I could talk to Seth.
- Excuse me.
And then there were three.
Thank you. If I had to listen
to one more Berkeley anecdote...
Come here.
- How did this go?
- Okay.
- It's not that cold, but...
- Well, I wanna see...
...what we are going to look like
next year.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm coming with you.
Providence College.
- It's only 20 minutes from Brown.
- Are you serious?
Yeah. I wanna give us a shot,
you know.
And I can't do that from
across the country, so...
I don't believe this.
What made you change your mind?
Taylor.
She made me see that at Brown you're
gonna be surrounded by smart people.
It's gonna make you feel really stupid.
So you need someone...
...to make you feel smart again.
I mean, you want me to come
with you, right?
Do I want you to come with me?
Summer, you're my little snow angel.
My little rabbit.
- Hey.
How do you feel?
Like I just got hit by a car
and shot full of drugs.
- Look, this is all my fault.
- Yeah, I guess.
But kind of Ryan's, too,
for reacting the way he did.
And Chili for coming up with
the whole surf contest in the first place.
And the chick who hit me
didn't help things.
You know what?
No matter how you slice it,
my knee's still screwed up.
Well, what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna get the operation...
...do the rehab
and get back on my board.
Things happen, Marissa.
What else you gonna do? Give up?
Gus.
I told your wife, I don't swing.
Oh, Kirsten.
What...? What are you...?
Hey, Julie. I was wondering
if we could get together tomorrow...
...and discuss business ideas.
Wait, you... You still wanna
go into business with me?
I asked myself why you
didn't go through with the scam.
You could be living
in Charlotte's beautiful condo.
But you're here.
- Yeah, I guess I could.
- I know you did it for me.
Let me do this for you.
- Hey, Julie.
- I got a gun, Gus.
That's cool.
Yeah. Let's do it.
Don't. Don't. Don't go there.
Don't do that again.
You did that one time.
- No more stories from me.
- Yeah, that's a good thing.
- Because I think we're about to lose Ryan.
- No, no, no. It's all great. I just...
I don't know if I'm ready
for the whole college thing.
How's that?
I look around, I mean,
I got a home, family.
Part of me feels like
I finally got it together.
I'm not sure I'm ready to leave that.
You know, going away to college
is not goodbye.
I know.
What happens on vacations,
do I stay in the pool house?
No matter where you go,
this will always be your home.
Hey, Dad, can I talk to you
inside for a second?
Yeah.
- Excuse me a minute.
- Yeah.
So tell me, in this leaving equation...
...is there a serious-girlfriend component?
Oh, boy.
Hey, sorry for ducking out earlier.
Yeah, you missed my story about
playing Nanki-Poo in The Mikado.
Oh, yeah, that's too... Too bad.
Listen...
...I don't want you
to get upset, okay?
But...
...I'm not going to Berkeley.
I wanna go to Brown.
I'm not upset. Brown's a great school.
I wish you would've told me.
Dad, I've been trying to for years.
You didn't wanna hear it.
It's that I want you to have
the same amazing experience that I had.
That is exactly why I need to go east.
It's exactly what you did.
You left everything behind,
and you forged your own path.
I need to do that.
You're already doing it.
Come here.
- Hey, Seth's applying to Brown.
- I think it's great.
Listen, Summer's upstairs
ordering things from L.L. Bean...
...so I have to...
- Hurry. Hurry.
So...
...it seems that we're gonna be
empty nesters.
True.
What do you think about getting
an apartment in Providence?
Providence.
She's a pretty important part
of your life.
Yeah.
You know, ever since I got here,
she's always accepted me for who I am.
I don't know if I can leave that.
Ryan.
- Excuse me.
- Sure.
- How's Johnny?
- He's okay.
He's amazing, actually.
You know, he says
he's gonna surf again.
I feel responsible.
Ryan, it's not your fault...
...or mine. It just happened.
We can't keep blaming ourselves
for everything.
And how do we do that?
Well, for starters,
I'm applying to college.
All right.
You know, as awful
as the shooting was...
...if I don't let it go,
it's just gonna ruin my life.
Both our lives.
- The essay?
- I'll say what happened.
You know, that I saved the life
of someone I love.
A college will either accept that or not.
I can't keep hiding from it.
It made me who I am.
There is no going back.
With everything we've been through
the past two years...
...and the fact that we're still here...
...it really makes me think
there's nothing we can't handle.
Sorry to interrupt.
I wanted to say good night.
I felt kind of weird sitting alone, and
I couldn't help overhearing.
I'm hoping that you both
will apply to Berkeley.
I think it'd be a good fit.
If you have any questions,
just give me a call.
- You guys dressed?
- Yeah.
Anybody hungry?
This one's gotta pack on some pounds
for the cold weather.
- Says Mr. Toothpick.
- Hey, Providence College?
- Wow, we're thinking about Berkeley.
- So we'll be in Northern California...
...you'll be in Rhode Island.
You and Seth will have to do the
long-distance thing. You better not cheat.
Well, it's college. Things happen.
- Are you questioning your sexuality?
- No.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group