If you haven 't watched The O.C.,
here's what you've missed.
- I'm not interested in Marissa, all right?
- Then prove it.
Just come down, Johnny, please?
- You're glad he's gone?
- Not gonna answer that.
- What do you want?
- You.
Late night last night?
Boy likes girl. Girl has access
to influential father.
Boy's boss needs to close a deal.
- I'm in.
- You're in?
Caleb would've been proud.
- Where's the line?
- I'm not worried about you...
...knowing where the line is.
Are you a friend of Johnny's?
I'm his cousin, Sadie.
I was wondering if I could
give you a hand.
We got unfinished business.
Come on.
We should take our pants off.
You wouldn't have come
if you didn't want to see me.
- Go away.
- What the hell's he doing here?
Some might say as a teenage girl
growing up in Orange County...
... everything is ours for the taking.
But sooner or later,
we have to choose.
- Hey.
- You don 't choose to choose...
...choosing chooses you.
- Okay, what's that?
And when we choose,
we're left with our ch...
Oh, my God, you're listening
to your own voice.
All the TV shows I watch,
all these women have voiceovers.
They gave one to April on The Valley.
Where most of these voiceovers
don't make much sense...
...they make your life
seem dramatic and meaningful.
Our lives need to be
more dramatic?
No, not yours.
It's our senior year, second semester.
I think things should be more poignant.
- We don't have much time.
- You're right about that.
We don't have much time.
We're late, come on.
- Seth and Ryan are waiting.
- I'll be right there.
No one said choosing would be easy.
But not choosing is even less easy.
Or something.
- So where is Atwood, anyway?
- I don't know, and I don't care.
Yeah, I haven't seen him for a while.
Yeah, but look at it this way:
The hot tub's roomier.
Plus, two girls and a guy.
I like those odds.
You know what? You're right, Cohen.
- Hot tub, house to ourselves...
- I have been kind of Ionely.
And I have kissed a girl before.
And I've always wanted to.
You guys are kidding.
You know what they say, Cohen.
- What happens in the hot tub...
- Stays in the hot tub.
Yeah, you guys are really committed
to this joke. I commend you.
- Who's joking?
- Yeah.
- Cohen, what's the matter?
- Nothing.
- You're not man enough for two girls?
- I gotta call Ryan.
- Be gentle, that pipe is old.
- lf you're such an expert...
...why'd you ask for my help?
- I didn't ask for your help.
- I almost got it. Almost...
- Wait, hold on.
- Not so hard, you're gonna break it.
- It's not gonna break.
- Don't twist so hard. Turn it off!
- I got it.
- Thank you for the help.
- Here's a towel.
Anytime, at your service.
You're too dry, though.
- That's mean.
- You okay?
Fine.
I'll get that. And some towels.
Hey, man.
Is this the Harper residence?
We've got some questions, ma'am.
- You were supposed to be here.
- I know, sorry.
We just finished painting
and the sink clogged.
I've got girls in bikinis
trying to seduce me.
Which sounds awesome.
But I'm scared.
- I'm wet and I'm cold, Ryan.
- Okay, all right. I'll be right there.
- Just gotta towel off.
- Why do you need to towel off?
- You should probably go.
- What are they doing here?
They have some questions
about Johnny.
- What kind of questions?
- They're saying his death...
...might not have been an accident.
- No. I saw what happened. I was there.
I know. So do they.
Just go home. I got this.
- You sure?
- Go.
Yeah. Okay. All right.
I was thinking of having a party.
Something small.
- Maybe you, me, Seth, Ryan...
- That's not a party.
That's a double date.
A double date?
Coop, that's a great idea.
- Why don't we do it this weekend?
- Can we just play it by ear?
Why? So you can come up with some
last-minute excuse to get out of it?
Hey, it wasn't me who didn't show
last night. That was Ryan.
That's true. Did you guys
come up with some sort of system?
Look, I'll call him later. We'll figure out
a time to sit down and talk. Okay?
I love our pep talks. So affirming.
Wish I could have them with my dad.
- What's wrong with your dad?
- He's been working hellacious hours...
...ever since Stepmonster left.
He was asleep when I left
this morning.
- Maybe he's just busy.
- That's the point.
He's been burying himself in his work
to avoid staring into the emotional void.
- I'm sure he'll snap out of it.
- Yeah, so will you and Ryan.
What did I tell you? I'll be outside.
Hello?
Yeah, this is.
No, Aunt Gwen,
you just stay up there with my mom.
I don't know, but I'll figure it out.
I love what you've done there. Probably
get a cable show to pay for that.
HGTV's Extremely Sad
Home Makeovers.
No one's taking your house.
I promise.
- Okay. I love you. Bye.
- Hey.
I just thought I'd stop by,
see how everything's going.
The bank's gonna foreclose
on my aunt's mortgage.
And until the cops figure out
how Johnny died...
...there's no insurance money
from his accident.
So now the insurance
company's frozen the claim.
- He fell off a cliff.
- Do they think Ryan pushed him?
Guess they've recovered
new evidence.
- What evidence?
- I don't know. They wouldn't say.
Don't worry,
it's not you they're interested in.
They asked questions
about Marissa.
- And?
- And I said they should talk to her.
As you can tell, we are over
our advertising budget for the month.
Maybe we can put something on
OCNewMatch. com.
We could call our Newport publisher,
see if he could put NewMatch...
...in one of his high-end
lifestyle magazines.
You want some more coffee?
Julie, are you even listening to me?
Yes, of course I'm listening. You've been
talking ever since I got here.
What's going on?
You've been zombie-like all week.
Another late one with Doc Roberts.
In the back of his Maserati, no less.
I didn't know Maseratis
had back seats.
Maybe you two should stop
sneaking around and go public.
I don't disagree,
and neither does my chiropractor.
But, you know, with the death
of Marissa's friend...
...and Summer being left
motherless for the second time...
...we just don't wanna make
any unnecessary waves.
- Hello?
- Good morning, gorgeous.
- How'd you sleep?
- All by my Ionesome.
We've gotta to do something
about that.
Just found a note from Summer.
I think she's getting suspicious.
I hate keeping secrets from the kids.
Yes, well, maybe we should
discuss that.
- Covertly, of course.
- How about tomorrow night?
I know the perfect hideaway.
Well, I like the sound of that.
Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
Oh, Kiks, I'm so tired.
I could really use a quick catnap.
Wake me in 20.
Well, I pulled the permits.
Unfortunately, I think I left them at...
Scratch that. I'll fax them from here.
You need to start tying
a string around your finger.
Do I?
Yesterday it was your wallet,
Monday it was your BlackBerry.
Well, I find you very distracting
in the morning.
And in the afternoon, late at night.
Does that mean
you're coming over tonight?
Matt, we are way out of time
with the hospital. You've gotta talk to...
- Maya. What a nice surprise.
- Morning, Sandy. You're looking well.
You too. I'm sorry to interrupt.
- Buzz me when you're free.
- Oh, he's free now.
Nobody respects company time
like a company girl.
- Thank you for...
- Yeah, I'll have my assistant...
...pick up some string
for those fingers.
- Say hello to Kirsten for me.
- You bet.
Already the early office drop-in.
You two are hitting it off.
- Yeah. She is really great.
- I'm glad to hear it.
If we don't get that proposal
to Dr. Griffin and the board by Monday...
...we're dead in the water.
Yeah, I know.
But the way things are
between Maya and I...
...I just can't ask her
to get us a meeting with her dad.
I don't do this right,
it could backfire.
You need to come through.
The clock is ticking.
Yeah, can you just tell him
that his daughter called again?
Thanks. Oy.
- As in "vey"?
- Attagirl.
Apparently my dad's
in "surgery" all day.
How many calf implants does it take
to fill a hole in the human heart?
- Hi, friends.
- Hey.
So, what are we talking about?
Summer's worried her dad's burying
his pain and Ioneliness in work.
- That's so sad.
- Yeah.
What's the plan?
- You guys don't have a plan?
- Do you?
Off the top of my head?
Get him into therapy to explore the root
of why he can't express himself...
...in a lasting partnership.
Or, find him a hot date,
take his mind off being utterly alone.
Does he still have the things
on his thing?
- A little penicillin cleared that right up.
- Great.
It looks fantastic.
Good. That's good.
You know, I would offer up my mom,
but she's not a big second-chancer.
What about getting Seth's mom
to take your dad as a client?
- That's not a bad idea.
- But the last person...
...that should be choosing my dad's
next great love is my dad.
But me, on the other hand...
...I can make a list of all the stuff
he should be looking for...
...and pick the girl myself.
- That's good.
I'll start brainstorming ideas
for fun things...
...for old people to do on a first date.
I've been trying to find you.
Police talk to you?
Yeah, they call you too? They must
wanna talk to everyone who was there.
No. Actually, Sadie said
they only asked her about you.
Me?
Yeah. You want me to go with you?
No. No, it's okay.
Whatever it is, I don't wanna
drag you into it.
- Look, I'm...
- So how's it...?
Look, I know I haven't
been around much lately.
It's okay. You're helping Gwen.
That's important.
Yeah, actually I need to go
over there after school...
...but maybe we could
get together later?
- Talk.
- Yeah, of course.
I'll call you. Tell Sadie I say hi.
You know, you might wanna see Sandy
about the police.
I'm sure it's nothing. Thanks.
Hey.
So I figured we'd start
by patching up the wall.
Which is really more fun
than it sounds.
No, it's not.
You look like you're on a mission.
That's because I am.
- Everything okay?
- It will be.
Once I get done smacking
that stupid bastard around.
- Oh, who's getting smacked around?
- My uncle.
- Johnny's dad?
- lf you wanna call him that.
The patching will have to wait
until after I get back from Brea.
Yeah. Sure. You want a ride?
- I've got a car.
- You're gonna need some company.
I kind of already have some.
- Hey, what's up. You ready to roll?
- What is this guy doing here?
That's funny because I was about
to ask her the same thing about you.
- You've always been kind of slow.
- But I'm quick at kicking your ass.
Running away is more
how I remember it.
Really? Well...
...I'd love to jump back in the ring.
- Too much testosterone.
Volchok's dad used to be
buddies with Jack Harper.
- He knows where we can find him.
- He can give us the address.
Well, I'm kind of looking forward
to a road trip.
- You know, catching up?
- We'll send you a postcard.
Ryan, don't.
Why don't you just
write down the address?
Whatever. Any chance to avoid
Johnny's dad sounds good to me.
- I hate that guy.
- Thanks. I'll send him your best.
So if you're gonna be with her, does that
mean your girlfriend's all alone?
What goes around comes around.
Wanna tell me the deal
with you and Volchok?
I was visiting Johnny one summer.
And I was younger. Stupid.
It didn't work out.
Hard to believe.
You wanna take the 5
to the 57?
It's faster.
Right, because you know so much
about driving inland.
When was the last time
your parents' $80,000 SUV...
...was east of South Coast Plaza?
The Cohens are my guardians,
not my parents.
Grew up in Chino. Dad's in prison.
My mom couldn't make it work.
I just knew there was something
about you that didn't quite fit in.
In a good way.
I wonder if your dad
knows my Uncle Jack.
- Why would he?
- From prison.
He's been in a couple times.
I'd put him back if I could.
He owes my aunt years of child support.
He's her last hope.
Now she needs that money.
- So you think you can turn him?
- lf I don't try, who will?
What would you feel about dinner?
Sure, whatever you feel like.
Tomorrow night.
Me, you, Kirsten and Maya.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Have you been locked in your office
all day planning our social lives?
Let me ask Maya about the proposal.
- Sandy, I said I'd do it.
- No, it's better this way.
I'll bring it up. It'll be easier.
Marissa. Come on in.
I went by the house.
Kirsten told me you were here.
Oh, the door's always open, honey.
You remember Matt.
I think I need some legal advice.
The cops wanna talk to me
about Johnny.
They don't seem to think
it was an accident.
Did they suspect
Ryan's to blame for this?
No, I actually think...
...they're trying to blame me.
- You?
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm supposed to be at the station...
...giving them a statement.
I'll call and get that rescheduled.
We'll do it at the house.
If you don't mind,
I'd kind of like to keep Ryan out of this.
Of course.
- Feel free to use my place.
- Thanks, Matt.
But before that,
we'll go over what you're gonna say.
And you're gonna have to tell me
everything you know about Johnny...
...and you and that night.
Hey, Summer. I didn't know
you were joining us tonight.
Seth just went to pick up dinner.
Actually, I came to see you guys.
Oh, is everything okay?
Well, no, not really.
It's my dad. He needs, like, serious
and immediate help with his love life.
Really? What makes you say that?
I've never seen him so miserable.
He's barely ever at home.
He's either at work, which is so lame...
...or at the gym,
which is weird.
He's already dropped like 20 pounds.
Well, maybe he's getting into shape
in case he meets that special someone.
- Or maybe he's already met her.
- Oh, please don't say that.
My dad has disastrous taste in women.
If I don't step in, he'll wind up
with the first money-grubbing slutbag...
...that gets into the back seat
of his Maserati.
Julie, would you like to take this?
Actually, all I need is,
like, a list of candidates...
...because I did all the work myself.
They're all blond.
Sharon Stone in Basic Instinct?
It's the look my dad goes for.
And this is a list of non-negotiable
qualifications that she must possess.
"Mental stability.
Crossword enthusiast. Love horses."
"Must have own money.
Plastic-surgery free. Fluent in Italian."
This doesn't leave
much wiggle room, Summer.
It's just that my dad didn't have much
in common with his first two wives...
...and they left,
so it's just not fair to him or to me.
- Okay, well, we'll see what we can do.
- Really?
Thank you guys so much.
This means so much to me.
I'm gonna go see if my dad's
actually coming home tonight.
Bye.
- What are you gonna do, Julie?
- I don't know.
Is it possible I'm not enough
woman for him?
Do I really need to be all these things?
Julie, you're never gonna be
any of these things.
Okay, blond, maybe.
Fluent in Italian? Not so much.
You have to tell Summer the truth.
The guy really keeps up
on his yard work.
Yeah, Uncle Jack
is a really good neighbor.
Hi, we're looking for Jack Harper.
But you're not him.
He in some kind of trouble?
No. No trouble.
No. Good news, actually.
Too bad. I fricking hate that guy.
He owes someone money
and we're trying to collect.
He moved to Indio. That's all I know.
A phone number? Forwarding address?
No one here was
looking to keep in touch.
Okay. Thank you for your help.
You find Jack Harper,
you won't be thanking me.
So we're going to Indio.
Ryan, Indio's like two hours
into the desert.
We won't even be able
to start looking until morning.
Yeah, so we spend the night.
I think you might be missed.
I will make some calls.
- You don't have to do this.
- I want to.
Good evening.
Julie?
Buena sera, doctor.
What's a 13-letter word for secretive?
Surreptitious.
I don't think you can smoke here.
Julie, what is all this?
Oh, do you like it?
Because tonight is all about you.
I didn't know you do crosswords.
No, Mom, they're out of bibimbap.
Yes, all gone.
How about bulgogi?
Two orders?
Mom, next time
let me call in the order.
I know, that's why they call it
"Korean barbecue."
Okay. Goodbye.
So, what'll it be?
Blond, Italian, philanthropist?
I can be all of them.
Tell me, in your wildest dreams, what
would you do with a willing woman?
Okay.
So did you guys make plans
to talk or what?
Yeah. We agreed we'd talk,
we just didn't pick a time or a place.
Coop, usually a time and place...
...are crucial aspects to any plan.
- I know.
You and Ryan
have been getting along okay.
That's because
we haven't been talking.
Just call him.
- Do it.
- Fine. Bye.
- You play poker?
- What's the pot?
Well, I got like 20 bucks on me.
That's not gonna do it.
Then what?
You ever play strip poker?
Yes, I have played strip poker.
I'm wearing more clothes
than you are, though.
Yes, but I think
I'm a way better player.
You think so?
- Yeah. Just deal.
- Okay.
Loser sleeps on the floor.
Which basically means
you're on the floor.
Sure, sure.
Your bookie?
No, just Seth.
I'll call him in the morning.
Hey, it's Ryan. Leave a message.
- Room service.
- What's on the menu?
Black coffee and jelly doughnuts,
courtesy of the Circle K.
- Poolside service.
- I gotta remember this place.
So I was flipping through
the yellow pages and I found this.
- Think that's him?
- When we were kids, he was Big H...
...and Johnny was Little H,
so it's gotta be.
All right. I'm gonna shower,
wake myself up.
I didn't actually sleep so well
last night.
If you wanna sleep in the bed,
don't bluff with a pair.
Did you call Seth back?
- Dude, where are you?
- Indio. How much trouble am I in?
Mom and Dad think
you're helping inner-city kids...
...paint a overpass mural.
I'm rolling around in your bed
so it looks slept in.
- You'd do that anyway.
- So? How about a little gratitude?
You're right, I owe you,
but it's for a good cause.
You wanna clue me in on
what that cause is?
Less you know, the better.
Just keep doing what you're doing.
Except the bed thing.
That's just creepy.
- Seth, what are you doing?
- Ryan's painting a mural.
- What are you doing?
- How did you get in?
Never mind all that,
this is an emergency.
Summer's gonna majorly wig when
she finds out who her dad is dating.
Yeah, well, whoever it is,
staying out of it.
Julie Cooper. I caught them
having an illicit liaison...
...and the way they were talking
was perverted.
Wait, perverted how?
- Just what are we gonna tell Summer?
- What's who gonna tell Summer?
- Do I need to call a locksmith?
- What are you doing here, T-bag?
You know what, she's your girlfriend,
you should tell her.
Oh, please, not you two again?
Oh, no. No, no, no,
I'm totally over that weirdness. No.
Your dad and Julie Cooper
are doing it.
It's a shock. I wouldn't have
believed it myself...
...if I hadn't seen it with my own eyes.
It was all very mid '90s, overwrought...
...thriller, a sort of a Verhoeven shape.
- It's like a Sharon Stone movie.
- Oh, my God.
- Okay, but hold on.
This kind of broad reveal
requires independent confirmation.
Fine. You can see for yourself.
I happen to know
where their next tryst is going to be.
Keep your eye on the ball and...
...swing through it.
Okay?
Right? Your turn, come on.
Neil, I am not very athletic.
Spread your feet a little bit. Okay.
Let the grip rest gently in your hand.
You keep your eye on the ball, and you're
gonna swing through the ball. Okay?
- Raise the club gently...
- Now, if I break a nail...
...your next fantasy better involve
a French manicure.
Are we gonna do this now?
- Look at the ball.
- Okay. Okay. Yes.
There's no way.
This is my dad's sacred place.
He would not bring a woman here.
Maybe he doesn't think of Julie
as an actual woman, just a golf buddy.
Who he makes out with.
I cannot believe this.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Let's go!
- That's so horrible.
- I think they're cute.
Jack Harper in?
He's out on a job.
- lf you need a bond, I can take care of it.
- No, we don't need a bond.
We're looking for him.
When do you expect him back?
- Who wants to know?
- Well, his dead son, for starters.
- Get out of here.
- We don't mind waiting.
I got authority to protect
this property with lethal force.
You know what that means?
- Means we'll be out in the car.
- Yeah.
Hey, Marissa! Come up here!
You gotta see this view!
Was your friend Johnny a big drinker?
- No.
- But he was drinking that night.
- Any idea why?
- You're asking her to speculate.
Did anything happen
to Johnny that day?
Anything that might've made him
want to drink? A fight with a friend...
As bad as I wanna be with you.
I love you.
And I think you love me too.
- Yes or no.
- Excuse me, detective...
...we need a minute alone.
- " What we're doing here...
... isn 't only unfair to you, it's unfair to..."
This next part's burned here.
Ryan. To Ryan.
- I'm with you.
- But that's not the whole story, is it?
Recovered from a fire pit
on the beach.
"I'm not in love with you,
and I never will be."
May I see that?
Come on, come up!
Seems like Johnny
took the news pretty hard.
I can 't imagine that it made
your boyfriend very happy either.
Ryan didn't even know this existed.
He has nothing to do with this.
- Let him ask his question.
- No. I wanna tell him.
Ryan didn't push him.
And Johnny didn 't commit suicide.
If you really wanna know
what happened, he slipped.
Johnny!
No, thanks.
You know, Johnny and I
used to be friends.
Yeah, he and Chili
used to follow me and the guys around...
...trying to get us to teach them
how to surf.
Yeah, well, what happened?
He got better than me.
And I didn't like that.
Your secret's safe with me.
- I should go.
- Look...
...if you ever wanna kick it or hang out
or something, I'm around.
- I'm not interested.
- You sure about that?
I can keep a secret too.
How did it go?
Well, there were a few surprises.
There doesn't seem to be evidence
pointing to suicide or foul play...
...so if that's the case,
they'll have to rule it an accident.
I'm glad.
Honey, you look exhausted.
Well, thank you.
You look beautiful, as always.
I was up most of the night
finishing this hospital proposal.
Maybe we should reschedule
with Matt and Maya for next weekend.
Oh, I wish we could,
but it would defeat the whole purpose.
- I thought the purpose was dinner.
- Well, dinner...
...and Maya's our chance at
a second hearing at the hospital.
The way they've been getting along,
I think he really likes her.
I thought you abandoned
this idea weeks ago.
Why would we abandon it?
She's not naive. She might wanna help.
She might wanna rethink the relationship
if it doesn't go well. I know I would.
Oh, honey, we're all adults here.
And this project has the potential
to do an awful lot of good.
Stakeouts are so much cooler
in movies.
That's because they cut to the part
where the guy shows up.
That's him. Come on.
Jack Harper?
- Who's asking?
- Friend of your son's.
- I don't have a son.
- I know, Uncle Jack.
That's why we're here.
Sadie?
Aunt Gwen says thanks for the card.
- I didn't send her a card.
- You know what else you didn't send?
Child support for
like the last three years.
See, I needed that money
to start my business.
Really? So is this truck
here a part of your business?
Yeah, matter of fact it is.
Oh, it's nice.
You must be doing well, so you won't
mind paying her what you owe her.
I don't owe that bitch anything.
Sadie.
Hey, you're joking, right?
- Come here! Give me that!
- Get off her!
Get off of her!
Get off of me!
- Let go of me! Let go!
- You know, this ain't high school, kid.
Stop! Stop it! You let go of me!
Ryan!
Get off me. Get off. Get off me!
Ryan! Let go. Ryan!
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's not that bad.
Except when you do that.
No, I'm sorry
that I dragged you into this.
Yeah. Well, if I remember,
you kind of begged me not to come.
I just wish we got the money.
What do you think Johnny's mom's
gonna do now?
I don't know.
Jack was kind of her last chance.
I bet it's kind of hard for you to imagine
Gwen married to a guy like that.
Easier than you think.
Turns out Johnny and I
kind of had a lot in common.
You okay?
I will be.
First time I laid eyes on Matt
was at a tailgate party.
He was doing a keg stand.
I thought it was when
you rushed my house as a little sister.
No. That's the first time you saw me.
I was stalking you for months.
I used to walk behind Kirsten
on her way home.
She lived on the opposite side of
campus, but I lived to watch her walk.
And I called campus security.
Yeah, it was worth every minute
I was detained in questioning.
Now, here we are.
I'm running Kirsten's father's company.
Matt here has been working like a dog
on a proposal for your dad's hospital.
Yeah. I wish that had worked out.
We don't give up that easily.
We were hoping you could help us
get one more shot.
We've listened to what he had to say
and we reworked the proposal.
You're a passionate man, Sandy,
I'll give you that.
Why don't I take a look at it.
If I like what I see, I'll pass it along.
- We'll set up a meeting for next week.
- Well, we can't wait that long.
The board is moving forward
on Monday.
- I see.
- Maya, it's not a big deal.
- Don't worry about it.
- It really is that big a deal.
You're our only chance. Sorry in advance
if this is too much pressure on you...
...but this hospital could help
a lot of people.
That's the only reason we're asking.
But we are asking. We need your help.
Sandy, we're eating.
Can we at least wait until after dinner?
Matt, do you want me to show
the proposal to my father too?
Yeah, I would.
Then I'd be happy to, Sandy.
Will you excuse me?
She said she'd be happy to.
Wait, but...
- Wait, Seth.
- What?
What if my dad actually falls for her?
Would that be the worst?
You and Marissa are already like sisters.
Why not make it official?
No, but it's not about Marissa.
It's about what's right for my dad.
And it's definitely not Julie Cooper.
Okay, I mean, no offense,
but she's Julie Cooper.
So what? I kind of like her.
I don't care that she married my grandpa
for money or had sex with Luke.
I think she's got moxie.
Summer? You home?
Gross, I'm studying. Get off me.
- Hey, sir. How's it going?
- Hello, Seth.
Dad. How was your day?
One of the best on record, actually.
Oh, really? Any particular reason?
Well, I think for the first time
in a long time, I might be happy.
Sweetheart, do you have plans
tomorrow? I'd like to talk to you...
...about something.
- No, I'm free.
Good. Then it's a date.
Hey, Dad, Dad...
Nothing. It can wait.
Okay.
Right now?
- I'm proud of you.
- Well, you heard the man. He's happy.
- Oh, no.
- I've got so many hormones.
Oh, get off...
- You must be dumber than you look.
- I just wanna talk.
- I got nothing to say to you.
- Good, you can listen.
Oh, man.
My father did a lot of bad things. Drank,
beat on my mom, my brother and me.
- That's a real sad story, kid.
- But the worst thing he ever did...
...was go away.
Leave my mom with nothing.
No money, we had no shot.
Any chance we had at a better life...
...it pretty much disappeared.
- What do you want me to do about it?
- Make things right with Johnny.
It's a little late for that now.
I mean, it's not like Johnny
would ever even know.
Maybe not...
...but you will.
Get him out of here.
I don't ever wanna see you again.
- What is this?
- It's a start.
All right, talk to you soon.
That was Matt.
Maya loved the proposal,
said she's gonna give it to her father.
Congratulations.
And then she broke up with him.
She's moving back to New York.
They've known each other for years.
They could've had a future together.
Aren't you taking this match-making
too seriously?
She's moving because she wants to.
You've done a complete 180.
A few weeks ago,
you were uncomfortable about this.
I'm still uncomfortable with this.
I'd rather be defending criminals.
But this is what I do right now,
so I might as well try to succeed at it.
So this is just another day
at the office.
I wouldn't put it that way.
Remember when I said
that I wasn't worried...
...about Sandy Cohen
knowing where the line is?
I'm officially worried.
What are you gonna say
about your face?
Sandy and Kirsten are used to it.
And Marissa?
You know,
when you mentioned this trip...
...I really wanted to come with you.
I didn't even care
what you were doing...
...I needed to get out of town.
Feel something different.
Yeah, this was definitely different.
Now that you're back?
Marissa and I need to talk.
- Hey.
- Hey. How was your weekend?
I've had better.
Everything okay with the police?
Sandy seems to think so.
I called you yesterday.
I know.
- This is hard.
- You don't have to say it.
No, I do. It's not because of Johnny
or Trey or anything else.
- No, I know.
- It's just...
Not working.
Hard to believe after everything
we've been through...
...we've got nothing left to say.
We never were that good
with words anyway.
- I guess, well, I'll see you at school.
- Yeah.
See you.
Hi.
So I was unpacking the car,
and I was just thinking...
Any chance you're up for a rematch?
- Deal.
- Okay.
Okay.
Thanks.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group