Previously on The O.C.:
I'd do a few surf competitions...
...maybe hook up with some sponsors,
turn that into a career.
I'm gonna get the operation,
and get back on my board.
- What's going on?
- I can talk to him.
Knowing that you're pulling for me,
it keeps me going.
- Mom, hi.
- Hurry, I'm running late.
- lf you'd just loosen up, you would...
- I would be one of the popular girls.
Truth is, I'm looking down the barrel
of divorce two.
I live in a trailer park.
No student has ever been
involved in a shooting.
Apparently, the parents are protesting.
They want Marissa out.
Who's ready for another "faux-jito"?
I think I kind of hit a wall
on the "mocktails."
- It's a school night.
- It's not a school night.
It's our last night, before our last
semester of our last year of high school.
- So we have to make it last.
- It's hard to argue with that logic.
You guys, this has been
a really fun winter break.
- Yeah.
The four of us,
hanging out like old times.
Yeah, it's gone by so fast.
I wish I could TiVo it so we could
play it over until graduation.
Unfortunately, after tonight, it's back
to regular scheduled programming.
For you guys.
I gotta go back
to Newport Union by myself.
- I gotta pee. You gotta pee?
- No, not really.
- I gotta pee.
- Okay.
Screw it. I'll go get us some drinks first.
- What if it doesn't have to end?
- Winter break?
No, the four of us being together.
It's a new year, but it's our last chance.
Senior photos are this Friday.
The Harbor Class of 2006 will be
immortalized in the yearbook for all time.
- Marissa has to be part of that.
- Are you saying what I think?
Yes. The dirty dean, he's gone. Right?
And Dr. Kim,
she's always seemed pretty reasonable.
Yeah, but the board kicked out Marissa,
not Dr. Kim.
- Plus, concerned parents...
- Whatever.
Out of sight, out of mind.
Time heals all wounds?
If you love something, set it fre... No?
- Maybe they're over it.
- Yeah. This town's real forgiving.
They were all out of "faux-jitos"...
...so I got a couple "I'll Fake Manhattans"
and a "Safe Sex on the Beach."
Ryan, what if the four of us can
all finish senior year together?
Summer's planning
"Operation Free Marissa."
Secure allies, go behind enemy lines...
- Been watching The War Channel?
- It's the new Food Network.
- I'm up for a little danger and intrigue.
- See?
You seriously wanna do this?
Okay. All right. But we don't tell
Marissa until we have a plan.
Cheers. To get Marissa
where she belongs.
Anyone have an idea how?
I cannot believe
it is our last semester of high school.
I know.
College applications have been sent off.
Studying, homework, learning.
All the reasons
to come here are irrelevant.
Good. With your free time
you can help out with "Free Marissa."
And to what are we freeing her from?
Exile to public school?
A year of solitude, ill-fitting gym shorts,
mediocre lunches. Hey, there's Ryan.
Hey. Can't talk.
Appointment with Dr. Kim.
- What are you gonna say?
- Just gonna come out and ask.
All right. Direct approach. I like it.
Good luck.
Excellent.
Prong one of the campaign initiated.
You and I will take on prong two:
Grassroots movement.
You know, information booth,
petition, maybe a protest rally.
- How many prongs are involved in this?
- Dude, like, so many prongs.
Ryan, come on in.
What can I do for you?
Dr. Kim. Sorry I'm late.
I wanted to talk about Marissa.
- Oh, how's she doing over at Union?
- Good, good.
As good as can be expected.
Actually, I was wondering
if you might consider reinstating her.
- l...
- Grades are good, hasn't been in trouble.
I understand Marissa's expulsion
seemed terribly unfair to you...
...frankly, I wish the outcome
had been different myself.
- Would you let her reapply?
- Even if I wanted to...
...only the Board of Trustees has the
power to readmit an expelled student.
Great. Could we meet with them?
They're meeting on Thursday
to discuss the new semester.
It's a little late...
...but...
...I could probably get
her case on the docket.
- That would be great.
- You're fighting an uphill battle.
- Wouldn't be the first.
- They rarely reverse decisions.
- All we need is a chance.
- Students are not allowed to speak.
You'll need a parent advocate.
I know someone who'd be
right for the job.
Thank you, Dr. Kim.
You might check the library
for transcripts of old meetings.
There might be a precedent.
Say...
...fall semester, 1996.
- Hey. Marissa.
- Johnny. Hey.
How was your break?
I feel like I haven't seen you in forever.
Just been laying low since the operation.
Started physical therapy.
- Great.
- What have you been up to?
I don't know, just hanging out with Seth
and Summer, Ryan, doing nothing.
It was kind of great, actually.
Well, look, if you still got
nothing to do there's this...
...thing I want you to go to with me.
Okay. What kind of thing?
It's a party, actually.
You see, PacWest is doing
this big press event for their...
...2006 surf team on Thursday.
- The PacWest surf team?
Coach called asking
how the surgery went.
It turns out one of their guys
failed the drug test.
I got an alternate spot.
I can do my physio- on the road,
and compete by summer.
- That's amazing, Johnny.
- Thanks.
We can only bring
one guest to the party, so...
...what do you say?
- Well, I mean, shouldn't you...
...take your mom, or, I don't know,
one of your entourage?
- I'm sure Chili's dying to go.
- No, I want you to go.
I mean, none of this would
be happening if it weren't for you.
All right, then I wouldn't miss it.
- Hey, I'm really happy for you, Johnny.
- Thanks.
- First meeting of a new year.
- Of a brand-new enterprise.
- Let's dig in.
- Okay.
Divorced, divorced, separated, divorced.
So many broken marriages
in this town.
- It's an epidemic.
- Speaking of which...
- Dr. Roberts is getting a divorce?
- You didn't hear it from me.
I need to go say hi.
He's been so good to Marissa.
- Hey, Neil, how are you?
- Julie. Julie.
- Well, happy New Year.
- Should old acquaintance be forgot?
I don't think that you're in much danger
of being old, or forgot, any time soon.
You're too sweet.
I never properly thanked you
for having me over for dinner.
It was a pleasure. Took the focus off
of Gloria's conspicuous absence.
You haven't told Summer
about your separation?
No, she thinks Gloria didn't call
because she's in some Zen retreat.
Marissa thinks I'm supervising
the longest condo renovation in history.
I feel a couple of New Years
resolutions coming on.
If we're gonna launch a campaign
to get Marissa back...
...we have to find someone
who can organize the masses...
...someone who they'll follow
into battle.
You mean, General Townsend?
Affirmative.
- Hey. Taylor. Hi, Mad. Hey, Ash.
- Mad, Ash.
Summer, Seth. Hi! I left you guys
a message about my Boxing Day party.
I guess you didn't get it.
How was break, awesome?
Yes. So awesome, in fact,
that we need your help with something.
Oh, you want my help?
Whatever you need.
I'm there for you 110 percent.
- Cool. We're launching a campaign...
- I love campaigns.
- to get Marissa back into Harbor.
That's...
...aggressive.
- Are you serious?
- Taylor...
...who out of our group...
...would be better at winning the hearts
and minds of the student body?
- Did you say, "our group"?
- So you'll do it.
It's an honor to share your foxhole.
We're going in front
of the trustees on Thursday...
...so I was thinking you could
go home tonight and brainstorm...
...we could go over the plan at 0800?
- Sounds good.
- Thanks, friend. Bye.
Oh, my God. Taylor.
Marissa is your number one rival.
If she gets back into Harbor,
she'II, like, totally socially crush you.
Grow up, Ashley.
That is so last semester.
I hate to be the one
to burst your popularity bubble...
...but isn't your mom
still head of the Parents Association?
- So?
- So she's the one who started...
...the petition to get Marissa kicked out
in the first place.
Also last semester.
- I'm sure she's totally over it.
- Your mom? Over it?
And, in 1996, the board voted
to reinstate a kid due to...
..."extenuating circumstances" after he
threatened another student with a knife.
You've done your homework.
So that's precedent, right?
Yeah, but a precedent is just
a small piece of a bigger puzzle.
It doesn't guarantee anything.
Look, if you're saying we don't
have a case, then it's fine, I get it.
But if this is because you
don't want Marissa...
...and me going to the same school...
...I promise you,
things are different now.
- You have a shot. But it's a long one.
- Okay.
We need a parent advocate
to address the board. Would you?
A good cause, poor odds, a chance
to ruffle some Newpsie feathers?
How could I say no?
Who's the chairman this year?
- Guy named Mercer.
- Jim Mercer?
- Yeah. You know him?
- He's a judge.
- I've argued before him many times.
- And that's a good thing, right?
Well, he's what they call a
"hanging judge." He's a real hardass.
- We'll have to present a good case.
- Great.
Now, all we gotta do is...
Cross your fingers
because it is all handled.
Any luck, you'll be back Friday morning.
Is that the good kind of speechless
or the bad kind?
Good kind.
I just... Wow, could it really happen?
It's not a sure thing, but, yeah.
Look, I know that you just got settled
at Union, you made a few friends...
...if you're happy,
I don't wanna mess it up.
No, are you kidding?
I'd love to finish
high school with you guys.
All right. I'm gonna grab dinner,
check in with Sandy and call you later.
- Hey, when's the meeting?
- Thursday.
- This Thursday?
- Yeah. That all right?
Yeah.
Hey.
- Hey, did you talk to Ryan?
- Yeah.
Not exactly the triumphant
enthusiasm I was expecting.
I'm sorry. I really do appreciate
everything you guys have been doing.
- But?
- Does anyone...
...even want me back at Harbor?
- Other than your three best friends?
- What if it doesn't work?
It's gonna work.
- And the meeting is this Thursday?
- Coop, what is going on?
It's just that PacWest is
announcing Johnny...
...as an alternate on their
team that night...
...and I promised him I'd be there.
Well, that's really nice of you
but you're gonna have to cancel.
Sorry.
He'll be happy for you.
The boys seem really excited
about getting Marissa back into Harbor.
- You think she has a chance?
- There's a good argument to be made.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
The boys have poster board and paint.
I love student activism.
Yeah. Did you get a chance
to call Judge Mercer?
He's gonna be out of town
until Wednesday.
But I did speak to another trustee, and
we'll be given a fair chance to present.
Let us know if there's anything
we can do. We should go.
Yeah, Summer will kick our ass
if we're late with our supply drop.
- Have fun.
- Thank you.
This isn't the same Judge Mercer
that jailed you for contempt?
Six hours in the slammer.
He didn't like my closing.
And to this day...
...I don't understand what it is I said
to the guy that struck such a nerve.
All I remember is that he hated you,
passionately.
- Maybe he won't remember.
- Not likely.
And he's not out of town.
He's ignoring me.
Thinks anything a counselor has to say,
should be on record.
Oh, come on.
It's not like this is an actual trial.
Tell that to Judge Mercer.
You need to see the PacWest doctor?
Why can't your doctor send your charts?
It's something to do
with their insurance.
I'm sure it's just standard stuff.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
If you want, I can give you a lift
to the doctor's at lunch.
If you want,
I can give you a lift any time.
I thought you were done
with the doctors.
Yeah, it's just a routine postop thing.
It's no big deal.
- Okay.
- So, what's up?
I was gonna call you last night.
I don't think I can make it to your party.
- You're not sure, or...?
- No. No, I can't.
See, there's this board meeting
at my old school...
...and I have to be there...
...because they're gonna decide
whether or not I can reapply.
- You're going back to private school?
- Well, it's not a done deal.
- But, yeah, I'm gonna try.
- That's great.
Really? Because I was worried
you might be upset.
- Why? I mean, I'm happy for you.
- Right. Of course.
Chili will be stoked, you know.
He was next in line for the party, so...
I'm really sorry.
You'll go to the next one.
All right. See you later.
- Okay, how many flyers do we have?
- Four stacks of 200.
Okay, good.
I want one on every locker by lunch.
You put the extras
on bathroom stalls and mirrors.
- Any word on the T-shirts?
- Ryan's supposed to get them at lunch.
Great. I'm gonna pressure my button guy,
see if I can get them at the same time.
Fire in the hole.
- Taylor.
- Mom, what are you doing here?
- My pre-meeting.
- Taylor's mom's on the board?
Do you know there's a motion on the
docket to reinstate Marissa Cooper?
- Yes.
- Flyer?
May I have a word with you?
I don't know what she's saying,
but it can't be good.
"How dare you do this
without talking to me."
I can read lips. Star magazine,
"What the Stars are Really Saying."
- I'm helping my friends, Mom.
- You don't have any friends.
Which is one of the reasons
why I had Marissa Cooper...
- "Removed from school in the first place."
- That's so demented.
Oh, you dropped your...
You dropped your... Your flyer.
I can't help you guys anymore. Sorry.
Taylor...
- I guess that means no button guy.
- Oh, Seth.
I wanted to meet the button guy.
I'm looking at a comp sheet
that puts the property value at 12.
Yeah, I'm meeting him right now.
Okay, I'll call you back in 20.
So...
...I say we put a cash bid
on the Urbina building at eleven-five.
You said the Urbina building
was overvalued.
Before my guy found out
Lockheed will build a plant in the area.
Oh, well done. Your guy?
Yeah. I have a guy.
He's your guy too.
Licensed private investigator,
registered with the state.
Completely legal. Above the board.
Maybe he could dig up something
on Honorable Jim Mercer.
- Who's that?
- Head of the Harbor Board...
...who has final say on whether
Marissa will be readmitted.
- That's a problem?
- He's not a fan of mine.
I'll put in a call.
Just a background check.
See what comes up. It'll be fun.
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- I dropped by to give you an update.
- And some schwag. What do you think?
- I love it.
What's next? Coffee mugs,
baseball caps?
- Whatever it takes.
- I can't believe this is happening.
Where's Johnny?
Doesn't he eat with you?
Yeah, well, he had a
doctor's appointment.
PacWest is giving him a second chance.
- Really? That's great.
- Yeah.
Everything's finally working out.
Hello?
Okay.
Are you sure?
Okay, well, then I'll come right now.
All right.
- Everything all right?
- Yeah, that was just Chili.
I guess he's not feeling well
so I need to bring him this book.
- You need to bring him a book now?
- It won't take long.
- All right. I can drive you.
- No, you get back.
Help Summer on the front lines.
I'll see you guys at the diner, okay?
- Yeah.
- Thanks for stopping by.
Yeah.
Don't tell me there's a problem
with the shirts.
T-shirts are fine. They're in the car.
It's Marissa.
I just came from Union. She got a call
and took off. Something I should know?
- Well, there might be a slight issue.
- Right.
I mean, not like an "issue" issue.
A friend issue. A Johnny issue.
She's afraid she might
be abandoning him.
- Of course she is.
- Wait! Stand down, private.
It's the way she's wired.
You wouldn't love her if she wasn't.
She wants to come back here
and she told Johnny.
If you wanna get mad
and punch somebody...
...or something, why not Taylor's mom?
You need to get your ass back into gear,
and start handing out some buttons.
- Neil.
- Julie.
- What a nice surprise.
- Yes. Yes, it is.
I mean, I didn't expect
to see you at home.
- I'm looking for Marissa.
- The girls aren't home.
Why don't you come in.
So no rhinos to plasty today?
No, Gloria called. She wants her things
sent to her sister's in Napa.
So I cleared my schedule...
...thought I'd talk with Summer.
Aren't we two peas in a pod?
Now that Marissa might go to Harbor...
...the money I've saved for a new place
will go to tuition.
Kind of forces my hand
with the trailer situation.
- I don't know what she's gonna think.
- She's gonna be grateful.
Her mom making sacrifices
for her future.
Oh, yeah.
Girls should be home...
Should be home any minute.
They were up most of the night
working on that petition.
- They're so hopeful.
- Here we are to ruin everything.
Really.
It's really selfish of us
if you think about it, isn't it?
Yeah. You know, I suppose
I could wait a few days, you know?
See how everything pans out.
Seems like more of a
weekend conversation.
- You are so right.
- You know, I could really go for a drink.
You read my mind.
Oh, my God.
Where is he?
Who knows?
PacWest doctors
refused to sign off on his knee.
Said it's too soon to tell whether
he'll be back 100 percent.
They won't let him tour.
I've never seen him like this.
Not even after the accident.
- Well, we gotta find him.
- Tell him what?
Everything's gonna be okay?
The guy's future's trashed.
He's lost everything.
I don't know if he'll
make it back from this.
I can't believe we spent
all day canvassing...
...and we only have,
like, 13 signatures.
Say what you want about Taylor,
the girl's connected.
Cheerleaders, water polo players,
the band.
- When she turned, they turned.
- All right. It's down to us...
...the AV Club, and the comic geeks.
- Actually, Leon's still a bit of a holdout.
- Wait, shut up. Just act positive, okay?
- Hey.
- We are gonna rock that hearing.
- We really are.
- Guys, I don't think I can go.
- What? Why? What happened?
- I appreciate everything you have done...
...but I don't think
I can go back to Harbor.
- Hi.
- Hey.
So I know I didn't feel
like talking about it last night...
...but I owe you an explanation.
- It's Johnny.
- I kind of figured that.
- Don't be mad.
- I'm not mad.
It's just, I wanted to
come back to Harbor.
Okay. So, what's wrong now?
PacWest changed their mind. They're
not letting him on the tour after all.
He's really freaked out.
- You gotta stop making this your problem.
- But it is my problem.
I mean, his girlfriend, the accident,
getting kicked off the team.
Are not your fault. You can't give up
your one chance to go back to Harbor...
...just so Johnny
has someone to hang with.
- I never asked you to do this.
- So you're saying we shouldn't have?
No. No.
I don't know. I'm sorry.
Well, we're meeting here
before going to the school tonight.
Just so you know.
My guy came through on your judge.
You don't have to use it
if you don't want to, but it's interesting.
- And not irrelevant to the matter at hand.
- Tell me the short version.
The judge has a son, Nick.
And he's got a drug problem.
Got kicked out of military school.
Nobody's heard from him since.
Case where he and I squared off,
I was defending a kid like that.
Well, if the judge wants to play hardball
with Ryan's friend, you have ammunition.
To what?
Exploit his family's tragedy?
Embarrass him in front of the community?
- I just thought you'd wanna know.
- I do.
Thank you. It's gonna be tricky.
There will be four very disappointed
kids if I make a wrong move.
Free Marissa.
Help Marissa get back into Harbor.
- Sign our petition?
- Sign this, geek.
- I'm not gonna sign his genitals.
- Okay, we are, like, getting crushed.
I don't understand why this is happening.
Even if people don't like Marissa...
What? Whoa. Everybody likes Marissa.
Even if they didn't, they could still sign.
What do they care?
That's the point. They don't.
This school is apathetic.
They need someone who can inspire.
Someone who can intimidate.
- They need Taylor.
- Yeah.
You know, maybe it's better
to be feared than loved.
You have my permission
to do whatever it takes.
- And what is "it"?
- I'm picturing, like, Indecent Proposal.
You're Demi, naturally, and Taylor is the
leather-faced guy who talks to horses.
- You want me to trade sex for signatures?
- Just get her.
I need Marissa back at this school.
I feel so dirty.
- I'm not going to school today, Mom.
- Mom just left for work.
She let me in on her way out.
Marissa told me about the tour.
I'm sorry, man.
- She send you to check up on me?
- Doesn't know I'm here.
But she is the reason I came.
- Is she okay?
- That depends on how you look at it.
She's... She's decided to stay
at Newport Union.
You private school kids find it hard...
First, don't lecture me
about public school.
Second, she's not staying for the quality
of the education. She's staying for you.
- Well, I didn't ask her to do anything.
- You didn't have to.
No matter what anyone says...
...it's still gonna be her choice.
Just wanna make sure
she feels free to make it.
Sandy?
- Hey.
- You have lunch yet?
I was signing a new client at the deli and
I picked you up a turkey pastrami on rye.
- With mustard?
- Spicy Dijon.
My hero.
Bad day?
I've been faced with an ethical dilemma.
Well, if I do say so,
my ethics are excellent.
Try me.
- Judge Mercer.
- Hates you and tried to get you disbarred.
The very one.
Turns out he's the father of a junkie.
His kid got kicked out of school...
...and he fell right off the map.
And you think you can
use this information...
...to shame him into
helping Marissa?
The thought has crossed my mind.
Well, what would you do...
...if you were a public defender
and Marissa your client?
Taylor? Hey, we need to talk.
Well, I'd love to talk to you.
About anything but Marissa Cooper.
I have been sanctioned to
offer you sexual favors.
I swear, Summer said it was okay.
Anything else,
you would be facing a long night...
...involving candle wax, tube socks,
and the new Fiona Apple CD.
But Marissa? I can't.
Well, lucky for both of us,
I've optioned to forgo man-whoring...
...and make an appeal to your heart.
I know you have one.
- Seth, don't.
- Now, I am your friend.
So is Summer, and so is Ryan,
and if Marissa came back, her too.
Okay. You don't get it.
My mom's a sports agent.
A sports agent? I thought
she was just a bored, bitter, Newpsie.
A bored, bitter, ball buster.
Three-hundred pound football players go
to her when they need something done.
- She'll take away my car.
- We'll give you a ride.
- Not pay for college.
- Scholarship.
- I'm sorry.
- Fine.
But as your friend,
I'm gonna beg you to do one thing.
Do not grow up to be like your mom,
because you're too good for that.
I don't want any pigeon pie, Gus.
I think it's terrible
what you do to those little birds.
- Neil. Wow. This is a surprise.
- Well, I figured I owed you one.
So this is what one of these
looks like on the inside, huh?
- Pork rinds.
- Yeah, well, when in Rome.
Not dressed for the hearing?
I was hoping you might need a ride.
Thank you, but truthfully,
I don't think I'm gonna go.
Marissa just might be better off
without me.
Well, that's nonsense.
Every girl needs her mom.
And I'm gonna be in your corner.
I give a lot of money to that school.
Give me five minutes.
I'll just take these and I'll be outside...
...trading stock tips
with your friend Gus, huh?
- No word back from Taylor.
- We gotta leave and no sign of Marissa.
Wait. So, what are you guys saying?
- That this was a valiant campaign.
- Yeah. Really valiant.
One any general would be proud of.
Surrender much?
I bet Napoleon never talked like this.
He should have,
right before he was defeated and exiled.
Summer, my little empress,
this is our Waterloo.
We need to retreat
and minimize collateral damage.
Well, can't we just wait a couple minutes
before we raise the white flag?
She's always late. I mean,
maybe she got lost, or something.
Marissa? Aren't you supposed
to be at that Harbor thing?
No. But, hey, have you seen Johnny?
Because I've been looking for him all day.
I know, it's crazy, right?
I gotta go,
we'll be late for the PacWest thing.
- Wait. What PacWest thing?
- You haven't talked to Johnny at all?
It turns out that that fancy surgeon
that you hooked him up with...
...went to med school
with the PacWest doctor.
He convinced the guy Johnny would make
a full recovery. He's back on the team.
- He didn't tell me.
- It's been insane.
They want him to leave next month.
Hired some tutor to help with the GED.
I've hit up my dad for flyer miles
so I could tag along.
- Wait, you're going too?
- It's the chance of a lifetime.
Anyways, it's kind of funny
how it all worked out, huh?
I mean, Johnny and I hitting the road,
you going back to your old school.
Yeah. Hey, I gotta go. If you see Johnny,
will you congratulate him for me?
- I will.
- Okay.
Summer, we can't wait any longer.
Marissa's not coming.
Okay. Fine.
All right. I'll tell Sandy.
Sandy's waiting in the car.
I told him we'd be right out.
You guys ready?
Yeah.
- Thanks so much for doing this.
- Yeah, it means a lot.
Ornery judge, captive audience,
righteousness on my side.
I feel right at home.
This is what you do. You'll be great.
Judge Mercer. Sandy Cohen.
I know who you are.
It will be a cold day in hell, Cohen.
I'm looking forward to this.
Oh, yeah. You gotta bury him.
Sandy. Hi, Kirsten.
Sorry to bother you both, but...
- We're about to start here.
- I know. You wanna hear this.
- All right. Be right back.
- Okay.
Mom, please, if you wanna do this,
it's your decision...
...but don't make me face
my friends while you do it.
You are either with me,
or against me.
Now, which is it?
I have to go to the little girls' room.
- Dr. Kim, may I have a word with you?
- Yes, Veronica.
- I had my guy keep digging.
- I've been thinking. I don't know.
Tell me everything.
- Hey, Taylor. It's Seth...
- And Summer.
Hi, Seth and Summer.
We were hoping
we might see you at the meeting.
Yeah.
No.
Sorry, guys.
- I know you must be really mad at me.
- No, it's okay. It's your mom. We get it.
Well, listen, thanks for trying.
We'll just...
- We'll let you know how everything goes.
- Thanks.
That's really nice.
Look. Speak of the devil. Literally.
- Neil, always a pleasure.
- Veronica.
- You know Julie Cooper-Nichol?
- Hi.
Of course. Marissa's a real
chip off the old block, isn't she?
I couldn't agree with you more.
Brains, beauty and a flair for fashion.
Excuse me.
Maybe this was a bad idea.
Good evening. Thank you all for coming.
I see it's a full house tonight,
and I think we all know what...
...or should I say who,
brought in the crowd.
So why don't we just start
with the matter of Marissa Cooper.
Ms. Townsend, you're speaking
on behalf of the Parents' Association.
Would you care to open?
- Where's Dad?
- He'll be right back.
Thank you, Judge Mercer.
As I'm sure you all know,
Marissa Cooper shot a boy in the back.
As head of the Parents' Association,
and a concerned parent myself...
...I can tell you,
this is not what the parents want.
And not what the Harbor students
want either.
Yes, it is.
Sit down, young lady.
Children are not permitted
to address the board.
But they're allowed
to address each other, right?
Taylor, why don't you show us
what you've got.
It's a petition.
With over 300 signatures.
Basically, the entire student body.
Well, this is all well and good.
But Ms. Townsend is correct.
Students do not make the decisions
on these matters.
Well, I am not a student.
And I would like to tell everyone here...
...that Marissa has shown dignity and
maturity throughout this entire nightmare.
Of course you think so.
You're her mother.
You're absolutely right,
so I'll speak on behalf of Ms. Cooper.
Go Dr. Roberts. Right. You... Sorry, sir.
Marissa's been living in my home
for the past few months...
...so I can say without hesitation...
...that this young lady
would make any father proud.
This school would be lucky
to have her.
That's a nice sentiment, Dr. Roberts.
And this student petition
is certainly meaningful.
But I don't think I can advise the board
to break precedent here.
This school has never readmitted
a student...
...who has been expelled
for reasons relating to violence.
That's not exactly true.
- There is precedent.
- He's right.
Ten years ago. A case not all
that different from Marissa's.
It was a knife, not a gun,
but the incident occurred on campus.
And after no criminal charges were filed,
the expulsion was reversed.
The students need to respect
the sanctity of this hearing and shut up.
Unfortunately...
...though this young man
is speaking out of turn...
...he's right.
- But I still don't have to reinstate.
- You don't have to reinstate...
...but you might want to.
- Oh, enlighten me, Mr. Cohen.
Why would I wanna do that?
Because sometimes a good kid
goes through a rough time.
And we might think
by closing a door to her...
...or to him, we're teaching a lesson.
And when the child needs us the most...
...we're not there for them.
There isn't a person in
this room that thinks...
...Marissa Cooper is a threat to anyone...
...or that she wasn't a model student,
or that she wouldn't continue to be.
So, what are we doing here?
Instead of proving a point,
let's right a wrong.
It's so rare in life...
...that anyone gets a second chance.
The board has reached its verdict.
And with only one dissenting vote...
...we have decided to let
Marissa Cooper return to Harbor.
Hello.
Do you guys think that I could
get a ride home?
- Yeah, we can manage that.
- Okay.
A ride? Hell, no.
Sister, you're sleeping over.
- Your Honor.
- This isn't a courtroom, Mr. Cohen.
Right.
Well, I just wanted to say thank you.
I know what you were doing.
But you made your case.
And I appreciate that you've kept
your information just between us.
l...
- I know where he is.
- What?
The private detective tracked him down
to Los Angeles. He's safe.
My friend brought him to this shelter.
He said he'd like to see you.
Thank you.
My hero.
- Thanks for being here, Mom.
- Oh, Marissa.
I feel like I've let you down
in so many ways.
That's really not true.
There is no condo. No renovations.
I live in a trailer park.
I was too ashamed to tell you.
Well, I knew
there was something, but...
I'll come home whenever you want.
Oh, sweetheart.
Thanks, Dad. That was pretty cool of
you, standing up for Marissa like that.
Too bad Gloria wasn't here to see you.
Yeah.
Listen, sweetheart.
I don't think your step-mom's
gonna be coming back.
I'm sorry, Dad.
But you didn't have to be so scared
to tell me. I mean, we do okay, right?
- Right.
- Okay.
I think that we are gonna go to the diner.
We'll see you later.
- Coop.
- Coming.
- Ready?
- Have fun, you guys.
Okay.
You know, all things considered,
I think I raised a pretty good kid.
I think we both did.
- You wanna...?
- Drink?
- Hey.
Hey.
So, what changed your mind
about coming back here?
Well, Johnny got put on the PacWest tour
and Chili said he was gonna go with him.
It seemed stupid
to stay at Union by myself.
All right. It wasn't me?
- No.
- Little bit?
- Okay, a little.
- Okay.
- Coop, Atwood, come on.
- Coming.
- Why don't I meet you at the diner.
- Okay. All right. I'll see you there.
Called your house.
Your mom said you'd be here.
Told her I was really happy for you.
Getting back on the team.
Yeah, well...
...just lucky I guess.
Thank you.
She deserves to be happy.
All right, we'll see you around?
Yeah, sure.
See you.
Harbor rocks!
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group