Previously on The O.C.:
Your mother has a drinking problem.
She needs help.
Mom, please. You gotta do this.
Who knew my new PlayStation idol
would be your new girlf...
- Your new...
- Friend.
- I would love to go to Cabo with you.
- Cabo?
I know about you and my dad.
My dad just got out
of a marriage...
...and I don't want him
rushing back into another.
The board is watching you,
waiting for you to screw up...
...and you're screwing up.
What's it gonna be?
Hospital or Matt?
- You and Marissa are gonna be okay?
- Yeah, of course.
He's leaning forward,
indicating all focus is on her.
See how her palms face up?
She's open to what he's communicating.
Star magazine. " What Stars'
Body Language Is Really Saying."
Well, I've talked to the guy...
...and what Ryan is saying
is he and Sadie are just taking it slow.
Oh, no. Bodies don't lie.
I'm sounding out
a hot-new-couple alert.
- Act like you know nothing.
- I don't.
Hey, so I think we're gonna head out.
- All right, we'll go with you.
- No, just stay here.
I'll get him home safe.
All right, so they're into each other.
You know what?
I'm actually happy for them.
You don't feel weird about Marissa?
Even I feel a little weird
about Marissa for you.
Nope. I'd feel weird about Marissa
if I saw Marissa.
Thought she was staying
at your house while your parents...
...are hooking up on the high seas.
- She's been sleeping at the trailer.
This breakup has hit her hard.
She said she needs time to process
her feelings and heal in solitude.
- Or party with 200 sweaty teens.
- What?
Oh, my God.
- So if the body doesn't lie...
- Then it's saying "ew."
"Ew" or "touch my pooper"?
Coop. It's me. Your best friend.
You know,
the one that you tell everything to.
- Dude, my head.
- Well, what time is it?
I know it's not big in there.
My voice travels.
- Okay, you gotta hide.
- What?
- You live in a trailer.
- Coop.
I'm coming, Sum.
Here, take these and... And this.
- Go.
- Coop.
My hand doesn't remotely hurt.
- Hey.
Hey. Looking good, Coop.
Very Kate Moss, pre Vanity Fair cover.
What you doing?
You know, nothing.
- Did you have a good time last night?
- Yeah.
Synapses are really firing, huh?
I think I have a bit of a head cold.
As long as you don't have
any other infectious diseases.
What?
Hang on.
Hey.
Hi, Mom.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- How's my girl?
- Hey, Daddy.
- We're back from our trip.
- Did you guys have a good time?
It was wonderful.
Can you have dinner with us tonight?
Fine. What time?
Don't sound so excited.
- Eight-ish.
- Yeah, perfect. Bye.
Okay. Bye.
- My dad.
- My mom.
- Dinner?
- Eight.
You go get dressed,
I'll drive you to school...
...we can talk about that
and other stuff.
Okay, give me a minute.
I think you're gonna need
a little bit more than that.
- Come here. It's cherry.
- Look, you gotta go.
It's wake and bake, baby.
Always cures a hangover.
Hey, what's up, man?
Someone's in a chipper mood
this morning.
Yeah, you know, I had a really good time
last night. I like that place.
The Bait Shop?
We should hang out there more.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Maybe...
Maybe tonight. Sadie likes the DJ.
She... She kind of wants to get me
on the dance floor.
- No.
- What?
You're the one who's always telling me
to loosen up. Go out.
Tense, tightly wound, shut in.
That's all I want out of you. Okay?
It's kind of a Boo Radley shape.
Far from The Bait Shop...
...and all its unsavory characters.
- Hey. Sandy, what's going on?
- Good mood, huh?
- Yeah, well...
Things must be working out.
- Dad, Ryan just smiled.
- Well, she seems great.
- Everything okay with you?
- Yep, just work. Not to worry.
All right. Well, listen, fellows,
love to chat, gotta get over to Sadie's.
Got a few minutes before school,
but cheer up, okay?
Hey, handsome men.
- Where?
I just made the same joke as my Dad.
A bad sign.
Your father happens to be hilarious.
It's just harder to tell.
Well, then it's a good thing
that we have a date tonight.
- What?
- Romantic dinner by the water...
...followed by an even more
romantic walk on the beach...
...followed by...
- Nothing.
Followed by nothing.
You will walk and eat.
Oh, jeez, I'm afraid l...
I can't even do that.
- You're canceling?
- Postponing.
I wanna be in the right frame of mind
to eat and walk with you. I'm sorry.
Something's wrong?
It'll all be fine.
So Dad's been working a lot
lately, huh?
Look, I'll be your date.
We haven't gotten a chance
to hang out in a while.
- I thought you forgot you had a mother.
- Hey.
Lay off the guilt. I said I'm in.
I just get to pick the movie.
So we're a couple thousand feet short
of a McMansion...
...but hopefully someone will take it.
- With that sales pitch, who could resist?
- Are you saying you find me irresistible?
Paint smell, realtor on the way over.
It's romantic and all, but...
Yeah. Plus I should probably
get to school too.
- Okay.
- No, no, wait.
- No.
- We can pick this up tonight.
I could give you a tour
of the pool house.
Yeah, we'll see
if you can close the deal.
Gotta go.
You didn't mention a word to Ryan?
Spoil his good mood?
He skipped out of the kitchen.
Atwood skipping?
Now there's a disturbing and odd visual.
Picture this one: Ryan dancing.
That's what this woman does to him.
If we wanna keep this skip in his step,
we gotta keep Volchok off his radar.
You play.
Volchok is Atwood's kryptonite.
He'll totally Hulk out.
You're mixing comic-book metaphors.
You think we can keep Marissa quiet?
She can barely put words together
these days.
- She's such a wordsmith.
- What does she see in that guy?
- He's so dirty and greasy.
- He's got good abs. Women like abs.
I got a six-pack myself, I know.
Oh, Cohen, those are your ribs.
Well, listen,
let's just not tell anybody anything.
All right. Heads down,
lips sealed, smooth sailing.
He's also got really defined triceps.
I like that.
I'm gonna get right to it.
I talked to Griffin.
You're firing me?
Yes. I'm firing you.
I have no choice.
It's for the good of the hospital.
What kind of garbage excuse is that?
- The truthful kind.
- Yeah. When it's convenient for you.
Every time you need to do
something that makes you feel bad...
...you're doing it for the hospital.
- It's either you or the hospital.
Griffin will not move forward
unless you're gone.
You don't even see what's happening.
He's making me the fall guy.
There's no need to pedal
in conspiracy theories, Matt.
- You are no angel.
- Neither is Griffin.
He's been taking kickbacks
from vendors for years.
- I like to know who I'm in business with.
- Those are bold accusations.
I can back them up. And I'll be happy
to share everything I know about him...
...and you to whoever will listen.
Thanks for the heads up.
- I know I'm doing the right thing.
- You think things are complicated?
You haven't seen anything yet, boss.
A little champagne
won't hurt you girls.
- It is a toast.
- How often do we get engaged?
Don't answer that.
- Engaged?
- You guys are engaged?
I'm so happy for you.
- Thank you, baby.
- Really, you are?
I mean, you may be
Mrs. Cooper-Nichol-Cooper-Roberts...
...but if you make Dad happy...
- She does.
- I do.
- Then I'm happy.
Marissa, how about some champagne?
Sure.
Marissa, do you have anything to add?
One sec.
Hey. Yeah.
You are? Okay, bye.
Congrats.
Will you excuse me for a moment?
- l... Me too.
- Marissa.
Where do you think you're going,
young lady?
I gotta go, Mom.
My friend called, he needs me.
I need you.
I don't have to tell you
how important this is for us.
Yeah, well, don't worry, Mom. I'm not
gonna screw up your golden ticket.
I don't know if I'm a fan
of yakuza films.
It was an interesting movie.
But a fun night.
Yeah. I would say anytime
you get to watch a guy...
...rip off his arm and continue
fighting, that's a good night.
- I didn't understand the other fellow.
- The guy that produced...
...the ball of energy
and then destroyed the world?
I think it's pretty self-explanatory.
You remember
when I took you to Fantasia?
Because I do.
Sorry you didn't like the movie.
Oh, it was worth it
to spend some time with you.
I've missed you.
You wanna do it again?
You want a second date?
Yeah. But I get to pick the activity.
- Sure.
- Tomorrow night?
I have an idea already.
- Hey.
- We have a major problem.
Marissa just bailed
on our parents' engagement party...
...to skank out with the surf Nazi.
- Your dad and Julie got engaged?
You kind of buried
the lead there, Summer.
- Julie and Dr. Roberts?
- We got bigger fish here.
Marissa's on a slut spiral.
We need to stop her.
- It's a little out of my league.
- I know. We need Ryan.
- The code of silence has been lifted.
- I'll talk to him.
But he's been in such a good mood.
So this is the pool house?
You interested in making an offer?
It's a little small.
But it's got great views.
What? Locked?
When did this door get a lock on it?
- Little busy, Seth.
- You're not the only one.
I don't wanna have to tell you this
through the door...
...but Marissa's been hooking up
with Volchok.
Oh, hey.
- Sadie, I didn't realize...
- Yeah. Good night, Seth.
- Good night.
- Call me, okay?
Yeah.
- Guess I ruined the mood, huh?
- Just a lot.
When I put the locks on,
I thought I solved the problem.
You know me. When I have information
to disseminate, nothing can stop me.
- Not walls, not locks.
- Not women?
So, what are you gonna do?
Well, reschedule with Sadie
and go back to her place.
No, I meant about Marissa.
What do you mean,
what am I gonna do?
Well, Summer seems to think
this Volchok guy...
...is not exactly a beacon
of morality.
Not my problem. Not my girlfriend.
Well, I know. Two coffees.
Look, man, she makes her own choices,
so do I.
I choose Sadie's tonight.
You're so Zen these days.
It's simultaneously inspiring
and disconcerting.
Just feeling good, man.
Just feeling good.
Cheers.
I can't believe
you're getting married. Again.
You make it seem
like an everyday occurrence.
- It almost is.
- This time it's gonna stick.
It just feels real.
Not everyone can have that
Kirsten-and-Sandy relationship.
That bionic, Kevlar-wrapped,
robo-marriage...
...that can withstand
anything you throw at it.
Well, you've seemed happier
than I've seen you in a long time.
Neil has mellowed me.
No more manipulative bitch...
...no more scheming,
no double-crossing.
Which will be disappointing to some.
Not for Dr. Roberts.
You know, we both just
kind of found each other...
...right at the moment
when we really needed someone.
- There's no agenda.
- He does have a palatial estate.
Kirsten, if he wanted to live together
in this trailer, I'd do it.
Not that I'm offering.
Real classy, Gus.
It's them Big Gulps.
They go right through me.
Sneak up on me too.
- That's a nice final image.
- What's going on?
Oh, my God.
You the new tenant?
Nice to meet you.
We really need to get you out of here.
Hi.
Hi. What's up?
Missed you in class.
- Yeah, there was traffic.
- We had that test today.
That was today?
Thanks. Gotta go.
Totally and completely untrue.
And if Matt tried to print that...
...I'll sue him for libel.
- He seemed pretty sure of himself.
If it wasn't for me, your firm
would be belly-up right now...
...which is why I don't appreciate
your accusing me.
I'm not accusing anybody of anything.
And forgive me for saying, Henry,
but you seem a touch defensive.
The only business that I am in
is the business of helping people.
I would like to believe
that we are partners in that.
You give me your word,
I'll give you the benefit of the doubt.
Sandy, I didn't become a doctor
to get rich.
You have my word.
Thank you. You did a wonderful job.
Thank you.
Bye.
I'm from the Philippines.
Oh, well, then...
Wow, Coop.
You make a really good hood ornament.
- Funny.
- I know.
- Are you getting drunk?
- More like staying drunk.
- Oh, good plan.
- I can't deal with this right now.
Well, you're gonna have to.
Because now, Coop, we're sisters.
Right. Which means you're not my mom.
I know about Volchok.
Saw you at The Bait Shop, I know you're
shacking up with him at the trailer park.
Well, aren't you
a regular Veronica Mars?
- Way to solve this weeks' mystery.
- What has gotten into you?
- Since l-know-who has.
- What do you care?
You have Seth, Ryan's got
his new girlfriend, Johnny's gone.
What difference does it make
what I do?
- I'm not hurting anyone.
- You're just the saddest girl in the world.
Grow up. Get over yourself.
Take a shower.
Fine. Take your little emo boyfriend...
...drive off in your Beemer,
go home to daddy's mansion.
Oh, yeah? Go with Volchok to one of his
heavy metal vomit parties...
...and listen to heavy metal and vomit.
- Wow, you're being so lame.
- Not as lame as you.
- Fine. Bye.
- Later.
- What are you doing?
- Taking what's mine.
You were to turn over your key.
- You're trespassing.
- These are my personal files.
Which your office conveniently
forgot to send. I'm taking them.
- You're not.
- What are you gonna do, arrest me?
Fight me? You act
like you got something to hide.
- You're acting like a child.
- lf you're sure I don't have a case...
...you shouldn't care
if I leave with this.
- You threatening me?
- Doesn't seem like I have a choice.
Game on, Sandy.
This is so romantic. And original.
Yeah. Well, what can I say?
I'm a creature of habit.
Yes, yes. The lure of the chili fry.
Natural aphrodisiac.
Well, I think we'll be fine
as long as Seth is nowhere nearby.
Seth, right.
Well, good. I have something
to tell you. I have some good news.
- Yeah?
- I can't believe Volchok missed today...
...he's gonna be pissed.
- He won't care.
He's hanging with that chick, Marissa.
- She seems kind of lame.
- Yeah, lame and hot.
She ain't innocent. Volchok show you
the scratches on his back?
- Why don't we take this to go.
- No, it's fine.
- Let's just go. Come on.
- It's... Sadie, it's fine. Sadie?
Sadie.
I'm not mad. I just feel like once again,
you know, the mood was kind of ruined.
- Okay, we can turn that around.
- I think we're trying too hard.
Maybe we need to let
the perfect night just happen. Okay?
Give it some time.
All right, all right. Fine.
Let me at least drive you home.
- Okay.
- Just give me a second.
Ryan, come on. Don't go back.
- Hey, look, it's little bitch.
- Volchok around?
- You looking for your girlfriend?
- No, for him.
And if you see him, tell him that.
And to meet under the pier tomorrow.
You think you can remember all that?
You need me to write it down for you?
Yeah, bro. We'll tell him.
You know, I just knew.
It was only a matter of time
until you got in my face again.
- I just wanna talk.
- About what?
Your girlfriend or mine?
I got stories about both of them.
I bet you do.
This where you tell me
I better leave her alone?
- That she's too good for me?
- Whoever Marissa wants to be with...
...it's not my place to judge.
- I saw her at school, didn't look so good.
- That girl couldn't look bad if she tried.
She was drinking.
You know she has a problem?
She drinks. She gets drunk.
I don't see the problem.
Just so you know,
I'm not looking after her anymore.
It's on you now.
Treat her right. She deserves it.
- Good morning, ladies.
- I'd say a great morning.
Our new family,
first breakfast together.
And tonight we're going to have
our first family dinner.
Something that hopefully
will become a weekly tradition.
Nothing like all sitting down
together to a meal.
Discussing current events,
catching up.
- Doesn't that sound fun?
- Tons of.
Marissa has several events
she would love to share with the family.
Summer, you can make that dessert
I like, the one with the graham cracker.
Oh, I'm sure daddy's little girl
would love to.
Excuse me.
Sisters.
Sadie?
- Hey, man, I was looking for Sadie.
- Hey. Yeah, she's in the shower.
Or was.
Ryan. Did you meet Bob?
Hey, Bob.
What's up?
- Garage door sticks a little.
- Cool.
- Make yourself at home.
- Thank you.
See you.
One bad date
and I'm already replaced, huh?
- All right, all right. Two bad dates.
- Bob?
He bought the house. He lives next door
and he made a really great offer.
- My news last night, if you'd listened.
- I know. I'm sorry, I was distracted.
- You wanna tell me what's up?
- Sure.
It's Volchok and Marissa.
But it's all good now.
There was a conversation
I needed to have, I had it...
...I'm done.
- That's good.
It's just, I think I'm done too.
- What do you mean?
- Well, my aunt's business is handled.
The house is sold.
- There's no reason for me to be here.
- No reason?
Ryan, I never intended
to stay this long.
I think it might be easier
for me to leave if...
If we didn't happen?
- Have you thought about this?
- Yeah, I have.
- Have you?
- Yeah.
If I stayed,
I'd have to find an apartment.
Then what? Wait for you to finish
high school? Follow you to college?
We're getting a little
ahead of ourselves, I mean...
I don't know, I honestly didn't think
that much about the future.
I was just hoping
to take you to dinner.
You eat, right?
You haven't thought about it
because you're not ready to.
Which I totally get.
But I can't change my whole life
to be with someone who's distracted.
So that's it then. No more smiling...
...no skipping, no dancing.
- You were never a fan of dancing.
I might have come around.
Now we'll never know.
Yeah, I can't just ask her to move here,
change her whole life.
Well, relocating to Newport
might not be that big a deal.
Yeah. Puts a lot of pressure on us,
you know? On the relationship.
Ryan Atwood loves pressure.
He's not comfortable unless his entire
body's being squeezed in a vice grip.
- That is not true.
- Yeah?
You moved to Chino to help a girl
with a baby that might not be yours.
- Theresa needed someone.
- Stayed with Marissa...
...for several years of tortured torture.
- She was there for me too.
- When it comes to pursuing happiness...
...with a great girl who seems
to be relatively issue-free...
- I gotta ask her to stay.
- Yes, you do.
- All right.
- I saw that smile. Smiler.
I told you, the kid's just posturing.
He's trying to get a rise out of you.
Well, Matt said he has documents.
He said he could prove
what he's saying.
Look, Sandy, I apologize.
- Now what are you saying?
- I'm saying...
...I've let you shoulder too much
of the responsibility on this situation.
- I'll handle it from here.
- Well, that sounds a little ominous.
- What are you gonna do?
- You focus on the hospital.
There's people counting on you
and there's a lot of work to be done.
Now you've done too much already.
What was that you were saying
about 18 holes at Big Canyon?
- You're wearing that to a family dinner?
- Who says I'm going to dinner?
Okay, Marissa, be mad at me
if you want, but it is our family.
Whatever. Save me some dessert.
- Hey, what's up?
- The slut is spiraling.
- I thought I told you to talk to Ryan.
- I did.
I tried to activate his savior complex,
but it seems he's been cured.
I gotta go.
I'm hanging with my mom.
- With your mom?
- I know, it seems weird.
We're trying something different.
I'll talk to you later.
- Fine.
- Okay, bye.
- All set?
- Yeah.
Where we going?
Cardio Barre? Yogalates?
Something new.
Let's give Marissa
a couple of more minutes, shall we?
Actually, we should just get started.
Personally, I'm starving.
Why don't we just dig in and bond.
What were we gonna do at this dinner?
Discuss current events?
- I think we live in a very fascinating time.
- Riveting.
Julie, why don't you
ring her on her cell.
I did call. Several times.
Well, I'm concerned, she never missed
dinner when she was here last semester.
That's because I wasn't here.
Marissa and I haven't
had the greatest...
Luck.
But you've always stood
by each other through hard times.
- Isn't that great, Dad?
- Yes. It is.
You Cooper girls are really something.
Thank you, Neil.
And thank you, Summer.
Will you pass the potatoes, please?
I thought you and your mom
fought all the time.
It's not my mom...
...it's Summer.
You know, the only other time
we really fought was in the fifth grade?
When I sat on the bus with Luke
on the way to the Museum of Tolerance.
Who's Luke?
Summer and Luke were engaged.
In the second grade.
She doesn't like to talk about it.
- Why all the questions? All of a sudden?
- What do you mean?
You just seem very interested in my life.
I just...
We're hanging out, seems like...
What?
You deserve to be treated right.
If I wanted to be treated right,
I wouldn't be with you.
Works for me.
You want a bump?
I don't... I mean, I've never.
There's a first time for everything.
Guess I'm partying solo.
Okay, what is this place?
You'll see.
Crappy rec center basement, bad coffee.
Don't think you're in Weight Watchers...
...so either you're
in a community theater group...
...or have converted
to an under-funded religion.
Hi. I'm Ellen,
and I'm an alcoholic.
- Hi, Ellen.
We will begin
with our reading of chapter five.
- Seth.
- Thank you, Ellen...
I thought if you knew
you wouldn't have come.
Well, good instinct.
Going through this the first time
wasn't enough?
This place has saved my family,
my marriage, quite possibly my life.
These people know more about me
than my family.
Who's fault's that?
Like you talk about what happened.
It's not like you ever ask.
- lf this is how you act when I share...
- There's sharing and then there's lying.
Well, we're here,
and I'm not leaving.
So you can wait in the car
or you can do this for me.
Just give me an hour.
It's important that you be here tonight.
Is anyone gonna rip off their arm,
keep fighting?
Metaphorically speaking, yeah.
Matt, this is Mitchell Kiven
from The Register.
I've got your message, and I'm
very interested in the Griffin story.
You got the number.
Hey, Matt, it's Sandy. We need to talk.
Will you call me back
as soon as you can?
- It's cool. Take whatever you want...
- This isn't a robbery.
- Hey.
Is Sadie around?
- No, actually, she...
- Do you mind if I come in and wait?
Well, I mean, might be a while.
You just missed her.
She left for Oregon a couple hours ago.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
Sorry, I figured you were spending
your time under the pier these days.
- I can go.
- No, it's fine. I'm... I'm not gonna stay.
Where's Sadie?
Gone. Back to Oregon.
Went to see her, she'd already left.
Without saying goodbye?
Guess she thought
it was easier this way.
And is it?
You don't have to answer that.
I'm gonna go.
But...
Enjoy, then.
I'll leave it as I found it.
I'd pissed in the streets...
...eaten out of garbage
and accidentally shot my wife.
Not once, but twice.
Thank you very much.
That's a heartwarming tale.
He's been sober 30 years.
Thank you for that, George.
Before we leave,
we have a couple of chips to hand out.
Kirsten, if you'd like to join me.
Congratulations.
- You're nine months sober.
- Oh, thank you.
All of you.
And especially my son, Seth,
who's here with me tonight.
- Hi, Seth.
- Hey.
He doesn't know this...
...but he's the reason that I got sober.
The look on his face
at my intervention...
...he was so disappointed in me.
But he believed that I could do this.
And he was right.
Congratulations, Mom.
Only 29 years
and three months more to go...
...until you're as normal
as William S. Burroughs over there.
This is the final boarding call
for bus number 338...
... with continuing service to San Diego.
Never expected to see you here.
Yeah, well, I'm just glad I found you.
There's a lot of ways
to leave Newport.
- Bus, plane, boat.
- Greyhound.
- Way to hedge your bets.
- I'm just glad you're still here.
- Why?
- Because I don't think you should leave.
Ryan really cares about you.
He told you that?
Well, I mean, he didn't have to.
After everything we've been through,
I know him well.
Bus number 465 to Portland,
with stops in Bakersfield...
- Yeah, well, this is my bus.
- He wants you to stay.
- He didn't try to stop me.
- Yeah, he did.
He was just a couple of minutes too late.
Why are you doing this?
Well, I guess because
you make Ryan happy.
Bus number 465
to Portland, Oregon is now boarding.
- Neil, dinner was amazing.
- Yeah.
Marissa's gonna be sorry she missed it.
Well, we have years
of family dinners ahead of us.
Julie, you know this engagement
is a trial, right?
What?
A trial.
For you, me.
Us together. For the girls.
I mean, if our families aren't a good fit,
then we really shouldn't get married.
Of course.
I mean, love doesn't really conquer all.
Well, we both have
the broken marriages to prove that.
But, Neil, surely this time...
I don't mean that in a punitive way,
I'm just trying to be practical.
I've got some reading to do.
I'll see you in a minute.
Hi, baby.
- Good night, Dad.
- Good night.
I couldn't help overhearing
what my dad just said.
But don't worry, he always gets this way
when he starts to get close to someone.
Actually, Summer, the only thing
I'm worried about is my daughter.
Yeah, me too.
- Hey, vodka on the rocks, please.
- You got ID?
- I drink here all the time.
- Yeah, when Volchok's guys are buying.
Can't you make an exception
this one time?
- I used to date the manager.
- Sorry.
Look, I'm having a bad night,
and I really need a drink.
You and me both.
Matt?
Oh, my God.
What happened?
Like you don't know.
- What are you doing here?
- You tell me.
There's another bus in an hour.
What do I have to do
to get you to stay?
I think you're doing it.
Glad to see you back.
Wasn't sure if I should...
No more talking.
Here, let me help you with that.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group