She's already taken
a whole box of tests.
She's gonna take another one.
You're humiliating her.
- Silas, she's fine.
- She's pregnant!
We're going to confirm that.
Why do you have a home pregnancy test?
Do you want me to kill you?
I can't pee.
Drink some water.
I was just asking a question.
- I ask the questions.
- Alright.
- I'm the mother.
- Okay.
- How did this happen?
- You don't wanna hear it.
Oh, but I really do.
If I had to bet, I'd tell you
it was 3 weeks ago in my room,
doggystyle, when I pulled
out the condom was gone.
Megan has really strong
muscles, must have sucked it...
Stop! Stop! Stop!
You asked.
- Wanna be the cool mom.
- No. No, I don't.
Million things in
this world I wanna be.
Cool mom...
nowhere on that list.
I hope grandma is on that list.
This is all so exciting.
Isn't this exciting? It's exciting!
Are you nervous about the audition?
A little.
There's nothing to be nervous about.
- Hodes? Isabelle Hodes?
- She's right here.
Hey.
Do your best.
- Hello.
- You're late.
I'm running for elected office, Dean.
Believe it or not, I
have better things to do.
I have a job interview.
For a job, Celia, which we need
so we can afford your campaign.
Of course, who's rejecting you today?
Just try to make sure our daughter gets out
of here with some modicum of self-esteem.
Try not to get tazered this time.
Your girl is in there right now.
That's wonderful.
- You want a maple bar?
- No. No, thank you.
I'm getting a corn syrup contact
high just sitting here.
I'm comfortable in my skin.
I want my clothes to
reflect what's within.
Good things come in big packages.
The bigger, the better,
the Huskaroo sweater.
Excuse me.
Huskaroo lets you be you.
Isabelle!
Mom?
She's fantastic!
This is us.
These are our pot growing
armenian neighbors.
10 houses on this block, 4 of them growing.
How in the fuck, fuck,
fuck, does that happen?
Hey, can I ask you for your pen?
I love the smell of Sharpies.
Oh, did you ever
smell dry erase markers?
Hey!
Don't any of you people fucking get it?
We just opened up a Burger King in
the middle of fucking MacDonald's.
Except Ronald is this tracksuit wearing
motherfucker named bizarre
with a last name who's like a eye
chart ready to cut your dick off
and mail it on 4 different directions.
We're butt naked in
front of George Bush
with our dick in his daughter's mouth.
Enough with the dicks.
What if those houses
accidentally burned down?
Okay, no thank you. No thank you.
We got a house full of plants, Lacey.
We need to pack 'em up in soil.
Rent us some U-Haul and get
the fuck out. We have to move.
Can we at least hire the guys outside
of Home Depot to move us?
I've got a lower lumbar pain.
We're not going anywhere.
- I don't believe that you heard me.
- I heard you dicks and MacDonald's.
We've as much right to grow pot
in our rental house as they do.
We're staying.
I'll take care of it.
British port, Connecticut.
Lifeguarding.
Charlie?
Lawrence?
Ellen?
No? No.
I wanna talk to them by myself.
Oh. Okay.
It's gonna be great.
Text message me right after, okay?
Here you go.
What's this?
New  bakery. New location.
Under the X.
You're opening a bakery in
a residential cul-de-sac.
A special kind of bakery.
Special how?
Special in that we won't necessarily
bake anything there.
What are you going to do in this
bakery if you do not bake?
We're going to... that
is to say we're already...
growing.
- Growing?
- I grow.
That is special.
You didn't tell me
about this in Las Vegas.
- You're mad?
- This is visionary idea, Mrs. Botwin.
- You're mad.
- Something like that.
The circles, these are...
Other visionaries.
Hostile visionaries.
I'm wondering
what you think about it.
I'm thinking this
wasn't one of my vows.
Silas got his girlfriend pregnant.
- Doggystyle.
- What?
They're  telling her
parents today. I should be at home
waiting for him but I can't
'cause I have this problem.
I have fires in 2 houses, Mr. Botwin.
Mr. Scottson.
- I gotta get back to work.
- Oh.
Go be a mom.
Chedarella.
No crust.
So...
I don't know.
She  wanted to do it alone.
I said okay.
But she hasn't messaged me yet.
She's probably dealing
with a lot right now.
Maybe they took her phone.
Yeah, maybe that's it.
Water's nice.
I told Andy and Shane.
Do you wanna talk?
No.
Are you sure?
We went upstairs in this big building.
And after my uncle paid her,
Jade took me into a room
and told me to take off my pants.
Shut up!
- No way!
- Way!
- Did you do it?
- I did.
- You took your pants off?
- No way!
- Shut up!
Shhh!
How long did it last?
I'd say 45 seconds.
- Shut up!
- No way!
That's awesome!
We're supposed to be studying!
Study this!
Bitches gotta learn.
You guys wanna see
what she looked like?
Whoa!
My uncle likes Cindy.
But I had Jade.
I got some on my knee
and she wiped it off with a warm towel.
Oh, Chedarella!
Botwin house.
Not here, ma'am. Try back later.
What?
Shane?
We have reason to believe that
Shane was abused by a masseuse.
- Here at school?
- No, not at school.
At a massage parlor.
And if I'm to believe the conversation
I overheard with his friends,
he's suggesting that his uncle
took him to this establishment.
- His uncle?
- You.
What? Me?
Come on.
What kind of man
would take a prepubescent
boy to a massage parlor?
An irresponsible, morally
bankrupted degenerate!
Is that why you pulled me
out of the Yeshiva to tell me?
Yeshiva?
Yeah, at Amadrash la Torah
where I'm a full time
rabbinical student.
We're taught to contemplate,
ask questions and exercise restraint
before reaching conclusions.
And only then
and with religious trepidation,
do we attempt to
interpret.
What are you saying, Mr. Botwin?
What am I saying?
I'm saying...
he made it up!
He wanted to look cool
in front of his friends.
- He made it up?
- Shane is...
going through changes,
he's experimenting.
- Experimenting?
- He's masturbating.
Oh.
It's an akward time for a young man.
You remember that time, don't you?
Possibly.
You know you turn out the lights,
crowl into bed, you reach
down there and feel...
Think you're alone.
- Suddenly, it's...
- Halloween!
Your father is standing there dressed in a
bee costume...
watching you.
***
- The shame!
- Yeah, the shame.
So you didn't take him to see Jade.
I took him to a chinese restaurant.
We're gonna let young Shane
off with a warning.
That's superb.
We're not gonna mention, you know...
Your father and a bee costume.
- Have a good day, Mr. Botwin.
- Yeah.
Hello, my name is Debra Garringer,
calling on behalf of the Agrestic
Citizens for Change...
We're making a courtesy
call about the debate.
Hi, this is Nancy Botwin, I'm
calling on behalf of Agrestic...
Citizens for Change.
Would you like Agrestic to
be a drug free community?
Nancy, put a little
more perk in your pitch!
Hi, can I speak to Mr. Fuckyouson?
- I can't do this, Celia.
- What?
We're just letting people
know about the debate.
Debra Garringer,
Agrestic Citizens for Change?
Well, I can't just say it's me!
That would be too...
- Honest.
- Leading.
We're trying to let the
voters decide for themselves.
I guess it's only marginally delusional.
Hey, there's no gun
pointed at your head.
If you can't make time for the pressing
problems of greater Agrestic...
That's exactly it, I can't make
time, I've got problems at home.
Really? Do you wanna talk about it?
I don't wanna talk about it.
I just wanna go home.
You know, I tell you about
my husband's unemployment,
my daughter being the face
of America's trends fat so...
Tell me what's going on with you.
Please, Nancy.
- Celia.
- Aren't we friends?
- I just wanna go.
- You can't even say it.
You don't wanna be my friend.
Everything is not about you, Celia.
What the fuck are you doing?
Be my friend!
- Let go of my fucking hair!
- Be my friend!
- Be my goddamn motherfucking friend!
Selfish! Selfish! Selfish!
You two are just like sisters.
Hey, Deano.
Hey, you got the late shift.
Don't you have a debate
with my wife tomorrow?
Oh yeah, the debate thingy.
What's on the boob?
As your campaign manager,
I should tell you
she's been practicing all week.
Well, she's wasting her time.
Nobody goes to those things.
And besides, I'm great at debating.
Go ahead, ask me a question.
Mr. Wilson, what zoning
laws do you plan to enact
to combat suburbans problems?
Next question.
You're not even worried.
Worried? Nobody likes your
wife, you don't even like her.
I could stand up on that
podium tomorrow night
and take a shit on one of
those make-a-wish cancer kid
and people'd still vote for
me 'cause they hate your wife.
And... I'm likeable.
You almost make me feel bad for Celia.
Tell her that, maybe she'll fuck you.
See, I'm on your side,
buddy. Vote for me!
Bitchin.
Don't you think it's
the circuit breaker?
Next  question!
Come on, boy, zip it up!
I'm trying, Heylia. You got
to inhale more or something.
I ain't that fat.
Just put some backbone into it. Come on! 1, 2, 3!
Alright.
That's him! That's him!
- Give me the vanilla extract.
- What you need that for?
Just  give it to me,
he likes baked goods.
Okay.
Alright here. How do I look? How do I look?
You look good.
Shit! You ain't Joseph.
You got any coffee?
Conrad, get chicka some coffee.
- Make it black.
- She likes it black, Conrad.
Late night?
Helping my friend Lacey out.
Some kids at her neighborhood put
a hand ax to her electrical cables.
I had to drive over there and figure
out how to hook up a generator.
You'd think they'd leave
instructions on those damn things.
- Where does she live?
- Gardendale.
Lacey needs to get
herself a new address.
That's what she's coming around to.
Conrad, did you say something?
No, I'm just getting Mrs here some coffee ***, ma'am.
- Who's having a picnic?
- I am.
I can't remember the last
time I had a picnic.
Oh God, that's good.
Did you pack that kush?
Two of them. Two.
Hello. Hey, honey.
Calm down.
I'm coming.
- Is that Lacey?
- No, I need my stuff.
- It's almost ready.
- I need it now.
You'll have to give me a second.
I'll come back for it later.
- Where have you been?
- I'm here. What happened?
- Where were you?
- What happened to your face?
I just went to see Megan.
Calm down.
She hasn't been in school for 2
days. They took her to a clinic.
She  won't answer my messages.
I just wanted to talk to her.
I just wanted to talk to her
and he won't let me talk
to her and he hit me.
Hit you? Who?
I did.
You hit my kid?
I only wanted to talk to her.
Your son fucking stabbed me.
He put his foot through the window,
I grabbed ahold of him and
he grabbed the piece of glass
and he stabbed me. So yes, I hit him.
Silas?
Keep him away from my daughter.
Your son is a fucking loser.
You taught me how to drive.
Silas, get in the car.
He just wanted to talk to her.
What's the big fucking deal?
The big deal, Mrs. Botwin,
is that I had a decent,
respectable daughter.
Oh, please.
She meets your son,
she starts smoking pot,
she's doing ecstasy and
she's had an abortion!
She was the blowjob
queen of Dooey street!
And you're a shitty parent.
You lay a hand on my kid
again, I will kill you.
Do you understand me?
Are you fucking hearing me?
You need to leave now.
We're leaving. We are completely leaving.
Just drive.
You can make that choice for change
by giving me
your vote on election day.
And when elected, I promise to be
everything that Doug Wilson is not.
Active, Committed, Engaged...
ACE.
Thank you.
Mr. Wilson, your final statement?
Nah, I'm good.
Go Doug!
- Hey, Sanjay.
- Hey, Andy.
What's that humming sound?
The generators. The Armenians
cut the electrical cables.
Well, that's not very neighborly.
They're historically put up on people.
It's not neighborly
but it's understandable.
Why are you standing like that?
It's the only way to get Channel 12.
Oh.
Thanks.
We also get channel 34. Infomercials.
And you don't have to hold the antenna.
I bought diamonic earrings for Nancy.
I mean my mother.
- Good night.
- Bye!
- It's a raid.
- What?
The cops are outside everywhere.
They're all over the place, Andy.
Shit.
Shit! Shit!
What do we do? What do we do?
I don't know.
We gotta hide it. We gotta hide it all!
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Turn on the lights.
We can't turn on the lights.
We'll ruin the grow cycle.
Turn on the lights, Sanjay!
Conrad said never to
turn on the lights!
Fuck Conrad!
Okay. Goddamn it. Alright.
Shhh. Plants.
Shit. Shit! Shit!
Get the plants.
I said get the plants.
Wait, what do I do?
Flush everything. I gotta save the mother!
No. Oh no!
Okay, mamma.
Forgive me.
We had this pregnant hamster
in science class last year
and Denny Cohen put
a pencil up her butt
and later she had dead babies.
Kinda like an abortion.
Fuck you.
It's not a fucking hamster.
Shane.
What?
I don't want you playing
with Denny Cohen anymore.
Go get ready for school.
- Hello.
- I have a gift for you.
You do?
Yeah, turn on the TV, channel 8.
- Alright.
- I'd hurry.
The daring raid on 4
marijuana grow houses
took place late last
night in Gardendale.
Residents were awaken to the sounds
of police sirens and battering rams.
Over a 1000 plants
were confiscated and
dozens were arrested including
drug kingpin Aram Kashishian.
I'm here live with
agent Peter Scottson
from the Drug Enforcement Agency. He lead this raid.
He joins us now. Agent Scottson?
Hang on just a sec, will you?
Lieutenant Scottson, can you tell us
is this a common base of
operation for drug dealers?
Gated communities can
provide a perfect cover for
a drug operation. Insulation from the outside world.
But they can also provide
the ideal environment
for a well executed bust.
Gates keep people out, but
they can also keep people in.
In this case, an armenian drug cartel.
Not sure I would use the term cartel
but no doubt it was a major operation.
This is a drug free zone now.
Okay, thank you, agent
Scottson from the DEA.
Reporting live from the
scene, I'm Lynn Amarillo.
- Back to you and the studio.
- Thanks Lynn. In other news...
Yep.
As I was saying,
I was looking for the perfect
gift to get for my wife and so...
I got her neighborhood.
- You got me a neighborhood.
- I did.
You're very thoughtful, Mr. Scottson.
And you are very, very
beautiful, Mrs. Scottson.
Oh my!
Transcript/Synchro: Travis
- www.forom.com -