It so cool
we got in here.
Ok. You two have fun.
Where you been?
Where did you say
the bathroom was?
Upstairs. Second door
on the lt.
I'll be right back.
Man: there's our girl...
That's her !
Ingrid?
Hey, you guys
seen ingrid?
What are you doing
out of your bunker?
I was on my way to file
the things that i..
file.
Excuse me.
Hi.
I'm..
sean, hey.
Derek.
You must be
looking for your brother.
Yeah.
Right this way.
Brother as in..
that's hotch's brother?
Maybe hotch is adopted.
So, georgetown law?
You're doing big things.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Top of the stairs.
Come in.
Sean, hey.
Let me call you back.
Hey.
This is a surprise.
Haven't cut your hair
since thanksgiving.
That's what you said
at christmas.
Sorry.
Um..
it's your first time here,
let me give you the ur.
Yeah, i can't stay long.
I'm working
the lunch shift.
Well, not for long.
Congratulations.
You must be
pretty excited.
I'm not going
to georgetown.
What?
I changed my mind.
I got this job offer
to work at this
restaurant in new york.
It's not a chef,
but it's under
the right ones.
I can learn from them.
What are you
talking about?
I made up my mind.
Sean, you've always
wanted to be a lawyer.
Just like dad,
just like me.
And look what it
got dad, huh?
Heart attack. 47.
I think i'm doing ok.
Look, if it's about
being in new york,
nyu's got a great law school.
Columbia, fordham.
I don't ink
you're hearing me.
All i'm asking you to do
is think it through, you know?
The logical thing is for you
to go to georgetown.
I have to trust
my instincts.
Look, sean, it's typical
for someone
who lost his father
at a young age..
and you know what?
You're not him.
Then why are you here?
That's a really
good question.
Here he comes.
That's hotch's brother?
Uh-huh.
I don't see it.
Sean, listen to me.
All i'm saying is
you're 25 years old.
You know what,
don't profile me, aaron.
Now, i see it.
Terra mesa, new mexico.
5 dead, and all from mesa
university.
No signs of sexual assault,
and no sign of theft.
519-year-olds.
Minimal defensive wounds.
One of them was impaled
on a 6-foot wooden pole.
Who'd want to torture
5 college freshmen?
They weren't tied up
and no one escaped?
No single unsub
could've exerted
this much control
over so many people.
So you think
there was mo than two.
I think we're looking
at a pack.
A pack?
3 or more that kill
in unison,
as in, nature of
the group dynamic,
dictates the pack's survival
is dependent on their ability
to hunt successfully.
And as in nature of
pack will keep on killing
until it runs
out of prey
or is stopped.
Stopped by what?
Stronger pack..
Nietzsche wrote,
the individual has always
had to struggle
to keep from being
overwhelmed
by the tribe.
Sheriff, i'm
special agent hotchner.
The are agents
reid and gideon.
I was hoping
there were more of you.
The other agents went straight to
the station house
to look at
the victim's files.
Has forensics
had any luck?
County csu went through
for prints
and trace evidence.
They said with
all the workmen
trampling through here,
looking at footprints
would be a waste.
Come on.
The bodies were almost
completely skinned,
yet there's
so little blood.
I think i know why.
The unsub avoided
areas of skin
on the wrists
and the throat.
Areas where the veins
and arteries
are closest to the surface.
Why would they do that?
They didn't want them
to bleed out.
These kids
were skinned alive.
Two cases of beer,
two sleeping bags.
There's a third
sleeping bag upstairs.
Everything you need for a
night of teenage romance.
It's unlikely
the two couples
brought a fifth wheel
to take notes.
Sheriff, it's possible
there was a third girl here.
A sixth victim.
I'll get my deputies
to canvass the areas.
See if anybody saw a girl.
You said there was
another one outside?
Yeah.
He was like the others.
Coroner said
from the amount of blood,
he was alive
when they impaled him.
I know this is
gonna sound strange,
but the way the victims
were flayed alive,
mutilated,
and now
the impalement display
of this last victim..
what?
These were all
war rituals
of the native american
plains indians.
That mean something
to you, sheriff?
I'll say, it does.
Everything you see
around us is apache land.
This whole basin's
a sacred burial ground.
And was the sight of
a number of massacres,
as i understand.
So this development
is on their land?
It was their land.
But they didn't
have the money
or the inclination
to build on it,
so the town seized
half of.
Yeah, last year,
the supreme court ruled
cities could use
imminent domain authority
to seize and repossess
undeveloped private land
for private development.
And now the town
is looking for investors
to build on
the other half.
The apache
are fighting it,
of course, in court.
Is there been any violence
until now?
Nothing like this.
You know anybody
on the reservation
capable of this?
I don't know. Reservation's
federal jurisdiction.
Sounds like where
we need to go.
Go call garcia.
See what she can find.
Ok, one order of bad guys
on the apache reservation
coming right up.
Let's hear it.
Apparently there was
a militant group there
in the 70s
called the irm.
Any of them
still around?
No. There's a guy
on the reservation now
who's been locked up
more than a few times
for demonstrations,
resisting arrest.
Mostly political protest
type stuff.
Yowsa, get this.
His father was killed
in a shootout
with federal agent
wounded knee.
His name,
Benjamin blackwolf.
The son, john Blackwolf.
Thanks, Garcia.
Blackwolf?
John blackwolf?
You know him?
Indian activist.
He's been in
a little trouble.
Related to his activism,
but nothing violent.
Not around here.
Should we call
the reservation police
and alert them?
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Why not?
Blackwolf is
the reservation police.
Jane bear, these are
fbi agents.
Gideon.
Hello.
Hotchner
how do you do?
And reid.
Miss bear is the president
of the tribal council
and principal of
the reservation school.
President
and the principal.
You must be a busy woman.
We'rout here
on our own, agent Gideon.
We all do our part.
Is, uh..
John inside?
Is this about
the terra mesa killings?
They just want to
talk to him.
John blackwolf has done more
to help his tribe
than anyone.
Hell, jim,
how many times
have you called him in
to find lost hikers?
How many drunken campers
has he tracked down
for the park service?
John is
a peaceful man..
who would not hesitate
to defend this tribe
with force if attacked.
What does this have to do
with terra mesa?
Well, a lot,
if john considers
the building of
the terra mesa development
on apache land
to be an attack.
The developers have paid
a lot of families
to leave the reservation.
So many families
have gone now
that we can barely fill
a single class.
Forcing the dene,
the apache nation,
to abandon their homes
and live in
government controlled
internment camps.
Does anybody know
the last tribe
to surrender to
the american government?
It was
the chiricahua apache.
And does anybody know
the name of the last
leader of the apaches?
Geronimo.
That's right.
He was caught by
the u.s. Army 5 times,
but the ga'he had given him
so much strength
he escaped..
each time.
Samuel.
Yes?
Tell the men from the fbi
who the ga'he are.
The ga'he are mighty spirits
who dwell in desert caves.
Reid.
Is your name samuel?
Sorry.
Are the ga'he good spirits
or bad spirits?
They're both.
Like men.
I'll take over
for you, john.
Mr. Blackwolf,
i'm agent gideon.
These are agents
hotchner and reid.
You look like
a college professor.
You look like a student.
You..
you look like fbi.
We're with
the behavioral
analysis unit.
Profilers should
know better.
How's that?
We don't
do massacres.
You do.
Me, personally
your government.
Mr. Blackwolf,
'd like for you
take a look
at these photos
and help us figure out
how these kids were killed.
You're not asking
because i'm a cop.
No.
We're asking
because you're an expert
on native american culture.
I don't base my opinion
on pictures, mr. Hotchner.
I have to walk the ground.
We should start inside.
Forensics says the outside's
been contaminated
from all
the construction traffic.
Of all the native
american tribes,
the apache
are most renowned
for their tracking ability.
It's said they can track
a man or animal
through any condition by
simply noticing the slightest
disturbance in the environment.
He's profiling the dirt.
I notice you don't
carry a gun.
21 feet.
What?
Ask agent
hotchner there.
He's the real
gun hand.
Why do you say that?
You carry
two guns.
The maximum distance
an attacker with a knife
can close in the time
it takes to react,
draw your sidearm
and fire is 21 feet.
Inside 21 feet, i win.
Outside,
i have other options
besides shooting a man.
Like negotiating.
Like running.
Why do you say
i carry two guns?
Your right instep print's heaver
than your left.
And since
you dot appear
to have a clubbed
right foot..
you can't tell that
from my footprints.
it's no perceptible
difference between them.
Your problem isn't
with your prints.
It's with
your perception.
What do you see?
There's a saying.
Once too much blood
has been spilled
on the same ground,
that ground develops
a thirst for it.
This is all consistent
with native american
warfare rituals,
but it's not apache.
Whoever did this
carried out
the most brutal practices
of the apache.
Navajo, comanche, pueblo.
And sioux.
No one tribe
every did them all.
Not like this.
Real indians would know that.
This wasn't indians.
And if you wanto
figure out who did this,
it might help to know
there was a sixth person
in the house.
Why do you say that?
Female. 90, 95 pounds.
Size 6 shoe.
Fallen arches.
She was walking alone,
when she was ambushed
by two men.
We also believe
there were at least
three suspects.
Three?
Yeah.
Two over here plus at least
six over there.
Because while these two
carried this girl,
struling to their vehicle
to the east,
at least six others
ran single file
to hide their numbers
from the west.
So you're saying
that there were eight?
At least.
And one hostage.
You waed to see
how i behave
at the scene
of therime,
you can at least
tell me how i did.
You're lack of
anmotional reaction
at seeing the crimes
leads me to believe
you'rennocent.
A guilty man would've
feigned disgust?
Exactly.
Do you know what
counting coup is?
No.
The apache knew
they could easily prove
their superiority
by killing many
of the enemy tribe.
But they also knew killings
would start
a fierce blood feud
which would result
in t waste of
lives and resources.
Makes sense.
So the apache
proved their superiority
by counting coup.
Stealthily
stealing property,
usually horses,
from right under the nose
of their enemy.
To the apache, killing,
unless absolutely necessary,
was a sign of stupidity.
And weakness.
Ifhis your way
of saying you're not
the killer,
we already know that.
So why am I
still talking to you?
Hotch.
So if there was another
girl out there,
no one's
reported her missing.
None of the papers
have received
any claims of reonsibility
or ranm demands.
'D like for you
to stay
and help with
the profile briefing.
If it'll keep the fbi
off the reservation,
i'll stay.
Each torture ritual
had specific
religious significance,
but only to the tribe
that pcticed it.
It's highly unlikely
that any one tribe
would mix them
all together like this.
Meaning?
Whoever did this
obviously had knowledge
of native american culture,
but they had absolutely
no practical understanding of it.
What we know, ishis pack
shares a singular vision
whether they share
religious faith,
racist ideology,
or political manifesto,
each member of this unit
has surrendered
its individual identity
to the group.
It's the act of kidnapping
that reveals the nature
of this pack.
From the german
red brige
to the munich olympics
to iraqi insurgence.
The act of kidnapping
is a characteristic
of political terrorist groups.
We could be looking for
a domestic terrorist
organization
like the symonese
liberation army
that kidnapped patty hearst.
But these
are indians, right?
I seriously doubt it.
The torture
and mutilation you see here
are very confused
imitations
of warfare practiced by
native american tribes.
Are you trying to
tell us
that indians wouldn't be
so brutal?
No. I'm saying that indians
wouldn't be so confud.
Can we really
be sure he's right?
Well, i'm fairly certain
blackwolf wasn't in on it,
but you don't need
to be einstein
to realize
these people were indians,
or people that made it
look like indians.
Why would anyone want
to frame these indians
possibly to turn
public opinion
against them.
Sheriff, you mentioned
the apache were fighting
the land grab in court.
Public opinion would be
a significant factor.
Is there anyone
besides the developers
who might be
vehemently opposed
to the indians
getting the land back?
The adu.
Who's that?
American defense union.
Founded by a local businessman
named roy minton.
They're like the minute men
who control the borders,
only these guys blame
everything on the indians.
Who are the members?
Mion's people
are mostly white,
construction workers,
building supply vendors.
Working class people
that believe indians
are standing in the way
of progress.
And commerce.
Whether they feel
the indians
are standing in the way
of progress or profit,
or they're just
nuine racists,
i think minton and the adu
are strong suspects.
Let's bring minton in.
Mr. Minton, any idea
who might be behind
these killings?
The indians have a history
of violent behavior.
Pecially the apaches.
Did you know that they
used to kill white settlers,
decapitate the bodies,
put their victims heads
on wooden pikes
outside their houses?
That was a long time ago.
You still seem
pretty upset about it.
That was the other night.
My family's beenealing
with the apache
for years.
You know, your rhetoric
sounds just hateful enough
to justify violence.
We don't need to stoop
to their level.
We're fighting
the indians in court.
Is that right?
Then why
all the guns, roy?
Our recordshow
that your members
carry over firearms.
We're simply exercising
our constitutional right
under the second amendme.
We have the right
to defend ourselves.
guns, roy.
I don't think so.
That's n self defense.
That's plain paranoid.
Not anymore.
If minton is as fanatical
as he pretends to be,
he wouldn't file lawsuits.
Or organize labor unions.
The indians are keepg
minton and the members
of the adu
fr making a lot of money
on the development
and construction
of the apache land.
I agree.
He's using racist ideology
to cover simple greed.
Sheriff, i'd like you
to put minton under
surveillance.
You think he's guilty?
Not likely, but we've just
given minton reason
to believe
that some faction
of the adu
may have taken matters
into their own hands,
and minton
may lead us to them.
It's garcia.
Hey, what have you got?
I have an ncic hit
on one of the prints
on the sliding glass door.
Ingrid griesen,
19 years old,
family moved her here
two years ago from texas.
Where they require
fingerprints
for driver's license
applications.
She wasn't among
the victims on the scene.
Ok.
Nice job.
Think we might have found
our sixth victim.
How old was ingrid
when your wife
passed away?
14.
And then,
you raised her
on your own?
Why didn'tou report
your daughter
as missing, mr. Griesen?
I didn't know
she was missing.
She has her own place.
She has her own life
at school.
Her own friends.
When was the last time
you spoke to her?
Couple weeks ago.
She's been going
through a phase
the past couple of months.
Distancing herself.
Has anyone
threatened ingrid?
Not that i know of.
Have you received
any menang phone calls
or seen anyone
in the neighborhood?
Anything that's been
unusual at all.
No. Nothing like that.
We have reason to believe
that people
who kidnapped your daughter
may be politically
motivated.
They killethose kids,
and they kidnapped
ingrid in the name
of their cause.
Think the first thing,
or the best thing
you can do
to help your daughter
is for you to go
on the news.
How will that
help ingrid?
If we can personalize
ingrid to the public,
the public will take
any harm that
comes to her
at the hands of
the kidnappers personally.
Hurting her
would hurt their cause.
That'll stop them
from killing her?
It might.
Ok.
Hey.
So?
Fathers blame themselves
when a child is kidnapped.
As irrational as it is,
it's typical.
This guy didn't do that,
why not?
Well, in these situations,
innocentarents
don't hide their
feelgs of guilt,
while guilty parents do.
So we're thinking
this guy's guilty?
Of something.
Ingrid is my only child.
She's my whole life.
Please return ingrid to me.
Talk to her, and you'll see,
she's a sweet child.
She's never hurt..
you have to see this.
/.. anything you need.
/Contact me directly.
/I will try..
what do we do?
/.. everything i can to help.
We get rid of her.
/Whatever it takes.
/I'm asking you,
/please, leher go.
We've got a caller
on the line.
Has griesen been prepped.
Caller doesn't want to
speak to griesen.
In fact, he doesn't
want griesen to know
at he's even calling.
This is special ent
aaron hotchner.
Yeah. We have
ingrid griesen.
We'll turn ourselves
and the girl in
under one condition.
I'm listening.
You don't tell griesen
about it.
What does it matter to you
what i tell griesen?
Because he paid us
to kidnap her.
Don't move!
Hey, don't shoot.
Where's the girl?
She's in the van.
Got her.
Ingrid?
My name is Elle.
I'm with the fbi.
Are you ok?
Just tell me what happened.
Peter griesen
hired us.
He knew about
our records,
but he said
he'd ge us a chance.
Two weeks ago,
he called us
into his office,
said he had some
off the clock
work for us.
What kind of work?
He said his daughter
was in tuble.
He said he wanted us
to follow her, grab her,
and take her
to the motel.
You didn't question
his motives?
Well, of course, we did.
But then he gave us
half theoney.
He said if we
harmed her accidental
or otherwise,
he'dake sure
we paid for it.
So he wanted you
to kidnap her
but not hurt her.
Yeah.
So we grabbed her,
took her to the motel,
then we called griesen,
and he said co by
in the morning.
But he didn't show.
What about the killings?
We didn't know
anything about that.
We saw it on the news
the next morning.
We called mr. Griesen,
he said, hold tight,
he'd come around
in the afternoon,
but he didn't show,
so, then the next night,
he's on the news.
And he's talking
about kidnappers,
and.. look, man..
we may be dumb, all right?
We're not stupid.
I made the call right then.
You kidnapped the girl,
but then you leave
just minutes before
someone else comes
and kills those kids.
We didn't kill them kids.
We was with her
the whole time since.
You can ask her.
Well, that's quite
the story.
Thing is, they're telling
exactly the same one.
I believe it's the truth.
Why'd you kidnap
your own daughter?
You kidnapped your daughter
and coincidentally
saved her own life?
Right now, at
the very least,
it looks like you had
prior knowledge
of the killings.
And at worst..
i had nothing to do
with the murders.
You paid leland
and van owen
to kidnap ingridwhy?
I want my phone call.
Ifhat you're saying
is true,
it seems likely
your daughter
was somehow involved
in these killings.
She had nothing
to do with it.
You stay the hell
away from her!
I want the names
of all your daughter's
friends at school.
Boyfriends.
I want her class schedule.
Ingrid's very private.
We have 5 dead kids.
Tortured, mutilated,
and murdered.
And all we have to go on
is you and your daughter.
Do the math!
It's garcia.
I got this.
You re?
Yeah, yeah.
All right. Yeah.
Talk to me.
Hello, ingrid.
I'm dr. Spencer reid.
I'm with the fbi,
and i was wondering
if you could
griesen, ingrid..
Excuse me?
Griesen, ingrid.
Doesn't look like minton
or the adu were part of it.
My men have been looking
at him and his friends.
Checking on alibis.
Nothing.
The only thing
i'm certain of
is that peter griesen
is trying to
protect his daughter.
Hotchner.
Ingrid isn't
catatonic anymore.
But she's answering
evy question
with only her name
and social security number.
Like a prisoner of war.
There's more.
Garcia did some checking.
Ingrid hasn't been
enrolled in school
for over a year.
She had good grades.
Just suddenly dropped out
and vacated
her campus apartment.
She left
no forwarding, hotch.
We have no idea
where or how
she's been living.
Thanks.
I need to see
ter griesen's phone records.
How long has your daughter
been in a cult?
Unit 4, i'm still on
a code 6
outside the minton residence.
Looks like everyone's
gone to bed. Over.
/10-4, patrol. Base out.
About a month ago,
you placed a call
to a psychiatrist
in boulder named
dr. Richard frank.
He's a deprogrammer,
and his specialty
is getting kids
out of cults.
Your daughter joined
a dangerous cult.
And you couldn't
convince her to leave,
so you had her kidnapped.
Now you're
protecting her
because you think
ingrid and her cult
killed those kids,
and you're
probably right.
There's another killing.
A family of 5
was slaughtered
in exactly the same way
as the terra mesa killings,
and among the dead
are three girls.
Ages 5, 8, and 1
legally, this could
go a long way
in distancing
your daughter
from the others.
If ingrid had
a change of heart,
a case could be made
for brainwashing
or even
temporary insanity.
Mr. Griesen..
we need you
to tell us
what you know
about ingrid's
situation.
It's all my fault.
Ever since her mother died,
i've done everything
i could for her.
Somehow i left her
vulnerable to these people.
Given the wrong
circumstances,
this could happen
to anyone's child.
Tell us what happened.
Ingrid was in
her first semester.
She started acting strange.
She hardly visited anymore,
when she did, she was..
different.
How? How was she
different?
The way she spoke.
She kept repeating
these words.
This jargon.
I didn't know where
she was getting it.
And she just disappeared.
Cults commonly
have theirwn language.
They invent or redefine
certn words
only the cult members
understand.
It's a way of
isolating the members
from outsiders.
It's a very powerful form
of thought control.
If you could help us
identify some of
the key word
perhaps we could get
ingrid talking.
She said i was a trespasser.
That i had no right
to be here.
New mexico?
In the desert.
She said grandfather
had taught her the ways of,
oh, what was the word?
Ofahi, gaji..
ga'he.
Yes. That's right.
Thank you.
We're looking for
the cult leader.
Typically men between
the age of 25 and 35
with a high level
of intelligence.
Sociopathic underachiever,
with an extremely
abusive childhood.
And obviously someone
with an interest in
and affinity for apache
culture and rituals.
Look for males
with criminal records
for lesser type crimes.
Drug possession,
petty theft.
What about
school records?
The victims
from the first
crime scene
was terra mesa
university.
Maybe the leader
was there, too.
That's great.
Look for students
who stied
native american
cultures extensively.
We need to do it all.
With this second strike,
it could be a spree.
Sorry about
your man, jimmy.
I appreciate that.
That her?
She won't give us
anything but her name
and her social.
Thanks.
Ok. They're ready.
Everybody out.
Come with me.
My friend wants to
show y something.
Ingrid, name
is john blackwolf.
I know who you are.
You're the son
of benjamin blackwolf.
The chiricahua apache.
Come with me.
What do you think
happened here, ingrid?
I think three little
trespassers
met the vengeful blade
of the tribe.
Whatribe would that be?
There are only
two peoples.
The apache knows who
trespass against us.
You're not
apache, ingrid.
No. You are not apache.
Not anymore.
Grandfather tested me.
He sent me
to the desert mountains
to be blessed
by the ga'he.
The ga'he have brought
grandfather back to us
to build his new tribe.
To reclaim the sacred land
for the apache.
Where is grandfather?
Did grandfather
ever tell you
where the name apache
comes from?
It comes from
the yuni word, apachu.
It means enemy.
And if grandfather
knew the first thing
about the real apache,
he would've taught you
to refer to us
as the dene.
It means, the people.
Grandfather said
that you and all
the living apache
are like
the jews of old.
Lost and wandering
the desert
in search of their messiah.
And he has..
the dene don't believe
in a messiah.
You were lied to, ingrid.
The ga'he said..
don't use a word
you don't understand.
The ga'he are not
magic fairies.
They're not gods
as you understand them.
This is not the blood
of an enemy!
This is the blood
of a little girl
just like you are.
You've been fed
bits and pieces
of a culture
you don't understand.
You don't know.
What we do know
is you've been manipulated
and exploited by
a very disturbed individual.
You're a liar.
You have disavowed
your ancestors.
Only those who dwell
at the deadlands
deserve to live.
The deadlands are on
the southern edge
of the western tract.
You said cults like this
se out remote places, yes?
They like to isolate
their followers
and give them freedom
to create
their own societies.
Ok. I got it.
It doesn't get
any more remote
than the deadlands.
How big an area
is this place?
About square miles.
We'll need to
narrow it down.
We might just have
our cult leader.
It's a guy named
jackson cally.
He was expelled
from tmu six months
before the others.
What for?
Mescaline. Peyote.
Terra mesa was the last
in a string of colleges.
He studied religion
and native american culture
in every school and
he was in a seminar
in native american culture
with ingrid griesen.
That's how they know
so much about me.
I've been
a guest lecturer
in that seminar
for the past 4 years.
If cally's
our cult leader,
we need more
information on him.
Have garcia pull every shred
of cally's life of
the system.
She's already
pulling it.
Do we know he's still
in the area?
He was arrested
for trespassing
on a bunch of
motel properties.
Breaking into
unoccupied rooms.
But his last known aress
turned up cold.
Most cults don't have
any legitimate means
of paying rent.
They tend to seek out
abandoned, previously
standing structures.
Like manson's spahn ranch.
There's an abandoned motel
off route 29.
Right in the middle
of the deadlands.
Let's go.
I'll stay with reid,
and we'll pull
as much as we can on cally.
Fbi, don't move.
Put your hands
out to the side
and turn around
very slowly.
Jackson cally.
Grandfather.
There's no one
else here, hotch.
Where are the others?
Hunting.
Jackson Gordon Cally.
32 years old.
Spent most of
his childhood
moving from foster home
to foster home.
/Hang on a second.
/I'm gonna put you
/on speaker.
Ahead, reid.
Simply another sad
but unremarkable statistic.
Aside from the fact
that he had an iq of 189.
Any criminal record?
At 18 he spent 22 months
in prison for auto theft.
I just spoke to the warden
at the prison,
said when he was there,
he found religion
and began preaching
to his fellow inmates.
And that he once convinced
a mass murderer
he was doing time with
to beat to death
an inmate that was
threatening Cally.
Ever since he was a child,
this guy just survived
on cunning
force of personality.
Spent 22 months in the clink,
was released
and then bounced
from university
to university.
Studying, you guessed it,
native american cultures.
Ok, thanks.
What's his connection
to the apache?
Aside from
taking your class,
nothing that they
could find.
With sociopaths
like cally,
there is no connection.
If it hadn't been apache,
he would've found
some other culture
to attract and manipulate
his followers.
Like manson,
cally has been forced
to become an expert
profiler of sorts.
He reads the people around him.
He finds a way in.
And then he brainwashes them
to serve his needs.
And the only way to figure out his game
is to play it.
I'm gonna give him
exactly what he wants.
What's that?
An audience.
Mr. Cally, i'm special agent
aaron hotchner with the fbi.
You know, i spent
my whole life
talking to cops and doctors.
Something different
about you.
You're not just a cop,
are you?
You're very perceptive.
So, what are you?
I'm a profiler.
So am i.
Your colleagues
respect you a great deal.
Looking to you to find
all the answers.
Leadership is a grave
responsibility.
They don't call me
grandfather.
Well, in my tribe, grandfather is simply
another word for teacher.
Did you teach your tribe
to murder?
No, i don't teach murder.
I teach love.
Love of land.
Love of ancestors.
Love of the tribe.
These trespassers
poison the land.
The apache will soon
remember who they are
and they will hunt
these trespassers
off their land.
Until no one
but the apache remain.
You think you speak
for the apache.
But you're nothing
but a coward.
And a killer.
I haven't killed anyone.
Do you think that
your little tribe
is going to wage a war
with all the white
peoplen this state?
Pretty soon,
we won't have to.
Why is that?
What's going to happen when the angry
white men come to the doors
of your children
blaming you
for the killing
of their people?
What are you going to do,
call the cops?
No. You're going
to string them up.
You're going to put
their heads on poles
and rape their women.
Just like the savage animal
you really are.
Too bad you couldn't be the leader that your father was.
Before they shot him down...
Enough! Blackwolf !
Let me in with him alone.
I'll get him talking.
You've done more than we
could' hoped for.
You guys take cally down
to the sheriff's office.
You tell that man
he's welcome
on my reservation anytime.
I'll give you
a ride back.
Blackwolf got Cally
to reveal his true nature.
He's a racist.
None of this
was for the sake
of the apache.
Never was.
It was always about cally.
It was about power
and manipulation.
Charles manson claimed
that he ordered his
followers to kill whites
in order to initiate
a race war.
Something he referred to
as helter skelter.
And he believed
in the aftermath
of helter skelter, the blacks,
who he deeme inferior,
would need a white man
to lead them.
There was a large
cache of guns
missing from
minton's house.
Why? Why would cally
suddenly need guns?
His whole m.o.
Is to fight a war
using the native
american methods.
Maybe he isn't trying
to fight a war.
Maybe he's trying
to start one.
The first attack
was designed to look like indians.
In an attempt
to manipulate the A.D.U.
to retaliate
against the reservation.
But they didn't.
How could they?
We had them put
under surveillance.
So cally tried
to provoke them further
by killing the head
of the A.D.U.
Minton and his family.
Right, but that
didn't work either
so now he wants to attack
the other side.
He's trying to provoke
the indians
by staging an adu attack
against them.
Call blackwolf.
We need to get to
the reservation.
The school is for our most
vulnerable target.
Killing kids ???
In 61, cochise
led his followers to fight..
put that away.
What?
You don't need it.
Use your baton.
The are many paths
to the same place.
Trust me.
Just so you know,
you sound like
a fortune cookie.
Split up.
Find them.
Hey.
Psst.
Big mistake.
Stay down.
I don't want to hurt you.
Down!
Don't move!
Don't shoot!
I give up!
You ok?
Just had to shoot
somebody, didn't you?
The children?
They're fine.
We got them out before they got here.
We took down these four.
Without firing a shot?
Captain america here
shot number 5.
You're welcome.
Number 6 is cut up
pretty bad.
I don't think
he's gonna make it.
At least i didn't
shoot him.
I think i'd rather
be shot.
There's an old
apache saying.
You can take many paths
to get to the same place.
Be with you in a second.
nice.
What's this?
Paul morris. He's in
the new york field office
if you ever need anything,
give him a call.
He'll take care of you.
This your way of saying
i can't take care
of myself?
No. It's my way of saying
i'm a jackass.
Yeah, well, it must be
hereditary.
Sean..
it's really important
that you do this your way.
You know, what you feel
is every bit as important
as what you think.
Dad knew that.
I forgot.
You reminded me, and..
thanks.
This is, uh,
a pretty messed up
going away present,
you know that?
Brother worries.
You need to get out
of the office more.
Tell me about it.
So I'm starved.
How's the food?
It's pretty good.
Let me fix you
something special.
I'm in your hands.
Want a beer?
Sure, man. Thanks.