Can you tell
me what happened
at the end of last
season of Medium?
Oh, it was very...
It was a really nice story.
Joe was held hostage.
There was gunshots.
There were five of us
in that room.
Only two of us
made it out alive.
So he was told by his lawyer
that he could actually sue.
My name is Cooper Conroy.
I'm an attorney, Mr. Dubois.
Can you talk for a moment?
Talk about what?
About the millions of dollars
I believe you're entitled to.
What is this? It's a liability waiver.
So you're saying that if
I don't sign these,
I can't come back to work?
Allison was begging
Neve Campbell,
the reporter chick, not to print
the truth about her.
That reporter had to be, like,
a little snitch.
You cannot run this story!
Debra!
Please!
What about
my life?!
My husband's life?
My children's lives?
And now Allison's whole life is
in turmoil and in jeopardy.
Well, the press is after her.
Can you talk about
your relationship
as a spiritual advisor
to the district attorney?
Do you actually
talk to dead people?
Her boss is about this close
to losing his job.
This new D.A. came in,
started cleaning house,
and no one seemed to have wanted
Allison's services anymore.
I'd like you all to meet an
old law school buddy of mine,
Tom Van Dyke, Assistant
District Attorney
out of Flagstaff
and a good friend.
Well, I went to work.
No Devalos.
He's just not there.
Turns out his friend
they brought in to help
is suddenly running the place.
He sends an assistant
overto me
to tell me that my part-time
consulting services
probably won't be needed
for the foreseeable future.
Look, I understand
that Manny is in hot water.
I know you're on
thin ice where you are,
but neither of you
takes my calls?
Allison, Manny is on a boat
in the Gulf of Mexico fishing.
And as for you, what do you
want me to say? You're toxic!
Given the way
things are going,
nobody wants to
hear your dreams.
Nobody wants to hear
from Allison Dubois.
Now they both don't have jobs.
How are they going
to survive?
I don't know
what they're going to do.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, that makes
no sense to me.
No. We've been
negotiating this deal
for three
and half months.
Now he's insisting
we close it this second?
No. You can't
conference him in right now.
I'm with Ben.
What? Uh, hold on.
I'm losing you.
Yeah. Hold on
a second.
Ben, come here, buddy.
Dad?
Yeah, uh...
Fine. All right,
put him through.
Ben?
Uh, no, no, sorry,
Mr. Rivercott.
Can you just
give me one second, please?
Yes, Mr. Rivercott.
I'm here.
Yes, sir, and I'm ready
to do some business.
Well, if that's all
that's standing
between us and a deal, sir,
I'm sure we can...
Ben?
Ben? Buddy, can you hear me?!
Ben?!
Oh, God. Ben!
Ben?
Ben! Ben!
Ben!
Oh.
What?
Did you say
something?
Dream.
A little boy.
A kidnapping, I think.
Oh.
What are you
going to do?
Here. You want
to call someone?
There's no one to call.
Don't you reiember?
Oh, yeah.
I guess for a
minute there,
I was hoping that
was just a dream.
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
片名:MEDIUM 第4季第1集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：个人ID
校对：个人ID
时间轴：约克
Oh, no, not again.
Ugh!
We really need
to have a boy.
Mm...
And in the forecast-
oudy, windy and cold.
I'm just saying, I
don't think it's fair.
Fair? I don't think
it's about fair.
I mean, if what you're
saying is true, I'm sure
it's just 'cause they
want to know that
whoever they give the lead
role to can handle the pressure
and the
responsibility.
Being in a new school
and balancing that
with all the homework.
So you agree?
You think it's just fine that
because I'm in the ninth grade,
and it's my first
year in high school
that I shouldn't play the
lead in the school play?
Even though
it#s the perfect play for me
and it's the perfect role
for me and I'm perfect for it?
Here, babe.
It's no good.
I'm sorry, baby.
That's all the peanut
butter we have left.
Mom,
what do you think?
What do I think?
I think just because all
the other kids are saying
ninth graders never get the
lead doesn't make it so.
I think you ought
to wait to see
that you didn't get the part
before you get all upset.
Great. Just my luck.
When I'm in ninth grade,
they do The Sound of Music.
And then, when I'm in tenth,
they'll do The Wiz or
Dreamgirls. Just watch.
Yeah, it's tough
looking like you.
And now authorities
and the young man's family
are asking for your help.
Oh, no.
A $20,000 reward
is being offered
for any information leading
to the recovery of Ben Goldman,
and both the Chief of Police
and acting District Attorney
Van Dyke have pledged...
D.A.'s Office.
Of course, the election
is still several months away,
and just to put some things
in perspective,
only about 32% of the
eligible electorate
is even aware that there's
going to be an election.
But among those
that are,
slightly more than 70%
recognized your name,
and about half of them
indicated that
they were favorably disposed
to seeing you continue...
Excuse me a moment.
Can you tell him
it's about the
missing Goldman boy?
I- I think I may
be able to help.
I think I may
know some things.
As soon as he returns
to the office,
I'll give him the message.
And you have
all my num...?
Boy and girls?
Okay, I need
everyone's attention,
because today
we have a special guest.
So our mouths are closed
and our eyes and ears are open.
And now-
and this is pretty exciting-
I'm going to introduce
a real, live police detective.
From our very own Phoenix
Police Force, let's welcome
Detective...
Is it, uh, Scanlawn?
Scanlon.
I feel like
I'm having a nervous breakdown.
Who am I speaking with?
It's Allison.
It's Allison Dubois.
Uh, please don't hang up.
I know you're not supposed
to take my calls.
I know I'm persona non grata.
Allison, we've been
through this.
I had a dream
about the Goldman boy.
I called the District Attorney's
Office.
I left Van Dyke a message.
I know he's never going
to call me back.
I called the Phoenix P.D.
I can't get a detective
to take my call.
I don't know what to tell you.
Well, I have to do something.
I can't see what I see,
know what I know,
and not do anything with it,
not tell anyone.
I can't go buy peanut butter and
pretend that I didn't see it.
Allison, they've got me doing
public relations now.
I'm about the furthest thing
there is
from a homicide detective.
You are the closest thing
to a homicide detective I know.
Tell me what you saw.
It happened in a toy store.
They already know that.
He used a doll, a marionette,
to lure the boy.
Allison, none
of this stuff matters.
It has to matter.
Why would I see it?
Why would someone bother
to show it to me
if it didn't matter?
Did you see him?
Did you see the man
who took the boy?
Not from the front.
He was wearing a...
green jacket.
A green denim jacket.
All right, fine. Green denim.
I'll tell someone.
Whether they listen,
whether they care-
I can't control that.
Hi.
Have a seat.
Last time you applied
for unemployment benefits?
God.
Uh, sometime in the eighties.
Hmm.
Um...
Engineer?
Aerospace.
So, um, what are we
doing to find work?
I'm sending out
letters of inquiry.
I'm, you know, calling friends
and going to conferences.
It's tough because
there are really only
two other aerospace companies
in the area that do the work
in the fields
that I specialize in, so it's...
I got three kids in school,
so we-we really don't want
to leave the area.
You're in a
tough spot.
Made good
money, too.
Never see it
coming, do you?
"Dubois. "
Oh, my goodness.
Dubois?
I take that back.
Maybe you did
see it coming.
I mean,
maybe your
wife did anyway.
$111.80.
All right. Thanks.
Oh, ma'am, that
card's being denied.
Do you have
another card?
No, I-I don't need another card.
There's a mistake.
I know this card's good.
I just paid the bill
a couple weeks ago.
Is there a problem?
I have things I need to do.
There's no problem.
We're just
sorting something out here.
Okay, ma'am, that card's just
going to keep being denied.
And if you swipe
it one more time,
I'm just going to get a message
to take it away from you.
You got cash?
Well, not enough
for all this stuff.
Okay.
All right, let's just figure
out what you really need, okay?
My name? Rolen.
Allison Rolen.
Uh, I think I may have
some information ???
$240 a week.
You work for the same
company 15 years.
The government takes thousands
of dollars every month,
and then when you get fired,
when you can't get work,
they give you $240 a week.
And act like you really ought
to be ashamed of yourself
for even asking for it.
The guy at the
unemployment office
recognized our last name.
He knew about you.
Oh...
Maybe I should take
Marie out of preschool.
I'm home now.
It's not like
she has to be there.
No, don't do that.
We're not there yet.
Hell, haven't you
been listening?
I just got us $240 a week
to blow on anything we want.
Oh.
* You see I go by the code
Of the doctor of the mix *
* These reasons
I'll tell ya why *
* You see I'm six foot one
I'm tons of fun *
* And I dress to a "T"
* You see I got more clothes
than Muhammad Ali *
* And I dress so viciously *
* I got bodyguards,
I got two big cars *
* That definitely
ain't the whack *
* I got a Lincoln Continental
and a sunroof Cadillac *
* So after school,
I take a dip in the pool *
* Which is really on the wall *
* I got a color TV so I can see
the Knicks play basketball *
* Hear me talk about checkbook
* Credit card, more money... *
Hey, what is it?
Why are you
breathing so hard?
What'd you see, hmm?
He's white.
Or at least
his feet are white.
What I think he's doing
to that little boy...
Is there anyone to call?
Is there anything to do?
No.
SCANLON
What's that, Bobby, a joint?
Two wrongs don't
make a right, Bobby.
I know, they make a left.
Just say "no. "
Eat me, stupid.
Haven't you heard?
Drugs are bad.
Puppets.
They, uh...
they want me to try
'em with the older kids.
Third graders.
I hate my life.
You're still a detective.
What are you talking about?
What it says on my badge?
No. Yes.
If you think you know something,
if you think you can help...
I don't know anything.
But you said Allison Dubois
called you with... With nonsense,
with nothing that matters.
She told me that it
happened in a toy store.
The father told us it
Said the guy was wearing
a green denim jacket.
Besides, I'm on Romper
Room duty. It's not my case.
Make it your case.
Go to the store.
Look around.
Flash your badge.
Talk tg people.
You're not listening.
I'm on the Reefer Madness tour.
You're not listening,
after hours.
Look at the crime
scene photos.
Go see the family.
People don't get irate
because there are
too many cops asking questions.
Tell them the mayor's
office sent you.
Tell them I sent you.
You don't get it.
This new D.A...
Let me handle the new D.A.
*... six foot one
And I'm tons of fun *
* And I dress to a "T" *
* You see I got more clothes
than Muhammad Ali *
* And I dress so viciously *
* I got bodyguards *
* I got two big cars
that definitely *
* Ain't the whack *
* I got a Lincoln Continental
and... *
Hello?
WOMAN
Allison Rolen?
I'm... sorry,
may I ask who's calling?
This is Ameritips.
You called our 800 number
and left us some
information about ???
I'm following up.
My name is Cynthia Keener.
Uh, right, um...
What can I do for you?
Actually, I was wondering
if we could meet.
You could come
to our Phoenix office,
or I could come to your home.
Do we really have to meet?
Well, I do need to follow up.
I guess it really depends
if you're serious.
Serious about the information
you gave us.
Serious about the reward.
Uh, right, the reward.
I completely forgot.
I really don't feel comfortable
meeting at my home.
You know the Scottsdale Fashion
Square Mall?
How about we meet
in the food court?
Say tomorrow at 11:00?
Okay.
How will I recognize you?
Don't worry, I'll find you.
That's what I do for a living.
Hey, girls!
Come on, hurry up!
Daddy's going to pick up Marie
and Bridgette
and meet us at home.
Hannah, honey, do you
need a ride home?
Oh, my God!
I got called back
for Maria this afternoon!
Oh, my God!
I know!
Hey.
You nervous?
Terrified.
Look at her.
Brooke Greene?
I know her.
Yeah, well...
she's in the tenth grade,
and I hear she's amazing.
She's perfect for this.
I don't stand a chance.
Hey, the idea is to psych
her out, not yourself.
Never mind.
Hey, Brooke.
Hi, Hannah.
What's going on?
I just...
I know you're going
out there in a minute,
and I don't want you
to get rattled.
Rattled bx what?
Ariel's mother
is out there.
Okay.
And you know who
she is, right?
Yeah.
Well, she's Ariel's mother.
And the thing is,
she already knows
her daughter's
getting the part.
I mean, that's why
she's sitting out there.
I just...
I didn't want you to see her
and have it mess you up.
Brooke Greene? You're on.
Thing is, we just closed,
and it's pouring out.
Couldn't we do this
another time?
I mean, come on,
you guys were here
for two days. My
employees are still crying
about all the
wages they lost.
Yeah, well,
the store's closed now,
and no one's losing a dime.
How about you just
take 20 minutes
and walk me through it?
What's in this direction?
Two bathroom doors, both locked,
employees lounge and lockers,
warehouse space
for additional inventory.
Other cops already
been through it twice.
Yeah, well,
you know what they say.
Third time's a charm.
Who do you say
you work for again?
The Mayor?
That's what I said.
I hate him.
Oh, don't tell me
we have a leak.
I just had this damn roof
re-tarred a month ago.
You use red tar?
What are you talking about?
What's above us?
Toys, what do you think?
Who's up here?
Someone's up here!
It's the mice.
When it rains
they come inside.
It's the mice.
Am I above the spot
where that drop hit me?
You gotta go
towards the rail.
Hey, hey, take it
easy up there!
I gotta sell that stuff.
He's not here.
Is he?
What are you
talking about? Who?
I don't know.
I think I was asleep.
Then I felt it.
His head on my chest.
He was lying on top of me.
And it was so real.
I mean, I...
I could smell his hair.
Why doesn't someone call?
Ask for ransom?
Or the the police?
Why don't the police call?
Someone.
I think he's gone.
I think he just came to me...
said "good-bye. "
I think that's what it was.
What? What is it?
He's dead.
I think the little
Goldman boy is dead.
No... I don't
think so, honey.
I just got into bed.
I just got done
watching the news.
They didn't say
a word about it.
What are you
talking about?
It's the middle
of the night.
No, Allison, it's 11:45.
You went to bed
just after 10:00.
I stayed up to
watch the news.
I'm telling you.
Who you calling?
I'm calling Scanlon.
Maybe he knows something.
Hello?!
I'd like to speak
with the officer in charge.
Hello?!
Would someone point me towards
the lead detective, please?
That would be me.
You?
You found the boy?
I was unaware
that you were even assigned
to this case, Detective.
Some friends in
the mayor's office
asked me to look into it.
Kind of like an
after school project.
Who knows?
Who else knows about this?
Just me and the
store manager.
Coroner's on his way.
Other than that...
You haven't spoken
to any press?
I called your office,
the District
Attorney's Office.
That's the protocol.
That's what I did.
This boy's parents
are in a lot of pain.
I'd like to try to
keep this under wraps
for another 12 hours or so,
at least until the
coroner and forensics
have had a chance
to take a look.
Maybe generate some clues,
get us closer to the
animal who did this.
I think that would make
this a much easier pill
for the parents to swallow.
For everyone to swallow.
Certainly make
for a better story in the press.
Can I count on your
discretion, Detective?
Can I sleep on it?
No. Not unless you plan
on sleeping alone.
Let's keep your
girlfriend out of this.
I'm tired mf her calls
on your behalf.
I need to know if
I can count on you.
I don't know what to tell you.
It's after midnight and I have
to get up in five hours
to talk to a group
of student crossing guards
about the importance
of walking on the green
and not in between.
Really?
I'm sure I could
find somebody else
to take care of
that for you.
A valuable man like you, you
should be out in the field.
A valuable man like you
should be leading
investigations for my office.
It's not here.
What's not there?
Something I was
sure would be.
So now you're
the star of the play?
It's high school.
There are no stars, but...
I'm the lead.
Cool.
Do you know where Daddy is?
No, I agree with you, Mom.
Yes.
No, I agree with Oprah.
In a civilized society,
women should wear underwear,
particularly
if they're public figures,
getting out of cars,
being photographed.
Mom...
Yeah, Mom... Mom. Mom.
I need to borrow some money.
Allison Rolen?
Have I made a mistake?
Cynthia Keener.
Ameritips.
Allison?
Hi.
I thought I was going
to meet you ten minutes
at the food court.
Oh, I just, well, um...
I was early,
and I saw you standing there.
At Least I thought it was you
standing there.
I'm kind of intuitive that way.
Is-is this all right?
I'd be happy to wait till 11:00.
Oh, this is fine,
this is fine.
I know it sounds so ancient,
but I wanted to be a nun.
You just don't hear that
anymore, but I did.
I wanted to wear a habit
and sit in the front row
Christmas mass,
get mentioned in
Father's sermons.
So I took temporary vows of
poverty, celibacy and obedience.
And I don't know what happened
to the vows of poverty
and celibacy,
but it soon became very evident
that I had no talent whatsoever
for obedience.
So, then I decided to go
into the family business,
become a cop.
I went to college,
I studied criminology.
Me, too.
Back then, for a woman,
it was... tough.
Anyway, I saw an
ad for Ameritips.
And I've been an investigator
with them for 20 years.
And I got my wish-
I'm poor, I'm celibate,
and I don't have to
listen to anyone.
How many people phoned in
about the Goldman boy?
We logged about 1,400 calls.
1,400 calls?
Most of those
are cranks
and others are people fishing
for the reward money.
The credible ones
really jump out at you,
which is why I'm here.
"Green, denim jacket. "
That's rather
specific, isn't it?
Of course, it's not
the kind of clue
that's going to
get you a reward.
Oh, I don't care
about the reward.
I don't care about the money.
The money would be good-
it would be great- but...
I really can't get
that little boy out of my mind.
I know what you mean.
This is a ground floor
plan of the toy store
where the Goldman
boy was abducted.
I wonder if you
wouldn't mind
indicating with the
cursor where you were
when you saw the
man take him.
What do you mean?
Well, the "X" here
is where Mr. Goldman said
his son was standing
the last time he saw him.
And this green "X" here
is the position of the father.
Where would you have been?
I mean, you would have had
to have been fairly close
to see that the jacket
was denim.
Were you in the store at all,
Allison?
Enjoy your iced tea.
You should Google me.
My married name is Dubois.
Allison Dubois.
D- U-B-O-I-S.
I know what I'm talking about.
The jacket is green.
And the man who took him?
He likes to dance.
And...
I think the little boy is dead.
You think the
little boy is dead?
Well, I work for the parents,
and I think I would know
if the little boy is dead.
I think you're one of the
cruelest people I've ever met.
Well, I'm not trying to be.
I saw his spirit
visit his parents last night.
You saw?
Look me up.
It's on your computer.
Right there
for all the world to see.
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe.
Bridge.
Catch a tiger by the toe.
I know what I want for
Christmas. If he hollers...
I want my own room.
...let him go.
What are you doing?
Choosing who's going
to take me to school.
Well, now that you guys
don't have to be anywhere
in the morning...
I miss work.
Me, too.
What do you mean
there's no evidence, Detective?
This, this little boy's body
is covered with evidence.
He is drenched in blood.
Was he shot? Was he stabbed?
Poisoned.
Forced to ingest something-
we don't know what yet-
that very rapidly brought
on massive dehydration,
all the fluid in his
body is just gone.
The skin tissue is nothing
but a hard crust.
The blood you see there
came from his eyes,
his nose, his mouth,
and his anus.
That's enough, Detective.
We're gonna begin
reinterviewing
all the store employees
this morning.
I'm hoping
that fairly soon
the lab will be able to tell us
the exact nature of the poison.
That should certainly help
point us towards
whoever might have done this.
I don't think we can keep
a lid on it much longer.
I know you're not looking
forward to calling the parents.
I'm just afraid if we don't...
Too many people are aware-
cops, lab technicians-
for the media not to find out.
We don't have a single clue?
We don't have a single lead
on who this might be?
Well, there is one, but it's...
not much to hang your hat on.
I'm not even sure
if it's credible.
I need something for the press.
He may have been wearing
a green, denim jacket.
You found a fiber?
Allison Dubois had a dream.
Sir?
I'll, uh, call the parents,
I'll notify the media
the boy is dead.
There are no leads
at the present time.
This shocking news just in.
The Coroner's office confirming
that the body of Ben Goldman,
that young boy reported missing
since last week,
was apparently discovered by
authorities sometime yesterday.
Details of the discovery are not
being shared with reporters,
nor is there
any press conference scheduled
at this time.
* I need someone *
* Older and wiser
* Telling me what to do
* You are 17
* Going on 18 *
* I'll *
* Depend *
* On you. *
I could never do that.
What are you talking about?
You have the part.
Yeah...
but nobody was more surprised
than I was when it happened.
I was sure
it was going to be you.
What?
Your mother didn't tell you?
Tell me what?
She seemed to think
you knew.
you dreamt it
and made it so.
There was no use
in even trying...
Well, I didn't dream it.
The first I heard about you
being called back was
when you told me.
The first...
I heard about you
getting the part was
when you got it.
Mom, this girl
is Maria.
Hi, Mom.
Hey!
I thought you guys were
here the whole time.
Daddy let us play
at the park
until the Police came
and kicked us out!
Turns out the place closes
at dark,
which makes no sense to me.
Where are High School kids
supposed to go
and do the things
they can't do at home
if the park is closed?
Dad!
Did you grab the mail?
Yeah.
Why, you expecting
something?
I thought maybe
Mom... Grandma...
might have sent
me something.
Oh, what?
Joe?
I asked her
for a loan.
I tried to
convince her
it was gonna be cheaper
than bail.
Oh, Joe...
She said she was gonna
think about it.
Talk to her
accountant.
I guess I was just
kind of hoping
that her answer would
be in the mail.
It's the mice.
When it rains
they come inside.
It's the mice!
Am I above the spot
where that drop hit me?
You gotta go
towards the rail.
Hey, hey!
Take it easy
up there!
I gotta sell
that stuff!
Come on, pick up your phone.
Allison, it's
barely 6:00.
He's probably
sleeping.
The nut.
I don't know.
He's not taking my calls lately.
He hasn't been returning
them either.
Hi. This is
Detective Lee Scanlon.
Leave a message
and I'll call you back.
I mean, what is it
that you want him to say?
What is it that you
want him to tell you?
I mean, you dreamt
the boy was a mouse.
But clearly... he's not a mouse.
Well... it means something.
Who you calling now?
DiNovi.
Lynn? It's Allison.
I need to speak
to him.
Um, he's not here.
Yeah, he left a half hour ago.
He's at the toy store.
They're reinterviewing
all the employees
before the place opens
this morning.
You want the address?
Now the last time
you spoke to police
you mentioned that you
do open the store
Mondays and
Thursdays
and that therefore
you do have a key.
Is that correct Mr...
Mr. Kaye?
There's a lady here
to see you.
Detective,
I'm Cynthia Keener.
I'm an investigator
with Ameritips.
Well...
you're here early.
Didn't expect to see you
till rehearsal this afternoon.
Actually, that's
why I came by.
I need you to listen
to something.
What do you mean?
You want to sing something
for me?
Not exactly.
Brooke?
Now, Mr. Kaye,
obviously, what we
need from you is
someone to corroborate
your whereabouts
for the 24 hours prior tk the
discovery of the Goldman boy.
You have
another visitor.
A mouse?
It means something.
I'm sorry.
Not to me. Neither does
the green denim jacket
or the dancing.
I don't know what to tell you,
Allison,
but you can't hang around here.
I'm just starting to get some
traction with the new D.A.
If he finds out you were here... Fine.
Maybe you could do me a favor.
Maybe you could give me a call
when you're done with all this.
Or maybe, uh...
maybe you could pick up
the phone when I call you.
I could probably swing that.
I miss Devalos.
Me, too.
* Girls in white dresses
* With blue satin sashes
* Snowflakes that stay
on my nose and eyelashes *
* Silver white winters
* That melt into springs... *
I don't understand.
When we get back home...
what are we gonna do?
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I just can't spend
another day waiting
for permission
to be who I am.
I'm a lawyer.
I practice law.
It's all I really know.
And if I can't do it
for the people,
I'll open up my own office.
I'll start my own practice.
* These are a few
of my favorite things *
* Raindrops on roses
* And whiskers on kittens *
* Bright copper kettles
and warm woolen mittens *
* Brown paper packages tied up
with strings... *
Miss Heath...
apparently you also
have a key.
* These are a few
of my favorite things... *
What the hell is that?
Who...
Somebody unlocking
the warehouse door.
* When the dog bites *
* When the bee stings
* When I'm feeling sad... *
Well, I don't
understand.
I thought everyone who had
keys to the building
were here this morning.
Well, yeah.
Everyone
who works for us.
Oh.
Sorry.
You, you guys having a meeting?
Nobody told me.
And you are?
Oh, the exterminator.
We have a contract.
Put some poison out
the other day.
I'm just back
to pick up the mice.
The mice?
Mice.
Rats.
They've had a real problem
with them.
See, I put the poison out
a couple of nights ago.
But thing is,
once they eat that stuff,
it makes them really stiff
and bloody.
So you really want
to get rid of them
before it starts
to smell,
and it gets
into the air-conditioning.
Is it okay? I...
I won't make too much noise.
We should question him.
He has a key.
Uh, you know what?
I left my gloves
in my other jacket.
I just gonna run
to my truck.
Uh, you mind if I come with?
Yeah.
A little bit.
Who the hell are you?
I'm a detective
with the Phoenix Police force.
I'm investigating the murder
of a young boy.
I- I'd like to ask you
some questions.
* I simply remember... *
What was the color
of that other jacket?
Was it green?
* My favorite things
* And then I don't feel... *
* So bad! *
Hello.
Green denim jacket.
He was doing
a little dancy thing
when he first walked
in the room.
Exterminator.
Which I guess explains
the mouse.
So what are you doing?
Me, I'm just, uh...
I'm paying bills.
Well, no, actually...
Lee, someone's at the door.
This guy Van Dyke-
he's an idiot.
Let me try and talk to him
about you.
Let me see
if we can't get you back here...
at least part-time.
Raally. So they making snowballs
in hell now?
Lee, let me call you back.
I Googled you.
Apparently I owe
you an apology.
$2,500?
This is a personal check.
This is your check.
Why are you doing this?
I couldn't get you
the reward.
Um, you didn't find him-
I mean, your clue didn't
really find him-
but I thought
maybe we could
keep in touch.
Perhaps come to some sort
of an arrangement.
Not between you
and Ameritips,
but between you and me.
I'm an investigator,
and someone
like you...
I have a feeling
that we could do each other
a lot of good.
And as I mentioned
the other night,
I'm really quite intuitive, too.
I'll be calling.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入