Previously on Medium:
Sorry to interrupt.
Alison Dubois, this is Special...
Edward Cooper, of the FBI.
I'm very familiar with your work,sir.
I had a dream about this guy last night.
What's he got that I don't?
An amazing reputation as a
criminal profiler, for one thing.
You see things,don't you?
I dedicated myself to getting
inside the minds of killers.
It wasn't my choice.
You go into the heads of murderers
whether you want to or not.
I know what you did.
I know you put two
bullets into Richard Gomez,
and I will find a way to expose you.
Housekeeping!
You want turn-down service?
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Medium
Season04 Episode12
as of now,my combi. the combination of my amplification
mirror optics and unique software logarithms
make a consumer-grade solar
cell 10% more efficient.
At least 10% more efficient.
With additional funding, I think I can get
that number closer to 15,maybe even 20%.
Very impressive.
I'd fund your project.
Really?
And how much money do you have?
Including the redeemable bottles I'm
bringing back to the market, about $17.
You know what? I'm gonna
stick with Buchanon-Lockhart.
I think they're gonna
want to fund you,too.
Oh,they'd better.
They're the only venture capital
firm I could get a meeting with.
If this presentation doesn't go well,
I'm pretty much gonna have to hold
a bake sale to raise the capital.
You reading Cooper's book again?
I was just thumbing through
it when you were in the shower.
I just can't get that
dream out of my head.
I tried calling the FBI this morning.
They wouldn't tell me where he
was or what he was working on.
Well,I guess they're not in the habit of
supplying the whereabouts of
their agents to anyone who asks.
Guess not.
Well,even if you could
find him,what would you do?
What would you say to him?
How are you gonna stop whatever
it is you saw from happening?
You know the drill. This
guy-- he kills killers.
It's still killing.
No,I know. I just... I-I...
You know,you're right.
And you did let him
get away with it once.
Yeah. Don't think that
hasn't kept me up nights.
Mom!
Mom,I need you!
Bridgette's wiggling her
teeth while I'm trying to eat.
So what? Do you have a problem with
a kid trying to make some extra money?
Okay. What is the matter?
What is the commotion all about?
Bridgette's teeth are loose and she's wiggling them
with her fingers trying to get them to come out.
It's disgusting.
It is not disgusting if each of these
teeth is worth a dollar under my pillow.
Bridgette,honey, you're supposed to just
wait for your teeth to fall out on their own.
You're not supposed to use
your fingers to loosen them.
I don't know,Mom.
I've been hearing about how
bad the economy is and...
hereI am,sitting on 26 bucks.
I can make a difference.
That's the stupidest
thing I have ever heard.
All right,stop it.
Stop it,stop it. Listen.
Daddy has a really big day.
I want no more commotion.
I want no tugging.
I want no nuh-uh'ing. I want silence.
I'm here because the District Attorney
has asked me to bring my expertise to bear
on a potentially very difficult case.
I arrived in Phoenix
yesterday, but I've already...
concluded my preliminary
analysis of the police files.
Oh,my God.
Oh,well,this must be important.
I don't know if you've heard, but we've
got a serial killer here in Phoenix.
I may have heard a little
something about that.
What's on your mind,Allison?
Agent Edward Cooper.
I know he's in town working on the case.
I need to know what he's up to.
That's Gretchen Ballard.
She was a hooker,worked
the area around Shadyside.
Seven months ago a garbageman
found her body in an alley.
Somebody'd stabbed her 26 times.
Oh,God.
A buddy of mine caught the case.
He never solved it, but he always
remembered one little detail.
When they found Gretchen Ballard's body,
she was wearing a silver wedding band.
Really? A prostitute
with a wedding band?
That's weird,right?
Well,two days ago, some kids found
the body of another prostitute.
Amanda Boone.
Also stabbed more than
20 times. Also wearing...
a silver wedding band?
Okay,that's weird.
Cooper's in town to help us determine
if the two cases are connected.
He went through all the old
case files, and he found a third,
unsolved murder that's
a potential match.
A little over a year ago, a pro named Nina
Jarvis was stabbed to death in Glendale.
The ME's report said she was
wearing a silver wedding band.
Nobody thought much of it at the time,
but now Cooper wants to take a look.
So where's Cooper now?
Why does that matter so much to you?
If you've seen something that ties to
this case, why don't you just tell me?
I'll make sure word gets to Cooper.
Because I can't.
Cooper's the only person
I can talk to about this.
Now,where is he? Please.
Right about now, Cooper's getting
a little face time with Nina Jarvis,
our potential third victim.
They're exhuming her body to see
if her ring matches the other two.
Now,you didn't hear it from me, but
she's buried at Sycamore Hill Cemetery.
If you drive over there now, I'm sure
you'll find what you're looking for.
Mr. Dubois?
Can I get you anything to drink?
Oh,no,thank you. I'm fine.
It's a good sign, you know.
The fact that they're still talking.
It means your presentation went well.
Miss Doyle.
I'm sorry,Mr. Dubois.
As we mentioned in the meeting, we've already got
a couple of competitive projects in the pipeline.
We're worried about overlap.
It's okay. Really.
Uh,just grateful you were
willing to hear me out.
For what it's worth...
I fought for you.
I happen to think your idea's a lot
smarter than the ones we're backing.
Well,for what it's
worth, I appreciate that.
I just want to reiterate what an honor it
is to be working with you, Agent Cooper.
I've followed your career for many years,
even had the pleasure of reading your books.
I want to assure you that if we do
learn that these murders are connected,
my office is prepared to offer you whatever
resources you may need to catch the perpetrator.
And if it would be at all helpful,
I'm happy to liaise with the mayor's office
on your behalf, perhaps even the media.
That's quite a selfless
gesture,Mr. Van Dyke,
offering to stand in front
of all those cameras for me.
It's a match to the other rings.
Looks like you're going to end
up in front of a camera after all.
I'll inform the mayor.
Mrs. Dubois, what a pleasant surprise.
Welcome back to Phoenix, Agent Cooper.
I wish I could say I was
glad to be back in town,
but,unfortunately,you can
see that I'm here on business.
Speaking of which, I can't tell
you how disappointed I was to hear
that you're no longer consulting
for the District Attorney's office.
I'm sure you are.
I mean it.
I know how very good
you are at what you do.
I suspect I know it better than most.
I don't have much time, Agent
Cooper, so if you'll forgive me,
I'll just cut right to the chase.
I know what you're doing here in
Phoenix and I'm here to tell you
I'm not going to let
you get away with it.
You're not going to let me get
away with catching a serial killer?
I'm not going to let you kill him.
I had a dream and I
saw you murder a man.
I'm not sure what you think you saw,
but the fact of the matter is
I'm not like the men that I hunt.
I don't do what I do out of compulsion.
I do it out of necessity.
I only take action
when the system fails.
But I assure you my intention
is to bring this man to justice,
not deliver my own brand of it.
I know what I saw.
I saw you sneaking
into a man's hotel room.
You had your gun out.
I saw the look on his face
when you were closing in on him.
I'm sorry.
Did you just say that
you saw this man's face?
Can you describe him to me?
I know what you're thinking.
You don't want to give me a description
of a man you think I'm going to murder.
Prioritize,Mrs. Dubois.
Help me protect the citizens
of Phoenix from a serial killer.
Then you can worry about protecting
the serial killer from me.
Agent Cooper?
Is this woman bothering you?
Quite the contrary, Mr. Van Dyke.
Mrs. Dubois and I are just
working out the terms of a deal.
I'm sorry. I don't
understand. What kind of deal?
I'm assuming that your offer to provide me with
whatever resource I might need still stands.
Of course it does.
Good. Because I need her.
I need Allison Dubois.
Boy,have I not missed seeing that
sort of stuff around the house.
Sorry. They're Agent Cooper's.
He wanted me to look over everything he
had, make sure I was ready for tomorrow.
Gotta hand it to that guy.
He must be one hell of a salesman.
Salesman?
I'm just saying that this morning
you couldn't live with the possibility
that he might take another life.
And,tonight,he's your new partner.
He swore to me that he wouldn't
harm the man who killed these women.
You at least got a pinky-swear
to that effect,right?
'Cause,without one, he's really under
no legal obligation to stop killing.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't tease.
Frankly,I'm just glad that someone in
this house is bringing home a paycheck.
Honey,I'm sorry it didn't work
out with those venture capitalists.
I guess I could learn a thing or two
about salesmanship from Agent Cooper,huh?
Oh,come on. You know you
gave a good presentation.
They told you it was a good idea.
Yeah? Well,that and a quarter...
You know,if you're looking for investors,
maybe you might want to try Bridgette.
Well,she's having quite a
run with the tooth fairy.
A dollar a tooth.
You know,maybe if we feed
her nothing but taffy...
That's not funny.
I'm sorry.
Having had some time to familiarize myself with the
forensic evidence gathered from the three victims,
as well as the manner in
which they were killed,
I've prepared a very preliminary psychological
profile of the man we're looking for.
His methodology indicates he has
deep-seated issues with women.
He probably compensates for his
inability to deal with the opposite sex
by concentrating excessively
on his own appearance.
He's not an attractive
man, but he's a vain one.
I wouldn't be surprised if he adheres
to a rigorous exercise regimen.
Very impressive, Agent Cooper.
I'll give you that.
Hair color,eye color, approximate
age,height, and weight.
Given this level of detail, I take it we
now have a witness to one of the murders?
Let's just say that Mrs.
Dubois' consulting services
have already proven quite valuable,
and leave it at that.
You stand behind this composite then?
You're willing to stake
your reputation on it?
Why,Mr. District Attorney, I
thought we were in this together.
I'll make sure it's distributed then.
I've asked Mrs. Dubois
to work from here today.
Go through your mug books, see
if any faces jump out at her.
She's welcome to any
vacant desk in the bullpen.
- That'll be fine.
- I'm afraid that's not quite good enough.
Mrs. Dubois requires a certain
amount of quiet to do her job.
A certain amount of solitude.
I thought maybe you could put her
up in one of your private offices.
Agent Cooper...
Mr. Van Dyke.
I realize that you and
Mrs. Dubois have a history,
but surely you're willing to put that aside
in the interest of catching this killer.
After all...
I'd hate to have the
press get wind of the fact
that I was getting anything less
than your complete cooperation.
I believe we have an office
available on the second floor.
You're welcome to it.
That wasn't really necessary.
What wasn't?
That. Much as I love
watching that weasel squirm,
I didn't even have my own office
when Devalos was in charge.
Well,maybe he didn't value
your services as much as I do.
Well,while we're on the
subject of my services,
I had another dream about
our killer last night,
and you should know that your
profile was right on the money.
He was watching your press conference
while he adhered to his
"rigorous exercise regimen."
Did you see anything that
might help us locate him?
No,but he didn't look too happy
about having the darkest corners
of his psyche aired on television.
"Unhappy" is good, Mrs. Dubois.
If he's unhappy, he's that
much closer to making a mistake.
Mr. Dubois?
Hello.
I'm glad you found me.
My assistant's not always the
best when it comes to directions.
Please.
Well,I'm due back at the office, so
I'm going to get right to the point.
I'm here because I want to help you develop
your solar cell amplification system.
And I believe I have
the funding to do it.
Ms. Doyle,Meghan...
I don't know what to say. I
don't know how to thank you.
I don't know what you said to your
colleagues to bring them around,but...
Actually,I didn't say anything.
I'm sure they're just as dead-set against going
into business with you today as they were yesterday.
Then I'm afraid I'm a little confused.
You just said that you had the funding.
If the money's not coming from
Buchanon-Lockhart,then where...
Me,Mr. Dubois.
The money would be coming from me.
Like I told you yesterday,
I believe in your idea.
I think it's a money-maker.
And the truth is, I've been looking for
an opportunity like this for a long time.
I'm tired of making money
for Buchanon-Lockhart.
I want to go into business for myself.
I want to get my hands dirty.
I've saved about $300,000 just
waiting to hear the right idea.
And I think I've heard it.
Agent Cooper?
Agent Cooper,it's late.
I was going to head home.
Agent Cooper...
I see you've found my
high-tech security system.
I do it everywhere I go.
It's just something I use to make sure
that nobody's been in
my office while I'm gone.
It's a bit paranoid, I know.
But I'm afraid I just can't help myself.
Well,I went through
these files twice,sir.
Our killer's not in here.
I'm sorry.
Oh,no need for apologies.
Well,I just wish we were further along.
"Further along?"
Mrs. Dubois, because of you,
I have what could very well turn out to
be a physical description of the killer.
You've also given me reason to believe
that my profile of the man is accurate.
I think it's fair to say that because
of your involvement in this case,
I'm potentially weeks ahead
of where I'd normally be.
Well,thank you,sir.
I have to say it's been a long time since
anyone's taken my dreams so seriously,
especially here in the
District Attorney's office.
Well, shame on them for
ignoring your talents.
I would never be so obtuse.
I know what I have in you.
Good night,sir.
Good night.
Housekeeping. Do you
want turndown service?
Hello.
Allison,it's Lee Scanlon.
I'm sorry to wake you, but I knew
you'd want to hear this right away.
It's about Agent Cooper.
He was shot. Twice.
Oh,my God,no.
*********
Whoever killed Cooper didn't
leave much evidence behind.
Swept his hotel for fingerprints--
anything that might have DNA on it.
So far nothing.
Service weapon's missing,too.
We think the killer might have
taken it with him as a trophy.
I had it all wrong.
I thought I saw Cooper
hunting the killer.
The killer was really hunting him.
I hate to be the bearer of
even more bad news, but,uh...
Van Dyke wants to see you in his office.
Asked if you'd come
there as soon as you can.
I'm so sorry.
What did I tell you about apologies?
They're not necessary.
I wish I'd done more for you.
Mrs. Dubois,I only have
so many pep talks in me.
I've told you I'm happy with your work.
Now if it's all right with you,
I'd like to get down to business.
I'm going to be interviewing the
acquaintances of the most recent victim today,
and I'd like you to come with me.
Oh,sir...
I'm not sure you understand
what happened to you last night.
Well,actually,last night is a bit fuzzy.
Do you remember going home?
Going to your hotel room?
That man that you were looking for...
he was waiting there for you.
And he shot you twice.
And you... didn't survive.
This... this just can't be.
I don't know what you
think you're doing in here,
but those files are
no longer your concern.
And in light of Edward
Cooper's tragic death,
the Phoenix District Attorney's office
no longer has any need for your...
services. They're terminated,
effective immediately.
I need you out of the
building, Mrs. Dubois.
It's 11:00. What do you say?
I'm not ready yet.
The guy was a killer,Allison.
You couldn't tell me enough.
The guy was a killer.
That doesn't mean he
deserved what he got.
I got those papers
from Meghan Doyle today.
Turns out she has a rather flexible
definition of the word "partnership."
What do you mean?
On exchange for funding,
she wants 51% ownership.
I'm told that's a
non-negotiable figure.
I don't get it. That
only leaves you 49%.
Exactly. Minority share.
She's trying to buy
the right to be my boss.
Tell her no.
Yeah,it definitely crossed my mind.
I was also thinking
maybe I'd tell her yes.
I want to get on with it,honey.
I want to get on with my life.
I want to earn a living. I
want to accomplish something.
Do you want to give up
control of your idea?
No,of course I don't.
Then don't.
If Meghan Doyle thinks your idea
is great, somebody else will,too.
Somebody who's willing
to do it your way.
Okay.
Is that an official psychic prediction?
That's an official wife who
believes in her husband prediction.
What do you say?
It's past 11:00.
I'm just saying I thought the ending
was spectacularly stupid,that's all.
Fine,you don't like
romantic comedies. I get it.
I didn't say that.
The next time we go to the movies,
we'll see something about zombies.
Or ninjas.
Or ninjas fighting zombies.
You promise?
What's going on? You okay?
Yeah,I'm sorry. It was a bad dream.
More serial killer stuff?
No. It was a car accident.
- You need to call someone?
- No.
I don't know who they were.
I don't know where they were.
It's okay. Go back to sleep.
I'm going to get a glass of water.
COOPER: You have a
lovely home, Mrs. Dubois.
It's very you.
I wanted to apologize for
disappearing this morning.
I didn't quite have a
handle on my situation yet.
You know,if there's anything
you need me to do, maybe...
give a message to your loved ones.
Mrs. Dubois...
Are you forgetting that we
still have a killer to catch?
My own murder was unfortunate,yes, but it
hardly changes the nature of our collaboration.
Are you saying you're
here because of the case?
Why else would I be here?
My last moments were
extremely unpleasant.
Not because of the
considerable pain I was in,
but because,as far as I knew, I
wasn't going to close this case.
My killer reveled in that fact.
He stood over me as I
lay dying, taunting me.
He insisted that Gretchen Ballard and Amanda
Boone and Nina Jarvis were only the beginning;
that with with me out of the picture, no
one could stop him from taking more lives.
But with your help...
I'd like to show him
just how wrong he was.
Okay.
What would you like me to do?
To start with...
first thing this morning I want
you to go back to the police
and give them a description
of the man who killed me.
Okay. But I already did that.
You were there when we made the sketch.
Yes,I know. You told him
that he was a compact man...
long hair,hazel eyes, extremely fit.
And he was.
Well,no,actually,he wasn't.
The man who killed me
was short,middle-aged,
shaved head, bit on the pudgy side.
Frankly,I'm...
I'm a little embarrassed
that he got the drop on me.
I don't know whose face you've been
seeing in your dreams,Mrs. Dubois,
but he's not the killer
that we've been looking for.
******
I'm glad I caught you.
I need to talk to you about Cooper.
That's funny. I was just about to
call you about the very same subject.
A valet at the hotel where Cooper was staying
just got a look of your sketch of the killer.
He saw a guy who looked just like him peeling out of
the hotel parking lot the night Cooper was murdered.
Valet remembers the make
and model of the car,
and get this, he even got a
partial on the guy's license plate
because he thought the guy
might have been driving drunk.
Seems like a pretty good lead,right?
I was just about to go run it down.
Don't bother. The sketch is wrong.
What are you talking about?
The sketch came from you.
I don't know what to tell you.
Apparently,I got the wrong face.
Uh,and you know that because?
I know that because Cooper
came to see me last night.
And he saw the man who shot him and
it wasn't the person I described.
Okay,what do you want from me then?
A favor. I need to look
through the mug books again.
Why? You just got done telling me
you didn't see the killer's face.
Well,that's true I
didn't, but Cooper did.
Lynn,hey.
Sorry,it doesn't look like
lunch is in the cards today.
What am I doing?
You wouldn't believe it,
not in a million years.
His name is Donald Kessler.
Convicted of rape in '97.
Served ten years and
got out last spring.
Cooper's positive this is our guy?
He said there's no doubt about it.
Well,according to this, our friend Mr. Kessler
skipped out on his parole about six months ago.
Present whereabouts unknown.
It says here he's got
a sister in Glendale.
Maybe you could go talk to her and
see if she's heard from him lately.
Talk to people? Yeah,sure,I can do that.
Ask some questions--
not a problem.
Who knows,I might even
be able to find the guy.
Just try to remember, it's going to
take a whole lot more than the word of
a dead FBI guy for me
to actually arrest him.
Hey,partner.
Come on. Sit down. We have
some celebrating to do.
No,Meghan, I don't want a drink.
I'm not sure that I should even sit.
I just,I figured you deserved
to hear this in person.
Okay...
You found someone else, another firm,
somebody you think is better connected.
Willing to offer more capital?
No,no,it's not that.
For God's sake,sit down.
People are looking.
They think we're
lovers having a quarrel.
I'm sorry.
Meghan,uh...
I'm extremely flattered by
your interest in my proposal.
Um,I just... I didn't realize that you
were going to buy a controlling stake.
That's just not something
that I'm willing to give up.
I'm sorry.
But unless you're willing to rethink the 51-49
split, I don't see how I can do this with you.
Can I have a dirty martini?
Joe?
Gosh,you're going to turn me
downand make me drink alone?
Okay,fine. I'll have what she's having.
Someone win the lottery?
Ah,not quite.
One of Bridgette's teeth finally fell
out, so the Tooth Fairy owes her a dollar.
And all I've got is a ten, a five and...
89 cents.
I got wrinkled and non-wrinkled.
Martini,huh?
So how'd it go? How'd she take it?
Um,I signed the papers.
You're upset.
No,I'm not upset. I'm bewildered.
You told me you were
gonna turn her down.
I know,I know. And I,and I absolutely,
I should have talked to you first.
I just... she really wants it.
I don't know. When she started to tell
me about her plans for the business,
what she thought the upside would
be in three years and five years,
and I just can't explain it.
I just started to get a
really good feeling about her.
I guess you'd call it an intuition.
I mean, if anybody can understand going
with their intuition, it's you,right?
So what happened to "Let's be patient"?
What happened to being your own boss?
I don't know. Maybe I was
being a little naive about that.
According to her, there's no way that I
have the leverage to get a majority share
no matter who I sign with.
Probably wouldn't even
get close to 49% either.
Now,look,Al,I know this is out of
the blue, but tell me you're happy.
This is gonna be so much
better if you're happy with it.
I'm happy... as long as you are.
I am.
Well,then that's that.
We are officially happy.
Julia?
Julia? Baby?
You okay?
What just happened?
We were in a crash.
Somebody just hit us.
Stay here,okay?
I'm gonna go check on the other driver.
Hey,buddy? You okay?
Mrs. Dubois?
I found him, Mrs. Dubois.
I know where he is.
Where who is?
Donald Kessler, the man who murdered me.
He's at a
bar downtown--
the Old Stone Jug, 1818 Hamilton Street.
If you and Detective Scanlon go down
there right now, you'll find him.
You'll find evidence on him that
proves he murdered those women.
Move,Mrs. Dubois! We
haven't a moment to spare!
Wait a second. He said
it was the Old Stone Jug.
You sure it was this Old Stone Jug?
Well,1818 Hamilton Street.
This is absolutely the place.
Well,I don't know what
to tell you,Allison.
According to this,the place
got condemned back in '05.
No one's had a drink
here in a good long time.
Well,he couldn't have been clearer.
He said Donald Kessler
was here right now.
Honestly,I'm a little confused myself.
I know I never understood
exactly how your thing works,
but you always made it
sound like after you die,
you pretty much know everything
there is, was or ever will be.
So tell me, how does a dead guy,
especially one as smart as Edward Cooper,
make a mistake like this?
Oh,boy,this doesn't look good.
Wait. Pull over.
It's being handled.
I dreamt about this. Please pull over.
You wait here. I'll go get the scoop.
Looks a lot like the guy
in your sketch,doesn't he?
This is him. This is the
man I saw kill Cooper.
As much as I hate to disagree with
the ghost of a famous profiler,
that is the man who
killed Edward Cooper.
The name is Julian Pierce.
First cops on the scene found a duffel bag
on the seat of his car that had a gun inside.
They ran the serial numbers.
Turns out it was a
government-issued firearm:
Edward Cooper's
government-issued firearm.
What about Donald Kessler?
Donald Kessler didn't kill Cooper.
He didn't kill those three
prostitutes either. Julian Pierce did.
In addition to Cooper's gun,
they found a stash of photos.
Polaroids of
the dead women--
even a few close-ups of the wedding
bands he put on their fingers.
I don't know why Cooper claimed that Donald
Kessler killed them, but he was wrong.
Oh,no. No,he wasn't wrong.
He was lying to us.
He knew this was gonna happen.
That's why he tried to throw
us off of Julian Pierce's scent.
He knew if we arrested Pierce, before
tonight, he wouldn't have been in this car.
He wouldn't have died in this accident.
So you're saying this was a setup?
That Cooper sent you on a wild goose chase
to guarantee that this guy died tonight?
'Cause I have to tell you, Allison,
that sounds a lot like murder.
Not to Cooper.
To Edward Cooper, this was justice.
You should know, Mrs. Dubois.
The one thing I regret in
all this was lying to you.
Well,I can see that.
Look,you're all torn up inside.
I never intended for you to
come across that accident site.
And I certainly didn't want the death of
Julian Pierce weighing on your conscience.
I know how strongly you prefer working
within the confines of the justice system.
For what it's worth, I wasn't lying when
you first came to me at the cemetery.
I had absolutely no intention
of taking Julian Pierce's life.
But as you well know,
circumstances changed.
My death gave me a whole new...
perspective on the man and his actions.
New perspective.
I think you're underestimating
how well I know you, Agent Cooper.
This was revenge, pure and simple.
I won't deny I took a certain amount
of pleasure in Mr. Pierce's death.
But I assure you, what I did
tonight, I did for the greater good.
Tell yourself whatever you want.
I'm going to bed.
Ellen Hartley.
I beg your pardon?
She's a nurse at McCarren
State Penitentiary.
It's where Mr. Pierce would have ended up
had you and Detective Scanlon arrested him.
You'd like her,Mrs. Dubois.
She's a mother of three just like you.
In four years' time, Julian
Pierce was going to fake an illness
so he could spend the night
in the prison infirmary.
He was going to strangle Ellen Hartley.
I suppose he wanted just one more notch
on his belt before they executed him.
I don't believe you.
You're lying to me again.
It's all you've ever done.
If there was some way I
could prove it to you,I would.
But the fact of the matter
is you'll never know.
You'll never be certain
I did the right thing by facilitating
the death of Julian Pierce.
But I am.
I am absolutely positive
the world is a much better
place without him in it.
Why don't you just go away?
I'm not ready to move on just yet.
It occurs to me, Mrs. Dubois, that you
and I have a very unique opportunity.
This doesn't have to be
our last collaboration.
What are you talking about?
I can see a lot of
things from this side,
things I can't share
with anyone but you.
If I were to catch on
to another Julian Pierce,
you'd be in a unique position
to help me take care of it.
You want me to help you end more lives?
I want you to help me save lives:
potential victims,good people
who don't deserve to die.
It's so sad.
I'm sure at some point
you were a good man.
I don't know where you lost your way, but in
the end,you are no better than Julian Pierce.
You're a killer.
And before long, you're gonna wind
up in the same terrible place he is.
I would never help you.
Guess we won't know until we know.
Will we?
It's been a pleasure, Mrs. Dubois.
As always.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚