[J.D.] I was super-psyched to get
my scooter, Sasha, back from the shop.
But my new scooter insurance
hadn't kicked in yet,
so I was being extra cautious.
- [Sirens]
- [J.D.] Perfect.
Time for my morning slushie.
[Tires screeching]
Get out of the way!
The store's being robbed!
Freeze!
The wall! Hide behind the wall!
No!
[Gunfire]
Sasha!
All right, all right. OK.
There was a wall!
What's the matter with you?
Who's still shooting? She's down!
It's over!
- Is this gonna hurt?
- Don't be such a baby.
It's a magnetic image.
I apologize, Mr. Foster.
I'm a little upset.
My scooter, Sasha,
was assassinated this morning.
He was attached to that thing.
He used to wear a bracelet,
"Sasha forever."
Come on, Turk. It was just a joke,
and I only wore it for one week.
Whatever.
Now let's fire this baby up.
- [Machine humming]
- [Clanking]
OK, so I still wear the bracelet.
Idiot.
- Oh!
- [Clanking]
My watch!
- Hey, Carla!
- Earphones, Ted!
Sorry. Hey, Carla, did you hear
the lottery's up to a hundred million?
If I win that baby,
it's separate beds for me and my mom.
Yeah and you could spend
the other 99,999,000 on therapy.
What would you do with the money?
Carla, I can't believe
you're gonna be a mom.
I know. It was expensive,
but totally worth it. Right, baby?
Stupid lotto.
- Good morning, Mrs. Wilk.
- It's a great morning.
[Gasps] Whoa!
That is wrong. Care to join me
in a super-Ioud throat clear?
Absolutely.
One, two, three.
[Both clear throats]
Elliot, I can't believe
you would do that!
- What'd you do?
- Was it naughty?
[J.D.] When women want men
to completely zone out,
there's one thing
they can talk about...
Yesterday, I went shoe shopping
and there was this one pair
- of Manolo Blahniks...
- [both thinking] Shoe shopping.
Great, we can talk.
What were you thinking?
We kissed. I've been
treating his kid for a week now
and we hit it off, you know?
It started out with some flirting.
"Hi, I'm Dr. Reid."
"Why is there blood in my son's stool?"
- Huh?
- Whose stool?
- Strappy sandals.
- [Both thinking] Shoe shopping.
Continue.
[Elliot] And then I asked
where his wife was.
He said, "She's not with us."
And then, you know...
...blaah.
Cool. Oh, I almost forgot. Lace bra.
- Were they D's?
- Be specific.
Good news, Mr. Foster. The radiologist
said your scan is completely clear.
We'd like to keep you here for tests.
Whatever you say, doc.
[J.D.] Weird things
can happen in a hospital.
Like Doug not getting a dead body out
of his bed before rigor mortis sets in.
Give me a hand. He's not gonna fit
in the body bag like this,
so lie across his feet
and I'm going to push down his head
- and straighten him out.
- Fun!
And one, two, three!
- [Cracking]
- [Screams then grunts]
Ted?
[J.D.] The weirdest thing
is when a cool guy
who's fine and talking
to you one minute...
... is dead the next.
In hospitals, this happens a lot,
so you have to shake it off and move on.
Except when this happens...
Well, if it isn't
the Four Horsewomen of the Apocalypse.
There's a morbidity and mortality
conference tomorrow
to figure out who's responsible
for Foster's death.
And here's the exciting news:
I'm pretty sure it was one of you.
[Dramatic classical music ringtone]
You really gotta change
that cell phone ring.
Mom, not now.
# I can't do this all on my own
# No, I know I'm no Superman
# I'm no Superman #
[J.D.] So a patient was dead
and one of us was gonna be blamed.
[Dramatic classical music ringtone]
Dude, you've gotta change that ring.
You think so? Mom, not now.
[J.D.] With morbidity
and mortality conferences,
the first question sets
the tone for the day.
- Who the hell ate my scone?
- That would be me.
It was delicious.
My compliments to the little lady.
- I made those.
- I know.
Dorian, you admitted Mr. Foster
with coughing and shortness of breath,
is that correct?
Yes.
Mike check. Mike check.
And then what happened?
Dorian.
I'm ten feet away from you. Talk.
Mr. Foster had recently flown
to India where he had been exposed
to an outbreak of pertussis.
I was gonna check his labs,
but first I had to visit
another patient, Mr. Sutton.
So, Mr. Sutton,
when you came in with heartburn,
I bet you thought
I'd kick your butt out of here.
But not this guy. I admitted you and
stayed up all night studying your EKG
because I had a hunch...
and no girlfriend.
But mostly it was the hunch.
And that hunch paid off because,
if I hadn't found that blocked artery,
you'd be dead right now.
And here comes the gratitude, the two
words every doctor lives to hear.
Later, dude.
I can't believe he didn't thank me.
You'll thank me when you leave?
I don't know. Why are you so needy?
He keeps a hug schedule
with his friends.
OK, Turk, looks like someone's
getting crossed off their 2:00 spot
and penciled in for never.
How does that feel? Does it sting?
[J.D.] He's hurting.
Hug him. Hug him now.
You guys, what would you do
with a hundred million dollars?
A hundred million dollars?
The Super Lotto jackpot
was up to a hundred million dollars.
So earlier that morning...
I'm just saying, think of what you
could do with that kind of money.
- I could get a trained shark.
- Why?
Thanks for inviting me, Janitor.
Anytime, buddy. Anytime.
Wait for him... wait for him...
Can opener!
The lobster's in the pot.
Devour! Devour!
[Grunts] Something feels pinchy.
[Screams]
- [Static click]
- Save me a leg.
I'm in.
We could buy a lot more tickets
if we collect money from everyone.
- I'll go through their lockers.
- I meant asking them.
Seems kinda roundabout, but OK.
Hey, Dr. Cox, you want
to put in for some lottery tickets?
Oh, gosh, Carla, I would.
I really would.
But you see, I already set fire to
a big pile of money just this morning.
We have the same chance
of winning as anyone else.
And the category is... ding!
Things that have a better chance
of happening than you winning.
Ted-ski, throw ten seconds
on the clock for me, would you please?
- Go!
- Brain transplants,
Britney Spears having another hit,
the Rolling Stones going on
a farewell tour and meaning it,
me caring about anything
that happens on Wisteria Lane,
Jessica Simpson winning an Oscar,
Jessica Alba winning,
Simpson becoming Alba-Simpson...
- Time!
- Oh!
Anyway, that explains
why I went into the room and said...
What would you do
with a hundred million dollars?
- Me? Floating Head Doctor.
- Here we go.
I'd spend the money researching
how to separate my head from my body.
That way I could literally
be in two places at once.
Looking good, Mr. Henderson.
Looking real good, Nurse Myers.
- [Machine beeping]
- Uh-oh.
He's flatlining! Body, come!
[Bugle plays Reveille]
Damn it!
Starting CPR.
Ow!
There'd probably be some kinks
to work out initially.
Where is that whore?
- Who's a whore?
- That'd be me, sir.
Oh, of course.
Would you care to elaborate?
See, yesterday, I went shoe shopping...
Shoe shopping.
[All] Shoe shopping.
[Cox] Oh, please.
Jordan used to use that one on me
all the time. Immune. Watch this.
Satin panties.
Fine. I was checking on Mrs. Wilk and...
Mrs. Wilk, I just wanted
to explain to you my behavior before.
It's not like I was making out
with some random guy.
I wouldn't do that. Well, I did that
once. There was this Medi-Vac pilot.
Actually, he just
turned out to be an orderly
who got his hands
on a helicopter helmet.
But this is different. Sure, it
could get complicated. He has a son...
And a wife.
I've been making out
with a married man
while his sick child
slept a few feet away.
Oh, my God, I've become my mother.
Hi. You said your wife was dead.
I said she wasn't with us.
Don't make me out to be a bad guy.
Well, you're not a good guy.
Good guys don't lie about being single
or about helicopter pilots.
If you were a good guy, you would get
in there and tell her what happened.
- You're right.
- Hell, yeah, I am.
Wait, what?
[Elliot] You know how when something
horrible happens, like a car accident,
everything slows down?
[Gasping]
No!
Whore!
Where is that whore?
Hey, guys. What's up?
Would you do me a favor
and cover Mr. Foster for me?
I have to go to Mr. Sutton's
and get the thank-you I deserve.
You are so obsessing about this.
Like the time you
were convinced the cafeteria
was giving you small waffles.
How'd that work out for you?
They waffle-ironed my foot.
This is different.
- Look, I need a ride.
- Pass.
Oh, pass, huh? Well, this is what
happened last time you passed.
[Both gasp]
OK, put the foot away.
Put the waffle foot away.
This is where Sutton lives, right?
Let's get in there.
J. D...
Dude?
[Growling]
OK, just back away slowly.
Oh, no! Turk, they're organized!
- [Growling]
- Run!
[Stomach growl]
Good Lord, Bobbo, was that your stomach?
[J.D.] And there it was. Hope.
Dr. Kelso's inability
to deal with hunger was legendary.
We were as good as home.
I've heard enough.
Let's call it and go to lunch.
Just hold on.
That is not the way it works, Bobbo.
This is important.
You sit back down and get on with it.
Perry, I'm in charge here.
Ted, give him your sandwich.
I suppose I could spare a small corner.
Everyone just stay right where you are
and we will be back in... two minutes.
[J. D] One sandwich later,
we got back into it.
And then what happened, Dr. Dorian?
Well, sir, fortunately for us,
ostriches are flightless birds.
[Growling]
There goes the sentry.
Every three minutes, like clockwork.
Dude, can I admit something to you?
I kind of missed
not getting my hug today.
Here comes your vanilla bear.
J.D. J.D. Oh, J.D.!
- Whoa-oh-oh!
- Oh!
Dude, don't sweat it!
It says here that the ostrich
is generally a docile creature.
Thank God.
It also says their kick can kill a man.
What? I'm coming back up!
[Growls]
- Turk!
- [Growls]
- [Thud]
- [J.D. Screams]
Mr. Sutton,
I hope this isn't a bad time.
Who cares about Mr. Sutton?
So, Dr. Reid,
you were covering Mr. Foster.
Actually, sir,
I was on my way to cover Mr. Foster,
but then I stopped
in Mrs. Wilk's room and...
- What are you doing?
- Don't look at me.
Do you see
the woman standing outside?
- Yeah, I see her.
- I made out with her husband.
That's disgusting.
OK, just get out of here
and do PFTs on Mr. Foster.
Dr. Reid, why are you hiding?
You didn't do anything wrong.
If we all win this lottery then I am
using that money to find a decent man.
- [Beeping]
- [Man] You may kiss the bride.
Whoa, save it for tonight, big guy.
Mazeltov.
Why did I make him Jewish?
My parents will kill me.
Why ostriches?
They're majestic creatures,
don't you think?
And they're kinda like my children.
Plus, I make belts out of their necks.
Look, Mr. Sutton,
you're wondering why I'm here.
[Turk screams]
- There is a door.
- Man.
You OK?
Did you try and escape?
I did escape.
There was one waiting in the car.
That's Leon. Loves the car rides.
Likes to stick his head out the window.
I tell him it's dangerous.
He doesn't listen.
Mr. Sutton,
I cured you and you never thanked me.
Why thank you for doing your job?
I'm a garbage man.
How times a day
do you think I get thanked?
- Six.
- You're off by about six.
Twelve!
I'm starting
to see why Leon outfoxed you.
Stupid bird stole my hat.
I don't see why it's such a big deal
for you to say, "Hey, doc..."
- Why'd he just walk away like that?
- [Mumbles]
[Growls]
Ruh-roh.
Don't move.
I gotta admit he looks pretty phat
in your Kangol.
[Growls]
Hey! They're about
to pick the lottery numbers.
And remember that when we win,
we win as a family.
I set aside 20 tickets
for you and I to split.
Perfect.
Nurse Espinoza, Mr. Foster's cough
is getting worse and Dr. Dorian's gone.
Dr. Reid's covering,
but she's indisposed.
Kid, I'm about to become a millionaire.
Call Dr. Turk, he's the surgeon on-call.
You're missing out.
There's plenty you could do
with a hundred million dollars.
Oh, come on. You gotta make that shot.
[Pounding]
Let me out of here! I will kill you!
I'm watching the game.
Sweetie, you want to get naughty?
Ooh.
Ohh. Ahh.
Ahh.
Come on. Do it. Do it.
I can wait another day.
Button up and watch the game.
I gotta call my glass guy.
Mrs. Brown, I want you to know how
sorry I am for kissing your husband.
But we are two women who
have been wronged and lied to,
and the healthiest thing
for us to do right now,
walk away from each other with our
dignity intact. Don't you agree?
Do you know what I do with whores?
I punch them in the face.
Bring it, bitch.
Dude, are you really gonna sit here
all day just to thank your garbage man?
Jabbarie has been added to the
hug schedule. Want to wait with me?
I can't. I was supposed
to be on-call five minutes ago.
This whole experience got me thinking
about the nature of gratitude.
I guess in the end...
Whether you're a doctor
or a garbage man...
Dorian, what are you doing?
Sorry, sir.
Sometimes I like
to just sum things up.
Well, allow me to do that for you.
In the end, when Mr. Foster
started coughing up blood...
[horn honking]
... the on-call surgeon
was stuck in traffic...
... the nursing staff
was busy losing the lottery...
... his original doctor
was thanking a garbage man...
... and the covering physician
was incapacitated.
And what was Mr. Foster doing?
He was dying
in the hands of the interns.
How did I do, Dr. Dorian?
Sorry I'm late. I got the keys
to my Miata stuck in the cadaver.
Cut to the chase there, pee pants.
Mr. Foster's death was the result
of a pulmonary embolism,
probably caused by the 21 -hour
flight he was on from India.
Dr. Flannery, the radiologist,
should have caught it on the scan.
Working from an inaccurate report,
there was nothing any of you could have
done to prevent Mr. Foster from passing.
Which, I guess, leads us to you,
Dr. Flannery.
After a day like today, there's really
only one thing you can do...
To bad radiologists.
Wait, wait. Let me get in on this.
Let's also have a toast to Mr. Foster's
widow and his fatherless kids.
Dr. Cox, it wasn't our fault.
No, because you were lucky.
You know as well as I do, it could
have been any one of your faults.
Congrats again.
Have a... have a swell party.
[J.D.] It's not easy when someone
accuses you of screwing up,
especially when you know it's true.
When that happens,
you can't shrug it off,
because in a hospital,
the best way to learn from your mistakes
is to carry them with you.