How's your mom, ton'?
The same.
But my ex- goomar's cousin,
i got her coming in
to take care of her.
Russian girl.
Who was it telling me
about the bevilaqua kid?
You know that family has
money from construction?
That fucking matthew...
was never any good.
He sure cried li
ke a baby that night.
I think the family was
relieved he got taken out.
What are you
gonna eat?
Hey, waiter!
That's the closest
cw- 16 ever got tony
to discussing
the bevilaqua
murder on tape?
I think at this point
it's time to consider
16 bonpensiero compost.
Bonpensiero...
was crucial to
the webistics
stock fraud case.
So, rico- wise.
The airline tickets.
Mail and wire fraud.
Especially if
the mother testifies
in exchange for immunity.
C'mon, whose
own mother's gonna
testify against him?
I say focus on
his garbage business.
Extortion,
interstate trucking.
It's also the most
likely to yield
a prosecutable murder.
Richie aprile,
exactly.
No doubt about
it the cartel
had him whacked.
Okay, garbage, but tony
shows real due diligence
when it comes to
electronic debugging.
What about
the home?
Bonpensiero told me
him and tony talk
in the basement there
on more than
one occasion.
His own basement,
really?
Where's the due
diligence there?
Tony avoids talking business
in the house if he can.
But if he has to, he'll take
somebody out by the pool.
Except there he
fears parabolics.
The basement
has these
noisy a. C. Ducts.
He turns on the air
and he feels it's safe.
"Surreptitiously
enter said premises
and leave
without notice."
This is a "sneak
'n peek" warrant.
Correct,
your honor.
I said you could enter
the basement to drop a wire.
I mean, how many times
do we have to impact
this family's
right to privacy?
First, when the
home is empty,
we enter to take
sound levels,
determine where to
best place the wire.
Once that's decided,
the listening devi
ce will be fabricated
and we will reente
r to install it.
See that they limit
both entrances to
the basement only.
It's not a
"better homes and
gardens" tour.
Happy hunting.
The coffeemaker's gotta be
plugged in for it to work!
Same time
as yesterday.
Listen, i'll save
you some gas.
I'm just going
down to the
stationary store,
then i'll
be right back.
You don't gotta follow
me like yesterday.
Alright?
In order for the s. E. T. Te
to drop a wire in that house,
there's gotta be nobody at
home for at least two hours.
Actually, the maid is
gone for a little while
on tuesday afternoons.
Gone why?
English language
classes, she's getting
a u. S. Citizenship.
She's gone from the house
from 1:00 till about 2:45.
An hour class,
then she and her
husband usually have
a picnic lunch.
He's applying for
citizenship, too.
What's his
name again?
Stasiu
wosilius.
I'll run that by
anti- terrorism...
just for laughs.
Carmela's gone the same hours
on tuesday, tennis lessons.
As long as we have somebody
on her during tennis,
and on the maid
and tony
and everybody that's
got a key to the house.
The daughter's at
columbia, lives
in the dorms.
Why risk it,
she's 45 minutes
away via the g. W.
Put somebody on her.
Anyone of them
breaks for home,
we need to warn
the s. E. T. Team to get
the hell out of there.
Unit one,
this is control.
Baby bing
headed your way.
Copy, control.
Unit two, you got
badabing headed your way.
Excuse me.
Unit three, mrs.
Bing also in motion.
Unit five, you have visu
al contact of princess bing?
Roger, control.
Unit four,
in approximately one minute,
you'll have the maid,
gray jetta.
S. E. Team, the
location reads secure.
You have one hour
and 30 minutes.
Roger, control.
Control, we're headed into
the sausage factory.
Oh, look at this.
Just in time
for lunch.
Set a plate.
You got it.
I had him dart i
t in the shoulde
r like she wanted
and reinforced the hem.
It shouldn't hav
e torn like that.
Beautiful coat.
What the fuck
you doing?
Lunch is ready.
Wash my hands.
You just washed
your hands.
Then i tied
my shoes.
So what?
I can't stand touching
fucking shoe laces.
You ever go to
tie your shoes
and you notice the end
of your laces are wet?
From what?
Why would
they be wet?
I got no
fucking idea.
You go in public bathrooms
, you stand at the urinals.
Oh, c'mon,
will ya?
He's asking me,
i'm tellin' him.
And frankly,
it's important.
Even if the
lace is dry,
and even if you
don't touch the
body of the shoe.
Bacteria and
virus migrate
from the sole up.
You see this on tv?
I gotta watc
h tv to figure
out the world?
Your average men's
shit house is a
fucking sewer.
You look at
ladies' johns,
you could eat maple walnut
ice cream from the toilets.
Ah, there's exceptions.
But a men's...
piss all over
the fucking floor.
Urinals jammed
with cigarette
s and mothball cakes.
And they can pour all
the fucking ice they want
down there, my friend,
it does nothin
g to kill germs.
Even if you keep
your shoes tied,
and you're not dragging
your laces through urine.
Shut the fuck up!
Control, this
is s. E. T. Four,
i have access
to the box.
I'm disabling the line
to the phone company.
Phone line to
the alarm company's
now neutralized.
Go ahead,
cut it.
Hold your breath
, i'm clipping
the siren wire.
Pick it, wilson.
Control, we are
working on entry,
estimate
three or four minutes.
You're not hungry?
Have some bracioll'.
No, thanks.
I got no appetite.
Today would've
been our birthday.
Our birthday?
Oh, yeah.
Spoons.
Hey, happy birthday.
How old are you?
51.
Who was born first,
you or spoons?
Philip was my kid
brother by 11 minutes.
Hey, it was a
fucking tragedy.
What are you
gonna do?
It's the life we chose,
am i right, pat?
But my brother was never
a heavy guy with anybody.
He was a sweet,
gentle man.
Your brother was
your twin brother.
Philly.
Friends like u
s called him "spoons".
Somebody whacked
the kid
a couple months
before you came over.
You big mouth fuck!
Fuck!
It's you identical
twin or the
other kind?
Identical.
Here, have something
to eat.
There's a twin bond.
Unless you
experienced it
you can't understand it.
You okay with
onions, right?
Maybe it sounds
fucking crazy to you.
Hey, nothing sounds
crazy anymore.
The older i get.
It's over, right?
Don't it happen that
identical twins
a lot of times,
they'll die within a coupl
e of days of each other?
That would've been
okay with me, believe me.
Hey!
I miss him so much.
Well, that's natural.
But you're
with us now,
so why don't you leave
the morbid shit
back at junior's crew
and have a happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
Salut.
You want to
commit suicide,
tie your shoes and have
a bite of bracioll'.
Hey, stoonad,
it's a joke, c'mon!
Hello.
God don't
transfer me now.
Adriana la cerva.
How green was my
fucking valley?
Carmela.
Hi, ed.
Hey.
This is my friend
i was telling you about,
adriana la cerva.
Ed restuccia.
Well, i'm delighted to
teach any pal of carm's.
She's my most
disciplined student.
Perfect muscle tone
doesn't hurt either.
Unfortunately, listen,
i have to apologize, carm.
I thought i
called everybody.
But i'm not gonna be
teaching here anymore.
Everything's alright,
i hope.
Yeah, basically, kitty got
this dot- com job in san diego.
So, we're moving.
I didn't even know
you were married.
Yeah.
But you're in luck.
Birgit here is
taking over for me.
How wonderful.
I never even
played like once.
That's why
you're here.
Oh, carm,
before you start,
it'll really help
if i can get letters
of recommendation.
Oh, by the way,
this company
kitty's joining,
they sell antiques
on the web,
so if you ever wanted
a special piece...
i don't have antiques,
my house is traditional.
Um, i'm cutting in
to your lesson, sorry.
Carmela, bye.
Nice meeting you.
Take care.
Baby bing is leaving
school property.
I'm on it.
Taking orders, dude.
Peach snapple.
Me, too.
I only g
ot two bucks.
Mrs. Celeste almost saw
my board in my locker.
What kind of retard rule
is that, no boards at school?
Why can't they see how usefu
boards would be at school?
Like in the cafeteria.
Each person on line coul
d just roll past the food pans
or whatever and make
the decisions in
like half the time.
Yeah.
That food tastes
like ass anyway.
Alright, hit it!
I only had eno
ugh for one snapple.
A. J. , give me a hit
of your snapple.
Don't backwash.
I'm not doing anything
for this school.
My mom's all
,"get involved".
It's like,"hello,
i am involved...
with boarding."
Oh, it's egon.
Hey, kosma.
Okay!
Where you
been, dude?
Orthodontist.
S'up, slim?
What class you
guys ditchin'?
Assembly.
Excellent jersey.
Yeah, wait...
you went out
for j. V. Ball?
Yeah.
Excuse me, m
r. Quadripleg
ic of the future.
Remind me no
t to visit you
in the hospital.
It is a cool shirt.
Yeah.
Whoa!
What position?
Douchebag.
Okay, cut it!
...jell- o shots...
on bhs,
fight right
through that line!
Run that ball
to the goal line!
Y'all
should've come.
Where'd you go?
We started off
at smoke's as usual,
but we wound up
at this place ruby
foos'round, um...
broadway and 65th
or something.
It was so fun.
God, did i
get hammered.
Don't you have
a quiz today?
Frosh week technically
ended at midnight.
What do they expect?
I'll study now.
I know, i
have a bio lab,
i haven't read
any of the chapters.
Aww...
still miss
new jersey?
It's only like
half an hour away.
It's just
this transition.
It's a lot of work.
I just think new york
is an experience
that unalterably
changes a person.
It is really great.
All this freedom
of college.
When did you have
your last cocktail?
11:30 this morning.
Jesus, caitlin.
"What is the most
important right
guaranteed to
united states
citizens?"
Right to vote.
Special capers
from italy.
Soprano kids
don't like them.
"Who wrote'the star
spangled banner'?"
Martin luther king.
Stasiu,
you know this.
I want to eat.
Francis scott key.
"What holiday was celebrated
for the first time
by the american colonists?"
Martin luther king.
Stasiu!
That's answer
to number 49,
"who was civil
rights leader?"
Which sandwich
is for you?
I don't care.
Ready.
Start shooting
over here.
Back in lodz,
i was an engineer
with 20 employees
and a grant from the sta
te to do autonomous research.
Oh, it bores you?
Don't take those
steak knives out.
Put them with capers,
i take them home.
That's just for
anthony jr.
Looks like they're
expecting world war iii.
More likely
the columbo wars.
Hey, he's got
the black & decker.
I got one of those.
120- gallon
water heater.
My house we're shivering
after a shower and a half.
Whoa, wait a
minute, go back.
Look at the brown water,
right there, freeze it.
What?
You don't see it?
Creep forward, give us
some magnification.
That baby's
gonna blow.
My dad was a plumber.
Tony's got about six months
left to go on that lining.
Aw, it's a shame that
we can't warn him.
Maybe during the discovery
phase of his rico trial,
we can inform his lawy
er that tony needs a plumber.
Except that's
at least a
year from now
and by that
time...boom!
Okay, now you
see that lamp there?
Is that the c- 140
microphone?
They took
sound readings.
That's a new one.
Assumption is
the wiseguys
stand and talk
where the air
conditioning's loudest.
And that's where
we're gonna place it.
When's this puppy
going in?
Tomorrow.
Okay, fellas and gals,
our big day.
And as i speak
, i have baby bing...
right on time.
Handing off to
you, george.
I'm on baby bing's
car pool vehicle.
Furio giunta
cadillac dts returning.
Went past me up the street
about five minutes ago.
Well, well, well.
Der bingle's up early today,
he's in the caddy.
Copied, i've got
the handoff.
Roger that.
How's the
new stock doing?
Up three at the close
of the dow yesterday.
Another two
so far today.
Beautiful.
Listen, ton', i think
we may have a problem.
Log off.
That cookies shit
makes me nervous.
I think we may have
a problem about our
friend, the twin.
Yeah, so?
My goombah,
joey flies,
he hangs out at the
nest in bloomfield.
Gyp la monica's place.
Yeah.
So, our friend is
a fixture down there
and joey says lately he's been
into the booze very heavy.
He's all fucked up.
A couple of times, i had to
pick him up off the floor.
So, chip went to him.
"Pat, what the fuck?
Can i do anything",
etcetera.
Patsy launches into
this single malt diatribe
about how people can
smile in your face
and still
be a villain
and that he knows
how his brother died
and who's responsible
and all that there.
He mention me
by name?
No, me neither.
You hearing this?
How the fuck would patsy
know we clipped spoons?
What, that fucking
twin telepathy?
Somebody's putting
ideas in this
kid's head.
Sweet shot, really
beautiful shot.
He just set himself
up perfectly on
this hole...
don't let us interfere
with your golf game.
Maybe a cop
trying to flip him.
Getting him worked
up with theories.
He was talking weird
the other day.
What should we do?
We brought him ove
r from junior's crew
to keep an
eye on him.
So, that's what
we'll keep doing.
I mean, make
no mistake.
Part of this guy
loves you.
But it's gotta be hard
coming into work every day
looking right into the eyes
of the guy you know
ordered your
brother whacked.
And even having
to smile.
We always
have the option.
Mrs. Bing in motion.
S. E. Team, we got the
housekeeper to wait out,
then the house
is all yours.
Hit low to
high, carmela
and think
about your grip.
Fuck!
No, that's good.
Nice extension.
Ah!
Racquet back,
carmela, c'mon!
Fuck.
No, that's good.
Shouldn't that housekeeper
be out of there?
Edge closer,
take a look.
Ow!
Okay, guys,
collect.
Actually, ade, let m
e work with you here.
Carm, you collect.
Maid's car's
still here.
Okay, let's just focus,
be serious...
and follow through.
Right, right.
Almost, almost.
Did you hear
something?
I don't know.
We think we
heard something.
From inside the
sausage factory.
Hold your position.
Okay.
Stand up straight,
okay?
Okay.
Here you go.
Low to high.
I can't do this
with you.
She's leaving
the court.
Der bingle's leaving
the bing, too.
This does
not look good.
Mrs. Bing bearing north
on grandview avenue.
She's turned
onto foxwood road.
She's heading
toward the factory.
Abort,
repeat, abort.
S. E. Team get the hell
out of there now!
Abort, andy,
it's not a go.
Repeat, we
are not a go.
It must be a crisis
with one of the children.
Control, i place baby bing
in the school building.
Unit five report.
That's a big roger
from this end, too.
She went into her room
about two minutes ago.
I heard her tell her friend
she was gonna get some sleep.
You think
somebody made us?
I don't know.
But we're finished
for today here,
ladies and gentlemen.
10 years.
10 fucking years he
said this fucking
thing would last!
Fuck!
You said that, tony.
Are you doing
anything over there?
I told you not to put
this shit down here!
Fuck!
Never mind tha
t, save the pictures.
The prom.
Look at this,
fucking ruined.
Mr. Ruggerio
, thank god.
The fucking
water heater blew.
Just blew!
Your guarantee's
gotta be expired by now.
Madonn'.
Do we have any idea
what went down?
No.
It's a family
emergency of
some sort.
The plumber's truc
k went up there.
Look, we don't
have any idea
what happened, so...
let's not speculate.
All i know is that
we're shit out of luck
till next tuesday.
Send somebody up
there tomorrow,
stake the house out.
Maybe we got a
long- term problem.
Well, we're heading
back to quantico.
We got a job in denver
day after tomorrow.
A mosque.
Morning.
Hi.
We'd like to get onto your property
so we can trim some
growth in the back
that's posing a safety hazard
with all the powerline
s running through there.
Okay.
Go around
the side.
While we're at it,
our records show t
hat our repair department
had some crews
out here yesterday.
Were you affected
by any of the
shortfalls?
Yesterday?
No.
Oh.
The people next door
have had some trucks
go up there i think,
but, no,
we've been fine.
How about them?
Do you know if
everything's okay
over there?
As far as i know.
Well, we'll go
talk to them.
Probably you should.
They're in the--
pardon?
Nothing.
They're different.
For this neighborhood,
they're a little
different, that's all.
We'll get busy
in the back.
Thanks.
Still nothing
out of the ordinary.
Is the kid home
sick from school?
I don't see him.
But, i see an arm,
a piece of robe.
It could be tony.
He's eating
sugar pops.
Wait, somebody just walked
past the kitchen window.
No, that's the maid.
They're good.
Fresh this morning,
ferrara's.
How are things over
on bloomfield avenue?
The cuban was at
the casino last night.
And by the way,
big john's okay
with a 60- 40 split
because we own
the building.
What the hell?
What?
What the fuck,
is that pat parisi?
Oh, shit.
What should we do?
He's drunk!
Anyway, i told johnny,
i says,"look--
let's talk
downstairs.
Motherfucker...
i don't understand
this at all.
Cocksucker.
What's up, ike?
What happened at
the soprano house was
the water heater blew.
Our unit saw ruggerio
come back with a flatbed
and haul the old one out.
Ruggerio...
a plumber?
Why?
My sister used t
o live up near there.
She was friend
s with mrs. Ruggerio.
Yeah, it's mr. Ruggerio's
neighborhood.
Anyway, we have to
get this thing in there
before our warrant
goes stale.
Boy, we've had eve
ry one of tony's phones
bugged for four years.
But the guy says
less than harpo marx.
Next tuesday.
The wire drop's
a definite go.
Der bingle has
left the building.
They fucking
made me.
Wire drop is
still a go.
Confirming access
to switching box.
I'm going in.
Unit two,
mrs. Bing in motion.
Just the maid
and it's all yours.
Copy that.
Siren wire's cut.
The teacher
knows nothing.
Why do you quarrel
with him always?
English is his
first language.
C'mon,
waste our time
with those childish
trick questions.
"Stop,
men at work".
And how do we know
it doesn't mean
"stop all men
who are working"?
He shouldn't have taken
a point off my grade.
He thinks i'm a ha
ck cabbie from pakistan.
Lilli, lilli!
Where ar
e you going?
I'm going
back to work!
Excuse me, ma'am.
Scared me.
I'm sorry,
can you tell me,
is the west essex
language school
around here?
There.
Is it coed?
What?
You wouldn't happen
to be polish by any
chance, would you?
Yes.
My grandmother
is polish.
It's locked today.
Yeah, yeah,
my grandmother, she--
excuse me.
How can i
help you, sir?
I was just wonderi
ng if i could ask you
a few questions ab
out the language school.
How is it?
Sweet mother
of jesus.
Look at her today.
Hi, ade!
Hi, guys!
Be back
in a second.
Listen to this
now,"hi, ade!"
Hi.
Hey, you.
I love those.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, my god.
Where did you
get them?
Near my house.
Ay- ay- ay.
Wait, wait, wait,
this table's been moved.
Cleanup fr
om the flood.
It's not under
the right duct anymore.
Should we
move it back?
What, two, three feet,
who's gonna notice?
Yeah, you know, wait,
wait, wait, somebody might.
You gotta figure though,
normal course of events,
tony will assume carmela
moved it back or the maid.
If anybody
even notices.
Make an
executive decision.
Grab an end.
Easy, easy.
When hadley heard i
was deferring a year,
she was like,
"well that's sketchy."
Steve said eric scatin
o hates montclair state.
And he's been doin
g all this acid.
God, he was
so straightedge.
Hi, caitlin.
Hi.
This is hunter, my
friend from home i
was telling you about.
Wow.
Do you like
citron jell- o shots?
Actually, i haven't had
any alcohol in a week.
I know, i was gonna
say we should go
over to panchito's,
but i remembered,
bad idea.
I went over to
the health center.
That problem
swallowing thing?
They gave me this
prescription for buspar.
That's for like,
anxiety, right?
I guess.
There was like,
this weightlifter guy
on the subway today.
And he was eating thes
e cacciatore chicken parts
from this massive
tupperware thing
and spitting the bon
es back in the container.
And the whole car...
reeked.
This poor blind man
sitting next to him.
I mean, you could tell
he felt completely invaded.
We all did.
Everybody just stared
straight ahead.
New york.
Hey.
Where is everybody?
What are you doing?
Receipts f
rom sunday's game.
You got a problem?
What, ton'?
I said...
do you got
a problem?
With what, ton'?
I don't know, i heard maybe
you got a fuckin' problem.
Like you don't
like being here.
I like being here.
You sure?
Yeah.
Don't say you're sure
if you're not sure.
Who was telling me you bought
your daughter a nice house
after you came
over with us?
Yeah, that's nice.
Wonderful thing.
And your brother,
a buon anima.
You've recovered
from that shit there.
You put your grief
behind you.
Let me hear
you say it.
I put the grief
behind me.
I'm gonna go get
a coffee and a bun.
You got a younger
son too, right?
You oughta bring him
up to the house.
He can hang
out with a. J.
We can get
something to eat.
They can go
in the pool.
We'll have to leav
e this junk on the table.
Don't know
where to put it.
Control,
you hearing me?
Loud and clear,
leave the factory.
Roger that.
Wire's in,
bobby.
I'm good to go.
Control,
we're in motion.
We have left the
sausage factory.
Touchdown.
Dig, soprano,
c'mon, dig it!
You wanted to jo
in the football team.
You think it's all for
show and not for go?
Dig in,
you chubette!
You're out of
there, george.
Unit three,
we're in.
So, i got
a job for you.
Right.
It might get
a little messy.
I understand.
Wet work.
Alright.
I'll make it
worth your while,
don't worr
y about that.
I'm not worried.
Look over here.
Minimization,
40 seconds.
The old one blew.
Flooded the whol
e goddamn place.
I can smell the
mildew, you know?
So, lilliana say
s you're an engineer.
I figured maybe you
could rig some system.
If it happens
again, some pvc
shit or something.
So, if it happens again,
you get the overflow
and you put it over
into the corner over there
to a sump pump.
You chip out
the concrete.
4- 0.
Yeah, they're no
t discussing oc.
Two minutes, we're allowed
to check back in.
What do
you think?
Whatever.
Well, how much?
Time, materials.
I don't know how to
concoct estimate.
Hmm, well.
Fair enough.
Let me get measure.
Get started.
Alright.
Hi, stasiu.
You gonna
use this?
You want it,
take it.
No, you go ahead.
Go ahead, i'll
use the bike.
I have to sort through
meadow's laundry anyway.
She's gonna be here
at noon to get it.
Lilliana's making
her a leg of
lamb to take back.
Back in lodz,
i had grant from
the state to do an
autonomous research.
You got your workout
clothes on,
why don't you use it?
I'll take the bike.
Jesus, already,
no, you go ahead.
Stas said he could smell
the mildew down here,
right, stas?
We gotta open these
windows up, let the
place dry out.
Got some russian girl
coming in to take
care of my mother.
Oh, yeah,
where'd you find her?
Agency.
It was good coffee
this morning.
Vienna roast.
It's not as acidic
as the italian.
Cleaned me right out.
What you need is more roughage
overall in your diet
is what you need.
I've had something stuck
in my teeth for two days now.
Jesus.
You gotta use
the other floss.
Captions copyright 2001
home box office
division of time warner
company, L. P.