I want you to count
backwards from 10.
10, nine...
mr. Soprano,
there's someon
e here to see you.
Even here
you hector me?
The director has authorized
us to make you an offer.
Give up your nephew
tony, cooperate fully,
help take him down.
What do i get?
A guaranteed cure.
No more cancer?
Not a single
diseased cell.
I'm happy for you.
I know you've
waited a long time...
stay home, clip your
coupons, be a happy man.
Don't let certain people
take advantage...
i'm kiddin' you,
you old fuck.
Peppers and eggs.
Dr. Kennedy...
it's dr. Enloe...
i have the results
of the frozen section.
Can we move this
along, dr. Enloe?
I have a thyroid in
o. R. Six at 10:30.
Based on the preliminary
results of the frozen section
and depending, of cour
se, on the full path report--
is it clean,
enloe, or not?
Yes, it's clean.
Miles, you close.
Let's do it quickly,
i've got his bp back up,
but i don't know
how long it'll hold.
Watch and
learn, miles.
Watch and learn.
Well?
Your uncle
is a very strong
man, mr. Soprano.
He did very well.
The news is
all good.
Beautiful.
So, the
cancer is...
gone?
You bet.
I took a tumor
the size of a fist
out of his stomach.
Madonn'.
So, if you'll
excuse me,
i have another
patient waiting.
Cheryl, make sure
that marty gets
doc?
That goldman- sachs statement.
Yes?
I...
just want to
say thanks.
You know, my uncle
thinks the world of you.
If there's ever anything i
can do, a favor, anything,
let me know.
I'll keep that in
mind, mr. Soprano.
Game three.
That's $60.
Good luck
getting it.
I fuckin' won,
paulie, it's only
right you pay me.
And for other
things too.
Like what?
Fuckin' dom perignon
for everybody in the skybox
at the garde
n the other night.
Check comes,
suddenly you're m. I. A.
Chrissy, you're
too fucking worried
about what i give you.
Worry a little more
about what you give me.
Blow me with your
lectures, paulie.
Kid, you wearing
a wire?
Are you
fucking crazy?
Pasqual,
pat him down.
He fuckin'
touches me...
then make it easy
on all us all.
Take'em off...
everything.
New york reopened the books,
but they also laid it down.
Probationary period.
When i was coming up
this would never happen
to new made guys.
But too many people
are doin' a simulcast.
Maybe you,
you fuck.
Do me a favor and don't
take it personally.
I said everything.
Go fuck yourself.
Before i was
breaking balls,
now, you're beginning
to worry me.
I guess you could
call that a dick.
You're going,
young man, that's
all there is to it.
Jason mangelli
isn't going.
Tony, you wanna
weigh in here?
Tony?
What?
The washington trip?
No, you're gonna be on tha
t school bus to d. C. Tomorrow.
You're all packed and paid f
and you're gonna pay attention
and you're gonna
learn something
for a change.
We're going to
fbi headquarters.
So?
Excuse me.
What did you do
to this'scarrole?
It's delicious.
Balsamic.
That's all they ha
ve at king's these days.
Balsamic,
balsamic, balsamic.
My mother never
heard of balsamic.
I gotta go.
Problems at work.
It's sunday
dinner, tony.
I know.
I gotta go.
Alright, hug
h, see you later.
Can i be
excused too?
No, you may not.
He's got homework
to finish before
the trip.
Go ahead, anthony.
It's a nice
example he sets
for his son.
Ma...
the man's got
two speeds...
moping or yelling...
when he's here.
He's got an uncle
sick with cancer.
Oh, please.
They didn't
speak for a year.
Actually, if you
must know, tony has
been a little better.
We've been seeing
his therapist together.
What?
He's no angelo
stamfa, that's all.
What is that
supposed to mean?
You know angelo was
dying to marry you
and now, stamfa's is
a chain of drugstores.
So, what, he doesn't
need therapy?
He prescribes his
own tranquilizers?
Don't be
so sensitive.
What sensitive?
I gotta hear this
angelo stamfa shit again?
All i was
saying was--
i know wha
t you were saying.
Hugh, bring
your plate!
You are blowing this
all out of proportion.
We worry about
you, that's all.
Spare me your
concern, alright?
And spare me
your attitude too.
Or maybe you forgot,
dad's little strip mall on
route 17 was zoned residential
until tony made
a phone call.
Bullshit.
Oh, really, dad?
The contract you got t
o do at sparta high
for the hurricanes repairs.
What, all the
other builders were
too busy to bid?
Oh, please,
my heart bleeds.
What, the waters
don't part for you
wherever you go?
I earn it.
You two get
a free pass.
Hey.
Ton', what's up?
Hey, tony.
Anyway, four
dollars a pound.
Who brought
this in here?
Georgie.
It's wacky, huh?
What do you think,
it's a fuckin'
playroom back there?
What, ton'?
What, what, fuckin'
toys? This is a
place of business.
That's an office
back there!
I saw it at rite- a
id, they were selling'em.
What? What
did you say?
Ah!
I pay you a
fuckin' salary!
Carmela...
you sounded tense
on the phone.
Ah...
i just wanted to make sure
it was okay if i came alone.
I mean, because tony
couldn't make it.
I love the artwork
you have out there,
those country scenes.
Thank you.
That statue is
not my favorite.
Oh, come on...
look, it's not lik
e this when me and ton
y are here together.
You never give him
the silent treatment.
Is that what
you think?
I'm giving you the
silent treatment?
Maybe you could tell me
why you came today.
I'm worried
about my husband.
The mood swings.
I thought...
when his mother
died, maybe...
but still half the tim
e he doesn't even talk to me.
You've seen him
get like that,
that day he sat
here like a wall.
I know that
he's your patient
and i am only
the patient's wife,
but you try living with
that 24 hours a day,
seven days a week,
see how you feel.
I see.
Oh, you do?
Well, for your information
, i am not the only one.
The fact is, tony isn'
t under the weather today,
he just didn't
feel like coming.
"Fuck that shit",
i think he said, okay?
Usually happens when
we touch on a nerve.
He was distressed about
this young man's death
in the garbage
compactor.
See, he didn't say,
"garbage compactor",
did he?
See?
What is it
you believe?
You know
about his job.
He reports to
a strip club.
Who knows how he
spends his days?
I'm sorry.
I'm just frustrated,
that's all.
Tony's been out of
sorts, for so long
and there is...
there is nothing
i can do to help him.
I think coming to
therapy with him
has stirred up a lot
of feelings in you
that you would like
to address with somebody.
Oh, please.
I'm just a little
emotional today.
I would like
to help you,
but as you've pointed out,
your husband is my patient.
I'm not the one
who needs mental help.
I just needed
to vent.
In case you
change your mind,
here's the number
of a colleague
in livingston.
He was a teacher
of mine.
That really
won't be necessary,
but thank you
anyway.
Thank you
for your time.
You took
these yourself?
That's a samoan village
i lived in for a month.
You could send these int
o "national geographic".
So, i got back
your complete
surgical pathology
and op reports.
I feel 100%.
That's good.
It's possible though...
that there may
be some malignant
cells we didn't get.
See, when
we operate,
we have to decide
how much healthy tissue
to cut around
the tumor.
Alright?
The margins
weren't wide enough.
We took a small sampling
of the tumor from
the frozen section,
when we got back
the complete results,
it showed
nodal involvement.
Don't blame
yourself, doc.
So, what do
we do next?
It's called
amended surgery.
Oh, jesus.
Cut me again?
Mrs. Brody is here.
Don't let me
keep you, doc.
I am kinda
backed up.
Let's schedule you
for tuesday at six a. M.
We can admit and prep
you monday night.
Any questions?
When can h
e eat regula
r food again?
I'd guess two weeks.
Let's fill out the
surgical consent forms.
That's one less thing you have
to deal with in the hospital.
Take all the time
you need to read them.
No need,
you say sign,
i sign.
You tell me to take a crap
on the deck of the queen mary,
an hour later, they're hosin
her down with disinfectant.
I owe you
everything, doc.
How do i know what
nodal involvement means?
Didn't you
fuckin' listen?
A whole issue
of "u. S. News" on
seniors and health.
Bring somebody
with you to the
doctor's, it said.
Somebody to
ask questions.
You ask one dumb fuckin'
question about my diet.
Angie?
Carmela!
Hi.
What a surprise.
I didn't know you
shopped over here.
They're running
a special on iams.
Every penny
counts these days.
How are you doing,
angie, with pussy gone?
Oh, you know.
I'll tell you, shopping
for one is no picnic.
Why don't you
come for dinner?
It's jus
t me and tony,
with med at school
, a. J. 's on a field trip.
Who knows, maybe we'll g
et lucky and tony won't show.
That's coco's
worst time of the day.
I can't leave her.
Angie, that dog is
not a substitute
for human contact.
That french poodle is
all i got left of sal.
24 years, he disappears
one day, and i get
left with a sick dog.
The vet says i
should put her down,
but i want her to get
another operation.
I remember when
sal was around
there was nothing too
good for that dog.
Yeah, but where am i
gonna come up with $1200?
I mean, tony helps out
and i am so grateful.
It covers
the basics,
but anything extra,
there's no way, carmela.
Jeez, ang,
i'm sorry.
That must be
so tough.
I told the wallpaper
guy that this was okay.
Well, why
did you do that?
Because i didn't want to deal
with your parents anymore.
Anybody around here love
the word "jimmy choo shoes"?
No way!
Oh, my god.
They're gorgeous!
Or would the lady
prefer something in...
gold?
Say a nice...
i don't know,
whatever the
fuck that is.
They're all
yours, baby.
And they're from next seas
you can't even buy them yet.
What size
are these?
10.
10?
That's sasquatch
size, christopher.
I'm an 8. 5.
Fuck, fuck, fuck...
where'd i
get 10 from?
Yeah, where?
So, now what happens?
You gotta give
'em all back?
Temporarily.
I'll get you
8. 5's tomorrow.
All of'em?
You swear?
More even.
Since you been
, you know...
"in",
i just can't believe
the stuff we get.
It's so great.
Except for that
schmaccone paulie.
Fuck him and the coupe
de ville he rode in on.
He saying you're
holding back again?
Like i'm gonna give
that prick a full share?
C'mere.
What do you say?
I love you, baby.
Oh, you fucking better.
You better.
I do.
You could've
called.
Now everything's cold.
That's why the
y invented microwaves,
for inconsiderate
husbands.
It's just that
since we're alone,
it would be nice to
have dinner together.
Don't bust my
chops, carmela.
I got a lot
on my mind.
This is fuckin
' delicious.
Really.
Is this
the pecorino?
Right.
The hell with
heatin' it up,
it's good like this.
I'm glad something
brings you joy.
You're amazing,
your cookin'.
I'm having lunch
with our daughter's
dean tomorrow.
I gather you
won't be joining me.
I told you, all he
wants is our money.
Fine.
We already shell
out 40 grand a
year to those people.
It's well spent.
She's really learning,
she's out on her own.
And if she
passes us by--
if?
She did that
when she was 14.
Isn't that what you
want for your kids?
No.
I want them to be
backwards and ignorant
and sit around wit
h their thumb up their ass
and i'm gonna make sure
of that by not going to lunch
with some asshole who's
trying to shake me down.
Fine, tony,
don't go.
Guess who i ran into
at the supermarket today.
Angie bonpensiero.
Really?
How's she doing?
Her dog is sick.
What, that fluffy french
coco piece of shit?
What's wro
ng with him?
Her, osteoporosis.
Angie needs money
for an operation.
Well, take it
up with pussy.
If you can find th
e fat fuck, wherever
the feds put him.
I'd look in arizona,
you know, stake out
all the "tgi fridays".
He loves
their wings.
He left angie holding the
bag, which is not right.
And those fbi family value
loving cocksuckers,
how could they let him
go without his wife?
Into the program?
Yeah, that's right.
He ratted us out, carm.
Me and you.
And that's
where he is
and i don't want to hear
about him ever again.
Or his ungrateful
cunt wife.
His what wife?
Okay...
who was
your oldest?
Easy.
Chuckie periccio's
mother.
Shut up!
You had sex wi
th beverly periccio?
Yeah.
A whole
summer's worth.
Okay, my turn.
Who was your
most famous?
And bobby ditillio
doesn't count,
he's only famous
in new jersey.
Okay...
you know
penn and teller,
the magicians?
You fucked them?
Penn.
And i didn't
fuck him...
i gave him head.
Which one is he?
The big one.
They were playing a. C. ,
and they're funny as hell.
I was ther
e with georgette.
He followed me
into the ladies room
and he asked--
you lowlife
cunt whore.
Get the fuck
out of my sight!
Ow, you fucking
shitbag!
In the fucking
bathroom?
Who is it?
The fbi.
Come o
n, dickhead
, open up.
For fuck's sake paulie,
it's two in the morning.
I know.
It's an outrage.
Adriana,
you in there?
Yeah.
Sorry for the
intrusion, honey.
Put something on
and come out here.
You can't fuckin
' do this like this!
I can't?
You must've not read
up on the latest rules.
And put
that piece away.
What's all this?
The berezovsky
brothers jacked
a shipment from milan
off pier 87.
These are for ade.
Nice goods.
My broad wears
a size 10.
Patsy, pack up
some of these shoes.
Chrissy, you don't mind
if i take my taste now?
He's not
taking those.
Make yourselves
comfortable.
We'll just have a
little look around.
I'm still gonna get
more shoes, right?
I don't know, now i have t
o go into my pocket for'em.
This really sucks,
christopher.
You see the shit
i go through?
Motherfucker!
What?
Nothing!
Leave it on,
it's nice.
Meadow?
Didn't you hear
me knocking?
I was sleeping,
i thought it was vanessa.
You don't answer the d
oor when your friends knock?
They keep you
from studying.
And my first class
isn't until two.
I brought your laundry
and i made you the ziti
with the sweet sausage
that you like.
I'm so starved.
Jesus, it reeks of
cigarettes in here.
You're not smoking,
are you?
Caitlin.
I hope you're taki
ng advantage of some
of these offers here.
Look at this.
A boy just
handed this to me.
A seminar on the cia
and the cultural cold war.
Look at this.
This looks
interesting.
It's basic, we're
way past that.
I'm reading the ne
w barbara kingsolver.
I so wish i had
time for fiction.
So, how is the drama
queen doing anyway?
Fine.
Can we not talk
about this, please?
I'm trying very
hard here, med.
If you want me to
leave, i will leave.
I have an hour befor
e my lunch with dean ross.
You're going to lunch
with the dean?
Can we not talk about
this now, please?
Mom!
Yeah, his secretary called
last week and invited me.
Come on,
what about?
Money, i'm sure.
They probably want
a donation from us.
How corrupt.
The real reason i stopped
by to see you though
was to make sure
you're recovered
from this noah thing.
I'm worried it
'll affect your grades.
You call losing
a wonderful man
because of dad...
a thing?
Now, is that reall
y what happened?
'Cause you certainly kept
seeing him plenty long enough
after that business
with your father.
Look, don't drag me
into whatever bullshit
accommodational pretense
you've got worked
out with daddy.
What was that, last night's
reading assignment?
Alright...
let's hear it.
What's your big theory
about me and daddy?
No way.
I'm not
touching that.
Oh, fuckin' bitch!
Uncle jun', what the
hell are you doing?
Those marshals see
you coming in here?
'Cause i need being
remanded to a fucking
jail hospital
right now like
i need a fuckin'
case of crabs.
There's no car
out there today
and i come up throug
h the cellar like always.
Where the fuck
is bacala?
He's supposed to b
e doing this shit for you.
I sent him to
the drugstore
for more pepto.
You're getting
better, that's the
important thing.
You look better too.
If you're
gonna lie to me,
tell me there's a broa
d waiting in the car
who wants to
tongue my balls.
You want that, it's
a phone call away.
You still
want this?
I gotta get
nutrition somehow.
Kennedy says eat
only what i ca
n sip through a straw.
What's going on with y
ou and ralphie cifaretto?
Bacala tells me
there's bad blood now.
You don't got
enough in your plate?
I mean, in
your blender?
Worry about
your own problems.
When'd they
say you could
eat real food?
Who knows?
Kennedy's putting
me under the knife again.
Whoa, back up.
More surgery?
Don't think you should
talk to somebody else?
Get a second opinion.
Chemo?
Forget it.
With kennedy it's cut,
zip, over and out.
He has the hands
of an angel.
And don't
forget his name.
What?
I'm supposed to
be impressed
'cause the man's name
is john kennedy?
All the micks named their kids
that after the guy got killed.
I loved that man.
He was older than
me and now look.
You were g
one a long time.
How many
white castles
did you have?
I didn't, i swear.
I can smell them.
Let me call
cusamano.
He knows doctors
in the city.
He sent silvio's
mother to one.
It can't hurt
to make a call.
People come from the
city to see kennedy.
Good, then we won't
be fighting traffic.
C'mon, uncle jun',
you know i'm right.
Alright, you set it up
, you come with me...
to listen and
ask questions.
Good, good.
I'll let you
know, alright?
Alright.
My nephew thinks i need
a second opinion.
He doesn't like
it that i'm going
back under the knife.
Maybe there's
something to that.
Another expert
heard from.
Think on this,
burger boy,
anthony is a
cunt hair away
from owning all of
northern jersey.
And i am
that cunt hair.
So, maybe he
has something
else on his mind,
besides my full, complete
and speedy recovery.
Oh, junior,
all this cynicism...
this can't be
good for you.
Giorgio.
You speak italian.
Second generation.
Really, ross?
Rosetti.
1, 000 years of
a proud name undone
with one stroke of
a pen at ellis island.
A paisan.
And not fa
r from you either.
New brunswick.
Get out!
Any success
i may have,
i credit to the jersey
public schools.
They were somethin
g in those days.
Where did you
go to college?
Rutgers.
I went to
montclair state.
Good school.
What was
your major?
Business
administration.
To meadow soprano,
a valuable addition to
the columbia community.
Really?
Absolutely.
I don't know
her personally,
but i've talked to
her professors.
They say she's attentive,
inquiring, does all her work,
and makes insightful
contributions
to class discussions.
I am so glad to
hear you say that.
And here i was worried
about her adjusting.
Let's not
tell her though.
We don't want he
r overconfident.
It seems like she
sleeps an awful lot.
They all do.
Tony, what the hell?
You know, ang,
driving over here,
i was thinking about how
i was gonna handle this.
I been working
on my anger lately.
So, i figured it'd be good
if i could just quietly say
any kind of problem you got,
financial or otherwise,
you come
directly to me.
Please, leave carmel
a the fuck out of it.
Like that.
Of course.
Then i saw
the cadillac.
The money
i give you...
you're driving a
cadillac and you'r
e looking for more?
Shot the whole plan.
So, remember this...
you see my wife, you talk
about oven cleaner.
Anything els
e you come to me,
but think twic
e before you do.
Think about that f
at fuck husband of yours
and what h
e did to you.
Him...
not me.
Coco, please,
coco, down!
Hey, hey
, how are ya?
I'm sorry, tony,
i'm sorry.
Just push her away.
No, she's alright.
Good girl.
She don't
look sick.
It comes and goes.
So, your children don'
t feel boxed in by the city?
We're out
all the time.
Lately, felicia has us all
into kayaking on the hudson.
You all do
it together?
Yeah, the kids
love it too.
They're already
better at it than i am.
More wine?
Why not?
Remember i told you
i spend about half my time
involved in
student affairs?
Well, this is how
i spend the other half.
Taking parents
to lunch?
Development.
A fancy word
for fund- raising.
The new student center.
We break ground
next fall.
See the large
black marble wall
to the right
of the entrance?
Ah, yes.
That's where the donor
names will be inscribed.
Everybody who donates
gets their name up there?
The wall is reserved for
people whose commitment
begins at the
$50, 000 level.
50, 000?
It's what the giving
committee felt you'd
be comfortable with.
Based on your past generosity
to the verbum dei school.
You know what we
gave to verbum dei?
I'm half embarrassed
to say it, but it's
my job to know.
All the information including
tax benefits is in here.
Well, i will have
to talk to my husband.
50 grand?
You gotta
be kidding me.
He talked an awful lot
about meadow's having
the best possible
university experience.
Yeah, those jew pricks
are holding her hostage.
He's italian.
Jews with
better food.
They know from verbum
we're big givers.
We gave five
grand a year.
That's a long
way from 50.
This is college,
tony, new york city.
5, 000 is a slap in
the face to these people.
Well, let
'em say no.
Here...
it's around
five grand.
Run it through you
r household account
so, you can
write him a check.
And that's it.
Not a penny more.
A five- f. U. Based regimen with
cisplatin and doxorubicin.
This is the treatment
i would recommend.
Are you
getting this?
Sort of.
So, the chemotherapy
would be instead of
the surgery?
But i can't
guarantee
even that.
We'll have to
evaluate the results
of the treatment.
I could end up
having the chemo,
puking my guts out,
having the six hairs
i have left fall out...
and still have to
be cut again.
I'm afraid that's
a possibility.
You see, with kennedy you
don't get these "maybes"
and "possibilities".
Yeah, but you gott
a have the surgery again.
Dr. Kennedy is an
excellent surgeon.
Isn't there some
way you people
could just agree?
Sure.
Convene a tumor board.
What the hell
is that?
A meeting of the
chief of oncology,
an oncological
pathologist,
and other specialists
who then work together
to reach a consensus.
Then i guess you hea
r what they have to say?
Well, your uncle
will not be present.
They will pass their decision
along to both of you.
What you do then is
still your decision.
And kennedy
will be there?
I assure you,
no surgeon
would miss it.
Not much to him,
if you ask me.
What, you mean
he's not kennedy?
You make life
and death decisions
because of a
man's name.
It's only sloan
fuckin' kettering,
the best cancer hospital
in the whole world.
Excuse me.
And let me ask you
something about this
jfk worship of yours,
what about hoffa
and the teamsters?
That was
the brother.
Oh.
Dr. Krakower?
Hi, yes, thanks
for calling me back.
I was referred by
a dr. Jennifer melfi.
Yes, i would.
Any time that's
good for you.
That's gre
at, that's fine.
Grove avenue, right.
Okay, i gotta
go, bye bye.
Who was that?
It's the paving guy.
I'm thinking of having
the driveway redone.
You smoking?
What is this,
the third degree?
This says
with pulp.
You like it
Not this much, i like
the one that says some pulp.
What the fuck
was that for?
I'll write
you up a list.
Oh, honey, i
missed you so much.
You know, i figured ou
t that this is the longest
we have ever been
away from each other.
Did you miss me?
Sure.
Somebody drop this?
Well, ho
w was it?
It was pretty good.
They had playstation two
right in the hotel room.
And?
That was the sum
total of your trip t
o your nation's capital?
I guess.
Alrigh
t, i'm sorry.
The orange
juice is fine.
Whatever kind you
wanna get is fine.
Fuck the orange juice.
Alright, i give
up, what then?
All the money you give
to angie bonpensiero
and who knows what
other widows you've
got on your payroll.
It's a business
expense.
But there's not
enough to make sure
your own daughter
is protected?
I won't pay.
I know too muc
h about extortion.
Big deal, he
pat you down.
Pat me down i can do
standing on my head.
It's every
fucking thing else.
He came into my apartment
in the middle of the night
and embarrassed
the shit out of me
in front of adriana.
Yeah, i heard he
strip searched you.
I'm not fuckin
g kidding, tony.
He's a sick fuck!
He was sniffin
g her fucking panties.
What?
You heardme.
Look, i don't deny that
paulie could be a little...
quirky.
He always has.
Christopher, you're
moving up very fast.
Why do you
think that is?
Are you gonna say
it's'cause i'm
your fucking nephew?
So, be a big boy
and suck it up.
The patient,
soprano comma corrado,
male, caucasian,
72- years- old.
Presented three months ago
with severe weight loss
and early satiety.
He was scoped and
a four millimeter mass
in the greater curvature
of his stomach was detected.
A ct scan revealed no
evidence of metastasis.
Dr. Kennedy
was referred in
and he recommended
gastric resection for cure.
There were
no surprises.
I thought
we had it.
I was told we had
clean margins.
Often, too little
healthy tissue
was taken from
around the tumor site.
Which leaves the
possibility, a
s in this case,
for a false negative.
You want the man's
whole stomach?
If there's a problem
with the procedure,
we'll take it up
on a board level.
Meanwhile, what are we
gonna do with this guy?
He's high risk.
His pressure fell below 60
systolic for eight minutes
on the table.
The incision's
still fresh.
I can do it in
half the time.
If we don't do surgery,
we do 5- f. U.
Which works how well
on an adenocarcinoma?
Not very.
Which is why we decided
to go in, in the first place.
So, what do
i tell mehta?
Mehta?
Sloan- kettering mehta?
Your patient sought
a second opinion
with dr. Mehta.
Forget it then.
The last thing i
need is to operate
with that little shit
looking over my shoulder.
I'll tell him.
Yes, i'll have
him there, thanks.
Don't sugarcoat it.
If you concentrate
on your breathing,
it'll be easier
all around.
The girl said she'd
page dr. Kennedy.
Where the fuck
is he?
Alright, 20 minutes
and i'll be back.
You go too
easy on him.
Probably.
Hey, if my nephew
cubby wasn't dead,
i'd have a soft
spot for him.
Did you sniff that
girl's panties?
He told you that?
Fucking baby!
You got
to apologize.
T, i'm not
apologizing to him.
You were
out of line.
He's gonna marry t
he girl, for chrissakes.
As of the
wedding day,
anything that touches
her pussy is off limits.
You think
it's all up?
Soon enough there'll
be more where
that came from.
Sounds like you were going
at it pretty good in there.
My pain a source of
entertainment to you?
You see me laughing?
I brought you
a milk shake fro
m "31 flavors".
It's all your
fucking fault anyway.
I'm throwing up day and night
since i started the chemo.
Oh, right.
I gave you cancer.
You don't know what
this is like, anthony.
I can't do it.
Kennedy was right.
What's he
got to say?
I can't get him
on the phone.
The nurses won't put
me through to him.
Why not?
I leave messages
at the hospital,
at the office.
I sent him
a box of cohibas.
I couldn't get
past reception.
He didn't
call you back?
Who knows if they
even tell him?
Last night the
machine says,
"if it's an emergency,
press six."
So, i press six.
Still no call back,
24 hours later.
He must be
very busy.
Yeah, that must be it.
You go
t his number?
Three more weeks.
Three more
fuckin' weeks.
His fuckin'
answerin' machine.
What are ya
gonna do?
These doctors,
it's not like on tv.
Dr. Kennedy,
this is tony soprano,
corrado soprano's nephew.
My cell ph
one is 917- 555- 0157.
Call me back any
time, day or night.
It's important.
Batter up.
Bye.
Now what?
Get in.
You're not even
married yet,
you're dipping int
o whores already.
Didn't cost
me a quarter.
I don't
pay for it.
How'd you find me?
Better be careful.
If i can do it, so
can your bride- to- be.
So, what is this?
Some new rule
about who i fuck?
You want more
shoes, what?
No, funny thing is
they don't even fit her.
I don't know why i thought
she was a size 10.
I don't know either.
I'm here to tell
you one thing...
you ever go whinin
g to the big man again
about shit between
you and me,
we'll have a problem,
my friend.
You seen these?
The fuck is that?
My godson
got it for me.
They're all ov
er the fuckin' place,
we gotta bring one
into the club.
Watch and learn, phil.
Watch and learn.
What are you doing?
Hey, doc,
it's me, tony.
Corrado soprano's
nephew.
You belong to
this club?
Me?
No, no, no.
I came here
to see you.
If it's about
your uncle,
you'll have to
call my office.
You might need
a new secretary,
i don't think
you're getting
all your messages.
For you...
titanium.
I use one, added 1
0 yards to my drives.
Thanks, but i really
can't accept it.
For everything you'v
e done for my uncle.
Anyway, what a
m i gonna do with it?
I've already got one
and mr. Williams here...
he don't play.
Right?
Stupid fucking game.
What can i do
with it?
What is it, jack?
He'll just
be a minute.
Well, i could use a
little extra distance.
Who couldn't?
You know, my uncle, he's
not doing so well.
He's got a bad reaction
to that chemo.
That happens
all the time,
there's nothing
that i can
really do.
You know, there
are worse things
that can happen to
a person than cancer.
My uncle think
s he's gonna die.
He's convinced ofit.
You know how old people
are with their superstitions.
He thinks it's'ca
use he went against you.
I was his surgeon,
that's all.
You got a bee
on you hat.
Show that man the
respect he deserves.
Answer his
phone calls.
Cheryl, make sure
mr. Soprano is
scheduled for--
just rememberit.
Everybody's marriage
has problems.
Is he seeing
another woman?
You can make
that plural.
Yes, he sees
other women.
I sort of lo
ok the other way.
I want to help him.
Do you?
Moments ago you used
the word "divorce".
I said i was
considering divorce.
I may be overstepping
my boundaries here,
but you are jewish,
aren't you?
Is that relevant?
Well, us catholics,
we place a great deal of sto
in the sanctity of the family.
And i'm not su
re that your people--
i've been married
for 31 years.
Then you know how
difficult it can be.
He's a good man,
he's a good father.
You tell me he's a
depressed criminal.
Prone to anger,
serially unfaithful.
Is that your definition
of a good man?
I thought psychiatrists
weren't supposed
to be judgmental.
Many patients want to
be excused for their
current predicament
because of events
that occurred in
their childhood.
That's what psychiatry
has become in america.
Visit any shopping mall
or ethnic pride parade
to witness
the results.
What we say in here
stays in here, right?
By ethical code
and by law.
His crimes...
they are...
organized crime.
The mafia?
Oh, jesus.
Oh, so what?
So what?
He betrays me every week
with these whores.
Probably the least
of his misdeeds.
You can
leave now,
or you can stay and hear
what i have to say.
You're gonna charge
the same anyway.
I won't take
your money.
That's a new one.
You must trust
your initial impulse
and consider
leaving him.
You'll never be able to
feel good about yourself,
never be able to quell
the feelings of
guilt and shame
that you talk about...
as long as you're
his accomplice.
You're wrong about the
accomplice part though.
Are you sure?
All i do is make sure he's got
clean clothes in his closet,
and dinner
on his table.
So, enabler would be a more
accurate job description
for you than
accomplice.
My apologies.
So...
you think i need to...
define my boundaries
more clearly,
keep a certain
distance,
not internalize my--
what did
i just say?
Leave him.
Take only
the children.
What's left of
them and go.
My priest said i shoul
d try and work with him,
help him to be
a better man.
How's that going?
I...
have you ever read
"crime and punishment"?
Dostoyevsky?
It's not an
easy read.
It's about guilt
and redemption
and i think were
your husband to
turn himself in,
read this book
and reflect on
his crimes
every day for seven years
in his cell,
then he might
be redeemed.
I would have to
get a lawyer,
find an apartment.
Arrange for
child support--
you're not listening.
I'm not charging you because
i won't take blood money.
And you can't
either.
One thing you
can never say...
that you haven't
been told.
I see.
You're right,
i see.
You're fucking
poisoning me.
I don't know how much
more of this i can take.
You taking
good care of
this young man?
Jesus, dr. Kennedy.
How you doing, guy?
I been busy,
you alright?
Doc, don't bullshit
a bullshitter.
Is this shit
gonna work
or should we go
back in the room?
You got a
top guy here.
Him?
The guy i'd go see
if i needed to.
I'll be a
sonofabitch.
The important
thing is
you stay strong an
d keep fighting, alright?
That's m
y home number.
You start to feel
punk, you call me.
Thanks,
dr. Kennedy.
I'll check back
on you wednesday.
Take good care
of this young fella.
Carm.
What?
You sick?
Everybody else in this
family sleeps all day,
i thought
i'd try it.
You, uh...
depressed...
or what?
I figure in the division
of labor around here,
that's your job.
'Cause if you want
to go to therapy
on your own
or something...
i've noticed you b
een a little tense lately.
That's rich.
You suggesting
i go to a shrink.
I don't
have the time.
I'll still go to
yours if you want.
You know best.
That dean
called today.
Well, that
can't be good.
I told him to put us
down for the 50, 000.
Carmela, i
gave you five.
Now...
maybe i could go
another five, maybe 10,
but that's enough.
Tony, you gotta do
something nice for me today,
this is
what i want.
You gotta
do this.
Alright,
i'll go to 10.
That should be enough
for those morningside
heights gangsters.
I already
told him 50.
50 g's.
Yes.
You look like you could use
a night off from cookin'.
What do you say
we go out?
Captions copyright 2001
home box office
a division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.