NARRA TOR: Previously on Stargate SG-1.
(BABY CRYING)
Wait. Where are you going? I want to see.
She is Orici.
With the wisdom of the ages
she will lead us to glorious victory.
Merlin was conducting research
on some kind of new invention,
a weapon capable of
destroying Ascended beings.
MEURIK: Arthur and his knights left
to quest for the Sangraal long ago.
It is said that they journeyed
to three distant lands
mentioned in Merlin's prophecy,
Castiana, Sahal, and Vagonbrei.
(GATE ACTIVATION ALARM BLARES)
Six more worlds have fallen to the Ori.
Two were Jaffa strongholds.
They attempted to resist, but were
overwhelmed within a matter of hours.
According to those
who witnessed the battle,
the enemy is led by a young woman
of extraordinary powers.
Six planets in eight days and they don't
even have their full team in the field yet.
Why haven't they
made a move against Earth?
In all probability, the Ancient device
in Antarctica is giving them pause.
At least until the rest
of their battle fleet gets here.
I got it! I got it.
I made the connection.
Sir Gawain to Gwalchmei,
Culhwch, and Olwen. Verus Gen Bree.
And you say I'm hard to understand.
(STAMMERS) Oh, it's Vagonbrei,
one of the planets Arthur and his knights
went to in their quest for the Holy Grail.
I got the gate address.
While on PX1767,
we got the names of three planets,
Castiana, Sahal, and Vagonbrei,
three possible destinations
for Arthur and his knights
in their quest for the Holy Grail,
what we know to be Merlin's weapon.
Unfortunately, what we didn't get
were any corresponding gate addresses
and the process of going through that
library page by page looking for clues
could have potentially taken years.
So I knew we were going to have to
narrow the search parameters a little.
That's when it hit me. Sir Gawain.
Wasn't he one of the knights
who says, "Ni"?
He was a knight of the Round Table,
and in one his earliest incarnations,
an old Welsh tale, he went on a quest
to help rescue a lost love.
The legend says that Sir Gawain,
a.k.a. Gwalchmei,
visited several lands
over the course of his adventure,
including a place called
Gwlad Gan Brenhinol Gwir,
which is Welsh for
"The land of royal truth."
Translate that into Ancient and
you get "Verus Gen Bree." Vagonbrei.
So how does that get us a gate address?
It doesn't,
but it did give me something very specific
to look for in Merlin's library,
namely, references to Gawain.
Now, based on this information,
I started scanning through the titles
and I found this.
Now, the entire volume is dedicated
to Gawain's adventures
and includes several
very interesting illustrations,
including a depiction of a sword
he once carried.
Note the symbols engraved on the blade.
- A gate address.
- Vagonbrei.
Well, we won't know till we check it out.
Well done, Doctor. Colonel Carter,
what's the status of the Ori supergate?
Any attempts we've made to dial out
to the Ori galaxy have failed.
It looks like they're blocking us
from their end.
There is a mothership in the area that will
alert us to the arrival of any other ships.
More ships? We can hardly deal
with the ones that are already here.
You have a go. Find that weapon.
- Yes, sir.
- Will do.
I was talking to SG-1.
You're not going anywhere.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
General, I'm hoping
you might reconsider your decision
and allow Vala to come with us.
Given everything she's put you through,
you're the last person
I would have expected to ask me that.
Yes, sir, and I'm hoping that impresses
on you just how strongly I feel about this.
Look, I know she's no angel.
She's lied, she's stolen, she's cheated,
she's misrepresented herself.
She's lied.
But she also risked her life to warn us
that the Ori were on their way
and almost sacrificed herself
to shut down the very first Ori supergate.
I understand the contribution she's made.
The truth is, the Pentagon
isn't willing to roll the dice on her.
But you could convince them otherwise.
You see, 10 years ago,
General Hammond sat in that very chair
and he was faced with a similar decision.
As former First Prime to Apophis, Teal'c
had committed some terrible crimes.
As the former First Prime to Apophis,
Teal'c provided valuable insight
to the enemy's resources and tactics.
And as the mother
to the leader of the Ori army,
Vala may hold the key to stopping them.
If I push this issue
and the Pentagon agrees
to let her join you on off-world missions,
then I'd be the one ultimately
held accountable for her actions.
Yes, sir. I understand, sir.
So I'd be counting on you
to keep her in line.
Yes, sir.
So can I go on the mission?
No. You're not cleared
for off-world travel yet.
You still have to go through
a psych evaluation.
What's that?
It's sort of an interview given to
all prospective SGC personnel,
designed to assess
a person's psychological state,
get a sense of their mental well-being.
Oh, to find out if I'm...
(MAKES STRANGE SOUND)
...wonko.
Right. So, they're going to
sit you down in a little room,
get you talking about yourself,
and ask you a few questions.
- So it's a test?
- Sort of.
And all I have to do is pass.
How hard can that be?
I'm gonna have to do some research,
so I'm gonna use your computer
while you're away on this mission.
You know what? I'd prefer if you didn't.
There's a lot of sensitive material in there.
Great. Be careful!
Time to go.
I said no, and you can't access it
without my password!
Already got it. Thanks!
I... But the...
MITCHELL: This place is deader
than a Texas salad bar.
Hello!
It is obvious this village
has long since been abandoned.
General. What brings you by?
Just thought I'd see
how you were getting along.
What are you doing?
Just a little research
for my upcoming mental appraisal.
You can't cram
for a psychiatric evaluation.
That's what they want you to think.
It's a battle of wits.
My mind against theirs.
They'll try and confuse me
with their trick questions,
but I already have the correct answers.
There are no correct answers.
For instance, when they ask me,
"What do you consider your biggest flaw?"
No, they won't ask that question.
My answer will be that I feel
I am too much of a perfectionist.
You see, I put a positive spin
on a negative.
Yes, that was very transparent.
Question two. "You are in the desert.
"You see a tortoise lying on his back
in the hot sun.
"You recognize his plight,
but do nothing to help. Why?"
Why?
Because you are also a tortoise.
Guys, you should take a look at this.
Whoa.
I thought I liked to sleep in.
CARTER: Dr. Reimer.
REIMER: Colonel Carter, Colonel Mitchell.
I understand you've got a bit of
a medical mystery on your hands.
MITCHELL: What we have here
is a village full of skeletons.
CARTER: We found a few
lying on the ground,
but most seem to have died in their beds.
I think we can rule out violence.
Anything left besides bones?
Sorry, Doc, whatever happened
here happened a long time ago.
REIMER: Let's go take a look.
Did the village records give an indication
as to what befell these people?
No, but it does make mention
of some Ancient lore tied to the area.
According to legend,
a cave overlooking the village
was once home to Morgan Le Fay.
(EX CLAIMS)
In Arthurian myth,
Morgan was a powerful sorceress.
King Arthur's half-sister
and an adversary of Merlin.
That would suggest
she may have had a hand in
the disappearance of the weapon we seek.
Now, Morgan, like Merlin,
was a purported magic-user,
so it makes sense that, again like Merlin,
she was once Ascended.
One who foresaw the dangers
presented to her and her kind
by a weapon capable
of destroying Ascended beings.
So she took the weapon from Merlin
and went into hiding.
On three possible worlds. This being one.
We've got to find that cave.
Why did I have to tag along
on this little hike?
You got somewhere else you need to be?
Yeah, how about at home in bed?
I got pulled off inoculation duty on 865
to come here and pull a double shift.
I've been up 18 hours straight.
What is it?
Birds.
What birds?
My point exactly. I first noticed it in
the village, now here in the forest as well.
An unusual stillness.
There are no birds,
or any other animal life, for that matter.
All right. So what happened to them?
Vala. I'm Dr. Hutchison.
Have a seat.
So, how are you feeling?
Very well. Very well.
Well, you know, all things considered.
I mean, you'd assume I'd be a prime
candidate for acculturation difficulty,
enduring feelings
of displacement and alienation.
Perhaps even a little paranoid ideation.
But the truth is
I was able to adopt an abstract attitude,
which allowed me to release
some of my repressed feelings,
ultimately providing me
with a cathartic actualization.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
There's nothing here.
Maybe it's the wrong cavern.
We should continue searching the area.
CARTER: It's getting dark out, Daniel.
We should head back to the village.
Ackerman.
Yo, Ackerman! Wake up.
- What happened?
- We're done.
Sorry, Jackson.
Are you familiar with inkblot tests?
Okay. I'm going to show you
a series of images,
and I just want you to say the first thing
that comes to your mind.
Okay.
Courage.
Respect.
You look at this inkblot and the first
thing that pops into your head is respect?
Yes. Respect.
Okay. Vala, this is called a projective test.
It's designed to allow me a little insight
into your emotional state.
I just want to get to know you better,
not pass judgment on you.
I want to help, but to do that, I'm going to
need you to be completely honest
and spontaneous with your answers.
Do you understand?
- Of course.
- Okay.
I'm sorry.
Kindness.
Red team's wrapping it up.
Figured we'd do the same.
This can't be a dead end.
There has to be something here.
Take it up with Landry.
You can come back tomorrow,
knock yourself out,
strain your eyes all you want.
You're right. I could probably
get a fresh start in the morning.
All right, let's go home.
GRIMSBY: Hang on a minute.
Where's Ackerman?
Ackerman, come on! Bernie!
Ackerman. Let's go.
Yo, Ackerman! Wake up. Come on.
MITCHELL: He's asleep.
What the hell kind of diagnosis is that?
Dr. Reimer says he won't know more
until he's completed all the blood work.
There's got to be something more to it,
like a coma.
REIMER: No, I'm afraid not.
Coma patients don't respond to
outside stimuli. Pain, sound, touch.
Ackerman responds to all three.
He even flinches, reacts in his sleep state.
- Why can't we wake him up?
- I don't know.
I need to do more tests
before I can say anything for sure,
and we have to contact
Stargate Command
and have them send out
the necessary equipment.
I'm sorry, is that not something
you'd be better off doing back at the base?
Ideally, yes, but, unfortunately,
and just like Ackerman here,
all of our blood work
shows an elevated white cell count
and a marked increase in serotonin levels.
Whatever it is, we've all been infected.
You think this is the same thing
that killed the villagers?
Let's just say, for the time being,
I recommend we all try and stay awake
for as long as possible.
If we fall asleep, we may never wake up.
We're sending the medical supplies
through now, Colonel.
MITCHELL: Roger that, sir.
Sure you don't want a little more help?
I can send another team in Hazmat.
Until we know what we're dealing with,
sir, that would just be risking more lives.
- We can handle it.
- Understood.
I'm awake. I'm awake.
Compliments of Dr. Lam.
We have dextroampheta-something,
moto-whatchamacallit, caffeine pills,
and good old-fashioned coffee.
Go easy there, Grimsby.
How long have you been awake for?
I don't know, what, 24 hours?
Yeah, talk to me when you get to 40.
- You've pulled all-nighters before, right?
- Yeah, loads of them.
This feels worse, doesn't it?
Yeah, I thought it was only me.
I, too, am more fatigued
than I would have expected.
It has to be the infection.
It doesn't just keep you from waking up,
it makes you want to sleep
in the first place.
Well, in that case, Teal'c?
I prefer to rely on my tretonin.
Cheers. Reimer.
- What you got?
- Since we started monitoring him,
Ackerman has been in Stage 4 level,
what they call delta sleep
or slow-wave sleep.
We also noted that his brain is producing
a surprising amount of melatonin.
It's a hormone synthesized from serotonin,
a sleep-inducing agent.
That's what's keeping him asleep.
So all you've got to do is figure out
why his brain is producing the melatonin.
We're working on it.
Jackson, what did you find
in the town records?
A handwritten entry
from the village doctor
in which he mentions a sleeping sickness
that affected the town.
Now, he doesn't go into any great detail
but it does make mention of
a possible source for what was happening.
Morgan Le Fay.
See, it seems the villagers believed
she cursed them
for revealing her whereabouts
when King Arthur and his knights
came looking for her.
- So did Arthur find her here?
- JACKSON: Probably not.
If the villagers believed she cursed them,
then it's more than likely she escaped.
In any case,
we have to go back to that cave.
General, just wondering if they've reached
a decision on my mental well-being yet.
Dr. Hutchison isn't finished with you yet.
You're to meet with him again later today.
(SIGHS)
If I may speak candidly, General.
I have a feeling that
Dr. Hutchison is somewhat troubled.
In fact, I think he may be suffering
from Klinefelter syndrome,
though you didn't hear it from me.
The only thing Dr. Hutchison is suffering
from is the headache you gave him.
I suggest you stop playing games and
start taking this evaluation very seriously.
I thought I was.
Let's call that delusional memory.
(DOOR CLOSES)
MITCHELL: You know,
it was Jackson's idea
to come back here
and check this cave out again.
I can't help noticing he's the only one
who didn't make the trip.
TEAL'C: Daniel Jackson made it clear
that his time would be better spent
continuing his research
of the town records.
CARTER: Here.
Dr. Reimer wanted us
to take some soil samples.
Why?
Just in case this is where
Ackerman picked up the infection.
(BEEPING)
Hmm.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hello.
Hello. May I have a moment of your time?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm just on my way out.
I've got a meeting.
With Dr. Hutchison, I know.
That's why I'm here.
I promise to be quick.
My name is Richard Woolsey.
I work for
the International Oversight Advisory,
a civilian-run organization made up of
representatives from the various nations
involved in the Stargate Program.
And what can I do for you, Mr. Woolsey?
Why don't I tell you
what we can do for you.
We can see to it that you pass your
psychiatric evaluation with flying colors,
effectively putting any doubts Stargate
Command may have about you to rest.
And what would you want in return?
Just a little insight into the weekly
goings-on here at Stargate Command.
You see, despite the fact that
all signatories to the Gate Alliance Treaty
are de facto partners
in the Stargate Program,
my employers are often left out of the loop
when it comes to the more sensitive
developments here on the base.
We'd just like you
to keep us updated is all.
So you want me
to be a spy.
(CHUCKLING)
I've read your file, Ms. Mal Doran.
I don't think
what we're asking is that unusual
for someone with such a colorful history.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(BEEPING)
Cam, Teal'c? I think I found something.
What you got?
Well, it's a faint energy spike.
I almost went past without noticing it.
Shazam!
- I guess Daniel was right after all.
- MITCHELL: Yes, he was.
We should check this out.
Would it not be prudent for one of us
to return these samples to Dr. Reimer
as quickly as possible?
No, he's right.
We're on the clock
and we have no idea how deep this hole is.
All right, I'll go back.
Stay in radio contact.
At least as long as you can.
Do you really think these will hold me?
Oh, those aren't restraints.
We're hooking you up to a polygraph.
It's also known as a lie detector.
It measures certain variables,
like blood pressure and heart rate,
to determine
whether you're being truthful or not.
Oh. I see.
All right. Let's get started, then, shall we?
And what's your name?
Vala Mal Doran.
Where did you spend the last week
on Earth?
Here at Stargate Command.
- Have you ever stolen anything?
- No.
That depends on how you define "stolen."
These are control questions
designed to gauge your reaction
by eliciting both truthful
and deceptive answers from you.
You're doing fine. Just
try to relax.
(EXHALES)
You're looking very nice today.
Oh, thank you.
- You're looking rather dashing yourself.
- Oh, thanks.
I mean, nice.
(STAMMERS) I mean, not objectionable.
Colonel, come take a look at this.
This was in that soil sample
you brought back from the cave.
What is it?
I believe it's a parasite.
- Is it dead?
- No, it's dormant.
Ackerman may have
somehow awakened one.
Well, how? It doesn't seem
to respond to movement.
Excuse me. Let's see what happens
when they come in contact
with live tissue.
Whoa.
I'll lay odds that's your culprit right there.
These people would have
had no understanding of microbiology.
They probably came up
with the story of Morgan's curse
because they couldn't comprehend
what was happening to them.
CARTER: Hey.
Where's Grimsby?
He said he was on his way back.
He isn't here?
Oh, no.
Perhaps we should rest.
No. That's a bad idea.
And I am starting to regret staying up late
to watch Deuce Bigelow: European Gigolo
last night.
Check that,
I regretted it almost immediately.
(FAINT RUSTLING)
- Am I imagining things, or...
- I heard it as well.
Grimsby!
Sam?
JACKSON: Well, we found Grimsby.
He's asleep, and we can't wake him.
Dr. Reimer?
What's wrong? Has his condition changed?
Well, you could say that.
He's dead.
REIMER: I see evidence of a ruptured
aneurysm near the pineal gland.
There's something else in here.
REIMER: What the hell?
Morphology is identical to the parasite
we found in the soil sample.
Only it's grown 1,000 times bigger.
I'm assuming things didn't go well.
I fail to see the point
of that ridiculous exercise,
unless its purpose was
to thoroughly humiliate me.
Those questions weren't intended
to shed light on my character
or delve deeply into my subconscious.
They were merely little reminders
as to exactly why
I don't belong here.
Then I take it you've carefully considered
our offer and come to a decision?
I have.
Whoa.
(EX CLAIMS)
MITCHELL: Okay, question.
If what took out the village
is what killed all the wildlife around here,
how come that little sucker's
alive and kicking?
It may possess a natural immunity
to this mysterious affliction.
Yeah, that's exactly my point.
So, all we got to do
is catch Joe Bob there,
take him back up to Carter and Reemer...
Reimer, whatever.
They reverse-engineer an antidote and
Bob's your uncle. We sleep till Tuesday.
TEAL'C: Indeed.
Yeah.
Carter, it's Mitchell.
(RADIO STATIC)
We have progressed too far
within the cave system.
Yes, we have.
All right, well, we'll nab Junior first,
then we'll call Carter
when we get back up to the surface.
Progress?
We've been theorizing that when
the parasite enters the bloodstream,
it triggers the body's immune response
and the production of serotonin.
Then it makes its way to the patient's
brain, where it lodges and feeds.
Feeds?
- On what?
- Melatonin.
Our analysis showed the parasite
we removed from Ackerman
gorged itself on the stuff.
CARTER: It stimulates the production
of melatonin, which floods the body,
that's why the urge to sleep
is so powerful.
That's why the urge to sleep
And once you give in,
the parasite just keeps on feeding
until the engorged parasite affects
the surrounding cranial tissue,
eventually provoking a lethal aneurysm.
But we're thinking that it may be possible
to starve out the parasite,
so, to that end,
we have isolated a specimen that
we awakened from a dormant state.
(GROANS)
Dr. Reimer? Dr. Reimer!
It's his heart!
Sam...
He's dead.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Ah, Vala.
Oh, not you again.
You know, you have
another scheduled appointment.
What would be the point of that?
You people have already made up
your minds about me.
Is that what you think?
Well, it's not like I haven't encountered
this sort of thing before.
You know, I saw it every day
in the eyes of the people
who couldn't separate me
from the Goa'uld who enslaved them.
So, you know, instead of becoming
a victim of their arrogance and stupidity,
I chose to take advantage of it.
So I lied, I cheated, and I stole.
I'm not going to apologize for it
and, to be perfectly honest with you,
I can't guarantee that I won't do it again.
All right?
Of course, I have recently
found myself risking my life
for something other
than my own personal benefit.
Maybe it's just a phase. Hold it, please.
Or maybe it's because, for the first time,
I've actually met someone
who, in some small way,
actually believes in me,
but I'm sure you're right.
I'm sure it will pass.
What?
CARTER: Daniel!
- You can't fall asleep. Do you hear me?
- Yeah.
We can't take any more of these, either.
With our serotonin and melatonin levels
spiking, it's too dangerous.
We're going to have to rely on each other,
all right?
Okay.
Easy, there.
Easy. Don't worry.
I'm not going to hurt you.
(GRUNTS)
I've got it, Colonel Mitchell!
On your feet, Colonel Mitchell.
There is much ground to cover
if we are to reach the surface.
No, you... You go ahead without me.
I'm just going to...
I'm just going to stay here. I'm cooked.
Then I will carry you if I must.
Forget it. No.
Tretonin or not, it's going to
catch up with you at some point.
The important thing for you
is to take Kermit back to Carter
and what's-his-name
and get them started on the cure.
Indeed. I will return for you,
Colonel Mitchell.
And I'll be
right here
waiting on you.
Sam! Sam.
I can't do it anymore.
You have to. You got to hang in there
just a little while longer.
In here! Dr. Jackson, Colonel Carter,
where's the rest of your team?
Reimer and Ackerman are dead.
- Teal'c and Mitchell went to the caves.
- What caves?
Get them in the isolation pods.
No, wait. Wait.
No, wait.
We can't go to sleep.
It's okay. We'll take care of you.
No, you don't understand.
The parasite. It feeds on...
(INAUDIBLE)
(COUGHS)
Take it easy, Teal'c. We've got you.
Take it easy.
We've got some sort of animal here.
We need to take it to the lab.
Yeah, I was getting worked up, cussing at
Teal'c, telling him to, "Go on. Leave me."
Must have been 20 minutes
before I realized he had gone
and I was sitting there talking to myself.
JACKSON: What about you?
Any hallucinations?
Yeah, when they put me in the pod,
I imagined I was being put in a coffin.
I thought I was being buried alive.
Well, rise and shine. How are you feeling?
Rested and raring to go, sir.
I assume Dr. Lam got you up to speed.
CARTER: Yes, sir.
Between the sample
they collected from Teal'c
and the research
Dr. Reimer and I conducted,
they were able to produce a serum
that effectively isolated the parasite
and starved it out.
I just hate that that cave was a dead end.
We went through all that for nothing.
JACKSON: I wouldn't say that exactly.
I did find one reference in that library
that might prove to be useful.
Atlantis.
You think the location of Merlin's weapon
is hidden in their database?
I think it's worth checking out.
(PHONE RINGING)
Carter.
I see. We'll be right there.
There seems to be a problem
in the gate room, sir.
I never liked you
and I know you can hear me.
Dial the gate now! Dial the gate!
Don't make me come in there! You stop it.
What's going on?
I'm leaving.
I'm not staying somewhere
where I'm not welcome,
and don't even think about
making me stay against my will.
Wouldn't dream of it.
But I figured you'd want to stay
after going through all the trouble
of passing the psychiatric evaluation.
I passed?
Dr. Hutchison seems to think
that you have a lot of potential.
He does?
He feels you can make a significant
contribution here at Stargate Command,
and I agree.
Congratulations.
I'm a little
overwhelmed.
But as my first official act, I'd like to
report a rather disagreeable little man.
That would be me.
Mr. Woolsey's offer was part of the test.
We wanted to make sure
we could trust you.
I knew that, but were his sexual advances
part of the test?
What? That's... General, I can assure you...
Well, I would have even
considered playing along,
but some of his requests were...
Well, a little unusual, even for me.
General, I would never...
General... General, wait...
So when do I get
one of these SG-1 badges?
You don't. You're not a member of SG-1.
You're a probationary member
of Stargate Command
who will be subject to some very intensive
scrutiny for the next few months.
Oh.
Don't screw up.
And welcome aboard.
See, I still think it's cause for celebration,
so I say we go out, have lunch, and I'll pay.
Pay with what, exactly?
Well, Daniel will cover me
until I get my share of the loot.
Loot?
Yeah, from all the treasures we're going
to bring back from our off-world travels.
What, I have to wait until I'm off probation
before I can start collecting?