NARRA TOR: Previously on Stargate SG-1.
What exactly do you want from me?
The code to an Ancient tablet
that I helped Qetesh locate long ago.
CARTER: I take it
the anti-Prior device is working.
MITCHELL: Well,
he didn't stop us from zatting him.
What the hell is going on?
I had to be sure
this was working on her first.
We've got to go.
(CHATTERING)
You're bluffing.
You have nothing.
I'll tell you what.
I'll bet you everything I have
on this table against
that cargo ship of yours outside.
Your winnings wouldn't cover
the value of that ship.
- What if I throw in this?
- And what's that supposed to be?
(MEN GASPING)
You've got your wager,
as foolish as it may be.
I guess it's just my lucky day.
I thought this was
an honest establishment.
It is.
And that's why it's necessary
to have you searched.
I don't suppose we could call this even.
Adria?
Hello, Mother. It's good to see you.
It's been far too long.
I did not expect to see you again.
I had to return, Mother.
My work here is unfinished.
Who is this?
You really don't want to know.
Get out, all of you.
(MEN MUMBLING)
I don't suppose you're going to let me just
walk out of here?
I'm afraid not.
I'm sorry to have to tell you this, Mother,
but your attempt to destroy the Ori
was unsuccessful.
Am I supposed to take your word for that?
I've been personally supervising
the construction of dozens of ships.
Now that our intergalactic gate
is operational again,
there's nothing to stop them
from coming here.
We should have the entire galaxy
converted in a matter of months.
Just because you've been building ships
doesn't prove anything.
What are you doing here?
Where are your friends from Earth?
Friends come and go.
Have they abandoned you?
I'd rather not talk about it.
I really must know, Mother.
You do realize, in a traditional
mother-daughter relationship,
I'm supposed to be the bossy one?
Oh, whatever.
Makes no difference now, anyway.
I've got it. I figured it out.
Got what?
The answer you were looking for
to the Clava Thesaurusy thingami-jigamy.
The Clava Thessara Infinitas?
Right, that's the one. I know where it is.
The Clava Thessara Infinitas, literally,
"The key to infinite treasure,"
is the Ancient tablet
Athena was seeking from Qetesh.
Now, it supposedly holds the clues to
the whereabouts of a vast storehouse of...
Daniel, this is very interesting.
Get to the good part!
The good part?
I figured it out.
I know where the treasure is.
You solved the Clava Thessara Infinitas?
Yes, I most certainly did.
Daniel shared some of his findings
with me last night before I went to sleep,
and after a rather, well, nasty dream
in which I appeared on
a television program where it seemed
you had to dance with supposedly
well-known personalities
in front of a panel of judges,
a shape came to my mind.
The symbol for infinity?
Yes, infinite treasure, infinity. You see?
And it intersects with six symbols, which,
when combined, correspond with
a gate address.
Why would the Ancients use the Earth
symbol for infinity to hide their treasure?
Actually, no one knows the exact origin
of the symbol itself.
It's been found on Tibetan rock carvings
dating back over a thousand years,
as well as a host of other places.
For all we know, it could well
have originated with the Ancients.
You can rotate that symbol
any which way you want.
Yes, but this is how
it appeared in my dream,
and when we put these six symbols
into the database,
it came up with only one address.
Why does this all sound familiar?
Did Adria not send you information
in dream form to lure us to the planet
where the Sangraal was hidden?
Yes, but, no, this is different.
I came up with this on my own.
Okay, I suppose it is possible
that Qetesh knew its location
and this is simply a latent memory
being dredged up by Athena.
There you go.
Do we have any idea what
this Ancient storehouse actually contains?
No idea, sir, but it must be big if Athena
was so eager to get her hands on it.
I feel very strongly about this, General.
What can it hurt to send a team?
I didn't send you that information.
That's what I tried to tell them,
but they didn't believe me,
especially when the
reconnaissance team returned.
(ALARM SOUNDING)
What is it?
SG-3 and 8, they're coming in hot.
Open the iris.
(MEN GRUNTING)
They're right on our tail! Shut the gate!
Shut it down!
Do it!
Med teams to the gate room immediately!
What happened?
It was an ambush, sir.
Ori soldiers made our position
as soon as we stepped through the gate.
I lost two men, a couple more injured.
That's not possible. That can't be.
You tell that to the men who died.
- Colonel, debrief in my office.
- Yes, sir.
I was so certain that I was right,
I couldn't leave well enough alone,
and the very next night...
I had the same dream again.
Only this time, the infinity shape appeared
vertically rather than horizontally.
Note that, again,
it intersects with six symbols,
and that, again, the six symbols
only match one address in our database.
What?
What's the problem?
We need to investigate this.
- Vala.
- What?
- Do you not see what's going on here?
- No.
This is Adria telling us where to go
so she can pick us off.
Next, you'll have a dream
where the symbol is on a slight angle,
and I'll bet it will still correspond
to one single gate address.
- She's using you, Vala.
- No. I would know.
Well, you didn't know before, did you?
VALA: Things just got worse from there.
Daniel, what's happening?
It's not looking good. Most of the I.O.A.
Delegates think you've been compromised.
But I didn't do anything wrong.
I was trying to help.
It doesn't matter
what your intentions were.
If Adria can manipulate you like this
any time she wants to,
then you've become a security risk.
They're talking about removing you
from the team.
What?
They're also not comfortable
with the idea of letting you go,
given everything you've learned
about Earth's defenses.
I don't understand.
They're talking about confinement, Vala,
at Area 51.
You don't believe me either.
You can't lie to me, Mother.
I can read the truth in your mind.
I'm just surprised.
So was I.
How did you convince them to let you go?
I didn't. That's the funny thing.
VALA: I guess they thought a locked door
could hold me.
Or they never imagined
I'd make it off the base.
What do you plan to do now?
Well, I had just won myself a cargo ship
when you dropped by
and broke up the game, so...
Is that really what you want?
A life alone, always on the run?
That life no longer suits you, Mother.
You belong with me.
Return with me to my ship, and take up
your rightful place as Mother of the Orici.
Adria, stop it. I am not your mother.
I may have given birth to you,
but we are not family,
so stop pretending.
You just need time to think about it.
We will talk further on our way.
- Where are we going?
- To find the Clava Thessara Infinitas.
- You think it's real?
- I think Colonel Carter was right.
This might be knowledge from your time
as a Goa'uld
being dredged up
through your subconscious.
Well, you're too late.
Despite the fact that they didn't trust me,
they thought they should check out
the second gate address anyway,
just to be safe.
I overheard them planning the mission
as I was leaving.
Yes, but there's something
you're not telling me.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Don't play games with me, Mother.
If I have to force this information
out of you, it will be quite unpleasant.
They were worried about an ambush,
so they're taking the ship.
We can beat them if we travel by stargate.
Let's go. Now.
Howdy!
You didn't really think
we'd invite you to a party
and not disable
your funky powers, did you?
I have no idea what's going on.
Don't worry, Vala, it's all part of the plan.
Don't you ever speak to me, ever again.
Lower your weapons.
Buddy, I think you've got
the wrong planet.
Lower your weapons or we will all perish.
My master Lord Ba'al has targeted
this location from orbit.
What are you doing?
Carrying out my orders.
Okay, that wasn't part of the plan.
Welcome.
Don't waste your time.
I've learned a thing or two
from my Tau'ri friends.
This room is being flooded with
the same kind of EM field they generate
with that clever little device of theirs,
the one that prevents you
from using your mind powers.
You should know
that won't hold me forever.
Of course not.
But that won't be a problem
after I'm done with you.
They got the jump on us.
We had no time to react.
Exactly how did Ba'al
manage to pull this off?
I don't know,
but they had detailed intelligence.
He was aware of both our locations
and intentions.
The bigger question is,
what does Ba'al want with Adria?
Perhaps he intends to negotiate
for shared control of the galaxy.
She doesn't strike me as the sharing type.
Either way, we do not want
those two hanging out together.
Exactly. We have to get her back.
- We're on it, sir.
- Wait.
How's Vala?
Pissed.
Is somebody going to fill her in?
Absolutely. Just not us.
This isn't right, you know.
I escaped fair and square.
Bringing me back here
is tantamount to kidnapping.
Listen, we know you're upset, but you
have to understand, this is part of a plan.
Upset? Why would I possibly be upset?
Maybe because I was
betrayed and abandoned
by the only people in the entire galaxy
I thought were my friends. Don't be silly.
We are your friends,
and we did not betray you.
You didn't exactly back me up,
now, did you?
What she means is,
none of it actually happened.
What are you talking about?
This device is a slightly altered version
of the memory implant technology
we received from a race
called the Galarans.
We used it to create a fictional memory
and implant it in your mind.
And we knew you'd have trouble
understanding all of this,
so we took the liberty
of making a recording
before you underwent the procedure.
Look.
Tilt it up, all right. Oh, yeah.
Thank you, now I can see.
JACKSON: We're rolling!
Oh, we're on? Why didn't you say so?
JACKSON: Gum!
Thanks! Hello, gorgeous.
If you're watching this, you're obviously
back at Stargate Command
and you are probably thinking that
everyone around you has gone completely
- wonko.
- Wonko.
With the possible exception of Daniel,
who, let's face it,
was always a little bit...
JACKSON: Vala!
Sorry. Seriously, though,
substituting our memories was my idea.
Brilliant, I know, and incredibly brave,
but it was the only way
for the plan to work,
so if you are watching this,
you have obviously made it back,
and let me be the first to say, well done.
And enjoy the substantial pay rise
that's been promised to you
if the mission succeeds.
JACKSON: Okay,
that's enough. Thank you.
VALA: Okay.
How was...
We heard that Adria had returned
through the supergate.
Now, if the Ori are dead,
we thought we might be able
to convince her to leave quietly
with her army.
We knew that she'd be able to tell
if you were lying to her,
so, as far as you were concerned,
it wasn't a lie.
I escaped using a Sodan cloak.
You allowed me to be exposed to radiation
so that you could carry out your plan.
Your plan.
And no, that was also
part of the false memory.
We escorted you to the planet where
Adria found you and we dropped you off.
You slept through it like a baby.
So, no I.O. A?
No Reynolds' men?
No television program
about dancing with supposed celebrities?
Actually, that part was real.
How very disturbing.
Yeah.
- Comfy?
- You've made a terrible mistake.
Release me now and I will be merciful.
You're so much more pleasant
when you lack the ability
to snap my neck with your thoughts.
You're a fool, dealing with powers
way beyond your means.
When my army catches up to you...
Don't waste your breath.
Your army has no idea where you are,
and it'll be days before they even begin
to question your disappearance.
Even then, all their queries
will lead them to the Tau'ri.
If you intend to kill me,
you should know the Ori
will not halt their attacks on this galaxy.
I have no intention of killing you.
As a matter of fact, my whole plan
hinges on your being very much alive.
So you can ransom me for your freedom?
Far from it. You can offer me something
far more valuable,
control of your army.
- They'll never listen to you.
- No.
But they do listen to you.
There's nothing you can do
to make me bend my army to your will.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Agent Barrett has some information
regarding Ba'al's whereabouts.
I got a call from one of my agents,
undercover inside Ba'al's operations
here on Earth.
Apparently, the clones are planning
to meet as a group.
Where and when?
P3R-112, today.
- Not a lot of notice.
- I just got the intel an hour ago.
How reliable is it?
My guy's embedded at the top.
He wouldn't break cover
unless he was sure.
Well, we've been here before.
We have a pretty good idea of the layout.
- Take a Marine unit.
- Yes, sir.
Kind of a quiet spot
for such a big meeting.
- I think that's the idea.
- I'm not seeing a lot of movement.
I think I know why.
Looks like somebody got here before us.
No wounds. No sign of combat.
- Symbiote poison?
- I believe so.
Why would the Ba'als kill their own Jaffa?
I don't think the Jaffa were
the intended target.
At last, the guest of honor.
(SHRIEKING)
You two are about to become
very well acquainted.
Well, you've got to hand it to him.
The man throws a mean dinner party.
Well, he knows we're coming after him.
He's covering his tracks.
Indeed.
(BEEPING)
Stand back! I'm warning you!
- Just take it easy.
- We're not going to hurt you.
Much.
I thought they were all dead.
Apparently not.
And I believe I know why.
We've got a lead.
Once he woke up, our Jaffa friend
was surprisingly forthcoming.
He confirmed the fact that Ba'al was
behind the attack that killed all his clones.
Apparently, he had assembled them
for what they thought
was a meeting on the Adria situation.
Instead, he beamed in canisters
of symbiote poison.
Quite the door prize.
Yeah, whatever Ba'al's up to,
he doesn't want any witnesses.
Lucky for us, he didn't realize
one of his Jaffa uses tretonin.
- Any idea where he is now?
- Actually, yes.
The Jaffa was able to provide us with the
coordinates where Ba'al's ship is located.
The Odyssey is standing by.
You move out again in one hour.
Assuming for a moment
this Jaffa's telling the truth
and we actually find Ba'al's ship,
how do you propose we capture Adria?
Same way he got her off the planet.
We beam in, tag her and beam out.
It's a big ship, Colonel.
How are we going to find her?
Well, actually, it shouldn't be that difficult.
We're assuming Ba'al has
some sort of technology
similar to our own anti-Prior device.
Otherwise,
she would have used her powers
the instant he beamed her on board.
If we scan for those
specific EM frequencies,
we should be able to pinpoint her location
with a fair degree of accuracy.
All this presupposes that we get the drop
on him, and he doesn't raise his shields.
Yeah.
All right, then. Good luck.
Vala, you got a sec?
Sure.
You're welcome to sit this one out.
(STUTTERING)
Why? I mean, why would I?
You know why we're
bringing Adria back, right?
Sure, to tell her to take her army
and clear off.
And if she resists, we will take action.
By killing her?
- You're okay with that?
- Of course.
All right.
Wow. I take it we are cloaked?
- Pretty cool, huh?
- Yeah.
Colonel, the result of your scan is here.
This room shows a pronounced level
of the same EM radiation
generated by the anti-Prior device.
Looks like you were right.
Let's go get her.
That's it.
Don't worry. This will all be over soon.
(BEEPING)
Jaffa!
Odyssey, we are good to go.
Hey. Wake up.
Sorry.
It's not very comfortable.
Believe me, I know from experience,
but we're not taking any chances.
It's over, Adria.
(IN BA'AL'S VOICE) I'm afraid you're
mistaken. Adria is no longer available.
LANDRY: (ON SCREEN)
Ba 'al is in Adria?
Yes, sir.
It's the bad-guy equivalent of cordon bleu.
It actually makes sense
from his perspective, sir.
CARTER: Not only has he taken on
a more powerful host,
but Adria's also in control of the Ori army.
So he convinces them to do his bidding
and not hers?
When you think about it,
their goals aren't all that different.
Control of the galaxy,
worshipped by millions.
And if the Ori are dead, he'll never be
called to the carpet by the boys upstairs.
What do we do now?
Kill them both.
Hard to argue with that logic. It's a twofer.
Well, there's no guarantee that her army
would stop fighting even if she was dead.
The only way to be certain is
for her to order them to stand down.
Then how do we get her to do that?
Well, if Ba'al's symbiote is suppressing
Adria's consciousness,
we should be able to do the same thing.
- Swap Ba'al out for someone we can trust.
- The Tok'ra.
Doesn't suppressing the host
go against their fundamental beliefs?
Well, I'm sure they'd make
an exception in this case.
We've been trading intelligence with
the Tok'ra since the Ori ships first arrived.
They want to get rid of them
just as much as we do.
Get in touch. See if you can set it up.
In the meantime,
keep a close eye on your guest.
So, have you decided
what you intend to do with me?
Well, we're still weighing our options.
Teal'c here had a good idea.
- I can imagine.
- No, you cannot.
I must caution you against
doing anything too rash.
In fact, your best course of action
would be to release me.
I think we have
a difference of opinion there.
My whole plan was to order the Ori army
back out of this galaxy.
You let me carry it out,
we'll be rid of them forever.
That is our plan as well,
only without your participation.
What do you mean?
He means we're going to bring in
someone a little more reliable.
See, right now, you're like a Pinto engine
in a '71 Mustang.
We've got to swap you out
for a big-block Tok'ra.
It takes a great deal of effort
to suppress a consciousness this powerful.
The Tok'ra don't have the strength.
Not to mention the fact that I'll kill Adria
the moment you try to remove me.
Well, that's great. We can live with that.
Perhaps, but remember,
I'm sharing Adria's mind.
You would lose all access
to the knowledge I possess.
For example?
For one thing,
I can confirm the Ori are dead.
And that's just the beginning.
With my knowledge and your pluckiness,
we can accomplish a great deal.
Remember how we worked together
to locate the Sangraal?
As I recall,
your efforts were not particularly helpful.
Of course, it's your decision.
But it seems you only have two options:
Work with me to our mutual benefit,
or kill us both and miss out on
everything I have to offer.
You're just in time.
The Tok'ra contingent's about to arrive.
I am Ta'seem.
I will be performing the surgery.
These are my assistants.
Welcome on board the Odyssey.
I'm Colonel Davidson.
I'm sure you know Colonel Carter,
Dr. Jackson, and Vala.
Yes. I knew you as Qetesh.
Things have changed a little since then.
News that the leader of the Ori army
had been captured
came as a ray of hope to my people.
That being said, the extraction procedure
that we are about to undertake
is extremely difficult.
Even though we have refined
the process considerably,
there remains a very real risk
that Adria will not survive.
Well, the only other option we have
is to leave Ba'al in
and trust he's telling the truth, so...
Then we should begin immediately.
Zanuf, the symbiote that we brought,
cannot survive outside of a host for long.
The infirmary is this way.
Time to go.
What about our arrangement?
Oh, you mean the part
where you string us along
till you overcome the effects
of the anti-Prior device?
We'll pass.
(MONITOR BEEPING)
The sedative appears to be working.
Heart rate and BP are holding steady.
TA'SEEM: There it is. Let's begin.
We will need to work quickly.
The symbiote's autonomic response
can trigger complications,
even under anesthetic.
Initiating the first incision.
I need suction.
What's up?
Nothing.
Just didn't feel like sticking around
for the surgery.
You know, weak stomach and all that.
Hey, you sure you're okay with this?
Why does everyone keep asking me that?
Because she's your daughter.
And no matter what she's done, it must be
difficult to see her treated this way.
Let's get something clear.
She's not my daughter, Daniel.
The Ori impregnated me against my will
and forced me to bring her into the galaxy.
I was an incubator,
a shipping crate and nothing more.
I'm sorry, but I find it hard to believe
that you don't feel something.
I do. Satisfaction at seeing their plan fail.
There, I've severed
the primary nerve conduit.
You see how the filaments are retracting?
Now, moving on to the lateral...
(MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY)
What is it?
I was afraid this might happen.
- Hey, what's up?
- Trouble with the surgery.
What happened?
Ba'al decided to be
even more difficult than usual.
We were able to extract him,
but not before he released
a deadly toxin
into Adria's nervous system.
Can't the Tok'ra symbiote heal her?
Unfortunately, we were unable
to complete the implantation.
The host body was simply too weak.
Adria is unconscious at the moment,
but when she wakens,
she will suffer greatly before she dies.
The one thing we can do for her
is an increased dosage of the toxin.
It will kill her instantly.
In the interest of patient care
and for our own safety,
I recommend that
we administer it immediately.
Do it.
I'd like to be there.
Crap!
(ALARM BLARING)
Adria.
You and your friends
were trying to kill me, Mother.
I can't let that happen.
SG-1, come in.
What the hell's going on down there?
I'm getting reports that all sections
around the infirmary are being sealed off.
It's Adria, sir. She's barricaded herself in.
Is there any way you can
beam us directly there?
Negative.
She seems to be generating
some kind of EM interference.
We're going to need a cutting torch
down here ASAP.
You got it.
There's an auxiliary control console
on this level.
If I can get to it,
I might be able to override it.
Go.
(MOANS)
You can quit acting.
You're obviously not sick.
No, this body really is dying.
I just want to use what little time
I have left as wisely as possible.
By doing what?
Destroying me and my friends?
Don't be silly, Mother.
If I wanted to kill you,
I could have done it a long time ago.
No, I need time to prepare.
Prepare for what?
Ascension.
- Vala!
- Don't.
Vala, can you hear me?
Guys, it's Daniel. I can't reach Vala.
Daniel Jackson, what is your location?
Just outside the infirmary.
Adria's locked them in.
We are blocked as well.
Colonel Mitchell is attempting
to cut through one of the doors.
Well, you better hurry up.
I think I figured out
what she's trying to do.
Adria's trying to ascend.
Adria, you don't have to do this.
Granted, this wasn't part of my plan,
but I can still accomplish a great deal,
perhaps even more.
More what?
More deaths, more enslavement?
Don't attempt to play on
my compassion, Mother.
As you said, I'm not your daughter.
I'm an Ori.
Part Ori, part human.
That will soon change.
Great. Carter, how's that override coming?
Well, it's not.
I mean, it wouldn't do any good.
What the hell does that mean?
She's not actually in control of the system.
I think she's just holding the doors shut
with her mind.
Cutting torch will take too long.
- What is it?
- Your friends are very determined.
Daniel, I'm showing a coolant leak
in the hallway you're in right now.
Spotted that, thanks. It's Adria.
She's trying to distract us.
Well, it's a hell of a distraction.
That stuff's toxic.
You need to get out of there right now.
JACKSON: Yeah,
that's going to be a problem.
Can you shut it down?
I'll have to re-route coolant out of
the entire section. I'm on it.
Vala, if you can hear me,
I really need you to open the door!
Adria, stop it, please!
That's it.
I always wondered
if you had it in you to kill me.
Goodbye, Mother.
- Nice work.
- It wasn't us. Adria let go.
(COUGHING)
- Jackson!
- I'm okay.
Where's Adria?
She's gone.
JACKSON: And once Adria realized
she couldn't save herself,
she had no choice but to ascend.
What do you suppose this means for us?
To be honest, I'm not sure.
If the Ori are still out there,
then, presumably, she's joined the fight,
but if Ba'al was telling the truth
and the Ori are dead,
then she just assumed
all the power they once had.
Either way, we could see some incarnation
of her again down the road.
Holding a serious grudge.
At least we may take comfort
in the knowledge that Ba'al is dead.
Wouldn't put a deposit down
on that just yet.
When we were breaking Adria
out of Ba'al's ship,
I ran across another clone guarding her.
Killed him, but where there is one...
There may be more.
We captured and killed Adria and Ba'al
on the same day.
- Are you telling me this is all a wash?
- No.
We dealt the Ori movement
a serious blow today,
and we rid ourselves of Adria
for the time being.
That is definitely a step ahead.