Hey.
Jack Gallagher.
On and off. Where's Hank?
- That way.
Ok, tomorrow.
We'll have a room ready.
Same as last time.
Ok, he's here.
How long has he been up there?
Going nine hours.
Leonard Steinberg -
He checked in this morning
for a hernia operation.
Nine hours? Food, water?
A bathroom break?
Just stands there on the edge,
looking down,
Threatening to jump
if anyone comes close.
Uh-Huh.
Police negotiator's
getting so frustrated
He's about to
push him off himself.
I called you hoping
for a little magic.
Nine hours. Tommy!
Yes, Dr. Gallagher?
Do me a favor,
will you?
Call Mort's deli for me
and order, uh -
Order a sky-high pastrami
sandwich, lean, on rye,
With some new pickles,
and rush the delivery.
Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait!
Make that two sky-highs and
a couple of deli cream sodas.
Money's in my desk.
Thanks, Tommy.
There's no rush.
Plenty of time for a snack.
Hank, push the button.
You want to see me
go splat?!
Take another step,
dumb cop!
Mr. Steinberg, at least let us
get you some dry clothes.
Come on, a little closer!
See the middle-aged Jew
take his first flying lesson!
Sir, you don't
want to do this.
You want to bet, grandpa?
I'll even give you odds!
Who's this clown?
Gallagher, head shrink.
Wow.
Nice night for it.
You think you're gonna
talk me down.
Wouldn't even consider it.
Everyone's got a right
to die, Leonard.
News choppers were here earlier
before the weather blew in.
Sorry I missed it.
My family show up?
No idea.
"No chance"
is more like it.
Is that a new pickle?
Uh-Huh.
I could tell
from the crunch.
Mmm.
Man, that's good.
From mort's?
Where else?
Cole slaw or potato salad?
Neither. I'm watching
my cholesterol.
Me too!
Good one.
I'm kind of hungry.
Hey, you want some?
How come you're not trying
to reason with me?
Don't you have some medical
ethics or code or something?
Situation like this?
Kind of a gray area, Leonard.
You're weird.
Got to be to work
in a place like this.
Yeah, sure.
What the hell.
Catch.
Wha-
Gah!
You did that on purpose!
Who in their right mind would
toss a perfectly good sky-high
off a nine-story building?
Gone for good.
Splat.
Hey, I've got another one.
This time, how about
I hand it to you?
Oh, I get it!
Of course you do.
I've got another soda, too,
and a pickle.
The new ones are the best.
It's supposed to rain
again tomorrow.
No chance.
You want to bet?
I guess I could
hold off a day.
It's your choice.
My choice.
Okay, sir.
Easy.
You're some
piece of work.
Well, we all
are, Leonard.
I recommend it.
What?
Life.
- =Http:/www. Ragbear. Com=-
English Corrections P.L
- =Ææàãğü÷öä»÷é=-
Ê±¼äöá¼ºàïöº
Fong is out
with the flu. Still?
Mm-Hmm. Body aches,
congestion, temp of 103.
You know, I offered to go to her
place and rub hot oil on her chest,
But for some reason,
she declined.
Maybe you were too subtle.
You think? When's Dr. Belle
back from Australia?
It's a two-week conference.
What about Dr. Mayberry?
His wife's birthday.
Dr. Sunn?
Also the flu.
I guess we're gonna
have to call off the game.
Not yet. Malcolm says he's got
a few ideas he's working on.
Hey.
You working a double?
Uh, yeah, everybody's got the flu.
I feel great.
What's up?
Uh, we got a poker game we
organize about once a month -
People from the ward.
There's an opening
if you're interested.
When?
Tomorrow night.
It's just for laughs, you know,
cool off from work - Friendly.
Friendly? How friendly?
Who's coming?
It's me, uh, Dr. Jones,
Dr. Suarez, a couple of others.
All right, why not?
Where's it at?
Your place, 8:00.
we rotate hosts.
Uh-huh.
Sandwiches, drinks, and
something sweet, if that's cool.
Sure.
Great.
I'll tell everybody.
Suckered again.
Ms. Crane.
I'm Dr. Gallagher.
I'm - I'm looking
for Dr. Howard.
We have a deposition scheduled
for this morning.
Actually, the deposition
is with me.
What?
I'm filling in.
yeah, I don't think so.
Marcie Crane. I need to speak
to judge latimer immediately.
Yeah, I'll hold.
Excuse me.
I don't know what you and
the public defender's office
Are trying to pull, but
I'm here to depose Dr. Howard
Regarding his memorandum
to the court in the matter of -
Trey Hansen, charged
with first-degree murder.
I wrote the memorandum,
not Dr. Howard.
You did?
Yes, ma'am.
I assumed
you'd read my report.
Uh, of course
I read it.
Great. You're
the court reporter?
Yes, I am.
You ladies
like to follow me?
I'm sorry
for all the confusion.
Dr. Howard
was originally retained
By the public defender's office,
but he became unavailable.
So I stepped in.
Mr. Hansen
is a patient of yours?
Yes, yes, he is.
He's currently undergoing
treatment for his condition.
I'm sure he is.
This is some kind of crusade
for you, isn't it, doctor -
Save the innocent patient
from the clutches of the law?
Prosecutor or not,
Ms. Crane,
Shouldn't this be a crusade
for you, too,
as a representative
of the state?
Except that
your innocent patient
murdered another
human being.
Allegedly.
Marcie, Lynn Conivar,
PD.'s office.
We've met at several
bar functions.
Of course, Lynn.
Nice to see you again.
You don't remember me,
do you?
Sorry. No.
If I could have a moment
To review Dr. Gallagher's
memorandum?
No problem.
Can I offer anyone
anything to drink?
Tea? Coffee?
Pint of blood?
No, thank you.
I'm fine.
I, um, think
we're ready.
No objection.
I'd like to state first,
for the record,
That this deposition
is being held
At wharton memorial hospital
Per the defense and
so ordered by the court.
Noted.
Dr. Gallagher, when is the first
time you met Trey Hansen?
15 days ago.
So, approximately nine months
after the murder of Andrew Wohl?
That's correct.
In general, is nine months
sufficient time
For a psychiatric patient's
mental state
To change significantly,
for better or worse?
In general, yes.
So, the memorandum
that you prepared
describes Trey Hansen's
current mental state,
rather than any mental state that may
or may not have existed
on the day
the crime occurred.
Certain characteristics
wouldn't have changed.
Yes-or-No question,
doctor. It's "yes" and "no. "
Meaning that your report
may or may not be valid.
Objection.
Dr. Gallagher, what is
Trey Hansen's I.Q.?
I didn't conduct
those tests.
But you're familiar
with the results.
It's around 75.
Low.
Below average.
Is Trey Hansen capable of
distinguishing right from wrong?
Yes.
Is he capable
of understanding
The consequences of his actions,
cause and effect -
For example, the cause of
his running a sharp knife
across the throat
of Andrew Wohl
And the effect of Mr. Wohl
bleeding to death
within minutes?
Objection.
Trey Hansen understands
cause and effect.
Thank you.
I'd like to direct
your attention now
To paragraph two
Of your very
imaginative report.
That concludes
my questions.
Well, that wasn't
too terrible.
It gets worse.
May we talk in private?
Of course. I'd like
Dr. Gallagher to stay.
This is my best offer -
Voluntary manslaughter,
15 to 20,
based on the retardation.
My client is innocent
of any crime.
Going...
...gone.
I'll see you in court.
I can't believe it.
Did we just break through?
Too soon to tell.
But it's definitely
a new wrinkle.
Anyone drop by to see him?
I called his ex-wife and kids,
told them he was here.
No takers.
Medication?
Haldol, Ativan, Cogentin -
5, 2, 1.
That should have
calmed him down.
Oh... he told me he knew
how to swallow his tongue
and suffocate.
That's a myth, isn't it?
Unless he bites
it off first.
How do you feel about
dying today, Leonard?
Thinking about it.
Any particular reason?
Well, I sure screwed up
my life pretty bad.
That's a fact.
And then there's the 56k
as of yesterday.
What happened yesterday?
No way the Cubs
lose that game!
Garza on the mound, Robinson
on a 16-game hitting streak,
St. Louis in the cellar -
No way!
Throwing error in the 9th.
Two runs scored.
Just my stinking,
rotten luck.
Wait a second.
You bet 56k
on a baseball game?
25.
Would have put me square
with Jimmy
And paid for
the hernia operation.
Now I'm dead meat.
Jimmy's your bookie?
He does this thing
with a ball peen hammer.
Then he throws you
off a freeway overpass.
And you figured
you'd skip step one.
Ah, you don't want
to kill yourself, Leonard.
How do you know?
You enjoy a good
pastrami sandwich too much.
It's not like I've got
other options here.
I'm tapped out,
asset-Free.
Cpa in another life.
Friends with money?
I hate pain.
That's very sensible,
Mr. Steinberg.
Leonard, supposing I wanted
to get in touch with Jimmy.
How would I go about it?
You came back, I see.
Dr. Gallagher.
The truth is,
I never really left.
I have another meeting across
the street in 20 minutes.
It was quiet here, so...
I have 131 messages
and e-Mails to return.
Wow.
Yeah.
Sorry if I broke any rules.
Well, you don't seem to have
done any permanent harm.
You know, I admire
the work you do.
I even admire what you're
trying to do for Trey Hansen.
Does that mean you're gonna
go easy on me in court?
Now, what did our friend
from the p. D.'S office tell you about me?
That you're a legend -
Unstoppable, never lose a case.
Destined
for great things -
Politics, private practice,
write your own ticket.
She mention my nickname?
"The great white. "
Flattering...
Till you stop to consider
It's Trey Hansen's blood
in the water.
It's never personal.
Really?
Come with me.
I shouldn't be here without
Mr. Hansen's attorney present.
He can't see you,
can't hear you.
Even so...
Trey Hansen lives
with his grandmother.
He has since he was 6.
I know that.
He works, he comes home,
And the two of them
cook supper together,
And then they watch tv.
Their favorite thing to do on
the weekends is go to the zoo.
He's terrified. He won't
last even a day in prison.
Now, tell me -
How is that not personal?
I don't make the law.
Whatever happened to the
victim's stolen wallet?
It was never found.
Absence of evidence
is not evidence.
You should have
taken the deal.
Your honor,
members of the jury,
We come here today
seeking justice.
The facts in this case
are brutally simple.
On the evening
of november 12, 2005,
Andrew Wohl -
Age 35, happily married,
With two children,
kevin, 8, and andrea, 6-
Entered Rock Garden - It's
a sports bar in west L.A. -
With the intention
of meeting two friends,
Having a beer, and watching
the game on the big-Screen tv.
You will hear testimony
from the victim's two friends,
Mr. Greer and Mr. Walker,
Describing an altercation
that occurred
Between Mr. Wohl and Trey Hansen
in this case...
How Trey Hansen went a little
overboard with his drinking...
Ugh!
...and his demeanor.
Don't touch me!
Hey, man, what is your problem, man?
Nothing.
I'm talking to you.
You will hear, as well,
The testimony of the bartender,
jason garcetti.
Ms. Crane?
Sorry, your honor.
The defendant
was subsequently ejected
From the rock garden by
the bartender, jason garcetti.
Get off, man!
Get off!
No, I'm not leaving!
Now, it should have
ended there, but it didn't.
About an hour later,
with the game nearly over,
Andrew Wohl left rock garden
and his friends
To return home to his family.
He never arrived.
Acting on descriptions
From Mr. Greer,
Mr. Walker, Mr. Garcetti,
And others that were present
at the rock garden that evening,
The police traced Trey Hansen
to his home.
They found there
a hooded sweatshirt and jeans
Stained with the victim's blood.
Also, they found
the murder weapon.
They found a diary entry
in Mr. Hansen's diary,
Describing the attack in detail.
Confronted with this evidence,
Mr. Hansen confessed
To the murder and robbery
of Andrew Wohl,
A confession
that was later withdrawn.
We come here today
seeking justice,
Justice for the murder
of Andrew Wohl,
Justice for his grief-Stricken
family and friends,
Justice for a heinous,
tragic crime.
We look to you,
members of the jury,
For justice.
Ms. Conivar,
your opening statement.
Is this inappropriate
contact?
Yes.
But it's not punishable
Unless I attempt
to influence your testimony,
Or you my performance.
Neither of which
is possible.
It's punishable to try.
Punishable - That's a good word.
That's a prosecutor's word.
Not right or wrong,
nor good or evil - Punishable.
It's how
we administer justice.
In your world.
Speaking of which,
you were brilliant.
See, there's no way that
you could know this, doctor,
But...
The trial's
already over.
And that's justice?
That's reality.
See, I have
a sympathetic victim,
A nervous defendant,
strong evidence, and -
And you never lose.
Someday I will.
Not today.
One question, counselor.
If your case
is so airtight,
Why did you offer a plea bargain
to the defense?
It couldn't be an act
of mercy, now, could it?
How much time do I have?
Prosecution witnesses
then another recess -
A couple of hours,
at least.
Okay, I'll be back in time
for my testimony.
I'll keep it moving along.
Is he in my office?
Hey, Jimmy brought
his bodyguard.
Two against two -
Fair fight.
Uh, you haven't seen
the bodyguard.
You got it?
Got it.
How much?
$15.95.
Let's go.
Old-fashioned sit-down
In a shrink's office -
That's a first.
Leonard Steinberg
owes you 56k.
Plus the vig.
There's no way he can pay.
Nice meeting you.
Wait.
In case you forgot yours.
This cost me $15.95.
It's gonna
cost you $56,000...
...plus the vig.
Lay it out for me.
Leonard's cut off for good.
He's out of options.
He's a compulsive gambler.
He needs treatment, not action.
I'm in the action business.
Give him a year
to get back on his feet.
Then he starts paying the
interest at a reasonable -
Reasonable rate.
Can't do it, doc.
Worrying about bad debts
keeps me up nights,
And I'm way down on sleep.
How many nights,
say, in a month?
Why?
How many hours sleep would you
say you average on a night?
Three, four.
Three or four? That's not
enough. You need at least six.
Sleep disorder is among the most
common psychological problems
We deal with...
and the most serious.
How's your
medical insurance?
You're looking at him.
well, there's this clinic.
It's hard to get into,
but I've got some influence.
Maybe we can work
something out.
That's all you got?
Maybe not.
Who does your taxes?
My sister's third husband.
The government's
eating me alive,
And idiot boy's
setting the table.
Leonard is a cpa.
75% of his hourly rate
goes to paying the debt.
What's in it for you?
9th inning, 2 down.
Your team's one up.
They've got two runners on,
And their best hitter's
at the plate.
What do you do?
Bring in a closer.
What if your closer
strikes him out?
Gets a save.
Well, that's what's in it
for me.
Just the occasional save.
I love baseball.
Conivar: based on your tests
and observations, doctor,
How would you describe Trey Hansen's
psychological condition
Now and at the time
of the murder?
He suffered then
as he suffers now -
From a tendency towards
magical thinking and misattribution.
Can you define those terms
for us?
Well, magical thinking
is pretty much as it sounds -
A belief in non-Causal,
nonscientific events,
Confusing fantasy
with reality.
Misattribution,
on the other hand,
Is having or believing in
false memories.
And could Mr. Hansen's
relatively low I.Q.
Be a contributing factor?
Yes, although
both conditions
can occur in highly intelligent,
highly educated individuals.
And those conditions
could explain the defendant's
initial confession
and diary entry?
We can't know for certain
what happened in that bar.
There are
conflicting accounts.
And if Mr. Hansen wasn't
the aggressor, as he contends -
And especially given
his inebriated state -
It's possible that he concocted
a revenge fantasy.
Then later, when confronted
with Mr. Wohl's murder,
He took it further,
Imagining himself
as the slayer.
That's why he picked up
the knife - his knife -
And brought it home.
And he recorded
that fantasy in his diary,
Later recounting the fantasy
as his story to the police.
So, how was court today?
Pretty much
as I expected.
Who are we
waiting on?
At least one,
maybe two.
What's up there?
Oh, bed, bath, closet, you know.
You renting?
It's all I could find on
the internet on short notice.
Is this your family?
It's my mum and dad,
sister, and I.
Dad died about a year
after that was taken.
Oh. I'm sorry.
Mum remarried
a couple of years later
To an american naval officer
serving with n. A.T.O.
When his tour ended,
he brought us back to the u. S.
They retired recently
to florida.
And your sister?
I haven't seen becky
in four years.
That's a long time.
I'll go.
What are you
doing here?
Playing poker.
not with me, you're not.
You want me to go.
Yes. No, no.
Look who I found!
I can't even
buy a hand.
All right. The pot's good.
Three players.
Bets.
Four bucks.
Raise you.
Mm-Hmm.
Call.
Re-Raise.
Again.
Call.
Last card.
Uh, check.
Bet.
Raise.
Call.
On their backs.
Three of a kind.
Straight.
Ohh!
you had to bet?
Yes. I flopped a nut straight.
Of course I had to bet.
Couldn't you know that he -
That he caught the flush?
Had you beat.
Oh, god. Unbelievable!
Read a book
or something.
Learn how to play
the game.
You're the expert.
There's frozen yogurt
in the freezer.
Okay, good night.
Night.
I'll walk you out.
Oh, no, don't bother.
Hey, thanks for everything.
Yeah. We're on again
next month.
Do me a favor - Don't cash this
for a day or two, all right?
I know you're
good for it.
Nothing like
a friendly game, huh?
Uh, Dr. Moore
requested a psych consult.
Right here.
Thank you.
I need help.
not here.
See me tonight.
I can't.
I'm dying.
Uh-huh.
I'll try.
Thank you, doctor.
Is this real
ice cream?
Real soy ice cream.
Don't think
I'm not grateful.
You got to get
used to the taste.
I'm talking about Jimmy,
what you did for me.
I just don't think
it can work.
Why not?
I'm gonna get the urge,
Dr. Gallagher.
Maybe not for a while.
Maybe I'd fight it.
But when it hits,
it's gonna hit hard,
And I'm gonna be looking
for someone to take my action.
Jimmy's not the only fish
in the pond.
You walk
out of here tonight,
How long before
you're back on the roof?
What if it's better
this time?
My losing streak's got to
take a turn sooner or later.
Jimmy went over
your losses with me.
Now, you usually bet
on the favorite, right?
Sit down for a minute.
That means that you should have
won maybe 60% of those bets?
That's what I'm saying.
I'm due.
You're cursed.
I'm cursed?
I want to try something -
An experiment.
I think I've got a deck
around here somewhere.
Yeah.
High card wins.
You want me to do that?
I- I got it. I got it.
All right.
Again?
Damn.
You want to
make it interesting?
Sure.
Okay, you're down 2-0.
8 more cuts, 100 bucks a pop.
My money against your time.
You win even one,
you get paid.
I win all eight, you owe me
eight weeks at gamblers united.
I'll sponsor you.
0 for 10?
You're on.
Damn!
What are the odds?
Astronomical.
I am cursed.
You see, there's - There's
something I don't understand.
How I can throw away my family,
my career, everything?
No, it's a disease, Leonard.
That I do understand.
Then what?
Well, you say you crave
the action, but what action?
What kind of thrill
can there be when you -
When you know you're gonna
lose almost every time?
Where's the fun in that?
No more questions,
your honor.
Ms. Crane, would you like
to cross-Examine this witness?
I would, your honor.
Proceed.
Dr. Gallagher,
the defendant, Mr. Hansen,
Isn't psychotic, is he?
No.
Bipolar, schizophrenic, or delusional?
Nope.
Clinically depressed
or suicidal?
Addicted to any substance or
a pattern of aberrant behavior?
No.
Suffering from
any neurological disorder
that might make him a danger
to himself or others?
None.
Would you describe
the conditions
Magical thinking
and misattribution
as serious mental diseases?
No, but they can have serious
consequences, as in this case.
Thank you for that
clarification, doctor.
If I saw a burning bush
on my way home from work today
And in the crackling sound
I heard the voice of god,
Could I be described as having
lapsed into magical thinking?
Well, that would
very much depend
On what type of smoke
you'd inhaled
And whether or not
you had much of a yearning
To be a biblical prophet.
Magical thinking, then,
Represents
a kind of wish fulfillment,
Seeing what one wants or needs
to see or experience?
To a degree.
Magical thinking
is wishful thinking.
That's
an oversimplification.
Is wishful thinking the product
of a diseased mind, doctor?
No, but, um -
Then I assume
it's entirely sane
For us to act
to fulfill our wishes?
Of course.
Such as robbing and butchering a
man we perceive to be a threat?
Objection.
Sustained.
Misattribution - The conviction
that a false memory is true.
More or less.
A man witnesses a murder.
He then remembers himself
not as a witness,
But as having committed
the murder.
I believe that's
exactly what happened.
Well,
the defendant confessed...
Then he un-Confessed.
When his true memories
reasserted themselves.
Or else, faced with the
possibility of incarceration
Or execution
for premeditated murder,
Mr. Hansen did a little more
magical thinking,
Instead becoming
the blameless witness,
Making the lie the memory.
Mr. Hansen has a history
of good behavior,
A steady job,
Good relationships
with co-Workers, friends, and family
Who universally describe him
as passive, shy,
And very good-natured -
No trouble with the police,
no acts of violence,
Despite a lifetime
of being made fun of
For being just
a little bit slow.
That's Trey Hansen,
Not the murderer
you're making him out to be
For the sake
of winning this case.
We know what, uh,
what you believe, doctor.
You - You care
about your patient,
And it also suits your case
to see him in that light.
But what about Hansen himself?
I'm curious -
How suggestible is he?
Could you, for example,
reconvince him
So that he, in fact, believes
he did murder Andrew Wohl?
It's possible to implant
false memories.
Could I,
hypothetically?
Hypothetically.
Given his ongoing condition,
Mr. Hansen
may never be 100% certain
If he actually
is a murderer or not.
Possibly not.
Then how on earth
can you be so certain?
How on earth can you?
I have a defendant with a desire
and opportunity to kill.
I have the murder weapon
in his possession.
I have his clothing drenched
with the victim's blood.
I have two confessions,
one unsolicited.
I have evidence, doctor.
Not wishful thinking.
I am certain.
That's how it's done.
Winning?
The job.
I gave you honest answers
without agenda.
You took what I said -
You twisted it.
You repackaged it
And sold it to the jury
as something else.
It's called advocacy.
Lynn, as an advocate
for Mr. Hansen,
Did a decent job
on your redirect.
It tends to balance out.
Sure, Lynn did a decent job,
but she's not in your league.
You were better.
You were tougher.
You were more driven.
So a man ends up
guilty as charged.
There's judge and jury.
There's court of appeals.
I'm a small part
of the process.
That's your excuse.
Why do I need one?
Someday, Marcie, you may.
I just hope when the time comes,
you'll know, uh...
You'll know where
to find the help.
Psychiatrist.
It's all so clear to you.
Do you think you know me?
What if the jury
comes back not guilty?
They won't.
What if they do?
Will you think
you might have been wrong?
Will you actually
take a look at Trey Hansen,
Not as a prosecutor
but as a human being?
Because if you did,
You'd realize all the
so-Called facts in this case
Prove nothing.
The real win here
is to set him free.
Set yourself free.
Jury's back.
"In the matter of the state
of california vs. Trey Hansen,
"On the count
of premeditated murder,
We, the jury,
find the defendant... "
And you...
"we, the jury,
find the defendant... "
"We, the jury, find
the defendant, Trey Hansen... "
Guilty.
"... Guilty of murder
in the first degree. "
guilty.
What really happened?
Hansen was waiting for the bus,
just like he said -
Wrong time, wrong place,
wrong emotional state.
He saw the murder.
He saw everything.
Resulting
in emotional shock,
Magical thinking,
and misattribution.
Here was his tormentor,
his enemy,
Lying helpless at his feet.
Who knows what Trey had imagined
on his own?
Whatever it was,
this was so much more.
What happened in the bar?
They found the real killer
eventually.
He had the victim's wallet,
and after he confessed,
The police went back
to the rock garden
And re-Interviewed
the witnesses.
Wohl and his two buddies -
They were regulars.
They knew the bartender.
They had too much to drink that
night and started riding Hansen,
You know, tripping him,
spilling beer on him.
He didn't know
how to fight back.
So he complained
to the bartender.
But when he did, he was the one
that got thrown out.
And everyone was very
contrite after Hansen died.
That's when the truth
came out.
Too late for Hansen.
Strangled in his
holding cell,
Waiting for transport to state
prison after the guilty verdict.
And too late for Marcie Crane.
She had a complete breakdown.
I read about the case
in the journal,
Got in touch
with her doctors.
That's when
we hatched the plan -
You know,
to re-Enact the trial.
How many times
have you tried?
This was strike two.
You see, all during
the trial, it rained.
So, whenever it rains
For more than a couple
of days in a row -
She relives it.
Yeah.
For Marcie,
winning is a reflex.
She won't give in.
She doesn't know how.
So, it's no good,
Us just pronouncing
Trey Hansen innocent.
We tried it the first time.
It doesn't work.
We have to somehow build a case
that's convincing enough
So that Marcie
is willing to lose.
At least,
that's the theory, anyway.
Next time,
can I play Hansen?
I don't know.
Can you?
I'll meet you downstairs.
Okay.
We came closer this time.
She almost tripped up over
the new memorandum to the court
And the new diagnosis.
Then there was
the plea-Bargain offer.
Also, she opened up to you
more than she has.
She even hesitated before
pronouncing the verdict.
You nearly
got to her, Jack.
Yeah, but in the end,
her verdict was the same.
Don't be discouraged, doctor.
We'll try again.
Next rainy days.
I'm sorry, denny,
but what am I supposed to do?
Half the staff's
still out with the same bug,
And they need me
to cover for a while.
Uh...
Well, that - That's sweet,
but don't bother.
I'll, uh, I'll get
something to eat
When I, uh,
when I-I get home.
Yeah, no, I mean, uh,
before I leave.
Okay.
Yeah, I-I love you, too.
Bye.
All clear?
I have to be home
by 11:00.
That'll have to do.
Oh, hey, wait up!
Hey!
Mort's?
Where else?
Pastrami?
Uh, brisket...
with new pickles.
sounds good.
Y- You know, you don't
have to go in with me.
Confession time?
When we cut the cards,
I stacked the deck.
I, uh, figured.
We're not so different,
you and I.
I'm scared, doc.
I mean, uh, eight meetings
of gamblers united -
That was the deal.
So why am I scared?
Well, maybe
because this time...
There's actually something
important at stake.
Win some, lose some, right?
Right.
www.tvsubtitles.net