Commentary, Suarez.
Uh, the patient
suffers from depression,
anxiety,
and disorganized thinking.
Artis.
Mr. Sawyer's
all over the map.
He also has
a very good grasp
of medical,
psychological terminology
straight out
of the DSM-IV.
Leading you to conclude?
Factitious disorder.
Do you suspect
Maliering?
There's no indication of symptoms
manufactured for material gain, no.
Correct...
both of you...
this time.
Is there something else,
Dr. Belle?
Our new Director of Psychiatric
Services arrives today,
but make no mistake,
as senior staff attending
with the overall responsibility
for your supervision
and training,
ultimately, whether you find
a place at this hospital or not
depends entirely upon me.
Any sign
of the new head honcho?
Nada.
I don't even know
what I'm looking for.
Country mouse
adrift in the big city.
He ran a clinic
in Vermont, Carl.
He wasn't plowing
the back 40.
God,
what was Nora thinking?
I say give him
the benefit of the doubt.
Maybe Dr. Gallagher
has something to add.
Like zero experience running a
high-volume psychiatric facility?
You're taking this well.
After I was
screwed out of the job,
I suppose it could have
always gone to you.
Should have.
Not while I have a pulse.
I refuse to get hysterical
about it.
Last name Martin,
first name Vincent.
We matched him up
to a missing-person's report.
He was stark naked, no I.D.,
screaming his freaking head off,
standing in the middle
of the highway.
Okay, pal.
Behave yourself, huh?
Docs here are gonna
fix you up just fine.
I see you!
- Have a Code white.
Get it off!
Security, code 3,
first floor.
I know who you are!
I can't be the only one.
Look.
Flesh -- human flesh!
No, no!
Hold it right ere.
You'll never make me
like you!
Keep away!
You can't have me!
Hey!
- Get back!
I'm real, too.
Flesh -- human flesh!
You're not alone.
Get down on the floor and
put your hands behind your head.
What about them?
We'll fight em together.
I've got your back.
Except we're outnumbered.
Might be better
to choose our battles.
Not give up!
- Not give up! Not give up! Bide our time!
Live. Live to fight
another day.
Huh?
Trust me.
Scratch the Haldol,
doctor.
Let's take the patient
to seclusion and clean him up.
Excuse me?!
Who the hell are you?
Dr. Jack Gallagher.
I guess
I'm the new head honcho.
Staff meeting
tomorrow morning.
I'll introduce you to everyone.
And after that, it's all yours.
So, there I was,
first day in the big city.
Suddenly,
it occurs to me...
"take
all your clothes off.
Give the hardworking folks
in admitting a cheap thrill."
You have to admit,
it did the trick.
You acted to gain
a patient's trust. Fine.
But what about the respect
and trust of your staff?
You think getting butt naked
on your first day of work
helped you
to achieve that?
Couldn't say.
Never tried it before.
'Sides...
it'll be forgotten
by tomorrow.
Really?
Posted
on the Hospital intranet.
Want the advice of a Harvard
Business School graduate?
Seek royalties.
It's been downloaded more
than Paris Hilton's sex tape.
You look great, Nora.
Move in, doctor,
but don't get too comfortable.
Another stunt like that,
and you'll be out...
...on your very public ass.
Did you hear
what happened?
I can't believe
we missed it.
Looks like we're about to become
a clothing-optional facility.
You have a problem
with that?
Mind says no,
but the body says follow.
Doctor.
Jack.
Veronica.
So, you worked under
my predecessor -- Dr. Friedman?
Yes, for 10 years
since my internship.
He was my mentor.
Can't believe he's gone.
Or that they brought in an outsider
from nowhere to take his place?
So, you're from the U.K.
Originally.
What tipped you off?
And you were in Somalia
with Doctors Without Borders.
That must have been
intense.
Yeah.
Huh.
Nice talking to you.
They're doing some
experimental drug therapy...
Vincent Martin,
I'm Dr. Gallagher.
We, uh --
we met earlier.
Do you remember?
I don't.
They gave me something.
Eh. That's just enough joy juice
to take the edge off.
All right,
here's the deal, Vince --
I'm gonna cut you loose, and you're
gonna promise not to get too excited.
It's okay, Ray. Anyone gets
hurt, I'm in a world of trouble.
You buy a one-way ticket
to Thorazineville.
When can I go home?
Answer a question first.
Why did you stop
taking your meds?
The blood work came back
your system's clean.
Been off maybe
two or three weeks.
I don't know.
Maybe I just forgot.
It happens.
The thing is,
according to your records,
it hasn't happened to you
in 12 years.
What do you see
out there?
It's not real.
It's in my head.
I know. I know that.
Well, that puts you
way ahead of the game.
I thought I could do both.
I can't. I was wrong.
Thought you could do both what?
- Don't worry about it.
Just put me back on my meds
so I can get back to my life.
Just slow down there, Vincent.
You just got here.
Come on. Let's take some time.
- I don't have time!
No!
Okay?
- I got to get home.
Getting you home
is what this is all about.
Grayson, hi.
I'm Dr. Hayden-Jones.
I understand that you'd like
to attend my resident day clinic
once you've
been released.
It's a condition
of my suspended sentence.
I understand
that you're a cat lover.
Cats are very intuitive.
A cat person is about the
nicest thing you could call me.
I agree. I just wish
I could have one now.
But my husband's
allergic.
And I like the longhairs
the best.
Mm. I have all kinds --
Tabbies, Siamese.
So I heard.
You had 20 in your apartment?
Mostly strays --
They follow me home sometimes,
or people give them to me.
I also heard
from the police
that you had a bunch of them
in your freezer.
When they died, I-I-I couldn't
bury them in the ground --
so heartless.
And I couldn't burn them,
you know?
Their beautiful fur?
When we lose someone we love,
it -- it just plain hurts.
But eventually, we --
we learn to let go.
I don't know
how to do that.
Well, that's what
we can work on here.
In-house pharmacist,
report to satellite pharmacy.
Dr. Gallagher.
I'm Edolie Martin,
Vincent's sister.
Oh,
I'm glad you're here.
Uh, you can see Vincent,
of course.
But first, I've got
about a million questions.
Um, I know
he lives with you.
Did you know
he's discontinued --
I want Vincent released
to me immediately.
I'm having him
transferred.
No, you're
having him committed.
To Twelve Oaks
Psychiatric Facility.
Ms. Martin, Vincent shouldn't
be institutionalized.
He's self-aware,
self-sufficient for many years.
This is a mistake.
I'm not asking, doctor.
I have Power of Attorney.
Sign here.
By law, I have 72 hours
to observe him.
He's only been here 8.
Then I'll be back in 64.
Oh, Dr. Gallagher.
I was wondering,
have you had the chance
to go through
the department budget?
Gave it a shot
last night.
Man, talk about a cure
for insomnia.
You do understand, of course,
that it's a part
of the Director's job
to approve the budget.
I'll get around to it.
- Oh, you're gonna have to do better than that.
For one thing,
the funding is about to expire
on my resident
day clinic.
This program,
which I founded --
Sure.
Resident Day Clinic, RDC.
I'll drop by later
and check it out.
Uh, okay.
Our new Director of
Psychiatric Services comes to us
from the Pinewood Veterans
Post-traumatic Stress Clinic
in Killington, Vermont.
Dr. Gallagher is board-certified
in psychiatric medicine.
Please join me
in welcoming Jack Gallagher.
First staff meeting.
Hot coffee, juice...
Jelly doughnuts.
The, uh --
the problem is,
we're in here,
and they're out there.
Who's out there?
Patients.
You see, gang, I'm thinking
this whole secret-society thing
isn't the best way to go.
So, starting today,
I've invited a few
of the patients to sit in.
You want us discuss
diagnoses and treatment
in front
of the patients?
Bang on.
There's a tendency --
and I'm as guilty as anyone --
to wall ourselves up from
the people we're here to help.
But it's -- it's really more
their hospital than ours.
We work for them.
They have the right to be
involved in their own recovery.
We're M.D.s,
not social workers.
M.D. as in "medical doctor,"
not "medical deity."
It's their heads.
These people are in our care.
They're our responsibility.
There are
liability issues.
Find the joker.
It's not there.
Unlocking the mysteries of
the human brain is no easy gig.
So, why not use
every possible resource?
Experiment,
break the mold,
use every trick
in the book --
Anything that gives us
an edge.
And if you're uncomfortable
with that, look,
I'll respect your prerogatives
as medical professionals.
And I hear
they're hiring at County.
Gypsy, come on in.
Have a little seat
right there.
What's the task?
Oh.
We're creating
personal agendas,
goal setting,
time allocation --
just determining
priorities.
Is there ever any, uh,
unstructured activity?
No.
- Oh.
You disapprove?
Hey, I'm just here
to observe.
Then observe.
Terrific, Steven.
Hi.
Oh, really? Okay.
I'll be right back.
Can I see you a minute,
doctor?
Ooh!
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
I heard the music.
It sounded cool.
I just figured --
you just figured
that you could waltz in here
and, on a whim, tamper
with my course of treatment.
It's a break from routine.
Three months ago,
most of those people
could barely get out of bed
and shower by themselves.
With the help
of my routine,
they're beginning
to lead productive lives.
All right.
You've created a safe,
quiet, controlled environment.
But reality is loud, messy,
and full of surprises.
The question is,
does it translate?
Just let me
ask you a question.
Do you honestly think
you're qualified for this job?
Probably not.
Then why are you here?
New challenge,
new surroundings.
Do you really care?
No, what I care about
is whether or not
you're planning on reading
the damn budget and funding me.
Can we finish this later?
What's going on, Vince?
Useless.
What is?
This is trashed.
I'll call maintenance.
Okay, Vincent,
you're an artist.
Not anymore.
"Can't do both."
Okay,
take another right there.
Oh, oh!
- Now take a left, take a left.
Oh, got it.
- Hey, hey.
Hi?
Is your mum around?
Um, are you
a friend of hers?
I'm a friend
of your uncle Vincent.
Is he okay?
My mommy said
he's sick.
When's he coming home?
I'm not too sure yet.
One second.
Um, I made something for him.
I-I'll be right back.
One second.
What do you want?
Some information
about Vincent.
You have
his medical records.
I need to know what he's been
up to for the last few years.
What's changed?
- Joshua, honey, can you go watch TV for a while?
Night before last,
my kids and I were awakened
in the middle of the night
by Vincent
ranting to himself.
When I tried to talk
to him,
he pushed me down on the lawn
and ran off.
You had no idea
that he's gone off his meds?
If I had, I would have
done something about it.
The police found him standing
in the middle of traffic!
He could have been killed...
or someone else.
I won't let that happen.
I am responsible for Vincent,
not you!
Kids seem
pretty attached to him.
When I was 15,
Vincent chased me
and my 7-year-old brother Leo
around the house
with a screwdriver.
Joshua and Emily have never
seen him when he's like that.
I intend
to keep it that way.
I know how schizophrenia
can rip a family apart.
Does Leo have much to do
with Vincent.
Vincent can't live here
anymore.
I don't suppose
I could see his room?
Visiting hours are over,
doctor.
Um, will you give this
to Vincent?
Of course.
Thanks.
Nora, hi.
Well, how the hell did he
just walk off the ward?
All right. Never mind.
Uh, no, no, no, no, no.
T-tell the police
not to confront him.
That's important. Tell them
to wait till I get there.
Yeah.
All right.
Come on in, doc.
Here he is.
Thank you.
Hey.
Go away!
I got to work.
If I lose this job,
I'll never get to go home.
Vincent, this is
what you do all day?
Uh-huh.
For 10 years.
They like me here.
I'm a hard worker.
Every day, I show up on time.
They can count on me.
That's all good.
- I'm independent.
I get my own paycheck
every week,
and I take it
to the bank.
I'm not a problem.
I take care of myself.
Is my boss
gonna fire me?
He doesn't want to.
You're a valuable employee.
How much trouble
am I in?
I can cover for all that
if we go back
to the hospital now.
No, no, no,
I need to stay here
and show them that they
can still trust me.
You need to get well.
Everything will be okay
if you put me back
on my medication.
I was stupid to think
it would be different.
What would be different?
Oh, I really messed up
this time.
Hey.
This is for you.
It's from Emily.
She sends her love.
She wants you
to get well, too.
Okay.
Hey.
Hi, guys. Come on in.
I have an assignment for you.
- Sure.
I need you to find Vincent's
younger brother, Leo, and talk to him.
He works for
a nonprofit organization
called, um, Earth Now.
It's on the West Side.
- I'll make some calls.
No, no, no, no. No, I need you to go
there and talk to him face-to-face.
You want us
to leave the ward?
Yeah. Problem?
We don't do that.
We're residents.
We treat the person,
not just the disease.
Vincent's friends,
family,
relationships that are
outside this hospital.
It's -- it's all the stuff
you can't pull off the chart.
Anything in particular
you want to know?
Yeah. For starters, I want to
know why he went off his meds.
Got it.
Good.
Okay. Thanks, guys.
Are you always as pissed off
as you look?
I'm a doctor,
not a freaking detective.
Yes, my sister.
Man, talk about having
a stick up your ass.
I take it you guys
weren't close.
No way -- I've barely talked
to her or Vincent
since our folks died.
That is about a year ago,
right?
Uh, yeah
car accident.
But we were a pretty
dysfunctional family anyways,
especially after Vincent
went bonkers.
Hey, Planet Now, guys.
Thank you.
My parents couldn't deal
with it at all.
They just kind of
checked out.
Who looked after you?
Well, pretty much Edolie.
So, maybe that's why she's got
that stick up her ass --
taking care
of a younger brother,
worrying about an older one
with a mental illness.
I know. Leo the jerk.
What else is new?
Hey, do you guys know
how many harbor seals
die every year off the
California coast of pollution?
I'm guessing
more than five.
Can we put a pin on saving
the planet for a minute?
Why do you think Vincent
went off his meds?
Well, my mom and dad left the
house we all grew up into Edolie.
I guess they figured
Vincent was too out of it
and I was just a druggie,
which I was.
Not anymore.
Uh, anyways, Edolie had
just gotten a divorce,
and Vincent was living
with her and the kids,
so they all moved back into
the parents' house together.
Vincent must have found
his old drawings.
It's just a guess.
Hey.
Are you seeing anybody?
So, if he'd never seen
the old drawings...
he never would have remembered
his old life.
Other than the carving
on the wall,
has Vincent tried to draw
anything since he's been here?
No. It's an interesting
thought, though.
Nice work, you guys.
You really should get out more.
Yeah,
I'd like a cab, please.
Ms. Martin? Anyone home?
Sir, put your hands
where I can see them.
Busted.
What's next?
Scaling the Hollywood sign?
Uh, celebrity stalking?
I made a house call.
Without
the owner's consent,
it's called
breaking and entering.
You're a hospital
Department Head!
You don't
make house calls!
I played a hunch.
It paid off.
Nice ride --
very L.A.
I just hung up
with Edolie Martin.
She's prepared to drop
all criminal charges against you
and forgo any civil suit
against the hospital...
if you agree...
to release Vincent
to Twelve Oaks now.
I still have 24 hours.
What could possibly change
in 24 hours
except for
that you lose your license
and the hospital
goes bankrupt?
Thanks
for bailing me out.
This is serious, Jack.
I have to convene
a medical-review panel.
Bring it on.
This panel
is here to discuss
treatment options in the case
of patient Vincent Martin.
We're on the record.
Here's the plan.
Bag the Haldol.
Let's detox him completely.
No medication, nothing?
I'll stabilize him temporarily
without drugs.
To what end?
12 years ago,
a doctor mixed Vince
a medication cocktail,
and he improved.
Since then, he's changed.
Hell, how we treat the disease
has changed.
Let's get rid
of the old chemistry
and figure out
how sick he really is.
Stabilize how?
Megavitamins, neurofeedback,
acupuncture,
homeopathic medies...
juggling tomatoes --
whatever works.
You can't treat schizophrenia
with aromatherapy.
The pharmacology's
been successful for...
a dozen years, huh?
Why deviate?
You call it a success.
I say the patient's
been crippled.
You mean creatively.
He's a gifted artist,
and for the last 12 year
he's been stuck
in a plumbing warehouse,
moving boxes
from one pile to another.
And that's
about to get worse.
He's about to be filed away
in an institution for life.
The preferred methodology
would be to restore Mr. Martin's
drug intake to prior levels
then reduce it incrementally
to establish a new threshold.
He's already gone through
most of the withdrawal.
We don't have the time
to go back to square one.
So, you said, "stabilize him
temporarily without drugs."
He's gonna need drugs.
Of course he is.
And counseling.
But the point is, we have
an opportunity right now
to build him
a new regimen.
Y-you don't have time
for that, either.
I talked to the attorneys.
Even if this panel grants you
the 20 or so remaining hours,
after that, the sister gets him,
and we risk getting sued.
I want every single hour.
It's worth the risk.
What happened?
Well, they found another freezer
in Mr. Emerson's garage.
More felines?
No. His wife.
Really?
- Mm-hmm.
I wouldn't have taken him
for a sociopath.
Oh, no.
She died of natural causes.
He doesn't kill.
He stores.
Cold comfort
to the wife.
Excuse me.
Could you give us a minute?
Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
Grayson,
are you all right?
Don't be disappointed with me.
- No, I'm not.
April was my whole life.
I wanted to stay close
to her until...
Until what?
The technology became available,
you know, to bring her back.
I just...
couldn't let go.
I-I enjoyed
talking to you.
I hope we can continue
our conversation.
We will,
because you'll come back.
Okay.
Take care, Grayson.
Go away.
Cut me some slack, Vincent.
I could use the company.
Huh?
What time is it?
It's late.
I-I can't.
That's all right.
We've got all night.
You got a minute?
Anything you need.
Oh, Jack wanted you
to be present today
at his meeting
with Edolie Martin.
No.
I'm in no hurry.
You can take as long as you need
to find a replacement.
Ronnie, why?
You know why.
You made your choice.
This is too quick.
Give yourself time to adapt.
Why should I adapt?
I'm worked here
my entire career.
This is my home.
And now I have to adapt?
The hell I will.
You me some guy
on a ski vacation.
Next thing I kn--
First of all, it was a conference.
Second of all,
I saw his clinic.
Can you help me out, nor
can you make me understand?
Jack Gallagher
hadn't been here five minutes
when he
stripped down naked.
Oh, I was there.
Would you have,
under any circumstances?
Would have found
another way.
Been more profession.
- Yes.
In that moment,
Jack didn't care about anything
but the patient --
not propriety,
not professionalism,
not ridicule.
That's why I hired him.
Sleep on this, please.
If you come back
tomorrow,
I won't try to talk you
out of it.
You never would have hired
Gallagher two years ago.
Go on, say it --
before I had cancer,
no, probably not.
That would have
been crazy.
Time's up.
Five minutes.
That all I ask.
Then you can lock the door
and throw away the key.
I love my brother.
I also know
what he's capable of.
I've lived with him
my whole life.
But now I'm a single mother
with two young children.
I won't put my kids
through that.
Sign it.
Look at these.
I-I've seen them.
I have hundreds of Vincent's
old illustrations.
He was a prodigy
before he got sick.
He won awards.
He hasn't worked since
he drew these last night.
He wanted that to be his last.
After that it's a quick
trip to the funny farm.
What are you proposing?
Vincent's now drug-free.
From here, we comprise
a new cocktail, get him stable.
This is Dr. Hayden-Jones.
She runs a day clinic here, and
it's shown remarkable success
in bridging the gap between
full-time and part-time care.
I would be
more than happy to --
to tell you all about it,
if you're interested.
What does Vincent want?
Vincent wants to go home,
be with his family.
And if that means
going back on his meds
and giving up
on his amazing gift and --
and hauling boxes
around a freaking warehouse,
well, then, so be it.
He's -- he's willing
to sacrifice everything...
because he loves you
and the children so much.
I'm not offering
guarantees.
The last thing
anyone wants to do
is put you or your children
in danger.
This is a chance...
- No more.
Thank you.
Uh, Dr. Gallagher,
join me.
Please.
Thanks.
How are you
settling in?
Sure opinions would vary.
Made quite an impact.
???A a change
from our last director.
He tended to operate
below the radar.
Probably very wise.
Dr. Friedman and I
had an agreement.
Hopefully you and I can achieve
a similar understanding.
Anything's possible.
As you may or may not know...
...I specialize in the fields
of addiction, pharmacology.
Growth areas.
And I've been
fortunate enough
to bring major
pharmaceutical companies
here to Wharton to conduct
their research trials.
That's impressive.
It is, and quite profitable
for the hospital.
So,
about this understanding?
In the past, I've enjoyed
a certain degree of autonomy.
Ah.
In exchange, perhaps
I can help you out, too.
I appreciate the thought.
Thank you.
I think you and I can become
great allies, Dr. Gallagher.
Looking forward to it.
You continue to have
a great day, all right?
Enter.
I just wanted to thank you
for supporting the clinic.
It's a good program.
Come in, come in.
Sit down.
Ay-Yi-Yi.
Yeah. Another roller-coaster day
in the fun house
and with you driving,
I have a sinking feeling
we're in
for more of the same.
Yeah.
You're married.
Yes.
To a jazz musician.
Eight years this June.
You're not.
Close...no cigar.
So, who was she?
Someone I met in med school.
- Mm-hmm.
She was an oncologist.
Nearly went that route myself.
So, how did you
wind up a shrink?
I guess I've always
had brains on the brain.
Short story?
Dad was in the military.
Mum worked as a nurse
at the V.A. Hospital.
Sometimes I used to
go by there after school.
Hey, kid.
Comeere.
Come here.
Do me a favor,
will you?
Scratch my foot.
I can't reach.
No, no, no.
The other one.
Whew!
Come on!
It's killing me!
Whew!
Thanks a million, kid.
So, here's this guy,
and his head's telling him
there should be a foot there,
even when his eyes
can't see it.
And I'm thinking,
"interesting."
Still is.
And I'm thinking,
"I haven't got a clue
who you are or if that story
is even remotely true."
Hang in there.
It'll be fun.
Oh,
I'm not going anywhere.
How are you feeling?
I'm feeling.
Everything seems
really different.
Medication didn't just take away
your ability to paint.
It took away the --
the passions, the pains,
the highs, the lows --
everything that made you human.
I'm afraid I'm gonna
lose control again.
It's possible.
It's got to be worth
the chance, though, right?
Look, if it comes down
to a choice
between my drawing
and my family --
hey, no choice.
- Of course.
But be patient.
You've only just started.
Right over there.
See?
Uncle Vincent!
Finally!
I missed you!
I missed you, too.
Looking good.
- How's it been going?
It's been kind of rough,
actually.
Well, you're back.
Hi.
Hey, guys.
It's good to see you guys.
Yeah.
Beck?
I'm glad you've called.
I was thinking about you.
Becky, please say something.
Let me know you're there.
I'm in L.A., too.
Can you believe it?
Listen, Becky,
you don't have to,
but maybe you could give
mum and dad a call.
They're, uh...
They'd love to talk to you.
You don't have to say anything.
You know,
just if you feel like it,
you could give them a ring.
I'm at Wharton Memorial.
It's on 3rd street.
You can always get me there.
Listen, Becky...
you know,
if you need anything --
Um, money or, uh...
Hey, hey, it's Jack.
Leave a message.
. Gallagher,
this is Wharton Memorial.
L.A.F.D. is in transit
with a potential suicide risk
for intake.
Female, age 15,
suspected drug- and
alcohol-related intoxication.
Please call in A.S.A.P.
Thank you.
Subtitles by LeapinLar
www.tvsubtitles.net