Previously on "Weeds"...
This was not what I had
in mind. Those are people's homes.
Fema's gonna set them
up at the marriott.
It's time to move on -- we
take you off the sales floor.
Traffic?
You'd bring in lots and lots of mota.
Holy shit.
That house belongs to celia.
Celia hodes.
She ran the whole thing.
They're all lying! Please help me.
Nancy: We're going to ren
mar. We're going to see bubbie.
She's somewhere far, far away.
The nurse was fired.
A family member called and said
he was taking over her care.
Hey, dad, it's your family.
Who the hell are you
bursting in here like this?
Why are you always such a prick to me?
I'm just not sure you're mine.
- What, are you on the run?
- Yes.
Well, that at least I
can wrap my head around.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Weeds
Season04 Episode02
Bingo.
Bubbie --
who knew?
Nice dress, mom.
We should have done this years ago.
Burn down the house
and move to the beach?
We can hear the ocean.
How great is that? Listen.
That's silas watering his
pot plants in the shower.
Silas!
Okay. The hair...
identity crisis, new
start -- I get it.
More importantly, the plants.
The plants need to grow somewhere
else, out of this house now.
What are you so paranoid about?
I'm paranoid about len.
He wants to be called lenny.
If len sees those, he might flip...
or steal them or smoke
them -- we just don't know.
The bottom line is -- we don't shit
where we eat or eat where we shit.
Either way, words of wisdom.
Well, then where am I
supposed to put them?
Figure it out, young
botanist. Just get them gone.
Where are you going?
I need to buy a bed skirt.
I want to go shopping for a bed skirt.
You don't even know what a bed skirt is.
Do too. It's like a dust ruffle.
How do you know what a dust ruffle is?
- All gay boys know what a dust ruffle is.
- Silas.
That's right, I'm a big
fag, so you can suck my dick.
Please, can I come with you, mom?
No, honey.
I need some alone time, and you just told
your brother to suck your dick. Gross.
Where are you really going?
I just told
you -- errands.
Dressed like that?
Good morning, andy.
- len.
- Lenny.
How long does it take portnoy
up there to finish his business?
Use the downstairs bathroom.
I don't like the toilet in there.
It's got a padded seat.
It's like taking a shit on a mushroom.
I've taken a shit on mushrooms...
and on a mushroom, actually.
Of course you have.
Listen, bonnie and clyde, I don't
know what you two are running from.
And you know what? I don't care.
Why don't you just give me $300 in
cash right now, and the subject is dead?
Okay.
Nice doing business with you.
Hey, so, I'm doing something
potentially illegal today.
What sort of potentially illegal activity
are you engaging in in that dress?
I got a page. He gave me an address.
Who? Your john?
Guillermo.
"Psychotic gangster, burned
down agrestic" guillermo?
Do you want to keep
living with your father?
It's work. It's fine.
Keep your cellphone on.
In case of injury or imprisonment?
In case I need something
from the supermarket.
Like a rape kit? I don't think
they sell those at ralph'S.
It's work. It's fine.
Okay, have a good day at the office.
Maddy shaheen. I'm the public
defender assigned to your case.
Am I getting out now?
You just have to sit tight
a little while longer.
The charges won't stick.
Oh, good. Thank god.
No one actually saw you drive the escalade into
the convenience store, so we're totally cool.
Escalade?
It's says "escalade." That's
what came through the window,
unless it was a highlander or
one of those big lincoln things.
What is it? A navigator?
What are you talking about?
- Felicia harken?
- Celia hodes.
Hodes. Okay. Right. Hodes.
Hey, any relation to dean hodes?
He was this loser who was constantly
hitting on me in law school.
No. No relation.
Okay. Here we go.
No, that is not it.
Are you retarded?
I'm just disorganized. You don't
have to be a bitch about it.
Ooh, here it is.
Uh, yeah, you're not getting
out of here anytime soon.
I pose a bigger threat to the public than
someone who drove a car through a store window?
Antidrug crusader
caught with grow house?
You're fucked like a
stray dog in chinatown.
I-I-I shouldn't
be in here.
The toilets are metal.
Anyway, your hearing
date's in three weeks.
You were on city council, so if you slept with any
cops or judges, it's time to call in the favors.
I'll be in touch, sally.
- Celia.
- Yeah. See ya.
Felicia? Not felicia.
Mamacita!
Hey, blanca.
You said you had a job for me?
Yeah, I do.
And good morning to you.
You need to get that fixed.
Obviously.
You're gonna take a little
drive for me today, blanca.
Go down to tj and get
that brake light repaired.
In mexico?
Cheaper labor there.
I know a good garage.
Once you get over the border, take any
left off revoluciÛn and follow the river,
paseo de los heroes, and look for the
beer-can/horsehead thing hanging outside.
Beer-can/horsehead?
Yeah, it's on the wall.
- And that's it?
- No.
I also want you to go to a
farmacia, get me some inhalers --
ventolin and aerobid. 10 each.
No, 15. Don't get me
flovent. It gives me a rash.
Uh, ventolin and aerobid.
Can you give me the address of this
place, and I'll put it in my gps?
Just, you know, follow paseo de
los heroes and look for the horse.
Use your eyes, spoon-fed americana.
Hey, there's $10,000 in it for
you if you don't fuck it up.
Ooh, $10,000.
No, no. Cash on delivery.
That's for the inhalers.
I almost forgot.
We got you a present.
Wait. What is that?
Yo, be gracious when
somebody gives you a gift.
No, I don't really
do this kind of thing.
That's good luck, man.
Don't fuck with good luck.
Just say, "thank you."
Well... how thoughtful.
And really... stuck on there. Thank you.
Eh, you'll be fine. Just
smile and just act like you do.
And, you know, you're gonna come back,
this money's gonna jump into your purse.
- Be a good day for blanca.
- Yeah.
What am I really doing?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
The money doesn't like
it when you ask questions.
It gets very sad and
wants to crawl away.
All right, all right. Off to mexico.
Iviva zapata!
Lenny: I'm gonna be at the track until
4:00, so you boys are basically on your own.
Just check the monitors, keep an eye on her
feeding tube, and check her diaper for deposits.
And roll her in the afternoon.
That's so she doesn't get bedsores.
Few minutes on each side.
It's a shame you boys never
got a chance to know her.
But you can blame your mother for that.
- Now, you, alan ladd.
- Shane.
- And klaus.
- Silas.
If either of you boys have any big ideas
about going through my things while I'm gone,
you can forget it.
It's all rigged to
blow your fingers off.
So stay out of my stuff if you ever want
to handle your little shmeckies again. Okay?
Now, I don't believe in wireless phones.
So if something goes wrong,
you can page me at the track.
And, uh, if she dies on your
watch, it's your fault, got it?
She does that sometimes.
It's not necessarily bad.
Okay.
- It sounds bad, grandpa lenny.
- It's not.
And when your uncle andrew crawls
out of that rattletrap van out there,
tell him I expect to be reimbursed
for everything he eats...
and tell him he's a thief and
that he still owes me $20,000.
I got to go. Bye.
You're on first watch.
Doug: Guess who finished the monster
po' boy at the gumbo junction.
5 feet of fried-fish goodness!
And it was free 'cause he ate
the whole thing in under an hour!
People sang and threw
beads. It was awesome.
Why are you here? Where is dean?
He's down in the lobby hitting on some
frumpy chick who dug him in law school,
and he wanted me to let you know
he's sorry there's no money for bail.
You fuckers ratted me out.
That might be another reason
why he's staying in the lobby.
Where's nancy?
Who? That nice widow?
She should be in
here, not me -- nancy!
My cellmate, chita, says that she's
gonna make me her special girl.
I have to get out of here now.
It's good to make friends,
ceil. Breach the divide.
"Why can't we all just get along?"
I like your hair.
I couldn't decide, but I just did.
I mean, it's nice off
her face, isn't it?
It's youthful.
My life is in danger.
Oh, come on. You know, you're probably
safer in here than you are in town.
People are outraged, ceil.
You know, your house
burned to the ground,
but people still spray-painted
"hypocrite" in the charred remains.
You have to get me out of here.
This is a nightmare.
And it should be nancy's
nightmare, not mine.
She does look scared, doug.
I am, baby. Mommy is terrified.
Then maybe this is a
good time for us to go.
I don't want you getting all upset.
I mean, this must be
really hard for you.
- No, no, no.
- Please, please, please.
I don't -- I don't want to
be anybody's special girl.
Visitation is over. Come on.
Help me. Help mommy.
Hola.
Yo quiero una brake light para...
this car.
Guillermo.
Una brake-light
especial. øHabla inglÈs?
S?
I need to get my brake light fixed.
Guillermo sent me.
Hybrid, eh?
Yeah, hybrid car.
Got to save those fossil
fuels -- dead iraqi children.
What's wrong with that car?
Broken taillight.
You know, I-I'm still under warranty.
I really don't want to blow that.
So when you're fixing my light, if you can just
make sure everything's back where you found it.
Oh, and while you're in there,
can you override the thing that stops
me from doing gps while I'm driving?
- I heard you can do that.
- That's illegal.
What was Guillermo thinking?
He thinks with his dick.
She is hot though,isn't she?
Una hora, you come back, eh?
An hour. Great.
Oh, I need a bag.
Small planet. I'm doing my part.
øDÛnde est* la farmacia, por favor?
Tell her to go to my
cousin's farmacia on Third.
No,no.Doming's brother's place
is cheaper and they have more.
Dominga's brother is unethical.
Are you calling my
brother-in-law unethical?
That's what I'm telling
you,he's unethical.
Why?
Fuck you.
Farmacia m*xima.
End of street, red sign, eh?
End of street, red sign. Gracias.
Mucho bueno. Gracias.
NO APARCAR
Andy: 10 minutes. That's my limit.
After 10 minutes in the same room
with him, I want to kill or be killed.
Shane's in there...
Just staring at bubbie's machines,
scared to death she'll kick on his watch.
Lenny's a master at giving
kids age-inappropriate tasks.
I'm surprised he didn't have
shane drive him to the track.
He says you're a thief.
Who did?
Lenny. He said you
stole 20 grand from him.
- And he wants it back.
- Unbelievable.
Unbelievable. You know what?
You're better off without
a dad. It fucks you up.
You're better off. At least
you can be your own person now.
I didn't mean that. I don't mean that.
I like your hair. I did that, too.
Tried to give myself a mohawk
using my mom's lady shaver.
You're damaged.
I was born into it.
Hola.
Oh, terrific. So, it's done? Finito?
30 what?
Dollars --
for the light.
You're charging me. Guillermo?
So, uh, what do I do now?
You go home. Have a nice day.
Pinwheels! Pinwheels!
Miss.øGuitarra?
- No. Um, diet coke?
- Yeah.
Jarritos.
- diet jarritos?
- No.
- Iced latte?
- Okay. I get for you, miss.
- It's $3.
- 3
Do you have change for a $50? øCambio?
No. Nobody have.
How much?
- It's two for $30, but for you, $25.
- S?
Uh, the,
um --
øguitarra?Yeah, guitarra.
Do you have a red one?
Mellow out, jesus.
Hey, miss. Una m*s latte, se—ora?
Oh, god, no. No, no m*S.
Um, ba—O. Is there a
ba—o around? Toilet?
Oh, no, no. No ba—O.
But there is a jack in the box
on the other side in san ysidro.
Gracias. Perfecto.
Turn around.
Fine. Enjoy the show.
Oh, god.
Not you.
Hi, sweetie.
Where are you? I've
tried you like 50 times.
Uh, I was in a parking
garage. What is it, honey?
Isabel texted me.
- Did you know mrs. Hodes is in jail?
- What?
She got busted for a pot house.
Your pot house, mom.
She's ratting you out.
Fuck!
Yes, mom. Fuck.
Okay, honey. I'm kind of busy
right now. Don't say fuck.
- Are we safe?
- Of course we're safe.
- I think we should change our identities.
- Got to go.
Have your passport ready.
Fuck, fufu ck, fuck, fuck, fuck,
fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Man: No passport?
I didn't know.
So, what were you doing in mexico?
There's this skin cream
-- fade cream, actually.
Probably poison, but
definitely effective.
You came all the way
here for skin cream?
Oh, yes. My skin is
very important to me.
It's the first thing people see.
Is that alcohol, ma'am?
Uh, no, sir. That's my urine.
I see.
You mind unlocking your trunk?
Okay. Thank you very much.
I'm gonna need you to pull over
to the second inspection area.
Doug says everyone fingered celia.
Then he started giggling 'cause he said
"fingered," which leads me to believe he's high.
But he's almost always high, so I
believe the information is reliable.
There's mom.
How'd it go at the track today, dad?
Catch a few winner
no?Not one? Shocking.
How many races were
there? Nine? Anything?
Did you blow the whole $300?
I bet your grandpa doesn't
have $5 left in his wallet.
Can't pick a winner to save his life.
- August 14th, 1983.
- And away we go.
Kentucky mistress...
lady's a charm, please
pass the salt -- winners.
Not one
-- three.
That trifecta was the
overlay of the century.
I clocked their
workouts for four months.
You clocked your shits for four months.
I asked that prick over there
to pedal his little bicycle,
which I bought him, up to del mar
and throw down $100 on a sure thing.
Father of the year.
What the fuck does he do? He pockets it.
Goes out and buys himself
some "star trek" piece of shit.
It was boba fett.
I don't even know what that means.
Ganef!
I trusted you, and you lied to me.
"Oh, dad, the horse lost."
They did lose every other time.
You never won.
That trifecta was a fluke.
That's the beauty of gambling.
You lose, you lose, and then
you win big to make up for it.
You stole my win-big.
You destroyed the beauty.
What the hell were you doing, sending two
kids to the track to place your bets, anyway?
- Judah would have never - -
the whole thing was judah's idea!
Lower your voice. You'll
agitate your bubbie.
Bubbie was in on it, too!
She told us we should take your money, we should
go down to the boardwalk and have some fun.
"He'll never win," she
said. "He's a schlimazel."
- She never said such a thing.
- She did! She did.
- Tell him, bubbie.
- Leave her alone. She's a bag of broccoli.
If judah were alive today -
- She's trying to talk.
- If judah were alive today, what?
She's trying to talk!
Geharget mach.
What did she say?
Something about target.
Idiot. It's yiddish.
She speaks yiddish.
What does it mean?
It means "kill me."
You see what you've done?
- Oh, could I just - -
stay back behind the line.
Oh, you think there's a tiny, little
immigrant stuffed in my lipstick?
Joke.
You didn't laugh 'cause I was
redundant, right? "Tiny, little."
Bingo! This one is mine, boys.
Would you like to explain to me why
you have drugs hidden in your vehicle?
Welcome back, blanca. Took you a while.
I see you got some souvenirs.
They tore the car apart, couldn't
find anything. Your guys are good.
Good at what?
They're in the engine. Am I right?
What's in the engine?
The drugs.
Who said anything about drugs,
man? Where are my inhalers?
Uh, oh, right. The inhalers.
They were confiscated. Apparently,
I needed a prescription.
You buy a prescription for 10
bucks from the guy in the farmacia.
I ask you for one thing.
You know how much a ventolin costs here?
Shit!
Mira.
What?
It's a camera, like
"taxicab confession."
This was to see how you
did with the border cops.
We're gonna do postgame later.
You were recording me?
Edit down a highlight reel.
No, wait, wait. You were
recording me, and there's no drugs?
The car was clean?
It kind of smells like pee.
So, what, you're
just... fucking with me?
This is bullshit.
You think those guys who flew into the towers
-- that was their first time on an airplane, huh?
It's practice.
Go home and think about
what you did wrong.
Tomorrow, we review the tape.
Do I get paid for that, too?
You lucky you getting half.
You lost my inhalers.
I think I'm starting to believe you.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Weeds
Season04 Episode02