Previously on Weeds...
- Do me up.
- I sold you an eight ball yesterday.
- I need another one.
- How much you got?
My fiancé said the funniest thing.
You asked him to kill
some loco DEA agent?
Gee, thanks.
You did me a solid.
- We can't get our weed back.
- I will help you.
After I slam his dick
- in this drawer.
- I can do this.
I could sell a lot more makeup
if I give a free gift.
I can't steal their weed.
Just tell them
that you got ripped off.
I've got a crooked dick
and there's no pot?
It wasn't my fault.
Eighths go in the compacts.
Half ounces in the eye-shadow kit.
Everyone, let's see that plastic.
Adios, losers.
New condo.
I did this all on my own.
Selling You're Pretty! cosmetics.
May I help you, sir?
I want to make money
selling your face chemicals.
- You think you can handle a full order?
- Damn right, full order. Fill me up.
After the election,
we will be married and be a family.
- What election?
- I'm running for governador.
What the fuck was that?
Her name is Pilar Zuazo.
She's jut protecting
my public image.
This little milk ball was a mistake.
I am the father of this child.
Not according
to your dear friend Pilar.
I couldn't put Esteban's name
on the birth certificate.
So you put my name on it.
You're a frozen margarita, Andy.
- I'm a doctor.
- Why did you agree to go out with me?
I am fascinated by how this is gonna
play out with the gangster baby-daddy.
- Marry me.
- Let's go downstairs.
What are they saying?
Find out what's going on!
I love you and you love me,
so I am here, and I am not leaving.
Mom?
Weeds 510
Perro Insano
By the Fumistes team.
lesfumistes[at]gmail.com
Oh, my God! Oh, my fucking God!
Is he all right?
- Look at all my blood, Mom.
- Is it just his arm? There's...
- There's blood...
- I can't even feel it.
There's two holes.
One in, one out.
- Through the meat, it missed the bone.
- Is that a good thing?
Put our people on the street.
Bring me a name.
You don't shoot at a man
in front of his family.
It sounded like a slap.
He slapped me with a bullet.
Isn't that weird?
Shane, it's weird
and it's fucked up and it's scary,
and I want to go to the fucking hospital
right fucking now.
Hospitals report bullet wounds
to the police.
I don't care!
- I need a vodka.
- You're a doctor all of a sudden?
A nurse, in the army.
Like Hot Lips Houlihan?
Caliente lips.
Fuck you! Fuck your mom
in the ass with a screwdriver!
What was that?
The shooter.
Fucking A.
I don't get it,
I've been at this all morning.
I found a high-volume area,
followed the script.
- What am I doing wrong?
- This is our corner, get your own.
Cram it, brownie.
- I told you, I'm a nature scout.
- I know what I said.
No one wants your crap.
Go away.
We're trying to send goats
to African people.
- They already have goats.
- Not these goats.
You pinch one more of my sales,
I'm gonna flick you in the God nipple.
It's called a bindi.
Everyone knows it's "bindi."
I love You're Pretty! cosmetics.
- Really?
- Do you know Celia Hodes?
I just started buying from her.
Yes, Celia! Love that woman.
This is the same stuff.
- Really?
- Yep.
Perfect.
Yesterday,
I bought two eye-shadow kits
and I'm already out,
so I'll take two more.
Two eye-shadow kits in one day?
That is hot.
My husband would kill me
if he knew how much I spent on weed.
Yeah, right.
Wait... What are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
She thinks you're selling pot
like your friend, you fucking idiot.
It's been a while
since my trauma rotation,
but I'd say
you got pretty lucky here.
If you're gonna get shot, it's good
to get shot the way you got shot.
You didn't tell your mom
about me sending you out there, did you?
I like the bandages.
That Audra does nice work.
Percocet for the pain.
Take it easy with these.
- They're not Mentos.
- That's a lot.
I'm just gonna take two
for my headache.
Maybe three.
Did she ask about me?
You take this, you watch movies,
you feel better.
About your arm, life,
everything.
All I'm saying is that every time
I think shit can't get more fucked up,
shit gets way more fucked up.
I want to go float in Lake Esteban.
That pool's got a tide.
And me floating in it.
Like a leaf through a filter.
Or a bug.
Please don't tell anyone
I was a nurse.
No one gets inside. No one...
gets near you.
Do you like my watch?
It's yours.
They will tease me.
Say "medic."
I'm sorry.
Why?
- Because you got hurt.
- I'm okay.
Shane, you got shot.
That was bound to happen
sooner or later.
No, it's not supposed
to happen at all.
"When is he gonna get shot?"
It's not crossing your mind
when you pretend to be the Tooth Fairy.
It was this thing that happened today.
Other things happen other days.
- Things will happen tomorrow.
- You're not getting hurt again.
I promise you.
- I'm fine.
- Shane.
Shane, look at me.
You're never getting hurt again.
You should be worrying about Stevie Ray.
He's just a baby.
You're still my baby.
You think I can have
that sandwich now?
Oh, please...
Like I give a shit.
You're a hard man to find.
What are you doing?
It's a cup.
Of course.
I need a hookup.
Turn around. Let me see that culo.
Kiss my culo.
I'm looking for drogas.
Weed. Not Mexidick.
I need a steady supply
and I'm not talking
nickel-and-dime bags here.
I'm big.
Getting bigger. Major league.
So, you cut me a deal now and later,
I'll let you be my heavy.
You can sniff out
all the assholes in my life
and then bury them in the yard.
What's my cut?
Ten percent bonus
after first delivery.
I got to go.
Twelve? Twelve percent?
Fifteen?
- Seventeen point five percent.
- Twenty.
Fine.
Give me a call in a couple of days.
I'll have it ready.
The bullet was meant for me,
wasn't it?
You need to take your family
and leave.
No need to keep me in suspense.
Who wants me dead?
A person who will not stop
until she gets what she wants.
You cannot kill Pilar.
You'd be shot
before you even got close.
Why don't I start with the person
who's been reporting to her?
What will Esteban do when he finds out
you set up the mother of his only son?
- Think it through.
- Why didn't you just let it happen?
I realized your death
would be the end of him.
And his happiness is my happiness.
That's pretty gay, nurse Cesar.
I tell you what, I'm gonna forget
your momentary lapse in loyalty.
You spared my life,
I'm sparing yours.
But you owe me, big time.
And you hurt my kid.
So count to three.
Are you right-handed?
Count.
One...
two...
Three.
- There you are.
- Jesus, Andy. Heart attack.
You're stealing from a drug lord.
Bold. Hot.
My clinic has to fight for every swab,
but this stuff is just sitting here.
- Don't rat me out.
- What's my silence worth to you?
How about patching up
your 14 year-old nephew's bullet wound,
and neglecting to report it
to the police?
No, not enough.
You also have to go out with me.
To hear music, jazz.
Jazz, really? You like jazz?
For sure.
Name one jazz musician.
Doctor Teeth.
- He's a Muppet.
- He's a jazz Muppet.
Pass.
What? Wait, wait.
So, you reject me
over chips and salsa,
then you flirt with me
at little Stevie's weenie roast.
And now I'm asking you
on a proper sophisticated jazz date
and you pass?
I was too harsh on the date,
so I gave you a second look,
and you look good.
Then I looked closer
and that's when I saw it.
What? A cancerous mole or something?
How long have I got, Doc?
Give it to me straight.
You're hung up on Nancy.
What? Oh, God. No, no, no.
It's complicated.
We're family. I'm her baby daddy.
Ink, not sperm. Meaningless.
I'm trying to man up.
So yeah. Maybe I'm a little
tangled in Nancy's drama,
but it's a fledgling effort.
Jesus, Audra, why are you shitting
all over my effort?
Is this an occupational hazard,
aborting everything?
It's not a life yet, Andy.
You're just making excuses.
This is why you're single.
You're a hot doctor
but you're alone, 'cause you're always
making excuses instead of taking a risk.
This is a pretty valid
fucking excuse.
You said "fucking". I'm telling.
Goodbye, Andy.
Doctor Lehman.
Jesus, another one?
Are you stealing?
Is it really hurting?
I can set up a movie for you.
Maybe I can find a porn channel.
I get it.
If I got shot in my jerk-off arm,
I would be mad too.
I'm not mad.
How many pills did you take?
None.
Well, that's dumb.
I'll get you a glass of water.
Give me your pills, I'll open 'em.
Why have them
if you won't take them?
Because...
they're mine.
I like the way it feels.
Like a knife
popping the same balloon
over and over.
Only you don't have
to blow up a new one.
I can make the pain go away anytime
with a pill.
But I don't want to.
I don't have to think
about anything else.
It's great.
Great.
That's the last of it.
- Who knew you had so much stuff?
- Thank you for helping me move in.
I really appreciate it.
What's 12 flights of stairs
between partners?
Exactly, and we could not risk
using the elevator.
- There's an elevator?
- Where did those idiots
get all this pot anyhow?
Some guy named the Wizard.
Check it out.
Four dead bolts.
Steel-reinforced hinges.
Coded entry system.
You really got
this place locked down.
Plus, there is a security gard
downstairs,
and channel 3 on the television
picks up a live feed
of the front gate.
I am protecting our investment.
You are scary good at this.
Thank you.
- I know.
- What if I need to get in?
Maybe you need a secret knock.
Really?
- Cool, like what?
- I don't know.
Maybe you should make one up.
I got one.
How's that?
Security, there's a sweaty Jew
in my hallway.
- How much?
- A lot of money.
It'll be your bank account.
You can access it with an ATM card
from any country.
Also...
- Pick a place, somewhere far.
- Are you serious?
Europe, go to Europe.
Western Europe, the food's better.
- Amsterdam?
- Sure.
Amsterdam, start there.
I'll get you a Europass.
You can go to museums,
stay in hostels,
seduce traveling Australians.
What's the catch?
There is no catch.
This is what you do when you're young.
You travel through Europe
with a backpack.
Someone in this family
should be doing something normal.
Why not you?
I have been replaced
as candidate for governor.
You leave tomorrow.
It was Celia, she forced me to lie.
I didn't want to do it.
What did she promise you?
Sex? Money?
No, she...
She never promised me anything.
Betrayer! Cock-breaker!
How could you do this?
- I didn't have a choice.
- I am belly-up, buddy.
You put a key on my kite
in a shitstorm.
I dropped 5 grand on lip liner.
You took away my business.
My splooge doesn't want to come out.
It's stuck in a pocket
between my balls.
How do you think I feel?
She squeezed me out.
I was gonna be a drug kingpin.
I was gonna be Tony Montana.
I got nothing.
- What's with all the moving boxes?
- I gotta give up the space.
- I can't afford to keep it.
- This a fresh pot?
She looted me, buddy.
- Wanna call the Feds?
- I'd be disbarred.
- I'd be fine.
- We're in this together.
- Not until we're even.
- Even?
Teeny Deany.
- Dip 'em in.
- What?
Whip 'em out, dip 'em in.
Are you out of your mind?
Get away from me.
You want to go up against Celia?
You're gonna need my help.
Drop the pants.
Dunk the Dean nuts.
My ba... No, not my balls.
Yes, balls.
And I see you trying to get hard.
No way! Flaccid in the acid.
- But...
- Dunk.
You have the votes.
Why aren't you fighting?
You could win.
I don't know.
Pilar has an army.
You have the people.
In America,
we call it "wagging the dog."
Well, in my country,
dogs travel in packs.
So, that's it? She wins?
She won.
Now, we can be married.
And have a beautiful lavish wedding,
with all our friends and family.
I will feed you cake.
Small ceremony.
No friends. Limited family.
Chocolate cake, Entenmann's.
I cannot put you and your family
in any more danger.
So you would run if it wasn't for me,
if you didn't have a family?
I did not say that.
And you would win.
I would win.
Then do it.
So, I gave it some thought,
and I...
respectfully decline your offer.
No, you're not declining. No.
- I'm not going.
- This is not up for discussion.
Esteban's decided
to run for governor independently.
I'll be sure and wear
his campaign T-shirt.
Which means you not here.
Which means one son less
to keep track of, to worry about.
Shane is here. Stevie is here.
They're kids. You're old enough
to take care of yourself.
Your brothers will be fine.
Say "Excuse me."
I'm announcing in a week.
- You should be gone before then.
- Listen to him.
I appreciate you being preemptive
for once in our lives, but...
How is it that I have to beg
an 18 year-old
to travel Europe
with a wad of cash and my blessing?
How is it that you expect to me believe
that my brothers will be fine?
No one is fine around you.
So...
I'm staying.
Here, in this house.
This beer is warm.
Someone get me another.
Where's the fucking staff?
I have thirst.
No more beer.
And you... better protect us.
I can do that.
He can do that.
So, I'll...
move my shit in
and the two of you can...
stop dicking around already
and get married.
And on we'll go.
One big happy...
Get in the pool, fags!
You're early,
I'm not even dressed yet.
What's that?
Wedding present.
I filled out all the forms
to put Esteban's name
on the birth certificate,
so sign them and we're done.
You didn't make a registry.
So, this will have to do.
I actually did make a registry.
Weeks ago. Williams-Sonoma.
- We could use a new tortilla warmer.
- I'll get right on that.
- Are you sure about this?
- Yes.
Do you have a...
plan?
I'm gonna go back to the house
and spread out my life like a map.
Deliberate on the topography,
chart my path,
maybe call a girl
who calls me on my shit.
You love him.
You're going down a road.
I'm going down a road.
- I think I'm happy for you.
- I think I'm happy for you too.
See you downstairs?
Guess you and I are husband and wife
for the next...
15 minutes.
You want to fuck?
You in my fuck trailer.
I just had a baby, it'd be
like throwing a hot dog down a hallway.
You gotta work those Kegels.
I got a cousin, she practiced putting
pressure on a cucumber every day.
Then, she stopped,
'cause it got stuck in there.
Three months later,
a pickle fell out.
I'll have to try that.
- I could fuck you in the ass.
- That's tempting.
But I'm not here to socialize.
Why are you here?
I want her dead.
Cake?