Weeds 506
A Modest Proposal
By the Fumistes team.
lesfumistes@gmail.com
Previously on Weeds...
Ignacio will watch over you for now.
You helped Shane rob his teacher?
I am so sorry
that I exposed him
to the world of criminal activites
for the first time.
I wanna open a store.
Medical marijuana.
I want my cut.
Can we have a second?
We're new to this extorsion thing.
I have nowhere to go.
Do you think that you could allow me
to stay in your garage
while I figure out
what the fuck I'm doing with my life?
- Two days.
- I own a house here in Santa Playa.
- Did you just ask me to live with you?
- There's plenty of room.
Even room for him.
- I'm good.
- Me too.
I'm not sure
what I'm supposed to do.
I got the money. There is a lot.
- What? How?
- It doesn't matter.
We could be more,
I would like to try.
- Esteban...
- Write him a note.
- A note?
- Leave him a note.
Like the olden times.
Break his heart in ink.
He will understand
if he loves you.
These are terrible names.
Percy.
Clifford.
Who would name a son Humphrey?
Mr. and Mrs. Bogart.
Still a bad name.
It's true.
You always hear "Bogie and Bacall."
You never hear...
"Humphrey and Lauren."
I've decided that...
we will get married.
That is a prized family heirloom.
"Reyes" means "kings".
I don't know what "Botwin" means.
This just isn't
how I pictured this going down.
Well, I am sorry to disappoint you.
Purple.
Did you like the ring?
It's hideous.
That's the championship ring
of the soccer team I own.
I'm gonna want that back.
Are you really asking me?
Where was that?
We're not children anymore, Nancy.
We're not playing house.
I ask
that you give yourself to me
to be mine forever.
Mrs. Esteban Reyes.
Would that make you
Mr. Nancy Botwin?
I'll take a bowl of the best thing
you got on the menu, s'il vous plaît.
I'm trying to run a legitimate business.
You don't have a prescription.
Fine, I'll take it myself,
boy scout.
No, don't give me that look.
I do the same thing at Pretzel Time.
Come on, let's get faded.
Blitt and I need to close early.
For inventory, well...
What's left ot it, right?
Right.
Right, so...
Can you get faded somewhere else?
I'm hurt that you don't want
to smoke with me, Silas.
But I get it.
What really hurts though
is that you've been light
these last couple months.
Happens again,
we're gonna have a serious problem.
Bitch-ass bitch.
See ya.
My name is in this book.
"Shane: a feeling of guilt."
Was I an accident?
Who can remember?
Honestly, I was hammered.
- You should get to pick your own name.
- At what age?
If I'd given you that freedom at 3,
your name would be
Count Chocula Botwin.
Notice anything different?
About my hand?
He said he was gonna ask you.
He told you?
We had an hombre to hombre talk.
Mucho respect. I'm cool.
You're cool?
And you're guzzling coffee?
Ignacio says it puts hair
on your chest.
Spinach gives you instant muscles
and an anchor tattoo.
Time for summer school.
Escuela de verano.
Vámonos, muchacho.
Señora Reyes.
Felicidades.
Did Esteban tell everybody?
Everybody except for Andy.
You might want
to take care of that one yourself.
You wanna buy a Fresca
with a credit card?
Qué estupidez!
Estupidez, but es on the quiz.
School doesn't teach you
nothing useful.
You wanna learn español útil?
I teach you.
Lesson number one...
Common business transaction.
Repeat after me.
- What does that mean?
- That means,
pay up, motherfucker, or I crack
your head open with an ice pick.
Nice.
- All-purpose.
- Sí.
Can we ditch school?
- We don't need no stinking school.
- Yeah.
- What's up?
- My score.
That's what.
312,000
and counting.
Look out, Abdner Ashman.
Coming to get you.
- Who's Abdner Ashman?
- Guy from Queens.
Holds the record
Ms. Pac-Man high score.
I'm only behind him, like,
600,000 points, give or take.
- Look out.
- Silas.
I know I've got a ways to go.
I'm in this for the long haul.
It just...
It feels right, you know?
She gets me. We're in sync.
No words,
just a gentle touch of my hand.
I move left, she moves left.
I move right, she moves right.
Should I be worried here?
Yes! Power pellet.
Die, Inky. Die, Blinky!
Come here, Sue,
you filthy little ghost whore.
I'm worried here.
Don't worry about me.
Worry about you.
I'm worried about both of us.
You, because...
you're cracking up.
And me, because the cop
extorting money from me is cracking up.
- How much you got left?
- Of what?
Uncle Yitzhak's lost fortune
which fell miraculously into your hands.
Right, that's how it happened.
How much do you have left?
A couple thousand maybe, if that.
What? I thought...
You said there was like 180 grand.
Was. Look, look around you.
Geez...
You blew all that money
on this crap?
This crap
and General Lee.
- Fuck's sake.
- Please, step away from the car.
Please, step away from the car.
Dammit.
Why do I have to do this?
Because you're the only one
I could trust not to get turned on.
Doug, thank God you're still here.
I need a ride to the mall.
No can do. Gotta dry.
If I smudge, people know it's fake.
Yeah, that's how they'll know.
Ask Andy.
I did.
Conflicting engagement
with Ms. Pac-Man.
Have a nice walk to the bus stop.
Christ, I need a car.
My fucking feet are killing me.
If you actually wore
your sneakers to work,
instead of changing
into them there...
Sneakers are the footwear
of my corporate oppressor, Isabel.
I just thought
you might as well be confortable.
Do you think it's comfortable for me
to work at Super Sneakers?
Well, it's not.
But I will suffer for my beliefs.
You want to know who else did that?
Jesus.
I thought Jesus wore Birkenstocks.
Is she gone?
Make sure you get it even.
Hi, Andy. It's me, Nancy.
I thought maybe you'd...
pick up this time,
but you're probably really busy.
I gotta say, I think it kind of sucks
that you've been avoiding me
because I miss you,
despite what you might think,
and I hoped that maybe by now
you'd understand that...
I'm doing the best I can
to deal with everything.
Maybe that's asking too much.
Oh, yeah, guess what?
Esteban asked me to marry him.
I know, right?
No more Nancy Botwin.
Mrs. Esteban Reyes.
Mrs. Somebody... else.
Isn't that weird?
This is the part
where I thought you'd laugh
and make a joke
about outlaws and in-laws
and a fajita bar at the wedding.
Anyway... call me.
Come and see me.
I hope you're good.
And please don't have
a scraggly moonshiner beard,
unless you plan on starting a cult,
in which case...
go, beard.
Bye.
Fuck.
- Do I look even to you?
- What?
I'm working on my tan.
I found this George Hamilton
autobiography in the shitter.
This guy's a fucking genius.
You know he doesn't live anywhere?
His rich friends put him up
wherever he goes.
And he's constantly banging, like,
Britt Ekland or Anita Ekberg.
And you know what, Silas?
I want to be like this.
And to be like the "G. Ham",
I need the tan, man.
I need the deep, dark, savage tan.
C.P. came by today.
He threatened us
because his take's been light.
Of course it's been light,
the fucking guy's always hanging around.
No one's gonna want to buy weed
in frond of the bacon.
Skeeves people out, like midgets.
He pulled a gun on me.
Just messing around, but still...
What a douche.
Power corrupts, Silas.
We need to fight the power.
Great. How do you propose
we do that?
We ask ourselves...
- "What would george hamilton do?"
- What? Why?
The man slept with his stepmother
when he was 12 years old.
Clearly, he can do anything.
Next lesson.
Greetings and salutations.
Repeat after me.
Means "go fuck yourself in the ass."
This is fun.
Hey, fuck you, man.
No, this is fun.
You with the fucking names.
Yeah, new name.
Comes with a prize.
You like it?
Turns out you were wrong.
It wasn't "miss dead puta whore"
after all.
It was Mrs. Esteban Reyes.
Though, I might hyphenate...
Botwin-Reyes...
Just to keep my old self alive,
being a modern woman and all.
I'm impressed, blanca.
You know,
you remind me of my cat, Rosita.
I used to throw her
off the porch, and...
Damn if that little bitch
didn't land on her feet every time.
Of course, then I threw her
off the roof,
and she went splat.
So, why you come here?
Invite me to the wedding?
I wanted to share something
with you.
The other day, my fiancé...
He said the funniest thing.
We were eating breakfast.
He has brioche made for me.
It's my favorite.
And he said, "Mi amor,
"do you know
that I would do anything for you?
"Do you know
that I would even kill for you?"
He just kicked.
And you know what I said?
Maybe you asked him to kill
some loco DEA agent?
Did you do that?
'cause if that was you...
Gee, thanks.
You did me a solid.
Maybe soon we won't have
this glass between us no more.
You're not going anywhere.
We had some fun
at the driving range yesterday!
What do you wanna do today?
Tennis?
Wait! Wait!
Shit!
Fucking shoes!
Love your shoes.
Thank you.
I may work in casual,
but my heart is in couture.
Honey, I've been there.
Raylene Reynolds.
Regional sales director,
you're pretty! Cosmetics.
Nice to meet you.
Hop in, darlin'.
You look like you could use a ride.
How much weight can that thing hold?
If that fucking fat-ass
costs us our security deposit...
Growing up, young George
lived by one rule...
- Do the dumbest thing possible.
- What?
Time and again,
he'd get himself into trouble
just for the thrill
of weaseling his way out of it.
I want to be that weasel.
- Wait, no. Wait.
- Get out of my store.
Right now! Get out of my store!
I've had enough of you
driving my customers away,
and skimming my profit.
Don't care if you're the heat.
Don't take it in the back.
Not from you. No more.
I'm not gonna take it anymore.
You're making a big mistake, Wilson.
A big!
You know what else is big?
My Johnson. And you can suck it!
Shit!
What would George Hamilton do now,
you asshole?
You gonna put on a Zorro mask
and fuck him?
Oh, there you are.
I was gonna take a walk.
I made it from the bedroom
to the patio.
God! I'm huge!
Not for much longer.
Soon I'll be a new mommy...
Again.
And married... Again.
Again again, actually.
And you are ecstatic.
Ecstatic.
And huge.
And beautiful...
And radiant.
What does this...
Mrs. Esteban Reyes do?
Whatever she wants.
I'm pregnant and hormonal.
I just keep thinking
this Mrs. Esteban Reyes person
is going to kill Nancy Botwin.
Why must you always think
someone's trying to kill you?
It's just a name.
I'm not marrying the name.
I'm marrying you.
If you want to be Nancy Botwin...
Keep your name.
Really?
I'm still going to brand you,
of course, but...
... sure.
Time to go fence.
Have fun, d'Artagnan.
See you next time.
This is...
You got a pool and everything, huh?
No peacocks, but I suppose
they could be roosting.
You don't look so good, my friend.
Right on.
Well, Ignacio said he thought
Nancy might be down here, but...
she's not.
You fence, huh?
Tool.
I fence a bit.
You?
I have no formal training,
per se,
but...
I was Ren Mar JCC
lightsaber battle champ
'79 to '82.
That brings back some memories.
So, congratulations.
Thank you.
You're a lucky man, Esteban.
Just thought I'd come down,
give you and Nancy my blessing,
say there's no hard feelings.
Hard feelings? About what?
Nothing. Forget it.
Tell me, what is that strange sound
you're making?
That's not how it's done in Mexico?
You guys don't have sound effects there?
If you care for a friendly bout,
I will show you
how it's done in Mexico.
En garde.
Okay.
God damn it!
What's going on?
Andy is giving us his blessings.
So...
You and Esteban tying the knot,
taking the plunge, buying the cow.
- Seems kind of sudden.
- Well, it's not,
which you would know if you ever
called me back. Did you get my messages?
I got your note.
Said everything I needed to hear.
A note, Nance, seriously?
A note?
So, is this what you want?
Should've known.
You always seem to get what you want.
No, I wanted Judah to outlive me.
So, my blessing. You want that, too?
- You don't have to. I mean...
- No. Great and careful work, Nance.
I know the "God" part.
What's the rest?
"Blessed are you
who has kept us alive,
"sustain us, and enabled us
to reach this season."
I'm sorry, Andy. I'm sorry that...
- everything...
- Don't, okay?
Don't.
God bless.
But when Esteban dies,
which in his line of work will probably
be sooner rather than later,
when he dies and you're once,
twice, three times a widow...
don't expect uncle Andy
to stop by and make pizza eggs,
'cause I won't do it.
You know what I'll do?
Send a note.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Trying to get this damn tan off.
Fuck George Hamilton.
He can "love at first bite" me.
You are a sad, sad man.
What the fuck was that?
We cannot get married.
Excuse me?
Things have changed.
I'm sorry.