Previously on "weeds"...
we're gonna be doing some
remodeling around here.
We could save money if we
didn't use a contractor.
- I could do it.
- You're hired.
I turn 18 in a few weeks.
I'm not waiting.
We should be coyotes.
That guy who brought over davenport
and marzipan was such an asshole.
Why can't you buy your drugs in
the U.S. Like a normal person?
I have no health insurance,
no money, and an arrest record.
- Xanax?
- Yes!
I want some.
How about I sell you 300
pounds at 25 bucks a gram?
Fuck you. That's more than street value.
You don't like it, do something else.
I need to habla with esteban.
"we are here to inaugurate
this mobile medical unit."
I want a piece of the
next weed shipment.
You work for guillermo.
There's a chain of command.
But he said no.
I came to you first.
Thanks...
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Weeds
Season04 Episode08
Hola. Boss says time to start.
Boss?
Bubblicious or rhythm field?
I like bubblicious, but it's on back
order, and rhythm field fell off a truck,
so there may not be enough.
What happened to the solid subway
tile field with hex tiles on the floor?
I want to give you options.
You're the contractor, not the designer.
I can't express my opinion?
Why don't we discuss this after school?
Surf dicks and gym class. Can't wait.
It's your first day. Give it a chance.
A chance for what?
More emotional scarring?
I don't see why I have to go
to school if silas doesn'T.
You're our one shot at legitimacy.
No, I'm not. I'm very
corrupt. I'm a contractor.
Shane... stop it. You're
gonna go to school,
and then you're gonna grow up and become a
doctor or a lawyer or a business executive.
That's my copper pipe.
You're late. I hope
you have a good excuse.
Is your mother home?
I'm the guy you need to deal with.
Shane, you need to call
off your worker bees.
Cesar. Good morning.
How do you know my pipe guy?
You want to choose tile?
Fine. But i hire the subs, mom.
Shane. Not your pipe guy.
He would like to see you.
I have to take my kid to
school, and then I have work,
so maybe later on this afternoon?
No? All right.
Great. I'm being dropped off
in a limo with mexican plates.
So much for flying under the radar.
I'm so dead.
New school. First-day jitters.
Sometimes you eat the bear.
Sometimes the bear eats you.
Yeah, I'll remember that when they're
wrapping the tetherball cord around my neck.
Some people are victims because
they allow themselves to be.
That's right, shane. So don't allow it.
Eat the bear.
Here's $10 for lunch in case
you're still hungry after.
Can't I do drug things with you guys?
He's going to get his ass kicked.
He's used to it.
Mom. Mom!
Motherfucker!
Sorry, baby. Jail reflex.
You've got to take me to school.
Isn't there, like, a bus or something?
For some reason, the cordial suites
la jolla isn't on their route.
Just drop me on your way to work.
Okay.
And you've got to change and shower,
and you need to give me $10 for lunch
and you have to fill
out the enrollment forms.
Hand mommy her pills.
How about a breakfast bar?
- Maybe I'll walk.
- Good girl.
Absolutely. Absolutely.
Garza, slow down, slow down.
Plenty of matzo to go around.
This is what my people ate as we
wandered the desert for 40 years --
at least in the beginning.
Then we switched to manna,
which fell from the sky.
Doesn't really happen anymore.
I'm thinking it's either
global warming or god is dead.
I haven't committed either way yet.
So, thoughts?
40 years?
Moses... wasn't half the coyote I am.
Okay, everybody check their supply bag.
You should all have breath
mints, a portable fan,
and a copy of "padre rico, padre pobre."
If anyone's illiterate, I
have a few copies on tape.
That's a nice tree, huh? Looks
like someone had a fiesta here.
Is violar mata. Rape tree.
These are from girls who have
been under this tree with evil men.
Yikes. Uh, okay.
Everyone, let's move over there where
the scenery's a little less... rapey.
Do you guys sell sandwiches?
No. Sorry.
People just don't get it. We're a
gourmet shop, not a sandwich shop.
What about gourmet sandwiches?
I mean, you got your bread, your
meat, every spread on the planet --
just slap them all together,
take out your big knife --
stab you with it?
Shouldn't you be in school?
Is money not the goal of this operation?
Big divorce settlement, huh? Trust fund?
Money is very much the
goal of this operation.
I got screwed in the divorce
settlement, and, no...
There is no trust fund.
You might want to think
about making some sandwiches.
You are forbidden to say the
word "sandwich" in my presence.
Fine.
Or "sammich." Or "sammy."
It's all unacceptable.
If you're so into gourmet,
why are you smoking this?
- It's like the cheez whiz of pot.
- You're some big expert?
That's a bad blend.
It was harvested probably
a year ago and too soon.
It's dried out.
It's full of enough mold to cure strep.
I'm thinking you bought it
off one of rad's friends.
How do you know so much about weed?
Same way you know so much
about cheese. It's my business.
I am fucking a teenage drug dealer?
Grower. Small scale.
Soon-to-be dealer.
And we make love.
Oh, do we?
What's the greatest cheese ever?
But are we talking
sheep, goat --
yeah.That cheese.
This is better.
Oh, my god.
I've been smoking cheez whiz.
Entonces, guillermo.
Last week, nancy received
a portion of your shipment.
- øVerdad?
- S?
I instructed you to give her
that portion, and you did.
S?
You gave her that portion,
and then, from what I hear,
you announced that you would kill "the
marimacha bitch in front of her children."
But I didn't instruct
you to do that, did I?
No, I did not.
Now, guillermo, you know I
don't like to micromanage.
I work with people who do their
jobs well, and I leave them to do it.
However, slaughtering a
co-worker, in front of witnesses,
no less, has to be cleared
with upper management.
And your request is denied.
Julio's just doesn't travel well.
You know, in the restaurant,
this is delicious.
Entonces, guillermo, nothing bad
is gonna happen to nancy, right?
Course not.
I am glad to hear that.
I will increase your
commission for shipments.
You should live to enjoy your money.
- Gracias.
- Good.
Everyone's friends again. You may go.
Unh-unh, not you. You stay.
What's a marimacha?
Oh, that's an offensive
term for a lesbian woman.
You hungry?
Well, it smells great, but you
just said it didn't travel well.
No, we'll go to the source.
Someone make that noise stop!
Se—ora, that is three times today.
You're allowing criminals
into our business.
Where's nancy? I'm lonely.
You're back there with your
gun and your puzzles, movies --
I've just got the donkey that plays
"pop goes the weasel" 40 million time--
I don't feel good.
Se—ora! Despierte!
Se—ora. Oye. Breathe in.
Oh, ignacio. Okay.
Not here, though.
Que? No, no. Lev*ntate. Up. Come on.
What happened?
You take too many drugs.
You need to keep better care
of this store. Of yourself.
What did you just give me?
Stay awake.
Now your own store. S?
I'm on it. The store is me.
I'm tingly.
Fucking American.
Okay, mama. Let's get you dressed.
any action?
Nah. I think the word's out this
is a pretty tough point to cross.
We're doing good work here, wilson.
Fuck, yeah.
No immigrants storming through to steal fruit-picking
jobs from hardworking americans on my watch, my friend.
My retarded cousin, tom,
used to be a janitor. No more.
Mexican took his job.
After he got caught trying
to fuck a mop, but still.
Shocking. That's just shocking.
You know that woman I showed
you on my phone the other night?
Freaky steroid chick?
She left me.
- Is that good or bad?
- She was my masterpiece.
Six months of injections -- I took
her from 130 to 215 with a bmi of 18.6
She was two weeks away
from an adam's apple.
There'll be others.
Not like hope.
Sometimes, after making
love... she'd dead-lift me.
Now, that's one of a kind. Anyway.
This is desert eagle,
heading back to H.Q.
Here we go.
I will lead you now. You
shall be a free people!
Good idea. No time to waste. Yep.
Lady liberty beckons.
This is big and tall, checkpoint five.
Not a bean on the tortilla. I
repeat, not a bean on the tortilla.
All clear. No spic, just span. Over.
Davenport.
Aqu?
Ihola! Welcome to america. Happy days.
Have you seen this girl? Anybody?
Ah, nice to have you here.
Have you seen her? MarÌa?
øS? øNo? MarÌa? Nothing?
We did it, man.
- We sure did.
- We did.
OK,you're a ........
You've got......
Let's go!
What do we do with them now?
No idea.
So you are not a lesbian.
Um, around guillermo, I am.
Made it easier
to be friends --
when we were friends, before he wanted
to kill me in front of my children.
Oh, don't worry. It is fixed.
Don esteban! Don esteban!
See?I gave blood.
You are a good man,Julio.
Oh, you don't need a menu.
You order what you like.
Julio will make it, and
if he can't, he'll find it.
- Order anything.
- Elk.
S?
Wait, wait. I'm kidding.
Um, make the best thing that you make.
Look at you and your sway.
Yes. It's like you're
out with the mayor.
Much like that.
I have to pee.
Holy shit.
Run and call for help.
Take care of everybody.
Our food might take a little while.
You need to go.
It's ok.I'm ok.
The ambulance......
I know.I know.
Help Julio clean up.
Julio.I will.........
I strongly......
I'm going to stay.And......
Esteban.Please!
Take care of the........
Everyone...
...Don't .....
Everything will....
Do you have any neosporin?
Neosporin?
twizzlers. Some tampons.
I might have a tide stick.
Sit. Sit down.
I'm thinking we should
go out for chinese.
- Sit.
You never sipped from your beer
after you toasted the crowd.
That's very bad luck.
I don't like to drink from the bottle.
All right.
But clearly, that's not your issue.
Not my issue.
But then, I have trouble breathing after I've
been shot at, which, clearly, you don't, so...
I guess we all have our things.
Another school. Another first day.
Another sweaty glass of social stigma.
We're interesting and
worthwhile people, isabel.
Yeah. Well, if only life were a judd
apatow movie where geeks ruled the world.
But it's not, so let's
just suck it up. Chip?
No, thanks.
Hey, who's the king of the school?
The most popular, most athletic,
most often-laid guy here?
I guess it's dan.
Everyone wants to be friends with dan.
- I'm shane.
- I'm dan.
Don't fuck with me.
Medium, large, large, small, petite...
petite maternity.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Do you have this in blue?
Nice choice!
I will ring you up over here $42.99...
Please. Do you want it in a box?
In a bag? In a box in a bag?
I actually just want it in blue.
Well, why didn't you say so?
Oh, I'm sorry. I've
already checked the racks.
Can you just check in
the back for me, please?
Good idea.
The drill...
Soccer shoe. Soccer shoe.
The preggies keep coming.
We call it f˙tbol.
Igol!
Kill....
- So?
- So, what?
- Do you have it in blue?
- Just get it in green.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Green is the color of
spring who's next? Let's go!
You think maybe they want to
close up? We've been here a while.
When I finish my coffee, we'll go.
Who was trying to kill you?
Maybe the mzo.
Maybe the mexicate.
And let me guess. You're the hot sauce.
I am the table.
How often do people shoot at you?
They mostly shoot at each other.
And the occasional bystander?
I cannot control the streets.
Streets that provide the
latest in mobile healthcare.
My success in business allows
me to give back to the community.
Take a little blood,
give a little blood.
You question my motives?
Soothing your conscience
at the expense of others.
You question my motives.
You're bleeding again. It's your...
no, no. I'm okay. I'm okay.
Maybe if you put it under your pillow you
can get a dollar from the shrapnel fairy.
Well, it's part of the job.
If people see you're afraid,
they do not vote for you.
- Nothing scares you?
- Nothing.
That's a lie. You're afraid
of dirty beer bottles.
I'm not afraid. I just don't like them.
- Snakes?
- Fine with snakes.
- Failure?
- Not a problem.
Heights.
Are you afraid of heights?
Yeah.
What are you afraid of?
- calm.
- Before the storm?
The storm I can weather.
Come with me.
Okay. AdiÛs, adiÛS. AdiÛS.
You sure you're gonna be okay?
Lake davenport, florida.
Big fish. Lobster boy. Jeb bush.
We'll miss you.
Hasta luego.
You were right, andy.
This is a great business.
Helping the unfortunate.
Unlimited customer base.
- Reconnecting families.
- Low overhead.
We're doing god's work, and we're providing
the backbone of the american economy.
They paid you, right?
Two drills!......
Kill that....
Soccer shoe. Football shoe.
- W-whatever you call
it, I need more. - No m*S.
Please? Just a little bit? Helps me.
No m*s!
I'll pay you.
How much you got?
Hang on. I'll get my purse.
Suck......
Silas... I had a thought.
Oh, yeah?
About cheese.
Surprise, surprise.
About how it smells
-- very strong.
That is an understatement.
You can smell this
place from a block away.
It stinks.
Good thing you're sexy.
Okay. You're missing the point.
What's the point?
It's the kind of smell that
overpowers all other smells.
It is, isn't it?
Look at all of this room back here.
Maybe you know somebody
who wants to rent it?
You really don't want to
make sandwiches, do you?
Sandwiches are bullshit.
There are only 40 of
them left in the world.
And now I own three.
He will join the other
two at my zoo in coyoac*N.
My son has turtles.
Please tell me that's
also going to your zoo.
You might not want to watch this.
But you don't have a problem with it?
I enjoy it.
* Well, teach me, baby *
* oh, yes *
* a little
show-and-tell *
* teach me, baby *
* well one more time *
* how to see the sunrise
in the dead of night *
* teach me, baby *
* How to keep from loving you *
Ay, buenas noches, nancy.
I have found......
He helped......
He plied......
He wears.......
He calls......
El Andy.
* I'm not a weak girl *
* don't call me weak, no *
* I'm just a hungry girl *
* and you taste so sweet *
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents