Previously on Weeds...
- We can't get our weed back.
- I will help you.
After I slam his dick...
- in this drawer.
- I can do this.
You're Pretty! will front you
all the products that you need
to put yourself
on the road to financial freedom.
I can sell a lot more makeup
if I give a free gift.
No, I can't steal their weed.
No, just tell them that you got
ripped off by black people.
- Strike a pose, Harm.
- They really want to have sex.
Both of them? Use condoms.
All I know is
some Mexi-cunt screeches at you,
suddenly the marriage is off.
She's just protecting
my public image.
- Because she owns you.
- I am the father of this child.
I couldn't put Esteban's name
on the birth certificate.
So you put my name on it.
I'm not doing this for you.
This is for me.
I want something that matters.
This is unacceptable.
My son will be baptized.
Sorry. He's Jewish.
My son's not gonna be raised
by that pendejo!
That pendejo sticks around!
And he's not a coward.
Weeds 509
Suck 'N' Spit
By the Fumistes team.
lesfumistes[at]gmail.com
I need the bed, Andy.
It lives here.
I made up the couch for you. Soft...
Lots of blankets.
Great.
Enjoy it.
No! Jesus!
So, are you and Esteban over?
Looks that way.
He's pissed
about the Jew thing, huh?
I have no idea, Andy.
Why don't you ask him?
Can you turn off the light, please?
No. My bed, my rules.
- There's some things I want to say.
- Of course there are.
First, physical contact.
If we have to share a bed,
don't even think about spooning me,
that's not happening.
Second, pillows...
I use three.
Under the head,
between the legs, and a hugger.
Third, night farts...
happen.
Especially since I've been dieting.
So beware when you lift the covers,
and don't expect apologies...
I need sleep!
One night of sleep in a bed!
No sounds, no lights, nothing!
Fine.
But just so you know,
I'm not your rebound guy.
He's winding up. Go get him.
What about Lupita?
It's her night off.
You wanted to be a daddy.
This is your big chance,
night feeding.
It's where the big boys play.
- This is just so you can have the bed.
- Yes, it is.
There's breast milk in the fridge.
You can warm it up in the bottle
in a pot of hot water and test it.
And don't forget to burp him
and sing.
He likes that.
Me and Mrs. Jones.
Seriously?
We got a thing...
going on.
Can you check on the baby?
I fed him.
He probably pooped.
That's how babies work.
I was thinking
that you could handle the poop
and I would amuse him
by making funny faces.
You can make funny faces
while you wipe his butt.
I'm gonna pump.
What?!
I just changed him!
He's hungry again.
He wants his mommy.
Well, I'm empty...
from the last pumping.
Go pop a bottle in his mouth.
- You're trying to break me, aren't you?
- No!
This is what parenting is.
Shit and food.
Shit...
and food... mostly shit.
Wiping shit.
Keeping them away from shit.
Minimizing the external shit.
It's parenting shit.
What about love?
It's there, it's just...
buried under all the... shit.
I still feel used.
Talk to me after you've had something
clamped onto your breast
every 3 to 4 hours.
You think I never had
my nipples clamped?
Ashley Stepanski...
I don't care. Go.
He's crying. Go, go.
So, after the judge signs off
on the release form,
and after I get the pot back
from the cop at the evidence locker,
I put it in a black duffel.
I bought one just for this.
I'm not gonna charge you for it.
Anyway, I threw it
in the back of my car.
But on my way home,
Marine View Road is closed.
He'll be fine.
Rite of passage.
Granted, not...
exactly the Bar Mitzvah
that he should have had.
A moment of silence, please,
while I continue to enjoy
the sweet caress of alcohol
for the first time in far too long.
Can I talk now?
Now?
So, fucking male yeast infection.
That's crazy, right?
Who knew? It's like
a cross-pollination sort of thing...
Mad cow, hoof and mouth.
The human body is a complex
and mysterious experiment.
It's a sewer.
You're still reeling
from that diaper change.
That wasn't human.
You didn't see that.
I've seen it.
Well, he's Lupita's problem
for the next couple hours.
He's nobody's problem.
He's my son.
My third son.
My third... son.
The little bastard saved my life.
And he's pretty damn cute, right?
Like...
sick crazy cute.
These drinks are strong.
Why can't babies just talk?
They come out knowing how to breathe.
Talking should be a...
What do you call?
Involuntary action.
- For you, it is.
- Imagine
if Stevie could say,
"hey, I got something in the pants.
"Put me on the potty, stat."
You'll learn to read the signs.
God, I should have pumped.
- So, they hurt or...?
- Yes. Hurt.
- Do you want to go?
- No.
It's my first time out.
Hang on a second.
No way.
Fuck!
Okay.
Okay, relax.
Oh, god damn it.
Fuck it all to hell.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Hi. Yeah.
Could you come in here?
In the... bathroom, yeah.
Just shut up.
Just come in here. Bye.
My dream is dead.
Paradise lost.
We'll start over.
I'll grow in the upstairs closet.
I did it once, I can do it again.
This is America. You get one chance.
You blow it, that's it.
Adiós, losers.
I am out of here for good.
For great.
New Condo.
Ocean view. Covered parking.
Saltwater pool.
Good for you, Mrs. Hodes.
Thanks for stopping by.
- Enjoy packing.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, good for you. Who you fucking?
- Nobody.
I did this all on my own,
selling You're Pretty! cosmetics.
And I am selling a shitload.
That bullshit makeup company?
Yeah, that bullshit
is buying mama a new life.
God, it's good to be back on top.
- Engorged. I'm engorged.
- "I'm engorged"?
Engorged. It hurts.
Please, I need you to suck it out.
- Can't we just...?
- I tried!
- Maybe...
- I tried.
Please, be the baby!
I've done my share
of role-playing before.
Some crazy, weird shit.
- I was a werewolf...
- Shut up and suck!
Wait. Hold it.
- What's it gonna taste like?
- Rum and milk.
Here we go. Lips to nips.
- No teeth! No!
- Sorry. Sorry.
Spit, spit.
That's a really interesting flavor.
I imagined a spout,
but it's like a showerhead. It's like
You swallowed!
Yeah, well...
I don't want to be a hypocrite.
Why is the bed moving?
I guess we had an earthquake.
You're jerking off.
I couldn't sleep.
Well, take a fucking Ambien.
That's what I was doing.
Nature's Ambien.
The old tried-and-true male way:
cum, sleep.
I'm right here!
Well, I'm engorged. It hurts.
I need you to suck it out.
- Be the baby.
- This is too fucking weird.
I've seen you in the bathtub.
You watched me fuck your sister.
I suckled you.
But this is too weird for you?
Which is why we should cling to any
last shred of normalcy that we can.
Okay.
Just be two normal people.
Normal brother/sisters-in-law
sharing a house and a bed together,
raising a Mexican-American child.
- Just normal.
- Exactly.
Which means
masturbating on our own time.
'cause I'm swimming in that
these days.
Today was a bath of me time
and personal space.
Sounds like a feeding.
I'll get this. Go ahead.
Take your Andy time.
Can Andy time be about 15 minutes?
Just keep it
on that side of the bed.
Just so you know...
If you want to rub one out in bed,
I totally get that, and I'll stay
way over on my side.
You won't even know I'm here.
I just had a baby
less than two weeks ago.
The father of my child might be
gone for good,
so rubbing one out isn't exactly
at the top of my list, but thank you.
Just wanted to reciprocate.
- When you... You weren't thinking...
- Don't flatter yourself.
Here.
For when you...
burp.
Go ahead, sweetheart.
Share. This is a safe place.
Well, he says
that I can't do anything on my own.
He says no one will hire me.
That I'm too stupid to have a job.
He calls me dummy-no-jobby.
And whenever his friends come over,
he...
He what?
Locks you in the closet?
Dresses you like a maid?
Go ahead, finish the story.
What happened?
May I help you, sir?
Yeah, I want to make a lot of money
selling your face chemicals.
Well, we don't carry products for men,
so please leave the way you came in.
What?
You're kicking me out?
'cause I'm not some bored housewife?
What's that?
Sir,
You're Pretty! is for women
who have been marginalized,
disenfranchised
and who have never been allowed
the opportunity to succeed.
Well, I need
Please leave.
Okay, if you wouldn't mind opening
your incentive booklets to page 5.
Okay, okay. I see the game here.
And I'm gonna sue you
for sexual harassment. How about that?
- You mean discrimination?
- That, too.
I demand you let men sell makeup.
Look, asshole.
I will hook you up with a starter kit
if you get out. You're blowing my gig.
Starter kits are for pussies.
You think you can handle
a full order?
Damn right, full order. Fill me up.
And I want one of those booklets too,
so I have incentive.
- You single?
- I dig snatch.
Me too.
You want to go out?
Buy three full orders,
and I'll think about it.
Okay?
You have a pretty day now.
Very pretty.
Pilar was right.
I should be happy.
I should enjoy myself.
Life's too short, Cesar.
You should smile more.
He drank 4 ounces.
Nice.
Think that'll translate
into 4 hours?
Let us pray.
I can't.
I'm too tired.
Interesting.
How did you get in here?
You are in bed together.
Chill out. Look. Pillow wall.
A small house. Few rooms.
It's fine.
I'm not threatened.
Well, maybe you should
be threatened.
I have something to tell you.
- So, tell me.
- Alone.
I'm not leaving. This is my bed.
Say what you have to say.
Marry me.
We've had this discussion before.
I would like to have it
one more time.
Never gonna happen, pal.
Andy, would you give us a second?
- It's my fucking room!
- Okay.
Let's go downstairs for a minute.
Yeah. Do that.
I'm going back to bed.
I need my beauty rest.
What are they saying?
I can't hear that well.
I'll give you a dollar
if you go find out.
- What am I gonna do with a dollar?
- All right, 20 bucks.
- Why don't you go?
- 'cause I don't care!
Now get the fuck out there
and find out what's going on!
I'm gonna wind up
secretly engaged to you
until one day Steven asks me
who his real father is?
We will get married
now.
Steven will know who his father is.
Suddenly everything's fine.
Last night I had dinner with the woman
I'm supposed to be with.
Okay. Fuck you.
She knows the right people.
She says the right things.
She wears the right clothes.
She's the perfect candidate's wife.
But she turned you down,
so now you're here?
I love you.
So I'm here.
And you love me. So I'm here.
And we have
a beautiful baby together.
So I am here.
And I am staying here.
Get down!
Mom?