please, listen.
i'm telling you,
he's not like
our other patients.
the crimes that got him here
are nothing
compared to what he'll do
if we let him out.
but he responded
to medication.
medication inhibits
his delusions,
not his fantasies.
no pill can alter his sexual
proclivities.
but he's only
17 years old.
17-year-old boys
don't grow out of their sexuality.
they grow into it.
if he continues
his medication--
he won't.
the side effects
are too dramatic.
maybe if you explain
how important it is to him.
he put on 160 pounds
since he went on them.
he'll stop taking them. they all do,
and when he does,
he'll do this,
all of it,
every deviant,
sickening detail.
he was adjudicated
and committed.
the law says he turns 18,
we release him.
our hands are tied.
it's not your hands
i worry about.
you ought to change
your name to lucky.
thank whatever god
you got.
you're outta here.
i will.
???
alison. the usual.
come on.
oh, you gotta
be kidding me.
i got a polo mallet
in my trunk.
maybe you should
give it a shot?
sorry. none of my business.
3 hours.
just froze up on me.
you didn't save as you...
who has time to save
these days
with the kids
and the rap music?
you have a polo mallet
in your trunk?
small one.
- heh.
- can i?
oh. figures.
windows.
temperamental.
let's try...
voil?
heh.
good luck.
uh, um...
james. james baylor.
my friends
call me colby.
penelope. garcia.
my friends call me wonderful.
or garcia.
well, thank you.
oh, just happy to help.
uh, maybe i could
take you to lunch sometime.
sure. ok.
wh-why not?
here's my card.
ok.
that's...
i'll call you.
great.
good morning, princess.
good morning.
pump your brakes.
every day, i say,
"good morning."
every day, you say,
"i'll show you a good morning, hot stuff."
every day. not today?
i hate profilers.
do you know that?
spit it out.
fine. i met a guy.
you did what?
- where?
- coffee shop.
smoking hot.
i fixed his computer,
and then he asked
for my number.
- and you just--
- gave it to him.
can you believe that?
a complete stranger.
did i mention
he was smoking hot?
uh, yeah.
yeah, i think you did.
ok. it happens.
no, it doesn't, not to me,
not like this.
not like what?
i'm not the girl men see across a smoky bar
and write songs about.
- sweetheart--
- it's ok. i do just fine,
but it takes a minute,
you know?
ok, so what's
the problem?
you think it's all
happening a little too fast or something?
yes. i--i don't know. maybe.
what do you think?
i think you should
always trust your gut,
so sure, if he seems
a little too smooth
or maybe even a little
too smokin' hot,
then maybe you should
walk the other way.
hey. we got
a bad one.
how bad?
florida.
bridgewater, florida.
local girl,
abbey kelton, 19,
left her parents' home to go
to the local junior college.
she never came home.
3 days later,
joggers found her--
part of her--
in a nearby park.
what did that to her?
bridgewater's
off of i-75,
which is often referred to
as alligator alley
for reasons that
are now apparent.
everything below the waist
had been eaten.
ah, the circle of life.
suddenly i don't feel so guilty about
my alligator wallet.
alligators didn't cut off her fingers,
slit her throat,
or carve this into her chest.
an inverted pentagram.
locals believe the killing was committed
by a satanic cult.
some things
never change.
killer satanic cults
don't exist.
they were debunked
as a suburban myth.
what?
rossi's the one
that debunked them.
oh, right. thanks.
cult or not,
the killing was ritualized.
this will turn serial
if it hasn't already.
so killer satanic cults
don't exist,
but satanic serial killers do?
lasciate ogni
speranza ch'entrate.
oh. thanks for
clearin' that up.
uh, it's from
dante's inferno.
uh, "abandon hope,
all ye who enter here."
so that was a yes.
a big yes.
±¾×öä»½ö¹©ñ§ï°½»á÷£¬ñï½ûóãóúéìòµóãí¾
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
criminal minds 308
-=ææàãğü×öä»×é=-
·­òë: ğ£¶ô:
ê±¼äöá:abbiemcgee
"fantasy abandoned by reason
produces impossible monsters,"
francisco goya.
but we never found any evidence
of a killer satanic cult.
in reality, there are only 2 types
of violent satanic criminals.
uh, type one--
teen satanists
assume the satanic
identity to rebel.
minor crimes,
theft and vandalism
to churches, schools,
symbols of authority.
when combined with
drugs and alcohol,
they may turn violent.
yes, in extreme cases,
deadly.
that was out of my book
word for word.
oh, trust us, we know.
uh, killings
are accidental,
usually resulting from their hobby
getting out of control.
killings
won't turn serial--
hey, reid.
sorry.
ok. so that's one type.
what's type 2?
the adaptive satanist is
the one you have to worry about.
the typical serial killer
rationalizing his fantasies
by blaming them
on outside forces.
like satan.
yes. he adapts
satanic beliefs
to fit his specific
homicidal drives.
he doesn't kill because
he believes in satan.
he believes in satan
because he kills.
well, let's hope
it's the teenagers.
whether you're
religious or not,
the presence
of satanic elements
can affect even the most
experienced investigators.
and we're not immune,
so keep an eye on the locals
and keep an eye on each other.
i--i hear you.
i saw the exorcist.
my mother took us to church every sunday
until i moved out.
this whole devil thing
doesn't spook me at all.
maybe that's because you never
truly bought the god part either.
no offense, kid, but you
don't know what i believe.
well, i mean, logic dictates that if you
believe in the one,
you have to reconcile ile existence
of the other.
people's
reaction to satan
is what gives it appeal
to these offenders.
it has power,
and it would be a mistake
to underestimate it.
we found abbey's car
at a gas station near her home.
no sign of foul play.
dr. fulton?
the gators got to her
sometime during the night.
her nose was broken
at least 48 hours prior.
about the time
of the abduction.
blitz attack.
what was
the cause of death?
her throat. it was cut
roughly 8 hours
prior to the discovery
of the body.
sexual assault?
state of the body makes that
impossible to determine.
the pentagram.
that was done postmortem.
and the fingers?
all severed
at the first knuckle.
when?
i was unsure when
the fingers were removed
until i found this...
the contents
of her stomach.
the condition indicates
they were fed to her
just prior to her death.
all 10 fingers.
rossi, do me a favor.
you talk to the priest,
all right?
you'd rather interview
the grieving parents
on the worst day of their lives
than the priest?
if it's all right
with you, yeah.
good afternoon.
hi. father marks.
agent jareau.
these are agents
rossi and morgan.
it's good of you
to come.
we're sorry we have to be here
under these circumstances, father.
well, abbey's parents, bob and lee-ann,
are in my office.
we were discussing
her service.
agent morgan actually
has some questions for you.
all right. well,
uh, they're upstairs,
first door on the right,
and they're expecting you.
so how long has it been,
agent morgan?
i'm sorry?
well, since you've
been in god's house.
well, priests and dentists
can spot an overdue customer
a mile away, so...
how long's it been?
i didn't come here
to talk about myself.
occupational hazard.
my apologies.
is this the biggest
church in town?
well, we're the only church
in bridgewater proper.
you're aware of
the religious aspects
of this crime,
the pentagram?
yes, i am.
have there been
any break-ins, thefts,
threats towards
the church?
no.
parishioners
behaving strangely?
regulars who may have
recently stopped coming?
well, not that i'm aware of.
how about
questions about satan?
from your young members?
possession? exorcisms?
the occult?
well, now, that,
i'm sure i would remember.
good.
thanks for your time.
we're so sorry
for your loss.
they say we couldn't
have an open casket,
so we need to choose
a picture.
i didn't know which one to use,
so i
brought them all.
she's beautiful.
her first steps?
oh, bob took that.
thank god.
i would have missed it.
i was at a church retreat
for the weekend.
pretty young
to be walking.
9 months.
youngest girl
in the whole neighborhood to walk.
first to swim, too.
that's abbey.
when's her birthday?
uh, july 28.
leo. headstrong,
popular, generous,
center of attention.
am i right?
to a "t." that's abbey.
she was only 17
when she graduated.
she's studyin'
to be a nurse.
was.
what's that, dear?
she was studying
to be a nurse.
i, um--
i made the identification.
there was
a sheet over her.
doc pulled it down
just enough to see her face,
but i could tell--
i could s-see from where the sheet laid
over her body that...
that something
wasn't right.
detective jordan
won't tell me the details,
says i don't need to know.
and doc says
i don't need to see.
this is abbey.
this is my s-sweet abbey.
and i trust doc,
and i trust detective jordan,
but you're from the fbi,
and if you tell me
that i don't--i don't need
to see or i don't need to know,
i'll believe you.
trust me, mr. kelton.
these are the memories
you wanna keep.
thank you.
thank you, father.
take care.
hi, father.
for lee-ann and bob.
we feel so helpless.
we had to do something.
there's plenty of room
in the fridge, ok?
- go on. take it in there.
- thanks, father.
there's no evidence that any
of the local kids
were into devil worship
or the occult.
no, this is not
a group of teenagers.
it's a serial killer.
and considering what he did
with her fingers, a sadistic one.
that, i wouldn't
say just yet.
he cut off her fingers,
and he made her eat them.
if that isn't sadistic--
if it was, that's the only sign of sadism
present in the crime.
if he was purely a sadist, there would
have been more signs of torture.
the fingers
are a message.
what the hell's
the message?
"she's not my first."
none of the fingers found in abbey kelton's
stomach were hers,
and 6 of them
were index fingers.
hear ye, hear ye, the honorable
penelope garcia presiding.
speak and be heard.
uh, it's colby.
we met this morning.
you fixed my laptop.
yeah. uh, hi.
h-how's it going?
great. thanks to you.
heh. just happy
to be of service.
you know, i was wonderin'
if you'd let me
make that thank-you lunch
a dinner.
you really
don't have to do that.
i know, but i'd like to.
i'm askin' you out,
garcia.
tomorrow night.
tomorrow night?
you know, i would love to,
but i am coming down
with something.
are you ok?
y-yeah.
maybe some other time
when you're feelin' up to it.
yeah. that--
i have your number.
feel better.
thanks.
hey, what you
got for me, girl?
i just sent you
10 separate i.d.s belonging
to the 10 fingers found
in abbey kelton's stomach.
no 2 fingers belong
to the same woman.
10.
and you i.d.ed them already?
mm. 40-plus prostitution
arrests made it easy.
they worked truck stops
and rest areas
in the counties
surrounding bridgewater.
well, the unsub
knows the area well.
clearly. gotta go. bye.
hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
what, no snappy rhetoric?
what's goin' on?
not in the mood.
penelope?
uh, that guy from
the coffee shop asked me out,
and i took your advice,
and i blew him off.
oh. um...
well, good. smart move.
something was definitely
wrong with him.
wow.
you are some profiler.
you could tell how wrong he was
from what little i told you.
garcia,
i didn't mean to--
i wonder was it
that he was too handsome
or too interested in me
that tipped you off
on how wrong he was?
garcia, i--
just 'cause you wouldn't cross
a crowded room to hit on me
does not mean that a more perceptive,
less superficial guy wouldn't.
hey, derek, u want snappy?
you suck.
hey.
uh, garcia just i.d.ed
10 victims.
yeah, she's just sent the file through.
look at this.
last known locations
of the 10 victims.
has hotch seen this?
yes.
oh, yeah. hotch set up
the profile briefing.
uh, we're calling
the families.
you're briefing the locals.
abbey kelton and 10 others
murdered by a serial killer
here in bridgewater.
here? how can you be sure?
these marks represent where
the first 10 disappeared.
the void in the center
is his safety zone.
he avoids killing near his
home to escape detection,
and the void's center
is bridgewater.
why would he violate
his safety zone?
no one knew
he existed.
because no one
knew he existed.
that's why he left us
the fingers.
if he wants us to know,
does he want u to catch him?
no. killing gives him power.
our knowing gives him more.
he won't stop.
he's just getting started.
detective jordan.
yeah.
yeah, i got it.
you were right.
he's just gettin' started.
so yesterday afternoon,
tracey lambert
told her roommate
she was going for a hike.
he was waiting for her.
uh, blitz attack, probably like
abbey kelton's at the gas station.
our, um, unsub was likely
in a mental institution.
why do you say that?
one neat aspect.
the severely mentally ill
have chaos all around them.
when institutionalized,
they're given order,
taught to keep their
rooms clean and neat.
when discharged,
they stop taking their meds.
their minds
fall back into chaos,
but often they do one thing
to keep some order back into it.
ok. i'll call garcia,
tell her to check
state mental records.
hey.
what's he doin' here?
i called him.
state search and rescue's
out of tallahassee.
it'd take at least
4 to 5 hours to set it up.
so?
well, tracey's a member
of the church choir,
and my congregation
is feeling helpless.
at least this way,
we'll feel like we're doin' something.
it's not
a good idea.
the unsub could be a member
of your church.
so?
serial killers like to insert themselves
in these investigations.
look, tracey is the second girl
to go missing around here.
and we all know
what happened to the first.
now, i am conducting
this search.
sir, we're here to help, ok?
let us set it up.
if we have to do a search,
we can try to draw him out.
volunteer sign-in sheet
should give us a good suspect list.
all right, let's do it.
please have your i.d.s out
and ready for the volunteer sign-in.
as soon
as you've signed in,
move towards
the staging area,
and officers will instruct you
on search procedure.
every search pair
should have one whistle.
thanks, father.
hey, father.
???
next.
tracey.
tracey lambert.
tracey?
sheryl?
all units, codal8.
timmons, sheryl--white female,
age 32, 5'5", brown hair,
last seen wearing khakis
and a pink shirt.
all units
respond immediately.
unit 18, roger.
responding.
copy.
slow it down,
buddy!
help!
what am i gonna
tell my boys?
i mean, matt's old enough to know
what's going on.
it's all my fault.
i shouldn't have left her.
hey, how's it going
with father marks?
any of the volunteers
jump out at him?
not yet.
garcia?
i'm still running
the particulars
of our homicides
through vicap.
nothing so far.
ok, i just sent you
the volunteer search list.
ok, and i'm cross-checking the names
against mental institution records.
pay attention to individuals
who were involuntarily
committed in florida.
uh, rossi's
convinced our unsub
is the type that likes
to stick close to home.
got it.
talk to you later.
hey, garcia, you normally call morgan
about these kinds of things.
is everything ok?
god, i hate profilers.
ok, come on. tell me.
i met this guy at the coffee shop
i go to every day.
right. got it.
what?
when a woman tells a man
about her feelings,
she doesn't want him
to fix her.
she wants him
to shut up and listen.
so?
i know these people
better than anyone,
and none of them
fits the description
of the man
you've described.
one of them does.
i'm sorry. i--i-- i--
he's a mimic.
he imitates faith,
attends service every sunday,
but only goes because
everyone else goes.
you know him.
i do my best to guide
my congregation, ok?
but these days,
most of them--
not just the younger,
unmarried men--
are imitating faith.
almost all of them come because
the rest of them do.
my job is not--
none of that is important
right now.
what is important is that
i'm looking for a killer,
and he is on that list.
and i don't know him.
i can't help you.
i'm sorry!
tell that to sheryl timmons'
husband and children
when they ask you to pray
over what's left of her.
i'm sure they'll
find it real comforting.
and i'll be praying
for their sake and yours
that i never have to
do that, agent morgan.
good luck with that.
what happened to you?
only someone who grew up
with religion
could have so much contempt
for a priest he hardly knows.
when i was a kid,
something bad was
happening to me...
and i went to church every day,
and i prayed.
oh, i prayed
for it to stop.
you know
what god did?
nothin'.
he never gives us
more than we can handle.
your god expects way too much of
13-year-old boys.
father marks seemed
pretty shaken up when he left.
yeah, well, he had
enough reason to be.
you're still pissed i threw you
under the bus with him yesterday.
am i?
you know, in my day, if your partner
made a request like that--
well, i was just giving you a chance
for personal growth.
i get you, dave.
you're not a mystery
to me, man.
they said you couldn't interview
serial killers.
you did.
they said you couldn't
put together a profiling team.
you did.
they said there was no way in hell
you would ever come back here.
you did.
it's in your nature,
rossi.
it's who you are.
well, if you
knew all that,
why would you tell me
you didn't want to talk to the priest?
i was giving you an opportunity
for personal growth.
where you goin'?
to apologize.
i'm sorry to interrupt.
um, i'm lookin'
for father marks.
did you see that?
ma'am.
excuse me, ma'am.
whoa.
please.
please don't hurt me.
i have children.
please.
relax.
this is gonna feel
real nice.
well, she's hispanic.
clearly she's neither of
the 2 women we're looking for.
ok, i got it.
all right, her name
is maria lopez.
she's 34 years old,
numerous arrests
for solicitation
and prostitution
just like the others,
but she was reported
missing 9 months ago.
she's been dead 72 hours,
and i can say with certainty
there was no sexual assault.
why would he keep her alive
for 9 months
and then kill her
3 days ago?
dr. fulton, can u check the tissue to see
if the cells have burst?
you think
she was frozen?
why?
because i think he's eating them.
dr. fulton confirmed it.
maria lopez was frozen
shortly after her death.
well, that explains
why we haven't been able
to find the other victims.
he's keepin' '.
how you get
the cannibalism?
he didn't take them for sex,
and he took their legs.
he was trying to tell us
by feedinghe fingers
to abbey kelton.
fingers were a message.
"i've killed before"
was only part of it.
"i'm eating them" was the other.
cannibalism,
the greatest taboo.
that explains his drive to blame
his appetite on an outside force.
why would anyone want
to eat human flesh?
it's like a sexual urge,
a cross-wiring of the 2 most basic
human drives--
sustenance and sex.
it all fits.
hey. garcia,
i'm putting you on speaker.
so i can't find
any patients in florida
who have the charmheg of being
both a satanist and a cannibal.
however, hazelwood mental institution
is the place to go
when looking for florida's
most dangerous kinds of wackos,
and they had a fire in 1998
that destroyed all their records.
how far away
is hazelwood
70 miles.
uh, jj, tell 'em
we're on our way. uh, reid.
let's go.
as i told agent jareau
on the phone,
we have no existing record
of that patient you described.
but your records only go back
as far as 1998.
we were hoping that perhaps
you would remember him?
i'm sorry. i don't.
jim lorenz was in charge
of the adolescents.
adolescents?
only reason we release a patient
??? disturbed
is if he had been admitted
as a minor and turned 18.
could we speak
to dr. lorenz?
he died in the fire.
he was leaving
when he heard the alarm.
he came back inside...
and became trapped.
why would he come back?
he was a very dedicated man.
could it be because there was something
in his office
that he felt
was worth risking his life for?
dr. nash?
there is something.
the grounds people found it in a tree
just below his office.
jim, uh, must have
thrown it out of his window
just before he...
i started reading.
i had to s-stop.
"the--" uh,
"the patient's symptoms
"go far beyond normal psychosexual,
oral biting fixation
of a typical 7-year-old boy."
rossi, we've got something.
i need a name, reid.
"admitted after biting
a large piece of flesh
- out of his 9-month-old sist."
- a name.
believes he is
possessed by a flesh-eating demon."
- reid.
- floyd feylinn ferrel.
feylinn?
floyd feylne?
- you know him?
- sure i do.
he dropped his last name.
would he be
bat obvious?
absolutely.
he's not that bright.
he believes satan would protect him
from getting caught.
go right.
clear.
dear god.
sheryl timmons?
- yes.
- you're safe now.
is tracey lambert
here?
no.
keep it together.
i need you to look at the faces.
do you see
tracey lambert?
no. no,
tracey's not here.
tracey lambert?
she's not here.
fbi! don't move!
get your hands
where i can see 'em.
do it now!
feylinn!
i got him.
get up.
where's tracey lambert?
let's go.
francisco goya,
known the black paintings.
lorenz's notes say that
feylinn was exposed to them
as part of his
therapeutic art therapy.
i don't think
it worked.
he kills them
after 72 hours.
tracey's been go for 24.
see if you can find out where she is.
do what i can.
"kobe girl steak," huh?
that's where you massage
the meat, rit?
floyd, these are some pretty unusual recipes
you got here.
you try 'em all?
hmm?
must have tried
some of them, right?
talk to me.
which ones
did you try?
they have
a smiley-face by them.
others have
a frowny-face.
they sure do.
why?
ey didn't
turn out so good.
well, thank you for that.
you hear voices, floyd?
i'm not smart.
but i have a smart friend
who tells me things.
what's your
smart friend's name?
he wants me
to tell you somethin'.
tell me what?
your watch
has stopped.
he's tryin'
to spook him.
it won't work.
yeah. um...
i was meanin' to change the batteries
over a month ago.
you know, we thought you
chose athletically built women
because you were
attracted to them,
but that was only
part of it, right?
like a woman with a little
meat on her bones, don't you?
makes for better recipes,
doesn't it?
hmm?
somethin' i'm missin'?
skinny ones take drugs.
so, what, you don't
like drug users?
they taste funny.
where tracey lambert,
floyd?
i'm not supposed
to tell you.
i'm only supposed
to tell father marks.
i'm gonna
stop talkin' now.
???
????
you gotta let me do all the talkin'.
you hear me?
thank you for comin',
father.
anything i can do to--
floyd, i had to pull some serious strings
to get him here.
my bosses didn't like the idea at all
of sendin' him in.
now, they're gonna allow him to sit
right here and listen,
but you're gonna talk
to me, all right?
ok.
i've done some
really bad things.
everybody's done things
they're not proud of, floyd.
the only thing that helps
is to talk about 'em,
tell other people.
things are always better
after you talk about 'em.
not everything.
this is strange.
when he entered
the park,
feylinn signed the volunteer
sign-in sheet,
but his name's not on the list
of searchers.
come on, floyd.
i got him here
like you asked.
now it's your turn.
tell us.
where is tracey lambert?
something's wrong.
father, i feel so alone.
i feel like god
has abandoned me.
why?
you are not alone, my son.
god is in all of us.
we need to stop
the interview.
so is
tracey lambert.
you son of a bitch.
you son of--
father marks!
father marks, no!
come on! no! help!
you son of a bitch!
get him out of here.
he was feeding
the volunteers.
16th-century english novelist
thomas deloney wrote,
"god sends meat,
and the devil sends cooks."
blaming the devil
for his cannibalism
wasn't enough
to lessen his guilt,
so he tricked others
into participating.
he made them all
as guilty as he was.
he caught every break
possible, rossi.
gets released
from the hospital.
his records get destroyed.
gets pulled over with a victim
in the trunk of his car,
and they let him go.
i've never seen anyone
that lucky.
what's your point?
you been doin' this a long time.
you've seen a lot of things.
you think it's possible
that feylinn would--
i don't know. that he was
gettin' some kind of help
from somethin' else?
it's irrelevant.
the job is to find evil,
to stop it,
not to know
where it came from.
let somebody else
take that job.
this one's tough enough.
you know,
reid was right.
about?
if you believe in one,
you have to believe
in the other.
i--i really enjoyed
myself tonight.
me, too.
i guess it's lucky
my laptop froze up
on me when it did.
uh, i don't know about luck,
but it was awfully good
that i was there to fix it.
you don't
believe in luck?
not really, no.
huh. do you believe
in coincidences?
i believe that everything happens for
a really good reason.
oh. oh, i think
you're right about that.
oh. this--this is it.
yeah. well...
good night.
oh.
yeah.
hey, garcia.
yeah?
i been thinkin' about
doin' this all night.
ææàãğü×öä»×é
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
»¶ó­¼óèë