Previously on Fringe...
When we were in Jacksonville,
there was a pie chart with names.
Yeah, all the kids
from Walter and Bell's trials.
I made a list.
Nick Lane and James Heath.
They were both part
of Walter's tests.
Of all the children
that Walter and I have prepared,
you are the strongest.
The storm is coming,
and when it is over, I fear there
will be little left of our world.
I'm not from here, am I?
You didn't just open up
a hole to the other side.
You brought me back.
That's why I can't remember
my childhood.
- You were dying.
- That's why my mother committed suicide.
She knew.
Walter, Peter checked himself out
of the hospital three hours ago.
He's gone.
Mr. Secretary.
Hello, son.
Anomalous energy signature detected.
Local... Brooklyn.
Confirmed...
We've got a breach.
I was thinking, "Maybe a slow day,
it being Saturday and all."
No rest for the wicked.
You're not wicked, Charlie.
You just pretend really well.
- Somebody playing my song?
- Class one event, sir.
I can see that. You?
- Yes, I can.
- Clear as day.
Okay, people, nap time's over.
Let's go to work.
So exactly how big would the worms get
if you stopped dosing yourself?
They're not worms.
They're arachnids.
Sit rep as follows.
Class-one molecular dissolution.
Numbers show severe
molecular cohesion failure.
This isn't just a little tear.
We got a full-fledged hole here.
- Has anything come through it?
- No data yet.
On site in less than 60 seconds.
Long as it's not bugs.
It's probably bugs.
What? Bugs like you.
On my six!
I want science and risk reports
in three minutes.
Site's secure, boss.
Chief, this is bad.
I'm showing stage-three degradation.
I need data that tells me
this event is contained, Captain.
I'm trying here.
Damn it.
We're in potential
quarantine range here, sir.
Send up a looker, stat.
The looker's being
dispatched now, sir.
Hi. I'm agent Dunham
with Fringe Division.
- Could I see your show-me, please?
- Sure.
You ain't gonna
quarantine the place.
There's nothing to worry about.
But if you could tell me
what you saw...
Even small things
could be important.
I'm getting decreased gravity
measurements here, Colonel.
Activating quarantine potentiator.
Agent Farnsworth?
Broyles. Phillip. Colonel.
Risk assessment.
I need to know
if this thing is spreading.
- We can't have another Boston, Captain.
- I know that.
You think I don't know that?
Quarantine device unlocked.
Recommendation, Agent.
Quarantine will result in excess
of 10,000 casualties.
Warning.
One minute to quarantine.
Massive loss of life will result.
Warning...
Recommendation, Agent.
Gravitational and molecular
degeneration are decreasing,
but outside acceptable parameters.
- Recommendation, Agent Farnsworth?
- Calculating.
Massive loss of life will result.
- Really?
- 40 seconds to quarantine.
- Quarantine device unlocked.
- God, and I didn't even update my will.
- Massive loss of life will result.
- Frank would just spent it all anyway.
30 seconds to quarantine.
Recommendation, Agent Farnsworth?
Event is terminating.
No quarantine recommended.
Captain, you are clear.
Do not quarantine. Repeat...
- Do not quarantine.
- 20 seconds to quarantine.
We got to stop doing this.
Hey, guys!
We got something up here.
I wish it was bugs.
What is that?
These look like carcinomas.
There's no way anyone could live long
enough to develop tumors this severe.
- Witnesses have anything?
- The usual...
They heard a tearing sound. They saw
a blue flash through the window.
I gave them chips
so they could get radiation scans.
See if he has any ID.
Guy may have had a wife and kids
before the universe sucked him up
and spat him out.
Poor guy.
That's not a show-me.
Check this out.
Who the hell is Jackson?
Come on. Come on. Let's go.
Come on, everyone.
Keep down.
Come on. Come on.
_.•´¯¯LIAISON¯¯`•. _
¯`•. __Team__.•´¯
Retrouvez-nous chaque semaine...
pour découvrir les énigmes de
Saison 2 Épisode 22
- Over There, Part 1 -
Bon épisode...
I can take you back
where you belong, son.
They have our coordinates.
But if you come with me,
you won't be able to come back here.
You have to make a choice, Peter.
Let's go.
- Hello?
- Hello, Agent Dunham.
There is something
I am supposed to remember,
and I can'remember what it is,
but it's about Peter.
I think something is going
to happen to him,
something...
Something terrible.
I think this is what
I'm supposed to remember.
One of those men, the Observers...
I think he left it for me.
After I brought
Peter from the other side,
some years later,
one of them came to visit me.
He told me that I had to agree
to never let Peter
return to the other side.
Why?
Because if I did, this would happen.
What is this, Walter?
What does it even mean?
It is exactly
what it appears to be. See?
I think my son...
is going to be responsible
for the end of the world.
Walter, we have get Peter back.
- He went off by his own free will.
- But he didn't know about this.
- Even if he wanted...
- How do we get him back?
We have no way of contacting...
How?
- I'm sorry, sir, I can't let you go...
- Don't even think about it!
- What is this?
- We believe your company
is manufacturing weapons.
- That absurd.
- I want every data
- related to the other universe.
- Are you out of your mind?
Stop it, both of you!
Peter is in danger.
Walter says that this technology
has a very specic
and recognizable design.
- I dare say Nina would agree.
- Dear God.
- What side is this?
- Does it matter?
This is William's technology,
but we didn't build it.
Nina, listen to me.
Peter's been taken.
You have to help us cross over.
The thing is, to get over there,
that's really a misnomer.
In truth,
the two universes are overlapping.
And to get to the other side,
our universe needs
to pass through you,
literally, like water passing
through a cheesecloth.
Our cells need to separate
on an atomic level.
The problem is,
when they come back together,
they don't come back together
with the same cohesion.
Somehow, Bell managed to
cross back and forth,
although precisely how,
we can find no record of.
But I suspect that
whatever methodology,
he crossed so many times
that he's become
like this coffee cup.
Molecularly unstable.
As many atoms in each of us
as there are stars in the sky.
It's why Belly never
came back, isn't it?
Because he was scared that
the same thing would happen to him.
I don't know.
I've sent him communications,
but if he got them,
he hasn't been able
to communicate to me.
There has to be a way.
What about how you crossed over
when you first got Peter?
The last time I opened a door,
it set in motion the ripples
that weaken the very fabric
of our reality.
To do so again could
instantly shatter both worlds...
And likely would.
Brandon, give us a moment.
Unlike William,
you have the ability to
cross over safely.
I can't. I mean, I can't control it.
I've flashed over for a few seconds,
or Bell's pulled me over,
but I can't control it, not on my own.
Not on your own,
but if there were
two or three of you,
a larger power suply, as it were.
- I'm not following.
- With more cortexiphan children,
their collective
psychic energy could...
You know, Belly and I always agreed
that primal part of the brain
which allows us to cross universes
is also responsible for a host
of paranormal activities...
Pyrokinesis, telepathy,
thought control.
And that we all had these abilities
until there was a moment in history
when something was done to us,
and it was shut down.
I suspect aliens.
Unfortunately,
the only other cortexiphan children
that we have located,
they have failed worse.
You...
are the only one left.
Actually...
she's not.
There's still over a dozen of
cortexiphan subject unaccounted for.
Prudence dictated we determine what
we might be dealing with in the future.
So you woke all three of them up?
Actually, five.
We've tracked down some others.
About six weeks ago,
Massive Dynamic proposed
a series of experiments
to help them gain control of
and repurpose their abilities.
These three have been
quite successful.
James Heath can now cure disease,
not cause it.
Sally Clark is becoming a fully
functional pyrokinetic.
And your friend Nick Lane's empathic
transfers can now be controlled.
Olive.
Nick.
Very good, baby.
Welcome to the monkey house.
This is new. Who authorized it?
Senate intelligence...
Thanks to Peter.
It was part of a list
of demands he gave me
right before I went
to secure our funding.
This is very Mission: Impossible.
I know you. You're the man
that experimented on us.
- I could kill you where you stand.
- Each of you could.
What I did...
was inexcusable...
Barbaric.
The collateral damage
has been extensive.
But know that we had noble goals,
We believed
that our world needed guardians,
protectors, that you children
would be those protectors.
We fostered your talents
because we foresaw
that the day would come
when both universes
would be in jeopardy.
So...
Horrible as it is to say,
today is the day
for which you were created.
What I could never have imagined
is that I would be asking you
to help me save son.
I'm so sorry.
If none of you are gonna kill me...
I think I'll go
and have a bit of a cry.
Man,
that's not the same guy I remember.
He's exactly the same.
Dr. Bishop has identified a likely spot
to attempt a crossover.
Brooklyn, New York.
You go at 0800 tomorrow morning.
- You might want to get some rest.
- Hey, FBI guy.
We're about to go
save the world, right?
Two worlds even.
Can't we have a night off?
Whatever they want.
Who are you?
I was never lucky, you know?
Sometimes people
need some good luck.
Tonight I guess that's me.
Who else do we have?
Sweet.
Me or the strawberry?
Both of them.
So what would you like this time...
To feel what I'm feeling
or what you're feeling?
Both.
Please, God...
Aunt Liv, what time is it?
It's early.
I have to go on a trip, and...
I wanted to give you
something before left.
It's pretty.
My mother...
Your grandmother...
gave it to me before she died.
She told me
that it would keep me safe.
So now I'm giving it to you.
Thanks, aunt Liv.
You are welcome, baby girl.
You're up early.
I didn't even hear
you come in last night.
No, I've been working a case.
Think you'll be home for dinner?
I hope so.
I'll call you and let you know.
You okay?
We should do this more often.
It's nice.
Sure.
Look what aunt Live gave me.
Even assuming this works,
that you make it to the other side,
you still have no idea how
you're going to locate Peter.
No, but I spoke to Nina Sharp, and
she sent a message to William Bell
asking him to meet us at the Grayshot
bridge in central park at 4:00 p.m.
I think he'll help us find Peter.
Massive Dynamic didn't
make that weapon over here.
That means Bell may have made
it on the other side for them.
No. I trust him.
In any case, Nina has no confirmation
that Bell even gets her messages.
In which case, you're essentially
invading enemy territory without a plan.
You don't know anything
about the opposition, the landscape...
We're ready.
We're ready to try this.
You can't tell me you
think this is a good idea.
I don't think that
this is a good idea.
Do you got a better one?
It was lovely, wasn't it?
Now...
faded and broken...
just like me.
So how does this work, Walter?
Remember your shakespeare, dear.
"All the world is a stage"...
Or in this case, both worlds.
You will form a circle.
I will stand in the middle,
and I will lead you across.
You can't do this.
- He is my son, Olivia.
- You can't do this. I won't allow it.
I believe I can.
Or else they cannot.
I can't ask them to do something
that I'm not willing
to chance myself.
Thank you.
Well, if any of you have chang
your minds, I will understand.
We were talking about
it on the way over here.
Maybe you did damage us.
But on the other hand,
maybe you made us special.
Fate is a tricky thing.
So...
you would want to take a few steps back,
I think, Agent Broyles.
Now, I want you to clear your minds
and just relax.
All right?
Now, ignore everything
except the sound of my voice.
Now...
Spread out your arms.
You remember how.
Spread them out to each other.
Yes.
Good.
Now, I want you to think back
to when you were
just young children,
back to when you were
just young boys and girls.
Think back to when your imagination
could take you
wherever you wanted to go.
Imagine this universe slipping away,
opening like a curtain.
Allow the universe
to pass right through you.
Allow your imagination
to take you to the other side.
Help me.
- Walter, what do we do?
- Look...
We made it.
We're on the other side.
Okay, come on, James.
You've got to get up.
We've got to hide now.
Nick, I don't feel so good.
Through here.
Come on.
I want science and risk reports
in three minutes.
Nick, make them leave.
I've been trying.
It's not working.
What's wrong with us?
- I don't know.
- Nick, I'm scared.
Check this out.
Who the hell is Jackson?
- Got a junior?
- Yeah.
Going to a strip club later?
Someone's got to visit your sister.
The paper's real.
The detail is amazing.
Why would someone go
to this kind of trouble?
What in God's name did you all find?
Nothing useful. Dead end so far.
Well, whatever it is you scanned
just raised a red flag over at the DOD.
The Secretary wants to see you.
Charlie, you ever met him?
I shook his hand once when
I graduated the academy.
- What about you?
- My dad knew him.
That explains so much.
Yeah, you don't want to
leak worms all over the guy.
Makes a bad first impression.
They're not worms.
He's waiting for you.
Go ahead in.
Mr. Secretary.
Thank you.
Agent Lee...
I'm sorry about your father.
- He was a good man. Fine jurist.
- Thank you, sir.
- And this is your team?
- Yes, sir.
Agents Francis and Dunham. Sir.
I understand you're investigating
a fringe event in Brooklyn.
That's correct, sir.
And in this event,
there was a casualty... a man?
- That's correct, sir.
- So far, we haven't been able to...
Agent, I believe that I may
have insight into who that man is
and where he was from.
What I'm about to tell you
is classified.
But I think it's time you knew
what you were dealing with.
Agent Dunham, what can
you tell me about the Fringe Division?
Okay, I'll play.
The Fringe Division is a special adjunct
branch of the Department of Defense.
It's primary focus are natural
and environmental disasters that began
in 1985
with the zero event at Reiden Lake.
And what are these
natural disasters?
They're holes in the fabric
of the universe, sir.
A-plus.
And how do you know all this?
I know it because I read it
in The ZFT in 1995
when you wrote and published it.
ZFT.
The natural decay of our world.
What would you say if I told you
that The ZFT is a lie
or a half-truth anyway?
These tears are not natural.
They are the work of man.
These holes...
don't simply lead to nothing.
There is something
on the other side.
What?
- Another one.
- Bravo.
- Another what?
- Another universe...
A parallel Earth just like this,
but slightly different.
And it was their attempt
to penetrate our world which created
the pattern of destruction
that we struggle with daily.
The $20 bill was...
From the other side, and so was he.
And I suspect he didn't come alone.
As you know,
I am not a lover of war.
But I have reason to
believe that these
invaders are anything but peaceful.
They must be found,
and they must be found quickly.
We'll get them, sir.
I'm burning up, Nick.
It'll be fine, baby.
Scan your ID, lady.
Sorry.
We're gonna have to walk.
Central Park is 59th street.
That's three miles from here.
Okay, then we better get started.
How are you feeling?
I'm okay.
You've been asleep for three days.
Your fa...
Walter said you might feel a bit dizzy.
Maybe you'd like to sit down.
I'm okay.
You must be starving.
I made some eggs and...
bacon.
Do you still like bacon?
When you were a boy, we...
I love bacon.
I've missed you so much.
- Stop for a second.
- It's fine. I'm fine. Let's go.
You've got to know something.
What the hell is wrong with us?
I suspect that somehow
the human circuit was flawed.
Did any of you engage in extreme use
of your abilities last night,
far more than normal?
Perhaps poor Mr. Heath...
- You've got to help her.
- I can't.
But if we're lucky,
perhaps William Bell can.
It's the Grand Hotel.
They never built it.
Things that might have been
in our world, but weren't.
Come on.
It's not far.
Coffee's quite hard
to come by over here.
It's been rationed
for some time now.
But Walter's very well connected.
It's funny, I...
I never had bacon
when I was growing up.
My mother was vegetarian,
so she never made it.
Until today, I always thought
I imagined having it as a kid.
I'm sorry...
My mother from the other side.
I'm sure you don't wanna hear
about that.
No, on the contrary. I want
to hear all about your childhood.
What's...
Are you close with her still?
I mean...
Did she take good care of you?
She took very good care of me.
But...
she committed suicide
about ten years ago.
My mother from the other side...
She was wonderful,
but she wasn't strong.
In fact, she was very, very sad...
- Which I suppose is because of me.
- No, listen.
In the end,
we have to take responsibility
for our own decisions,
the good and the bad.
Your father's going to
be so pleased to see you.
He had said he wanted me
to help him with something.
Yes, he's staying in the city tonight.
But he asked me to give you this.
God.
Look, Nick.
These were my favorite.
Can I get one?
I don't think so, baby.
We got to go.
I like it here.
Maybe... maybe we can stay.
I'm gonna stay.
I know, baby.
I know.
Come on, let's go.
Do you see him, William Bell?
There's a water fountain.
Come on, I think it'll help.
Are we late?
Maybe he didn't get the message.
- Bell has betrayed us.
- Run, run, run!
Don't move!
I think I'm staying here.
You stay.
We'll stay together.
I don't want to hurt you.
Step away.
Screw you.
Man down. Med team
to Grayshot Bridge. Man down.
Where's the ambulance?
Dizzy...
Must be the onset
of hemorrhagic shock.
But...
I'm still walking, so...
the bullet couldn't
have hit my spinal column.
I'll be perfectly fine.
Excuse me.
Do you really understand all these?
Maybe.
I'm not sure yet.
Good night, Peter.
Good night.
I tried to wait up.
How is he?
Well, he's got third-degree burns
over 90% of his body.
He's gonna need three months
in a nanite regeneration chamber,
but he'll live.
I'm sorry, and on your last night.
I'm going for a week,
not until the end of time.
- Details.
- Might be a good day to start drinking.
God. I would if I could
only stand the taste.
So what happened out there?
Just a small anomaly
that set off a fuel cell.
It was just bad luck
of the draw is all.
Come on, no more work.
- I know what you need.
- Yeah? What's that?
Back rub.
You are a god.
- I'll get the oil.
- Really?
On your last night?
I'll take it.
It's good to see you again.
- How did you know that I...
- I suspected you would come here.
- So where were you at the park?
- I received Nina's message,
but when I got to the park, it was
too late. There was nothing I could do.
My dear Olivia,
I know...
you have good reason
not to trust me.
But I'm afraid you're gonna have to.
Walter is in trouble.
And I'm quite confident
we don't have much time.