- Previously on Fringe.
- A series of events has occured.
These events appear to be
scientific in nature.
- It's being referred to as the Pattern.
- He worked out of Harvard,
in an area called Fringe Science.
You're telling me my father
was Dr. Frankenstein.
You were in an accident.
You were missing from your car
for at least an hour
before you came crashing back
through the windshield.
What if there's a part of my brain
that's trying to protect me?
- What's this?
- Sam Weiss.
The man who helped
put me back together.
Have the headaches started yet?
They will.
None of that vanilla hazelnut crap.
Normal coffee, all right?
I already called it in.
- Yes, Colonel?
- It's time.
Get to Suburban Station.
He'll be wearing a black trench coat
and carrying a black briefcase.
Where are you, Gillespie?
Seriously, for the last time,
where are...
Set the briefcase down now.
What's this about?
What did I do?
You give me the briefcase now.
- What's the problem?
- I got it under control.
Give me the case.
Stop! You can't do that!
You can't take that!
Officer, what's the matter?
_.•´¯¯LIAISON¯¯`•._
¯`•.__Team__.•´¯
Retrouvez-nous chaque semaine...
pour découvrir les énigmes de
Saison 2 Épisode 03
-Fracture-
Bon épisode...
The rabbit goes around the tree
then through the hole.
I know how to tie my shoes.
Knowing how isn't the issue.
You suffered some wicked head trauma.
Don't think about your hands,
don't think about the laces.
Your shoes will get tied just fine.
Just by magic.
But that would be pretty cool.
What exactly did you do
for Nina Sharp?
I taught her
how to eat French fries.
Pick one up, dip it in the ketchup,
stick it in your mouth, repeat.
Simple enough, unless you've got
a cybernetic prosthetic arm.
Nina was a mess.
See, I prefer
the bunny ears method
to the one loop wrap.
But it does require
more coordination.
- You'll get there.
- Don't take this the wrong way, but...
- I can't waste my time.
- Are you sleeping at night?
You've got circles
around your eyes, pale skin...
You don't get more than two
or three hours at a stretch, do you?
Lingering pain from the accident?
In my leg and my shoulder.
And you say the headaches
haven't started yet?
Let me know when they do.
You can take the shoes off now,
we're done.
That's it?
Unless you want me to mop up
the men's room. I'm closing now.
Come back tomorrow, agent Dunham.
We've got work to do.
How about this one?
"Two bedroom, two bath loft
in Oak Square.
Cook's kitchen, hardwood floors,
and a breakfast nook."
Does it face the east?
Riverview, so it faces north.
Then it won't do.
I need the morning sun.
Fine, how about this?
"Three bedroom duplex
in Allston, facing east."
All the morning sun
a waking scientist could want.
I never liked Allston.
Arlington either, for that matter.
I'm perfectly happy
with our present accommodations.
Well, I'm not, Walter.
I need my own bedroom.
- I woke up this morning
- to him singing an aria from Pagliacci.
Your father has a wonderful voice.
Not when he's doing jumping jacks.
And did I mention he was naked?
A good morning
sets the tone for the day.
Come take a look at this.
I've been running a filter for atypical
FBI case reports. I just got a hit.
Some sort of bomb
went off in Philadelphia.
Single explosive device.
11 dead, 28 wounded.
This last part
is what caught my eye.
They can't find any explosive residue
at the scene.
How's a bomb go off without leaving
any trace of it afterwards?
Shall I get my coat, Peter?
I'll call Dunham.
Agent Farnsworth,
get my portable chemistry set.
This means bodies.
The bomb guys don't know what to make
of it. Given the nature of the wounds,
you'd expect an explosive device filled
with nails or steel ball bearings.
- But it wasn't.
- No. In fact...
there's no forensic markers at all.
- So what about eye witnesses?
- I've got half a dozen eye witnesses,
but nobody who saw anything helpful.
It's weird. This place has
major anti-terrorism security.
EMP disabling devices at every entrance,
explosive materials sensors...
We checked,
and not a single sensor is tripped.
So what did
the surveillance cameras show?
Nothing,
nothing but magnetic static.
It seems that whatever happened
in here wiped the images.
- Would you mind if we see those tapes?
- I'll see what I can do.
Let me guess, you got a friend?
Maybe I do.
Excuse me, sir?
Do you have a badge?
No, I don't have a badge. Do you?
I got it.
What's going on?
This rather unpleasant young woman
is interfering with my work.
Is he with you?
Yeah, but don't hold that
against me.
We're FBI.
Go ahead.
So? What is it?
Shrapnel, I believe, from the bomb.
Some sort of crystal.
Hard as a diamond.
Salty. Silica, I guess.
Well, I'll need to examine
the rest of the bodies, if...
If that's all right with you, miss.
Thank you.
I spoke with
our counter-terrorism analysts.
No one stepped forward
to claim responsibility.
And there's been no increase
in chatter from our usual suspects.
I found this wedged in a bench.
It's a badge.
Philly PD, officer Gillespie.
Were there any police among the wounded
taken to the hospital?
So, where'd he go?
I was wrong.
The crystal...
I think it's not geologic in origin,
after all.
In fact, I'm certain it's organic.
Is that...
an ear?
Well, I think Walter might have just
found officer Gillespie.
This looks like fungiform papillae.
Taste buds.
Tongue.
Walter, as much as I am enjoying
this anatomy lesson,
what exactly are we doing here?
Well, that's obvious, my dear.
We're searching for clues.
Scientific evidence to reveal
what type of device
this man was wearing
which caused him to harden,
then shatter.
I understand Peter's looking for
a new place for you guys to live.
It occurs to me, that I've never
asked you where you live.
Where I live?
Diaphragm.
Well...
most of the time I live here.
But my apartment is in Sommerville.
You should go for a walk sometime...
explore the neighborhood.
The other day, I...
turned the wrong way in the street,
and discovered that Busby's...
has the world's best apple fritters.
You see,
I have everything I need
where we live now.
I know what you mean, Walter.
I'm a creature of habit, too.
Of course,
you never would've found
Busby's apple fritters
if you hadn't gone
the wrong way down a street.
You really should try them,
they're quite delicious.
Brain.
Okay, that's it.
That's the best I can do.
That must be Gillespie.
But I don't see a bomb.
Then it cuts out.
You know, I told her
you were a genius, Joe.
Don't prove me wrong.
Then you're gonna need
a smarter genius.
Do you have any idea
how something like this could happen?
The static? No.
Maybe radio wave interference.
Certain high frequencies
can tweak electronic signals.
Look at the time code.
That's about 20 seconds
before the bomb went off.
So why do we lose picture
before the explosion?
How's it going, Walter?
Any theories?
Several.
Peter, do you remember
that jigsaw puzzle
we put together when you were a kid?
The jigsaw? No.
As I recall, her name was Melissa...
something.
500 pieces.
Yes, I do remember.
Melissa was a playmate.
Miss July, right?
Putting together a jigsaw
of a nude centerfold was
Walter's idea of how to explain...
What was it? Human reproduction
to his ten-year-old son.
So what does any of that have to do
- with the bomb in Philadelphia?
- Patience, son.
Meet Officer Gillespie.
Fantastic.
So apart from the obvious,
anything out of the ordinary?
Needle marks between the toes.
It was some form of transformative
serum, I would think.
I can't say what yet.
From his tissues,
it appears to cause
a chemical reaction
on the cellular level
that both solidifies the water
in his cells
and emitted massive energy,
which shattered the body.
What are you saying, Walter?
You think he did this to himself?
On purpose?
Well, I stopped counting
at 47 needle marks.
I can't imagine it was an accident.
When you think about it...
wearing a bomb
is rather unimaginative.
This way, there's no need to smuggle
in an explosive device, because...
Officer Gillespie was the bomb.
Fascinating, yes?
We were planning to start a family.
I can't believe
he's not coming home.
Dan always came home.
After every shift on the job,
two tours in Iraq,
he always came home.
No one would tell me what happened.
Just that it was...
some kind of bomb.
We're still investigating.
I'm so sorry.
Where was he stationed?
In Ramadi.
Did you serve?
No, a civilian contractor,
based out of Baghdad.
But from what I remember,
there was heavy fighting in Ramadi.
Was he on any medication,
or under any sort of medical care?
No, Dan was healthy.
And I don't understand, what does
this have to do with the explosion?
You all right, Dunham?
Excuse me, do you have
a bathroom that I could use?
Yeah, it's down the hall.
Dunham, you all right?
Mrs. Gillespie, can you tell me
what these are?
I don't know.
I've never seen them before.
Dan Gillespie doesn't fit
the profile of a suicide bomber.
Well, how do you explain this stuff?
'Cause I'm assuming it's more
than likely that this is exactly
what Walter was talking about.
What turned him into a bomb.
Yeah, well, I can't yet.
But I mean, what makes
someone blow themselves up?
Typically, they're either
waging a war,
or making a statement.
Dan Gillespie was
a decorated cop and soldier, just...
getting himself back together.
- It doesn't make sense.
- Is there anything else on your mind?
Like what?
The headache.
Didn't the doctor
say that would happen?
They said they might.
That it was totally normal.
We should get that back to Walter.
Maybe he can figure out
where those vials came from.
Let me help you with that.
Colonel.
We need to talk,
captain Burgess.
I'm calling you
back to active status.
You're going to DC on Friday.
Hotel reservations, plane tickets,
all-self-explanatory.
Now that phone,
keep it with you at all times.
Check in with the hotel,
wait for me to call you
with further instructions.
Do you have a cover story
prepared for your family?
Yes, sir.
I'll say I'm visiting my sister.
She lives in Georgetown.
Have you been taking the serum?
- Yes, sir.
- Good, because from this moment on,
Tin Man parameters are in effect.
So, how'd you know?
The headaches started.
Well, it's about time.
Can you just cut the Yoda crap
and tell me what's happening to me?
The short version...
The headaches mean
you've finally sparked the battery.
You've been experiencing...
an acute nominal aphasia,
Agent Dunham.
It's common with head trauma.
Parts of your brain
are still asleep.
But once they wake up,
all that memory will get flushed out.
When?
When will I get my memory back?
You know, everywhere you go
the scoring apparatuses
have changed.
Computers, no fun.
Here, we do things old school,
with a dull pencil and
all your third grade math skills.
You know, this is ridiculous.
I'm not bowling, I can't even walk
without this damn cane.
You're not bowling.
I've got a kid's league coming in here,
you're gonna keep score.
How is that gonna help my memory?
I mean, how is that
gonna help me at all?
Well, for starters,
it might teach you some patience.
Is that food I smell?
Bless you!
While examining Officer Gillespie,
I've discovered something else.
Given the amount of serum
that we found in his tissue,
and the rate at which
it would've metabolized,
I suspect that
he would've had to inject it
every day for a very long time.
Well, how long?
At least a year, I would think.
A year?
That would mean Gillespie
started injecting
while he was still
on his tour in Iraq.
Did his army personnel file
come through yet?
I haven't seen it.
Let me check though.
Interestingly...
When the serum is
first introduced or injected,
it's fairly harmless.
But then something else occurs,
a secondary reaction.
Some sort of trigger
causes these bombs to blast apart.
The triggers...
If you are going to eat
that cheeseburger in here,
could you at least
be a little discreet?
Fine.
This trigger,
could it be a radio wave?
There was some sort of interference
on the security tapes
inside the train station.
Most likely caused by radio waves.
Yes. I suppose so.
I've got Gillespie's military file.
What's cyanogen chloride?
It's a chemical weapon.
His whole unit was
exposed to cyanogen.
According to this file,
Gillespie should've died in Iraq.
Four words that should
never show up in a sentence.
"Classified experimental
military project."
How much you wanna bet that
Tin Man has everything to do
with those injections
that Gillespie was taking?
It says here
that Project Tin Man was shut down.
Shortly after Dan Gillespie
returned home.
And all the names of
the U.S. military personnel
associated with the project
were redacted from the record.
But it still lists Malik Yusef,
Abbas Khalef, and Howard Ziad
as Iraqi doctors
who worked on the program.
- Where are they?
- Presumably still in the country.
CENTCOM has agreed to look for them,
but it may take a few weeks
to track anything down.
I may be able to help.
But I'm gonna need
a few things first.
I need to go back to Iraq.
I know somebody who can
help us find those doctors.
Seems a long way to go for a maybe.
W have to assume that Gillespie
was not a solitary event.
There may be others
out there like him, walking bombs.
- We don't have two weeks to wait.
- What is it you need?
Private air transportation,
$20,000 in cash,
and a passport without
my real name on it.
I'm still on
a couple of watch lists.
Then you're gonna need
a federal agent with you as well.
I'm reluctant to send you,
Agent Dunham.
With that said, we need
to keep this trip between us.
You look after each other.
You ready for this?
Baghdad, here we come.
Maybe I should wait outside.
Then what would I do?
You're the one with the gun.
Assalam waleikum.
In that case, we speak English.
I need your help, Ahmed.
A US military program named Tin Man.
It's operating out of a hospital
in Samarra.
I need to find
one of the Iraqi doctors
who was working in that program.
I can pay you, of course.
When I heard you had been killed,
I knew this could not be true.
Because a person like you
is good at one thing.
More than anything else,
a person like you
is good at looking out for yourself.
Now you are here...
asking for my help?
Yes, I am.
Maybe someone else
will want your money.
I don't.
A lot of innocent lives
may be on the line.
I see.
And this is something
you care about now?
Yes, I do.
I may be able to save them...
with your help.
What are the names of these doctors?
Have some tea.
I will see what I can do.
You gonna tell me
what that was about?
What did I tell you
about experimenting with fruit?
I just cleaned
this lab up yesterday.
Relax, my dear.
Just injecting a very small amount
of the serum into the watermelon.
Just to crystallize it.
The serum we found
at Gillespie's house told us
how he became a bomb. But...
the question remains,
what triggered it?
So you're using radio waves
like Peter suggested?
Radio waves would also explain
the eyewitness reports
of flashing lights at the train station
before the officer exploded.
Quite ingenious, really.
The same principal
applied to proximity fuses,
and World War II arial bombs...
In fact,
my uncle Henry was killed by one
in the battle of the Guadalcanal.
This is it!
- Quickly, what's the frequency?
- 331.6 megahertz.
What happened?
It stopped.
I'm not sure.
It works.
No more fruit, Walter.
Ready for something
a little harder than tea?
Sure.
Red Russian?
- Mint tea and vodka.
- Well, it sounds weird and awful.
Actually, it's worse.
- You'll get used to it.
- How long were you here?
Which time?
I had to leave a couple of times.
Seems like you made
a name for yourself.
I've been known
to leave an impression.
To all that's weird.
Doctor Malik Yusef...
{\We understand you worked
They consider me a traitor.
We were hoping
to ask you some questions
about a program that you worked on.
A program called Tin Man?
I do not know anything about this.
The program didn't work,
it was too dangerous.
The soldiers had been exposed
to a synthetic neurotoxin,
a nerve agent
developed under Saddam.
Cyanogen?
We had been trying to find
a way to neutralize it
to counteract the affects.
And that's what they called Tin Man?
We had developed a...
a treatment.
Daily injections of a serum.
We treated over 200 soldiers.
Only a few of them survived.
We know of one, Daniel Gillespie.
Daniel, kind man.
Over the course of the program,
there were three others.
- Do you remember their names?
- Of course, I saved their lives.
There was Joan Klump,
Ross Cavanaugh, and...
Diane Burgess.
Okay, Diane, you're all set.
Suitcase is at the front door.
You sure you don't want me
to drive you to the airport?
But it was too dangerous.
The serum had
an unintentional byproduct.
We had discovered that after it
built up in human tissue,
It reacted in a very unexpected way.
It turned people into bombs.
How did you know that?
Doctor Yusef, how many other people
knew about this?
Five doctors,
a dozen U.S. officers, and...
whoever they reported to, I suppose.
Someone is triggering these people
to explode. It could be anyone.
There was a man, a colonel.
When the program was shut down,
he argued it should be continued.
Do you remember his name?
Gordon...
Colonel Raymond Gordon.
A word of warning...
Gordon is a vicious man.
He has no regard for human life.
You all have briefing packets,
so I'll just point out the highlights.
Information has come to this agency
that a bomb may be detonated
today somewhere in this city.
But in this instance,
that bomb is a human being.
Three of the four known operatives of
Project Tin Man have been accounted for.
Daniel Gillespie, you're all
familiar with. Two others
have been taken into protective
custody. Which leaves Diane Burgess.
We believe Captain Burgess traveled
to DC this morning, under an alias.
Though we do not have any intelligence
on her potential target.
A bolo has been issued to all metro
and state police in the area.
All potential high-value targets
are under close surveillance.
Agent Dunham and I will coordinate
Captain Burgess' apprehension.
Based on our investigation,
it's likely there
is a second suspect
controlling detonation
from a remote location.
We believe it's this man,
Colonel Raymond Gordon.
The Pentagon lost contact
with Colonel Gordon six months ago.
He's off the grid.
Officially designated
a rogue operative.
Now based on Dr. Bishop's analysis,
the explosion is triggered
by a specific VHF frequency.
Now if we can locate Captain Burgess
in time to get within range,
we may be able to jam the signal
and prevent her detonation.
On that point, we suspect
that Diane Burgess
is unaware she is being used
in a suicide bombing.
Which means that she is also
a potential victim here.
We're gonna do
everything that we can
to get her back to her family alive.
Diane Burgess has just been located.
She's in a D.C. metro cab.
Dispatchers say she's headed
to the Federal Center Metro Station.
We have time to set up
before she arrives.
Our objectives are as follows:
To prevent the detonation
of Captain Diane Burgess
and to apprehend
Colonel Raymond Gordon.
This is Broyles, go ahead.
Video surveillance and
3-D triangulation model online.
Stand by,
we'll wait for Diane Burgess.
Snipers ready.
Target sited, arriving at
Federal Center Station, south portal.
The phone's encrypted, sir.
We can't tap into it.
There's no sign of the colonel
outside of the station.
Copy that, keep an eye on it.
Where are we on that signal?
Attempting to acquire
signal 331.6 megahertz.
Excuse me, Agent Broyles...
Is there an EMP detection device
in this station?
All capitol transportation hubs
had them installed after 9/11.
- What's the problem?
- No problem.
It's just that the security device
would scramble all types
of radio wave triggers.
- That sounds to me like a good thing.
- Frequency acquired.
Jamming. Ready.
Prepare to jam the signal.
- Stand by to apprehend target.
- I'm thinking that if the colonel
wants Ms. Burgess inside the building.
Then in order to trigger the explosion,
he must be inside as well.
Which means we should
be able to triangulate his position.
But in order to do that, we would have
to leave the frequency open.
We can't jam it.
This could be our only chance
to find Gordon and apprehend him.
Target's about to enter the station.
Do we move, sir?
I said stand by.
How long from when he activates
the signal until she detonates?
30 seconds, at best.
That should give us long enough
to be able to locate him.
All units hold position.
Let the target
get into the building.
Go.
Your contact will be wearing
a black trench coat.
I have a briefcase for you.
Accept the briefcase
and proceed by taxi
back to your hotel.
- Is that it, sir?
- That's it, Captain.
I'll meet you there.
Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
Diane Burgess should be standing
near the northwest side of the terminal.
We're still waiting for Gordon
to activate the VHF signal.
I got her.
She's by the front entrance.
Keep an eye on her.
Do we have anything from Gordon yet?
The signal hasn't
been activated yet, sir.
She's on the move.
Still no sign of Gordon.
That's it. That's the VHF signal.
- She'll detonate in 30 seconds.
- Agent, tell me where Gordon is.
Something's wrong. Sir, the signal's
scrambling our equipment.
- I can't get a lock on Gordon.
- Smart.
The signal is scrambling
our equipment.
I think you have something for me.
One Mississippi...
Two Mississippi...
30 seconds.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
We've got her speaking to a man
with a briefcase.
It is not Gordon.
Can you get a lock on the signal?
- We can't get a lock.
- Then jam that signal.
We're jamming the signal, I'm not
risking these lives to get Gordon.
Sir, it's not working.
The signal's too strong
for our equipment. I'm locked out.
We have a problem.
Attempts to jam the signal have failed.
She's going to detonate.
We have a problem.
The signal cannot be jammed.
I repeat, the signal...
Peter, I think we lost radio contact.
We need to find Gordon..
Copy that.
The trigger's been activated,
we don't have much time.
I don't know who you are.
My God!
I spotted Gordon.
I'm taking him out.
Twenty-four Mississippi.
Twenty-five Mississippi.
Twenty-six Mississippi.
We're back online.
The signal has stopped.
All agents, move in.
What's this?
An apartment.
Two bedroom, semi-detached.
Furnished housing for professors.
It's a nice neighborhood.
Down the block from
where Belly used to live.
I'll call Broyles,
see if we can lease it.
Okay, seven and a quarter inches.
Why "hmm"?
I think your hand just seems
smaller to me.
Okay, we're good.
We're good, what does that mean?
It means that's all for tonight.
Go home.
I just got here.
I know, but I'm tired.
It's been a long day.
You look like you could
use some sleep yourself.
Come back tomorrow. By then I'll have
found you the perfect bowling ball.
You listen to me you son of a bitch.
I am not here to bowl,
or to try on shoes,
or to have you play games
with my head.
I am here because I was told
that you could fix me.
Take care, agent Dunham.
Meanwhile, we go
through our lives unaware.
The enemy is among us
and nobody's doing
anything about it.
We don't have any idea
the end is coming.
So we had to take matters
into our own hands.
We had to send them a message.
What was in the briefcase?
They told you I was crazy,
didn't they?
The Pentagon.
They said I'd had
a psychiatric break.
I told them what I'm telling you.
That they are here.
Collecting data.
Making observations.
That's what's in the briefcase.
They've been planning for war.
And they've been passing
the information via courier
right under our noses.
Who are "they"?
We don't know who they are.
But I can tell you what they want.
They want to exterminate us.
So they're studying us...
Our culture, our technology,
our science...
and they plan to use it against us.
One way or another.
We'll find out who they are.
But by then,
I suppose it won't really matter.
Because whatever is in those cases
is going to destroy us all.
À la semaine prochaine !