Previously on Fringe...
When objects from the other universe
cross to our side,
they have an energy.
- Someone described it as a glimmer.
- How can I see it?
The cortexiphan trials.
I was part of the trials
when I was a kid.
It was a highly experimental drug.
It might enhance certain abilities
in predisposed children.
I've never met anyone
who can do the things that you do.
I'll go get my coat.
Please don't tell him.
You sure you don't want some soup?
Tea or coffee? To warm you up?
No, thank you.
I have trouble
keeping anything down.
Your office told me
how busy you are.
I really appreciate you coming.
I'm sorry.
I keep trying to remember you.
I understand.
It was a long time ago.
We were just kids.
So is that when you think
you were exposed to something?
I've seen about
a half dozen doctors,
specialists.
They think it's the only explanation
that makes sense.
Maybe I can help you.
Look, I'm grateful
you're doing this,
but that's not why I asked to see you.
- I wasn't looking to make money.
- Of course. I understand.
But if someone's responsible
for your illness,
- my firm can absolutely help...
- The last doctor I saw,
he suggested that
if I could find some of the other kids
we went to school with...
If some of them
have the same symptoms,
it might help him identify
what it is that's making me sick.
I'm sorry.
I really don't remember names.
It's so long ago.
You know what?
I do remember one boy.
Lloyd...
Lloyd Becker.
He made me eat a bug
on the playground.
I remember him.
Lloyd Becker?
Sounds like a budding sociopath.
Yeah, right?
I really appreciate
you helping me out.
Neil Wilson.
Could you make an appointment with that
oncologist over at Rhode Island General?
- The one who always calls me "honey."
- Was it Gorski?
- Gorlami...
- Dr. Gorlitsky?
That's right.
- I'll call him right now.
- All right, thanks.
I should be back in 20 minutes.
Bye.
Come on!
Hey, what's going on in there?
Miss.
You okay?
Help me.
_.•´¯¯LIAISON¯¯`•. _
¯`•. __Team__.•´¯
Retrouvez-nous chaque semaine...
pour découvrir les énigmes de
Saison 2 Épisode 17
-Olivia. In The Lab. With The Revolver.-
Bon épisode...
Hello?
Is that you, Dunham?
I thought you'd quit bowling,
took up another sport.
It's been a while.
I see you're still not sleeping.
Not so much. No.
Can you pass me a nut?
Yeah, sure.
Which one?
Dealer's choice.
Perfect.
What's on your mind?
Well...
After my car accident,
you said that...
I would experience things.
I have.
You want a beer?
It's 6:30 in the morning.
When you've been up all night,
time is just a matter of semantics.
Thanks.
So I suppose you're here
to find out what happens next.
Suppose I am.
I can't tell ya.
You have officially gone
beyond my field of expertise.
But I believe I can tell you
why you're not sleeping.
And it has nothing to do
with your accident.
You're a cop.
You must make a dozen decisions a day,
many of them life and death.
One of them you're not happy about.
You think you did the wrong thing.
I'm right, aren't I?
But it wasn't the job.
Not exactly.
I agreed to keep a secret.
A secret.
I'm on my way.
It's a good thing
you didn't take the beer.
I'll see you later.
You're a good person.
One of the few I know.
If you agreed to keep this secret,
I'm sure you had a good reason.
Killington?
As in skiing?
They just had a fresh snowfall.
I had no idea you were a skier.
Oh, yes.
I was quite a hotdogger.
I remember
there was this secret trail.
They called it "the backside,"
but not for the reason
you would think.
It was a nude ski run.
By the time you got down to the bottom,
your testicles would be in your mouth.
I'm sure Agent Dunham
is very thankful for that image.
Walter's advocating
a father-son trip.
And I'm sure Agent Dunham
is not interested in that.
I understand that Agent Broyles
has a body for us to look at.
Her name is Miranda Greene.
30 years old, unmarried.
She was an attorney.
Lived here in providence.
EMTs responded to a 911 call
phoned in by a good samaritan.
She was dead
by the time they arrived.
Doctor.
This is Agent Olivia Dunham.
- This is Peter Bishop and Dr...
- Walter Bishop.
John Potash. I took your advanced
biochem seminar, Dr. Bishop.
I apologize.
I remember I was
a bit of a slave driver.
You were.
But also inspiring.
The truth is
I was considering changing majors,
but you encouraged me to stick
with it and become a doctor.
I never thought I'd get
a chance to thank you.
Your father is a great man.
Doctor,
which one is Miranda Greene?
Right this way.
I'm sorry.
This might be a bit unpleasant.
Epidermal blistering.
Tissue necrosis.
Symptomatic of cytotoxins.
Could you get a sample
of this pus please, Peter?
I always get the good jobs.
According to her coworkers,
when she left for lunch,
she was perfectly fine.
Any signs of illness.
That was about two hours
before the 911 call.
I was considering
that these are contact burns
from some sort
of synthetic chemical.
No, these aren't chemical burns.
They look more like
malignant tumors.
Cancer?
Sarcomas, to be exact.
But that kind of cancer
presents beneath the skin,
not on the surface.
Normally, yes.
- Do you have a black light?
- Yeah. Somewhere.
- What is it, Walter?
- I'm not sure.
Cancers always start
with a specific point of origin,
and they spread from there, so...
Here you go.
Agent Broyles, lights, please.
The cells near the point
of origin of the cancer
should show more progression,
and hence refract a different color.
Like that.
- It looks like...
- Fingers.
Indeed.
Right hand, I'd say.
Which indicates
not only what killed this woman,
but also who.
Of course, somehow
we'll need to retrieve a print.
What you're suggesting
is impossible...
That someone touched this woman
and gave her cancer?
It seems you've forgotten
my very first lesson, Doctor.
When you open your mind
to the impossible,
sometimes you find the truth.
28 degrees fahrenheit,
and they're predicting snow
next week.
Hardly ideal beach weather.
Why are you going to Atlantic City?
I was thinking
of taking Peter there.
Used to love
saltwater taffy as a child.
So what are we looking for?
Why are we cutting off
this poor woman's arm?
The handprint shows
an extraordinary level
of cellular detail.
I'm hoping...
Hoping to be able
to remove the tumor, and...
bake the skin, and...
Hopefully identify a fingerprint.
And I'll need
two hot baths and an oven.
You really think someone may have
touched her and given her cancer?
Terrifying possibility,
but a possibility nonetheless.
We need glycerin,
corn starch and food coloring.
Food coloring?
Not for her, but since we're baking,
we may as well make some taffy.
I've worked with Miranda
for about seven years.
She was fairly private,
but if she was sick,
I think someone would know.
So what sort of cases did Miranda
usually work on, Mr. Messing?
Mostly toxic tort litigation.
Class action stuff.
Asbestos, lead poisoning.
She had a real thing about protecting
those who couldn't protect themselves.
And is this what she was working on?
She was prepping a case
against Intrepus Pharmaceuticals.
Trial was supposed
to start next week.
How much money
was at stake in the trial?
North eight figures.
Wait, are you suggesting
that someone did this to her?
I thought she contracted
some kind of crazy disease.
we're not sure,
but we like to be thorough.
Can we take her files
on the Intrepus case?
Of course. Yeah.
Miss Greene had meetings
scheduled for yesterday.
Do you recognize those names?
First two are deposition prep.
I don't recognize the third one.
Neil Wilson.
She was supposed to meet him
about an hour before she died.
Do you really think that Intrepus
Pharmaceutical killed this woman?
Maybe. You don't?
I've never heard of a drug that can cause
what happened to Miranda Greene.
It seems like an awful lot of trouble
to go through to kill somebody.
Why not just hire a hit man?
A hitman would draw
too much attention.
Really?
And spontaneous
fatal tumor-growth wouldn't?
I suppose you have a point.
You want to come on inside, we can
noodle on it? Maybe order a pizza?
Thanks, but, no.
I didn't get much sleep last night,
so I should probably head home.
Anyway, I'm not
really hungry, but...
- All right.
- Thank you.
Agent Dunham.
You're up early.
I ran Neil Wilson's number.
It's a disposable cell phone,
and it was deactivated yesterday.
It's a pretty common name.
I checked, and there's more than
50 Neil Wilsons in the tri-state area.
Do you want me to start
running them down?
I'm pretty sure he gave her
a fake name anyway, so...
Could you give
Walter and I a minute?
Sure.
Don't mix up the spoons.
Help me stir.
Walter, I have to tell him.
I got to tell Peter the truth.
- But that's not what we discussed.
- I know, and I'm sorry.
But he deserves to know the truth
about who he is.
No, you don't understand.
Things have never been
better between us.
I can't lose him again. I can't.
You won't.
Once he knows the whole story.
You saved his life.
I'm sure that he will understand.
No, he won't.
He will never forgive me.
I have to tell him.
If it was the other way around,
I would want him to tell me.
I'm begging you.
Not yet. Please.
Give me time to prepare.
Please.
Hey.
I didn't realize you were coming.
I would have got you one too.
Cappuccino.
Two squirts of peppermint.
And, Astrid,
tall, nonfat, double macchiato.
Just the way you like it.
Miranda Greene used her credit card
at a Downtown Providence cafe
about a half hour before she died.
Sounds like her meeting
with Neil Wilson.
Excellent. I'm up for a road trip.
How about you?
I remember her. Pretty lady.
Comes in here all the time.
- She's a lawyer, right?
- Yeah.
Do you remember if she was with anyone
the last time that she was here?
Some guy.
She was taking all sorts of notes.
What, does she sue doctors
or something?
- Excuse me?
- Well, the guy she was with,
he looked real pale and skinny.
Dark circles under his eyes.
- You think he was sick?
- I'd say pretty bad.
Looked my uncle did
when he was fighting cancer.
You thinking what I'm thinking?
Well, I'm thinking that
cancer isn't contagious.
It wouldn't be
the strangest thing we've seen.
But it would be close.
Getting ready for a triathlon?
Just trying to stay healthy.
You okay, sir?
Yeah, I just...
You need me to call for some help?
No, I'm fine.
Yes, I'm an old friend of Mr. Becker's.
We went to school together.
I must have the wrong Lloyd Becker.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Miranda Greene had lunch
with someone just before she died
with a man that may have had cancer.
Does that suggest anything to you?
Cancer isn't contagious, of course.
That's what I said.
Although...
Are you familiar with the chinese
notion of Ch'i, Agent Dunham?
No.
Dim Mak.
The Touch of Death.
Exactly.
The Chinese believe that
all living creatures
contain an energy, our Ch'i,
and, that with proper training,
a simple touch
can affect their Ch'i.
Reverse it.
Can cause sickness, even death.
Except, of course, they can't.
'cause the touch of death
is just a legend.
Of course, what would be
more interesting
wouldn't be a transfer of energy,
but an exchange.
Meaning what?
This other man,
you say that he was sick too,
that he had cancer as well?
Possibly.
And at the time she met him,
miss Greene was perfectly healthy.
Then I suggest
what we're looking at here
adheres more closely to tantric sex.
- Sex?
- Yes.
Insofar as the goal of tantric sex
is a heightened state of perception,
of awareness.
The partners are not interested
merely in the sexual experience.
They are seeking
an exchange of energy.
Okay, so what does this
have to do with Miranda Greene?
His cancer...
For her health.
It's possible that the man that
miss Greene met, did this to her
as a way to delay
the progression of his own disease.
Hi.
Lloyd Becker.
Oh, yeah, right.
You're Alex.
Alex Taylor. Thanks for seeing me.
Of course.
Yeah. How you doing?
- Come on in.
- Thanks.
Victim's name is Lloyd Becker. 30.
A neighbor saw his door open.
She came in and discovered his body.
There's no sign of forced entry.
No sign of a struggle.
Clusters of
malignant sarcomas.
Just like miss Greene.
Did anyone see the suspect?
Police canvassed the building
and the neighborhood. No luck.
The malignancies appear
to originate in this hand
and then appear to spread out.
Maybe from a handshake.
That's a fine deduction, Peter.
What do you see?
Nothing.
Nothing that tells me
why Lloyd Becker
was chosen as a victim.
There must be a connection.
Where's Walter?
The ME's gonna transport
the body back to the lab.
He told Walter he could ride along.
- What?
- It's nothing.
I think I know what it is
that's bothering you,
why it is you've been
so awkward around me
for the last couple weeks.
That trip down
to Jacksonville was crazy.
We were both exhausted.
We were both emotional.
And, you know, if something
had happened between the two of us,
if we had actually kissed, then we'd
have to deal with that, but we didn't.
No. No, we didn't.
Right.
This past year, this is the longest
I've ever stayed in one place.
So this thing that we have,
you, me, Walter,
this... This...
Our little family unit
that we've got going...
I don't want to do anything
to jeopardize that.
I don't either.
Okay, so we're good then, right?
Yeah.
Good.
I found more victims.
Five deaths over the past 20 months,
from Chicago to Hartford.
Each person died from the same
kind of rapid onset cancer.
And healthy people keeling over like
this didn't set off any alarm bells?
A couple were considered
medical anomalies,
and local police looked into another,
but nothing suggested it was murder.
So what is it about these people
that's making them targets?
Astrid, we need to
cross-reference their files,
see if we can find
what they may have in common.
All right. I'm on it.
Timothy Ober.
Is his middle name Michael?
Yeah. Timothy Michael Ober.
Why? You know him?
How?
I don't know.
What's up, buttercup?
It's past midnight.
Do you feel like playing a game?
Clue?
Yeah.
I thought it might be up your alley.
Colonel Mustard with the revolver
in the billiard room.
See, that's the third time
that you've guessed the billiard room.
I've always wanted a billiard room.
I thought that you would
make a better detective.
I detected that you needed company.
You've lived here a while,
but you're still
living out of boxes.
Maybe you moved around
a lot as a kid.
A tumultuous childhood.
A hard time forming relationships.
I may not be the gumshoe you are,
but I've got some skills.
Well, you're right
about moving around a lot.
- I was a military brat.
- That would explain the uniform.
- The uniform?
- Yeah, bland clothes.
I don't think I've ever seen you
in a primary color.
It's because it's more
than a job to you.
You're a soldier.
Protector.
God, you'd be a blast
at dinner parties.
- I don't get invited to many.
- No.
So what about you?
What made you the way you are?
I don't know.
I'm older than I look.
I barely remember my childhood.
I'm also taller than I appear.
That's it.
What?
What did I say?
- Hey.
When we were in Jacksonville,
there was a height chart
on the wall with names.
First name and last initial.
All the kids that I was in daycare with.
Yeah, all the kids from Walter
and Bell's cortexiphan trials.
So while I was there,
I wrote down all their names
and I made a list.
"Timothy O." Timothy Ober.
He was there.
We were both part of Walter's tests.
So that's where
you remembered him from.
Keep looking.
- Miranda G. and Lloyd B.
- Julie H. Alan D.
They're all there.
All five of his victims.
So what does that mean?
Why is this guy...
Killing cortexiphan kids?
I don't know.
I think we should wake up Walter.
That won't be necessary.
Agent Dunham.
Peter.
Is it morning already?
Oh, no. No, no.
It's still the middle of the night.
Walter, what is that smell?
It's taffy.
I'm making it for Peter.
I think she was probably referring
to your other project.
Is that the killer's handprint?
I think we're close
to getting a fingerprint.
The papillary ridges
on the forefingers
are quite clear now.
Once it's cooled a little, I should be
able to run it through the scanner.
Well, whoever the killer is, he's
started to target cortexiphan subjects.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Why?
Why would he do that?
Well, we were hoping
you may have some idea.
I don't know.
But I have an idea why
they might be susceptible.
To the cancer?
The energy exchange
that this man is creating,
I don't think
it would work on everyone.
Cortexiphan was designed to...
to allow children to access
untapped parts of their brain,
untapped energies.
So you're saying that whatever
he's doing to his victims,
like, exchanging his illness,
it could only work
on cortexiphan children.
Yes.
- I think so.
- So then I guess the question really is:
how does he know about
the cortexiphan trials?
And then how is he
tracking those people down?
Now, you've said that you and Bell
never kept a list of the children
- that you experimented on.
- I didn't.
And if belly did, I never saw it.
Okay, but what about Nina Sharp?
I mean, she started working
with bell around the same time.
We asked. Last year.
When Harris was tracking down
Nick Lane and Nancy Lewis, we asked her.
She doesn't have a list.
Yeah, but I believe that Nina Sharp
isn't always so forthcoming.
Why would someone be hunting
cortexiphan test subjects?
I don't know.
Walter thinks that they could be
particularly susceptible.
That's troubling.
Did William Bell
ever show you a list?
Of cortexiphan subjects?
No.
And there's nothing in
the massive dynamic archives?
As I've told you before,
there's nothing on record.
Do you doubt me, Agent Dunham?
I don't know.
I've always been a little
foggy as to your motives.
What are you implying?
Well, you've kept information
from me since I met you...
Information that has prevented me
from understanding the origin of many,
if not all of the cases
I've investigated
while working with Fringe division.
And I know about Peter.
I know the whole story.
Does Peter know?
Have you told him?
No.
But I'm going to.
No. You won't.
What makes you so sure about that?
Because you haven't told him yet.
And I'm guessing you've had
any number of opportunities.
Well, I've had my reasons
for waiting.
This is the right thing to do,
and Peter needs to know the truth.
Whether or not
it's the right thing to do,
I recognize the look in your eyes.
I know that working together closely
with someone can bring
about feelings.
I'm fairly certain that you're not
prepared to lose him.
You didn't come here today
to ask me about a list
that you already knew I don't have.
And you didn't come here to announce
that you're going to tell
Peter who he really is.
You came here...
to have me talk you out of it.
Mrs. Lane?
Yes.
I'm sorry to disturb you.
I... I tried calling.
My name is John McHugh.
I went to school
with your son, Nick.
No, Nick is my nephew.
You... You look awful.
Why don't you come inside?
Thank you.
The red wire goes in the red hole.
- The blue in...
- Yes, thank you, Walter.
I was able to figure that out
all by myself.
Hey.
How'd it go?
Nina didn't have anything.
- How's it going here?
- Well,...
- we'll soon see.
- Don't be so skeptical, Peter.
You liked the taffy, didn't you?
Absolutely.
- I have my doubts.
- Ready?
What's it doing?
Familiarizing itself with
the genetic composition.
Dismissing any foreign elements.
It's amazing how much filth
we carry around on our hands.
Go ahead, dear.
It worked.
Of course it did.
We need to run this through
the joint law enforcement database.
See if we can get
a name for this guy.
Well done, Walter.
Thank you, son.
Nothing.
He's not in our system.
No priors, no arrest record.
So...
we're nowhere.
You said you went
to school with Nick.
A long time ago,
back in Jacksonville.
We have a mutual friend,
Lloyd Becker.
- He said I could find Nick here.
- I remember Lloyd.
Such a sweet boy.
Nick lived here a while
after his parents died.
He moved to Brooklyn...
Several years ago.
Do you know how I could
get in contact with him?
- Do you have his phone number?
- I'm afraid not.
I haven't heard from him
for some time.
It's funny, though.
Someone else
from Jacksonville came by,
six months ago asking for Nick.
She must have gone
to school with you as well.
You don't by any chance
remember her name, do you?
God, what am I missing?
I think I may have found our killer.
His name is James Heath,
and he was
a cortexiphan subject too.
I think that may be
how he's doing this.
James Heath? Wasn't Heath
the last name of the first...
Yep, of the first victim...
Julie Heath.
She was his sister.
James was in the hospital.
She was visiting him, and she just
suddenly collapsed and died.
He was having chemo treatment.
He had cancer.
Do you have the name of the hospital
where Heath was treated?
It's Abington Memorial Hospital.
It's just outside Philadelphia.
Okay. I'll see if they have
a current address for him.
Thanks.
You're Olivia Dunham.
You probably don't remember me.
My name is Nate Reed.
Nick Lane gave me your address?
You and I went to school together
when we were kids.
Back in Jacksonville.
I see.
What can I do for you?
I was hoping you'd have
a few minutes to talk.
Sure.
Why don't you come in?
It's me. He's in my house!
You stay down.
I didn't want this.
I didn't want to hurt anyone.
Then why did you?
A man...
came to see me
when I was in the hospital.
He said when I was a kid
scientists had experimented on me,
that because
of the experiments, he could
teach me how to fight the cancer.
But it didn't work.
I didn't get better.
I got worse.
So what happened to your sister?
She stayed with me
while I was in the hospital.
She never left my side.
And when the pain got bad,
she'd hold my hand.
For hours.
And then,
one day,
it just happened.
I called the nurses for help, but...
it was too late.
I watched her die.
But you got better.
I had to find that man.
I thought someone
from Jacksonville might
know him.
And then I found Timothy.
And you killed him too.
Not on purpose. It just...
happened.
But...
that's when I realized
how it worked.
I think...
if that man had never...
come to see me,
I would have died
the way I was supposed to,
and my sister would still be alive.
They'd all still be alive.
In here.
It's okay.
How come you didn't call Broyles?
- I've got you on speed dial.
- Really?
I'm number one on
Olivia Dunham's speed dial?
Well, no,
but I didn't think that Rachel
or Mr. Iyer from the indian takeout
would be much use.
Thank you for coming.
You're welcome.
He's in a drug-induced coma,
which seems to have stopped
the progression of his cancer.
And the man who tried to activate him,
do we know who he was?
He sounds like the same man
who Sanford Harris hired
to activate Nancy Lewis
and Nick Lane.
I assume the activation failed,
and Mr. Heath's... ability
was just an unfortunate side effect.
So I don't imagine you called me
all the way down here just to
share in your victory.
Aside from Olivia Dunham,
there are still nearly a dozen
unaccounted for people
from the Jacksonville experiments, and
30 more from the drug trials in wooster.
If they all have capabilities
anything like the ones we've seen,
- and if someone were to find them...
- Well, Philip,
then we need to find them first.
Is Peter here?
No, he went out.
Good, because
I would like to talk to you.
Please. Please, Walter. Just...
Let me finish.
I think that you may be right.
I think that maybe some truths
can do more harm than good
and that some pandora's boxes
are better left unopened.
So...
I'm not gonna tell Peter.
Thank you, Olivia.
The truth is...
I've done enough damage,
and it's...
time to start...
to put things right...
whatever the consequences.
And that starts with
telling Peter the truth.
I have to tell him who he really is.