Previously on Fringe...
Surgeries that Newton performed.
He was removing
transplanted brain tissue.
You nearly died when you were a boy.
Walternate found a cure for Peter.
Peter is dead.
I'm talking about the other Peter.
The one on the other side.
I'm not from here, am I?
- Son...
- I am not your son.
Peter checked himself out
of the hospital three hours ago.
He's gone.
Drink that, avoid the radar,
you'll be in Oakland in no time.
That is for you, Raymond.
Your burger should be up in a minute.
So... Where was I?
You were in the middle of telling me
how you moved around a lot as a kid.
But I got to tell you, now
I'm hopelessly intrigued with these CDs.
I'm sort of known here by the regulars
for my playlists.
I base my tracks on people's aura.
How often do you think I'd have to
come here to be considered a regular?
I might be able to get you
on the list.
First, you have to tell me
where you're from.
Technically...
I'm from no place
you've ever heard of.
But let's just say Boston.
So how long are you here for?
I was just planning on the one night...
Passing through.
To?
I don't know yet.
Peter from Boston.
I'll burn you one.
Really?
- What did I do right?
- It's a long road to "I don't know yet."
I want to make sure
you stay awake out there.
And I like your eyes.
So there's that.
Where are you staying?
I'm staying
at the Drake's Bay Motel.
I'll drop it by after my shift.
Okay, I'll see you then.
I'll see you then.
What are you doing to me?
_.•´¯¯LIAISON¯¯`•. _
¯`•. __Team__.•´¯
Retrouvez-nous chaque semaine...
pour découvrir les énigmes de
Saison 2 Épisode 21
- Northwest Passage -
Bon épisode...
It may not be the best season for skagit
valley's famous waves of color,
but with record warmth,
it is still going to be one
for the record books.
In mount Vernon, John Hofferste,
Q13, Fox News.
Your room's got a bed, you know.
What time is it?
6:00 AM.
Did a pretty girl
happen to drop by here?
Hello?
Krista?
Destination.
- Please say a city name.
- Portland.
Portland. Please proceed
to the highlighted route.
That was obviously way too easy.
Destination.
Please say a city name.
Mars.
Sorry. Please say the city name.
How you doing?
I'm sheriff Mathis.
This is Deputy Ferguson.
Hi, there.
Peter Bishop.
Were you a customer here last night?
I was.
Do you remember your waitress?
Krista, sure.
- Why, did something happen to her?
- Do you have any identification on you?
Of course.
Krista told a coworker she was planning
to meet you after her shift last night.
You gonna tell me
what's going on here?
You first.
Yeah, we made plans.
But she never showed up.
She was gonna meet me at the Drake's Bay
but I just fell asleep in the lobby.
You can call the front desk,
ask the guy there.
Why don't you just
hang here a sec, okay?
Where are you goin'?
Who are you lookin' for?
No one.
Come on, you got to be kidding me.
Krista Manning went missing
last night.
And you talked to her.
You two spent some time.
I'd just like to hear about it.
I'd like to do that
at the station, okay?
Six feet, brown hair.
Officer, I wasn't staying
under the name Bishop.
I was registered
under the name Stewart.
He says he was staying
Right, okay. Thanks, Tom.
Tom over at Drake's Bay confirms that he
was passed out in the lobby all night.
Why did you check into the motel
under an assumed name, sir?
Sheriff?
- This is Mathis. Go ahead.
- Dogs have found a body...
The spillway off route 219
and mile marker 8.
White female, coroner's on his way.
Oh, my god.
Noyo search and rescue,
what's your 20?
ETA about 45.
Confirm this is recovery,
not rescue.
That's right, Wes.
It's a bad one.
The coroner says the victim had
some sort of operation done to her.
A piece of her skull cut out.
Over.
Sheriff, can you let me out
of the back of this car?
Please, I'm sorry,
But you're gonna have to be patient.
Hold on for one second.
I was listening to your radio.
They said that she had
a piece of her skull cut out.
Is she missing a part of her brain?
That that's a weird question,
but you need
to ask the coroner whether she's missing
a piece of her temporal lobe.
Please.
How the hell did you know that?
You're FBI?
What exactly is
a civilian consultant?
Sometimes people
with certain areas of expertise
can offer them to the bureau
on a consulting basis.
My area of expertise is...
weird.
- You mean difficult to explain?
- No, I mean
the strange, the inexplicable.
So...
Can you talk me through this again?
You knew that they took her...
- temporal lobe.
- Temporal lobe
because it's like a case
you worked on before?
Exactly. We were never able
to catch those responsible.
So that's why you're out here.
You're tracking them down?
No.
But I think that they
may be tracking me down.
- What'd they want with you?
- I'm not sure yet.
But I thought I saw one of them earlier
outside the crime scene.
His name is Newton.
And I think they called me
at the drake's bay motel.
There was no voice on the
other end of the line.
It was just static, and then
a series of strange noises and clicks.
I think they killed
Krista to find me.
By taking her brain?
I told her where I was staying.
- She's the only person who knew.
- Why wouldn't they just...
ask her where you were staying?
Or force her?
I mean, why cut out her brain?
It's possible that they needed details
about me she didn't know she had.
I'm sorry. I'm not following.
I know that this is complicated.
And I'm sorry that I can't give you all
the answers, but the case is classified.
It is possible, however,
that I could show you
what I mean.
Just give me a minute.
I'm gonna go make
a few calls, Peter.
Of course.
- Where are you?
- I'll save you the trace.
I'm in Washington State.
Look, I need a favor.
You're about to get a call from
the Noyo County Sheriff's Department.
- They're checking up on my credentials.
- Are you in trouble?
In fact, just the opposite.
I stumbled into an investigation,
and I offered them my services.
We'll ask them to extend
you every courtesy.
Thank you. Listen...
I don't want you to tell Walter
where I am.
In fact, I don't even want you
to tell him that we spoke.
If you owe me anything,
you owe me that.
But, Bishop... if you change your mind,
I'll send someone to pick you up.
Thanks.
- I got to go.
- Take care of yourself.
Krista seemed like a sweet girl.
Did you know her?
She and my sister went to
school together.
So explain this to me.
The temporal lobe is
responsible for memory.
So think of the brain as the greatest
recording device ever created.
Every sight, sound, smell,
all recorded in perfect detail.
But imagine that there was a way
to get that data out of the brain.
So what I said, what I was wearing,
What time it was,
where I was staying...
I know how it sounds.
But believe me,
if you can imagine it, it's possible.
If that's true,
if they were trying to find you,
why didn't they just come
for you last night?
I don't know.
These are not your
ordinary bad guys.
The tissue is very pink.
It's not normally like that.
It only happens when our
bodies metabolize adrenaline.
Her adrenal's must have
spiked right before she died.
My God.
"Find the crack"?
That is the worst police
slogan I've ever heard.
It's not a slogan.
In the darkness,
there's always a crack.
It's how the light gets in.
Ferguson gave it to me...
on our first case together.
Nobody else thought
I could hack it, but...
It's an inside joke.
It looks expensive.
Yeah.
That's what he keeps telling me.
If that's an accurate account
of your statement, please sign it.
It is, very.
I'm gonna get a room
at the Northwest Passage.
I'll be staying under the name of...
Gene Cowan.
- If you need me, that's where I'm at.
- You don't want a police escort?
No, I'll be fine.
You say that there are people out there
cutting people's brains out to find you,
- and you're smiling.
- Look, they may have found me.
But now that I know they're here
for sure, I found them too.
And now we're gonna catch 'em.
What?
- I don't know about this guy, Ann.
- He knew his way around there.
He's like a medical examiner.
He knew the brain,
biology, medications.
Doesn't mean he's legit.
You read your books about Ufos,
Roswell, whacked-out theories,
government conspiracies,
I think that you want to believe.
What makes you trust him?
I don't know.
I'm a good judge of character.
I'm the only one here who likes you.
Closed. What do you want?
If you open up,
I'll make it worth your while.
Mathis?
What do you want from me?
It's Mathis.
Who did you tell?
- What are you talking about?
- I just got one of those phone calls.
They know where I'm staying.
- And I only told you.
- I didn't...
Ask your partner!
That's what I'm calling about.
Ferguson's...
Ferguson's disappeared.
The last time you spoke with him?
About two hours.
He went back to the scene
where Kristawas found.
Felt we've missed something.
That means that he disappeared
30 min before I got the last phone call.
You think they used him to find you,
like they used Krista.
What is it that makes you special?
Why haven't they taken you?
I don't know.
I don't even know what it all means,
but I do know that these
people have the answers.
It's exactly why I must find them.
All right,
call your friends at the FBI.
- Let's get these guys!
- No.
The FBI has the expertise.
- They have the resources.
- If we call them,
they're gonna descend here,
and these people will disappear.
I am this close.
And I am going to get my answers.
You said you got calls at Drake's Bay
and Northwest Passage, right?
We pulled those phone records.
Those calls never happened.
These people can pull
memories out of brain tissue.
You think they can't make
calls disappear?
I can do that. People have been doing
that since the '70s.
I understand.
You don't want me to be right,
'cause if I'm right, that means
your partner is most likely dead.
With the exception of who you are,
I haven't been able to verify
anything you've said to me.
It's all either classified,
or it's incredible.
I'm calling the bureau.
Your partner did disappear.
And I did talk to Krista.
And I did get those phone calls.
What if he's alive?
What if he's out somewhere, thinking
I am doing everything in my power,
including calling the FBI,
to save him?
Then that is all the more reason
for us to find him ourselves.
If you make that phone call,
we never will.
Excuse me, please.
Thank you.
Toaster pastry.
"Corn starch,
"soy lecithin,
Potassium... Bromate."
Potassium bromate?
This supermarket
is trying to kill us!
You... Potassium bromate,
do you know what that is?
- Are you okay, sir?
- It is known
to induce renal cell tumors...
Mesotheliomas of the peritoneum!
- Can I call someone for you?
- Call someone?
You know what you're putting
into our bodies? Death!
Delicious,
strawberry-flavored death!
- Okay, I'm calling security.
- Yes!
They had no right to make me
wait at the police station.
It's the makers of those
toaster pastries
that should be in jail.
Let it go, Walter.
You're home now, and you're safe.
I wasn't expecting guests.
Why didn't you tell me
you needed help?
What am I going to do...
Call you every time
I run out of pudding pops?
- If you need them.
- I need
to learn to care for myself.
If Peter doesn't come back...
They'll send me back to
the hospital, won't they?
I won't let that happen.
Thank you.
I do...
I do need pudding pops.
We don't know if he made it,
but this is the last place
he said he was going.
Isn't it protocol for him to call in
once he gets here?
Well... Sometimes
he doesn't do that.
Dummy.
Bishop?
Bishop!
Mathis.
What did you see?
I saw Newton and one other guy.
You didn't see them too?
They came running right past you.
What's wrong?
What the hell are you doing?
Put down that gun.
Who are you?
Bishop... Lower... Your... Weapon.
In the morgue,
you dropped something.
Who gave it to you?
- What is wrong with you?
- Answer the question!
My pen?
It was a gift from Ferguson,
my partner.
Why is there blood on your jacket?
There is blood on my jacket
because there is blood on my wrist,
which I got when I fell, running.
Show me.
I'm sorry.
I needed to know
that your blood was still red.
What other color would it be?
So these shape-shifters, they...
make themselves look
like other people?
It's a technology
unlike anything you've seen before.
I want to level with you.
I...
believe in the unknown.
Yeah. "Find the crack".
I get it.
No, I mean...
I read books about...
Ufos and conspiracy theories.
But I do think...
I mean, I am wondering right now...
if you are not completely
off your rocker.
- They were there.
- I didn't see them...
or the dart they shot.
I know you didn't,
because they removed it.
I know how this must look...
from your point of view...
I mean, I was there once too. But...
You just did it.
- Did what?
- You just questioned your own sanity.
- I'm not questioning...
- When was the last time you slept?
I'm not hallucinating.
And I'm not paranoid.
And I'm not questioning my own sanity.
I was wondering why you
would listen to me.
You're desperate.
Ferguson is more than just
your partner, isn't he?
So there is something
between the two of you.
You said back at the
precinct that...
that I was trying to rationalize
that he was still alive.
You may be right.
I may be doing it right now.
He may be dead.
But I won't believe
it until I see his body.
I can't.
Mathis.
You want me to go look?
Sheriff. The victim's a white female.
She has part of her skull missing.
I don't recognize this girl.
- You never seen her before?
- No, I've never seen her before.
Who is she?
I talked to Gwynn right
before her shift ended.
We'd talked about her coming over
last night to help me color my hair.
I figured she just got tired.
I should have called her.
You couldn't have known.
I'm sorry.
Did your sister ever hang
out at the hilltop cafe?
I don't think so.
What about the Mosser brothers
gas station out on route 202?
I filled up there
on the way into town.
Her pickup's a diesel, and
I don't think Mosser's carries diesel.
Fine, what about the drake's bay motel?
Would she ever go there for any reason?
- What's this about?
- It's just...
Part of our investigation.
If you could just write down
your address for us.
She is grieving,
and you are not getting anywhere.
The hadron super collider
is less complicated
than that infernal dishwater.
Next time, don't use
laundry detergent,
- and the dishwasher will work fine.
- Thank you, Astrid.
You're a federal agent.
I doubt, during
your years of training,
that you had dreams of babysitting
a helpless old man.
You are not that helpless.
A little disorganized, maybe.
Don't you usually keep
this in the bathtub?
I took this little car
from the zelazney building.
Objects from the other
universe like this
emit a glimmer,
a distinctive energy signature.
It may be possible
to detect that signature.
So?
So I need you to gather
all the objects from the other side
that we recovered
from the Zelazney building
and from Jacksonville
and bring them to the lab.
- Okay, why?
- To build a device to read
that energy signature!
Peter emits the same energy,
don't you see?
This is how we will find Peter.
I must have seen Gwynn somewhere,
or she had to have seen me.
I mean...
She has to have had
some value to them,
some knowledge that they needed.
We'll go to your motel
and get your things,
get you something to eat, and...
You can stay at my house tonight.
It's okay. I'll be fine.
You're my only connection
to finding Bill right now.
I want you safe.
What color was Gwynn's truck?
Tan brown.
Driver's side window is rolled down.
Glove compartment's open.
Okay, so this girl
pulls over her truck,
rolls down the window,
and then opens up the glove box.
- You tell me... why would she do that?
- She got pulled over by a cop.
Or someone pretending
to be a cop... or Bill.
- Pretending to be Bill?
- These shape-shifters,
they take on the appearance
of people in positions of authority.
- Where you going?
- I'm calling the FBI.
Why?
First, you said they
cut out his brain to find you.
Now you're telling me he may
have been shape-shifted?
Which is it, Peter?
Did I make a mistake
not calling the FBI?
I am very scared right now.
Wait, wai... wait.
Just hold on for one second.
Those people, when they were taken,
they must have been afraid, right?
And when they were killed,
they must have been terrified.
- So?
- So I know how to find them.
Do you know how airplanes
have blackboxes?
To record flight data, sure.
Yeah, well, human bodies
collect data as well.
Both Krista and Gwynn's muscle tissue
was flooded with adrenaline.
Yeah, I remember.
Well, the tissue would've
partially metabolized the adrenaline.
So we should be able to measure
the rate of absorption,
which will tell us
when the adrenaline was first produced.
What about Newton?
- How does that help us find him?
- Look...
Normally,
your adrenaline levels are flat.
Then you experience fear.
A spike in adrenaline.
Sometime later,
you experience more fear,
say, in the moments right
before you were killed...
another spike, two points of fear.
We already know where the girls were
abducted. So if we can just determine
how much time took place
between these two intervals...
Then we can figure out
where they were killed.
Exactly right.
There is one more thing.
We're gonna need a control sample.
Can you stick that
in the centrifuge?
It's that thing right over there.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry.
I just needed to scare you.
I'm gonna need to take
a tissue sample from you.
How is Dr. Bishop doing?
Walter's trying to adjust
to a very difficult situation.
He's concerned about
being sent back to St. Claire's.
Will he be able to function
if Peter doesn't come back?
I'm sure that Peter will come back.
Do you know something?
Have you spoken to him?
Krista Manning's adrenaline
spikes were 42 minutes apart. So,
assuming that Newton drove
the speed limit, 60 miles an hour...
On these roads, that'd be a good way to
get killed. He would have stuck to 45.
All right, 45.
Okay, the center point
is where Krista was taken.
At 45 miles per hour,
The farthest they could have gone
would be 31 1/2 miles.
Gwynn, our second victim...
was taken much farther out of town,
almost on the other side of the county.
Her adrenaline spikes
are 57 minutes apart.
Again,
factoring 45 miles per hour...
That's it.
That's our kill zone.
You're assuming he killed them both
in the same place.
They were using complex equipment.
It's not easy to move an operating room.
Much simpler to just bring the victims
to a specified location...
Someplace out of the way.
Like an old dairy farm?
Just ask him something
only he would know.
Hello, there.
It's Craig, right?
I don't know if you remember, but,
I think you were in choir
with my sister up at St. Andrew's.
Actually, I was at Good Shepherd.
- Good memory, though.
- Good Shepherd, that's right.
- So what can I do for you?
- Your old dairy farm up the hill.
Could there be people up there?
- People?
- Yeah, you get up there often?
Not much, since we shut it down.
Why?
We got 12 outbuildings...
The milking parlors,
- the barn, and the holding stalls.
- Those are all good places to hide.
That's a lot of ground to cover.
I'll go call backup
to help with the search.
- Need any help with the search?
- I think it's best if you stay here.
- Let me get you the keys.
- Sure.
Who are you? Where's Newton?
Peter, stop!
I couldn't stop.
The girls...
I wanted to be close to them.
I just couldn't stop.
Where is he?
Where's Ferguson?
What did you do to him?
He's still breathing. Thank God.
It's just ink.
There's no incision here.
I'm gonna go call an ambulance.
Stay with me, baby.
I'm here.
I'm here now.
I'm here, Bill.
- I don't know what to say.
- You saved Bill's life,
and you tracked a killer.
What else is there to say?
I wish there was something
I could do for you.
Whatever your experiences are,
whatever you
can't or won't tell me about...
I think you're looking
for meaning in things that...
have no meaning.
I don't know who I am anymore.
When I was in college...
My family was killed, murdered.
I'm sorry.
Sometimes I still think...
one day I might catch
whoever did it.
I was alone for a long time.
But I found my place.
You will too.
Once we isolate the glimmer,
we can find Peter.
Is the spectrograph ready,
Agent Farnsworth?
- Walter, you put in the wrong numbers.
- No, no, I believe they're correct.
No, they're not.
But, then, you know
that already, don't you?
I thought you wanted to find Peter.
What if he won't forgive me, Astrid?
All I have now is hope...
Hope that he will come to understand
why I did the things I did.
What if I find him,
and he won't forgive me?
What do I have then?
I found Peter.
- Where?
- He's in Washington state.
I'm heading to the airport now.
Would you like
to come with me, Walter?
I'll need to pack a bag.
Mr. Secretary.
Hello, son.