Previously on fringe...
They're calling these
events "the pattern,"
As if someone out
there is experimenting.
Only the whole world is their lab.
Anybody you need, you can have.
His name's walter bishop.
You're saying i can talk to john?
You could access his memories.
You fall in love with your partner,
Who betrays you... he dies in your arms.
I saw him last night. Hello, liv.
I grabbed my gun, but he was gone.
When you were in the tank,
part of his consciousness
Crossed over into yours.
Hey.
Hey. Sorry.
I've been calling your cell.
The west side highway was a parking lot.
Did they start?
Charlotte's been tap dancing
for the last 20 minutes.
Wait, wait...the tie.
Oh. Thank you.
Don't forget this. Thanks.
Breathe.
And extenzalife's market has
remained remarkably stable.
Especially given wall street's
recent financial difficulties.
But let me turn things over
to the man you've come to hear.
Mark.
Sorry. I'm late.
Thank you for your patience.
It's quickly fading.
Right. So let's get started.
Okay, as you can see from figure six,
The three-Year rate of return
on extenzalife products...
Well, mr. Young, a rocky start.
But i'll be letting the board
know we're in good hands.
Thank you.
Bastard.
Son of a...
Lauren and craig will be here.
Remember craig? He's from south africa.
Yeah, i remember him.
Are you sure bobby's
gonna be okay with it?
You know, beth, not
everybody likes a surprise.
Oh, please, the man loves
being the center of attention.
Do you know how many times he told me
The he didn't want a
party for his birthday?
Anyway, i'm glad you're coming.
It's been ages since...
...had a chance to really talk.
Yeah, can you hold on one sec?
I've got another call.
Hello?
I need you to pick up the others
And get to marlboro airport.
Okay, i'm gonna tell you something.
You're gonna think i'm
joking, but i'm not.
I quit.
Only just for the next couple of days,
Ani'i'happy to rejoin the others
After the weekend.
Runway 14. The plane will be waiting.
So where are we going?
Multinational corporation.
Secret biological research.
Defense department's largest contractor.
Massive dynamic.
Seems like such an innocent name
For a corporation, don't you think?
Hmm. That's odd. What?
The lacerations on the body.
These, no doubt, were
caused by shards of glass.
But these under the shirt...
If they were caused by the glass,
How come the shirt's not torn?
A fall of such height
Would cause compound fractures,
Massive internal bleeding,
All in evidence in this poor chap,
I'm sorry to say.
But wounds this delicate
are most unlikely.
So what do you think caused 'em?
Too early to tell.
It's a shame i don't have a lab,
I'd like to examine him.
You do have a lab, walter.
Your lab at harvard.
Yes, i do, don't i?
Mark young was a capable executive
Who displayed no signs
of emotional dysfunction.
He was one of our more
promising analysts, in fact.
Popular among his co-Workers.
Then why do you think he
would jump to his death?
I don't want to sound
callous, agent dunham,
But when you run a company
of over 300,000 employees,
You sometimes see a small percentage
Who succumb to the stress
of their responsibilities...
And on occasion, the nature of our work.
What do you mean by that,
"The nature of our work"?
I was simply referring to the pressure
To deliver results,
Which the private
sector seems to require.
You would find it exhilarating.
Are you trying to change the subject
By offering me another job?
Well, i'd hate to sound like a suitor
Who is constantly being
turned down for a date.
Just to be clear, as flattered as i am,
I'm going to go wherever
this investigation takes me.
I would expect nothing less.
And i would expect more from you
Than the polite
appearance of cooperation.
You knew this man.
He was a rising star in your company.
There must be something mo
you can tell me about him.
When one's domain includes
the cutting edge of science,
There is a risk of exposure to...
Ideas that aren't easy to reconcile.
Certain realities.
I'm sure you know what i mean,
Doing the work that you do.
For some, it's too much to take.
Do you ever wonder how
we survived as a species
Without drugs?
The hard drive is password protected.
Once we break the encryption,
we'll send you his data.
Okay. Thank you.
Well, he wasn't planning
on killing himself
Three days ago.
He just booked a plane ticket. To where?
Omaha, on the 22nd of december.
Christmas in nebraska.
Sounds depressing.
Yeah, well, maybe he's got family there.
Did you find something?
No.
Seems my suspicions were correct.
These wounds go all the way down
To the bone itself.
As if they originated on the inside
And pierced their way up
through the body tissue.
How did that happen?
That is an excellent question.
Peter, do you know what
i've been remembering?
Aspects of your childhood.
That's charming, walter.
Blood samples are ready.
Anything in there that
explains those lacerations?
No, i don't believe so.
Typical medications.
All of them surprisingly legal.
So they wouldn't have harmed him?
That is correct.
Although they could have
been used as a carrier
To transfer the foreign
compound to the victim's brain.
What foreign compound?
Oh, didn't i mention? A
synthetic in the blood.
An ergoline derivative.
Perhaps he was treated for migraines.
But it does not explain
what caused these wounds.
Coffee yogurt.
The synthetic compound?
Peter.
When he was 13,
All he would eat was coffee yogurt.
Almost drove his mother to tears.
walter, that wasn't me. That was you.
Hello?
If that's agent dunham,
Tell her to bring some coffee yogurt.
Can you hold on for one second?
He's right. About the yogurt.
In case you haven't noticed,
i can be quite obsessive.
Really?
Hey, you still there?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
I just... i just didn't
realize what it would do,
You know, hearing your voice.
Listen...
No, listen, don't bother
making up a story, peter.
I know you're back.
I need to see you.
Peter?
I can't get away right now.
Well, then, when?
Hey, liv, what do you know
about a bunch of frogs?
I just got a p.O. Request
from agent farnsworth
Asking to send a terrarium
And ten pounds of live insect larvae,
And charge it off to
the mark young case.
There something you
want to talk to me about?
I had some frogs transferred
to the lab as evidence.
These frogs, you think
they had something to do
With why the guy jumped
out of the window?
Probably not.
Okay.
Charlie.
Yeah?
Come with me.
You know after john died,
You told me that i should
maybe take some time off?
You said that what happened with him
Was going to affect me in ways
That i couldn't even anticipate.
Yeah. Yeah.
You were right.
I feel like i'm going clinically insane.
Literally.
I told you i saw him
Standing right in front of me.
This happened again?
And he's called me.
And he sent me an email.
And at first i thought
it was him helping me,
Like when we were partners.
I know how it sounds.
Have you spoken to dr. Katz? Uh-Uh.
Even though it's confidential,
I'll still have a psych eval ony record.
I know, it seems so
selfish to even say it,
But i... i was thinking maybe
I could just take a personal leave.
Just do nothing for a week or two
And maybe clear my head.
Think that'll help?
I don't know.
Dunham.
Agent dunham, it's me.
Dr. Bishop wants you back immediately.
He thinks you've cracked the case.
What?
You are not gonna believe this,
But, um, the guy who
jumped out the window?
Dr. Bishop thinks it's
because of the frogs.
Oh, thanks.
Hi. Hi.
I wasn't sure you'd be here.
That makes two of us.
You look good, tess.
You look older.
Older?
When my father first saw me,
He told me he thought i'd be fatter.
But i gotta tell you,
older actually kinda hurts.
Your father... since when
do you see your father?
Long story.
Wait, listen to me.
If i can find you,
then they can find you.
I know.
They'll hurt you.
Can i get you a cup of coffee?
Something to eat, maybe?
Nothing changes with you, huh?
It's the same old peter.
You just play it fast and loose
Until it's too late. Tess...
It was easy enough for you
to leave the first time.
Why should it be any
different now, right?
I know that you believe that, tessa.
But you have to trust me,
it was harder than you think.
Trust you?
I'm not sure i ever even knew you.
Yeah, you did.
Maybe better than anyone.
You still do.
What does that say about you?
I'm not kidding.
You need to leave boston
and never come back ever.
Is that what you want me to do?
How can you ask me that? Come on.
Tessa, look, it's comp...
Michael. Things have changed.
Yeah, apparently.
It'll be worse for you if you stay.
Psychophysiologic effect,
Otherwise known as psychosomatic.
The ability of the mind to cause actual
Physical changes in the body.
Mind over matter, like
when you get scared
And yoget goosebumps. Precisely.
Although it is possible
for the body to manifest
Physical changes imagined in the brain
In a far more dramatic fashion,
This test subject is in a
highly suggestible state,
As you can see in this archive footage.
A form of hypnosis.
I convinced him that
he was in a meat locker.
And what is more impressive,
I told him that this ice cube
Was a burning coal.
Oh, my god.
Cruel, i suppose,
But very enlightening.
So, walter,
What does this have to do with frogs?
Uh, toads, actually... bufo alvarius.
A species which secretes
a psychoactive compound.
The substance which i couldn't identify
In mr. Young
Was in fact a concentration
Of the venom produced in the skin.
Properly altered, it's an hallucinogen.
A very powerful one.
Quite unlike anything i have taken.
It directly affects the amygdala,
Which is the fear center of the brain.
So you're saying that
mark young hallucinated
Being cut on his body,
And then his mind made
it actually happen.
Yes.
A very clever means of murder.
What do you mean "murder"?
Oh, come on, we've discussed this.
I'm sure we have discussed this.
No, no, you and i did
Before olivia got here.
The potency of the dose that i found
In mr. Young'slolo
Was at least 30 times that
That any sane person would ingest.
Which suggests that someone
else gave him the drugs.
So whoever those frogs belong to
May be the killer.
I already ran a property record search
On the shed where you found the toads,
But nothing came up.
How'd you even find
it in the first place?
It's a long story.
Walter. Walter.
The shed where i found the frogs,
John scott led me to it.
You've been seeing him again...
Because his memories
are still in your head.
His memories?
Yes.
Trapped like fragments...
Snapshots in your mind.
Your work on this case must be a trigger
To some knowledge he had.
So how long?
I mean, how long is this
gonna keep happening?
Could last for many years.
I need to get it out.
I can't keep having john's life
Flash in front of my
eyes every few days.
There must be something you can do.
Perhaps...
Using a form of
repressed memory therapy,
We may be able to bring the memories
To the surface,
And purge them from your unconscious.
But...
Bubuyou'd have to put
me back in the tank.
Yes. Yes.
And i would always advise against that.
The risk of physical,
Not to mention mental
damage, it might cause
Could be catastrophic.
Walter, i'll do it.
I need to do it.
Yeah?
Peter, it's agent farnsworth.
Um, where are you?
Putting some gas in
the car. Why, what's up?
I think you should just come back.
Ugh, walter!
How long is going to take?
Miss dunham, what we're doing,
What you have asked me to do,
Is pushing the boundaries
of all that is real
And possible.
We're not roasting a turkey.
The library was not open.
I had to go to the book store.
What for?
When you're in the tank,
you must listen to my voice
At all times.
Uh... uh, this is a technique
i developed decades ago
In this very lab.
Most of which i don't remember.
Is pet c cing? Yes.
Is that a bible?
Yes.
Last time you were in the
sensory deprivation tank,
You went into a state
of shared consciousness
With agent scott.
During that time, part of his memories
Crossed over into your brain.
By putting you into a
state of deep hypnosis,
And by giving you substantial doses
Of psychoactive drugs,
I can help you to access
those alien memories
At your mind has repressed.
My voice is your guide.
It is also your tether to reality.
You must focus on my voice,
Or you may risk being
lost in the memories.
What?
I just got an erection.
Oh, fear not.
It's nothing to do with
your state of undress.
I think i simply need to urinate.
That's good to know.
Will you get her in the tank, please?
Are you sure
About doing this again?
All i want is for it to stop.
But if his memories can do some good,
Then at least i wasn't
deceived for nothing.
You'll begin to feel sleepy.
You must listen to
my voice at all times.
Concentrate on the name of the man
From whom you seek information.
And look for signs.
Signs?
I'll tell you when you get there.
Walter,
What was the bible for?
Well, you're taking
untested psychedelics,
Lying in saline with an electric charge
In the base of your cranium.
Among other things, i
thought it appropriate
To pray you don't get electrocuted.
Praise the lord.
Amen.
Next!
"Then i will sprinkle
clean water upon you."
"And ye shall be clean.
"And of all thy filthiness,
"And all thy idols,
"I will cleanse thee and a new spirit
"I will give to thee.
And a new spirit i
will put within thee."
Wow, nice.
I didn't know you were so religious.
I'm not. Not anymore.
Olivia, can you hear me?
Yes.
Good.
You see the end of
the escalator, olivia?
You will step off in five,
Four, three, two, one.
Take a moment.
Look around.
What do you see?
I see nothing.
Just light.
Olivia, listen carefully.
Apart from my voice,
What else do you hear?
Music.
Excellent.
Where's it coming from?
You should be able to see something.
There's nothing.
I don't know where i am.
stand by.
She needs a passage way.
Anything now?
What do you see?
Nothing.
Wait.
There's a door.
Good.
Walk through it.
Tell me where you end up.
I'm in a restaurant.
Does it look familiar?
Sort of.
But i don't know why.
This is where we had our first date.
And there we are.
This is our first date.
Can... can you see yourself and john?
What's going on?
She's gone back in.
What?
Olivia went back in the tank? Why?
Son, i need your help.
Walter, you said that
this was dangerous.
Oh, it is. Very.
She thinks john scott
Had information about the
man who killed himself.
So what?
She went back in the tank
to go talk to john scott?
To see his memories.
Look at him.
He looks so alive.
So real.
I need you to adjust the drugs.
Well, what did you give her this time?
Drugs i'd rather be taking myself.
Set the iv to ten drips per.
Peter, please.
I'm getting up.
What should i do?
Fear not. This is just a memory.
Um, just visiting.
They cannot see you.
He's alone.
John.
He cannot hear you or speak with you.
You're in a memory.
He cannot interact with you.
Olivia, i'm going to take you elsewhere.
I loved you.
Tonight, during dinner,
But you were lying to
me about who you were.
I mean, did you ever have
any feelings for me at all,
Or was it all just...
Mark young killed himself yesterday.
He sees me.
No, olivia.
He definitely does not see you.
I'm somewhere else.
I'm in john's car.
Good.
Do you see any clues?
I'm alone.
He must be there.
Find out where you are.
There's no one here.
It's his memory.
He must be there somewhere.
I see them.
Who?
Ask her what she sees.
Wh... what do you see?
There's four men.
There's john, a black guy,
One who looks latino,
And the fourth i can't see.
I don't know who they are.
Let's give him a minute.
This is a big decision
he's about to make.
All right, i'm good.
Oh, my god.
It's mark young.
I see him. He's here.
Can you hear him?
I'll get closer.
Young's leaving with the latino.
I'm going after them.
Now you just do your part
And we'll take care of you.
What did i tell you?
I don't mess around.
They've disappeared.
That's because you're
not in their memories.
You're in john's.
You must go back to him.
You know if it's on time?
It will be.
He'll deliver.
He's just a little nervous.
See the look he gave
me when you told him
How much you'd be willing to offer?
I hope you're right.
If we get into another ashby situation,
We're screwed.
No! Stop!
Get me outta here!
Walter!
So just a little less chin.
Okay.
How'this?
That's it.
That's the latino guy
I saw in john's memory.
He's the only one of
the four still alive.
We need to figure out
who he is and find him.
So can we get this to charlie,
And maybe we can get it id'd?
Got it.
Hey.
You're on my clothes.
Oh, sorry.
That's okay.
You okay?
Yeah.
John's memories gave us a lead.
So i better get a move on.
I need to see broyles.
You want some company?
No.
Thanks.
Olivia, if you need me, i'm here.
Yeah, i know.
We believe mark young was murdered
For selling technologies
to black market buyers.
And we believe at t ts man
Was part of an underground group
Responsible for brokering a sale
Of a synthetic hallucinogen manufactured
By massive dynamics' drug division.
And what would be the
black market applications
Of this hallucinogen?
The drug could easily be mass produced
As a cheap street drug or worse.
In its potent form,
Used as a chemical weapon.
Apparently it can literally
scare you to death.
Then don't let me slow you down.
Sounds like you're doing fine.
There's just one more thing.
We're gonna need massive dynamic
To disclose every
project that mark young
Was working on.
You're right.
Although that'll be
easier said than done.
I'll see what i can do.
If you touch her again, i'll kill you.
Any luck?
We've been running facial
recognition software.
So far no matches.
Witness sightings?
Nypd's passing the composite around
Young's apartment building
and office as we speak.
Oh, yeah, i need you to cross reference
All of john scott's case
files with mark young.
Yeah.
Hold on.
From nina sharp.
Mark young's projects.
Yeah, can you call me
back if you find something?
Thank you.
Hello?
Hello, i'm calling on behalf
Of your long distance carrier.
I'm not interested.
And i don't want you calling again.
So you better take me
off your list, okay?
'Cause i don't mess around.
What did i tell you?
I don't mess around.
I need this phone traced.
This is our guy.
How do you know?
I recognize his voice.
You recognize his voice?
It's him, charlie. I swear.
Come on.
Almost there.
Got it.
It's a land line, but it
was forwarded to a cell.
Where?
He's in transit on route 3
heading to lincoln tunnel.
How far out are we?
About a mile and closing.
We got 'em.
Name on the account is george morales.
Age 43.
Purchased a plane ticket this morning.
3:45 flight down to
sao paolo out of jfk.
So he must be on his way there now.
According to ncic,
He's a black market
trafficker, high end.
So how far out are we?
550 yards.
Echo flank left foxtrot.
Flank right.
Wait, he stopped.
What, did we lose the signal?
No, he just stopped.
So do you think he ditched his phone?
I don't know why he would.
There's no way he could've spotted us.
So what happened?
Looks like he hit traffic.
Where's the transponder?
Let's go.
Charlie!
I'm told you wanted to see me.
Yes.
I want to make a deal.
I'll tell you everything i know.
I'm not sure what you have to trade.
Under title 18 of the u.S. Code,
We have you for possession
of chemical weapons.
On top of suspicion
Of murder of mark young.
I want protection. You mean immunity.
No, i mean protection.
From massive dynamic.
You ed to move me from here right now.
What are you talking about?
I didn't kill anybody.
Why would i?
That guy was a treasure
trove of unbelievable things.
Massive dynamic killed him.
Massive dynamic killed mark young?
That's right.
Why would they?
Maybe as a warning to any employee
Who's thinking of doing the same thing.
Maybe?
I think it's easy to invent a story
That you think i want to hear.
Really?
Did i invent zfd?
Flight 627?
The northwoods group?
John scott? The pattern?
The whole thing is... is a hoax.
It's all a smoke screen
So massive dynamic can
do whatever it wants
To whoever it wants.
Do you understand that?
Massive dynamic is hell.
And its founder, william
bell, is the devil.
And i can prove all of it.
But only if i get protection.
So why me?
Why do i get the privilege
of your cooperation?
Because i know i can trust you.
You don't even know me.
John scott told me about you.
Immunity...
And complete protection.
And i will tell you everything i know.
Agent dunham, i don't recall seeing you
On my schedule today.
Well, i don't need an
appointment, ms. Sharp.
It's all right.
No matter where my
investigations take me,
They always come back here.
Well, i don't know what you've heard
Since we last saw each other,
But i would hope that my cooperation
Would've garnered some
benefit of the doubt.
Massive dynamic has nothing to hide.
It's about time.
What took you so long?
See, i believe that your
cooperation is an illusion.
It never leads to something tangible.
It only leads to more questions.
And that's the point, isn't it?
To keep us all asking questions?
All just chasing our own tails?
Are you sure you're
feeling well, ms. Dunham?
I think perhaps you're perceiving things
That are entirely in your mind's eye.
I wanted to thank you
for all your job offers.
And i'm sorry that it's taken me so long
To give you an answer,
But i, um, i think i finally have one.
Yes, it's obvious in your expression.
Well, i understand that
you've captured your suspect.
I imagine that in an effort
To seek anmmmmity
agreement from your agency,
He's attempting to blame massive dynamic
For all his foul deeds.
Are you protecting
your ceo, william bell?
Because if you are,
Now is the time to tell me.
Once our witness talks,
You lose all leverage in a plea.
I seriously doubt that
your witness will be able
To provide any actionable evidence
To implicate massive
dynamic or william bell
Of any wrong doing.
Oof!
No, please!
No, john, please!
Don't...
I won't say anything.
No!
Dunham.
Our witness is dead.
What?
seems he was drugged
With the same substance as mark young.
How?
We had guards on his room.
We don't know yet,
But a nurse saw his throat open up
Right before her eyes.
Nina sharp.
Excuse me?
She got to him.
And there'll be no evidence of that.
Just like you said.
Dunham, nina sharp and massive dynamic
Have been nothing but cooperative
With this investigation.
I suggest you keep your
unfounded accusations in check.
Walter.
Hi.
Can you come out?
Um, i need to go back in.
In our room?
Uh, no.
In the tank.
There are too many questions.
Like who's working for whom?
And why?
Who should be arrested?
Who's plotting what?
And if john had the answers,
Then the answers are
still in his memory,
Which means that they're in my memory.
Ms. Dunham... please, walter.
We're wasting time.
It's dangerous.
I am prepared to take that risk.
There is little that makes me happier
Than taking drugs.
Perhaps administering them,
Designing and carrying out experiments
That bend the plane of
what we consider reality.
I'm rarely if ever opposed
to such things except now.
But i tell you,
You'll damage yourself.
Every time you go back in,
The risk of permanent damage:
Seizures, aneurysms,
memory loss, death...
But if i don't go back
in, others may die.
And if you do, the
death could be your own.
There are no guarantees
that you will retrieve
The memories you're looking for.
And remember, there can
be no interaction with him.
You can't just ask.
He did see me.
No.
No, that is not possible.
Give me some time.
I will try to develop a safer technique.
But not tonight.
You need to rest.
Sleep well.
You too.
Tell him to have the money
Or i'll have to break his legs too.
I gotta go.
What the hell happened to you?
He's back in town.
Peter bishop.
Peter bishop, really?
Transcript : yyets.net