Almost there, boys.
Just five more to go.
- Minutes?
- Miles, Jerry.
Hold up. Come here. Come on.
This here's your lucky day.
- You know what we got here?
- Yeah.
- A seriously mammoth pile of--
- Bear scat. Fresh.
Any brave soul wanna investigate
this particular bear's diet?
Sure.
My old man always said
l was full of this stuff anyway.
Now, bears are omnivores.
They'll basically eat anything.
lt's not unusual
to find digested berries, deer sinew,
even bones
in a single scat specimen.
So, Jerry, tell us.
What's this one been eating?
l think maybe people.
Trust me. You gotta see this.
- l'd rather shower.
- Every newbie's worst nightmare.
This liver shows signs
of advanced cirrhosis.
lt's clearly consistent with
the jaundiced skin we noticed earlier.
Now, if you'll come closer,
you'll be able to see
the inflammation of the pancreas.
Oh, hello.
Scalpel, please, Mr. Palmer.
Every cadaver
has its own story to tell.
ln many cases,
it's just a whisper that reveals--
All new agents are required
to observe an autopsy.
You should have seen McGee.
Hurled.
Emptied the contents of his stomach
onto Ducky's shoes.
lt's not only visual cues we look for.
Odours can be helpful too.
Note the putrid smell.
l think he's talking about you, Tony.
There's no need to be shy.
Odours like sticks and stones--
We had the same test at Mossad.
lf you fail, they terminate you.
How do you fail an autopsy?
By doing that.
- What happens if you fail here?
- lt depends, Officer David.
Some of them go on
to become our director.
You're gonna have to reschedule
your class, Duck.
The rangers found a body
in Shenandoah Park.
Well, perhaps you'd be willing
to share the specifics with the class.
Yes, the three most frequent causes
of death in our national parks
are heart attacks, hiking accidents and
prolonged exposure to the elements.
Not this time.
A sailor was eaten...
...by a bear.
Yet another reason
why l never wanna go camping.
Actually, Tony,
bear attacks are quite rare.
- Really?
- Do you wanna tell this guy that?
- Not a big fan of nature, huh?
- l'm a big fan of nature
as long as it's on TV.
l'd say 325 pounds.
Maybe 6 foot, standing, Agent Gibbs.
You found the dog tags here,
Ranger Hendricks?
On the other side
of the clearing.
l followed the tracks back
and found--
Found what was left of his body.
Well, name matches the dog tags
recovered by the park rangers.
Petty Officer Benjamin Riley.
Bag it. Probie,
you were a Boy Scout
or whatever, right?
Yeah. Well, technically,
l was a Webelos, but--
Whatever. Use your expertise,
and go and bag and tag
that bear poo down there.
Bag the poo.
Here.
When you're done collecting scat,
- find out what happened to Ducky.
- Got it, boss.
This entire area was supposed
to be off-limits to campers.
A hunter was bear baiting
here last month.
Bear baiting?
Have you spent any time in the woods,
Special Agent DiNozzo?
Well...
As much time as l can, l'm in the
woods. l'm a big fan of Mother Nature.
ln the off-season, hunters set out food,
always in the same place.
Bears get used to being fed and come
season, all they have to do is wait.
That's clever. l'll have to try that
the next time l'm out.
lt's illegal, Tony.
lf l had my way,
hunting would be too.
Who was baiting the bear?
A local. Jason Edom.
We pulled his license
- and banned him from the park.
- For life.
Petty Officer Riley know
this was a potentially dangerous area?
We hand this out to every visitor.
Had a bad drought this year.
Berries the bears feed on
have been scarce.
A hungry bear
will eat about anything.
The sad fact is they're gonna
track down this bear and kill it
because your stupid sailor
couldn't be bothered
to read a three-page pamphlet.
You'll have to forgive her. She's what
we like to call opposed to hunting.
Yes, that's not
the only thing she's opposed to.
You said Riley checked in alone?
Monday afternoon.
l signed him in myself.
We need to organize a search.
l'm one step ahead of you. l've got
a team out tracking the bear now.
lf he's still in the area,
we'll find him.
l'm more concerned about the woman.
There's two sets of footprints.
One is Riley's.
The other's a ladies' size 7.
Are you sure about that?
Yeah.
Unless these are Navy issue.
Listen up.
l want four-man teams in each sector.
At least two of them
armed with rifles.
She's been out there
at least two nights,
possibly injured and most definitely
scared out of her mind.
All communications
will run through mountain tac one.
All right, let's go.
They worked
search and rescue in the park
before l got stationed here.
- They'll find her.
- Hope it's before the bear does.
l'm sorry we were so late, Jethro.
Mr. Palmer's navigating skills
still leave something to be desired.
Honestly, doctor, l thought that
moss grew on the south side of trees.
lt does, in Australia.
Petty Officer Riley's vehicle
isn't in the parking lot.
According to the red--
The local guys,
campers park their cars
at the general store
- outside the main gate.
- Park's been having problems
with vandalism and theft
of unattended vehicles.
- Find it, DiNozzo.
- On it, boss.
Move over, Palmer. l'm driving.
- Don't.
- Don't what?
Don't encourage them, probie.
- Didn't you ever see Deliverance?
- No.
When you do, just remember that l'm
Burt Reynolds and you're Ned Beatty.
lt's Riley's.
''Jackrabbit Slim's''?
Just like the diner in Pulp Fiction.
You can't say ''porcupine,''
but you know the diner
from Pulp Fiction?
Believe it or not, we actually have
movie theatres in my country.
- Locked.
- Keys are probably inside.
Afternoon.
Five-dollar shakes.
Girls dressed like Marilyn.
This might be a little slice of heaven.
Or not.
Do you feel like dancing?
They drinking cappuccinos?
Probably fuelling up
for the banjo-duelling contest later.
- What's that?
- Those are scones.
They're like an English coffee pastry.
l think, probie, that Ziva was referring
to the jar next to the scones.
Those are pickled pigs feet, Ziva.
l think you'd enjoy them.
l'll pass on that.
They're not exactly kosher.
Can l help you folks?
- l'll take a double shot, extra foam.
- NClS.
You here about
the sailor eaten by the bear?
Well, yeah, l guess his car
is in your parking lot.
Yep.
l figured someone
would show up for it.
l charge park visitors ten bucks a day.
l'm gonna have a hard time collecting.
- That's a good guess.
- Jason.
The key to the Cherokee.
Jason Edom?
- Here you go.
- Thank you, Jason.
l know you, lady?
Not yet.
You see anyone with PO Riley
when he dropped that off?
Nope. You?
Nope.
You're wasting your time,
sweetheart.
l don't date your kind.
What is your kind, Mr. Edom?
Breathing?
You wanna keep working here?
You better learn
to keep your damn mouth shut.
l'm sorry about that, miss.
The boy's a little on the touchy side.
Yeah, l'd say so.
Thank you for your help.
Ziva, come on. Let's go.
The American black bear has a narrow
muzzle and a large, hinged jaw
with enormous crushing power.
600 pounds per square inch.
No animal of equal size
is nearly so strong.
You never discovered any of that,
did you?
- How do you know that?
- When Mr. Palmer sponged him,
we didn't find any evidence of slashing
or wounds on his hand and forearm.
- He didn't defend himself.
- More than that, l'm afraid.
The bear's claws and teeth
have rounded edges
that pierce the flesh.
Yet when l examined Mr. Riley's heart,
it revealed a very different story.
Our petty officer
was killed with a flat blade.
Death would
have been instantaneous.
Yes, he was dead.
Before the bear started eating him.
According to Petty Officer Riley's C.O.,
he's been on leave the last six days.
Nice vacation. A little camping.
A knife to the heart. A little trip
inside a bear's digestive track.
- Yeah, l'd fire my travel agent.
- Yeah.
You're late, Ziva David.
l almost forgot it was Abby's birthday.
Do you think she'll like them?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
- Think we should have told her?
- No.
No, me neither.
Little square, little square,
where have you been?
Stuck on the behind
of Riley's missing girlfriend.
Oh, hey. l was just about
to call Tony and McGee.
l think they were having sex.
- Tony and McGee?
- No. Riley and the missing girl.
l found this in their camp trash.
One of those little sticky thingies
you use when trying to quit smoking.
But it had residue of medication on it.
lt was progestin and oestrogen.
Birth-control patch.
- Yes. ls that burrito for me?
- Nope.
But these are.
Happy birthday, Abby.
Thank you so much.
You shouldn't have.
You're right.
l guess l shouldn't have.
l mean, l could get you
something else.
No.
l love them.
Hey, is Gibbs in yet?
- l haven't seen him.
- Okay.
ls something wrong?
No. Nope. Nothing's wrong.
lt's just that every year,
Gibbs usually takes me out to dinner
the night before my birthday.
lt's like a tradition.
Well, he probably just forgot.
Yeah.
l mean because of the case.
- l could remind him when l--
- No.
Don't remind him.
lt's really no big deal. l mean,
l don't wanna distract him
and Gibbs is gonna want
a name to go with this patch,
and that means
that l have work to do.
Thank you for the flowers.
Nice flowers, Ducky.
l should hope so. l went
to four flower shops to find them.
Apparently, they're sold out
all over the city.
What if we're not looking
for a damsel in distress here, probie?
No one saw our missing Jane Doe.
Not the rangers
when Riley checked in.
Or the hillbillies
when he parked his car.
- She didn't wanna be seen.
- We could be dealing
- with a black widow here.
- Lions and spiders and bears.
Oh, my.
What, Mr. Movie doesn't know
The Wizard of Oz?
l'm talking about
a predatory female here, Ziva.
Mates, then kills.
Reminds me
of my father's second wife.
- l don't buy your theory.
- Well, what's to buy?
She lured him out to the woods,
made love to him, then whacked him
- while he was sleeping.
- Or ran off
while Riley was being
stabbed to death.
- How about neither?
- Rough night, boss?
Well, yeah, DiNozzo.
l spent it tracking our missing woman
with a bunch of volunteers
in Shenandoah Park.
- You found her?
- No.
- So she's still out there?
- Park Service thinks so.
Here, McGee.
Take the film dooeywhacker out
of there and put it up on the plasma.
Well, boss, actually,
this is a digital camera.
They use memory cards now.
l'll put the dooeywhacker in.
There wasn't a sign or track
of a ladies' size 7 boot
ever leaving that campground.
- How'd she get out here, boss?
- Like this.
- So, what's this?
- Snipers call that a ghost, DiNozzo.
Someone who can move
through the woods almost undetected.
l followed them for 300 meters
before l lost them.
They only left two obvious signs.
The back edge
of a military boot heel,
and this.
- Jewellery?
- Get it to Abby.
You think someone
carried her away?
Ziva, l think she didn't just
float out of that campsite.
We need to find out who she is.
Right. l talked to the guys Riley
worked with at the Navy Yard.
Only one of them, a Seaman Brad
Phillips, knew he was going camping.
Riley mentioned taking a girl he met
weeks ago. Phillips never got a name.
- Pull Riley's phone records.
- Has a cell phone he doesn't use.
Went back two weeks. Made a couple
of calls to his family in New York,
and the rest were to local businesses
and government agencies.
- Check out his room.
- Went through his room.
Nothing unusual.
No sign of a girlfriend.
Rangers set up a temporary aid centre
inside Jackrabbit Slim's for volunteers.
l want you both there.
l had them pull the files
of all other deaths
that happened in that park.
Looks like another chance to hit
on that cute ranger, yes?
lt's gonna be tough but not impossible.
Misreads are part of the game.
True, except l was talking about me.
Maybe she drove out here
on her own.
That's why no one saw her
with Riley.
Registration could give us a name.
l assume Gibbs would have
checked that out last night.
Rule eight,
never assume anything.
To be precise,
it's ''never take anything for granted.''
To be more precise, what would
you do if l started head-slapping you?
l'd most likely kill you.
lt's a reflex thing.
Gentlemen.
People with guns make me nervous.
- l noticed.
- l was talking about you, actually.
Still holding any vehicles
for campers?
Your Agent Gibbs asked
the same question last night. Nope.
Looks like the search is good
for business. Yes?
Yeah.
Special Agent DiNozzo. Ziva.
- Find anything?
- Not yet.
We've expanded the search area
beyond the initial five-mile radius.
lf she was abducted,
she could be anywhere.
Park's 1 98,000 acres.
That's over 300 square miles.
- lt's a big area to patrol.
- Yeah, unless you like to exercise.
Well, as a matter of fact,
l like to walk and--
Our boss would like any records
you have on deaths in the park.
- Bobby?
- Follow me.
These are every death
over the last ten years.
All ruled natural or accidental.
Thank you. Listen, l just wanted to--
We may have gotten off
on the wrong foot,
and l just wanted to let you know
that l'm not a hunter.
l was trying to impress you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Got anything?
Define ''anything.''
- No, thanks.
- Hair follicles?
- Our missing woman?
- Most likely.
- And?
- And Caucasian. Brunette.
lt's at the anagen, or growth, stage,
so l can probably get DNA off the root.
- What about the one on the right?
- lt's from Petty Officer Riley's car.
- They're from the same person.
- She drove with him.
- You think?
- ls something bothering you, Abby?
No. l did a further test on our lady's
birth-control method of choice.
lt's a low-level oestrogen patch.
Prescription dosage is based
on weight and height.
So odds are she's
of average to small stature.
ls there anything else
l can do for you?
Find me a name.
Now l know how Molly Ringwald felt
in Sixteen Candles.
Slam dunk.
We're going out next weekend.
That's not bad, Tony.
Landis asked me out tonight.
l said no.
l don't want him to think l'm sleazy.
The term is ''easy.''
- What's the difference?
- Mostly the makeup.
- What do we have?
- Over the last seven years,
there's been eight deaths
in the park.
Three from natural causes, a stroke
and two heart attacks.
- The others?
- All accidental.
ln 2000, a couple drowned
while canoeing.
The woman's body
was never recovered.
ln 2002, a couple got lost hiking.
Their remains were recovered last year.
- ln 2004, a woman named--
- Tracy Roberts' body was discovered
nine months after she went
into the park to photograph wildlife.
- Her remains were--
- Too ravaged
by animals and the elements
to determine a cause of death.
- l wanna see a profile on them.
- l found something.
- Passports. Get me--
- Boss?
- What, McGee?
- Sorry.
l found something here.
The three dead women,
they all fit the same description.
- Twenties, Caucasian--
- Brunette, petite?
Yeah.
Since we all know
how you feel about coincidences,
l decided
to pull their driver's license photos.
Wow, they look like
they could be sisters.
Something tells me their deaths
weren't exactly accidental.
We're dealing with a killer who's using
park accidents to cover up murder.
Three almost identical women.
All of them end up dead
in Shenandoah National Park.
And if our missing woman
fits the same profile,
we could be dealing with a serial killer.
One who uses park accidents
to cover up abductions and murder.
- So, what do you think?
- l'm not sure yet, McGee.
But l think that
this might be unforgivable.
Well, yeah.
Of course it's unforgivable.
- What if he had a really good reason?
- A good reason?
Yeah, like he was really stressed out
or, like, overworked.
- What difference does that make?
- Nobody's perfect.
- Abby, there is no excuse.
- McGee, that's so sweet.
You know what? lt's just a stupid
birthday. Who cares if Gibbs forgot?
Why, l guess that l do.
That's why l love you.
When you get all hot and bothered
like that, it really turns me on.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah.
Are you two done playing grab-assy?
Or do l need to transfer McGee
to a weather station in the Antarctic?
- We were just--
- l think l found our missing girl, Gibbs.
And McGee
was just congratulating me.
The birth-control patch
that our Jane Doe was wearing
turned out to be a Rosetta stone.
lt delivers
a very specific oestrogen cocktail.
lt's usually prescribed for women
whose systems can't handle the pill.
- The pill is the most common--
- l've had a few wives, Abby.
And yet you know
so little about women.
Luckily, this patch was still
in the rollout phase,
so the company is required
to maintain detailed medical profiles
on the 3,000 women
that are using them.
l crossed those profiles
with the data l pulled off her DNA
profile, her race and her blood type.
l came up with 200 women, Gibbs.
- Find out which one's missing.
- l'm not done yet.
From the hair samples, we know
that the woman was brunette.
So if we subtract blond women
and those with black hair,
that brings us to 43.
Of the 43, only 1 4 live
in the Mid-Atlantic.
l called them all, and l got 1 3.
Number 1 4...
...is Jessica Fagan.
She works at HUD in D.C.
She didn't show up for work
on Monday. She's missing, Gibbs.
- Got a picture?
- l was waiting for the DMV
to email me one before l called you.
But fortunately, it's already here.
Boss, this definitely
doesn't look like a coincidence.
You think, McGee?
lt's confirmed, boss.
She told a co-worker
she was going camping
with her boyfriend in Shenandoah.
Duck, all three of these women's
deaths were ruled accidental.
Pull their autopsy records, along
with the guys who died with them.
To look for what, specifically?
- How they were murdered.
- Oh, right.
- Nice place you got here, Ziva.
- Thanks.
They cut our wildlife conservation
budget, and you guys have a skylight?
- Nice.
- l understand things
have taken a turn
for the worse, Agent Gibbs?
lf by ''worse'' you mean multiple
homicides in your park since 2000,
then yeah, worse.
- Well, there goes that theory.
- What theory?
l was prepared to say that
this could all be just a coincidence,
- but when you see them like that--
- lt's more than a little disturbing.
Yeah. What can we do to help?
We're looking for someone who knows
his way around your park. Like a local.
We've got a list of the usual
troublemakers, poachers and vandals.
But l never figured any of them
for a serial killer.
Most likely you wouldn't, James.
The successful ones
blend into their environment.
Yeah. l mean,
look at the BTK killer, right?
Pillar of the community, Cub Scout
leader, president of his church.
- You're saying it could be anyone?
- Not in this case.
We're looking for someone who
carried a woman through the woods
and hardly left a track.
- An experienced hunter?
- Or someone with military training.
l'd like to send the photo of the missing
woman to our search teams.
- DiNozzo.
- l'm on it.
Get it to Pete at Jackrabbit Slim's.
Tell him to post it on every pole,
every fence, every car near the park.
- Gibbs.
- Got something if you're interested.
Yeah, we're on our way.
Abby's got something.
Our forensic scientist.
You'll like her.
She's a vampire.
So would you like me
to email that or fax it?
Email is fine.
Email it is.
So is it just me
or is it hot in here?
lt's probably a little bit of both.
Email sent. There you go.
So l was thinking
about this weekend and...
About trying camping?
- ls something wrong?
- l'm married.
- Then why'd you ask for my number?
- She's dead.
lt was a-- lt was a pottery accident.
Kiln overheated or something.
Very unexpected. Very unexpected.
l thought l was ready to move on.
Oh, you.
Oh, you poor, poor man.
l swabbed what's left
of Petty Officer Riley's clothes.
lt's mostly his blood and what
l now know to be bear saliva.
He was eaten by a bear.
Tell me something l don't know.
About the case
or something more personal?
Abby.
l also found traces
of a cornucopia of different chemicals
sprayed all over his clothes.
Phenylacetic crystals,
methyl anthranilate and acorn,
caramel and bergamot oils.
- A hunting lure?
- You are correct, Mr. Ranger, sir.
More specifically,
it was Uncle Bebo's Bear Attractant.
Somebody hosed
the officer down with it.
l can pull a list of every hunter
that applied for
a bear-hunting permit this year.
You don't have to. McGee just found
who sprayed him with it.
Boss, we pulled multiple prints
from the equipment at the campsite.
Most of them are Riley's.
A bunch, l assume, are--
You assume, McGee?
Well, l meant we're working on getting
Jessica Fagan's prints to clear them,
but we have three other matches
belonging to a third individual.
Jason Edom.
Looks like he was baiting
more than bears.
This man makes my skin crawl.
Can you interrogate him
without breaking bones?
Truthfully? No.
l agree. That's why l'm doing it.
You're gonna spend
the next few hours
studying everything we know
about him and the evidence.
And supply the answers
to you in there?
No. No, l've got DiNozzo
doing that.
You're on Edom's side.
- Meaning?
- Meaning,
you're going to defend him. l want you
to assume that he's innocent.
- The man's a serial-killing racist.
- He probably is.
- But you're still gonna do it.
- Why?
Because you can't walk in there
and interrogate him.
Yet.
You mind telling me why l'm here?
You like hunting.
Last time l checked,
that wasn't illegal.
Your hunting license was pulled.
You're a Marine, huh?
l can tell.
My old man was a Marine.
Hated his guts.
''Get your hands
out of your pockets, boy.
Shave your face, boy.
Cut your hair, boy.''
See?
A lasting impression.
Semper fi.
He teach you how to bait bears?
No, l learned that for myself.
He was just a real loser.
Your record includes
more than bear baiting.
l guess l'm a complicated man.
You did time for assault and battery.
lt was a bar fight.
l didn't even start it.
- Do you know him?
- Yeah.
That's the idiot
who got eaten by the bear.
He was murdered first
with a hunting knife.
You baited the area
where that occurred.
Lookie here, Mr. Marine.
l haven't been in that park
for over a month.
News flash.
l happen to be banned for life.
Your fingerprints
were found at the campsite.
Last time l checked,
that was inside the park.
No, that's a damn lie.
l ain't been nowhere near that area.
Know her?
Nope.
How about them?
Like l said, no.
Okay?
l didn't have nothing to do with this.
l wouldn't...
Wouldn't what?
Kill people.
l may be a lot of things,
but l'm not some psycho.
- Yes, l'll hold.
- You shave, right?
- What?
- Nothing.
So how'd the killer's prints
end up at the campsite?
Obviously when he murdered the sailor
and abducted the girl.
No, Gibbs wants you
defending him, Ziva.
McGee, what objects
were the killer--
Sorry, sorry. Edom, Edom.
--Edom's prints found on again?
Two cans of tuna,
one pack of AA batteries.
All items sold at Jackrabbit Slim's.
Okay, so, what if Riley
bought these items
and Edom placed them in a bag?
Yeah. That one's actually plausible.
Nice job. But it is hard to prove.
- l'm still here, yes.
- Okay, Edom's a hunter, right?
He's familiar with the area
- and he's done time for violent crime.
- Thank you.
And we found his prints
at the campsite, so--
- He didn't do it.
- Okay, you're not getting this.
- You can't just say he didn't do it.
- Ziva, he's right.
You need to back your side up
with facts and rational--
The night Riley was murdered,
Edom was at his daughter's
dance recital in Manassas, Virginia.
Multiple witnesses.
- Unbelievable.
- l agree.
l thought for sure this was our man.
No. l mean, this guy
actually reproduced?
- Gibbs, we just--
- Confirmed Edom's alibi.
He was in Manassas
the night of the murder.
- He didn't do it.
- l know.
- He knows.
- So, what now?
You're gonna go
and have a talk with him.
Why? You just agreed
he didn't kill the petty officer.
Because he knows who did.
lt's not poisoned.
Afraid of germs?
l didn't kill those women.
l know.
You were at your daughter's
dance recital.
You know...
...l used to spend
most of my time on stage...
...searching for my father's face
in the audience.
But he was never there.
Even when he promised he'd...
l drove all the way
to South Carolina once.
To watch your daughter dance?
What's her name?
Sarah.
That's a Hebrew name.
lt means ''princess.''
l didn't know that.
Each of them was
someone's princess, Jason.
She should have never left him.
Not like she did.
Left who?
Wes.
Boss, state troopers
just missed Wes Rowan.
He left Jackrabbit Slim's
with a rifle and a backpack.
- Said he was gonna help search.
- He is the search, McGee.
Jessica Fagan was
Wes Rowan's childhood sweetheart.
lt was over when she filed a restraining
order against him in 2000.
Why am l finding out
about this now?
She changed her name.
lt used to be Parker.
Most likely to make it difficult
for Rowan to locate her.
When he couldn't, he took his anger
out on women who resembled her.
Explains why she never
let anyone at Jackrabbit Slim's
- or the park see her.
- Oh, you think, DiNozzo? Gibbs.
- Abs, l have no time. Two minutes.
- lt's really important.
Boss, state troopers are setting up
roadblocks on all highways
- leading down from the mountains.
- He took his backpack with him.
He's not planning on coming down.
Grab your gear.
l'll meet you out back in five.
Guess what, guys?
Rowan is a hunting guide,
- apparently one of the best in Virginia.
- Great.
He'll be like finding
a pin in a haystack.
A needle in a haystack.
Well, aren't pins
just as hard to find?
- No.
You've got two minutes, Abby.
Starting now.
l don't need two minutes. Just
a minute or maybe 45 seconds.
- Abby.
- l pulled skin cells off the rhinestones
that you found in the park, and the
DNA matches Fagan's hair.
- You could've told me on the phone.
- Well, l also found traces of blood.
l have a theory, Gibbs.
l made this in high school.
- Minute, 33.
- Okay. l screwed up a bunch of times.
Pulling these things off is really hard.
l cracked two nails and l cut my finger.
Oh, hell, she's leaving a trail.
That's great work, Abs.
Wait, l still have
a minute and change left.
l know you're really busy with the case,
and l understand.
- Understand what?
- That you forgot my birthday.
- l didn't forget.
- You didn't?
No. l remember how old you are too.
Oh, you can forget that.
Check your desk.
No.
l have been working in here all night.
There is no way you snuck by me.
This is so Pulp Fiction.
l've been searching
the building for you.
- You found me.
- She may be still alive, Jethro.
l re-checked the
Rappahannock County ME's records.
All three victims
had hairline fractures.
The medical examiners assumed
that these were caused by animals
- or falls in the woods.
- They didn't know she was murdered.
- That bastard beats them.
- l'm afraid so.
How does that make her alive?
Some of the fractures
had minute calcification.
They'd begun to heal, Jethro.
- How long?
- Well, l'd say a week or 1 0 days
perhaps after he beat them.
He'll find you, my dear,
hopefully before it's too late.
There are hunting cabins along this
edge. He could have taken her to one.
- Any cabins in the park?
- Two.
Birch and Pine. Gotta reserve them a
year in advance. They're real popular.
- ls anyone there now?
- No.
We open them Memorial Day
to Labour Day.
- Where?
- Pine's here. Birch is here.
The other night,
l lost the trail around here.
Jessica could be in those cabins.
Checked them the first day.
What if he held her in the woods
while you searched the cabin?
Search them again.
Where's Ranger Landis
and his search party?
- Razorback Ridge.
- He's a lot closer than we are.
Have him search them. McGee!
DiNozzo, you're with me.
Ziva, stay
with Ranger Hendricks.
- l'd be better suited if l actually went--
- We're taking him alive. Let's roll.
l hate it when men try to protect you
because you're female.
He's not trying to protect me.
He's afraid l'll kill Rowan
before he tells us where the girl is.
For a ghost,
he's sure leaving a lot of footprints.
- He took a knee here.
- Maybe he heard McGee coming.
No.
He's tracking.
Tracking who?
He already knows where the girl is.
James? Bobby. How you doing?
Almost to Pine Cabin. l've got
Beaufort and Max checking Birch.
- You be careful, you hear?
- Don't worry about me, Bobby. Out.
- You both live here?
- Jim does.
l got me a log cabin
about a mile down the road.
Built in the 1 830s.
- ls that old?
- Yeah, around these parts it is.
l'm sorry, that was bitchy.
l get that way when l'm tired.
Yeah. Me too.
That'll be more searchers.
l better go brief them.
Do you mind if l grab a bat nap?
No. Just hang from the rafters.
What is it, boss?
The trail's too obvious.
Rowan doesn't know
that we're tracking him.
Or he's setting an ambush.
McGee, l want you 30 meters
to my right.
DiNozzo, 30 to my left.
l'll stay on this trail.
What if it is an ambush?
l want you guys to get him
before he gets me.
Go. Go. Be ghosts.
l got him.
- l thought it was you, boss.
- Me too.
l was trying to find Jessica.
- We gotta get him to a hospital.
- Let the bastard bleed to death.
He dies,
we may never find that girl alive.
Your station can't be far.
Maybe a quarter of a mile that way.
- You got him?
- Come on.
- Jim made it in. They got Rowan.
- Call 91 1 .
l just did for Rowan. They're bringing
him in wounded. How?
You tell me.
She was in your root cellar.
l thought you were leading
the search.
Bobby radioed
she had fresh searchers.
l was cutting back to pick them up
and l spotted Rowan
sneaking through the woods.
He wasn't sneaking,
he was tracking.
Jim, this is Bobby.
Officer David found Jessica Fagan.
She was in your root cellar.
- Jim? Jim, do you read me?
- Drop that shotgun.
- Jim, are you there?
- How many?
Twenty-seven.
No, 26.
Can't count Jessica.
l didn't finish with her.
Now, drop that shotgun!
- Take him.
- No. What are you doing?
- l'm gonna go help boss.
- Doesn't need you. Look at him.
- Boss didn't--?
- No. He wouldn't do a thing like that.