What an adorable child, Yoon.
She's like a little doll.
How come l have never met
this little munchkin before?
She usually stays with the sitter
while we go shopping.
She's such a cutie.
Well, we're running a little late today,
so if you'll excuse us.
Oh, here, let me help you, dear.
- Oh, thank you.
- Sure.
l doubt they'll hear us.
They've been playing
that Chinese stuff all morning.
Actually, it's Korean.
Oh, right, sorry.
You know, Sun usually leaves
the back door open. Come on.
My aunt burned down
her house like this.
She really should be more careful.
Oh, now that's better.
l'm not usually one to complain.
l don't understand, McGee.
Sensitivity training?
A seminar on the basics
of communication
- and understanding in the workplace.
- l know what sensitivity is.
l'm asking why we have to spend
the whole afternoon studying it.
Professional development?
lf it were survival training,
advanced demolitions, perhaps--
l don't think that Sympathetic
Seminars, lnc. offers those classes
Skilled investigators should already be
well-versed in the subtleties
- of inter-human communication.
- l like ltalian women.
You're ltalian, right?
l like lrish women, too.
- l stand corrected.
- You two better hurry up.
- You don't wanna miss out on the fun.
- Where are you going?
Prior engagement.
Take notes for me.
You do understand the meaning
of the word ''mandatory,'' don't you?
l have been ordered to inspect
the secure-file room, probie.
Sadly, that conflicts
with your exciting seminar today.
No, it doesn't.
This order is for next Wednesday.
- What?
- Look on the bright side, Tony.
lt should only take
about five to seven hours.
There's gotta be some way out of this.
Maybe l could injure myself.
- What? l was only trying to help.
- l was only kidding.
Sensitivity training
is gonna have to wait.
We got a double homicide
at Quantico.
Marine wives. Grab your gear.
Yes.
- lnappropriate?
- A bit.
You're probably the reason
we have to take these classes.
- Today.
- On your six, boss.
You know, this kind of reminds me
of my cousin's house,
minus all the blood.
Unless you count
that Thanksgiving back in '98.
Family does have a way
of fraying one's nerves.
Take my mother, for instance.
She insists on watching Jeopardy
every night on the television.
What's wrong with that, Duck?
The same episode,
over and over again.
l made the mistake of taping it
for her once.
l always say, you can pick your nose,
but you can't pick your family.
There's a touch of the poet in you,
Mr. Palmer.
l'd say you're just more touched.
DiNozzo.
House belongs to
a Sergeant Malcolm Porter
and his wife, Sun, boss.
She's the one on the left.
Sergeant's still on liberty
trying to track him down.
The other vic is Min Crane.
She's married
to a Sergeant Floyd Crane,
currently deployed in lraq.
Sign of an unhappy marriage.
Funny, l thought it looked like
a hole in the wall.
lt's about fist size.
Husband probably hit the wall
instead of hitting his wife.
- What else do you see?
- Judging by the position of the body
- l'd say they were taken by surprise.
- Yeah? Why?
Body posture. They're too relaxed.
They didn't fight back.
That could also mean
they knew the identity of their attacker.
Search the rest of the house.
Little girl's becoming quite the crime
scene investigator, isn't she, boss?
l'll go help McGee
talk to the women who found them.
- You got a TOD yet, Duck?
- Very recent.
Both liver probes indicate
about two and a half hours ago.
Triple tap, all in the heart.
Yeah, but notice these burn marks
around the entry wounds
here and on this one.
So both of those, the weapon
was in direct contact with the body
- when fired.
- Two from across the room.
Then one each up close,
just to be sure.
l don't believe the term ''overkill''
would be inappropriate,
under these circumstances.
- Bullets didn't penetrate.
- Maybe they were small-calibre.
Did you find any casings?
The shooter policed his brass, Duck.
Policed, sir?
Yes, it's military terminology
for cleaning up after one's self.
We may be dealing
with a professional.
- Professional what?
- Killer, Mr. Palmer.
These poor women
weren't so much murdered
as executed.
She just needs her bottle.
l know l packed it.
Look, look, look. Your mom's
right there. She's right there.
Did you ever hold
a baby before, McGee?
- No.
- l didn't think so.
Boss, this is Mrs. Dawson.
She found the body along
with the next-door neighbours.
We were going into Koreatown,
shopping.
l'm the only one with a car.
Sun asked me
to come pick them up.
lf we'd been on time--
You need some help?
Any idea where Sun's husband is,
Mrs. Dawson?
No, he's never here
when we come over.
l don't think he likes Sun
having friends.
What makes you think that?
He's very controlling.
- Sergeant Porter abused her?
- Sun wouldn't admit it.
But we suspected.
He drinks.
Says mean things to her.
Wouldn't let her speak Korean
in the house.
We tried to reason with her but--
- She wouldn't leave him?
- She was ashamed.
lt's hard for a Korean woman
to ask for help.
- Find Porter.
- l'd start at the ''E'' Club.
- James.
- l'm Yoon's husband.
Listen, if you don't find Porter there,
you might wanna check some
of the bars outside the front gate.
l'm on it, boss.
Everything's gonna be okay now,
honey, okay?
Gibbs. A word, please?
l just talked to her a few hours ago.
Gun safe.
l found it in the master bedroom.
Open and empty
except for a handful of shells.
.40 calibre.
Thinking maybe
the husband did this, yes?
l guess the polite term, Agent DiNozzo,
would be ''bastard.''
He was always borrowing
my husband's tools
and never returning them.
l should've known this would happen.
Stealing tools isn't really a prerequisite
for murder, Mrs. Goodwin.
All l'm saying is the two of them
had one hell of a marriage.
You wouldn't know it to look at her,
but Sun's got a set of lungs.
Or at least she did.
- So they fought a lot?
- Oh, hardly a night went by
you didn't hear all sorts of screaming
coming from this house.
- You ever think to make a complaint?
- l don't like to stick my nose in.
Good thing, too. lt could have been me
that got slaughtered.
On our way, McGee.
Sergeant Porter was spotted
30 minutes ago at the "E'' Club.
- McGee's almost there.
- Thanks.
Probie's not gonna make a move
on his own, is he, boss?
McGee can take care of himself,
DiNozzo.
You're on the hump.
- He's gone.
- Nice job, probie.
The bartender turned around,
Sgt. Porter wasn't there anymore.
- You let him get past you?
- lt was before l got here, Tony.
What's Sergeant Porter driving?
- What kind of car does he drive?
- A black 2004 Ford F-1 50, boss.
Hey, come on.
Boss, we got a weapon
in the front seat.
l think he's dead, boss.
NClS. Don't move.
Get your hands on the wheel.
l wasn't gonna drive.
Come on, it's not DUl
if l don't have the key
in the ignition, look.
- What's he talking about?
- l think he thinks we're busting him
- for driving drunk.
- Well, you're not?
No.
- lt's for double homicide.
- McGee.
Wait a minute.
What are you talking about?
l knew he was alive.
Precision, Mr. Palmer.
lt's what separates the professional
from the dilettante.
Thank you, doctor.
Now, careful.
Not too much pressure.
But not too little either.
All right, come on,
come on, come on.
Let's see. Yes, very good.
Not bad. Not bad at all.
Keep a steady hand.
There's no room for error.
You never know
which element of the enigma,
however minuscule,
can lead you to the solution.
Palmer just got some of your elements
on his plastic thing.
- Occupational hazard, l'm afraid.
- What can you tell me, Duck?
Both women were shot
three times in the chest.
lt's hard to say which of these six
was the fatal wound.
Suffice to say,
neither woman died of old age.
- Anything else?
- Yes. Mrs. Porter
has some swelling and fissures
on her fingers and knuckles.
- Defensive wounds.
- Possibly.
Yeah, but these didn't happen today.
There are also bruises on her wrists.
l'd say they were at least a week old.
She was abused?
Yeah.
- Thanks, Duck.
- You have the man in custody now?
Yeah.
There's no need
to be gentle with him, Jethro.
You missed a spot.
We're looking at
a Beretta Cougar 8040, Gibbs.
lt was registered
to Sergeant Porter in 2003
- and it's got his fingerprints all over it.
- Bullets?
Cross-point .40 calibre
Smith and Wesson.
Also called a "Short and Wimpy,''
although l do not know why.
They lack the power
of a 1 0-millimeter auto-load.
You don't need that stopping power
when you gun down housewives.
- What about gunshot residue?
- lnstant Shooter Kit came negative
- on Porter's skin, shirt and pants.
- Could've worn gloves--
Or he could've changed clothes.
l'm way ahead of you.
That's why l'm doing a full analysis
on all of Porter's wardrobe.
''How long, Abby?''
Well, it's gonna take some time.
And since this stuff
doesn't smell very good
l don't think laundry was a priority.
''Abs.''
Two hours. Whenever l know
something, you'll know something.
''You got one. Anything else?''
Yes, as a matter of fact.
This is for you.
- Why?
- For getting me out
of sensitivity training.
We were about to do trust falls
and those guys in administration
have wandering hands.
''Just give me their names, Abs,
and l'll break them for you.''
l know you will, Gibbs.
And that is why l love you.
Boss, l'm sorry. l didn't see you.
What did l say
about apologising, McGee?
Sign of weakness.
So is barfing on your tie.
This isn't mine.
We've got Sergeant Porter
in interrogation.
l actually managed
to dodge most of it.
Good news is
that he is sober enough to talk now.
l got some on you, here,
let me get this.
- Don't.
- Sorry.
l mean, it won't happen again.
- Who's watching him?
- Tony and Ziva.
l was actually just gonna go
change my shirt.
No, you won't. You're gonna follow up
on other leads.
We found Sergeant Porter with the
murder weapon. What other leads?
A good investigator
doesn't sit back and wait.
You run down every angle,
every lead.
Assume everything you've been told
is a lie until it checks out.
Got it.
There's only one time
l want you to stop, McGee.
- When you tell me.
- When you're satisfied.
When you're satisfied.
Okay.
- Hey!
- Yeah?
Get me another cup of coffee.
This is gonna be good.
Gibbs will rip this guy apart.
l don't know if that's the right tactic
in this case, Tony.
What, are you an expert
on suspect interviews, now?
lnterviews, no.
lnterrogation techniques, yes.
Like hooking a car battery
up to a guy's privates?
l'm sure it's effective,
but judges tend to frown on it.
l've learned from Gibbs
that in certain cases
you can attract
far more bees with honey.
Flies.
- What do flies have to do with honey?
- Flies don't like vinegar.
Vinegar?
lt's complicated. Here he comes.
Here you go.
There.
You look like you could use it.
My wife's really dead, sir?
How?
Drink your coffee, sergeant.
When you're ready
we'll work our way up to it.
What's he doing?
Where's his strong-arming?
The intimidation?
The psychological bullying?
The Gibbs?
Bad marriage, huh?
lt's okay.
l've had a few myself.
lt wasn't perfect,
but l loved her, sir.
Problem was...
l don't think--
l don't think she ever loved me.
l'll bet she loved that paycheque,
though, right?
Yeah.
l should have known it.
Just look at me.
She was way out of my league,
you know?
She just married me
to get to the States.
lt happens.
Thing is...
l guess l always thought she
might change her mind, you know?
Then she started
sneaking out to the "O'' Club,
hanging out with officers.
l've seen it before.
She thought she could trade up.
She didn't want me.
No matter what l did.
lt just got to the point--
l just wanted her to disappear.
Yeah, when you get pushed,
you want to push back.
That why you decide
to blow her away?
Excuse me, sir?
ls that the reason you shot Min Crane
and your wife to death today?
Okay, here we go.
He hasn't confessed yet.
- He will.
- Maybe.
- How much do you wanna bet?
- How about nothing?
- Twenty bucks?
- Deal.
l'm telling you
l didn't kill them, sir.
The murder weapon
was in your truck, sergeant.
Someone must have put it there.
Your fingerprints are all over it.
l didn't shoot my wife, sir.
Did you use your fists
on her, sergeant?
Knock her around a little bit,
or maybe
that just wasn't cutting it anymore.
l never laid a hand on Sun.
Your neighbour heard the fights,
sergeant.
l saw the hole you punched.
l only punched the hole in the wall
so l wouldn't hit her, sir.
Her hands were all bruised
and cut
from where she fought you off
all the time.
- That's not how it happened.
- Really?
How did l get it wrong?
How'd it happen?
She was the--
She the one who was abusing me.
You don't believe me?
Take a look at this.
Sit down.
Sun was violent, sir.
She hit me. She called me names.
She threw things.
l tried to hold her off
but l never--
l never once laid a hand on her.
l just wanted it to stop.
- Pay up.
- He didn't confess.
- lt was damn close.
- Close doesn't cut it, DiNozzo.
Well, we got enough evidence
even if you didn't break him
in interrogation, boss.
Not to say that
you couldn't have broken him
if you wanted to.
l really like that shirt.
Tony's right. we have Sgt. Porter's gun
with his fingerprints in his car.
He blows away his wife and her friend
in a rage. Gets drunk. Passes out
- before he can commit suicide.
- Why did he police his brass?
- Habit of a well-trained Marine.
- He worked the motor pool.
According to his records,
he failed to qualify twice
on the pistol range last year.
Abby get the results of the GSR tests
on his clothing yet?
- All negative, boss.
- He could have worn gloves
- or got rid of the clothes he's wearing.
- But he leaves his pistol
in full view on the front seat.
Boss, l think l've got something here.
l just spoke with the director
of the Officers' Club.
Apparently Sun Porter
was a regular fixture there.
Almost always with Min Crane.
A month ago, they were all banned.
- For what, McGee?
- One of their husbands showed up,
made a scene, had to be carried out.
Another nail
in Sergeant Porter's coffin.
lt wasn't Sergeant Porter, Tony.
Sergeant James Dawson.
Yoon's husband.
Heard you guys got Sergeant Porter at
the "E'' Club with the murder weapon.
l knew they were having troubles,
but never expected this.
Where's your wife,
Sergeant Dawson?
She's taking a nap with our daughter.
Why? ls something wrong, sir?
What happened at the Officer's Club
last month?
Let me refresh your memory.
You had an altercation
with two Marine captains.
Yeah, it was nothing.
lt was just a misunderstanding.
Big enough for a Letter of Reprimand
in your SRB.
Maybe we should ask your wife
about it, sergeant?
- She had a rough day. l'd rather not--
- Down the hall?
Yeah, but l'd rather not disturb her.
- We'll see if she's still breathing.
- You think l killed Sun and Min
because they had a couple of drinks
with my wife at the "O'' Club?
Mrs. Dawson, NClS.
We're gonna ask you a few questions.
Yoon. lt's me. Please.
Yoon, open up.
- Do you have a key?
- lt's locked from the inside. Yoon.
Yoon.
lt's okay. lt's okay.
lt doesn't make sense, sir.
Someone kills
my wife's two best friends,
then they decide to kidnap her?
When's the last time
you saw her, sergeant?
About an hour
before you showed up.
She was putting the baby to sleep
in our room.
- You didn't hear anything?
- No.
Can we stop standing around
and do something?
We are.
We are. Sit down.
And what exactly is that, sir?
Figuring out if you're a suspect
or a victim.
The window was broken
from the outside.
Whoever did this slipped in,
grabbed her and slipped out.
None of the neighbours heard
or saw anything unusual, boss.
MP's are searching the area.
Also checking every vehicle
leaving the base.
- You think she still might be on base?
- lt's possible.
We need to be out there
looking for her.
lf she's still on base we'll find her.
Someone put a lot of effort into taking
her away without alerting you.
There's a good chance
she's not dead yet.
Yet?
Oh, God,
why would someone do this?
For the same reason
someone killed her friends.
You think l had something
to do with this?
Sit down.
What happened
at the Officer's Club, sergeant?
lt was nothing, okay?
Sun and Min go there all the time.
Yoon just drops them off.
This one time she went in
and had a couple of drinks.
She couldn't drive home
so she called me.
- Gibbs.
- Boss--
When did you get into a verbal
altercation with the Marine captains?
They were drunk, okay?
They were hitting on my wife.
They tried to stop me
from taking her home.
What would you do, sir?
You think one of these captains might
have had something to do with this?
We're wasting our time. l'm telling you,
l had nothing to do with this.
l know that.
Your alibi just checked out.
The sergeant was on duty
at the time of the shootings.
So what now, sir?
Three Korean women met
and married Marines in Seoul
at roughly the same time.
Two of them are dead.
Our prime suspect was locked up here
when the third went missing.
Think it's a racial thing?
No. Definitely do not think
that it's a hate crime.
ln my experience there's only
one colour in the Marines.
What l've seen of your Marine Corps,
it's very ethnically diverse.
He means green, Ziva.
And l think he's right.
Well, maybe it's a Korean thing.
Maybe something in their past.
Like some kind of blood feud.
Competing villages, ancient oaths,
revenge from across the ocean.
This is not one
of your stupid action movies, Tony.
No, it isn't.
lf it was, you'd be dressed differently.
And you'd be far better looking.
You'd be dead
by the opening credits.
Did you ever stop to think that maybe
l am the plucky comic relief?
You find out what the hell happened
to Yoon Dawson yet?
Plucky?
- Well, Ziva and Tony and l--
- Were just working on that, boss.
We're going through a list of anyone
who had access to the base
in the last two days.
So far, no solid leads.
What about the Marines
Sergeant Dawson fought with?
Both transferred
out of Quantico last month.
One at Camp Pendleton,
the other is in Okinawa.
The two dead women lived
insular lives.
They spent most of their time together
with other Koreans.
Yoon Dawson seems to be the only
one who embraced American life.
Any reason to believe that Sergeant
Porter isn't still involved in this?
He could have had
an accomplice, probie.
He could have had three, DiNozzo.
We need more information.
Actually, boss, Abby and l,
we have been working on something.
We got the women's phone records,
credit card receipts, address books.
Abby is referencing to see
if there's a pattern.
DiNozzo, l want to know
about anybody in the area
who's made threats against Koreans,
foreign Marine wives, or women.
Oh, is that all?
- On it, boss.
- Find out about their lives
before they married Marines.
Come on, you're with me, Elf Lord.
lt's amazing how much you can find
out about someone
without actually meeting them.
For instance, me and these women
have absolutely nothing in common.
They web-browse
for cake recipes, gardening tips
and Min Crane has some weird
obsession with stained glass.
That's not even mentioning their
music downloads. One word: Yanni.
Good point. Who cares?
Their schedules
were pretty regulated.
On Wednesdays and Fridays
they trekked to Koreatown.
They'd shop for a couple of hours,
then they'd have tea
at Lee's Neighbourhood Market.
They alternated paying.
lt was Sun Porter's turn, by the way.
Not exactly groundbreaking
police work there.
- She's not done yet, McGee.
- Thank you, Gibbs.
Within the last month, all three of them
received regular phone calls
from a pay phone located just outside
Lee's Neighbourhood Market.
lt is owned and operated
by Lee Sung.
He sells Korean delicacies,
fruits and vegetables
and those cute little anime figurines
with the funny faces.
Oh, l love those.
He also has a catering business,
Lee's Delights.
lt's authentic Korean food.
Very high end.
All three women have worked
for him as hostesses
and they were scheduled to work
an event for him tomorrow afternoon.
- How do you know?
- Because.
Lee's Sung e-mailed them
the instructions.
lt's a Korean diplomatic event
at the Pacific Rim Society.
Tell me l didn't just smack McGee
for no good reason.
You didn't smack McGee
Last night, Yoon Dawson
used her cell phone
to call the pay phone
outside Lee's Market.
Two hours later...she's missing.
Why is this important?
Because someone is still using
her cell phone to call that pay phone.
- Can we get a fix on the phone?
- Negatory, McGee.
l know it's somewhere in Annandale,
Virginia, but they turn it off
before l can get an exact location.
The last phone call was an hour ago.
McGee, l want a tap
on that damn pay phone.
Abby, l wanna know who answers it.
That's good work, Abs.
What was that for?
For mocking my groundbreaking
police work.
l was not mocking you--
Won't happen again.
Damn, l can't believe this.
l don't really like waiting
here either, Tony.
No, Nick and Jessica broke up.
l'm always the last to know.
Hey, DiNozzo.
- Shut up.
- Shutting up, boss.
Hey, probie, you getting this?
Yeah, got it, Tony.
lt's Yoon Dawson's
cell phone again.
l want a location, McGee.
Whoever it is, they disabled
the onboard GPS chip.
We'll have to do this
the old-fashioned way.
Just take a moment to get a bead on
the cell phone grid it's interfacing with.
We got someone headed
to the phone, boss.
- You want us to take him down now?
- Negative.
Wait until we trace the call.
Okay, l've got
the cell phone grid located.
lt's coming from this neighbourhood.
Somewhere on this street.
You copy that, DiNozzo?
Well, we're scanning for targets now.
There are a lot of possibles.
lf you don't respond,
l'm gonna hang up.
Don't, l have information for you.
Wool cap, head down,
heading towards the pay phone.
Got him.
Drop your weapon.
Federal agents, move!
lt's Yoon Dawson, boss.
She's rabitting.
We're cutting her off, DiNozzo.
l know she didn't pass us.
Well, where the hell did she go?
lt's like she disappeared.
She didn't disappear.
lt's her hat.
She climbed her way out.
lf l am here, l answer the pay phone,
Agent McGee.
Many people in this community
are poor.
Can't afford phone service,
so l take messages for them.
You see, it helps them
and it is good for my business
when they come to pick up.
Boss, did you find her?
Yeah, McGee.
She's hiding in my coffee cup.
We didn't find her.
Just give us one second, please.
Has he calmed down yet?
Well, he's a little shaky
but l think he's ready to talk.
Min and Sun.
They are dead?
lt's my fault.
l take responsibility.
l try to help people new
to this country.
Find jobs for them,
get them training, classes.
Sometimes even loan money.
You hired all three of them
to work for your catering company?
l did.
l would notice when Yoon was tired,
her accent would change.
Sometimes she would use words not
common in my country since the war.
Yoon-Sook Dawson
wasn't South Korean.
l began to believe
that she was from the North.
Perhaps a spy?
Why didn't you go to the police?
Well, l couldn't be sure.
What if l was wrong?
l asked Min and Sun to find out
where she grew up,
what schools she go to.
Then l check her answers
and try to locate relatives
from Korea.
- Nothing.
- Who else knew
- you were checking up on her?
- Min Crane, Sun Porter and myself.
She was trying to protect her cover?
She failed.
We're taking you
into protective custody, Mr. Sung.
No.
l will not hide.
- Mr. Sung, she could come back.
- Let her.
l am ready this time.
l won't stop living my life
because of people like her.
- Sir, l really don't think that this--
- Mr. Sung.
Thank you for your help.
lf you think of anything else,
give me a call.
Yes, l will.
And please thank your agents for me.
Boss, you're not really
gonna let him just--
McGee, you know the FBl
does not exist only to piss me off.
Sometimes they can actually
be useful.
Hey, Fornell.
l got one right up
your jurisdiction.
Like my father always said,
''Be careful who you marry, Anthony.
She may end up
being a homicidal maniac.''
- Your father actually said that to you?
- No, but l'm sure he thought it.
Probably he knew
your taste in women.
Abby's got active taps
on Sergeant Dawson's cell,
home and work phones, boss.
- lf she calls her husband, we'll know.
- She won't.
The FBl team shadowing Mr. Sung
is tied directly into MTAC.
They're last report had him
loading up a catering truck for a job.
No sign of Yoon Dawson yet.
lt's highly doubtful she'd make
another attempt on his life.
We've got four agents providing
surveillance on Dawson's house.
She definitely won't be
returning home.
And how do you know this,
Officer David?
Because Yoon Dawson wouldn't.
Now tell us what you'd do.
lf l was Yoon, everything l've done up
to this point was to protect my cover.
l've dealt with the two
possible threats on base and--
lf by ''dealt'' you mean gunning down
two defenceless housewives...
l attempted to deal with the third,
but my cover was blown.
l'm now only left
with a few possibilities.
You rush back to your country?
Or carry out whatever mission l was
assigned before l'm captured or killed.
She's been in the States
for three years.
lf you had a mission,
wouldn't you have carried it out?
Not if l'm a sleeper, McGee.
She could be here for decades
before being activated.
So tell us, Jane Bond,
how do we track you down, huh?
You don't, Tony.
By now l've changed my appearance,
l've replaced my identity
with backup documents
and l've relocated.
Promise?
Okay, so that about wraps it up.
Who's up for lunch?
You might think about this,
l'm gonna pay.
No one's eating until we find
Yoon Dawson.
lt's not that Tony couldn't stand
to lose a little weight
but we'd all starve to death
before that happened.
She's playing it like l would.
She's gone.
There's one difference
between the two of you, Ziva.
You don't have a baby girl.
Most likely part of her cover
or an occupational accident.
- lt's more than that.
- How can you tell?
My gut. Come on.
You're with me. Let's go.
Hey, probie.
Let me ask you a question.
You don't think she was serious about
the whole losing a few pounds thing?
Are you gonna hit me
if l tell you the truth?
No, man. We're buds.
Yeah.
My wife is not a spy, sir.
Her South Korean passport's
a forgery.
lt's not possible, okay?
Yoon loves this country.
She knows more about it than me.
She was trained to,
it's called a honey trap.
Her assignment was to meet
an eligible serviceman,
seduce him and gain access
into this country.
Oh, yeah? Then why was she
trying to convince me
to leave the Marine Corps
and go to college?
Most likely you were not part
of the assignment.
- You were a means to an end.
- Listen. Okay,
l've lived with her for five years.
She's the mother of my child.
l'm telling you, there's no way.
- What's this?
- Your wife.
No, that can't be real.
lt's real.
Min Crane and Sun Porter?
She killed them?
- Oh, my God.
- Has she tried to contact you?
- No.
- She's a foreign agent, Marine.
You lie about this, it's treason.
She hasn't. She hasn't tried
to contact me, sir.
Okay, we think she might.
lf she does and you confront her,
she will most likely kill you.
l just can't believe this.
Go ahead.
- Hello?
- lt's me, James.
Yoon, what the hell is going on?
NClS is here.
- They're telling me all sorts of things.
- Don't speak.
Just listen to me, okay?
You need to come home now.
lt's too late for that.
l've done things.
- Terrible things.
- l don't care, all right?
Tell me where you are
and l'll come and get you.
There's one more thing
that l need to do.
l don't have a choice.
- l never had a choice.
- Just tell me why.
- Please, sweetheart.
- No matter what they say,
what they tell you about me,
know that l loved you
with all my heart.
That it was for real.
And tell Rebecca--
Tell her Mommy is sorry for this.
All of it.
This is insane.
Yoon, you can't do--
l love you both so much,
more than you can imagine
but l can't let it happen.
Yoon, don't. Yoon, don't hang up.
l got her, Tony. She's at a pay phone
in Annandale, Virginia.
The corner of Raven Road
and Lancaster Drive.
- Way to go, Abs.
- Kind of a weird place to be hiding out.
There's nothing there
except country clubs.
Lee Sung's catering job?
The Pacific Rim Society.
lt's in Annandale!
Either that's a coincidence or she
really, really wants to kill this guy.
- l don't believe in coincidence.
- ''l don't believe in coincidence.''
No. No, Yoon.
Where is it, Lee Sung?
Have you no honour left, woman?
More than you.
Scream and l kill you.
Found out why the FBl
isn't responding, boss.
- She's definitely here.
- Keep looking, DiNozzo.
l'm right behind you.
l will kill you
if you don't answer this time.
Where?
ln the truck.
Drop the weapon.
There's a bomb set
to go off in this building.
lf you kill me now, we all die.
Put your weapon down.
l was a North Korean operative.
We kind of figured that part out
on our own.
The part that you don't know
is that my cell included Sun Porter,
- Min Crane and this man.
- She's lying.
l swear on the life of my daughter
that l'm trying to prevent this attack.
And l swear if you don't release
your weapon, l will kill you.
The bomb is in his truck.
Please, we may
only have minutes left.
- Now do you believe me?
- Can you disarm it?
lf l had a couple of days,
maybe. You?
l could try.
But l suggest not standing within
five miles of here while l attempt it.
- l can.
- She put it there.
She's trying to kill us all.
They're evacuating the building, boss.
And the--
- That's a really big bomb.
- You think, DiNozzo?
l didn't kill them to maintain my cover,
Agent Gibbs.
l did it to keep my family.
- l failed.
- She's a North Korean spy.
Not anymore.
At least let me prevent this.
McGee, get Sung out of here.
- Get the cuffs off her.
- Gibbs.
lt's not a debate, Officer David. Go.
Go on. Get out of here.
All of you.
Get a clear distance away.
l'll handle it from here.
l don't care
how hard you whack me, boss.
- l'm not going anywhere.
- Nor am l.
lf we survive this,
you're both fired.
lt's supposed to do that, right?
lt's done.
The bomb is no longer armed.
So what happens now, sir?
The FBl will take her
into custody, sergeant.
And then prison?
Your wife is an agent
of a hostile power.
lt all depends what kind
of a deal she can make.
She was also responsible for bringing
down an entire North Korean cell
and saving hundreds of lives,
sergeant.
l'm sure that will be taken into
consideration. Right, Officer David?
Yes, of course.
Her knowledge of the inner workings
of North Korean lntelligence
should proved to be invaluable.
Guys, give her a minute.
l'm
so sorry.
l was trying to do the right thing.
Everything you said to me
on the phone,
l believe in you.
l'll always believe it,
no matter what happens.
Come here.
lt's okay.
- l'm so sorry.
- l know.
Let's go.
Tony,
Ziva, what happened back there
with the bomb,
- l want you both to know--
- You don't have to say it, boss.
We know how you feel about us.
Gibbs, we're a team.
That's what we do.
l was going to say,
if either one of you two wing nuts
ever disobey a direct order again,
l'll kill you myself.
That's our boss.