Sorry, Caitlin.
Oh, Caitlin.
l am so sorry.
Why me, Gibbs?
Wasn't stopping
one bullet enough for you?
Why did l have to take two?
l don't know.
You don't know?
Come on, Gibbs,
what's that famous gut tell you?
Why did l die instead of you?
Found Ari's sniper's nest, boss.
Roof of an abandoned
office building to the east.
Didn't police his brass.
They're Lapua .308s.
l didn't mean
that you couldn't see that, boss.
l can't without my glasses.
Lapua's match-grade sniper ammo.
You guys find any bullets?
None that match the casings.
l left three guys on the roof
searching.
McGee and l
will go back to the roof, boss.
Tony, you're soaking wet.
Go put some dry clothes on.
Ari's rooftop
wasn't much higher than ours.
Rooflines behind us were lower.
No telling how far a full metal jacket
bullet would go,
after killing Kate.
How's he know
it's a full metal jacket?
Didn't you see Kate?
l didn't want to.
Her head was intact.
Oh, so she didn't look bad?
No. No, not at all, Probie.
ln fact, a little mortuary putty
right here
and she'll be good as new.
Of course, she was having a bad hair
day, though, right back here.
A full metal jacket will put
a hole the size of a grapefruit
- right about there.
- Tony.
Please.
Sorry, kid.
Three rounds. Only one hit?
He must've popped off
a couple rounds
when we were weaving
across the roof.
l was standing still
when Kate was shot.
McGee lasered the distance
at nearly 600 metres.
Five seventy-two.
Slight shift in the wind, he misses you.
He hits Kate.
There was no wind.
What are you saying?
He was aiming at Kate?
- You're the one he wants to kill.
- Ari had a thing for Kate.
What are you talking about?
She told me that he was always
coming on to her. ln Autopsy,
when he kidnapped her
and let her go.
She never told me that.
- Gee, what a surprise.
- What?
Don't do that, Tony.
When was this hit, Tim?
When l was pinned down.
Ari have a shot at it?
A car was between the terrorist
and the controller.
There's no way
he could have hit it.
l'm sorry. l should've realized
that it was Ari.
- Why didn't he pop McGee?
- Oh, thanks, Tony.
All l'm saying is you're
a sizeable target. The controller isn't.
- Are you saying l'm fat?
- No.
All right, maybe a little
around the waist, under the chin.
He didn't have an angle on Tim.
You owe that shooter
from the warehouse a thank-you.
He saved your life.
The bullet entered here.
lt could have ricocheted into the car.
l'll-- l'll get on it.
- Abby should be in by now.
- Tony,
see what you can pull off that brass.
l'm going for coffee.
Can l get you boys some?
- No.
- No, thanks.
That's a first.
- He called me Tim.
- He patted my back.
lt's kind of nice.
Nice?
l don't want nice.
He's not Gibbs if he's nice.
You're a mess, girl.
Red eyes. No makeup.
lf ever there was a time
for black lipstick, it's now.
Remember when we first met?
l couldn't believe
you were a forensic scientist.
l thought goths had bats for pets
or vice-versa.
l really liked you, Kate.
A lot.
Don't start that again.
Where are your pigtails?
l love you in pigtails.
That's better.
You were persistent, Abs.
First, the dark lipstick.
Then the black nail polish.
Next thing you know,
l have a tat on my bum.
Oh, God. Ducky's gonna see it.
l'm dead and l'm embarrassed.
Abby.
Hey, Tony.
Are you okay?
l will be as soon as
l tie up my pigtails.
There.
What can l do for you?
- What?
- You're weirder than Gibbs.
How so?
He's being nice.
Gibbs is always nice.
To you and Ducky, maybe.
Me, he growls at
and smacks on the head.
Which makes you feel wanted.
Yeah.
What do you got for me?
.308 casings from Ari's sniper's nest.
You would have to give me
the most popular calibre in the world.
Well, hey, l just found them.
Can you tell what weapon he used?
- A .308.
- What model .308?
- You don't know?
- Would l be asking?
- Well, how am l supposed to know?
- Because you're the firearms expert.
That l am.
And when l'm done,
l will tell you the propellant, the primer,
the percentage of nickel and copper
in the brass,
whether or not all three rounds
were fired from the same weapon
which you assume,
but l can prove or disprove.
l will tell you
who manufactured the ammo,
the batch number
and, perhaps, where it was sold.
l will also,
with some degree of accuracy,
tell you if it was fired
from a lever-action,
a bolt-action, a semi-automatic
or an automatic weapon.
However, there is no way in hell
l could tell you
which of the 87 different .308 models
fired those rounds.
The rounds are Lapua.
What?
Lapua made the ammo.
Logo's on the rim.
Tony, l'm gonna miss her.
Me too.
- You hit?
- No.
- You're heavy.
- Sorry.
No wonder you're so heavy.
Tony, you're all muscle.
Abby:
Packing a nice booty too.
Hey, is this how you deal
with getting shot at?
- l don't know. lt's my first time.
- Abby.
Boss, down. We're taking fire.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Close off Anacostia Park
between the bridges.
- Tell Metro cops it's a crime scene.
- Okay, right.
What if he has a night-vision scope?
That's a good point, boss.
l will get you bullet-proof glass.
- There's no such thing, Gibbs.
- Okay, bullet-resistant glass.
Ari didn't shoot at you
and hit Kate by mistake, did he?
He's after me now.
l was walking by that window
when he fired.
You're just saying that
to make me feel safe.
l'll keep you safe, Abby.
l promise.
l appreciate your keeping me covered
in front of the others.
Especially Tony.
Yes, l know how modest you are.
Were.
l'm dead now, Ducky.
Shouldn't be.
l could have killed Ari right here.
ln Autopsy.
Why did you hesitate?
His eyes.
There was something in his eyes
that made me not wanna kill him.
His eyes were ice to me.
Ari fired into Abby's lab.
Good Lord.
lt had to come from across the river
in Anacostia Park.
Was Abigail hurt?
No, she's a little shook up.
Tony's with her.
ln the lab?
ln the squad room
writing up an incident report.
You should have brought in
another M.E., Duck.
Couldn't.
Not for Caitlin.
l've lost men in combat.
You hope you won't.
You know you will.
- This is different.
- But it shouldn't be.
Kate was an agent.
She knew she had to lay her life
on the line.
But you're right.
lt's different.
Well, you just said it.
You've lost men.
Have you ever lost a woman?
Let's face it, Jethro, you and l
are a couple of old chauvinists.
Women will never be equal in our eyes
until they're equal in death.
Why, Ducky?
Why Kate? Why not me?
- Well, maybe he meant to hit you.
- No.
No, him sniping Abby
means he's after my people.
Women first.
Then he's torturing you.
One has to wonder
what made him such a sadist.
l don't give a damn.
l just wanna kill the bastard.
Hey, McGee, take a look at this.
l think it's a .308.
Stop staring at my butt
and get me an evidence jar.
Drop it.
Oh, l found another one.
Boss, we found a .308 slug.
Two. They were plugged
in the trunk.
These fired by the dirtbag
in the warehouse?
Yes. Those l found in the right side
of the car. Nine mil slugs.
Ari missed with his first shot.
Hit the controller with the second.
Where were you
before you took cover?
Right here.
Tony's right.
You do owe that terrorist a thank-you.
He didn't police his brass again.
Metro P.D. found a .308 casing
in the park next to tyre tracks.
- And?
- Nothing.
l was waiting for you to tell me to
tell them to bring the evidence.
l have to tell you that, DiNozzo?
You always do.
- Tell Metro P.D. to--
- Already did, boss.
Oh, and by the way, the director
wants to see you up in MTAC.
Why are you baiting Gibbs?
l'm trying to get him
to stop being nice.
l like him nice.
Signal is strong.
We have a solid channel.
Distributing the infrared--
What do you have?
Brass from Ari's sniper's nest.
Three bullets.
Tyre tracks in Anacostia Park
from where he fired a shot
across the river into our forensics lab.
Unusual for a sniper not to police his
brass, isn't it?
- Yes, sir.
- l've received calls
from every director l know promising
to hunt down this sniper
as if he'd killed one of their own.
FBl might be the most help.
Ari Haswari is their mole.
l endorsed your recommendation
to award the Presidential Medal
of Freedom to Special Agent Todd.
- Thank you, sir.
- According to your after-action report,
no one actually saw the sniper
who killed Agent Todd.
Ari was on a rooftop
600 metres away.
- Extraordinary shot.
- No, sir. Not really.
- You were a sniper with the Corps?
- Two tours.
Vietnam?
l'm not that old, sir.
Panama and Desert Storm.
- l thought you were older.
- Target vehicle approaching.
We have a hard lock.
Target confirmed. Engage.
Weapon free.
Good lock. On target.
Well done.
Good job, everyone.
Where was l?
Avoiding using Ari's name and the word
''sniper'' in the same sentence, sir.
Your anger is understandable, Jethro.
You lost an agent.
- You want payback.
- Don't you, sir?
lt's a passion l can't afford.
Do you honestly think it wasn't Ari?
No. But there are those who do.
Those who ran him.
Those who thought they had
the holy grail of moles.
Those people covering their asses
right now.
Make sure you cover yours
when you bring him in.
Won't be a problem, sir.
l won't be bringing him in.
Anyway, you're not my problem
anymore, Jethro.
You firing me, sir?
l've been offered a deputy director's
position at Homeland Security.
You'd leave NClS, sir?
Well, the agency could use
some younger blood.
Well, who'll be replacing you,
sir?
Not me.
Much as l like you, Jethro,
l would not shoot NClS in the head.
He's your problem now, director.
Hello, Jethro.
Should we skip the
''you haven't changed a bit'' bull?
Why start lying
to each other now, Jen?
Any problem taking orders from me?
As director or as a woman?
Either.
lt was six years ago.
The past won't be a problem.
You were a damn good agent
especially undercover.
Jethro.
Madam Director.
You have no physical evidence
linking Ari to the shootings.
No wonder agencies
here and abroad have doubts.
Bastard killed one of my people.
He's trying to kill more.
l'll tell you something else. No suit with
a tight sphincter is getting in my way,
and that includes you, Jen.
Special Agent Gibbs.
On the job,
it is Director Shepard or ma'am.
Okay. What about off the job?
There won't be any ''off the job,''
Agent Gibbs.
That's too bad.
l missed you, Jen.
Don't make this difficult, Jethro.
Fair enough. lt won't happen again.
Director.
We can continue
this conversation in private.
l've gotta change my clothes.
We can talk in my car.
- Gibbs.
- Hey, l got a dead agent
and a sniper on the loose.
l do not have 1 0 minutes to spare.
Tony, where are we?
McGee and Abby
are working firearms analysis.
- l'm matching tyre tracks to vehicles.
- No one is to leave the building.
McGee's on protection detail
with Abby. l'll be back in an hour.
Your mother should have washed
your mind out with soap.
Gibbs leaves with a woman
and your only thought is: nooner.
Was not.
Was too.
l've always known
what you were thinking, Tony.
What?
What are you up to?
Tony, l just died
and you're having a sexual fantasy?
Can't help it.
DiNozzo.
Sometimes
l used to picture you naked.
l'll call you back.
Hi.
l was just--
Having phone sex?
Phone sex? No.
- Charades.
- Charades?
- Like:
-You've played.
Never on the telephone.
Yeah.
My partner and l were coming up
with quotes for Saturday night.
You play charades
on Saturday night?
To kill time before l go clubbing.
Who are you?
Ziva David.
Mossad.
You're lsraeli?
Very good.
The way you made that connection.
Mossad, lsraeli.
What can l do for you, Ms. David?
Nothing.
l'm here to see Special Agent Gibbs.
How do you know l'm not Gibbs?
- Gibbs.
- He'll be back in an hour.
Are you sure l can't help you?
l don't think so.
We got off to a bad start.
l'm Special Agent Tony DiNozzo.
l wasn't playing charades.
l was remembering my partner.
- Naked?
- No.
Yes. l--
l was just--
Look, l'm not the only man
who does it.
Oh, women do it too.
With handsome men.
And even an occasional woman.
Now you're teasing me.
Didn't your partner tease you?
Not about sex.
Kate was kind of puritanical.
- Sorry.
- Well, it didn't matter.
l wasn't interested in her.
We were partners.
She wasn't attractive?
She was, but not to me.
Then why did you imagine her
naked?
Miss David, you can sit there
and slouch provocatively for an hour
if you'd like,
or you could tell me what you need
and maybe l can help.
You can't help because l'm here
to stop Special Agent Gibbs
from killing a Mossad officer.
Ari Haswari?
Yes.
l'd wish you luck,
but l want the bastard dead too.
ls this the same boat
you were building six years ago?
- Nope.
- What happened to it?
- l burned her.
- Why would you--?
You named it after an ex-wife.
Let's go.
- Which one?
- You know damn well which one.
- Why didn't you change the name?
- Because it wouldn't matter.
Every time l went out on her,
l'd think of Diane.
You could have sold it.
And watched some other guy
sail off on her?
You didn't care
who sailed off on Diane.
Leroy Jethro Gibbs,
you are a strange man.
Me.
You were a good agent, Jen.
- Were?
- Yeah.
Director's job is pure politics.
l'm good at politics.
NClS needs someone who can shake
the money tree on the Hill
and work with sister agencies.
Wait, you won't call a boat a ''she,''
but it's ''sister agencies?''
l'm a schizoid libber.
lt comes from working
with chauvinists like you.
l can't believe you would give up
field work for rubber chicken dinners.
l don't think they serve
that dish at Palena.
- Never heard of it.
- Why would you? lt isn't takeout.
So which of the tight sphincters
is taking you out to dinner?
Please tell me it's not Fornell.
CBS Early Show.
They want background
before l go on TV.
Jen. Jen, you can't do that.
Excuse me?
Ari is a chauvinist.
He is taking out the women
l work with before me.
Jethro.
People who should know
don't believe Ari Haswari is the sniper.
And you haven't provided any evidence
to prove them wrong.
Have you ever doubted me?
Professionally? Never.
Why are you doubting me now?
l have to establish a working
relationship with these people.
Who are you gonna side with, Jen?
Them or me.
Give me a tough question.
What is with this music?
l'm playing it out of respect for Kate.
l thought
you were from New Orleans.
- So?
- Well, don't they play jazz at funerals?
Coming from the cemetery
after the body has been buried.
On the way to the cemetery,
we play a dirge.
- Do you know what a dirge is, Timmy?
- Creepy music?
Go back to the squad room
and let me do my job.
l can't.
Why?
Gibbs-- Gibbs told me
to watch over you.
That is so sweet.
- You're from a wealthy family.
- Really?
Born and raised on the East Coast.
New England boarding school.
Spent some time in the Midwest.
And Philadelphia.
How would you know that?
Shalom, Jen.
Shalom.
Did l miss it?
- Yes, you did, but we didn't.
- You first.
Ziva David, Mossad.
She's here to stop you
from whacking Ari. Yours?
Director Jenny Shepard.
Same mission.
Which agency?
Ours.
Yeah?
Special Agent Gibbs.
Ziva David, Mossad.
Ziva.
Director Shepard
has spoken often of you.
- Really?
- Ziva and l worked antiterrorist ops
since 9/1 1 .
You saw one today in MTAC.
That was yours?
l only acquired the intel.
Excuse me.
Yes, l really am
the new NClS director.
Yeah.
Good to have you back, boss.
Shalom.
Miss David, whose balls get cut off
if Ari is not a Mossad mole,
but a terrorist?
Mine, l suppose.
Since l'm his control officer.
They promote control officers
young in Mossad.
Have to. The good ones are dead
at your age.
Do you know
how l located Ari's terrorist cell?
GPS fix off
his encrypted cell phone.
He wanted you to know
the terrorists' location,
so you could stop the missile
instead of him,
which would've blown his cover.
Only an NSA satellite
can GPS an encrypted phone.
Ari didn't know l had that asset.
You give him less credit
than he gives you.
Who hung up first? You or him?
Ari knows a fix
takes only 1 9 seconds.
When Sharon visited Bush, Ari's
Hamas cell kidnapped Agent Todd.
Why didn't he kill her instead of freeing
her to warn the Secret Service?
Why don't you arrange
a meet and he can tell me?
Ari Haswari is a Mossad
operative undercover in Hamas.
He hasn't turned on us or you.
He didn't kill Agent Todd.
Gibbs, even if you're right,
we owe them proof.
That's all we ask.
- Don't kill the wrong man.
- Like Mossad did in Norway?
That mistake cost us dearly.
Not as dearly
as the Palestinian waiter you killed.
Ziva, assure your deputy director that
even though Ari Haswari is a suspect,
no action will be taken
unless we have evidentiary proof.
Proof before action.
You were my sweet superhero,
Kate.
You're a naughty boy, Timmy.
Oh, my God. l'm becoming Tony.
Wow, what?
l-- l--
Stop ''ah-uming,'' McGee. Spit it out.
l-- l was thinking about Kate.
Me too.
l kind of still feel like she's here,
you know?
l want you on Ziva's ass.
She's not really my type, boss.
- To tail her.
- l knew that.
She's been in contact with Ari.
That's the only way she could know
l hung up on him.
- l don't want you to get pissed--
- l thought you wanted me pissed?
l did. lt was kind of weird
when you were being nice.
Not that you're not nice. l mean--
Will you spit it out, DiNozzo?
What if Ziva's right
and Ari knew you'd trace the call?
Maybe he wasn't the sniper.
She is right.
Ari wanted me
to raid the warehouse.
He set me up.
And it cost Kate her life.
ls he a mole or a terrorist?
Whatever works to play his game.
lf Ziva leads me to Ari?
Shadow him and call me.
- So you can bring him in?
- Yeah. So l can bring him in
to Autopsy.
The FBl database
gave me six weapons
whose rifling patterns
fit the bullets you recovered.
l've been able to eliminate
all but three.
Two SWAT weapons,
the Tango 51 and Bravo 51 .
- And this--
- My old friend.
A Marine M40A1 sniper rifle.
lt looks sweet
the way you hold that, boss.
Sweet?
Yeah. lt's an expression that means--
Yeah, l know what it means,
McGee.
You think Ari looked sweet
when he shot Kate?
Of course not, boss.
My vote is for the Tango
or Bravo 51 s.
What do you think, Gibbs?
Your test rounds
show more gouging than Ari's.
He was hand loading
and moly coating.
You are so good.
- ''Moly coating''?
- Yeah.
Molybdenum disulfide.
lt's a lubricant.
lt decreases barrel wear
and increases accuracy.
McGee, run a trace
on Tango and Bravo 51 sales.
Last six weeks. Tri-state area.
- Check the Bravo first.
- On it, boss.
Any prints on the brass?
No.
ls your gut telling you something?
Yeah. l need coffee.
No, Gibbs. Come on.
This isn't just another investigation.
Todd was your agent,
but Kate was my friend.
So can you stop it
with the John Wayne stare
- and tell me what your gut says?
- What don't l believe in, Abby?
UFOs, mystics, coincidence,
saying you're sorry, excuses.
l could go on all night.
As a Marine sniper, l used
hand-loaded Lapua .308 boat-tail
full metal jacket,
moly-coated bullets.
Gibbs.
You know what a sniper calls
a Bravo 51 ?
No.
A Kate.
My shoulder hurts
when it rains, too, Gerald.
Good night, Kate.
Autopsy.
Hello, Dr. Mallard.
Gerald.
How are you, my dear fellow?
l've been better.
- Oh, what's wrong?
- He's having flashbacks.
- Well, who are you?
- Oh, l'm hurt.
You don't recognise my voice?
You bastard.
You do remember me.
lf you harm Gerald--
l have no intention
of harming Gerald.
l think one ruined shoulder
is enough.
lt certainly is for me.
What do you want?
A professional courtesy,
one doctor to another.
Yes, well, l'd be most willing
to provide a free autopsy.
Dr. Mallard,
l want to prove l didn't kill Caitlin.
By taking Gerald hostage?
Gerald is free to go if you'll listen
- to my side of this tragedy.
- l'm listening.
lt's a long story and l'd hate
to have somebody trace this call.
Well, no one is here but me.
And Caitlin.
lt must have been
a difficult autopsy for you.
l'm truly sorry, doctor.
Will you get on with it?
Will you meet me alone?
What happens to Gerald?
Come alone
and you can exchange places.
Doctor, don't come. He'll kill you.
Learn to trust, Gerald.
l may have shot you in the shoulder.
But l've never lied to you. Doctor?
You have my word.
Thank you.
Re-evaluating your convictions?
How many times did you tell me there's
no such thing as a coincidence?
Jethro?
l know it's been a difficult day
for both of us.
That's what my Dl used to say.
Never believed him.
Jen...
Are you going to dinner with CBS?
l am.
Don't do that interview.
Please.
l'll see if l can delay it a few days.
Good.
Good night, Jethro.
Night.
Ducky. How nice to see you again.
And you. Congratulations.
- Going home?
- Yes.
Ducky.
So are you back at work, Gerald?
Next week.
l've always found
that work is the best--
A vintage Morgan.
How Ducky.
Flash your lights.
Roll down your window.
Now wait in the good doctor's car
while we talk.