Previously on "In Treatment"...
i really don't remember what happened.
I was on my bicycle
And a car ran into me and--
What did they tell you afterwards?
That i flew my bike right into the street.
They told me that i needed
the opinion of a psychiatrist
Because
the insurance company of the car that hit me
Has a problem with my injuries.
How do you get on with your dad?
|| He's the only person in this world
Who truly loves me.
The only one except Cy.
Who's Cy?
This is Cy.
He's my coach.
Hello?
Sophie
Stop the car.
Calm down.
I wanna get out!
- Did you hear what i said?
- Just calm down.
I wanna walk. - It's pouring.
I don't care if it's raining.
I wanna walk!
No,
it's too far to walk. - Fine!
Sophie.
Aare you-- - I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Cy says you have to experience the rain, so,
Ii've experienced it.
I'll get you some dry clothes.
I'm fine.
Really?
Are you sure you wouldn't be more comfortable if--
Wait a second.
Here we go.
- Are they your daughter's?
Did you ask her if it was okay?
No, but i'm sure she won't mind.
I'll put yours in the dryer
And they'll be ready by the end of the session.
Well, you'll have to help me.
I haven't got dressed on my own
since my accident.
Are you gonna help me here or not?
Did you ever hear of an umbrella,
kiddo? My goodness.
Sweetheart, look at you.
You're just all skin and bones, aren't you?
Okay, i will have these dry for you
Before you leave.
How on earth do you manage
with two broken arms?
I don't.
What, one arm wasn't enough for you, huh?
Okay.
You know, i broke my arm
when i was 12 and i was roller-Skating.
And the best thing about it
was that i got to whack my little brother
In theead with my cast when he was bugging me,
Which was pretty much all the time.
All right, let's do your shoes.
|| She's cool.
- Kate? - Yeah.
She's awesome.
True.
You could learn a lot from your wife
About how to talk to people.
Wish i could take her with me to the gym.
She could tell everyone the truth to their faces.
Who do you want her to tell the truth to?
Did you write my evaluation?
No.
Did you?
What the fuck?!
Why didn't you?
That's why i'm here.
That's all i need from you,
That stupid evaluation.
Actually, i don't think i know you
quite well enough
Yet, Sophie.
So why didn't you write yours?
Well, i tried
With my dad, but,
But he's too busy with his exhibition.
He's an artist? - A photographer.
He hates the word "artist."
He always has his exhibitions at home
Because he's against galleries.
Anyway,
he said it was totally unprofessional
For me to write my own evaluation
And that you sound like a quack.
Are you a quack?
No, i am not a quack.
I promise.
And then i tried to write it with my mom.
That didn't work--
Obviously.
Why do you say obviously?
Because she's a total tool
and a retard.
A tool and a retard?
Yeah.
We got in a fight.
And i was like,
"i so do not need this right now."
So i left.
I went to this apartment near the gym
Where the foreign girls stay.
I told them my parents were going out of town, so,
they let me crash there.
And then i tried to get Cy
to help me write it,
But he's too busy getting everyone
ready to leave for training camp, so,
So i didn't do it.
So why did you and your mom get into a fight
Trying to write the evaluation together?
She actually wanted to write it for me.
And i was like, "no, mom, i can do it myself."
And she was like, "we'll be here
until the next olympics."
And i was like, "bite me."
- So i left.
So you didn't want her to write it.
You just
wanted her to help you,
- What, phrase it? - It doesn't matter.
We got in a fight, for a change.
But this time, Sophie,
You left home.
So?
- Have you done that before?
- No.
So something was different
about this particular fight.
What do yothink it was that was different?
Did you-- Did you come from home
Or did you come from the gym today?
- The gym. - Gym-- Is that far away?
That's why i was late.
Sophie,
Before you arrived, i, uh--
I got a phone call, and, um,
i heard you asking somebody
To let you out of the car.
well, i--
I tried to call you
to tell you i was on my way,
But, um, then i figured
That we were like five minutes away, so...
i thought i hung up
before the call went through.
Was that your father?
You could've hung up, you know?
Or do you always eavesdrop
on other people's conversations?
Sophie, if you were my patient,
i'd ask if you thought
It was a coincidence that i
overheard that conversation.
But i'm not your patient.
I wouldn't see a therapist
Who i thought was an eavesdropper.
I'd be out of here.
So did your dad bring you in?
I told you, i had a fight with him!
I thought you said the fight was with your mom.
It's really none of your business
who i came here with.
Earlier on you said that you'd like
Kate to go to the gym with you.
What would you like Kate to,
to tell the girls at the gym?
Your daughter's clothes are gross.
- Why is that funny?
Well, why are they gross?
They're hideous.
Okay.
I'm really not getting my
evaluation today, am i?
This is stupid.
I should go. Are my clothes dry yet?
I wouldn't think so.
Well, can you check?
And call Kate, because i need her
to help me put them back on.
You people are such tools.
I can't believe you get paid for this.
Why didn't you tell me before
that you heard my conversation?
I was waiting for you to tell me.
So now i'm a liar too?
I di't say you were a liar, Sophie.
It's what you're thinking.
Why do you need Kate to go to the gym with you?
I don't need her to.
Can i ask you something?
How do you get along with the girls at the
at the gym?
They're assholes, okay?
All of them.
The whole place, it reeks of hypocrisy.
Did you know, like, every girl there is
a Mia or an Anna except me?
They know it.
They just don't do anything about it.
- They encourage it.
These girls, Anna and Mia,
Are they friends of yours?
You don't know these girls?
They're fun girls, especially Anna.
Rexic?
Anorexic.
Okay. And Mia, bulimia?
You're sharp as a tack.
Thank you.
So the girls at the gym
Are anorexic or bulimic
except for you?
You can't keep your weight down otherwise.
And if you're not skinny you can't compete, so,
So you have no choice, you have to.
But who says you can't compete?
Cy and Regina.
Regina is our physical trainer.
All the girls follow Cy around
like little groupie sluts.
"Cy, was that okay?"
"Cy, can you show me how to do that move?"
"Cy, i'm about to fall. Quick,
put your hands between my legs."
But not Regina
'Cause she's russian.
So her bullshit detector is like nuclear.
And at the end of the day
Cy and Regina decide everhing--
Who competes,
who's gained weight and can't compete.
After my accident,
Karen Scott and Audrey England
came to visit me.
They had these pathetic looks on their faces, like,
Like they felt my pain.
But i knew they were happy.
I would have been happy if something
had happened to one of them
Right before the olympic tryouts.
Honestly,
If it was me,
I would have done what Shirley did.
She didn't even come.
Me and her, we're like the best
ones there by far.
It was like she was saying,
"drop dead for all i care.
Just get out of my face."
At least that's honest.
So they're leaving tomorrow
For training camp in California
And i have nowhere to go.
They won't let me stay
at the apartment by myself.
They promised Cy i could go,
Even though i can't train.
And now he says they've changed their minds.
- Who's they? - The sponsors--
The money people.
Anyway,
I picked a fight with him.
That's what you heard on the phone.
It wasn't his fault.
Why is it so important for you
to go with them?
To the camp?
Everyone will be there.
You mean, Karen, Audrey and Shirley?
But-- But you said you can't stand them.
You said you don't even like them.
And you can't train anyway, so,
i don't understand why
it's so important to you.
It's not important.
But i was looking forward to it.
Sounds like, um...
you and Cy are, uh--
- You're very close. - No.
Why? Can you tell that over the phone?
You said he wanted to take you to camp
Despite the fact that you had an injury, and,
didn't he-- Didn't he drive you here?
It was on his way.
He wants me to come to the camp
to at least watch the training
So i don't lose focus.
But no.
He couldn't make them pay for Darlene either.
- Darlene? - Cy's wife.
She has to pay her own way and Dana's too.
Dana is the little girl you used to babysit?
Why did you stop?
Who told you i stopped?
Did i tell you that last week?
You have good memory for an old fart.
Thank you.
So why did you stop?
They didn't need me anymore.
Dana used to have all these
breathing problems, but,
then she had this surgery
and they got better, and,
And darlene came back from Wisconsin
Where she was like
learning to process her own
cheese or something, so,
So they didn't need me.
Did you work there for a long time?
No.
Sort of.
And Dana must have become very fond of you.
Did she become attached to you?
Yeah.
She's the cutest.
She hasn't stopped talking
about me since i left.
She said she doesn't want to go to California
If i'm not going to be there.
They told her that i wouldn't
be able to babysit her anymore
'Cause i'd had this accident.
But see, i'd already told her before
That i couldn't keep living with them
once her mom came home.
- I waed to prepare her, you know?
But they didn't tell me
what they were telling her, so,
the whole lie became mixed up in her head.
- What?
You look scared all of a sudden.
I look scared?
Like you're looking at a psycho
or something.
I was just remembering that
the last time you were here you put your--
Your casts together. Do you you remember?
And you said,
"this is Cy."
Yeah, the mermaid that he drew.
You said that when Darlene came home
You knew you couldn't keep on living there.
I never said i lived there.
But you told dana you wouldn't
be able to go on living there.
Yeah, because she's a child
But, so it felt to her like i lived there.
It was just,
'Cause she'd go to school and,
come back and i'd be there, and,
you know, she got used to me being around.
So
even when he was home she'd nt me to stay--
Cook them dinner, do her homework with her.
Sometimes she'd wake up screaming
Because she stopped breathing in her sleep.
Cy told me that.
What the hell is going on here?
What do you mean,
what the hell is going on here?
My dad was right. I'll go to therapy
And i'll end up a psycho
Just like your daughter.
Everyone thinks she's a freak.
Are you trying to hurt me, Sophie? No.
But you should know what people say about her.
She had this thing with this guy
And afterwards
everyone says she'd turned out psycho
'Cause her dad is a shrink.
Shrinks' kids are psycho. Everyone knows that.
Well, maybe that's because--
Because some people are afraid of therapy.
They're afraid of what they might find out.
They're afraid that it might
touch those wounds
That are deep inside them.
I think there are things that...
perhaps...
you feel deep inside,
Sophie, that you'd like to talk about.
I'm fine.
You wanna worry about a little girl?
Worry about your own kid.
Does it bother you that people
talk about my daughter?
Why would it bother me?
Because maybe you know what it feels like.
- Maybe i don't. - We were talking
about your coach
And then suddenly
you brought up the story of my daughter.
Yeah, because i thought you should know.
Are there people who say things
about you, Sophie?
At the gym maybe?
You know, Sophie, sometimes
when people are jealous
They say things to hurt us
Because they envy us.
Do you think that some
of the girls at the gym might be
jealous of you, and,
how close your relationship is with Cy?
Don't talk to me like i'm a child, please.
Fair enough.
Sophie, i get the feeling that you're afraid
To tell me something that
other people say about you.
Are my clothes dry yet?
Can you go check?
If i won't be getting an evaluation today
I'd at least like dry clothes.
Okay.
Well, i have started to write it.
Can i see what you've got?
I'm, uh-- I'm not quite finished yet.
I'll bet you haven't written a word.
"Sophie's evaluation:
16 years old, a gymnast.
She is an olympic hopeful.
She came in for evaluation
After a near-fatal accident.
During first session appears to be
Very impressive,
sensitive,
Mature for her age,
Very intelligent
And a highly-Independent personality."
I tried to write it...
with my mom but--
We didn't fight. I just said "never mind."
Do you really think those things you wrote?
Absolutely.
They're just generalities at the moment.
It's not enough for a real evaluation.
You know,
This morning i tried to brush
my teeth
like you.
- Like me?
Like--
- How'd it go?
- I couldn't do it.
I just stick it in there.
Why'd you try that?
'Cause i wanted to know how it feels.
How did it feel?
I felt useless,
Like demeaned or something.
I'm homeless.
I have nowhere to go.
What about your dad?
I told you, i had a fight with him.
Not a real fight, but he pissed me off.
He knows how much i wanted
to go to that training camp with them
And he didn't even offer to pay.
I wouldn't have taken his money anyway.
Obviously, the exhibitions are expensive, but--
Why is it so important for you
to go to this camp, Sophie?
It's not important...
anymore.
How do you get along with Cy's wife?
Fine.
I don't wanna talk about t em.
Okay.
When you're ready, we will.
You know, when you walked in here
I thought to myself
Somebody in your life has broken the rules.
And i felt that,
That if i had helped you
change your clothes,
That i would have been doing the same thing.
I felt like you were
testing me.
I felt like you wanted to make sure
That this was a safe place,
That the same things that happen out there
Don't happen in here.
Right when the accident happened...
i don't remember anything, but,
But right afterwards
I remember the whole world was silent.
Not just silent, soundless.
You know, like there had never been
any noise ever,
Not even that hum that you hear
when you're in an empty room.
Nothing.
Even inside the ambulance,
People were talking and it was like--
It was like i'd gone deaf.
I felt relieved.
I thought that i would never have to listen
To anybody ever again.
Sound came back though,
At first from r away.
The E.M.T., she kept saying,
"I have to hear your voice.
I have to hear your voice, sweetheart."
She wanted my parents' phone numbers.
She wanted them to come meet me
when i got to the hospital.
There was no way.
They can't even sit in the
same section at my meets.
I have to wave to two different
spots after my routine.
I look schizo.
I tried to sit up.
I told the emt that i wanted
to see the outside. Why ?
You know, when you see an ambulance
Tearing down the street, you turn and look.
Well, i wanted to see what it was like
Being on the inside looking out.
You know, seeing people's faces
on the sidewalk
Wondering,
"who's in there?
Is she going to be okay?"
I couldn't sit up.
The E.M.T.,
She had this mirror
that she tried to angle
So that i could see out,
But all i could see was myself.
And i remember thinking,
"both arms, Sophie?
Did it have to be both arms, you idiot?"
Our time is up.
Okay.
We'll, um--
We'll take it up there
When you come back next week.
You're n going to training camp
with everyone else in the universe?
I'll go get your clothes
And call Kate.
He didn't offer you a cup of tea even?
Are you su that doesn't hurt?
All right, you,
Arms way up.
Okay.