So, you ever been here before ?
No.
Oh, I don't mean here here.
I mean Baltimore.
Yeah, I've given several lectures
to the Baltimore Homicide Division.
What's wrong with your mouth ?
- I got a tooth situation.
- Well, go to a dentist.
All right, I will if
it doesn't get any better.
- Ow ! Man !
- Are you afraid of the dentist ?
- I'm not afraid.
- Welcome to Balmer.
This is, uh, actually a federal
flood abatement project,
which is why we called you.
K-9 unit was using it
for an exercise,
and one of the cadaver
dogs went berserk.
When they dug up the cement...
No, that's concrete.
Cement is an
ingredient in concrete.
Yeah, that's a real important
distinction to make
at this juncture.
So, what do we got, Bones, huh ?
Do your thing.
Nothing.
Nothing. Nothing ?
No, I can't see enough
of the skull, the tibia, the pubis.
Nothing. Nothing.
Wait a second. Nothing.
Oh, sorry about that.
We drove all the way here so
you could just tell me nothing ?
All right, so what do you,
what do you want to, uh,
get the whole slab
of cement... Concrete.
...concrete, whatever...
shipped back to the Jeffersonian ?
Abso...
Sex ?
The mandible suggests male,
and the tibia suggests
he was between five
six and six feet tall.
Waffle-soled training
shoes and a track suit.
- You know who wears track suits ?
- Athletes ?
No. Huge tubs of lard
or retired people.
And rap stars.
The teeth suggest
early middle age.
So not a retiree.
Uh, calcified holes
with radial fractures
in the left clavicle and
scapula are consistent
with ballistic damage.
- He was shot to death ?
- And stabbed.
But neither killed him.
The wounds healed.
Shot, stabbed, but lived
to die another day ?
Rap star.
There is a small hole
in the back of the cranium.
Get the skull out first,
establish cause of death,
then give Angela something
to work with to ID the guy.
Where is Angela ?
I'm really not good
at this kind of thing.
You know, I don't...
I don't get the significance.
One year ago today,
you buried your mother.
You laid her to rest.
Here.
You're marking the anniversary.
Angela, I simply don't believe
my mother retained
sentience beyond death.
Well, part of you is made up
of your mother, right ?
In a manner of speaking.
So, honor that part of yourself.
Visualize a memory of her.
See what it brings up.
I have very few distinct
memories of my mother.
I'll wait in the car.
Hiya, honey.
I was hoping you might show up.
I don't... I don't
want to talk to you.
We're standing here
in front of your mother's grave.
Obviously, you've come
for some kind of answer.
Maybe I can... provide 'em.
You're a killer.
You burn people.
Yeah, I'd like to report
a sighting of Max Keenan
at Eternal Spring Memorial Gardens.
He's a wanted fugitive.
I love you.
Yes, I'm sure.
Because he's my father.
"Bones" Season 02 Episode 18
... your dad at all before
you called the cops ?
No. Why would I ?
Well, I mean, I haven't
seen my dad in a long time,
and if I had the opportunity
to talk... Ow !
­
Go to a dentist.
Oh, I will if it doesn't
get any better.
Based on decomposition
of the track suit,
Hodgins is estimating a postmortem
interval of two years.
Based on bone deterioration,
I like three years.
Well, what killed him ?
The victim was dead shortly after
this hole was punched
into his skull.
Too small for a projectile.
No radiating stress lines.
A slow entry, a piercing wound.
Like a-a screwdriver ?
Nail gun ? Ice pick ?
Yeah, something along those lines.
Oh. Cold steel to the brain...
would that kill him ?
Depending how far it penetrated.
Yeah, it's Booth.
I need, um, all murders
in which a penetrating wound
to the back of the head figured.
Great. Thanks.
Don't freak out.
Oh !
You broke into my house ?
That is not acceptable.
This, uh,
little device here...
it jams cell phone frequencies.
That is illegal.
Unfortunately, illegal
is what I do best.
I'm not staying.
I just want you to do
something for me.
I want you to take a
look at my rap sheet.
- Why ?
Because I want a chance to talk to you...
actually talk to you...
without you calling
in the 82nd Airborne.
How is reading your police record
going to change my mind ?
Just do it.
I think our victim was killed by Ice Pick.
Angela did a facial
reconstruction of Cement Head.
Concrete Head, you mean.
No, Cement Head...
it's got a nicer ring.
So, I ran it through
IntelPlus and got a match.
William Raymond "Billy Ray"
McKenna. West Virginia.
"Assault, manslaughter, kidnapping,
torture...." This here...
This here is, uh, Hugh Kennedy.
Uh, I think he
killed Cement Head.
Why ?
Well, West Virginia,
likes to use an ice pick
on his victims, plus Ice Pick
and Cement Head were both employed
by a regional crime
boss in West Virginia
named... Gallagher.
Well, what are we
going to call him ?
Gallagher.
But he runs most
of the, uh, prostitutes,
strippers, gambling,
bootlegging, meth,
extortion in West Virginia.
Five years ago, the West Virginia
State Police began pressuring
Gallagher's criminal operation,
making a lot of arrests.
Including Ice Pick and Cement Head.
Cement Head goes to jail.
- Ice Pick ?
- Out on bail, babe.
You say that like
it means something.
Oh, I talked to the officer
in charge, and he said
that Ice Pick wouldn't say anything,
so they punished him
by letting him out
on bail.
How is bail punishment ?
'Cause it makes Gallagher think
that Ice Pick cooperated
with the cops.
You know, it's criminal
psychology, Bones.
You know, you wouldn't get it.
Just read. Just continue
reading there, will you ?
"Half a million dollar bond.
"Kennedy jumped bail.
"Killed in a car accident
while fleeing a Bail
Fugitive Recovery agent."
Bounty Hunter.
"Car burned the remains to ashes."
All they got was a severed leg.
They didn't actually
get Ice Pick's body.
So, are we going to talk
to the bounty hunter ?
No, I am. You're gonna make sure
that that severed leg actually
belonged to Ice Pick.
Well, someone kept the leg ?
The severed leg was
frozen as evidence.
So, you think Ice Pick
might still be alive ?
As a friend of mine
likes to say, "Don't jump to conclusions
until all the evidence is in."
If the facts are in, then
it's not jumping to conclusions,
so I never said that.
I never said that the friend is you, okay ?
Does it have to be completely
thawed for you to examine ?
No. My interest lies
only in the femur.
I need to get some tissue
for DNA testing.
I'm the bounty hunter
you want to talk to.
Veleska Miller.
You want to know about Kennedy's leg ?
Anything you want to tell me
outside the official report,
that's great.
Sure.
How it smelled, his body
cooking over the fire.
Otherwise, I stand by the record.
How'd you find him ?
Tip from someone I know
who provides documents
to fugitives.
Tailed him, he made me, took off.
Boom !
Found his leg about 30
yards from the vehicle.
And you saw him burn ?
Yeah.
Why ?
That's it ?
That's it.
I'm a little disappointed.
I was hoping you'd
keep me here a while,
ask me some dumb-ass
federal questions, check me out.
How's about I buy you
a nice breakfast, huh ?
Guy like you must be going
crazy in the FBI.
What kind of guy
is that, exactly ?
I'm a bounty hunter, sport.
I read people fast, or I die.
You are not standard
government issue.
Take a walk on the wild side.
I have more fun, fewer rules,
and a lot of money.
Yeah.
You make a compelling case.
Booth.
Coroner's report said
Kennedy's leg was severed
in the car accident.
We don't call him Kennedy.
We call him Ice Pick.
Hold on for one second. Sorry.
Yeah. Aah.
Listen, I got the, uh,
bounty hunter here.
She was an eyewitness to the crash.
Saw him incinerated.
Tell Booth that Ice Pick's
femur is sliced cleanly
at 90 degrees.
I can hear you, Bones.
Okay ? It's a speakerphone.
Look, amputation
like that could happen
in a bad wreck, right, Cam ?
Yes.
Well, there are kerf marks.
She's seeing evidence
of a saw, Booth.
Look, I know what
kerf marks are.
Booth should arrest
the bounty hunter.
I can hear you, Bones.
What am I gonna arrest
her for, huh ?
For lying, for perjury.
For aiding in a cover-up.
If she's there with you,
just detain her.
Okay.
Hey, look at that, huh ?
DNA is a match.
West Virginia state troopers
got a DNA sample at
Ice Pick's arrest.
This is definitely his leg.
Was she pretty ?
Ice Pick is a male.
I mean the bounty hunter
who gave Booth the slip.
You know, she didn't get away
because she was pretty.
She was a she ? No, she was a...
Oh...
What's wrong with your mouth ?
I'm guessing the anterior molar
on the left side is infected.
The leg was surgically amputated.
Go to a dentist.
He's afraid of the dentist.
These kerf marks are
consistent with a type
of wire saw used
to remove horns
from heifers. Ah, so...
Ice Pick and this bounty hunter
set up a car accident
with a dummy victim so everyone
stops looking for him.
Two years later
he kills Con... Cement Head.
She hoodwinked you
'cause she was hot.
All right, look, you know what ?
She wasn't hot. In fact,
she looked like a man.
The amputation was probably performed
by a livestock veterinarian.
Hey, Bones, I've got that other
thing you want to discuss.
Oh, let's...
go to my office
so we don't disturb Cam.
Booth ? Yeah ?
Livestock amputation.
That is one tough,
determined old criminal.
Be careful.
You know, I was going
through your father's
crim... Shh !
... criminal record and
he was right about one thing.
You know, he never ended
anyone's life who didn't
have it coming to them.
He's a sociopath.
Well, maybe, but at least
he aimed in the right direction.
- Ow !
- Let me take a look at your tooth.
All right, just...
Go easy. You promise ?
Okay. All right.
Open up. You know,
What ?
In the Old West,
he would have been
considered a hero.
Yeah, well, the Old
was a time of chaos and violence that,
anthropologically speaking,
our country is still Ow !
trying to recover from.
Yeah, I was right. Anterior
molar on the left side,
it's infected.
You know, your father never killed
any hardworking, tax-paying
citizens or honest cops.
Ow ! You still think
that society should forgive him ?
All I'm saying
is if I have an opportunity
to arrest him, I will.
But you know who maybe
should forgive him ?
His daughter.
Oh, look at that.
The small town crime
boss is here.
Let's go have a little
chat with him, shall we ?
Billy Ray McKenna shortly before
he became Cement Head.
I like nicknames.
They are universal
mnemonic devices.
Why are we doing this ?
Don't we know that cause
of death was brain scrambling
due to an ice pick ?
The technical term is "pithing."
And it's not how he died.
It entered the medullary
pyramids, and beveling
on the entry site suggests
it was...
I don't believe there's
an English word that
adequately describes...
Wiggling. Up and down
is wiggling. Okay...
wiggled, thus paralyzing the victim
and causing some
difficulty breathing.
But he would live for upwards
of several hours. Smart.
Very little blood spilled.
How did the victim die ?
This is the bad part.
It appears that the concrete
was poured over him while
he was still alive.
Oh...
These chunks of concrete
are in the shape of...
a sinus cavity,
bronchial tubes,
plus a kind of a hollow
around the middle finger.
You said he was paralyzed.
Well, if the ice pick was
inserted and then waggled...
... it would affect
the median nerve
and the T1 nerve roots.
Which control the flexor
carpi radialis.
Anterior palm, thumb,
index and middle fingers.
But if it was...
Wiggled.
... the victim would
lose the ability
to move the ring and pinky fingers.
We think he wiggled
instead of waggled.
Because he could still
move his middle finger.
It's a terrible way to die.
Our conclusion is that he was
trying to swim to the surface
using only his middle finger.
The last time I saw Billy Ray McKenna
he was "So long, suckering" me
from his F-150
and heading off on a
well-earned vacation.
Well-earned by
torturing a journalist
who was talking too much.
Well, I resent your inference.
Get him my, uh...
whatcha call it ? Tax papers,
employment records.
Did I get that right ?
Not quite. You resent
his implication.
He's implying that
you're a criminal.
You're taking inference
with hisimplication. Have at it.
According to this, Mr. Lightner
is your flight instructor.
That is correct.
I have wide-ranging enterprises.
Clark here is helpful
in getting me
where I got to get.
And William Raymond McKenna
is down as a media liaison.
Yep, by breaking
journalists' fingers.
You know, you never
asked me about, uh,
Billy Ray McKenna
there, big dog.
Well, I assume,
big dog, that, uh,
Billy Ray is deceased.
Why ?
He was a valued employee.
Disappears for three years,
I got to assume the worst.
His body was found
encased in concrete.
Tell you what, we're gonna
claim his remains.
We'll bury him proper.
Where'd you send him on vacation ?
- Canada.
- Canada ?
Was it the Mounties that
found Billy Ray
encased in cement ?
- Concrete.
- Hmm ?
Not cement. It's a common error.
Baltimore Police.
- Is Baltimore on the way to Canada ?
- Well, the most
efficient route is up
through Detroit,
but Billy Ray, hell,
he loved Vermont so.
Do you have any idea who might
want to kill Mr. McKenna ?
Oh, hell, yeah. He, uh...
- Well, how would you put it ?
- Aggressive.
- Yeah.
- Both socially and sexually.
How about Hugh Kennedy ?
Hugh Kennedy.
Yeah, handy with the ice pick.
According to this,
you hired him as a "Liquor
License Consultant
on a per case basis."
Yes, yes, yes, yes. I remember.
Taciturn type. Very dour.
Right. In jail for murder once,
manslaughter twice,
and suspect in four
unsolved murders,
all involving ice picks.
You know, good old Hugh did not put
none of that on his ràÍum ?
If I recall, Mr. Kennedy
was killed in a car accident
fleeing a bail
enforcement officer.
Got burned up.
Well... you guys look us up
if you're ever
in western West Virginia.
We're at Snackie's
Roadhouse and Grill.
Where the 119 hits the 64.
I'll make a note of that.
119 hits the...
64. 64.
Hey, T, look.
Snickerdoodles. What do...
Oh, come on, you used to love them.
When you were a little girl.
I got a message for
you from your brother.
What message ?
Uh, he says, um... He says "hi."
Have you turned Russ
into a criminal, too ?
Hey, I haven't committed a crime
in over 15 years.
I'm straight. Except for
killing, gutting, and burning
the deputy director of the FBI.
He was trying to kill
Russ, and then he was going
after you. It is not
a crime to protect your family.
Some fathers do it without killing.
Did, uh... you and Booth
take a look at my, uh, rap sheet ?
Yes.
And ?
He'll arrest you
if he has the chance.
What else ?
So the snickerdoodles. Come on.
You don't remember ?
You loved them as a little girl.
I don't remember.
I'd come home, and then you'd
be jumping around. You were five
or six years old and you'd say,
"Come on, why don't you put
on the trying song ?
Put on the trying song !"
The trying song ?
It was my favorite song.
I used to sing it.
It was, uh... by Poco.
The band.
Hugh Kennedy ?
Bad guy, but he's dead.
About five years ago in a car
crash in West Virginia.
Recent evidence suggests
otherwise. How do you know him ?
Well, him and his ice pick
were pretty famous in some circles.
I've got to go.
- Now ?
- Yeah.
You speed-dialed Booth.
He's been listening
to everything and the...
the SWAT team's on its way.
I mean, I'm just guessing.
But there is something
I do want to say to you.
Mom ?
It's not about Mom,
it's about you and
it's about stuff
that she wanted you to know.
She never got the
chance to tell you.
Hey, Booth, there's a couple
of things that you should
know about this guy, Kennedy.
He's got an addiction
to model airplanes.
Try some of these again.
You'll love them.
Wait, Dad... What's...
What's the second thing ?
Mmm, he's wily.
You be careful, okay ?
Did you get that ?
I've got to tell you,
you were right, Zack.
Every model airplane freak
from Baltimore is here.
We prefer the term "pilots."
Yeah, okay.
So you're into
this stuff, too, huh ?
Yeah, forensic anthropology
is only one of my doctorates.
The other is in
applied engineering.
I'm extremely adept at
practical aeronautics.
Do you see Ice Pick ?
A lot of these guys
are kind of old.
You know, they're
wearing those, uh...
those sunglasses that
wrap around their heads.
Well, how many of them
only have one leg ?
Well, half of them
are sitting down.
Okay, how am I going to get
them to stand up ?
Crashes bring
everyone to their feet.
W... uh, shoot down
one of the planes.
That's great, and the
next thing you know,
I'm being evaluated by
my shrink again.
That's not going to happen.
Drive onto the field.
What ?
Put your car where they like to land.
Everyone will stand up
and yell at you.
This better work.
Okay, just stay with me here.
Oops.
Look at that, huh ?
It seems to be working.
Ha, ha. Oh, they're mad.
Do you see him ?
They're all wearing long pants.
I mean, how can I tell if any
of them are wearing a prosthetic ?
The prosthetic will cause
a slightly unnatural
alignment of the spine,
which will result in
a compensating adjustment of...
Booth, the instinct will be
for these men to step
toward you.
One man will be standing
perfectly still.
Okay.
Yep, I got him.
Sorry.
I apologize.
Just passing through.
Afternoon.
Anybody asking after me ?
Nope.
What the hell ?
I'm gonna need his room number.
Maybe I can help you.
What did you hit me with ?
Huh ?
Only reason I ask is my tooth
doesn't hurt anymore.
You know, you're the first guy
that got the drop on me
in ten years.
I used to get that a lot.
Can I ask you a question ?
As long as you answer
one for me, then.
Huh ? What's your story ?
Billy Ray got in the
back of my cab.
Don't know which one of us
was bigger surprised,
but it must have been Billy Ray
'cause he's the one ended up dead.
Hey, what's your question ?
How you people find him
under all that cement ?
A dog.
- Dog, huh ?
- Yeah.
So why am I not dead ?
I never killed nobody for fun.
It was my job.
And I'm retired.
Now, listen.
I know you fellas get in trouble
if you lose your gun.
I'm taking the bullets,
though, if you don't mind.
Oh.
- Well, what about me ?
- Settle down.
What ? Settle down, relax.
Someone'll find you.
You have a good day now.
I just want to talk
about your mother.
Booth is missing.
It's been over 18 hours.
He tried to take down Hugh
Kennedy by himself ?
He's only got one leg and he's old.
Yeah, you know how he got old ?
By being fast and paranoid.
He cut off his own leg.
Booth is tough.
What does the FBI say ?
Nothing.
Yeah, "need to know," right ?
Mm-hmm.
I want to do something, but
I don't... I don't know what.
Are you asking ?
You'd help find the man who's
going to put you in jail ?
Well, Booth will...
will do the best he can,
I'll do the best I can,
and we'll see how it works
out when we get there.
W-Where did he find Kennedy ?
Baltimore.
I'm afraid that's not Hugh Kennedy.
What's that called when they
wrap a sausage in a pancake ?
Pigs in a blanket.
Now how'd you get here ?
How'd you get here ?
Billy Ray was killed by
an ice pick in Baltimore.
We asked around.
Was it Hugh Kennedy that
bundled you up in a carpet ?
Look, I can't discuss
an ongoing investigation
with civilians, all right ?
So just cut me out of here.
Hey, what are you doing
with my gun ? Put that down.
Okay, time to step out
of your comfort zone, people.
What comfort zone ?
We've stopped working.
I'd like to start again.
We process evidence.
There's no more evidence
for us to process.
He's right. We process, Booth interprets.
I'd like to give it a try.
Yeah, we suck at interpretation.
We absolutely blow.
Um, what do you want us to do ?
Work what we know.
McKenna was probably killed by Kennedy.
Booth ran afoul of Kennedy.
I'm with you.
I'm with you, not ahead of you.
Okay, is there any forensic
evidence on our victim
that might lead
to Kennedy and Booth ?
Yeah, I mean,
I've finished the inventory
on McKenna's tracksuit.
There were flakes of tobacco,
fibers from the upholstery
of a Crown Victoria,
popcorn, chocolate,
a host of other wool
and cotton threads.
Okay, what does that tell us ?
That the man was a pig ?
All right, look, there were also
cellulose fibers consistent
with newsprint,
gum from a number
of different mouths.
Uh, he had dried chunks
of human mucous,
a half dozen filaments of nylon
consistent with women's hosiery.
Oh ! Uh, Kennedy
was a transvestite.
Keep going.
The rest was just waxy buildup
from soap or upholstery cleaner.
Let's assume all this adds up to a place.
Crime scene.
Close your eyes
and imagine the smell of all those things.
Tobacco, snot,
gum,
popcorn,
a lot of clothing, chocolate...
A porno movie theater !
You can't smoke at the movies.
I don't know about porno.
Upholstery cleaner,
Crown Victoria...
I got it.
A taxi cab.
McKenna was killed in a taxi cab.
Yes.
Where are you going ?
To tell the FBI
they're looking for a one-legged
cabbie in Baltimore.
You know, you guys,
it's not like
we all know each other off
the field, so...
But you know a man with
a prosthetic leg ?
Uh... yeah, I've seen him around.
We need his name.
No, honey, he'd be using a fake name.
No, we need to know where he lives.
Well, maybe he's listed
under his fake name.
He's too careful for that.
He drives a cab.
How do you know that ?
My associates are very good, Dad.
Can I ask a question ?
Do you guys have any, like,
official I.D. or anything ?
- I can have the FBI here in 20 minutes.
- No, no, no.
- Screw the FBI.
- No, no, no !
Hold on ! Easy !
Take it easy, pal.
- Where does he live ?
- I don't know !
- Dad !
- No !
All right, all right !
Halton Inn on Decatur.
- No, no, no !
- Dad, he told us !
Are you lying to me ? Because
if you are, I'll know it !
Halton Inn on Decatur,
just past the tracks. Easy.
Wha... ? !
What's that all about ?
Thank you.
You're welcome. Your dad's a psycho,
by the way. You have no idea.
Do you have a one-legged
old man staying here ?
Give me 40 bucks.
Room number, please.
Dad !
I... I have money.
Dad, look out !
Who is she ?
I don't think she's going
to tell us.
Come on, help me !
Pull ! Pull !
Hey. Hey, listen to me.
I like you.
But if you make
another move on me,
I will hurt you. You understand ?
If her name's Veleska,
she's the same bounty hunter
who brought in Kennedy's leg.
How'd you find him ?
It's not that hard
to find a one-legged,
old, white hit man in Baltimore.
Why is she after him ?
She has to make sure that Kennedy
stays gone. I helped
a wanted fugitive evade arrest.
I'm not going to jail.
What have you got ?
It's a left anterior molar.
It's Booth's tooth.
Where's Booth ?
Temperance, honey !
Kennedy has Booth, Dad.
He's got Booth ! Okay.
Perhaps he didn't see Kennedy.
Yeah ? How'd you come to that thought ?
Well, Kennedy would have left him
with an ice pick
protruding from his head.
Just one simple question, big dog.
Did you see Kennedy ?
Well, we could get our own ice pick.
Make it look like Kennedy killed him.
You know we can't let you live, right ?
You've been struck and restrained.
Technically, kidnapping
a federal agent is as bad
as murdering him these days.
How would you like to kill him ?
First, I got to know for sure
if Kennedy is dead or alive.
Good luck with that one, big dog.
Oh, big dog.
I suppose we could do that thing
that McKenna used to do,
but I'd need a blowtorch and
a sharpened screwdriver.
Just tell us.
Woof.
Cute. Oh !
- Must be his kid.
- Yeah.
Head like a anvil.
I hurt my hand.
All right.
I'm gonna let you take
a look at your sweet boy,
consign his face into your memory,
and then I'm gonna ask you which
one of your eyes you like best.
Definitely Booth's tooth.
I knew it.
Brennan...
You're not alone in this.
I know I'm not alone.
We all want to find Booth.
I know.
This is one of those times when
I have no idea what's happening.
Brennan, wait.
- I have to go, Ange.
- What's going on ?
I've got to find Booth.
I'm coming with you. No.
I can't fight or shoot a gun,
but if something bad happens,
I can spit with deadly accuracy.
Thanks, but no.
Why can't you tell me ?
By definition, I can't tell you.
All right, all right, Hodgins
is outside in his fastest car.
It's Italian.
One call and he follows you
everywhere.
Angela...
All right, you're after
a crazy, old, ice pick hit man
who has Booth.
You need help.
Look at my face.
Do you really see me backing down ?
I... I already have help, Ange.
From who ?
From someone worse than Kennedy.
Are you serious ?
Don't say it.
- You're father is helping you ?
- I have to go.
Dad !
Was it Booth's tooth ?
Yes. Stop that.
What are you doing ?
Well, we have to know for sure
if Kennedy is alive or dead.
I mean, what if she and
her friends took Booth ?
If this bothers you,
maybe you should go.
No, alpha male, man of action...
I... I get it.
Now, tell us.
Okay... okay...
Kennedy is alive.
I was chasing him for the bail.
He was smarter than me,
and he gave me a choice:
help him fake his death
or die myself.
Where'd you get the body ?
We stole some dead old geezer
from a mortuary in Charleston.
Where is my partner ?
When I got here, no one was here.
I swear.
What do we do with her ?
The room is paid for through
the end of the week.
Kennedy does not have Booth.
How do you know ?
He's only got one leg.
So ?
Well, so he's retired.
He's like me.
He just... he just
wants to disappear.
Then who's got Booth ?
Well, there's only one other
significant player in all this.
What am I going to do with you
when I get to the lab ?
I'll just take a nap
here in the car.
Awfully exciting day for
an old guy like me.
Booth is being held
by Melvin Gallagher.
That's a leap. How do you know ?
Can we just go with this, please ?
Of course not.
Obviously, Brennan
found out from her father...
- who is a wanted fugitive.
- Ange !
Now that I can go with.
We need to figure out where
Gallagher is holding Booth.
Has anybody noticed that every
time there's a panic situation,
all eyes turn to Hodgins ?
It's okay.
What's he supposed to do ?
Shoes. Shoes ?
Gallagher said the last
time he saw McKenna
he was leaving for vacation
after a tough night at work.
You think Gallagher might
have a place
he takes people for
that sort of thing ?
Let me go over Cement Head's
shoes... see what they tell us.
Methyl-Ethyl-Ketone.
It's a solvent.
See if it has any specialized uses.
Also chromic
MEK and chromic acid are both
used to prepare metals.
Prepare metals for what ?
Coating... painting mostly.
Electroplating.
I'm seeing micro-thin deposits
of aluminum here.
Shavings ?
No, it's more anodized...
vapor deposition.
Gallagher flies everywhere ?
An aluminum propeller requires
a coating that could withstand
between ten and 20 tons
of centrifugal force.
Preferably anodized.
These are Gallagher's tax returns.
We're looking for
the purchase of any machine
that could be used
for anodization.
What, like a copier, or... ?
Oh, that's so cute, but no.
Look for the words
"lamination, electroplating."
"Alloy membranes,
catalytic bed reactor..."
"A serial thermal processor."
"Vacuum pyrolysis."
"D-330 Vacuum plating processor" ?
Yeah, that's it. That's it.
Yes, this is Dr. Brennan
at the Jeffersonian.
I just received a call
from Agent Booth
that he's being held at...
the Purdue Airfield
in Oakville, Virginia.
Send backup, I'm going in.
You just lied your ass off
to the Federal Bureau
of Investigation.
That is so hot.
If you lie really still,
you may not die.
I need your car.
Max Keenan, you're under arrest.
Not if I get the keys.
They're in the ignition.
Well, it's not like I actually
gave him the keys.
Why didn't you just...
just tell them about Kennedy ?
Well, I needed to give
you time to find me.
I've been tortured worse.
So, uh, you hear anything
from your old man ?
He left my car in the garage.
He'll be back.
How do you know ?
Max Keenan does not strike
me as the kind of guy
who, uh, leaves things undone.
Next time he shows up,
what do I do ?
Do I call you ?
Do I knock him on the head ?
What's my obligation ?
Well, if I were you, Bones,
I'd want to know what he has
to tell you about your mother.
But, uh... that's just me.
There's, uh, this old song.
It's called "Keep on Trying."
Yeah, Poco.
You know it ?
Yeah, what about it ?
It's a good old song, right ?
Right.
Transcript : www.1000fr.com
Modification transcript : Flolo