- You should have worn the gumboots.
- I'm fine! You know, I'm...
I'm agile...
So, Hodgins asked
Angela to marry him.
Twice.
Oh, and she turned him down? Both times?
I heard all this from Angela.
Yeah, but did she tell you
that he said that he was...
he wasn't gonna ask
her to marry him?
- Yes.
- And she said...
"I'd like to marry you. "
Kind of sudden, Bones.
Let me think about it.
What? No, Booth, that's
what Angela told Hodgins.
You're joking.
You know, a lot of
psychologists say that jokes
are the way we manifest
our hidden desires.
Yeah...
Geez!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
What do we got?
During a foot pursuit last
night, suspect tosses a knife
into this muck in an effort
to avoid incarceration.
The effluent gets drained,
we start finding stuff.
Define "stuff. "
Stuff... cell phones,
guns, knives, crack vials.
Evidently, you want to lose something
in this vicinity, you toss it in here.
The miscreants probably think
it's some sort of bottomless pit.
Does the word "concise"
mean anything to you?
Well, we found that.
Concise enough?
Small.
Is it a kid?
Female.
Pelvic girdle and skull
sutures suggest preadolescent.
- A child's pencil case.
- How long has she been dead?
Does this freeze over in the winter?
Yeah. Solid.
It's possible she was placed
here as long ago as last fall.
Cause of death?
It looks like a gunshot
wound to the back of the head.
- Can you guess the caliber?
- Nothing larger than a 22.
- Find any 22s?
- Two.
All right, let's get an FBI forensic team
down here and search for bullet fragments.
I'll go call it in right now.
"I love you."
You said that pedophiles can delude themselves
into thinking they love their victims.
A nice traditional church
service. Very ecumenical.
That's great.
As long as the reception
makes Caligula blush.
Let's hope he got his invitation.
- Hey, what are those?
- They were found in this case.
Probably belonged to the victim.
And these are water samples
teeming with organisms.
I found an inordinately large
number of dead fairy shrimp
in the mud beneath the remains.
I will not make a "clap
for Tinkerbell" joke.
How about we not discuss child murder
and our upcoming nuptials
in the same conversation.
That's a good idea.
Hey, do you want me
to... change my name?
Do you want me to want
you to change your name?
Do you know what you're looking at?
The neck bone.
That's... connected
to the shoulder bone.
There's arthritic lipping here
and here, on the posterior dens.
Arthritis? For this
to occur she had to...
she had to look up like this.
- Maybe she prayed a lot.
- Four to six hour a day?
What did she want so badly?
Her father?
Hey, baby.
Dad.
Booth.
- Put your hands up.
- Booth!
I was hoping that we could get a
drink or something before this part.
Max Keenan, you're under
arrest as an escaped felon.
Oh, okay, so I guess that's
"no" on the drink, huh?
Bones, grab the cuffs out
of my back pocket there.
- No.
- What do you mean no? Bones...
It's okay, baby. I don't want
to handcuff my own father.
Plus, remember when he saved your life?
Hey, just throw them over
here. I'll do it myself.
He's telling me what to do.
Put your hands on the wall.
- Dad, what are you doing here?
- I heard you were getting married.
What? No.
Angela's getting married
to Hodgins, not me.
Oh, the bug guy.
- Well, that's great.
- Will you shut up, please?
long enough for me to mirandize him.
You got the right to
remain silent. Got it.
- We'll talk more later.
- Look, I'm sorry, Bones,
but he killed the Deputy Director
of the FBI. I'm just doing my job.
It's okay.
He's right.
Kisses, baby.
Uh, sweetie... was that your dad?
::Italian Subs Addicted::
[www.italiansubs.net]
Transcript: swsub.com
Synch: javawaarior2003, Smoking Bianco.
Bones, Season 02 Episode 21:
"Stargazer in a Puddle"
What do you mean that's not Max Keenan?
Cherie, you know that's Max Keenan,
and I know that's Max Keenan,
but to the rest of the world, that
man is a hardworking electrician
from Coos Bay, Oregon,
named Art McGregor.
That electrician was a bank robber for
15 years and murdered two FBI agents.
Only one was still an agent
at the time of his demise.
The guy was Deputy Director!
And a crooked, murdering son of a
bitch, not to speak ill of the dead.
Driver's license, credit
cards, tax returns...
And this library card
was issued 11 years ago.
- A complete history?
- Yes.
We'll keep digging, but
Cherie, I don't know.
I gotta cut that guy loose?
Legally speaking, that man is a law-abiding,
tax-paying, fully certified, dues-paying member
-  of the international brotherhood of...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
since 1984.
Tell me something, Max, on a job site,
what's the most hazardous
classification for an electrician?
Class 1, Division 1. You
planning a career change?
Ah, you're checking out my prints.
Max, you know I like you
and I hate to hurt Bones, but
it's my job to catch you.
And I'm very good at my job.
You'd have to be to work with
my daughter. What do you say?
Shake hands with an old con.
Or is that bad for the FBI image?
You abandoned her as a child.
You don't think she feels that,
every time you pop in
and out of her life?
You're just saying that so I'll hit you.
Then you got a reason to lock me up.
20 years ago...
that would have worked.
Your estimate was correct. This hole
is consistent with a 22 caliber slug.
I learned "slug" from Cam. It's a...
colloquialism for projectile.
Which so far the FBI
has been unable to find.
Okay, I have a face, but
you are not going to like it.
That is an old woman.
I provided you with the tissue data
for a ten-year-old Caucasian female.
Well, when I actually held
the skull and started...
the tissue markers felt wrong.
Angela, with all due respect to your
art, facial reconstruction is a science.
It's both, babe, and this time
art made science her bitch.
Hey, moan all you want. I stand by this.
We should recheck for other
indications that we got the age wrong.
Because art made science her bitch?
Because the lipping on the
vertebrae had to have been caused
by looking up over a
period of several years.
That's a scientific
rationale for rechecking.
Hey, Brennan.
I'd like to ask you a favor.
Well, it's not so much ask a
favor as, as extend an honor.
I mean, I hope you
see it as an honor and
don't think of it as some onerous duty,
which I don't think you will, but then
again I've never done this before...
Angela... just ask.
Will you be my maid of honor?
At the wedding?
- Is that yes?
- I am...
- completely, totally honored.
- Really?
- I thought I'd have to tell you...
- I don't even care
how awful the bridesmaid
dresses are. I'm...
so glad you asked me.
I have your brother set up in a
little auto supply place. It's a...
shade-tree mechanic situation.
You set him up where? Oregon?
It's better that you
don't know. He's, uh,
- in violation of his parole.
- Because you made him leave the state.
Your brother is on a slippery slope
and... yeah, I know,
I know, the irony of me
being a good influence,
but it's true, I am.
It's nice to see you smile.
That's, that's something.
Booth is going to find
proof of who you are.
- Then he'll arrest you.
- Not tonight.
Did you come here just to
tell me that Russ is okay?
No, actually, I have
something for you that...
that belonged to your grandmother.
I have a grandmother?
I know your mother and I told you that
you didn't have grandparents, but...
Try it on.
I... I have to go to bed.
There are some inconsistencies
with the remains,
which I have to address
first thing in the morning.
Okay.
You're welcome...
to stay here if... you want.
The couch would be great.
No, Dad, I, I made up the guest room
in case you...
Good night.
His fingerprints don't match?
There's nothing to compare them to.
Max Keenan got himself
wiped from the system?
That's right.
Who is this guy? Some
sort of super-criminal?
It must have been Deputy Director
Kirby. Yeah, he wanted Max dead, so...
he made him invisible first.
That would be an ironic twist,
seeing as how you want to
arrest Max for Kirby's murder.
You don't have doubts about
catching this guy, do you? I mean,
- he is your partner's father.
- No.
Bones gets it.
You hope she does.
I'll get you a warrant to
collect a DNA sample from the man.
You, find something to compare it to.
No wisdom teeth suggests prepubescence.
The lower bone plate and
the radius have not fused.
Angela's wrong. The
victim was not yet 20.
What?
The arthritic lipping on the vertebrae,
degeneration in the collarbone,
spiking on the superior
articular process.
And all the large bones in her body show
osteolytis and advanced deterioration.
- Meaning Angela was right.
- Meaning you were not wrong,
which is not the same as being right.
Progeria...
She had one of the aging diseases.
Anyone want to hear about the hit
my sketch got off the NCIC database?
Chelsea Cole... age 22,
went missing last November.
Good, Angela.
Really good.
- Zack?
- I really should've thought of that.
A disease which prevents the
sufferer from entering puberty,
but simultaneously ages her otherwise.
I'd like to ask you to be
my best man on Saturday.
Things aren't always either-or.
Sometimes they're both.
At my wedding.
Saturday.
To Angela.
My best man.
- When do I have to decide?
- You have to think about it?
Yes.
Fine.
Let me know what you decide.
You found her in a shopping cart?
- Yes.
- From Tuft's Grocery?
How did you know that?
Chelsea loved Tuft's.
Give her a dollar and she'd go
down there and buy a candy bar
or some cheap toy.
Everybody knew Chelsea,
walking along with one
small thing in a big cart,
bringing it home to show me.
Did Chelsea draw these?
Yes.
She's 22 years old. These are
the drawings of a young child.
Chelsea had a...
- condition.
- Werner's syndrome.
- How did you know?
- What's that?
It's an aging disease in which
mental development can be a factor.
Your daughter spent...
a long time looking up. Correct?
Chelsea was obsessed with the stars.
She thought they were signals
from heaven, showing people...
the way home.
Mrs. Cole, when Chelsea disappeared,
you gave the police a name?
Joe Mellon.
He was a caretaker provided by the city while
I was going to classes at community college.
One night I came home from class
and her hair smelled like
the shampoo I use... lemons.
I always use baby shampoo on Chelsea.
That, that wasn't part of
his job... bathing Chelsea?
Definitely not!
I complained to Child
Services, and they...
launched an investigation.
Which ended as soon
as Chelsea disappeared?
I guess so.
No victim... no crime.
I absolutely...
did not molest Chelsea Cole.
- Why'd Child Services let you go?
- They didn't let me go.
They reassigned me because they
knew I didn't do anything wrong.
What did you not do wrong, Joe?
Chelsea Cole had the mental
capacity of a six-year-old.
She got jam all over her and
freaked out from being sticky.
That's why I ran her a bath.
And I sat outside
the bathroom door and made her
talk to me while she was in the tub.
She used her mom's shampoo and
it stung her eyes. She cried.
I went in and rinsed
the soap out of her eyes
and then I went back out
and let her get dressed,
which is what she told her
mother, who did not listen.
Then why is Cynthia Cole so insistent
that you were inappropriate
with her daughter?
I crossed the line, man. I...
suggested that Cynthia consider
an alternate solution for Chelsea.
What? Like an institution?
The woman was exhausted. She,
she was looking like crap.
She was failing all of her college
courses. She couldn't hold onto a job.
Everything was going downhill.
Listen, Joe.
I want you to look me
in the eye, and tell me
that you never touched that little girl.
I wiped the soap
out of her eyes.
And I wrapped a towel around her.
That's it.
This ring was passed down from
oldest daughter to oldest daughter.
It was a tradition in your
mother's side of the family.
You told Russ and me that
we didn't have any relatives.
Well, honey, we were underground. We
had new names. We had to tell you that.
What's the truth?
Your mother's the
oldest of three sisters,
and if you want to seek them out,
you show them the ring, they'll know who
you are and accept you into the family.
What about on your side?
Your mother was the only family
I ever knew. And you and Russ.
You abandoned me for 15 years.
And I'll do whatever
I can to make repairs.
- While running away from the FBI?
- I have more.
A message from your
mother. On videotape.
- Well... what does she say?
- I don't know. It's for you.
When you're ready.
I am sorry to interrupt, but
I have a warrant here to...
take a DNA sample from you, Mr.
Arthur McGregor from Coos Bay, Oregon.
I'm really sorry.
Zack?
There's a recalcification
around this hole.
It healed.
Zack, I'm getting married Saturday.
Two short days, man.
I need to know if
you'll stand up with me.
I don't need a formal response.
A simple "yes" would...
Iraq?
You can't go to Iraq.
- The president is asking me personally.
- No.
Not personally. The president
has a machine to sign for him.
He's probably talking to every forensic
anthropologist in the country. You can't go to Iraq.
No.
No way. You, you stay here and you be
my best man. You let someone else go.
He's says I'm at the
forefront of my field,
- that my country needs me.
- You can't go to Iraq.
Zack.
Will you be my best man or not?
No.
- Why?
- Because,
if I decide to do what the president
wants, and go to Iraq and get killed,
you won't be able to remember
your wedding with happiness.
Okay, big assumption there, buddy.
Rationally speaking, I'm
not good at social ritual.
You should ask Booth.
Everything isn't rational.
It should be.
I no longer believe
this is a bullet hole.
I believe this was created by a drill.
Chelsea had brain surgery
when she was three.
- They had to drill into her skull?
- Yes, to relieve the pressure.
- These are accurate.
- I beg your pardon?
These are all constellations.
Centaurus, Aquarius... Gemini.
I knew Chelsea loved the stars but I
never thought her drawings were actually...
- They're real?
- This one's Delphinius.
The Dolphin. It was...
my favorite when I was a child. My
mother and I both loved dolphins.
So that was something that we...
shared.
Mrs. Cole, why exactly did...
your daughter require brain surgery?
Why do you ask it like that?
- You think I did something to Chelsea.
- Head injuries are...
extremely common in children
who are physically abused.
Excuse me, but it's very important
that I take my medication on time.
My daughter, at age
three, fell out of bed.
She didn't stop crying until
I took her to the hospital.
She had the surgery. It
was because of that injury
that they discovered that
she had the aging disease.
Did Joe Mellon tell you that
I physically abused my daughter
because I grabbed her arm once?
Once?
- Booth.
- Dude...
- will you stand up for me on Saturday?
- Against who?
No. I mean...
be my best man?
Sure. Wow.
I know. Big honor.
No, no, no. Yeah, that, but, you
know, you didn't give me much time to
- put a bachelor party together.
- No bachelor party.
- Is that Hodgins?
- Yeah. He wants me to be his best man.
Well, if there's no bachelor
party what do you want me to do?
Stand there. Make a toast.
Hand over the ring.
Tongue-kiss the maid of honor at the
reception when people clink glasses.
Nice. Excellent. Okay,
who's the maid of honor?
No idea, but most of Angela's
friends are really hot.
Well, I'm the maid of honor.
Why?
Uh, listen, do you need me to, uh,
connect with the bride's father?
Put together the, uh, the
toast, the speeches and all that?
Hodgins, you there?
Angela's father.
Oh, I forgot all about him.
- She has AIDS.
- Angela?
Cynthia Cole, the victim's
mother. HIV or AIDS.
What, all that medicine she took?
I recognized one of them.
We'll ask Cam.
In the mud sample taken
from beneath the remains,
I found a high concentration
of dead anostraca.
Also known as "fairy shrimp."
Shrimp can live outside the ocean?
They're not actually shrimp; they're
brachiopods. Main differences being...
- Moving on.
- I want to know if they can be poisoned
by feeding on decomposing flesh.
Oh, God.
- Please tell me that is not...
- That's not human.
That's Spam.
Which has been injected with
a number of organic poisons.
We'd like to introduce a
colony of Artemia Salina.
Commonly referred to
as sea chimps.
If they die, I can check to see if running them
through the spectrometer reveals what poisoned them.
What do you want from me?
Permission.
- Why?
- Because you said
you'd fire us if we did any more
experiments without clearing them first.
Boys,
you've got Spam and sea chimps.
You get anything out
of that, and I will...
buy you each a car.
- Release the hounds.
- What?
Pour in the sea chimps.
I found that anticlimactic.
Yeah.
- Do you like your father?
- Love my father.
I think I love my father.
Well, that's normal.
But he ran out on me and Russ.
He robbed people.
He's a murderer.
He got my mother killed. You
know, how does he expect me to...?
It's hard to trust someone
who's abandoned you.
Especially a parent.
Am I...
Am I terrible for not...
wanting to let myself
care about my own father?
Look, Bones, your father is going to do
something tomorrow that's going to hurt you.
How do you forgive that?
I'm not a bad daughter?
Bad person?
You're not a bad anything.
Hodgins figured out
what killed Chelsea Cole.
Branchinecta Lindahli. Also
known as the fairy shrimp.
Not a true shrimp,
actually, a branchiopod.
You want to hurry it up there,
Hodgins? I got a tux I need to rent.
Right. Zack and I did a brief
experiment involving sea chimps.
Sea chimps? I love sea chimps.
To confirm that they would feed
on decomposing human tissue?
Great, thanks for ruining the
whole sea chimp thing for me.
- Did they?
- Those sea chimps went after that pork
by product like piranhas after
a skinny-dipping missionary.
Did you find anything in the fairy
shrimp beneath Chelsea Cole's body?
Yeah.
They were exposed to
lethal concentrations
of non-nucleoside reverse
transcriptase inhibitors.
- I feel bad for the sea chimps, but...
- Booth.
Chelsea Cole was poisoned
by an overdose of Navirapine.
What's that?
- AIDS medicine.
- AIDS medicine...
It was her mother.
We'll probably be able
to trace this to you.
- I loved my daughter very much.
- The hell you did.
She got to be too much for you
to handle, so you killed her.
You don't understand.
I don't think you'll
ever find anyone who does.
You know, your daughter had
the mind of a six year old.
She loved the stars; she trusted you...
We're here.
and you killed her.
Ritonavir...
MK-0518...
Tenofir.
None of those is a trade
name for Navirapine.
Wait... MK-0518...
is still in experimental
trials to replace Navirapine.
She used her old medicine to
poison Chelsea. Thanks, Cam.
Cynthia Cole, you're under arrest for
the murder of your daughter, Chelsea Cole.
Could you please take down
the pictures Chelsea drew?
I don't want anyone to come
in and just throw them away.
You threw away your own daughter.
Why would I do you a favor?
You have the right to remain silent. Anything you say
can and will be used against you in a court of law.
In 1978, Max Keenan
robbed a Piggly Wiggly
in Carbondale, Illinois.
The clerk conked him on the
head with a baseball bat.
Keenan pressed napkins to
his head to staunch the blood,
left them behind.
Don't tell me.
State Police have said
napkins in evidence.
Agent Booth, you wanted me to get
this information for you, correct?
Good work, Charlie.
Hey.
I mean...
You get that a lot, right? The whole...
Rrr, rrr, rrr... thing.
- Can I help you?
- I'm... Jack Hodgins.
You seem okay to me so far.
Well, I suddenly realized...
My best man said,
speeches at the wedding...
- You know about the wedding?
- Oh, yes.
It's no coincidence I'm here.
Well, it occurred to me that
you might have a traditional...
You're Texan, and...
I mean, really Texan.
Guitars and hot rods Texan, so...
So I figured I should ask you for
your daughter's hand in marriage.
As a sign of respect.
You're making a huge mistake, son.
- Marrying Angela?
- No.
If Angie finds out that a man, you,
asked another man, me...
me, for her hand, or any
of her other fine parts,
horrible complications will ensue.
- I didn't think of that.
- You could get us both killed.
Okay. Good advice.
You got any more?
Always play it in the
key of G demolished.
I don't know what that means.
Well, if you do, you do.
If you don't, you don't.
Forget it.
Hodgins.
I've got cars and I've got guitars...
and I got guns.
You treat my little girl right,
you'll only see the business
end of the cars and guitars.
Am I going to need to use my gun, Max?
You got your piece of paper?
Max Keenan, I'm placing you under arrest
- for the murder of Deputy Director...
- Oh, fine, fine. Sure.
You know what? You can take me. You're
right. I'm not going to abandon her again.
- You're not going to resist?
- It's your lucky day, I guess.
- Great.
- No.
No. Wait a minute. No.
See, I'm wrong. I can't just
go quietly. It's not my nature.
Max, I got a gun.
I can't surrender. You're
going to have to shoot me.
You... You understand.
Not your nature?
Yeah, maybe it's a character flaw.
Yeah, shoot me. Shoot me. But in
the leg, please, if you don't mind.
Ok. Hold up.
One second, please. Thank you.
Ready?
Hey. Hey, that's good,
kid. You're throwing.
What's the matter? Got a glass jaw?
You know what? You talk too much.
Right in the face? Geez. Time. Time.
- You had enough?
- Wait.
-  I'm old. - There's no
time-outs during an arrest.
Ok, I'm done. I'm done.
It's over. I'm finished.
Let's go.
Oh, God. That really hurts.
Hi, Temperance. It's Mom.
I don't know when or
if you'll ever see this.
I hope to put it in your hands myself,
see you again with my own eyes,
but this is a hard, hard world.
Your father and I left you and Russ
to save your lives.
People would have killed you to get us.
But that's not what this is about.
Today is your 16th birthday.
I'm so sorry... not to be there to
to tell you all the things that a mother
should tell her daughter when she turns 16.
And sorry not to give you this...
It's an heirloom from
my side of the family
and starting today, it's yours.
I don't know how long it will
take me to get it to you, but
I promise you I will.
You're going to hear a lot
of things about your parents,
especially about your father.
He is a good man.
It was my insistence to leave you kids.
Max would have kept us together,
fought until the end.
I'm not sure he'll ever
forgive me for that.
So, please, Temperance...
I need you to forgive me.
And if you can't forgive
me, I beg you, honey,
forgive your father
because he is a very good man.
Remember this:
you were cherished in this world.
Adored.
What I did to you may have been wrong,
but I did it out of love.
I did it out of love.
Chelsea thought that
stars were signals from heaven,
showing how to get home.
Your AIDS cocktail wasn't working.
You were sick...
dying.
They put you on an experimental drug
and you felt even worse.
Your worst nightmare was coming true:
Chelsea was going to outlive you.
No foster parent would take her.
You did what you did...
out of mercy.
We went to the park.
And I gave, uh...
told Chelsea that it was candy.
We...
we sat there looking up at the stars.
I didn't know what to do with her.
I didn't have any strength left.
And then...
I remembered the water.
And I thought it was deep.
Peaceful, you know?
And then...
like you were being punished,
the experimental drug
started to work, didn't it?
You got better.
What you did was wrong...
but you did it out of love.
How do I look?
Good.
How come yours looks so much better?
I took this and yanked.
Have you been to Iraq?
That's classified information,
and you aren't cleared for that.
Does it hurt to get shot?
What?
I've been blown up. That
wasn't as bad as I expected.
But I've never been shot.
- Booth?
- Yeah.
Better?
Wow. You look great.
You said I looked good before.
Whose day is it, huh? It's
Angela's. Come on, let's go.
There you go.
- Bones?
- Yes?
Listen, I'm
I'm sorry, I had to arrest your father.
We don't have to talk about that right
now. You did your duty. I understand.
Yep. But...
- Bones?
- What?
- He could have gotten away.
We got into a fight. Your dad
could have escaped capture.
- So he beat you in the fight?
- No, I didn't say that.
You beat him, but you gave
him a chance to get away?
No, I didn't say that. I don't
see any other alternative.
No, Bones, your father chose to
be arrested because he felt if
he abandoned you again,
he'd lose you forever.
I just thought you should know.
Thanks, Booth.
Hi.
I'd like to get married now.
Welcome, everyone.
We have gathered here today
to join together in matrimony
Jack Stanley Hodgins and
Angela Pearly Gates Montenegro.
Who gives this woman?
I give you this beautiful woman.
I got a show.
Have a good time, everybody.
Angela and Jack have
invited us all here today
to be part of something beautiful.
Two people standing
before their friends,
family, and community to say,
"You are the one I love."
"You are the one for whom
I forsake all others."
Excuse me?
Is this the
Hodgins-Montenegro nuptials?
It's trying to be.
I'm with the State Department and it's imperative
that I speak with Hodgins and Montenegro
before these proceedings... proceed.
Come on then. Let's
get this figured out.
We'll, um... be right back.
- Booth?
- Yeah.
Is there any sense in ducking
when someone shoots at you?
Your body ducks whether
you want to or not.
- Why?
- You can read this later,
then explain it to everyone.
Why me?
You know more about duty and
honor than anyone else I know.
Angela is already married?
Angela is totally,
unmistakably, legally married.
As federal employees
with security clearance,
your marriage license
underwent special scrutiny,
especially since your
wedding was so hurried.
You were married in Fiji four years ago.
I jumped over a broomstick with a guy.
I'm sorry.
Jack, I...
- This is my fault.
- No worries...
No worries. We'll just...
We'll, um...
There's just a lot of people
in there expecting a wedding.
Yeah,
I made this huge deal out of
getting married right away and
and they all... and... Run.
What? Flee. Scram. Skedaddle.
I like it.
Change of plan. Please go to the
reception. Have a great time on us.
Thank you for coming.
What do we do now?
Transcript: swsub.com
Synch: ::Italian Subs Addicted::