So, you ever
been here before?
No.
Oh, I don't mean here
here. I mean Baltimore.
Yeah, I've given
several lectures
to the Baltimore
Homicide Division.
What's wrong
with your mouth?
I got a tooth situation.
Well, go to
a dentist.
All right, I will
if it doesn't get any better.
Ow! Man!
Are you afraid
of the dentist?
I'm not afraid.
Welcome to Balmer.
This is, uh, actually a federal
flood abatement project,
which is why
we called you.
K-9 unit was using
it for an exercise,
and one of the
cadaver dogs
went berserk.
When they dug
up the cement...
No, that's concrete.
Cement is an ingredient in concrete.
Yeah, that's a real
important distinction to make
at this juncture.
So, what do we got,
Bones, huh?
Do your thing.
Nothing.
Nothing. Nothing?
No, I can't
see enough
of the skull, the tibia,
the pubis.
Nothing.
Wait a second. Nothing.
Oh, sorry about that.
We drove all the way here so
you could just tell me nothing?
All right, so what do you,
what do you want to, uh,
get the whole slab
of cement...
Concrete.
...concrete, whatever-- shipped
back to the Jeffersonian?
Abso ???
Sex?
The mandible
suggests male,
and the tibia
suggests
he was between five
six and six feet tall.
Waffle-soled training shoes
and a track suit.
You know who wears
track suits?
Athletes?
No. Huge tubs of lard
or retired people.
And rap stars.
The teeth suggest
early middle age.
So not a retiree.
Uh, calcified holes
with radial fractures
in the left clavicle
and scapula are consistent
with ballistic damage.
He was shot
to death?
And stabbed.
But neither killed him.
The wounds healed.
Shot, stabbed,
but lived to die another day?
Rap star.
There is a small hole
in the back of the cranium.
Get the skull out first,
establish cause of death,
then give Angela something
to work with to ID the guy.
Where is Angela?
I'm really not good
at this kind of thing.
You know, I don't...
I don't get
the significance.
One year ago today,
you buried your mother.
You laid
her to rest.
Here.
You're marking
the anniversary.
Angela, I simply
don't believe
my mother retained sentience
beyond death.
Well, part of you is made
up of your mother, right?
In a manner of speaking.
So, honor that
part of yourself.
Visualize a
memory of her.
See what it brings up.
I have very few
distinct memories of my mother.
I'll wait in the car.
Hiya, honey.
I was hoping you
might show up.
I don't... I don't want
to talk to you.
We're standing here
in front of your
mother's grave.
Obviously, you've come
for some kind of answer.
Maybe I can... provide 'em.
You're a killer.
You burn people.
Yeah, I'd like to report
a sighting of Max Keenan
at Eternal Spring
Memorial Gardens.
He's a wanted
fugitive.
I love you.
Yes, I'm sure.
Because he's my father.
www.1000fr.com present
Capture:FRM@MAOREN
Sync:FRM@∫„–«
??? your dad at
all before you called the cops?
No. Why would I?
Well, I mean, I
haven't seen my
dad in a long time,
and if I had
the opportunity
to talk... Ow!
Go to a
dentist.
Oh, I will
if it doesn't
get any better.
Based on decomposition
of the track suit,
Hodgins is estimating
a postmortem interval
of two years.
Based on bone deterioration,
I like three years.
Well, what
killed him?
The victim was dead
shortly after
this hole was punched
into his skull.
Too small for a projectile.
No radiating stress lines.
A slow entry, a piercing wound.
Like a-a
screwdriver?
Nail gun?
Ice pick?
Yeah, something
along those lines.
Oh. Cold steel to the brain--
would that kill him?
Depending how far
it penetrated.
Yeah, it's Booth.
I need, um, all murders
in which a penetrating wound
to the back of the head figured.
Great. Thanks.
Don't freak out.
Oh!
You broke
into my house?
That is not
acceptable.
This, uh,
little device here--
it jams cell phone frequencies.
That is illegal.
Unfortunately,
illegal
is what I do best.
I'm not staying.
I just want you
to do something for me.
I want you to take a look
at my rap sheet.
Why?
Because I want a chance to talk
to you-- actually talk to you--
without you calling in
the 82nd Airborne.
How is reading
your police record
going to change my mind?
Just do it.
I think our victim
was killed by Ice Pick.
Angela did a facial
reconstruction of Cement Head.
Concrete Head, you mean.
No, Cement Head--
it's got a nicer ring.
So, I ran it through
IntelPlus and got a match.
William Raymond "Billy Ray"
McKenna.
West Virginia.
"Assault, manslaughter,
kidnapping,
torture...."
This here...
This here is, uh, Hugh Kennedy.
Uh, I think
he killed Cement Head.
Why?
Well, West Virginia,
likes to use an ice pick
on his victims, plus Ice Pick
and Cement Head
were both employed
by a regional crime boss
in West Virginia
named... Gallagher.
Well, what are we going
to call him?
Gallagher.
But he runs
most of the, uh, prostitutes,
strippers, gambling,
bootlegging, meth,
extortion in West Virginia.
Five years ago,
the West Virginia
State Police began pressuring
Gallagher's criminal operation,
making a lot of arrests.
Including Ice Pick
and Cement Head.
Cement Head goes to jail.
Ice Pick?
Out on bail, babe.
You say that
like it means something.
Oh, I talked to the officer
in charge, and he said
that Ice Pick
wouldn't say anything,
so they punished him
by letting him out
on bail.
How is bail punishment?
'Cause it makes Gallagher think
that Ice Pick cooperated
with the cops.
You know,
it's criminal
psychology, Bones.
You know, you wouldn't get it.
Just read. Just continue
reading there, will you?
"Half a million
dollar bond.
"Kennedy jumped bail.
"Killed in a car accident
while fleeing
a Bail Fugitive Recovery agent."
Bounty Hunter.
"Car burned the remains to ashes."
All they got was a severed leg.
They didn't actually get
Ice Pick's body.
So, are we going to talk
to the bounty hunter?
No, I am. You're gonna make sure
that that severed leg
actually belonged to Ice Pick.
Well, someone kept the leg?
The severed leg
was frozen as evidence.
So, you think
Ice Pick might still be alive?
As a friend
of mine
likes to say,
"Don't jump to conclusions
until all the evidence is in."
If the facts are in, then
it's not jumping to conclusions,
so I never
said that.
I never said
that the friend is you, okay?
Does it have to be completely
thawed for you to examine?
No. My interest lies
only in the femur.
I need to get some tissue
for DNA testing.
I'm the bounty hunter
you want to talk to.
Veleska Miller.
You want to know
about Kennedy's leg?
Anything you want to tell me
outside the official report,
that's great.
Sure.
How it smelled,
his body cooking over the fire.
Otherwise,
I stand by the record.
How'd you find him?
Tip from someone I know
who provides documents
to fugitives.
Tailed him, he made me,
took off.
Boom!
Found his leg about 30 yards
from the vehicle.
And you saw him burn?
Yeah.
Why?
That's it?
That's it.
I'm a little disappointed.
I was hoping
you'd keep me here a while,
ask me some dumb-ass
federal questions, check me out.
How's about
I buy you a nice breakfast, huh?
Guy like you must be going crazy
in the FBI.
What kind of guy is that,
exactly?
I'm a bounty hunter, sport.
I read people fast, or I die.
You are not standard
government issue.
Take a walk
on the wild side.
I have more fun, fewer rules,
and a lot of money.
Yeah.
You make a compelling case.
Booth.
Coroner's report said
Kennedy's leg was severed
in the car accident.
We don't call him Kennedy.
We call him Ice Pick.
Hold on for one second. Sorry.
Yeah. Aah.
Listen, I got the, uh,
bounty hunter here.
She was an eyewitness
to the crash.
Saw him incinerated.
Tell Booth that Ice Pick's
femur is sliced cleanly
at 90 degrees.
I can hear you, Bones.
Okay? It's a speakerphone.
Look, amputation
like that could happen
in a bad wreck,
right, Cam?
Yes.
Well, there are kerf marks.
She's seeing evidence
of a saw, Booth.
Look, I know
what kerf marks are.
Booth should arrest
the bounty hunter.
I can hear you, Bones.
What am I gonna
arrest her for, huh?
For lying, for perjury.
For aiding in a cover-up.
If she's there with you,
just detain her.
Okay.
???
Hey, look at that, huh?
DNA is a match.
West Virginia
state troopers
got a DNA sample
at Ice Pick's arrest.
This is definitely his leg.
Was she pretty?
Ice Pick is a male.
I mean the bounty hunter
who gave Booth the slip.
You know, she didn't get away
because she was pretty.
She was a she?
No, she was a...
Oh...
What's wrong with your mouth?
I'm guessing the
anterior molar
on the left
side is infected.
The leg was
surgically amputated.
Go to a dentist.
He's afraid
of the dentist.
These kerf marks are
consistent with a type
of wire saw used
to remove horns
from heifers.
Ah, so...
Ice Pick and this bounty
hunter set up a car accident
with a dummy victim so
everyone stops looking for him.
Two years later he kills
Con-- Cement Head.
She hoodwinked you
'cause she was hot.
All right, look, you know what?
She wasn't hot.
In fact, she looked like a man.
The amputation
was probably performed
by a livestock veterinarian.
Hey, Bones,
I've got that other
thing you want to discuss.
Oh, let's...
go to my office
so we don't
disturb Cam.
Booth?
Yeah?
Livestock amputation.
That is one tough,
determined old criminal.
Be careful.
You know, I was going
through your father's
crim...
Shh!
...criminal record and he was
right about one thing.
You know, he never ended
anyone's life who didn't
have it coming to them.
He's a sociopath.
Well, maybe, but at
least he aimed in the
right direction.
Ow!
Let me take a look
at your tooth.
All right, just...
Go easy. You promise?
Okay.
All right.
Open up.
You know,
What?
In the Old West,
he would have been
considered a hero.
Yeah, well, the Old West
Ow!
was a time of chaos
and violence that,
anthropologically speaking,
our country is still
Ow!
trying to recover from.
Yeah, I was right.
Anterior molar on the left side,
it's infected.
You know, your
father never killed
any hardworking, tax-paying
citizens or honest cops.
Ow!
You still think
that society
should forgive him?
All I'm saying
is if I have an opportunity
to arrest him, I will.
But you know who maybe
should forgive him?
His daughter.
Oh, look at that.
The small town
crime boss is here.
Let's go have a little chat
with him, shall we?
Billy Ray McKenna shortly before
he became Cement Head.
I like nicknames.
They are universal
mnemonic devices.
Why are we doing this?
Don't we know that cause
of death was brain scrambling
due to an ice pick?
The technical term is "pithing."
And it's not how he died.
It entered
the medullary
pyramids, and beveling
on the entry site suggests
it was...
I don't believe there's
an English word that
adequately describes...
Wiggling. Up and down
is wiggling.
Okay...
wiggled, thus
paralyzing the victim
and causing some
difficulty breathing.
But he would live for upwards
of several hours.
Smart.
Very little
blood spilled.
How did the victim die?
This is the bad part.
It appears that the concrete
was poured over him
while he was still alive.
Oh...
These chunks of concrete
are in the shape of...
a sinus cavity,
bronchial tubes,
plus a kind of a hollow
around the middle finger.
You said he was paralyzed.
Well, if the ice pick was
inserted and then waggled...
...it would affect
the median nerve
and the T1 nerve roots.
Which control
the flexor carpi radialis.
Anterior palm, thumb,
index and middle fingers.
But if it was...
Wiggled.
...the victim would
lose the ability
to move the ring
and pinky fingers.
We think he wiggled
instead of waggled.
Because he could still
move his middle finger.
It's a terrible way to die.
Our conclusion
is that he was trying
to swim to the surface
using only
his middle finger.
The last time I saw
Billy Ray McKenna
he was "So long, suckering" me
from his F-150
and heading off
on a well-earned vacation.
Well-earned by torturing
a journalist
who was talking too much.
Well, I resent
your inference.
Get him my, uh...
whatcha call it? Tax papers,
employment records.
Did I get that right?
Not quite. You resent
his implication.
He's implying that
you're a criminal.
You're taking inference
with hisimplication.
-Have at it.
According to this, Mr. Lightner
is your flight instructor.
That is correct.
I have wide-ranging enterprises.
Clark here is helpful
in getting me
where I got to get.
And William Raymond McKenna
is down as a media liaison.
Yep, by breaking
journalists' fingers.
You know, you never
asked me about, uh,
Billy Ray McKenna
there, big dog.
Well, I assume,
big dog, that, uh,
Billy Ray is deceased.
Why?
He was a valued employee.
Disappears for three years,
I got to assume the worst.
His body was found
encased in concrete.
Tell you what, we're gonna
claim his remains.
We'll bury him proper.
Where'd you send
him on vacation?
Canada.
Canada?
Was it the Mounties that
found Billy Ray
encased in cement?
Concrete.
Hmm?
Not cement. It's a common error.
Baltimore Police.
Is Baltimore on the way
to Canada?
Well, the most
efficient route is
up through Detroit,
but Billy Ray, hell,
he loved Vermont so.
Do you have any idea who might
want to kill Mr. McKenna?
Oh, hell, yeah. He, uh...
Well, how would you put it?
Aggressive.
Yeah.
Both socially
and sexually.
How about Hugh Kennedy?
Hugh Kennedy.
Yeah, handy with the ice pick.
According to this,
you hired him as a "Liquor
License Consultant
on a per case basis."
Yes, yes, yes, yes. I remember.
Taciturn type. Very dour.
Right. In jail
for murder once,
manslaughter twice,
and suspect in four
unsolved murders,
all involving ice picks.
You know, good old Hugh did not
put none of that on his rÈsumÈ.
If I recall, Mr. Kennedy
was killed in a car accident
fleeing a bail
enforcement officer.
Got burned up.
Well... you guys look us up
if you're ever
in western West Virginia.
We're at Snackie's
Roadhouse and Grill.
Where the 119
hits the 64.
I'll make a
note of that.
119 hits the...
64.
Hey, T, look.
Snickerdoodles. What do...
Oh, come on,
you used to love them.
When you were
a little girl.
I got a message for you
from your brother.
What message?
Uh, he says, um...
He says "hi."
Have you turned Russ
into a criminal, too?
Hey, I haven't
committed a crime
in over 15 years.
I'm straight.
Except for
killing, gutting, and burning
the deputy director
of the FBI.
He was trying to kill Russ,
and then he was going
after you. It is not
a crime to protect your family.
Some fathers do it
without killing.
Did, uh... you and Booth
take a look at my,
uh, rap sheet?
Yes.
And?
He'll arrest you if
he has the chance.
What else?
So the snickerdoodles.
Come on.
You don't remember?
You loved them as a little girl.
I don't remember.
I'd come home,
and then you'd
be jumping around. You were five
or six years old and you'd say,
"Come on, why don't you
put on the trying song?
Put on the trying song!"
The trying song?
It was my favorite song.
I used to sing it.
It was, uh... by Poco.
The band.
Hugh Kennedy?
Bad guy, but he's dead.
About five years ago in a car
crash in West Virginia.
Recent evidence
suggests otherwise.
How do you know him?
Well, him and his ice pick were
pretty famous in some circles.
I've got to go.
Now?
Yeah.
You speed-dialed Booth.
He's been listening
to everything and the...
the SWAT team's on its way.
I mean, I'm
just guessing.
But there is something I
do want to say to you.
Mom?
It's not about Mom,
it's about you
and it's about stuff
that she wanted you to know.
She never got the
chance to tell you.
Hey, Booth, there's a couple
of things that you should know
about this guy, Kennedy.
He's got an addiction
to model airplanes.
Try some of these again.
You'll love them.
Wait, Dad...
What's...
What's the second thing?
Mmm, he's wily.
You be careful, okay?
Did you get that?
I've got to tell you,
you were right, Zack.
Every model airplane freak
from Baltimore is here.
We prefer the term "pilots."
Yeah, okay.
So you're into this stuff,
too, huh?
Yeah, forensic anthropology
is only one of my doctorates.
The other is in
applied engineering.
I'm extremely adept at
practical aeronautics.
Do you see Ice Pick?
A lot of these guys are
kind of old.
You know,
they're wearing those, uh...
those sunglasses
that wrap around their heads.
Well, how many of them
only have one leg?
Well, half of them
are sitting down.
Okay, how am I going to get them
to stand up?
Crashes bring everyone
to their feet.
W... uh, shoot down
one of the planes.
That's great,
and the next thing you know,
I'm being evaluated
by my shrink again.
That's not going to happen.
Drive onto the field.
What?
Put your car
where they like to land.
Everyone will stand up
and yell at you.
This better work.
Okay, just stay with me here.
Oops.
Look at that, huh?
It seems to be working.
Ha, ha. Oh, they're mad.
Do you see him?
They're all wearing long pants.
I mean, how can I tell if any of
them are wearing a prosthetic?
The prosthetic will cause
a slightly unnatural
alignment of the spine,
which will result in a
compensating adjustment of...
Booth, the instinct will be
for these men to step
toward you.
One man will be standing
perfectly still.
Okay.
Yep, I got him.
Sorry.
I apologize.
Just passing through.
Afternoon.
Anybody asking after me?
Nope.
What the hell?
I'm gonna need his room number.
Maybe I can help you.
What did you hit me with?
Huh?
Only reason I ask is my
tooth doesn't hurt anymore.
You know, you're the first guy
that got the drop on me
in ten years.
I used to get that a lot.
Can I ask you a question?
As long as you answer one
for me, then.
???
Huh?
What's your story?
Billy Ray got
in the back of my cab.
Don't know which one of us
was bigger surprised,
but it must have been Billy Ray
'cause he's the one
ended up dead.
Hey, what's your question?
How you people find him
under all that cement?
A dog.
Dog, huh?
Yeah.
So why am I not dead?
I never killed nobody for fun.
It was my job.
And I'm retired.
Now, listen.
I know you fellas get in trouble
if you lose your gun.
I'm taking the bullets,
though, if you don't mind.
Oh.
Well, what about me?
Settle down.
What?
Settle down, relax.
Someone'll find you.
You have a good day now.
I just want to talk
about your mother.
Booth is missing.
It's been over 18 hours.
He tried to take down
Hugh Kennedy by himself?
He's only got one leg
and he's old.
Yeah, you know
how he got old?
By being fast and paranoid.
He cut off his own leg.
Booth is tough.
What does the FBI say?
Nothing.
Yeah, "need to
know," right?
Mm-hmm.
I want to do something, but
I don't... I don't know what.
Are you asking?
You'd help find the man who's
going to put you in jail?
Well, Booth will...
will do the best he can,
I'll do the best I can,
and we'll see how it works
out when we get there.
W-Where did he find Kennedy?
Baltimore.
I'm afraid that's
not Hugh Kennedy.
What's that called when they
wrap a sausage in a pancake?
Pigs in a blanket.
Now how'd you get here?
How'd you get here?
Billy Ray was killed
by an ice pick in Baltimore.
We asked around.
Was it Hugh Kennedy that
bundled you up in a carpet?
Look, I can't discuss
an ongoing investigation
with civilians, all right?
So just cut me out of here.
Hey, what are you doing with my
gun? Put that down.
Okay, time to step out
of your comfort zone, people.
What comfort zone?
We've stopped working.
I'd like to start again.
We process evidence.
There's no more evidence
for us to process.
He's right. We process,
Booth interprets.
I'd like to give it a try.
Yeah, we suck at interpretation.
We absolutely blow.
Um, what do you want us to do?
Work what we know.
McKenna was probably killed
by Kennedy.
Booth ran afoul of Kennedy.
I'm with you.
I'm with you, not ahead of you.
Okay, is there any
forensic evidence on our victim
that might lead
to Kennedy and Booth?
Yeah, I mean,
I've finished the inventory
on McKenna's tracksuit.
There were flakes
of tobacco,
fibers from the upholstery
of a Crown Victoria,
popcorn, chocolate,
a host of other wool
and cotton threads.
Okay, what does that tell us?
That the man was a pig?
All right, look,
there were also
cellulose fibers
consistent with newsprint,
gum from a number
of different mouths.
Uh, he had dried
chunks of human mucous,
a half dozen
filaments of nylon
consistent with
women's hosiery.
Oh! Uh, Kennedy
was a transvestite.
Keep going.
The rest was
just waxy buildup
from soap
or upholstery cleaner.
Let's assume
all this adds up to a place.
Crime scene.
Close your eyes
and imagine the smell
of all those things.
Tobacco, snot,
gum,
popcorn,
a lot of clothing, chocolate...
A porno movie theater!
You can't smoke at the movies.
I don't know about porno.
Upholstery cleaner,
Crown Victoria...
I got it.
A taxi cab.
McKenna was killed
in a taxi cab.
Yes.
Where are you going?
To tell the FBI
they're looking for a one-legged
cabbie in Baltimore.
You know, you guys,
it's not like
we all know each other
off the field, so...
But you know a man
with a prosthetic leg?
Uh... yeah,
I've seen him around.
We need his name.
No, honey,
he'd be using a fake name.
No, we need to know
where he lives.
Well, maybe he's listed
under his fake name.
He's too careful for that.
He drives a cab.
How do you know that?
My associates
are very good, Dad.
Can I ask a question?
Do you guys have any, like,
official I.D. or anything?
I can have the FBI here
in 20 minutes.
No, no, no.
Screw the FBI.
No, no, no!
Hold on! Easy!
Take it easy, pal.
Where does he live?
I don't know!
Dad!
No!
All right, all right!
Halton Inn on Decatur.
No, no, no!
Dad, he told us!
Are you lying to me? Because
if you are, I'll know it!
Halton Inn on Decatur,
just past the tracks. Easy.
Wha...?!
What's that all about?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Your dad's a psycho,
by the way.
You have no idea.
Do you have a one-legged
old man staying here?
Give me 40 bucks.
Room number, please.
Dad!
I... I have money.
Dad, look out!
Who is she?
I don't think
she's going to tell us.
Come on, help me!
Pull! Pull!
???
Hey. Hey, listen to me.
I like you.
But if you make
another move on me,
I will hurt you. You understand?
If her name's Veleska,
she's the same bounty hunter
who brought in Kennedy's leg.
How'd you find him?
It's not that hard
to find a one-legged,
old, white hit man
in Baltimore.
Why is she after him?
She has to make sure
that Kennedy
stays gone.
I helped
a wanted fugitive evade arrest.
I'm not going to jail.
What have you got?
It's a left anterior molar.
It's Booth's tooth.
Where's Booth?
Temperance, honey!
Kennedy has Booth, Dad.
He's got Booth!
Okay.
Perhaps he didn't see Kennedy.
Yeah? How'd you come
to that thought?
Well, Kennedy would
have left him
with an ice pick
protruding from his head.
Just one simple
question, big dog.
Did you see Kennedy?
Well, we could
get our own ice pick.
Make it look
like Kennedy killed him.
You know we can't let you live,
right?
You've been struck
and restrained.
Technically, kidnapping
a federal agent is as bad
as murdering him
these days.
How would you like to kill him?
First, I got to know for sure
if Kennedy is dead or alive.
Good luck with that one,
big dog.
Oh, big dog.
I suppose we could do that thing
that McKenna used to do,
but I'd need a blowtorch
and a sharpened screwdriver.
Just tell us.
Woof.
Cute.
Oh!
Must be his kid.
Yeah.
Head like a anvil.
I hurt my hand.
All right.
I'm gonna let you take a look
at your sweet boy,
consign his face
into your memory,
and then I'm gonna ask you which
one of your eyes you like best.
Definitely Booth's tooth.
I knew it.
Brennan...
You're not alone in this.
I know I'm not alone.
We all want to find Booth.
I know.
This is one of those times
when I have no idea
what's happening.
Brennan, wait.
I have to go, Ange.
What's going on?
I've got to find Booth.
I'm coming with you.
No.
I can't fight
or shoot a gun,
but if something bad
happens, I can spit
with deadly accuracy.
Thanks, but no.
Why can't you tell me?
By definition,
I can't tell you.
All right, all right,
Hodgins is outside
in his fastest car.
It's Italian.
One call and he follows
you everywhere.
Angela...
All right, you're after a
crazy, old, ice pick hit man
who has Booth.
You need help.
Look at my face.
Do you really see
me backing down?
I... I already have help, Ange.
From who?
From someone
worse than Kennedy.
Are you serious?
Don't say it.
You're father
is helping you?
I have to go.
Dad!
Was it Booth's tooth?
Yes. Stop that.
What are you doing?
Well, we have to know for sure
if Kennedy is alive or dead.
I mean, what if she and
her friends took Booth?
If this bothers you,
maybe you should go.
No, alpha male,
man of action...
I... I get it.
Now, tell us.
Okay... okay...
Kennedy is alive.
I was chasing him
for the bail.
He was smarter than me,
and he gave me a choice:
help him fake his death
or die myself.
Where'd you get the body?
We stole some dead old geezer
from a mortuary in Charleston.
Where is my partner?
When I got here,
no one was here.
I swear.
What do we do with her?
The room is paid for
through the end of the week.
Kennedy does not have Booth.
How do you know?
He's only got one leg.
So?
Well, so he's retired.
He's like me.
He just... he just
wants to disappear.
Then who's got Booth?
Well, there's only one other
significant player in all this.
???
What am I going to do
with you when I
get to the lab?
I'll just take a nap
here in the car.
Awfully exciting day
for an old guy like me.
Booth is being held
by Melvin Gallagher.
That's a leap.
How do you know?
Can we just go
with this, please?
Of course not.
Obviously, Brennan found
out from her father--
who is a wanted fugitive.
Ange!
Now that I can go with.
We need to figure out where
Gallagher is holding Booth.
Has anybody noticed that every
time there's a panic situation,
all eyes turn to Hodgins?
It's okay.
What's he
supposed to do?
Shoes.
Shoes?
Gallagher said the last time
he saw McKenna
he was leaving for vacation
after a tough night at work.
You think Gallagher might have
a place
he takes people
for that sort of thing?
Let me go over
Cement Head's shoes--
see what they tell us.
Methyl-Ethyl-Ketone.
It's a solvent.
See if it has any
specialized uses.
Also chromic
MEK and chromic acid are both
used to prepare metals.
Prepare metals for what?
Coating-- painting mostly.
Electroplating.
I'm seeing micro-thin deposits
of aluminum here.
Shavings?
No, it's more anodized...
vapor deposition.
Gallagher flies everywhere?
An aluminum propeller requires
a coating that could withstand
between ten and 20 tons
of centrifugal force.
Preferably anodized.
These are Gallagher's
tax returns.
We're looking for the
purchase of any machine
that could be used
for anodization.
What, like
a copier, or...?
Oh, that's so
cute, but no.
Look for the words
"lamination, electroplating."
"Alloy membranes,
catalytic bed reactor..."
"A serial thermal processor."
"Vacuum pyrolysis."
"D-330 Vacuum plating
processor"?
Yeah, that's it.
That's it.
Yes, this is Dr. Brennan
at the Jeffersonian.
I just received a call
from Agent Booth
that he's being
held at...
the Purdue Airfield
in Oakville, Virginia.
Send backup, I'm going in.
You just lied your ass off
to the Federal Bureau
of Investigation.
That is so hot.
If you lie really still,
you may not die.
I need your car.
Max Keenan,
you're under arrest.
Not if I get the keys.
They're in the ignition.
Well, it's not like I actually
gave him the keys.
Why didn't you just... just
tell them about Kennedy?
Well, I needed to give
you time to find me.
I've been tortured worse.
So, uh, you hear anything
from your old man?
He left my car in the garage.
He'll be back.
How do you know?
Max Keenan does not strike
me as the kind of guy
who, uh, leaves things undone.
Next time he shows up,
what do I do?
Do I call you?
Do I knock him on the head?
What's my obligation?
Well, if I were you, Bones,
I'd want to know what he has
to tell you about your mother.
But, uh... that's just me.
There's, uh, this old song.
It's called "Keep on Trying."
Yeah, Poco.
You know it?
Yeah, what about it?
It's a good old song, right?
Right.
welcome to www.1000fr.com