What did you do ?
I read, walked on the beach, chilled.
Oh, you chilled, in Darfur.
You chilled in Darfur ?
In North Carolina.
I changed my vacation plans
to spend time with my brother.
Ross and I talked about it and
we really wanna find dad.
Okay, well, just so you know, the FBI's
gonna find your father,
no matter what you want.
My brother and i don't want the FBI
to backburner the search.
is it okay to go over
on two wheels like that ?
Only when making very sharp
turns at high speeds.
Hey, Bones, why don't you have a little,
uh, you know, faith in me, okay ?
I'm not gonna backburner the case.
All right ?
I'm gonna find your father.
My brother said you'd say that.
You really keep saying "my brother" a lot.
Well, I lost ross for 15 years.
I like the sound of it.
My brother.
What's with the siren ?
Why are you driving like a maniac ?
Two passenger cars
off the tracks.
One on the side.
There's gonna be fatalities.
Stan ! I need some gauze !
Danny !
You don't find the owner of this in the
next ten minutes, he'll bleed to death.
Starting... now.
Seeley.
Camille.
Don't call me Camille.
Don't call me Seeley.
Dr. Brennan.
Dr. Saroyan.
You two know each other, right ?
No.
Dr. Brennan, I'd like you
to check out the automobile
this train hit...it's probably
what caused the derailment.
Accidental ?
NTSB guy says the train struck a car
at least 200 yards from the nearest access.
Deliberate ?
Eight minutes, Steve !
Probably suicide.
Why are you
still here, Dr. Brennan ?
Because I'm not a coroner,
and I don't work for you.
Well, you got that half right.
Dr. Cam.
Still breathing !
Thanks, Steve ! All right.
Every survivor is one less
person for me to autopsy.
You look good out of your suit, Seeley.
But then, you always did.
Yeah. That's...
great to have you
back in D.C, Camille.
One minute she's holding a severed arm,
the next she's hitting on you.
No, she wasn't hitting on me,
and you know what ?
She is your boss, Bones.
No, goodman's my boss.
May I approach ?
All yours, Dr. Brandon.
Brennan. Dr. Brennan.
You want to guess my name ?
No, but there are thousands of you
in D.C and only one of me.
While you were away, goodman
decided that there should be
a head of forensics at the jeffersonian.
It....occurred to you
to check in, huh ?
Why didn't goodman hire me ?
Oh, my guess...
people skills.
You know, I have people skills.
Aw, all right. That firefighter's name
is Nelson.
It's at least the fourth time
that you've met him.
Odds are Cam knows his kids'
names after meeting him once.
A lot of jewelry. Male.
Thigh bone suggests he was tall.
An I.D Bracelet.
It's good quality gold, slightly melted.
Too melted for a regular car fire.
Do you see a skull ?
Hey, Bones,
I'm not looking for a skull.
Burn damage in the body is more
intense than I'd expect from a car fire
even if the fuel tank ruptured and
was absolutely full at the time of impact.
Oh, I don't know.
Do you see anything on this car
that isn't ruptured ?
Booth, three deaths
in the first-class car.
Oh, homicide.
That makes it my case.
One of them's a Senator.
That makes a difference ?
Facts of life, Bones.
Apparently Cam is autopsying a Senator.
A Senator ? Oh, we're moving up in the world.
They have a past.
Cam and the Senator ?
Cam and booth.
Look how she touches his arm
when he laughs.
You touch my arm when I laugh.
No, no, you touch me.
It's a big difference.
Okay, what do we got ?
Male, 40's, approximately
six foot seven, right-handed.
Six foot seven ?
Athlete in his youth.
Right shoulder is worn
from a repetitive motion.
Baseball pitcher maybe.
More like a...basketball.
Basketball.
Mm, six foot seven...
it makes sense.
Every bone in his body is broken.
Dude, he got hit by a train.
"W-A-R."
It's all I can make
out of one name.
And then, "love, Briana."
Dude !
You're saying "dude" way too much.
Forties, six foot seven, W-A-R, Briana ?
This is Warren Lynch.
Who's Warren Lynch ?
No way.
Warren Lynch ?
Lynchpin international Warren Lynch ?
Yeah.
I am not telling the press
that Warren Lynch killed Senator Paula Davis
before we're completely certain.
i know Senator Davis.
I signed a book for her
to give to her daughter.
Oh, man, I love Paula Davis.
She could of been President.
Warren Lynch and Senator Davis
killed in one accident ?
No way it's a coincidence.
Hey, hodgepodge...all engines reverse.
First we identify beyond the shadow of a doubt,
then we get paranoid.
I'm cool. As long as paranoia
is on the schedule somewhere.
It wasn't suicide.
Jagged edges to the breaks.
Small fragments,
a lack of circular
or radiating fractures,or adherent spurs.
What does that mean ?
This man was dead for several hours
before the train hit him.
We are tighter than
a nun's knees ononhis one.
No press, no conjecture
with anyone outside this room.
Why ?
Because we are gonna find the details
of Senator Davis's death
without giving oliver stone
or Michael Moore any ideas.
Are we assuming Senator Davis's death
was a coincidence ?
You want to kill someone,
planting yourself
in front of a train...
probably not the best idea.
But too early to make
any assumptions.
I am a diuretic seagull, people.
Everything goes through me.
10:00 A.M. ?
Here ? Tomorrow ?
Zacharoni, your turn
to bring the doughnuts.
Zacharoni ?
Cam noticed that I eat macaroni
and cheese everyday at lunch.
Every single day ?
You should be okay
with Dr. Saroyan
getting the head-of-forensics job.
Why is that ?
Because you are a strictly
rubber-to-the-road,hardball scientist.
You're not a flesh-pressing,
ink-stained,policy-making, wank-tard.
What are her qualifications ?
Chief coroner of new york for two years,
assistant federal coroner before that.
How am I doing ?
Very well. Impressive.
Brennan.
we were discussing her mother's case.
Fine.
Well, I'll be there in 15 minutes.
Yes. Good, Dr. Brennan.
We'll chat later.
It's a very interesting case.
Brennan identified skeletal remains
as her mother's,
killed by a blow to the head...initial
suspect was her father,
but in the end,we arrested a pig
farmer hit man in witness protection.
Added wrinkle, brennan
gets called...Dr. Hodgins ?
You're chattering me to
death 'cause you hope
i'll forget you called
me a wank-tard.
It's a made-up word.
No meaning.
My name is Lisa Supak
and I am the assistant U.S Attorney
attached to this case.
I'd like to hear first from the national
transportation and safety board, Mr. Hobbs.
Thank you. At 8:04 this evening,
a high-speed commuter train
struck a private vehicle.
The front car derailed,
killing three people,
including Senator Paula Davis.
Preliminary indications show
that the car was placed there purposely.
Dr. Brennan, was the jeffersonian able to confirm
that the driver of the car was Warren Lynch ?
Dental records and physical characteristics
establish that, yes.
The vehicle's registered
to Mr. Lynch.
We'll verify that the jewelry
found on his body was his.
Plus, we have this.
A photograph from the carpool lane ?
At 1:56 this afternoon,
Mr. Lynch drove illegally
in the diamond lane on I-270,
our good old maryland state police cameras,
they caught the infraction.
This is definitely the vehicle
found on the tracks ?
Nobody saw or heard from Warren Lynch
after this photo was taken.
You can't honestly expect
anyone to believe
that Warren Lynch committed
suicide by driving into a train.
Daniel burrows, securities exchange commission.
We were about to lead charges
against Mr. Lynch
that would not only
wipe him out financially,
but send him to prison
for several years.
I heard rumors, but for a man
like Lynch to kill himself...
Mr. Lynch did not commit suicide.
Dr. Brennan's examination
shows that he was dead
for at least six hours before
the train struck his car.
Dead how ?
I don't know that yet.
But can we assume that it was foul play ?
When it becomes public knowledge
that Warren Lynch is dead,
stock in Lynchpin International
is going to plummet.
Well, it sucks for the people
invested in Lynchpin
but otherwise...
that's motive for murder.
How is losing money a motive ?
It's called shorting a stock.
Uh, basically
you bet that the share price is gonna fall
and when it does, you collect.
How much we talking ?
Tens, maybe hundreds of millions.
Yes, these are Warren's things.
I bought him the I.D. Bracelet
on our first anniversary.
"Casu consulto."
What does that mean ?
"Accidentally on purpose."
Why do you know things like this ?
It was kinda my husband's motto.
Mr. Lynch wrote about it in his autobiography.
He played basketball in college.
Made it all the way in
the national championships.
Warren was the high scorer,
but a player on the other team
locked him out of the key.
Warren injured the opposing player,
sent him to the hospital,
and made it look completely inadvertent.
"Accidentally on purpose."
He wrote this about himself
as if it were a good thing ?
Well, you don't become Warren
Lynch by playing by the rules.
I'm still his wife so this
all comes to me now, correct ?
Still his wife, Mrs. Lynch ?
Are you and Mr. Lynch
having marital problems ?
Warren and I were separating.
Why ?
Infidelity.
On who's part ?
I found out that Warren
was seeing someone only...
the someone turned out to be...
some dozen.
Mm. I'm gonna need a list.
When Briana confronted Warren,
he had a private investigator
look into her activities.
I admit, he didn't come up dry.
Private investigator's name ?
Rick Turko.
He was one of Lynch's
all-purpose, go-to, dirty-work fixer.
Yeah, I'm familiar
with rick turko.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Cheating spouse stands
to inherit it all,
corrupt business practices
and turko the private dick.
Where do we start ?
Two types of glass were embedded
in what was left of Lynch.
Let's start with glass.
Tempered automotive safety glass
and silicate.
Tempered glass
came from the car windows.
What about the other ?
It's 70% amorphous silicone dioxide.
What's that ?
It's a common domestic container.
Oh, like a jar. Mm.
Why can't we just say "a jar" ?
Anything new, zackaroni ?
Zackaroni ?
The victim's left shoulder and elbow
we're badly dislocated postmortem.
You mean between the time he died
and the time he got hit by the train.
Blood flows nonexistent when
the dislocation occurred.
Okay, you guys do this stuff
and I'll start on turko.
What's that ?
A private investigator.
Turko's an affliction.
I'll set up a meeting and call you, okay ?
You shouldn't call me zackaroni.
Yeah, I knew that the moment I said it.
I'm going to get a bone mineral
density reading.
You didn't actually want
the job, did you ?
I don't even know
what the job is.
Well, Goodman will
explain his decision.
Goodman appointed dr. Saroyan
while I was on vacation
then took a two month sabbatical
to avoid me.That explains a lot.
All right, you know,
I think it's because
you are very task oriented.
Zack. Task oriented is a euphemism
for lacking overall perspective.
Oh, no. No.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, a little.
Like, when's my birthday ?
I could get the computer
to remind me about birthdays.
Oh, that's one of a gajillion examples.
You could tell me the other
gajillion minus one.
What do you see zack ?
Yeah, uh, bone loss.
Lack of bone density
suggests that Warren Lynch
is much older than his 40'S.
But the other indicators of age,
epiphysial rings, cranial
sutures, all disagree.
Age doesn't explain the
ossification of cartilage
where the ribs meet the sternum.
Well, what does explain it ?
Opiates.
Warren Lynch was a heroin addict.
A private investigator.
My greatest asset is my discretion.
Briana Lynch already told us
that you worked for
her husband, Mr. Turko.
Well, Mrs. Lynch is welcomed
to say whatever she likes.
That client confidentiality routine
no longer exists when the client is dead.
That's not the assurance
i give my very demanding,
very high profile clients.
'Til death do us not part.
Yeah, how would your
very demanding,
very high profile clients feel
if they found out that, uh,
you procured heroin for Warren Lynch.
What ?
Warren Lynch
was a heroin addict.
I'm gonna open up
a drug investigation
on you, Mr. Turko...once
the press gets wind of that
your very high profile clients
will find some other
unprincipled Mr. Fix-it.
Warren Lynch was a junkie ?
What's your evidence ?
Bones.
So what does all this mean ?
Sum it up for the man, Bones.
Warren Lynch suffered declining
bone mass due to long term abuse
of his hypothalamic
pituitary gonadal access.
Nothing says junkie like your
gonads access, Ricky.
I had no idea.
And I certainly...procured
any heroin for him.
Warren Lynch sure as hell wasn't trolling
for ten dollar hits
in lincoln heights.
Come on, agent booth, you know my rep.
I'm a sin eater.
I make problems go away.
You mean like when Lynch's wife found out
that he was sleeping with other women.
all right, anything I say
strictest confidence, correct ?
Warren Lynch brought me in
to deal with a blackmailer.
Warren Lynch was being blackmailed ?
By one of his girlfriends ?
That would be my assumption, yes.
I paid them off before,
but this was a much
bigger deal, more serious.
Had to be the heroin, right ?
How'd it play out ?
Well, I negotiated
the payment down from a mil
to a quarter million, paid them off.
That was three days ago.
How ?
Dead drop at rock creek park.
And you have no idea who it was.
Well, I had a phone call,
I traced it back,
it dead-ended on a stolen cell phone.
You did a good job.
Given your heroin bombshell,
I went back to what tissue
remained and found traces
of laudanine and raticuline.
Alkaloids found
in the opium poppy.
I'd like Angela to do
a facial reconstruction.
Confirm my finding ?
It's handy having a pathologist
right in the building.
To turn opium into heroin,
it's exposed to hot acidic and hydride,
which produces 18 neutral impurities.
The ratio of these impurities indicates
the heroin's origin, in this case mexico.
Mexican heroin is very common.
I wonder if there's anything we can do
to narrow it down further.
Gas chromatography...
shows there was also
fetanyl in the heroin.
What's that ?
This reminds me
of when you interviewed me
to be your grad student.
She knows what fetanyl is.
It's a narcotic which boosts
the effects of the heroin.
According to Metro Cops,
14 addicts od'd this week
off this one shipment.
Have you told booth ?
I'll leave that to you.
How'd I do ?
I thought she
did quite well.
You said you had
something else to show me.
In a car fire gasoline vapor
ignites at 280 degrees celsius
and rises to a plain temperature
of 2200 degrees.
If the gas tank were
full at the time of impact,
the fire should of burned
for approximately 20 minutes
without intervention.
Tell me that's
not a real skeleton.
No, we made him out
of calcium phosphate and hydroxyapatite.
And spam.
20 minutes now.
It's still a significant
amount of spam.
And according to the fire
department report,
the car burned for 40 minutes
and it still took
four minutes to put out.
Which means
there was extra fuel.
And the extra glass you found ?
Five gallon mason jars.
Six of them.
Filled with gasoline.
Yeah, or moonshine.
Why does the whole lab
smell like a luau ?
zack and hodgins are proving
that there was extra
accelerant in Lynch's vehicle.
Using what medium ?
Artificial bone
covered with spam.
Turn this off.
Why wasn't I told about this ?
I encourage
independent inquiry.
Your encouragement does not
signify my authorization.
If it happens again
i will take action,
and I'm from new york,
which means that I will take new york
action, am I clear ?
Not at all.
I'm from michigan.
Dr. Saroyan means she'll make us
watch musical theatre.
Wrong new york.
I'm more from the get mugged in broad
daylight tradition.
This is not a high school
science fair.
This is the jeffersonian institute.
Unauthorized experiments in
forensics will get you fired.
But we're hodgepodge and zackaroni.
And they work for me.
You know, what I'd really
like to do here
is enjoy a meeting of the minds.
But if you insist on an
organizational pyramid,
I will be at the top.
Spam.
Yup. There are mason jars
filled with gasoline in the backseat
intended to break when the train hit.
Mm, and they got this with spam ?
Yeah, spam.
And Cam, she got all
bent out of shape.
She wants to authorize
all experiments.
Great. You know,
zack and hodgins, they do an
experiment with fake Bones and spam.
Yeah, what is your spam fixation ?
Uh, defense lawyer hears
spam, he makes a joke,
the jury laughs and everything
we get from the jeffersonian
is framed as, uh,
goofy science, you know,
from a bunch of squints with no
connection to the real world.
That wouldn't happen.
Really ? And the time
you dropped the dead monkey
down the elevator shaft ?
No, that was to show...
okay, I take your point.
Look Cam's goal is a successful
prosecution in a court of law.
Same as mine and yours.
No, you're all about
finding the truth.
Okay, your words say good,
but your tone says bad.
So it's confusing.
Cam knows that too much truth
is just as bad as too little.
which is why she got the job.
Booth.
You know, Angela says
that you and Cam had a sexual relationship.
Does that effect your view of her ?
Patch me through.
Wildly out of line,
just so you know that.
When ?
Did you get the doer ?
personal prerogative is at the
heart of scientific inquiry.
Bones.
Thanks for the notification.
What ?
The man who was charged with
murdering your mother...
the pig farmer, vince mcvicar.
He was killed.
Today at Alexandria federal facility.
I don't...
he was the only connection to my father.
His trial was gonna be my...
how am I ever gonna find out
what really happened ?
That's not Warren Lynch.
How accurate is this thing ?
It's not the machine that's
accurate, it's Angela.
And she's good.
That is not Warren Lynch.
Hey, Zack provided a skull
and this is the face that goes with it.
You know, could it be the wrong skull ?
Zack doesn't make that kind of mistake.
He's also very good.
What about the dental records ?
I'll check them for a tampering.
But you're certain
that the body in the car...
is not Warren Lynch.
Absolutely certain.
the man in the car was
not Warren Lynch ?
No. No this was the man behind the wheel.
You had dental records.
Well, somebody digitized
Lynch's dental x-rays
and then re-filmed them,
utilizing authentic
alpha-numeric bar codes.
Their records were expertly faked.
Then where the hell is Warren Lynch ?
I've informed the FBI
that they might want to start looking for him,
in the meantime,
we're moving to I.D. This guy.
Mistakes like this cannot happen
when the case concerns a dead Senator.
Ms. Montenegro uncovered a fraud,
that's the opposite of a mistake.
Save it for the press conference, Dr. Saroyan.
Thank you.
Hey, if you'd made a mistake,
I'd have thrown you to the wolves.
The metro cops hated the guy
pushing the mexican heroin,
laced with fentanyl is Eddie Bean :
Young guy,
baldy-headed,
five-five,
145 pounds.
You know, if drugs
we're legalized,
they could be dispensed
from a clean, safe,
controlled outlets,
by trained personnel,
not in alleyways,
by criminals.
Yeah... right.
Hey, that's our guy,
let's go !
Hold on ! Whoa ! Shh !
What we're gonna do
is we gotta wait until he deals.
Catch him in the act.
We wait ?
For how long ?
However long it takes.
Well, what do we do while we wait ?
This is a stakeout,
we converse.
Well, I tried to initiate
conversation on the drug war, but...
Oh, god. Fine.
You know what ?
Let's just...
talk about something
we're not going to argue about.
have you been out
to your mother's grave ?
Not since the funeral.
Really ?
Why would I ?
Well, to connect.
She's dead.
fine. You know what ?
Forget it.
"Dead," as in gone from this world ?
Excuse me.
I'm curious.
Um, do you talk to the headstone ?
I mean, what do you,
what do you say ?
It looks like I'm talking
to the headstone,
but what I'm really saying
is that...
forget about where the words are aimed.
What I say is that...
I remember them.
They can't hear you because they're dead.
My mouth moves, words come out,
but none seem to get across
the drawbridge to the princess,
I know who waits within.
We're on !
What princess ?
Hey ! Ho !
Hey, Eddie.
How you doing, Eddie ?
pockets...watch out for needles.
Don't you have to read him his rights
before you strangle him ?
Empty.
Okay, you know,
I had to hold his throat closed
so he wouldn't swallow the evidence.
If you bite me,
I will squeeze your little pin head off.
Okay.
Okay, oh, easy.
There it is.
You shouldn't swallow heroin,
it's dangerous.
Great. Come on, Eddie.
Eddie...
Eddie ! Eddie, Eddie,
Eddie, Eddie. Hey, Eddie.
I'm gonna ask you a question.
Okay ?
You answer...you'll walk away.
All right ?
If you don't answer...
you book me, I get sick.
I know the drill.
If you don't answer...
I'm gonna cram this
back down your throat
without the protection.
All right. You sold some of this
crap to a tall guy,
over six-and-half feet tall.
Show him, Bones.
What ?
Show him.
I think that tall ?
Uh... nobody I know.
here. Come on, eat it.
Eat...that's it.
Get it in there.
That's it.
Ray !
Ray ?
Ray. Ray story.
Tell me about Ray. Huh ?
Everybody knows him down here,
man, he's a longtime skel.
When was the last time you saw him ?
He bought a stick of dynamite
about three days ago.
I feel I should alert you :
There's an additive in this
heroin that causes overdoses.
Well, thanks.
Hey, where'd you find her ?
Museum.
we should warn the addicts.
Yeah, like they do on a pack of cigarettes.
When ? Thanks.
What ?
They found Warren Lynch.
Mr. Lynch was thrown from a speeding car.
It's a minor miracle he survived.
It may be because he was
already unconscious at the time.
Unconscious ?
Yes.
Badly Beaten.
Internal bleeding,
broken ribs, both legs.
Some spinal damage.
Broken pelvis.
When can we talk to him ?
Any time you want.
As long as you don't expect a response.
This man has severe brain damage.
Off the record : He's not going to wake up.
Best case scenario :
He spends the rest of his life
hooked up to feeding tubes.
This is one of the richest men in the country.
Most of the time that might mean something.
Not now. Dr. Lawrence,
this man holds the key to how and why
Senator Paula Davis died.
I'm sorry.
Anything that man has in his head...
it's going to stay there.
Excuse me.
.... a hundred times.
It's important for us to explain
how the victim's shoulder
and elbow we're dislocated.
I recreated the most likely sequence.
The victim was dead when this happened.
He didn't feel it.
Run it again.
Almost like he was putting his jacket on.
Corpses don't usually do that.
These injuries occurred
when the corpse was forced into a jacket.
Yeah, most likely by two people.
Yeah, in a big hurry.
They had a train to meet.
You got anything on the H.O.V
Lane photograph ?
Yeah. It was relatively easy to get
the license plate numbers from these two cars.
Yeah, well...
I'll check 'em out.
Uh, there was another car.
In the next lane.
How do you know that ?
Well, rich guys keep their cars shiny.
Adjusting for the diffraction
of light caused by the curve...
it's a navigator.
But get this.
I don't know if that's of any use to you.
Yeah. That's of use.
Booth...
do either of these count as experiments ?
'Cause if they do,
we could both get fired...
by your old sweetheart.
you know, you just quit telling, Bones,
who you think I've slept with.
"Think" ?
What do you mean "think" ?
Two people forced a corpse into a jacket,
that's... excellent work.
Who's that ?
I think it's rick turko.
It means Turko's probably the last person
to see Lynch before he fell off the radar.
Of course, Angela and zack are scared
that this counts as an experiment,
and you are going to fire them.
Ah ! I am getting through.
Why did you take this job, Camille ?
Why shouldn't I, seeley ?
Because it's
basically herding cats
and you're a dog person.
Dogs herd cats.
Dogs don't do that.
Eh, chase 'em up trees, whatever.
Seriously, Cam, why did you take this job ?
These... are titanium
rib clippers from germany.
My last job ?
Used bolt cutters from home depot.
These are much, much nicer.
This autopsy table,
has down-draft ventilation
no rotting-corpse smell,
seeley.
My last table didn't even have a drain.
Think about that a second :
Leaky corpse, no drain.
So you took this job for better equipment ?
I've spent my whole professional life
in basement rooms with no windows.
Now I'm in the jeffersonian institute.
What ?
Gotta ask.
You so do not.
Did you take this job because of... ?
Oh, my god, the ego !
Go ahead, say it.
Nothing to do with you.
I need Bones this afternoon.
Okay.
It's about her mother's murder
and her father's disappearance.
Plus, she dedicated her book to you...
it's a legitimate case, Cam.
I know, I read the file.
Why hasn't she confronted me ?
About what ?
About me being parachuted in over her head.
Finds me intimidating, right ?
Hey, I intimidate people.
Yeah.
Bones doesn't intimidate.
Then what ?
Oh, you've seen the way
she stares at human remains
before she makes a decision.
Yes ?
You're human remains and
she hasn't made a decision yet.
How do I help her make
the right decision ?
Go for the truth.
Take care of her people.
Oh, and, uh,
I like the whole intimidation thing.
I think it's cute.
I got no reason to lie.
I'm facing life, at least
probably going to get executed.
What did you do ?
Mr. Downs killed his entire family.
I killed your friend
'cause he cut in the cafeteria line
and snagged the last orange juice.
Broke of a sharpened toothbrush
in his jugular.
Mr. Downs
the man you killed...
Mcvicar
...He's not my friend.
He killed my mother.
You come to tell me "thanks" ?
No. Mcvicar was my last chance
to find out some things.
Mcvicar might have known
something about my father.
I can't ask my father
because he left a message
on my answering machine, telling
me to stop looking for him.
I'll tell you what...
maybe...
look at Mcvicar's murder
as a second message from Max,
one that he didn't use
the phone for.
I never mentioned
my father's
name was Max.
I'm done
Did you perform a hit
for Max Keenan ?
You performed a hit
for Max Keenan.
Take it as a sign from god.
How am I going to tell russ our father
order the death of another human being ?
If he did that...and I'm not
saying it happened that way...
then your father took down
the man who murdered his wife.
Good people don't have other
people murdered.
Good people don't even know how.
Your father buried your mother
in a pair of new shoes
in the cemetery, with her dolphin belt buckle
that reminded her of you
because you both love dolphins.
That does not make him a good man.
People can be more than one thing.
We were at a dead end,
okay ? Now we're not.
Okay. We know that your
father got to mitchell downs,
persuaded him to kill mcvicar.
We find out
how he did that,
we're that much closer to finding out
what happened to your old man.
I mean that's... if you still
want to find him.
I still do
Okay. Silver lining.
Warren Lynch
was in on it.
Where'd that come from ?
He had his own dolphin,
that's not lots of "a's"
national championship ring ?
His own dolphin.
All of the rest of his jewelry was removed
and placed on the dead man:
His $10,000 watch,
his I.D. Band from his wife,
his two other rings,
but not the championship ring.
That's good, Bones.
The only reason they wouldn't rip
it off his hands is...
...because Lynch
was calling the shots.
And I know exactly who was in on it.
So, Warren Lynch and I conspired
to disappear him for a few days
so that we could profit from shorting
Lynchpin stock ?
Well, you know, that's my thinking.
then dressed a junkie in Warren's clothes,
planted him in front of a train and... wait.
Did I murder the junkie ?
No, Bones said you probably found him dead.
But what I think is that
you and Lynch intended
a white-collar crime,
but a Senator died.
Then I got all hinky and I tossed Warren out
of the car at 80 miles an hour ?
Is, is that a confession ?
No, no.
Just getting it straight.
You know, as a professional
investigator myself,
I have to point out that blackmailers
make much better suspects.
Lynchpin has no record of quarter-million
-dollar payout three days ago.
Well, there's not exactly a column
for blackmail payouts in the corporate books.
If I only agreed to the full payout,
Lynch might have...been taken
by those animals.
Hey, let's play a little show and tell, huh ?
'Cause we can put you with
Lynch moments before
he fell off the radar.
That's maybe me
before he fell off the radar.
We worked together.
You got nothing.
Booth. Do that lying thing.
Could you be more specific ?
Tell him Lynch woke up
and gave a statement incriminating him.
Turko knows the lying thing.
Tell him Lynch said something
only Lynch could say.
Ooh, great idea,
except for the "only Lynch could say it" part.
The ring ?
Ah, he'll ask for specifics of
the conversations.
I got to cut him loose.
He's going to get away with it ?
Well, you know, that
happens sometimes, Bones.
It's that brown little
smelly part of the job.
Shoulder and elbow.
The junkie's shoulder and elbow were dislocated
when they forced him into Lynch's jacket.
We don't know if Lynch was there for that.
It took two people.
It was him.
Come on, booth.
Part of you with the big gambling problem
must love this idea.
Right there.
That's the reason
you didn't get Cam's job.
Oh, two against one.
That's unfair.
Warren Lynch woke up.
Ah, and he's talking, right ?
Huh ?
Is he pointing his finger
straight at me ?
That's correct.
What's he saying ?
He let you take all of his jewelry
except his championship ring.
No, I asked,
what did he say in words ?
Hey, unless I'm under arrest,
I'm leaving, folks.
Mr. Lynch said it was difficult
getting his jacket onto the corpse.
Rigor mortis.
You have a train to meet.
You're in a hurry.
And the sound of the shoulder popping.
and elbow, like,
knuckles popping...
...only louder.
Sickening.
turko will admit to helping Warren Lynch
place a dead body in Mr. Lynch's car
and rigging it to burn
with the intent of moving the market.
Everything else, including
placing it on the tracks,
he says Lynch did on his own.
He's lying.
There's a small matter
of proving that in court.
What's the maximum sentence
on those charges ?
Ten years.
He killed three people.
And put one in a coma.
Yeah, but Lynch deserves to be in a coma,
so it doesn't count.
All right, look, turko puts
all the blame on Lynch,
he does ten years
and he gets all the money
for shorting the stock.
It's ten years or nothing.
I can only work with what I'm given,
and the forensic work
on this was not good enough.
What ?
You were fooled by fake dental records.
You baked some spam.
What did you want us to do ?
Your jobs.
Hey !
No, Miss Supek,
you want us to do your job.
My people gave you
all the evidence you need
to fry turko with any reasonable jury.
Forensically...
we gave you everything
you need to arrest turko.
Arrest in not a conviction.
We definitely gave you
enough to reject
his plea bargain and indict him
in the wrongful death of a Senator.
Indictment is not a conviction.
You accept that plea bargain,
the investigation stops.
Indict him,
give us time to give you what you need.
If you accept this plea bargain,
you don't deserve to be a federal prosecutor.
Dr. Saroyan...
yeah, it's scary.
The whole country will be
watching the trial and you
don't want to go in with
less than a sure thing.
But you put my people
on the stand as expert witnesses
and that's a sure thing.
Not Zack.
You tell the story of what happened,
using the evidence these people provided,
and if you have any ability as a prosecutor,
you'll win the case.
Are you finished ?
No, Miss Supek.
In the future, when you have
problems with my team,
you register them
with me in private,
not by grandstanding
in a public forum.
Okay...
um, I sort of see why she got the job.
Well, looks like your brother was here.
...Understood the idea
of bringing flowers.
Just for once, Bones,
do what people do, okay ?
See how it feels.
Come on. That's it.
Now I'm gonna go stand over here
while you, you know,
talk to your mom.
I told you, I don't do that.
Mom, it's me, temperance.
I have questions,
but you can't answer them.
No offense, but I don't think
there's anything here of you
but your Bones, so...
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Is dad a good man or...
a bad man ?
He had someone killed.
Had him murdered and...
what's the truth ?
Do I...
do I keep looking
or do I let it go like he asked ?
Who's he protecting, himself ?
Or me and russ ?
Booth.
I asked the questions,
and guess what.
No answer.
Well, maybe if you weren't
standing right on top of her,
took a step to the left,
showed just a little respect.
Sometimes it takes a while
to get an answer, okay ?
Just leave the flowers.
I get answers at a lab,
you get them from people.
Nobody gets answers
from a slab of stone.
Yeah, well, I see
an answer in the stone.
See, you buried your mother
as christine brennan,
the woman that you knew as your
mother and not by her real name,
Ruth Keenan.
That tells me who you are.
What do you got ?
A dolphin.
What does that tell you ?
My father was here.
Because he loves your mother
and grieves her loss
and he came here to talk to her.
You're tainting evidence.
It's not that kind of evidence, Bones.
It's evidence of something else.
Something that can't be tainted.
It's beautiful.