Oh,what happened?
Where am I?
Oh,come on!
Hodgins!
Hodgins,are you all right?
Can you talk?
Your legs.
What happened to your legs?
We're buried alive.
He must have got us.
Who?
The Grave Digger.
My superiors say to let you look at the...flying saucer.
It's not a flying saucer.
Well,it sure looks like one.
Local kids dirt-biking.
Something shiny poking from the dirt.
They dig it out,look in the window,see aliens.
Did you look?
Yes,ma'am.
Then called for backup. -Uh,why?
Well,on account of...well,they are aliens.
All right.
You want to take a look?
BOOTH: Are those what I think they are?
Yes.As long as you think they're two adolescent human males.
How long?
The amount of dehydrated tissue suggests the tank is sealed and intact.Years.
Two kids,huh?
I liked it better when they were aliens.
One set of remains shows trauma to the legs--
compound fractures,and his pelvis is broken in three places.
The other is virtually untouched.
Cause of death?
The amount of blood suggests that at least one of them bled out.
Probably the one with the injuries.
I've also noted a constellation of identical non-metric variants--
extra foramina.
BOOTH: Does that mean they were twins?
How did you know?
Matthew and Ryan Kent.
Kidnapped October 31,2001.
No one has seen them since.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=- Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-我是如此矫情 -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Bones Season 2 Episode 9
been positively identified as Matthew and Ryan Kent.
Come on,Peter,it's better than never knowing.
Agent Sanders,you were assigned to the Kent kidnapping?
Uh,Mr.Sanders-- I,uh,
retired from the FBI to pursue a career in general contracting.
Uh,when I'm sober.
Kim here was the Assistant United States Attorney attached to the case.
Still attached-- the file's still open.
The boys were snatched after a drinking party.
Was the ransom paid?
As the duly sworn representative of the FBI,I advised
Mr.Kent not to pay the ransom.
Unfortunately,the Kents listened to me and not the K&R guy,and,uh...
now their sons are dead.
K&R?
That's Kidnap and Ransom experts.
The Kent boys were the Grave Digger's third victims.
Third of the six we know of.
All together,four paid the ransom and lived.
And the other one that didn't?
Never found him.
That's why they call him the Grave Digger.
He takes people and he buries them.
You pay the ransom,and he tells you how to dig them up.
You don't,and,uh,you never see them again.
You won't catch him.
All due respect,uh,Agent Sanders,we have the beer vat and the human remains.
What are two dead bodies gonna tell you that four live victims couldn't?
Dr.Brennan,she's pretty good at,
uh,making dead people tell her things.
Look,my advice,talk to the K&R guy.
Kidnap and Ransom expert Thomas Vega,former FBI.
He literally wrote the book on the Grave Digger.
I became a Kidnap and Ransom specialist.
That's when I realized that the Bureau's policy
on non-payment to kidnappers is antiquated and dangerous.
You've dealt with the Grave Digger how many times?
In total,five.
Janine is a journalist-- she helped me write the book on the Grave Digger.
Next to me,she's the ranking expert on that...
Journalist,huh?
Oh,don't be like that,Agent Booth.
The Grave Digger is totally consistent.
No one ever sees the victim taken.
The ransom demand is made using a digitally altered voice.
A time limit is given.
There's never a second call.
As soon as the ransom is paid to a numbered untraceable account in Bahrain,
the Caribbean,et cetera,GPS coordinates are provided leading to the victim.
None of the surviving victims remembers anything before being taken?
Nothing.
Burn marks on the back of the neck suggest the use of a stun gun or cattle prod.
That'll scramble your brains pretty good.
Also,when you try to trace whatever container the boys were found in,you'll...
well,you'll reach a dead end.
He gets everything from landfills or cash auctions.
No last chance to pay up.
Never.
You know,most kidnappers are caught because they start negotiating the ransom.
The Grave Digger simply won't play.
I'm really not looking to help you write another book,you know...
Capturing the Grave Digger.
VEGA: Agent Booth,I have seen what this guys does to families up close.
You know what,dislike me as much as you want,
but I'm still gonna help you,because I want this...caught.
You were kind of mean to them.
Thanks.
Zack,did you catalog this anomaly between C-1 and C-2 on Matthew?
Yes.If you increase magnification on the atlanto-axial joint,
you'll see calcining on the articular process.
Bone burn.
YES.Over 300 degrees.
Stun gun.
Does the same mark appear on Ryan?
No.
Okay.
Get the FBI to send you photos and medical am results of the Grave Digger's victims.
See if he uses the same stun gun every time.
Aluminum. Aluminum?
The Brits say "Al-yu-mini-um," but it sounds,well,British.
Manganese alloy,strain-hardened and stabilized,traces on both sets of clothing.
From the vat?
No,the inside of the vat is pure copper.
Both boys' clothing was stained with a sooty residue made up of lead and carbon,benzene and aldehydes.
Engine exhaust.
Particulates from lots of engines,both gasoline and diesel.
Parking lot?
Underground,probably.
Think that's where the Digger grabs his victims?
Compare your findings with the results found on the clothing of the surviving victims.
See if they share anything in common.
Measure oxygen volume in the vat,find out how long the twins survived.
I'll get right on it.
Mr.Kent,I'd like to start by expressing the Justice Department'ssincere condolences
for the death of your sons,Matthew and Ryan.
If I'd ignored the Justice Department and listened to Mr.Vega here,
paid the $2 million,my boys would still be alive today.
Sir,I understand your feelings towards the FBI.
I doubt that.
VEGA: Jim,Agent Booth here is investigating your son's murder.
Now,you know my problems with the FBI's approach to kidnapping,
but when it comes to,uh,finding killers,you want these people on your side.
Ryan and Matty were spoiled.
I know.
They,uh,partied,they chased girls,they,um...
they got expelled from school...
but they weren't bad kids.
And there's no way that they deserved suffocation.
Is it...painful?
Like falling asleep.
Mr.Kent,the Grave Digger lied to you and the FBI.
That's unlikely.
doesn't play games.
Mr.Kent,is there any way you could've put together the ransom in 12 hours?
Oh,no way in the world.
Which is exactly why the Grave Digger provided Mr.Kent with 24 hours.
His sons only had enough air for 12 hours.
Oh,my...
Even if you had ignored the FBI and listened to Mr.Vega,
you still wouldn't have been able to save your sons.
Your backstopping for the Bureau.
There were two of them in that vat.
They used up their oxygen twice as fast.
The Grave Digger miscalculated.
No,he doesn't do that.
Then it was never his intention that these boys survive.
He just didn't care,Mr.Kent.
So my decision to listen to the FBI,to not pay the ransom...
If you'd paid the ransom,your sons would still have been dead by the time you got to them.
There's nothing you could have done,Mr.Kent.
You're in no way responsible for the death of your sons.
Has it occurred to you that God is a lot like the Grave Digger?
What?
He lays down the rules,no way to question Him or notiate,
then it's almost as though He doesn't care how it works out.
Either you do as He says,
make some sacrifices and are delivered or you don't and you end up in hell.
You know what?I'd appreciate if you didn't say things like that,
because I really don't want to get struck by lightning.
Do you go to church every Sunday? Yes,I do. -
Can I come with you?No,you can't.
Why?It might help me to understand.
I am not going to help you disrespect God in His own house,okay?
If you want to do some kind of,you know.anthropological study
you know,turn on the Religious Channel.
Each of these contain one of the Grave Digger's victims. -cozy.
We also provided your people with the clothes that each victim was wearing.
Regarding the clothing,every one of them shows traces of aluminum and sooty residue.
We know each victim was taken from an underground garage beyond the reach of security cameras.
The typical kidnap-for-ransom profile is middle-aged in a job that's beneath him.
Smart guy who's an underachiever and someone who enjoys control over somebody else's life.
There's just one problem.
What's that?
See,there's nothing typical about this guy.
Don't expect him to fit the profile.
Okay,the dimensions of the vat-- six feet wide by eight feet tall--
make it impossible for Matthew Kent to have fractured his brother's pelvis.
Even if Matthew knocked Ryan down and,you know,stomped on him?
Cam and I agree the fracture was the result of one hard blow.
A break like that would require a lot more force than Matthew could have generated
All right,so you're saying that Ryan was injured before he went into that vat.
Yes.With the amount of blood on the floor,
it can't be explained by his injuries alone.
What?
It was a mistake.
What was?
Look,he intended to take one boy,but he ended up with two.
That's why they died 12 hours ahead of schedule
If he intended to take two boys,
he would have put them in a container twice as big,all right?
The Grave Digger,he messed up.
He snuck up on Matthew,knocked him uncocious whatever,
and Ryan was there,he shows up and he fought the y.
No,Booth,not fight.
The leg damage,the fractured pelvis.
These injuries are classic human versus car.
Ryan interrupts the kidnapping of his brother...
And the Grave Digger runs him down.
It was a mistake.
The Grave Digger is not God,Bones,because God does not make mistake Mm,I don't know.
Putting testicles on the outside didn't seem like such a good idea.
Commercial stun gun,625,000 volts,still not enough.
Well,it sounds like a lot of volts.
Actually,it's the amperage that does the real damage.
But still,I've checked every commercial stun gun I can find,
and none of them generate the right amount of power to make those distinctive marks on the bone.
Well,what about a cattle prod?
Stun guns generate a lot more power than cattle prods.
If you haven't figured out the stun gun,
then I am this week's king of the lab,because I found something huge.
You compete to be king of the lab?
No.
Hey,Angela.I didn't know that you were...
This sucks.
I'm gonna go catch Brennan then bolt for the night.
She just left.
Hey...
Could you stop being so weird,please?
It's making me very uncomfortable.
You should give him a chance.
Excuse me?
I apologize.I didn't say anything.
Dr.Brennan!
What do you say we go to New York for the weekend?
I don't know.
Come on.We're two adults with no obligations.
Let it go to voicemail.
We're not cheating.
We're not hurting anybody,Seeley.
Then why are we keeping our relationship such a secret,amille?
Because we work together and we're professionals and it's nobody's business,that's all.
So,come to New York.
Oh,sure,we'll go to a musical.
Talking and singing and talking and dancing and more singing,you know?
If you want to stop,what we're doing,just say so.
You can fantasize about pulling out your gun and shooting everyone on sge.
You know you like that.
Seriously,we'll do something that you like
,like climbing the outside of the Empire State Building or swimming the East River or...
What?
What happened?
Temperance Brennan,Jack Hodgins have been buried alive.
Wire transfer $8 million to the following Grand Cayman account,
or they will suffocate to death.
ceipt of the wire transfer,
I'll provide you with Brennan and Hodgins' GPS coordinates.
This will be my last communication.
It will be his last communication,too.He's never varied.
He learned from the Kent boys.He got two of them.He cut the deadline in half.
Why is the Grave Digger demanding so much money?
It doesn't make any sense.
He's always been reasonable at knowing how much money people could raise within the time limit.
Has Dr.Brennan made that much money from her books?
It's Hodgins.
He's the sole heir to this thing called the Cantilever Group.
And what's that?
Just the third-largest privately owned corporation in the country.
Make sense now,Tom?
I was on my way to karate class,so we have lots of bottled water.
What happened?
Where are we?
Last thing I remember is being at the lab.
I'm really confused.
What happened to my legs?
Where are we?
Underground.
Buried.
I have a burn.
Zack was trying to figure out what kind of stun gun.
It has to be the Grave Digger.
I think he ran you down with his car
and then pumped you full of drugs to ruin your short-term memory,same as Ryan Kent.
How long have we been down here?
maybe two hours,I think.
Okay,so this vehicle has,say,60,60 cubic feet of air.
That's 20% oxygen,two people.
My brain is not working.
The Grave Digger is very consisnt.
If we started with 12 hours of air,we'll be unconscious in ten.
After that,if...
if no one pays the ransom...
We're dead?
How are we going to get our hands on $8 million?
Hodgins is rich. -He is?
"Rich squared to the power of ten times four" is how he describes it.
You're gonna pay the ransom,right?
FBI standard ops,they won't work.
Grave Digger operates outside statistics.
-They'll fire you. -That's cool.
One less reason to wear a suit.
How'd the Grave Digger catch Brennan and Hodgins together?
Bones was on her way to karate.
And Hodgins said that he found something huge.
He tried to catch Dr.Brennan.
Here!
Oh,my...
Oh,that's blood,isn't it?
It'll turn out to be Hodgins'.
Dr.Brennan doesn't like it when we jump to conclusions.
I'm sure she'll appreciate we're on a deadline.
Look,Hodgins interrupted the kidnapping,just like Ryan and Matthew.
The Grave Digger must have run him over.
What are we gonna do?
Well,it's a crime scene,right?
They'll look for tire tracks,they'll check the security cameras.
I need you to be Dr.Brennan.
I don't know what that means. It means keep working the case.
All right,I need to know why Hodgins was chasing after Bones.
I'll look at his notes. What about me?
Call Bones' brother Russ and tell him what's going on.
I'm gonna go talk to the chairman of the Cantilever Group.
We have water,towels,my mini kit,ibuprofen,
two cell phones with no batteries,a digital camera with a backup battery,and,uh...
a handful of pens.
That one's a laser pointer.
And,uh,a copy of my novel.
Hey,we can read it to each other if we get bored.
"Deep Rhapsody.
" Careful,that's three grand a quarter ounce.
Yeah,I'd make that face,too,if I spent $3,000 on perfume.
Oh,man!
Something...
My leg!
Okay,here,here.
I'm worried you have compartment syndrome.
Is that terminal?
I mean,within the next few hours?
No.
But?
It's gonna get painful.
More painful than now?
Slip-into-shock- and-die painful.
Well,there's nothing we can do about that.
Actually,there is.
Oh,I'm not gonna like this,am I?
What are you doing?
The Grave Digger modified a commercial stun gun to knock out his victims.
I figured out the voltage and amperage,
but not how he modified it to boost the current.
Which will not help us find Dr.Brennan and Hodgins.
I did figure out how Ryan Kent died.
Let's hear it.
He killed himself.He punctured his own carotid artery,
which explains the amount of blood we found in the vat.
He used a pen.There's a nick on the inferior angle of the mandible.
I don't know why he did it.I don't really do "why.
" I just do "how.
" He did it to give his brother more air,so his twin would survive.
That's why we found them holding each other.
How does that help?
When we tell Mr.Kent that one of his sons gave his own life in an effort to save his brother,
it'll mean something,Zack.
Just keep searching,okay?
Okay,I'm ready.
Was that a note to Angela?
Yeah,just in case.
If whatever you're gonna do to me sends me into shock,I might die.
Upside: me not breathing doubles your survival time.
I'm not interested in surviving that way.
What I'm going to do is make a long incision in the fascia to release the pressure inside.
And how...how long is a long incision?
Wait.You know what?Don't tell me.
It's best if I do it very fast and without empathy.
Here.
Hang on to something,d don't fight passing out.
Ready?
What is that?
Evidence of what happened to you.
Let's...let's worry about it later.
Here,just...
Put it in the pages of your book.
I'll take a look at it later.
It's best if you don't talk right now.
I'm nuts about Angela.
Over the moon.
Stupid in love with her.
That's why I bought her that...
that crazy,expensive perfume.
A man gives you a bottle of perfume like that,it says...
it says,"I love you.
" There.
I said it out loud.
Did you find Russ?
He's on a fishing trip with friends in the White Mountains.
No phone,no cell service.
You?
Hodgins seems to write everything in some kind of code.
I might have to get Zack over here to break it.
It says that the traces of aluminum found
on the clothing were almost certainly from t|| kidnapper's vehicle.
Like a box in the back of a trunk or a van.
You can read that?
Hodgins sends me a lot of notes.
Why bother with all of this?
We don't need evidence.
We need millions of dollars.
I can't get the ransom together-- not in time.
The Cantilever Group has got this policy--
no proof of life from the kidnapper,no ransom.
Not even for the boss? -It's his rule.It's no exceptions.
We need more time,except the Grave Digger doesn't give us that or proof of life.
Booth,I don't think it's a coincidence that he took Brennan when he did.
I was kind of thinking the same thing.
Thank God I didn't kill you.
How long was I unconscious?
For a while.How's your leg?
Better.
Lots better.What are you doing?
Hot-wiring the phone to the horn,so we can send a message.
From underground?
We get radio reception.
Direct current 12-volt will burn out the circuits in a 4.2 volt cell phone in a microsecond.
Better jury-rig a resistor.
Smart. --Might work long enough to send a single-burst transmission.
Very short text message.Booth can trace it to a cell phone relay tower.
What message shall we send?
"Good-bye"?"Nice to know you"?
What are we surrounded by?
Pain.
Despair.
And a subsoil accumulation of agglutinate aridosols.
Dirt.
I don't like the term "dirt.
" All right.
Tell me something I don't know.
Ash.
Hints of nitrogen and sulfur.
So where are we?
We're in coal country.
Bituminous coal country.
Basically...
Virginia.
We need more that that.
The laser.
And we need benzophenone.
Benzophenone...
It's in soaps,in plastic packaging,sunscreen.
We don't have any sunscreen.
Angela's perfume.
Three grand that cost.
Hodgins,I will split the cost when we get out of here.
There's something you don't know about me.
I'm rich.
Me,too.
No,no.You're well-off.
My family owns the Cantilever Group,and there's not many of us left alive.
One,to be exact.
Me.
Okay,I won't split it with you.
Smells nice.
I need the camera.
Okay.
I know where we are.
There's no negotiating with the Grave Digger.
You've been through this,what,five times with this guy?
Exactly.So I know him.
And he does not negotiate.
What?No chat room action with him?
Are you nuts?
I hate the ...
Why?
He's made you rich.
You know what?Youust need to deal with the facts.
If you can't put the ransom together in the time he gave you,
your partner is dead.
Here's the deal,all right?
You have a relationship with this guy-- what they call symbiotic-- you benefit from each other.
So know this,huh?
That deadline comes around,and my partner is still underground,
I will end you,you understand?
Three hours to live.
Better hurry.
This thing you found in my leg is anodized plastic film .
and coated metallic tape with dried-out adhesive
I think it's a bumper sticker.
You mean like,"If you can read this,you're too close"?
No.Like a prepaid toll road pass.
Someone ran me down with a car.
We knew that already.
Yeah,but now we've proved it,and I find I'm really annoyed.
Four to six seconds to enter message and hit speed dial.
I figured out a text message using eight key strikes.
How's your text messaging?
Thumbs like lightning.
I can do it.
Okay.
You ready?
Did it go?
I think it went.
Me,too.
Does it mean anything to anybody?
They're getting low on oxygen.
Hypoxia leads to mental confusion.
It's Bones.It means something.
Did you try just dialing the number?
I tried all the dumb guy normal stuff,okay?
That's why I'm here talking to the brain trust,all right?
Think,eggheads!Work it!
Booth,they're not cops.
We're running out of time.Minor correction.
Dr.Brennan and Hodgins will run out of air in four seconds.
We are out of time.
How much extra time?
A little.
Four other tires,but we can't get to them.
Is there anything else?
If the ransom was paid,we'd be out by now.
Why prolong the inevitable?
Booth will find us.
You have a lot of faith in Booth.
No.
Faith is an irrational belief in something that is logically impossible.
Over time,I've seen what Booth can do.
It's not faith.
No offense--
and I'm not just saying this because you filleted me with a knife--
we're out of air,we don't know if our message got out,
much less if anyone understood it,and we are buried underground.
What you have is faith,baby.
Sorry.The "baby" thing is a reflex.
You shouldn't talk right now.
To conserve air.
I need the camera batteries and the preservative powder from your kit.
Soda ash and lithium?
You're going to make a carbon dioxide scrubber?
If you can perform surgery out of thin air,
then I can pull a little thin air out of thin air.
Okay,Zack figured out what stun gun the Grave Digger uses,and how it's modified.
Thanks to Angela,we know that the Grave Digger has a customized aluminum case in the back of his vehicle.
I got about 100 agents working that angle.
What does this mean right here?What does that mean?
You're forgetting something.Brennan and Hodgins are out of air.
Great,you want to give up?
This is Bones we're talking about,and Hodgins.
You really think they didn't find a way to extend their air supply?
They found a way to send us a message-- ask us for help.
And you want to give up because of math?
Soda ash.Lithium.
Reacts with high concentrations of carbon dioxide.
Produces oxygen.
That gives us just long enough.
Just long enough for what?
For my next idea,which will kill us.
Air bags.
They aren't actually bags of air.
I'm not looking to extend our survival underground.
I'm looking to blow our way out of here.
Using the explosives from the air bags?
That could definitely kill us.
So will doing nothing.
Anyone you want to say good-bye to?
It's not a numerical-alphabetical code or an equation...
It's not GPS coordinates or indications of topography...
Then what is it? -Can I make a suggestion?
See,this is exactly why I was sent here.
You guys are brilliant,but you won't make intuitive leaps.
You mean jump to conclusions?
That's exactly what I mean.
This is a message from one of them to one of us.
Specific,focused.
Who was it meant to get to? --Easy,Brennan's cell to mine,right?
The message was for me.We have an understanding,we work together.
We all work together.
She's my best friend.
And Hodgins...Hodgins...
She's right.
We should assume the message is from Hodgins,not from Brennan.
Why?
Because they're buried alive.
And Hodgins is all about dirt.
Okay,great,the message is about dirt,but who is it to?
Angela.
Hodgins is all about dirt and Angela.
But it's numbers,Zack.
It's for you.
Hodgins would have written me a line of poetry or something.
Agent Booth.
Justine used her contacts and got me on all the local news shows.
I explained that we needed more time.I asked him to call.
I'm sorry,but he's completely consistent.
6-7-16.
Carbon,nitrogen and sulfur on the periodic table of elements.
They are buried in coal-rich soil.
You got to narrow it down,Zack.
Keep going,Zack.
The mineral components in coal are all the same.
It's the organic components that provide a unique fingerprint.
They're called "macerals.
" They fluoresce at different levels.
A reflectance of 1.4 is quite rare,
suggesting a high concentration of Inertinite.
Zack,tell me what that means.
It means he knows where they are.
Zack?
I know where they are.
Can this possibly work?
I'm not really an explosives expert,
but the dash might shape the charge enough to blow out the windshield.
If we're less than four feet beneath the surface,
this charge could blow us to freedom.
And if we're buried more than four feet deep?
Then the concussion will turn our brains into jelly.
Well,then we can run for congress,so it's a win-win.
We should get as far away from the explosion as possible.
I already am.
xxxxxxxxxxx
Okay,people,listen up.
I need everyone to look for any signs of recent digging.
Freshly overturned dirt,tire tracks,mounds,depressions.
Ready?
Dr.Brennan...
It's been a privilege.
hogies...
come on.
I went to visit you at the hospital.
I brought you this.
They...they let me go home.
No,they didn't.
You left without being discharged.
You stole crutches which I had to pay for.
They packed me...pumped me full of antibiotics,
stitched me up and gave me painkillers.
So...so I'm-I'm good to go.
Could you please look at me?
You were buried alive.
You were operated on without an anesthetic.
You were pumped full of drugs.
You really should be lying down.
He's out there,Angela.
He buries people alive.
I have to catch him.
If I can figure out the exact alloy of aluminum,then maybe I could...
maybe we could...
Plus the bit of-of-of...bumper sticker that Brennan found in my leg...
We're going to catch him,okay?
I promise you.
We're going to start tomorrow.
All of us together.
I can't sleep,Angela.
I thought that they gave you something for that.
No,I mean I'm afraid...
that if I close my eyes,when I...
when I open them I'm going to be back in that car,buried,running out of air.
Okay.
Then you should come home with me.
What?
When you open your eyes,I'll be there.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Okay.
You know I'm good for that crutch money.
What'd you ask for?
That's between me and a certain saint.
Although I did ask for a little help finding the Grave Digger.
Good move.
What's that smell?
The candles.
And I said thanks.
You should try it sometime.
If I were going to pray,I would've done it just before we set off the explosion.
And you didn't?
No.See,if there was a God,which there isn't...
Do you see where we are?
And if I were someone who believed He had a plan...
Which I do.
Then I'd be tempted to think He wanted me to go through something like
I went through because it might make me more open to the whole...
concept.
Which obviously it hasn't.
I'm okay with you thanking God for saving me and Hodgins.
That's not what I thanked Him for.
I thanked Him for saving all of us.
It was all of us.
Every single one.
You take one of us away,and you and Hodgins are in that hole forever.
And I'm thankful for that.
I knew you wouldn't give up.
bones Season 2 Episode 9
Sync: YTET-我是如此矫情 -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=- Proudly Presents