Can you make anything out?
Yes
It's a crater
We know it's a crater, Bones
The question is, what caused it?
You should ask
a geologist
I can tell you for sure
it's not a meteor
You get a look what's inside?
Not for long. State Troopers
didn't want anyone getting near it
until you people got here
That's very nice of them
But what did it look like?
I'm pretty sure it was meat
Meat wearing clothes
What do you want to do?
Let's take a look
So what do you think?
Dead?
Just saying
if he fell out of a plane that
plane is long gone by now
No sign of a parachute
What do those shoes
look like to you?
Loafers
He hit the ground
at approximately 200
kilometers per hour
How can you tell that
by his shoes?
124 miles per hour
is terminal velocity
for a falling human
So we're going to go
with the theory that this
was once human?
I've never read about
an alien encounter in which
the aliens wore loafers
How much you want to bet
Hodgins has?
The crows and critters
sure made quick work of him
Yeah, But these
Calliphora vicina eggs
will confirm time of landing
Blowflies on aliens
Who knew?
You're taking
a shot at me
because I happen to believe
that we are not all alone
and in an infinity
of space?
It's not the believing
in extraterrestrial life
that's odd
It's the believing
that they're visiting us
This guy is wearing loafers
Aliens don't wear loafers, people
Even if they want
to pass unnoticed amongst us?
no before taking us over?
Oh. Oh, this is harassment
You know, it's illegal
to mock people for
their fundamental beliefs
Is the tissue damage
consistent with a long fall?
Definitely
You've seen something
like this before?
Suicide off the Chrysler Building
At least this one
didn't hit pavement
A human being reaches
terminal velocity after falling
200 to 220 meters
depending upon
air resistance
Velocity would be achieved
between five and eight seconds
depending upon
atmospheric conditions
body position
and clothing
He fell from a minimum
of 1,200 feet
I can run through the math
if you'd like
- Send me an e-mail
- This is
I want to say anomalous
but I'm going to go with weird
- What's weird?
- These areas of radiolucency
here and here
- Extremely porous bones
- What's that mean?
That means he was ill
His right, femoral head shows
significant demineralization
- Zack?
- I'd put him at 130
130 what?
- Years
- Old?
There's an alternate
explanation
Then that's the one
we should go with
He was in outer space
So he fell from outer space
in a pair of loafers
Hodgins left too soon
Bones 219
www.1000fr.com present
Sync:FRM@mzinfo
The FAA reports
no recent accidents
involving anyone falling
from a plane, balloon or blimp
commercial or otherwise
The FAA doesn't have
jurisdiction over the entire
universe my friend
Little green men?
Gray, They're gray
Not green, Gray
Being as you're
half alien yourself
you should know that
If they dropped him from orbit
he'd have burned up
and his loafers
would have fallen off
If he wasn't
an abductee
tossed out of an
interplanetary spacecraft
why do his bones show
that he has spent an extended
time in outer space?
The only rational explanation
is that he was an astronaut
Astronauts lose two percent
of their bone mass
for each month
spent in space
Our victim's legs
hips and lower vertebrae
have demineralized
over 20%
indicating
ten months in space
Do we do that?
The longest shuttle
flight was STS-80
17.66 days, in 1996
The longest we know of
The man who's spent
the most time in space
was a Russian cosmonaut
That we know of
Why do you know that?
My knowledge is vast
Why did I ask?
Anyway, there can't
be all that many people
who have accumulated
ten months in space
That we know of
Call Booth
Tell him to see if anyone's
missing an astronaut
Meet Colonel Calvin Howard
Senior Training Specialist
and Crew Liaison
in the shuttle program
currently working in
the National Space Agency
in Bristol, Maryland
Angela just sent me her
work in progress off the partial
skull reconstruction
She says we expected
too much too soon
but the shape of the head
the cheekbones...
Close enough for jazz
Oh. Six months in
the International Space Station
plus a number
of servicing missions
to both the Hubble
and Lansing telescopes
Wait. Does that add up to
the right amount of bone rot?
Loss.Bone loss
And... yes
Has anyone
reported him missing?
No. Not exactly
Not exactly?
We know astronauts
are regarded as
viable terror targets
Their whereabouts?
Extremely confidential
Bet if you told the Agency
you were going
to identify Colonel Howard
to the press
they would be
a little more cooperative
Yeah. You know, I have been
a wonderful influence on you
Actually
I learned that move from Cam
Yeah, well, I went
the other way with it, okay?
Looked up his wife
in the phone book
Did my husband die in some kind
of training accident?
We don't believe so
ma'am. No
It couldn't have been
How do you know that?
Because the Space Agency
would be all over this
You're probably right
They wouldn't let anybody
else take the lead
not even us
You say your husband left
the day before yesterday?
On what airline?
Cal flies himself
What kind of plane?
He has a turboprop Cessna
out at McNichol
What exactly does a
Senior Training Specialist
and Crew Liaison do?
We're not supposed
to discuss these things
For the past three years
Cal's been training others to go up
Because he lost
his medical clearance?
How did you know that?
His X-rays show
that he was suffering from
a dramatic loss
of bone density
Must have been hard
on the colonel
training others to do
what he'd love to do
No, Cal was a team player
He was training her husband
James for almost a year
Actually
it was very hard on him
It would be hard on any of them
All they ever do is think
about going back into space
and all we ever
think about
is getting them
back home
Is there some
kind of rule
that astronaut's wives
travel in packs?
When you marry an astronaut
no one really understands, except...
Except other people
who are in the same situation
This is Cal's itinerary
Mainly when he intended
to call me and...
when he'd be back
You expected your husband
home today?
Yeah
Yeah. I just need to know
if it's still in the hangar or not
It's a Cessna turboprop plane
registered
to Colonel Calvin Howard
Thanks
It just seemed so odd
Those women
stick together like a harem
What? They support
each other, you know?
A lot of service
wives are like that
What about astronauts' husbands?
Look, their husbands
train for years, Bones
Their families invest
their entire lives
Yeah
Are you sure?
Okay. Great. Thanks
Well, plane's still
in the hangar
Well, if that's the plane
he got tossed out of
then it didn't fly itself back
If someone simply pushed him
out of the plane
there might not be any evidence
We have to hope
there was a struggle
Excuse me
Could I see
some I.D., please?
Yeah. Sure. I'll show you mine
if you show me yours
Right. Here you go
That airplane belongs
to the Agency
Our information
is that it belongs
to Colonel Calvin Howard
- The Agency leased it to him
- Well, it's being investigated
as a possible crime scene
You're Colonel Howard's boss?
Yes. Nina Sanborn
I carry a rank equivalent
to an Air Force general
Hmm. Why didn't you report him
missing, General Sanborn?
Equivalent, I said
I'm a civilian
Cal was...
Colonel Howard wasn't missing
He was barely
gone a day
General Sanborn
I know you people
are really tight-lipped
but I'm really good friends
with a very aggressive
federal prosecutor who is great
at getting warrants
Agent Booth?
We got the usual fibers
hair, particulates
No blood?
No sign of a struggle?
Nothing. You'll have my full
report by the end of the day
Great. Okay, I need to know what
Colonel Howard was working on
at the time of his death
Get your warrant
Agent Booth
Dr. Brennan
Hey, excuse me, Equivalent-
to-a-General Sanborn
I got that warrant
Why didn't you just
tell her that right away?
I was hoping
we could all be friends
Let me see that
These are the documents you
subpoenaed from the Agency?
Yeah, but all the info
is blacked out
Want me to see if
I can get anything out of this?
Can you?
No. I'd need originals
These are photocopies
Then why did you offer?
Well, why else
would you ask me here?
You're a conspiracy nut
and I thought you'd enjoy
filling in the blanks
With paranoid ravings?
Better than nothing
Lansing Telescope
- That mean anything to you?
- Yeah
A multi-gazillion-dollar
deep space, multifrequency
telescope that keeps
needing repairs
Why did you say it like that?
It doesn't need repairs
There's no rust in space
The so-called "repair crews"
are up there retrieving
classified information
What classified
information?
The telescope is pointed
up at the planet Pluto
Pluto's no longer a planet
It was demoted
And if the Lansing was
pointed away from the Earth
why would they need
to black out all this material?
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah
What's the deal on proposing
to--- you know a woman?
I mean, what is the
absolute proper way to do it?
I don't know. The one time
I did it, I got shot down flat
Did you do it by the book?
Mm-hmm
No...
We were waiting for
the stick to turn blue
or not to turn blue
and I realized
I wanted to marry her if the
stick was
blue or not
Yeah, that's sort of what I did
only without the sticks
You asked Angela to marry you?
Apparently I didn't do it right
Do it again
Go all out this time, right?
With the dinner and the getting
down on one knee, the violin
Forget the violin
Hey, hey
with his bone density
Colonel Howard sure as hell
wasn't going back into space again
Yeah, I know, that's why he was
training his replacement
His replacement? For what?
To repair the Lansing Telescope
Oh, brothers-in-arms
my brother
That replacement's the guy
who can tell you things
the Agency doesn't
want you to know
Ah
Makes you feel small
doesn't it?
Because the picture's so big?
No, because the universe
is so big
You're not looking
at the universe
You're looking at
an enlarged photograph of Earth
You see one thing
and I see another thing
Personally, I like what I see
Agent Booth
Dr. Brennan
I'm afraid Commander Adams
is scheduled for time
on the A300 Zero-G
You're welcome
to talk to him there
The Zero-G?
The Vomit Comet
Makes no sense
Man flies eight missions into space
and he falls out of a plane?
I don't think so
Look, you don't know anyone
who would want to throw
him out of a plane?
Look, I don't mean
to tell you your work
but shouldn't you
be tracking down
everyone who flew over that
particular piece of real estate?
We are, but not everyone
filed flight plans
And not everyone
sticks to flight plans
And you didn't
answer the question
I don't know anyone who didn't
like and respect Cal Howard
All these itineraries--
people keeping secrets
even from their spouses
Look, sir, I understand you
have to ask questions like these
but Cal Howard and Jean Marie
were a very solid couple
Did you ever get drunk together?
What?
What my partner
is trying to ask
is if you two were buddies
Go out and
have drinks
and exchange confidences?
Yes, that's what I asked
Yeah, sure
of course, at times
So you would have known
if his marriage was in trouble?
Yes, sir, I would
How can you be sure?
Because Cal knew when I was
unfaithful to my wife
Colleen?
Right. You guys met her
at Cal's place
Look...
that has to stay between us
Strictly between us
Cal Howard was my friend,
my colleague and my teacher
If somebody tossed him
from an airplane
I'll do whatever
I can to help
Why do I get the feeling
you want to tell us something?
Commander Adams
prepare to go weightless
We're about to go weightless
As the plane reaches the apogee
of a climb and then falls
we will have 15 to 20 seconds
of weightlessness
That was great
Oh, man, you're not kidding
I would like very much
to do that again
I believe you were about
to tell us something
Cal was talking to the STC
The what?
Space Travel Coalition
It's a privately funded
space exploration
and tourism group
And... did you?
Did we what?
Vomit in the Comet?
No, I didn't vomit
I'm sure they were trying
They can try me any time
It was truly amazing
She had a little bit
too much fun, okay?
So what's with this
whole thing about
space tourism?
Oh, celestial joy rides
for gazillionaires
Selling seats on a spaceship
that don't even exist yet
And won't be viable for
at least another few years
That's what they want
you to think
but these guys are
swimming in dough
I already bought my ticket
I want to see what's
going on up there
with my own eyes
What?
These are the
victim's clothes?
Yes
You'd like me to do
what with them?
Construct a three-dimensional
hypothesis of what caused
this damage to the clothing
Falling from an
airplane isn't enough?
That would explain the burst
seams and pressure tears
but this seems to be...
Slashes
yeah, When Zack gets ahold
of the bones
maybe you two can figure out
if something catastrophic
happened to this man
You mean before
he fell to Earth?
Yes
Go do your magic
Now?
Are you certain you can't
do what needs to be done
with X-rays alone?
Do you need continued access
to the soft tissue?
Why would the body burst
vertically when all the forces
are horizontal?
Ah, so you need more time with
the soft tissue to answer that?
Not really
Please explain to me
your reluctance to remove
the flesh from the bones
I'm all right with it, Zack
if it's absolutely necessary
even the boiling part...
but perhaps you could at least
acknowledge
that this is a person
Was, you mean
Was someone's husband, Zack
What does that have
to do with removing the flesh
from his bones?
Fine. Do what you have to do
Thank you
Igor
I beg your pardon
Dr. Saroyan?
Nothing
Hey, Bones
I ran a check on STC
They're part of the
tin-foil hat squad
What's that?
They wear tin
little hats
Probably to keep aliens
from controlling their minds
Oh, schizophrenics
It's hard to believe
that Colonel Howard
was part of an organization
like that
Do they have
access to planes?
Access? You kidding me?
They actually have a
"border patrol division"
Members fly
their own private planes
and do bimonthly sky patrols
in search of UFOs
Do they file flight plans?
Bones, you're a genius
Look, two nights ago they
had planes on UFO patrol
within spitting distance
of where Colonel Howard's
body was found
Look, we're not
a collection of kooks
Just ordinary people
with a mission
to promote a friendly
liaison with the Visitors
That's quite a
manifesto
Until you've had an encounter
you couldn't possibly
understand
You've been abducted?
Multiple times
Mm-hmm
Through hypnosis I've discovered
that medical testing was done
and follow-ups were required
Are there any side effects
from these medical
procedures?
You mean like tin hats?
Paranoia
outbursts of anger
loss of connection
with reality?
You asked me to come
I'm here
I run a very successful
aeronautics engineering company
I'm richer than God
Do I appear to have lost
contact with reality?
Well, what about post
abduction syndrome?
Similar to post traumatic
stress disorder
P.A.S. is very real
I admit to bouts with it
Frankly, it's one
of my main motivators
When we meet the Visitors
face-to-face
they will explain
so many things to us
Including why you were taken
And why they put
an implant in me
Only then to remove it
Great
- Do you, uh... know this guy?
- Colonel Howard, Of course
- So it's true that you offered him
a position with the STC?
- Yes
As a method of bringing credibility
to your organization?
Yes, but you have to
understand it was Colonel Howard
who came to us
Why?
He wanted to pilot
our suborbital flights
Till your spaceships were ready
he was going to help
you look for the UFOs
Laugh if you must, but Cal
didn't think we were crazy
He'd seen something
himself up there, you know
And he's hardly
the first
Quite a few astronauts and
military pilots have reported
seeing evidence
of the Visitors
- Colonel Howard told you this?
- Yes, he did
So trust me, I'd have been proud
to be the one who sent
Cal Howard back into space
Would have been?
He changed his mind
Six weeks ago
That didn't make you
a little angry?
No, not angry
Disappointed
Great, Then you wouldn't
object to my partner and I
taking a look at your fleet of planes?
No, not at all
Why do you think
Colonel Howard changed his mind?
They got to him
Through his wife
I believe
They?
The Agency
They can be
very persuasive
Persuasive?
In my opinion, the Agency would
rather have Cal die
than have him announce to the
world he'd seen a Visitor
That's not true
The Agency loved Cal
They valued him
Why didn't you tell
us about STC?
Because it's embarrassing
Cal wanted to get back into
space so badly
he would even listen
to those crazy people
Did you husband see
something up there?
Yes, something that made him
sympathetic
with Mr. Bahr's
organization?
Well, obviously
you know that he did...
or he said he did
And you doubted him?
It doesn't really
matter now
You know, that was
three years ago
It was his last mission
And the Agency
explained it in such a way
that Cal was satisfied
Look, it's important that we
know the truth, Mrs. Howard
Why?
Because from
what I've seen your husband
was a man of principle
and if he saw something
he wouldn't just back down to
save his career with the Agency
Even if his wife
begged him to
He insisted on filing
an official report
He wouldn't withdraw it
- They asked him to?
- Yes
But he stuck by his story
They weren't happy with him
but like I said
that's ancient history
Cal's friend knew about the STC
his wife knew
Maybe the Agency did as well
What, so they killed him
by tossing him out
of an airplane?
That field is less than a mile
from the coastline
Obviously they were aiming
at the ocean and they missed
Well, the question is why?
It's a big ocean, right?
- There has to be a reason
- Maybe it wasn't a UFO
that Cal saw
- Ah...
- He could have seen
something else
Oh, yeah, like--
a death beam or a space baby
I was thinking more
along the lines
of a spy satellite
or experimental technology
No, Maybe the Agency
was afraid
that Cal was sharing sensitive
information with the SCT
Well, regardless
our government does not kill people
okay, Bones?
You were a sniper
Wasn't it our government
who sent you to kill people?
Just saying
Mmm
something smells good
Help yourself
Ho!
These definitely human bones?
'Cause apparently
there are a few types
of aliens
races, if you will
One is quite reptilian
widely known as "Grays"
Definitely human
Another's bone structure's
more amphibian
These bones are as human
as you are
Oh, if you only knew
how irony-packed that is
It's a joke
Don't you be coming around
to boil me in the middle
of the night
There's a strange callous
formation on his right
femoral head
Also bone marrow edema
in the same spot
Healing from a fracture?
No. Some kind of tuberous
cortical defect
I've never seen anything
like this before
Now you're freaking me out
I have to get Dr. Brennan
to take a look at this
It looks like he was
in the initial stages
of osteonecrosis
What did you get
from the tox screen?
Excess levels of vitamins D
K, E, A and C
along with glutamine peptides
and creatine monohydrate
All the supplements
he was taking before his
last space mission
There's something odd
about the texture of this bone
Leucine
isoleucine and valine
He foresaw going back
into space
This is not bone
What is it?
A callous has formed
over some kind of thick
porous substance
Careful
It's an implant of some kind
I never saw anything
on the X rays
How could that not show up
on X rays?
What the hell is this?
Zoantharia of the order
scleractinia
Scleractinia has a calcium-
carbonate exoskeleton
with a porosity similar
to human bone
Which would make it
biocompatible
So it wouldn't
show up on X rays
Wait. So this is coral
like from a reef?
Suspended in a biphasic
hydroxyapatite-tricalcium-
phosphate coating
Theoretically, the calcium
from the exoskeleton would grow
hopefully overcoming the loss
of his degenerating bone
Then this attachment
would be...?
An electromagnetic device
implanted to accelerate growth
So it's a combination
of human and alien technology
Don't say that to Booth
But if that's the case
then all the vitamins
and amino acids
he was loaded up with
work mainly to ward
off infection
And he'd need them, too
Bone marrow's highly
susceptible
This is a very risky procedure
I got to say it-- Frank Olson
He was a U.S. Army scientist
in the '50s
and an unwitting participant
in Project MK Ultra
They said
he committed suicide
but an exhumation
45 years later
proved he was murdered
You need more
Project Paperclip
MK Artichoke
and who could forget
Tuskegee?
The government experiments
on people and then
abandons them or worse
What's the point
of this experiment?
The main obstacle
to long-term space travel
is bone demineralization
If the space program
could overcome this one effect
their funding would triple
overnight
Well, there you go
Experimental program
for deep space fails
and the evidence has
to be gotten rid of
By tossing it
from a plane?
Why not just have
the visitors toss him
into the sun?
That is a good question
No, it's not
Sometimes when people try
to cover things up
it goes wrong, that's all
First thing
we should do
is find out
the source of this technology
Colonel Reid
was Cal's commanding officer
on three missions
So you were the person to whom
he reported the UFO sighting?
Oh, for God's sake
You see what happens?
You people get all secretive
about things and...
What Cal saw was space junk
It was satellite parts
a discarded hatch
a screwdriver
That information isn't cleared
Sounded like more
than a screwdriver
Well, it wasn't
Cal just thought
we should be able to explain
why it was whizzing around
space at 25,000 miles an hour
and that's all
Was Colonel Howard in a cast
recently?
Last winter
said he broke his leg
parasailing in the Caribbean
All of our astronauts
suffer from brittle bones
I stepped off a ladder once
and my tibia snapped
like a twig
Why do you ask?
Because of this
We found it
in Colonel Howard's leg
We think it's designed
to counteract the effects
of osteonecrosis
Experimental surgery
on one of our astronauts?
Absolutely not
Our efforts to counter
bone loss are limited
to strength-and-resistance
training and supplements
I trust you have documentation
Follow me
Thank you
Colonel
have you ever
seen anything
any screwdrivers up there?
There's an awful lot up there
to see, Doctor
Trick is not to let it
cloud your judgment
Did it ever cloud Cal's?
Never, not once
And yet he wanted to go back
into space so badly
in spite of the physical
damage it had caused him
the pain he was in
Let me show you something
You see this?
That's me
And that there, that's Cal
20 minutes I spent out there
that day
and it is the last thing
I think about every night
I can imagine...
No. All due respect
you really can't
This was the best moment
of my life, counting marriage
kids, everything
I'm not saying
that's good or right
but I do know
it was the same for Cal
for all of us who went up there
And we would do anything
we could to get back
This coral's growth
was aided artificially
It was seeded
with resin beads
on glass plates
Which makes it rare
enough to trace to a
pharmaceutical supply house
based in Geneva, Switzerland
I searched the literature
There's a number of clinics
and researchers working on
bone replacement
The doctor most likely to
have performed this procedure
on our victim
is Dr. Henry Pascal
In Switzerland?
Based in Bethesda
with a clinic in Haiti
plus he worked
for the space agency
until 1998
What happened?
He lost his funding and turned
to the private sector
namely the Space Travel Coalition
The foil hat squad
funds this guy?
Booth is going to love that
- Why?
- Because he doesn't believe
in coincidences
Cal wasn't on vacation
when he hurt his leg
He was in Haiti
for a convention
Can you think of any
reason Colonel Reid would tell us
a different story?
No
Please, what
what's going on?
We found evidence
in your husband's remains
that he underwent
an experimental surgery in Haiti
What kind
of experimental surgery?
To replace his bone loss
That sound like him?
Yes
Was it like your husband
to keep it a secret from you?
Yes
Cal wouldn't want me to worry
Cal Howard's skeleton
before...
and after
he fell to Earth
Every bone showed trauma
His clothing before...
and after he fell to Earth
Ripped
every seam pulled apart
If I make the clothing
translucent...
we can see that some
of the clothing damage
lines up with the trauma
to his skeleton
And if you isolate the bone
damage caused by a device
capable of making robust cuts
in a linear path...
The guy was chopped
he chopped?
Yeah. Clothing damage
flesh wounds
Bone damage
He was chopped
Ange, tonight
you and me
reservations at
Les Deux Copains 8:00
Wow, fancy
Suit-and-gown fancy, baby
So leave your mukluks at home
What's the occasion?
An ax or hatchet
or machete makes sharp
well-defined cuts
These edges are abraded
This our guy?
Hey, do aliens use any weapons
resembling a...?
A broadsword?
How about a light saber?
No, those can cut through
any known substance
The victim would have
been completely
dismembered
If they existed, Zack
Makeup hair done
high heels
the whole enchilada
Only whatever's French
for "enchilada"
No mukluks. Got it
Dr. Pascal
Colonel Calvin Howard is dead
Not because of anything I did
Wow, didn't even blink
Colonel Howard
sought me out
I know how he died?
Let's just say it was
a really bad fall
And what's this got
to do with me?
Was your procedure a success?
How do you define success?
Just answer the question
That's actually a fair question
The results were heartening
There were extremely painful
calluses growing over your implant
I'd very much like to see that
And there was no indication
of an actual reversal of necrosis
The calluses were part
of the healing process
See, coral resorption is slow
but effective as a scaffold
for osteoprogenitor cells
Incorporating
the electrode was
speeding the process
In my opinion
Cal was only months away
from having mature lamellar bone
No way to know for sure now
right?
- Correct
- Probably to your benefit
to terminate your experiment
before it went wrong
Keep those venture capitalists
on the edge of their seats
You think I pushed
Colonel Howard off a ladder
Or out of an airplane
Look, you can have all my data
my projections
everything
Colonel Howard goes
on the next shuttle mission
to repair the Lansing Telescope
I'm in every medical
journal in the country
That mission's a month away
Would his body have been ready?
At the rate Cal was healing
I believe so
Did anyone at the Agency
know about this?
We were going to petition them
officially next month
Look, you may not like me
but I was his savior
and he was mine
I didn't kill Colonel Howard
Somebody's lying
to us, right?
Yeah, maybe everybody
Well, this is
your strength
reading people's minds
telling them they're lying
My strength?
Wait a sec
The trouble is-- no, no,--
you haven't given me anything
that I can spring on the suspect
to see how he reacts
- Like what?
- Oh, like a murder weapon
or whether or not the poor
bastard was dead
before he hit the ground
Zack and Angela say he was
Okay, well, that's something
Dead how?
Best guess right now
a broadsword
A broadsword?
Like King Arthur?
Yes
Broadsword
You know what, Bones
I like the whole alien thing
much better. Broadsword?
Where do you people come up
with this stuff?
I didn't say
an actual broadsword
I said,
"Like a broadsword"
It was the closest analog
I could access
No traces from the weapon
left on the bone?
Traces are left
when the weapon cuts deeply
into the bone
Whatever this was
wasn't very sharp
Left nothing behind
How about shape?
The pattern is consistent with
sharp-force trauma
from a curved blade
approximately
65 millimeters thick
And if I am late for dinner
I will find whatever it is
and I will hit
you with it
Wow, you...
you look incredible
- You really do
- You know what else?
I can tell just by
looking at you--
you smell great
You cannot see smell
The victim was struck
four times
A glancing blow to the head
right humerus
thoracic, and left femur
We couldn't figure out
in what order
It's almost as though
it were simultaneous
The blow to the head is
what killed him
Come on, four hits
simultaneously with a broadsword
What was he
attacked by the knights
of the roundtable?
65 millimeters
is too thick for a sword
Did you estimate
a velocity?
It was moving at a velocity
of approximately
116 meters per second
What's that in American?
About 260 miles per hour
All right, look
I'm no expert in broadswords
- but I do know...
- I know what happened
How fast does a propeller turn?
At full speed, the tips approach
the speed of sound
But Howard exits the airplane
in flight
The propeller
is ahead of him
and pulling away
How could he come
into contact with it?
There are pusher propellers
It didn't happen in the air
He was pushed into a propeller?
He would've turned
into steak tartare
Scratch one item
off the menu tonight
Not if the plane was idling
Propeller speeds would decrease
to a thousand or so RPMs
- Let's go
- Where?
We'll look for
a dented propeller
Come on
Which you do
not need me for
Hey
You're right, here they come
I hope you have
another warrant
This is for the hangar
not the individual planes
Then why are your people
looking at propellers?
Because the warrant
includes anything
that is in plain sight
Plane sight
Get it?
It's a pun
Yeah, and this is
not the only hangar
we'll be checking out
What plane are you
looking for specifically?
Well, we'll know it
when we see it
We believe that Colonel Howard
was struck by a propeller
We're looking for
blood stains using
alternate light sources
You think Cal walked
into a propeller?
No way he makes
a bonehead move like that
We surmise
he was pushed
But why?
Here he was
this great guy
but he was liability
to one of you
One of us?
Somebody wanted him dead
That's ridiculous
If it turned out that Cal
was able to reverse his bone loss
would you put him
on the next shuttle?
The one to repair the
Lansing Telescope again
Colonel Adams is slated
for that mission
Colonel Reid?
Well, Cal would be
my first choice, yes
All due respect, James
But why send the student
when the teacher can go?
Look, I take no offense
Cal was the best
Dr. Brennan
Agent Booth
Blood
A lot of it
It was washed
down this drain here
High-pressure hose
Can you tell which plane's
propeller may have done this?
Not within the parameters
of the current warrant
Some of these planes
have covers on the propellers
so we can't
see if they're damaged
That is your plane
isn't it, James?
Take it off
Take off the cover, James
I respectfully decline
It's not his plane
it's the Agency's
Propeller like that
wouldn't get you very far
Certainly not
over the water
Which is why you had
to dump Cal's body
short of the ocean
Booth
It doesn't make sense
The whole thing would take
at least two people--
putting the body in the plane
cleaning up the blood
shoving the body
out of the plane
Who are you protecting?
Mrs. Howard...
Is Colleen here?
Colleen came to see me off
Saw me talking to Cal
He was telling me that
he was going to be okay
in time for the mission
He was sharing good news
But it wasn't good
not to me
She slapped him
that's all
Because she loves me
She knew what it meant to me
not to go up
Cal took a step back
just one
He fell back into the propeller
Why didn't you just say
it was an accident?
I don't know
we panicked
Would they believe us?
Would they understand?
Would you ever get into space?
It happened because my friend
shared good news with me
and because my wife loves me
I'm a blessed man
How-how are you feeling?
What do you mean?
Good meal
nice bottle of wine
You feeling loving?
You didn't need to
do all of this to get me
in a loving mood
I don't mean in that way
I am madly in love
with you, Angela
And you are the
most amazing woman
that I have ever met
My life is so much
better since we...
Oh, my God
What?
Are you breaking up with me?
Why would I get you
all dressed up for dinner
just to break up?
I don't know
Because you're...
I'm not thinking straight
Go ahead
You know, I had this
all laid out in my mind
You are an upsetting woman
I'm sorry
Please go ahead
I believe that if two people
care enough for each other
the rest of the world
disappears to them
I feel that when I'm with you
I'm prepared to put you ahead of
me for the rest of my life
Angela Montenegro...
will you marry me?
Dear man
good heart...
No
Why?
I didn't do it
right again?
But...
How?
Oh, you're not
going to tell me
I don't know
Hodgins
If I knew
I would tell you
But when you ask me
I have to have this...
this feeling
It has to be...
I'll know it when it happens
and I hope you
won't stop trying
I don't know whether
I should laugh
cry or punch out the sommelier
I'm sorry
I hope that you choose laugh
I don't understand
I don't either
Look, let's just
finish the dessert and
go back to your place
and make love and
maybe it'll come to me
While we make love?
I said maybe
But you love me
More than you know
You eat yet?
I said I'd wait
How did you know that
James would tell me?
Well, man loves his wife
He may not be strong
but he has a conscience
See, I...
I can't tell that stuff
And I can't tell the difference
between coral and bone
so guess we make a great pair
Hey, speaking of marriage
Hodgins is going to
propose to Angela tonight
What?
I guess right now it looks
to me like marriage
is having someone
who'll slap your enemies
and then toss their dead
bodies out of airplanes
Try not to mention
that to Angela
welcome to www.1000fr.com