Previously on Heroes
I think Sylar's
beginning to emerge again.
I'm part of you Matt.
Whatever you did
to me I held on.
Now I'm inside your head.
I'm in control
here not the power.
I'm not you. You
son of a bitch!
Keppler! The guy's
name is keppler.
Lives in long beach.
You're supposed to be the
man with the plan, remember?
I'm not sure I'm
that guy anymore.
Why's that?
Because I've lost
my family, Angela.
Maybe changing your
name back to Bennet
Wasn't such a great
idea after all.
But they say college is
for reinventing yourself.
Have you ever heard of
the jump push fall test?
All we need is a dummy
The approximate size
and weight of Annie.
So where do we get our
hands on a dead body?
I guess she did
kill herself.
I met an empath.
You talk to him?
Didn't really
get a chance.
Claire?
Claire, it's
Gretchen. Open up.
Claire, we need to talk!
No darling, this
batch isn't for you.
I think
I think I found someone
to fill Joseph's shoes.
I'm going out.
Wearing that?
I draw unwanted
attention being myself.
Haven't worn a suit
since I was a boy.
My parents forced
us to be prim
Binding us to a life
of combed hair and
Shined shoes.
And then I discovered
I could control the
very earth under my feet
And I was liberated.
I could be filthy.
Tie still feels like a
damn noose around my neck.
Come here.
You don't have to leave.
You know I could I could
do whatever you want.
No. Thank you.
It's my responsibility.
Ever since Joseph died
I feel like the lights
Don't shine as
bright in here.
Feel like I'm missing
a part of myself.
He was my compass.
I'm afraid of where
we're going without it.
- I need it back.
- I'm sorry for your loss.
But you know you cannot
replace your brother.
No. You don't understand.
We have a need and
I have a candidate.
I just want to see
If he deserves a
place at our table.
Do you think that
you might go home
While you're out there?
No. I left that life.
I don't ever want
to go back again.
- How do I look?
- Like everybody else.
Hey. Are you
peter petrelli
The paramedic who saved
that cop's life last week?
- Yeah.
- That was awesome man.
- Here.
- Thanks. What's this?
You been served.
Guess you need
to be more careful
When you're saving
people£¬hero.
You expecting
somebody, Parkman?
Suspect's house
is over there.
How damn long does it take
a judge to issue a warrant?
We are gonna get
this guy, okay?
We're gonna find the stash
both get commendations.
It's gonna be
a great day.
Just relax.
Yeah.
It's not even
about that. I...
My 30-day sobriety chip.
I slipped. I used.
I'm still being haunted
By the ghost of all the
crappy things I've done past
And it got the
better of me.
A.d.a.
Yeah.
I wish I was a ghost.
It would be so much
better than this hell
Being stuck in your
miserable life...ehh!
I mean have you seen
yourself eat a burrito?
Why don't you just get
the hell out of here?
Well there's
only one way out.
Which is you need to figure
out how to undo what you did.
Give me back my body
and I will be happy
To leave you stewing
in your mediocrity.
You're a killer.
i'm a cop.
If I have to keep you
trapped inside this prison
For the rest of my life
So be it.
You really think you're
up to the challenge?
You got no power. None.
You're annoying as hell
yes but ultimately harmless.
I can just ignore you
until you fade away
Like a bad memory.
We'll see.
- We got the warrant.
- Good.
I want you on this job.
But you're not
going into that house
Until I know that
you'll keep it together.
I'm fine. Look.
It's the first day of
the rest of my life right?
So I put away my ghosts
and put my game face on.
- Let's go.
- All right.
Police open up! Open up!
I'll check upstairs.
Parkman.
I'm not interrupting
you, am I?
I'm everywhere.
Hey. Where you going?
He's in the closet.
Yeah.
Your drug dealer
is in that closet.
What kind of cop
doesn't check a closet?
And he has a gun.
You're done. Drop it.
Now!
Okay!
You're welcome.
Gretchen?
I told you that...
Dad. What are
you doing here?
"Hey dad. Nice
to see you.
Thanks for bringing the
house-warming presents."
Hey dad. nice to see you.
Thanks for bringing the
housewarming presents.
You okay? Yeah. I'm fine.
Your mother told me
About your roommate
Annie committing suicide.
I should have
called you. I know.
- I didn't call because...
- No. No no no I...
I don't want to
put you on the spot.
I just wanna make
sure you're all right.
I'm dealing with
it. I'm fine.
I know that fine. It's uh
It's not very convincing.
You want to try again?
It's not just the
whole Annie thing, it's
It's just an
adjustment college.
I'm adjusting.
I miss my family.
I miss you.
Mom. Even Lyle.
What do you say
we grab some lunch?
Spend a little time talk.
- If you're not busy.
- No.
Sounds like a plan.
- Let me just go get pretty.
- You look beautiful.
I'll be just a minute.
So this is your plan?
You're just
gonna avoid me?
I'm not.
Wow. You're even gonna avoid
admitting you're avoiding me.
No no no I'm not.
I was just busy
and-and studying and
Organic chem is a bitch.
How's uh art history?
So we're really not
gonna talk about this?
Look, whatever it is
You thought you saw the
other night,you didn't see.
I didn't see you hurl
yourself out a window
And then snap your
bones back into place?
No!
I mean yes I was-I
was on the ground
And I was testing your
theory you know jump push fall
And I think Annie
did commit suicide
Which is awful
and--and tragic.
You don't have
to lie to me.
Look you were
wrong about Annie
Just like you're
wrong about me.
Seriously what are
you a vampire an alien?
Some kind of freakish
government experiment?
All right. I just
have to change.
Hi Mr. bennet.
Who's your friend?
Oh that's uh Gretchen.
Nice to meet you.
Would you like to
join us for lunch?
Oh. That's nice.
You don't-you don't
have to do that.
It would be my pleasure.
I'm pretty sure
that Gretchen
Has an art history
assignment due tomorrow.
Isn't that
right Gretchen?
Yeah but I finished
my paper already.
- And I'm starving.
- Great.
Great.
Hey. We can do this the
easy way or the hard way.
So why don't you just tell
us where you hid the drugs?
- Why don't you ask my
lawyer? - Did he just--
I can't believe people
actually say that.
You can call
your lawyer after
We're done
searching that house
- No you can't do that man.
- We have a warrant.
You attempted to
murder an officer--me.
So we are gonna stay
here as long as it takes.
Or you could just
grow a pair and
End this
idiotic sobriety.
I'm gonna ask
you one more time
Stop asking. Use
your abilities.
I'm gonna go check
in the bathroom.
Not as easy to ignore
me as you thought.
It's because
I ooze charm.
- Looking in the wrong place.
- Stop helping.
Hey if I'm gonna
be stuck in here
I might as well
make the most of it.
I always thought I'd
be an excellent cop.
Fine. Ignore me.
Something doesn't
fit in this picture.
- Stuffed rabbit?
- A stuffed rabbit!
This house isn't
used for drugs.
It's used for
something worse
A lot worse.
Hi. I need a file.
Um Hooper William.
h-o-o-p-e-r.
Look it'll just
take a second.
It's my accident report. if
you could just type it in.
Seriously?
I get it.
You're just uh
doing your job.
I'm doing my job.
Save a guy's life
and he sues me for it.
I guess no good deed
goes unpunished right?
I'm talking to myself.
Who are you listening to?
Your headphones.
It's cool. I like
that band too.
You okay?
He's in physical
therapy right now.
Thank you.
'scuse me.
William Hooper?
Yes? That's me.
I think there's
been a mistake.
I've never
met you before.
There's no mistake.
Mr. petrelli.
You pulled me
from the 424 bus
After it crashed at
lexington and 53rd.
I remember you
were fast so fast
So negligent you
dislocated my arm.
Well I remember everybody
that was on that bus.
You weren't on it.
What is this a scam? You
recognize my family name?
You want money?
I'm not scamming you.
Don't need your cash.
- Then what?
- Empathy.
I'm in town because
of my brother Joseph.
He died and
There's a lot of loose
ends to take care of
When someone passes.
I'm all alone now.
I have to take care
of our entire family.
It's my responsibility.
It's my burden.
But I can't do that
on account of you.
Doctor says i won't
work for months.
If I don't work I
don't feed my family.
Are you the kinda man
That's going to allow
my family to starve?
You know what?
this was a mistake.
I'm gonna let the lawyers
handle it--good day.
Working two three
shifts at a time.
My lawyer already
checked on you.
I know what it's like to feel
the pressure of obligation.
But isn't it possible
i was on that bus
And you've become so
spread thin that you
Forgot?
No. It's not.
You're not
going blind Emma.
There's nothing
wrong with your eyes.
Then... what's
happening to me?
When you saw the lights
did other people see them?
Yes. Of course--
I just signed,
"Hey, do you see an Aurora Borelis
ink blot coming from that coffee mug?"
Did you ever hear
of synesthesia?
Corossing
senses together.
Yeah. Yeah.
People say that
they can smell words
Or hear numbers.
And, I'm what...?
Seeing sound as color?
It's possible. It's very
common in deaf cases.
Maybe your body's trying
to tell you something.
Couldn't it just
send an e-mail?
Emma. Emma.
This is serious.
You know you are
completely disengaged.
You file records when you
could be treating patients.
I like my job.
It's... quiet.
Is that why you
wear the headphones?
I wear the headphones because
the minute I take them off,
Someone's asking for the
time, or my phone number,
or directions to
the Statue of Liberty
I don't want to
see their faces.
That look.
Insensitive eyebrows
Oh, she's deaf.
Okay. We've
got saag paneer.
Baingan bharta.
Aloo gobi.
- Tikka masala.
- Seriously?
It just looks
like green brown
Yellow and orange.
Don't make the stink
face. you're gonna love it.
Except he
forgot the raita.
I don't want to
offend your dad
But what if i
don't like yellow?
- Just do the napkin trick.
- Sir?
Excuse me we also had an
order of raita for the table.
Clever. You're very
good at hiding things.
So gretchen
what's your major?
Physiology and
biomechanics.
I thought it
was art history.
I'm gonna change.
I'm obsessed with the
abilities of the human body.
The other day
I saw this girl
On youtube.
She was born
with this gene
That doesn't let her feel
any pain like nothing.
And her parents are freaked
that she could cut her hand
Or burn herself
and not even know.
So she's totally
cloistered.
Pretty cool huh?
It's unusual to
say the least.
So what do you
think, Claire?
Wanna audit some of
these classes with me?
What do you
think, Claire?
Why would I be
interested in that?
Because it's awesome
we could do it together
And you're
still undeclared.
Well I can be undeclared
till, uh, third year.
Yeah, but that's just like
denying the inevitable.
How long can
you do that for?
You know this yellow
is really good.
Yummy yellow.
So Mr. Bennet
what do you do?
Retired.
But I'm always finding new
reasons to go back to work.
Whose do you
think this is?
I mean it's not
his daughter.
Would you let
your kid play here?
Yeah, me neither.
Here I think these keys
go up to the garage.
- I'm gonna go check it out.
- Okay cool.
I'll keep an eye on him.
Okay, tell me what the
hell you think you know.
Come on, whose
stuffed animal is that?
Is there a kid
here? Tell me.
Right. you're
ignoring me now?
Doesn't feel
very good does it?
Somebody has
something you want
And they just won't
give it to you.
I never intended
for this to happen.
Unless you did,
Mr. Parkman.
What the hell's
that supposed to me?
Your life's a mess, Matt.
I'm stuck inside your
mind with your powers
And all your anxieties.
It's sad.
You're so desperate for
anyone to love you...
I mean Janice
or your kid.
And they never will love
you. And you wanna know why?
- Shut up!
- I didn't say anything, man!
Because you come in at a
zero on the confidence scale.
You're always
second-guessing yourself.
Listen, I'm innocent!
Sweating every decision
you make--literally.
- I swear!
- You know what I think?
I think you wanted me
in here to help you.
You wanted me to pick your
sorry ass up out of the mud
And help make you a man.
Very good, detective.
You found it
all on your own.
I'm almost impressed.
Now what are you
gonna do, Matt?
Are you man
enough to save her?
You were right,
Mr. Bennet.
This was outstanding.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
That mango lassi just
goes right through you.
Excuse me.
-Okay, look..
- I know things are difficult,
But I can't believe you
told her about your ability.
I didn't tell her!
She just found out.
I gotta contact the Haitian.
erase Gretchen's memory.
Clean this mess up.
Hey! Gretchen is not the
enemy. She's just a girl.
And she's the only
friend that I've made.
I appreciate your concern
But I don't need you
fighting my battles for me.
I can handle this.
Really? What's
your plan, Claire?
Stop. You make
that phone call
And I swear I
will banish you.
I will not call.
I will not email.
This is my mess and
I'm gonna clean it up.
So. What's for dessert?
- Where is she?
- What are you talking about?
This is what
I'm talking about
The girl you wrote
the ransom note for.
- Where is she?
- There is no girl.
Little girl's life
at stake, Parkman.
You don't have
a lot of time.
Use your power.
Under the stairs
She's under... She's
under the stairs.
What did you do?
What did you do!
What? Dude, what
are you doing?
Parkman! Parkman what
the hell are you doing?
A girl. He killed a girl.
Her body's
under the stairs.
- What girl?
- The girl!
The girl's body
Mike. she's right--
The stuffed rabbit.
where's the stuffed--
Pink stuffed
I used your own
power against you.
You're being sued?
This is a scam.
This guy wasn't even
in that bus crash.
According to
my log he was.
The hospital is not gonna
take the fall on this.
They're gonna blame you.
For what? I've been
nothing but committed.
Yeah I know.
You're everywhere.
Always the
first on scene.
What's that
supposed to mean?
There's a couple of
people floating the theory
that you cause the
accidents yourself.
Glory hounding.
So what you-you
believe them?
They ask if you've
been reckless
They ask if you've been
behaving suspiciously.
- You have.
- Hesam, you know me.
- We're partners.
- Partners?
Man, you run off the
second we get on scene.
I'm your chauffeur.
He was on the bus.
Look. Claire, I'm sorry
if I push too hard.
I push. I'm pushy.
Ya think?
You don't want to
talk. I get that.
Wanted to keep a
secret that got out.
When I was in junior high
The girls called me
retchin' Gretchen.
That's a
terrible nickname.
Yeah, they said that
I smelled like puke
Because I was bulimic.
Wow. I can't believe
they would make that up.
Yeah. Made it up.
I'll see you around.
Gretchen.
I really really
want to trust you
But my life has been a
complex series of disasters
And it's been a
really really long time
Since I felt safe enough
to tell anyone the truth.
But I'm tired of keeping
the secret to myself.
So ask me anything.
I'll tell you the truth.
Mr. petrelli. didn't
expect to see you again.
You look like you've been
running all over the city.
I need to
apologize to you.
You were on that bus.
I made a mistake
and i am sorry.
Thank you.
I'm gonna make it right.
No need to
concern yourself.
There must be
something i can do.
Have you ever
lost a brother?
No. no i haven't.
I used to work hospice.
I used to help families through
the worst pain imaginable.
Joseph and i
grew up nearby.
I thought i'd
go back home
To remember
the good times.
Can't bring
yourself to go?
Too many bad memories
mixed in with the good.
My trip here
started as one thing
But it turned into
something else.
Can't seem to find
any solace anywhere.
Grieving is messy.
I saw it all the time.
People can offer
their condolences.
They can tell you they're
sorry for your loss
But they don't know what
it is that you're feeling.
What do you
say to people?
I just sit with them
Be with them.
I'd let 'em know that
they're not alone.
So what made you
become a paramedic?
I wanted to save lives
instead of watching them pass.
You're exactly who
i'd hoped you'd be.
I'm dropping the lawsuit.
Thank you peter
for everything.
You know it's not
for nothing but if you
Made the trip all
the way out here
I really think that you
should visit your home.
I think i will.
Sorry to bother
you at this hour
But um
I grew up here.
My father used
to be the butler.
My mother was the maid.
My brother uh
recently passed away
And uh i just
Thought i could
take a look around.
Not here but in
the carriage house.
We're actually in the
middle of a dinner party.
Please.
This really is
not a good time.
Sorry for your loss.
So wait you're telling me
that you've never been drunk?
Because that's like 85%
of the college experience.
I know. it just
doesn't work on me.
I heal too quickly.
But the good thing is
You will always have
a designated driver.
Can I see it?
See what?
The healing?
If that's not
crossing a line.
The hand's always
the favorite.
Go for it.
I've never done
this before.
Well I would hope not.
It's okay.
Aah! oh my god oh my god!
I'm so sorry!
are you okay?
I'm just kidding.
i'm sorry.
That was mean. I'm fine.
I have to take this.
I'll be right back.
Dad I've got everything
under control, okay?
And I told Gretchen
everything about everything
And I know that
you're gonna be mad.
But this was my choice.
It's not just us anymore
And I'm gonna have
other people in my life
Friends and boyfriends
And I can't close
myself off with lies.
- Did you rehearse that speech?
- Yes.
I wanted to get it right.
No, it..it was
good. listen I, um
I think I owe
you an apology.
I was a bit harsh
earlier at the restaurant.
- A bit?
- Okay. Two bits.
It's just...
When I look at you
I can't help seeing
my Claire bear and, uh
When you get in
any kind of trouble
I feel this instinct
to protect you.
Well you can't
do that now.
I don't think I can
ever really do it again.
Not like before.
Look I will always
be here for you.
Always.
But you're right.
You can handle your
own problems now.
And I'll try to worry
about myself from now on.
Thanks.
Good night, dad.
Good night  Claire.
Good night.
Can I, uh, borrow this?
No.
Right. Sorry.
No, I..I mean yes.
Yes, but
Well you won't have
to borrow it because
It'll be here.
Do you want to
be my roommate?
Let me think, um
Rooming with a boring girl
who smells like pickles
Or the supergirl who's got
excellent taste in literature.
Well, all right
then. Roommate
I just I don't see any
other way out of this.
You crossed the line man.
What's gonna
happen to me, Mike?
You need to find yourself
a damn good lawyer.
This is gonna
ruin my life.
I am sorry.
Yeah.
Me too.
What are you doing?
I guess I'm just not
strong enough anymore.
Nothing happened here.
He attacked you.
I stopped him.
That's all.
Go call it in.
I'll go call it in, Matt.
I'm proud of you.
You're finally
becoming more like me.
Today is the first day
of the rest of your life.
Now they can
all be like this
Or you and I can
go find my body.
Weird, huh.
Sorry to make
you boys come out.
Three people died here.
Could have been a lot worse.
- So what happened?
- Sinkhole.
Sinkhole?