Previously on Heroes...
Whatever happens in your world,
you can always come back to this one.
I know.
I'll find my way.
- Nice to meet you.
- Mom, this is Emma.
She's gonna kill thousands of people.
It will be a bloodbath.
Tell me exactly what you saw.
You cannot save her.
But someone else can.
People think
that dreaming the future is a gift.
They're wrong.
I don't want to be alone.
And you're supposed to help me.
I can only imagine
what having a bunch of...
excuses could do
to someone's humanity.
In order to become human again,
he has to get rid of all of his powers.
Was that so hard?
- I'm Gabriel, a friend of Matt's.
- He's not here right now.
Could you tell me where he is?
It's important that I speak with him.
This is your fantasy.
This isn't my life.
Something wrong, sir?
Yes, something is wrong.
Where is everyone?
The carnival is closed.
Everybody saw
what you did to that town.
- They're afraid of me.
- Can you blame them?
We finally have a home here...
A place to make a life.
It's what we wanted.
- What you told us that you wanted.
- You don't trust me anymore, do you?
- You haven't for a long time.
- So show me why I should.
Out of trust is faith.
It must be very hard for you
to come by...
when you can steal a look
into someone's soul with a touch.
After all I've done for you,
for all of them, I'm the villain.
And you...
you seem to have become the empath
to replace Joseph.
Everyone's looking to you now
for their voice, aren't they?
What are you telling them?
Nobody respects you anymore.
And I'm gonna win it back.
I love them.
I need them.
And I'll do whatever I have to do...
to prove my worth.
Subtitles: Rebel (1.0)
www.sous-titres.eu
Don't worry.
I'm here to save you.
It's Peter Petrelli.
Is Emma Coolidge there?
Look, it's important.
Just...
I already went by her place.
She's not there.
If you see her,
call me, okay?
Thanks.
Ma?
Janice, honey, you home?
Haven't you ever heard
of making two trips?
Oh, God.
Are you back inside my head?
That's so two months ago.
Here, let me give you a hand.
Calm down, if I wanted you dead,
we wouldn't be talking.
What, then?
It's complicated.
My life's taken a turn
since last time.
You could say
I'm on a fact-finding mission.
Matt, honey.
I thought you'd be at work.
I took Matty to day care,
and my client canceled...
Lucky I was home, your friend Gabriel
was in the neighborhood.
He is full of stories.
Stories?
From when we were partners
on the force.
I figured you guys
would like to catch up,
so I put
a little late lunch together.
It looks so good, thank you.
Take a load off, have a nosh.
We really need to catch up.
This is probably not a good time.
In fact, it's not even a big deal.
- It's over. I don't need to tell him.
- You kind of do.
A superpowered serial killer
shape-shifted into a coed
and made a pie chart of your life.
It wasn't a pie chart.
It was more like a...
- Whatever. You have to tell your dad.
- Really?
When Sylar killed my real dad,
he didn't tell me.
I know.
You're right.
But you...
I know.
How long will you hold a grudge?
The whole silent treatment
is getting old.
We were in a good place
before all this.
Do you want me to come with?
I have to do this alone.
I could wait.
It's probably gonna be a while.
The list of things
we have to talk about... Sylar...
The cover-up of my dad's death.
Let's not forget about the carnival.
I'm sure there's plenty my dad
wants to say about that.
Good luck.
You'll feel better
when it's all over with.
Or if not,
at least you'll be caffeinated.
You gonna let me in?
Of course.
Where's my dad?
He just stepped out for a moment.
I brought some coffee.
Thought it was time
to talk things over with him.
I'm sorry...
but why are you here exactly?
- Your father and I are...
- No, that's not...
that's not what I was talking about.
You have Primatech files,
and satellite maps, and this is...
everything that my dad
said that he would put behind him.
- I'm just trying to help a friend.
- Friends do dinners and movies.
You want to help?
You tell my dad whatever it is
that he's doing, he needs to stop.
I wish it was that simple.
Why?
What's going on?
There was an incident.
It was Samuel Sullivan.
What did he do?
They're saying it was a landslide,
but we know it was Samuel.
Wait, you think he buried that town?
Can he do that?
He gains more power
the more specials he has around.
200 are dead,
they're still digging out the bodies.
What are you planning to do?
Your dad will be back any minute.
Why don't you just...
Actually, I have class.
Looks like you have this under control,
so just tell him I stopped by.
- Claire, wait.
- Enjoy the coffee.
I've always loved
the Black and Whites.
- Are they still Matty's favorite?
- How do you know that?
Like I said,
Parkman and I used to be pretty tight.
We went through...
addiction counseling together,
and faced our mutual demons.
You know what? I'll show Gabe
what I've been doing in the basement.
The world of Matt's projects.
You'll love it down there.
I'm sure I will.
You're on a fact-finding mission?
What the hell does that mean?
I had to make sure
I remembered it right.
Husband...
and father...
You figured out a way
to live with your ability.
You may not believe this,
but in some ways,
you're actually stronger than I am.
I'm not afraid of you, okay?
So if this is about revenge...
After what you did to me,
I was tempted.
I don't want to be
like that anymore.
I need you
to go inside my head again.
You're serious.
You are insane.
If I am, it's because
that's what my powers have made me.
I can't live with them anymore.
So you need to take them away.
You want me to...
How am I supposed to do that?
Create a mental block, repress them.
I don't really care, to be honest.
All I know...
is that once I'm free
from the temptation of my ability...
You're gonna be normal?
I'm sorry,
that ship sailed 50 murders ago.
I'm asking nicely.
The last time I was inside your head,
you turned my life into a living hell.
Why would I risk that?
Janice, and the kid.
I really do want to change.
But I'm insane.
Remember?
And all you have to do is point.
Fine, I will try.
But you have to let Janice go.
Consider it a gesture of good faith.
Hey, mom.
What's wrong?
It's Nathan.
The stonecutters called.
They needed a final wording
for his headstone,
and I didn't know what to say.
I guess it's the finality of it.
I mean, they're just words,
but when you write them down,
when you etch them in stone...
I know, mom.
Maybe it was selfish of me, Peter,
but I just needed to see you.
I needed to be sure you were okay.
Because of your vision.
I had the dream too, mom.
I saw all the people.
And Sylar...
I think he was trying to help Emma.
You saw that too?
Whatever this vision is, Peter,
remember this:
one isolated act does not make
Sylar your friend's savior.
I need you to help me find him, mom.
I know you know where he is.
Sylar's never been far
from my thoughts.
But I'm begging you, don't go.
He murdered Nathan, and the last time
you faced him, he almost killed you.
Mom, Emma's in trouble.
People's lives are at stake.
Nathan would never turn
his back on them.
And you know that I can't either.
This is gonna end badly.
Samuel is crazy.
My dad's gonna take him down,
and there is no way
this is gonna end well.
What?
What do you want me to say?
What do you think I should do?
I don't know. You've got
a humanities lecture in 20 minutes.
Here's a crazy idea,
maybe you should go to class for once.
Did you hear anything I just said?
I did.
Yeah, all of it.
But I mean, what are you
really gonna do, Claire?
Your dad was right about the carnival.
You never should have gone there.
Look, Samuel is a bad guy, yes.
But the rest of the carnival
is all family and children.
And they just want to live their lives
being open about their abilities.
I thought you said
they were giving Samuel his power.
But they don't know that.
You were only there for one day.
How can you know for sure?
I need to borrow your car.
I thought
you would back me up on this.
You say you want
a normal life, right?
Just let your dad handle it.
Come on, please.
Just come to class with me.
Or not.
Bring it back full.
- She's not answering.
- She said she had a class.
Claire,
call me as soon as you get this.
You shouldn't have let her go.
What was I supposed to do, drag her
by her hair and lock her in your closet?
What do you want to do?
We go.
If Samuel's escalating his attacks,
we can't sit around and wait to see
- what he's gonna do next.
- But you're also emotional.
Look, this Samuel is a threat
and not just to Claire.
You go in with less than 100% focus...
I can handle this.
You don't have to worry about me.
That's not an option anymore.
Let's go.
- We need to talk.
- What are you doing here?
Your father is coming for Samuel,
to kill him.
Claire, if Samuel finds out, he's...
I know.
That's why I came ahead.
I have seen things like this
go wrong before,
and I don't want my dad
or anyone else getting hurt.
But we don't much time.
Samuel will never go for it.
He'll never turn himself in.
We have to try.
He is not listening
to me, to anyone.
If your father is really on his way,
I should get Amanda.
And what, Lydia...
run away?
Has it come to that?
I can't say I blame you...
What I did to that town,
all those people.
I'd hoped you'd have
a better reason to come back.
How could you do that?
I don't know what I was thinking.
I wish I could take it all back...
And so many other things... Joseph.
Did I ever tell you
the first carnival act
that Joseph and I ever saw
was the trapeze?
The way they flung themselves
through the air,
we thought they had powers,
just like us.
But when we went backstage,
the man told us
the only power he had was gravity.
No matter how high he went,
it was always there to catch him.
I've come to realize that gravity
is different things to people.
For much of my life,
Joseph was mine.
I've been losing my way.
And now even my own family
is afraid of me.
- And the only strength I have left...
- You have to take responsibility.
You have to turn yourself over.
To your father?
He's not exactly known
for his mercy.
If you give yourself up,
he will not hurt you, I promise.
Please, Samuel,
listen to her.
If you care about this family,
then protect them.
There's Samuel on the midway.
Got him.
Wait a second.
Is that Claire?
At 2:00.
Dad, where are you?
Close.
I heard you stopped by earlier.
Thanks for the coffee.
What's the situation there?
Samuel wants to surrender.
Really?
- Why?
- To protect his family.
He's willing to turn himself over
as long as the rest of the carnival
stays safe and under the grid.
And you trust him?
If there's a chance
that we can do this without anyone
getting hurt, don't we have to try?
Dad, it's the best plan, all right?
You get Samuel,
and nobody gets hurt.
All right. Tell him to meet us
in the field outside of the carnival.
I'll see you soon.
He's surrendering.
And you think
he's just gonna give himself up?
I don't know, but Claire seems
to think so, and I have to trust her.
It's done.
He wants you to meet him in the field.
Are you sure this is a good idea?
I wouldn't worry.
If it's a setup,
you'll just get a better shot at him,
out in the open.
Wait a second.
I'll do down and walk him out.
Keep him in the crosshairs.
Be careful.
I know my recent actions
have caused some of you
to question
where it is my heart lies.
I regret
what I've done.
I acted impulsively,
and that has brought one of them...
An agent...
To our door.
It's okay.
They just want me.
Claire has helped arrange
a peaceful surrender.
I'll go with them.
No, no, please, listen.
I know everyone will not agree
with this decision.
But it's the only way.
The safety of each
and every one of you
and keeping this family together
is what matters most to me.
And if that means I have to leave,
so be it.
All right, Parkman,
I did my part.
I let Janice walk. Now it's your turn.
I know.
I said I would try.
Nothing's changed.
I know you can do this,
what's wrong?
I don't know.
- I can't.
- Try again.
Maybe it's not me.
Maybe it's you.
Maybe you're fighting it.
Maybe you really don't want
to let go of these powers.
- You're lying!
- I'm not!
- What's going on?
- Stop!
Oh, God.
Please let her go.
Look at me!
Come on, let her go.
She had nothing to do with this.
- I'll try again.
- That's not good enough.
You see what you made me do?
I don't even know
if I can do this for you.
Maybe you need
a little more motivation.
You will purge me of these powers...
or I will use them...
I will use them all.
And trust me,
I can get creative.
Damn.
Come quickly!
Put pressure on the wound.
I need your help. Come on.
You wanted to know
what was in my heart.
You... did... this?
I'm sorry.
So sorry.
I'm so sorry.
They needed a villain...
someone worse than me.
You gave that to them.
Thank you.
I'll do it.
It's too late.
She's gone.
Come on, Dad.
Pick up, please.
Dad.
I found him on the hill...
with this!
- Are you okay?
- I didn't do it.
- I didn't shoot anything...
- Murderer!
He's the one.
You brought him here.
You're one of them.
Back off!
Don't hurt them.
We're better than this.
Take him to the house of mirrors.
Tie him up.
And her?
My trailer.
Get off!
Dad!
Let go!
He didn't do it!
Get off!
- If you hurt her, I swear to God...
- That's the problem, isn't it?
One cruel thought is all it takes.
These powers make it so easy.
I understand that, believe me.
You don't have to use them like this.
Except I do.
The powers are me, now.
You've been there, dealt with them,
the constant temptation.
How do you compartmentalize?
How do you keep them
from overwhelming your life?
You start by accepting the fact
that you're more than your abilities.
We're people first.
Please, let her go.
Look, I'll try to do what you want,
but let me make sure she's okay.
Last chance.
Come on.
It's okay.
- That's Sylar, isn't it?
- I'm so sorry.
This is crazy.
He wants me to take away
his powers and make him normal.
I looked inside his head long enough,
he's serious,
- but I can't give him what he wants.
- Forget about that.
I work with monsters like this.
He's broken inside.
We have to bury him
so that he cannot hurt anyone else.
Just go,
don't come back until I call you.
Get on with it.
You were right...
I was holding back.
It's all about motivation, right?
What if I told you
that I can be special,
but to do it, I'd have to hurt
a lot of people? Should I?
You? You could never hurt anyone.
Mommy.
I don't...
I don't feel any different.
Try something, go ahead, on me.
Come on.
You did it.
My powers are gone.
They're just buried... somewhere
that you can never get to them.
You've threatened my family
for the last time.
- What did you do?
- I know exactly what scares you.
And it's being alone
with your immortality.
- What did you do to me?
- I have trapped you inside your mind.
You're gonna be alone, Sylar.
Very much alone...
In this nightmare
that will last forever.
And the best part about it,
when I leave,
you won't remember what I did.
And you'll live
every empty day like it's real.
You said you would help me.
Yeah, I guess there's still
a little of you left inside me...
Because I lied.
Enjoy hell.
Samuel said you'd come.
Thank God you're here.
I need your help.
Finally,
there's a doctor in the house.
- What happened?
- We were attacked.
You were attacked?
By who?
People who don't understand us,
Emma...
People who fear us.
It doesn't matter.
What matters is that you're here.
You're not just gonna heal me.
You're gonna help us make
a new world for ourselves.
We'll show them, Emma.
We'll show them how great we can be.
Hey, man.
Sorry, I was working downstairs.
- That's okay, man. Been a long time.
- Yeah, how are you?
What?
- Sylar is here.
- What are you talking about?
About what you're thinking.
You're gonna take him.
You can't do that!
People die, Matt.
Sylar has to save them.
Peter, he's a murderer!
Come on, stop.
Listen.
He's trapped, Peter.
- What the hell did you do?
- I went inside his head,
and I trapped him
in his worst nightmare.
He'll never hurt anyone again.
- I have to bring him back.
- No, you can't do that.
You go into his head,
you might not come out.
Noah Bennet told me to call
if anything went wrong.
I went to Bennet.
I thought...
Look what they've done...
These so-called normal people.
How could you let this happen?
What I did was wrong.
I know that.
But I was willing
to sacrifice myself to protect you...
To save this family
that we've all come to love.
The outside world
has proven once again
that people like us
will never be accepted.
We've all seen it...
In the eyes of those
who come to see our shows...
Dazzled by our abilities...
But filled with revulsion
of who we are.
I saw it again yesterday...
In that small town over the hill...
And today in the bullets that struck me
and murdered our dear Lydia.
It's time.
It's time we put fear behind us.
It's time we showed the world...
what we truly are.