There are many ways
to define our fragile existence.
Many ways to give it meaning.
I love you.
I love you, Nathan.
But it is our memories
that shape its purpose
and give it context.
- You're very sick.
- Brain tumor. I'm dying.
A private assortment
of images, fears,
loves, regrets.
We alone choose
the importance of each.
How do you feel, Hiro?
Building our own unique histories
one memory at a time.
What have you done?
Did you send a cello
to my apartment?
Cello, no.
Hoping that ones we remember
don't betray or trap us.
They are no bad powers.
You will learn to use your powers
to do good things in the world.
- Where'd you learn how to do that?
- Medical school. I dropped out.
Are you gonna go back to school?
Go be a doctor?
For it is the cruel irony of life
that we are destined to hold
the dark with the light.
The good with the evil.
- You betrayed me.
- I'm still your brother.
I need you to start
by retrieving some files
from the apartment
of a Mr. Noah Bennet.
- What do you want?
- We don't want anyone to get hurt.
So we'll just take what we came for,
and we will be on our way.
This is what separates us,
makes us human.
- Gone.
- So are your files.
And in the end,
what we must fight to hold on to.
- Where'd you get that?
- I stole it from my dad.
We came all this way
to go to a carnival?
Glad you could make it.
I think it's time...
for some soul-searching.
You're welcome to stay a few days
and do just that.
I'm gonna stay.
Just for a couple days.
I'm not sure she's gonna serve
a purpose for you.
It's not her I'm after.
Don't worry about Eli,
he's harmless.
I've caught him staring at me,
like, three times.
It's that you're new.
Everybody's talking.
Talking's okay with me.
Staring?
Not so much.
You have breakfast yet?
Yes, I had the blueberry pancakes,
and they were amazing.
I'm taking some to Samuel now.
He is in his trailer.
You know...
How about you take them to him?
Score some points.
Not that you need to,
but he does love
Mrs. Comey's pancakes.
Okay, sure.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Hope you brought extra syrup.
How'd you know I had pancakes?
I thought you were Lydia.
That's so very nice of you.
That box in there
looks a lot like the one
from the paper company
my dad used to work for.
As you may have guessed,
your father and I have shared
more history than you know.
- You can always fill me in.
- I'm not interested in the past.
Not when the future holds
such infinite possibilities.
- The homeland you talked about?
- We're almost there.
And I'd love nothing more
than for you to stay
and watch that come to fruition.
Like I said, I do have
to get back to class on Monday.
Your loss.
How do I look?
I'm going to the city.
Then you look very...
- urban.
- Good.
I need to make a positive impression.
I'm going to get someone...
Someone essential
for the plan coming together.
To help us build a place
where we can be free.
"Freedom is what you do
with what's been done to you."
- Sounds deep.
- Sartre. College.
I always thought freedom
was just another word
for nothing left to lose.
- That too.
- You'll see.
We'll stop running and find
a permanent place to live,
an ordinary place.
Then, you might even want to stay.
Or go.
It's your choice.
- So she's free to go?
- Not in my lifetime.
You make sure of that.
Subtitles: Rebel
www.sous-titres.eu
What are you doing?
- Give it up, little brother.
- It almost moved this time.
Let's see.
Far out.
Now come on.
I've got a show to do.
Just you wait.
I'm gonna move
bigger rocks than that.
People are gonna come
from all over the world to see me.
You mean
Vanessa's gonna come see you.
Vanessa girl.
- Come and see my dirt-moving show.
- Shut up.
I can't believe you're still carrying
a torch for that girl.
Don't you know
we're never going back there?
Tell you what...
If you can get people to buy a ticket
to see a kid not move a rock,
I'll invite her myself.
You're a jerk.
Just you wait.
Just you wait, brother.
Are you serious, Mom?
Come on!
- He's nice.
- He just got here.
I don't even know him from Adam.
I don't know his family.
- Since when do you care?
- The answer is no.
- Something funny?
- Sorry, no.
I just...
I've been looking for something
normal in this place
since this morning,
and I finally found it
when I was listening to you
and your daughter argue.
You sound like my mom and me.
We had some serious knock-down,
drag-outs, but...
I wonder if we had a place like this
if things would've been easier.
How so?
Lose a finger, it grows back.
Nobody looks twice.
Yeah, it's paradise here.
- You don't sound convinced.
- I didn't mean anything by it.
You know things, right?
I mean, you can see things.
Your tattoos.
Sometimes.
- Why?
- I was just wondering if you...
knew why Samuel wanted me here.
Lately he's wanted
a lot of people here.
Half of them
want to date my daughter.
Why's he bringing so many people in?
It's become an obsession of his.
He spent all morning in his trailer.
Yeah, with my dad's files.
If it isn't Nancy Drew.
- Can I help you, Nance?
- I was just looking for Samuel.
He's not around.
- Nice trick.
- I like to think so.
Aren't you on beautification duty?
Why don't you run along
and beautify?
Miss Coolidge?
My name is Samuel.
I've come a long way to see you.
I'm like you.
But I have a gift like you.
Emma, please let me explain.
You can read lips?
Emma, wait.
I'm the one who sent you the cello.
I'm interested in people like us.
I know that you can see
things that other people hear.
And that you feel them,
oh, so much more.
I know many people with gifts.
And one of them
can see from far away,
and she helped me find you.
We're all connected, Emma.
Thanks.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
that was from me.
- Giving it away was not that easy.
- Why?
It was meant for someone else.
Someone special in my life.
She and I... were close.
And then one day I lost her.
May I?
It's found its proper home.
I can see that now.
No, it didn't do that.
You did.
It was your own fear.
That's why I'm here.
You have to let go of that fear
and release your true ability.
I need your help.
I've tried in my usual way
to find this man.
But I've been unsuccessful.
He's overwhelmed by his gift,
like you've been.
But so much more lost.
He thought he was losing his mind
when the moss and the flowers
started growing in his footsteps.
He lost touch with this world
and fell into the cracks.
I'm told he lives in Central Park.
Cover the exits.
- Now you know what it feels like.
- Nice trick.
What do you think you're doing,
Barbie?
Let me go.
Tell me why you were
in Samuel's trailer.
- Listen to me, okay?
- You're a spy, aren't you?
- Working for your father?
- No. I came here on my own.
I believed
what Samuel was saying was real,
but he's collecting
people with abilities.
Yeah, why shouldn't he?
We're a family.
You wouldn't understand that,
would you, Barbie?
You only see the worst in people.
Makes me want
to pin you to that trailer
so Samuel can find you
when he gets back.
Samuel is using my dad's old files
to track people down and bring them in.
He's got a map of that valley out there,
and he is planning something.
And whatever it is...
You're gonna ruin it for everyone.
I'm not gonna let you.
I'm not gonna let you
ruin it for me.
Your gift is more
than seeing sound as color.
- And putting cracks in the wall.
- My true ability, what is it?
Your emotions can become one
with the music.
You can bring people to you.
Like a siren's song.
Siren?
Yeah, just play and you'll see.
Concentrate on him.
Draw him to you.
Now's your chance.
Make your prayers into song.
It's all right.
Let the music fill you up.
Is he all right?
I cannot thank you enough
for getting him in.
If you ever wanna help more of us,
there's a place I'd like you to visit.
We could use a doctor...
And a siren.
This'll help get you there.
- I will. Thank you.
- Thank you.
She's different, like me.
Not different.
Special.
I always thought
I was alone in the world.
I guess I'm...
Just a little scared.
So many of us are, friend.
So many.
But not for long.
Let's go home.
Sources confirm the remains found
in the the small plane crash
are that of New York
senator Nathan Petrelli.
The NTSB is promising a complete
and thorough investigation
into the crash.
At this time,
investigators are reporting
that the senator was the pilot
and sole passenger of the plane.
You're getting weak.
Otherwise
you would've forced my mouth shut.
Don't tempt me, Barbie.
I'm telling you.
Samuel's up to something.
And he's lying to all of you.
- He's a good man.
- Why are you so sure?
Because I'm good now.
This place is good for me.
I haven't done anything
wrong since I got here.
Joseph set me straight.
He showed me what was good
and true about my ability.
Is that who's in that picture
there next to Samuel?
- Samuel's brother.
- He didn't want to let me in at first.
Samuel convinced him.
Lydia said that Samuel was obsessed
with making the family bigger.
Why do you think that Samuel's
bringing in all these people?
Shut up!
- This is my home now, Barbie.
- Listen to me.
I don't want to destroy this place.
But if Samuel's bringing
people in for a reason,
won't it put everyone in danger?
You know me.
Do you seriously think
I want to destroy your home?
Talk to Lydia.
She knows.
Thank you.
- What are you doing here?
- I just went into Samuel's trailer.
He has a map of the valley.
What is he planning?
You wanted me to go in there
for a reason, why?
You know something
and you're not telling me what it is.
Samuel wasn't...
He wasn't always in charge.
Joseph...
He was our real father.
He made this...
place a home.
I miss him.
- We all miss him.
- What happened to him?
He killed him, didn't he?
He's lost his way, Claire.
I am scared for all of us.
I woke up this morning
and I wasn't sure about this place.
But this place is special.
For you, and for your daughter.
Even Doyle.
The only thing wrong with it
is Samuel.
You have to help us.
Please.
You have to find someone...
that can stop him.
I will.
No buried treasure for you,
Nancy Drew.
- What were you thinking?
- You told me to watch her.
She's not a prisoner.
If she wants to go, she can go.
Not a prisoner? Sure feels that way
with copy boy over here.
Don't you ever get sick of him?
Stay or go, Claire.
It's still your choice.
I'll go.
After you tell me
what happened to Joseph.
Eli, give us a minute.
Did Lydia tell you?
No, I asked her, she wouldn't.
It's true, isn't it?
- You killed him.
- I lost control.
Like that is an excuse?
He told the government about us.
You remember them, don't you?
They lured him in.
Very same people
that have been chasing us for years.
Emile Danko. Same one
who worked alongside your father.
The man who imprisoned you.
How do you think
your father got the compass?
This is not about my father.
Okay? This is about what you did.
What I did was awful.
Joseph put us all in danger.
After years of running free,
I wasn't about to let him get away
with that and take that away from us.
So murder was the answer?
You, of all people,
should understand
how far a father
will go to protect his family.
Hasn't your father lied, cheated,
even killed...
To protect you?
What's going on out in that valley?
Every artist needs his canvas,
Claire.
And Ian...
Well, Ian is Picasso.
I need water.
That can be arranged.
It's beautiful.
It's you.
It's who you are.
It is beautiful.
What is this place?
Our new home.
My brother would've loved it.
He never believed it was possible.
He certainly never believed
I could make it real.
This is why I need a bigger family,
to build the future.
This could be your home too, Claire.
I have a home.
And I'd like to go back to it.
Of course.
But just remember...
You're free, Claire.
Whatever happens
in your world back home,
you can always come back
to this one.
Whenever you want.
I know.
Claire, we need to talk.
Claire bear, call me.
Claire, hey, it's peter.
You need to call me.
Something happened.
We have a lot to talk about.
I'm glad you're safe.
From what?
Where I came from or this lie?
I know you took the compass.
And I'm not giving it back.
My brother Nathan taught me a lot.
He taught me...
How to ride a skateboard
when I was a kid,
how to hook a marlin,
he taught me how...
to catch a baseball.
Those are all things...
usually a father'll teach his son.
But dad wasn't around.
So it was Nathan.
And I wish to hell it
would've been my father,
because Nathan didn't make it easy.
He would throw it high,
or he'd throw it wide.
And I would yell at him.
I would tell him to throw it
right at me. But he'd say to me,
"that's not how it's gonna come
at you in a game, Pete."
I used to think he was just being
a big brother and he was picking on me.
But now I understand.
He just wanted me to be ready...
For anything.
I'm ready, brother.
For whatever comes.
Detail, atten-hut!
Detail, halt!
Flag.
Ma'am, this flag is presented
on behalf of a grateful nation
for the honorable and faithful service
rendered by your loved one.
Thank you.
Ready.
Aim.
Fire!
Honor, hut!