Previously on Heroes...
Wait a second.
Is that Claire?
- Samuel wants to surrender.
- Really?
- Why?
- To protect his family.
He'll turn himself over
as long as the rest of the carnival
stays safe and under the grid.
I found him on the hill...
with this!
She's gonna kill thousands of people.
It will be a bloodbath.
Tell me exactly what you saw.
- You cannot save her.
- But someone else can.
Don't worry.
I'm here to save you.
He's trapped.
- What did you do?
- I trapped him in his worst nightmare.
He'll never hurt anyone again.
- I have to bring him back.
- You can't do that.
You might not come out.
Peter, don't!
Is that really you?
Came to get you out.
It is you, isn't it?
I thought I was alone,
that everyone was dead.
- What are you doing here?
- To drag your sorry ass out of here.
Let's go.
There is no getting out.
I've tried...
for three years.
What are you talking about?
It's been three hours.
Wait a minute.
You're not...
you're not real.
This is my mind, isn't it?
This is my mind playing tricks on me,
as part of my punishment, isn't it?
You think I'll let you taunt me?
Stay away.
If you follow me, I'll kill you!
Do you understand?
I swear I'll kill you.
Get out of my head.
Calm down.
I'm telling you the truth.
I came to take you out of here.
Why do you keep saying that?
I went to Parkman's house.
He put you here.
- This is a dream.
- It's not a dream!
This is real.
You don't understand
this is a nightmare?
Hell, yes, it's a nightmare.
Three years, completely alone.
Not years, hours.
All right?
Parkman trapped you here.
- Parkman? Impossible.
- Is it?
What's the last thing you remember
before coming here?
I remember...
wanting my life to change,
thinking I was gonna spend
all of eternity alone.
Exactly.
And here you are.
I've got Parkman's ability.
I can take you out of here.
Why would you want to do that?
The brother of the man I murdered
coming to my aid?
Because I need you to help me.
I could leave you here to rot,
but I need you to save her,
my friend Emma.
In the dream, you save her
before she kills thousands of people.
Wrong guy. I'm not the savior kind,
and you should know that.
It's gonna happen,
and you're gonna save her.
Fine.
You really think
you can get us out of here?
Let me see you try.
Go ahead.
See?
We won't go anywhere.
We're trapped here, forever.
Subtitles: Rebel (1.0)
www.sous-titres.eu
- We got to do something with her.
- We will.
Excuse me.
I wanna see my father.
He's safe, unharmed,
which is more than he deserves
after shooting innocent people.
My dad didn't shoot anyone.
If he had, you would be dead.
You're not that naive, are you?
He came to this carnival with a gun,
intent on using it.
Isn't that why you tried
to negotiate my surrender?
- You were afraid he'd do this.
- I want to see my father now!
Your devotion to your father
is touching,
but you're blinded by it.
It's time for you to open your eyes
and see your father for who he is.
I know who he is.
Nothing you say will change that.
Of course not.
That's why I'll show you.
- Dad!
- Thank God you're all right.
Untie him.
Not quite yet.
Damien has the ability
to reveal a person's memories.
It's fairly painless
if you don't fight it.
You think showing my dad's memories
is gonna enlighten me?
You deserve the truth.
Let her go.
You don't need her anymore.
You afraid she'll see the real you?
Don't do this.
Take a peek.
See where it all began.
This one has it all.
White walls, wire wheel covers,
- wood grain, everything.
- The kids'll love it.
- What's the payment look like?
- $150 a month.
I know, that's kind of steep.
Look...
You didn't hear this from me,
but go to Val's Discount Motors
on La Cienega.
The same model, maybe a year older,
probably half of what you'll pay here.
Thanks.
Really appreciate that.
Guess who?
Let me see.
Soft, lovely hands,
long, supple fingers.
I don't know. Candy?
- Candy?
- I'm in trouble.
It's my wife.
What are you doing here?
I came by to see how
the most handsome salesman's doing.
If I see him, I'll ask him.
Me... not so good.
I stink at this job.
- I have no killer instinct.
- You don't belong here.
- You should be home writing plays.
- Somebody has to pay the rent.
Who needs money?
We can live on love.
Wouldn't that be nice?
What's going on?
Is something wrong?
I hope not.
It's just I have
some unexpected news.
- And promise me you won't get mad.
- Kate, what is it?
I'm pregnant.
I know we didn't plan this,
and you always want to be
the man with the plan, but...
You're happy?
Of course, I'm happy.
I'm gonna be a father!
You had another wife and family?
I'm sorry I never told you.
It doesn't matter.
Let him go.
You're not curious
about what happened to his first wife?
It's his business...
There are reasons he kept it secret.
Isn't that right?
Let her go.
You got what you wanted,
someone to blame, me.
Look at the fear in his eyes.
He knows what's coming.
I'll leave you with Damien.
You'll find it very informative.
Don't do this, you son of a bitch!
Did you order pot stickers?
Double order.
You're eating for two now.
Can you believe this?
You and me, parents.
What's it gonna be like?
I have no idea.
But I can't wait to find out.
The moo shu has arrived.
Go.
Delivery.
What happened to Mr. Yin?
He usually delivers.
He couldn't make it.
Okay, so... how much do I owe you?
All of it.
I can't move.
What did you do?
Where's the money?
- How did you do that?
- Kate, give him your purse.
- This is it?
- That's all. Take it and go.
What are you?
Kate... My God.
Give it up.
Can't go forever
without talking to me.
I mean, you've gone a month.
That's impressive.
There isn't anybody out there.
There never will be.
I won't spend the rest of my life here,
alone, with you.
It isn't exactly heaven
for me either.
Here.
I know you like comics.
I couldn't find Doc Savage or Flash.
What's wrong?
You need to stop messing around
and focus.
Focus, right? 'cause we got to get out
of here so we can go rescue...
What's her name again?
Emma.
Her name's Emma.
It's time to face reality.
That girl is gone.
If she was meant to kill thousands,
they're dead too.
Everybody's dead except us.
The only thing that's real is us.
You think you've been here for years,
but this is all just a dream.
If this is all a dream,
how are there books, huh?
- How did Parkman make books?
- Because it's your dream.
How could I know all the words
to Pillars of the Earth or Catch-22?
Maybe you read it somewhere,
- it's in your subconscious.
- I didn't read 9th wonders!
- I did.
- So now we're in your head?
I don't know! I don't know
how this all works!
- Don't you want to get out of here?
- Yeah, of course!
You don't, do you?
- You don't want to get out of here.
- Maybe I deserve all this aloneness...
This nothing, maybe I earned it.
Yeah, maybe you have,
but I can't do this on my own.
I need you to help me...
All right, Peter.
You want me to help you?
I want to help.
Where did that come from?
That's the wall from...
Parkman's basement.
What's it doing here?
- This is our way out.
- What?
Don't you get it?
We have to break through.
Can I help you?
I was just leaving.
You're hurt. Let me see.
I'm a doctor. Please.
You don't have to do this.
I don't want you to get in trouble.
I have a hearing loss.
Say that again?
My name is Lauren.
I came here to stop Samuel Sullivan.
You were with the man
who shot everyone. Bennet?
Bennet never fired his gun.
Your leader, Samuel,
is not what he appears to be.
He's the one responsible.
He wouldn't shoot his own people.
You're wrong.
He's done terrible things.
And now he's trying to galvanize
his people around a common enemy.
I got to check in with the doc.
Samuel's coming.
Don't tell him I'm here!
Everything all right?
It's all right.
I just want to talk.
Well, look what we have here.
Your first wife
was murdered by a special?
That was a long time ago.
And the person I was
then died that night with Kate.
I'm sorry I never told you.
That's okay.
Some things you just can't...
say out loud.
But that's the reason why
you joined the company.
That's how you became
Mr. Bag and tag.
I don't need to see any more.
Don't move.
- You want my wallet? Take it.
- Don't move!
I'm not after your money.
What, then?
Information. I know what you are.
I know what you can do.
- How?
- It doesn't matter.
I'm looking for somebody,
one of you.
One of me?
What are you talking about?
- There's someone else like me?
- Don't give me that.
What you do isn't normal.
You have to know each other.
The guy I'm looking for
is named Richard.
He's about 6 feet tall,
got dark hair.
Maybe 23 years old.
He can move things with his mind.
He killed my wife.
I don't know anyone else like me.
I swear.
I don't believe you.
- It was an accident.
- You brought a gun.
I didn't know what I would find.
I was scared.
The first time you killed anyone.
What happens next?
One owner, low miles,
hottest car I got on the lot.
It's the best I can do,
take it or leave it.
- You said...
- You know, I got another buyer
who's chomping at the bit.
What's it gonna be?
I guess we'll take it.
Excellent choice.
I'll have my manager draw up
the papers. Excuse me.
Hey, there.
- Can I interest you in a car?
- Not really.
I'm here to offer you a job.
- Do I know you?
- We've been watching you.
The way you killed that special...
The repairman.
We'd been tracking him too,
only you got there first.
Relax.
Your secret is safe with us.
We're impressed,
so impressed, in fact,
we'd like you to come work for us.
Who are you?
My name is Thompson.
My associates and I can help you
Find the man who killed your wife.
And then you can help us...
find the rest.
How's it working out for you, the...
"one of us, one of them?"
To tell you the truth,
it's been quite an adjustment.
I mean, Claude can go invisible
anytime he wants.
- It gives him a distinct advantage.
- Advantage?
You're supposed to be partners.
What is it, trust issues?
I mean, how could it not be?
He's abnormal.
I mean, sometimes when I'm alone,
I get...
this feeling in my gut
that he's watching me.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah, I do.
You know, your case
is highly unusual, Bennet.
How you came to our attention,
what happened to your wife.
It would be only natural
that you would harbor a grudge.
- What are you getting at?
- 17 cases,
three deaths, all attributed to you.
They were all accidents.
That's been verified.
Two corned beefs.
Need anything else?
No, we're all set.
Thanks.
At this point, the company
has too much invested in you
to cut ties.
But we do need you to make a change.
Take a wife, start a family.
Is that a joke?
It'll put your life in balance,
calm you down...
so there will be fewer incidents.
A wife?
- I can't do that again.
- Sure, you can.
That cute number who brought
the sandwiches will do fine.
And if I refuse?
You won't.
The company arranged your marriage.
They encouraged me but I chose
your mother because I loved her.
You know that.
The company seems to make
a lot of decisions for you.
They made many decisions.
That's all over with.
All the memories you're seeing now,
that's all they are.
It's just the past.
Hey, Mr. Bennet.
What are you doing here?
Came to see Claire.
Would you know where she is?.
No idea.
You don't have to lie for her.
I know that Claire stole the compass,
and I would bet good money
the two of you drove out
to the carnival together.
My question is,
why didn't she come back with you?
She wanted to stay.
She said she'd be back on Monday.
You left her there?
Do you not see what's happening?
That she is getting
involved in something
that she clearly doesn't understand.
Maybe she wants to understand it.
This isn't a game.
These carnival people are killers.
You don't think I know that?
She needs to be with people like her.
If they're not good for her,
trust her to know the difference.
You have to stop encouraging her.
You need to work with me on this.
- I want her to be happy.
- She is happy,
with you here in college,
Living a normal life.
What if that's not enough for her?
It has to be.
What's he doing here?
Are you gonna erase my memory?
Not if you do what I ask.
You were missing. I didn't know
how to find you, if I would find you.
- You don't trust me.
- I don't trust Samuel.
- Gretchen is fine.
- You threatened her!
And this was not some distant past.
This was now.
- You should eat.
- Don't need to eat.
Don't need to sleep.
Don't need anything.
Any progress today?
It's just like yesterday...
- And the day before that.
- And...
the day before that.
Now it's been...
I don't even know
how long it's been.
- Don't tell me how long it's been.
- You can't even dent it, Peter.
I don't know how much longer
you can keep this up.
As long as it takes.
I know that look.
You have it all the time.
What look?
Like when Kaplan beat you at the dash
and we ran to school every morning
and kept training
and kept it up, right?
That is Nathan's memory.
That's not yours.
I told you to stop doing that.
You're not him.
You're nothing like him.
So you've told me.
Look, I know that I've said it before,
but...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I killed him.
I'm sorry that I took him from you.
Sorry!
You keep saying that
"I'm sorry. I'm sorry."
That's not gonna bring
my brother back.
- It doesn't change anything.
- You're right!
Nothing changes!
We're stuck here forever,
you and me!
I can't take it anymore.
You're with that company,
- cut from the same cloth as Bennet.
- This doesn't have to end badly.
You can turn yourself in,
release Bennet and his daughter.
- Why would I do that?
- You love your family,
and you don't want them to get hurt,
and they will get hurt.
You people are always
so sure of yourselves.
I know what's best
for my own family.
- And what is that?
- Change.
We're strong enough
to show ourselves, take what's ours.
You don't have the right
to take anything.
Of course we do.
We deserve admiration, respect.
And you intend
to hurt people to get it?
What would you have me do?
Continue with this life?
Live in a carnival?
Why not? You've lived here
happily for years.
Wasted years, unfulfilled years.
I could've been so much more.
You know about me?
About the film?
Do you know how powerful
I can really be...
if I brought them all here?
My brother said
I could move mountains, cities.
I wonder. Is it true?
Can I change the world?
I hope to God we never find out.
What did the world ever do to you?
Should've treated me better.
Don't do this, please.
The Bennet girl left
the house of mirrors.
Well, I'll just have
to have a word with her.
It's time to gather the family.
Tell them to pack up.
We're moving on to biggerthings.
Tell them it's gonna be
the greatest show we've ever done.
You've been quite helpful, Lauren.
You and your friends
take care of her, would you? Thanks.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna end this.
I can't bring Nathan back, Peter.
But I can sure as hell
swing a sledgehammer.
I'm sorry to put you through that.
I hope through this painful experience
you can finally see the truth.
You were right, Samuel.
My dad is a bad guy.
I belong with you.
You're my hero.
That's what you want to hear,
what this is all about.
Why didn't you show me the memory
my dad has of shooting Lydia?
That wasn't on the program?
Maybe he didn't pull the trigger
last night.
But does that negate
all the times that he has?
To this day, he lies to you,
deceives you, his darling daughter,
because he can't trust any of us.
You actually thought
that I would turn on him?
You just don't understand, do you?
Maybe it was
'cause no one ever really loved you.
You call these people your family,
but they're not.
They fear you.
Give me my dad, and we're leaving.
No, sorry.
You're too important.
Especially
when everything's ready to change.
What's going on?
Where's everyone going?
I was talking to a new friend
about who I am, what I can be.
The way she looked at me,
She was so afraid.
I want to see that look again
a thousand times over.
Meaning what?
It's time for our biggest show ever.
No more hiding in the shadows.
It's time to show ourselves, be strong.
We're going to New York City,
bring the whole place to Central Park.
We'll show them how powerful we are.
You can't do that.
Some lives will unfortunately be lost,
but they'll fear us, respect us.
- It's what we've always wanted.
- I have never wanted that.
You will inherit this new world.
It's your legacy.
You will remind them what I've done
long after I've gone.
That's why
you must be a part of our family.
You are desperate.
And you're small.
I will never be
a part of your family.
You sound just like your father.
I had so hoped to convince you.
In time, you can change your mind.
Don't hold your breath.
Right.
Your father's
in the souvenir trailer.
I had a little trouble
with the government lady,
playing some cat and mouse,
but the mouse got away.
- Do you want me to go find her?
- Not worth it.
- Everything okay?
- It will be.
Claire Bennet needs some time
to think about my offer.
I'll give her that opportunity.
I want to explain what you saw.
We'll talk about it later.
What is that?
Now I'm ready to go.
- New York City.
- Sounds fun.
It will be.
I'm afraid
you'll have to join us later.
There's loose ends to attend to.
Before Lydia died,
she spoke of people
who want to interfere
with our plans.
I'll need you to stop them,
permanently.
Happy birthday.
It's not my birthday.
I know.
You just wore out your other copy...
and I saw that one, digging around.
I appreciate you...
being patient with me,
keeping me sane.
That's very kind of you.
Thank you.
You want to know something weird?
Every time you pick that thing up,
I think you'll hit me really hard.
That is weird,
every time I pick it up,
I feel like I'll hit you too.
- Really hard.
- Why?
Because you are who you are.
I wish I could accept your apologies,
but if I forgive you,
I'm not doing right by him.
If you let go of your anger,
you're afraid you'll lose him forever?
So you've held on to it
this entire time?
I feel it slipping away, but...
then I look at you,
and I see you killing him.
You took my brother away from me.
We've been here
for I don't know how many years.
Together.
I've changed. I've repented.
I'll never hurt anyone ever again.
And all this time,
you were afraid to let me out.
I'm not that guy anymore.
You know that.
I know.
I know you're not.
How long has it been, really?
Half a day, maybe.
It feels like
we were in there for years.
Does that make it any less real?
Let's save Emma.
Sorry to break up the love fest,
but I'll make sure that doesn't happen.
No signal.
- You all right?
- Yeah, you?
Here, help me get these ropes off.
Is that a lantern over there?
- We're buried.
- How far down do you think we are?
I don't know.
It felt like we dropped
40 or 50 feet.
Can anybody hear us?
Help!