Previously on Heroes...
- What happened to your parents?
- I touched them, they died.
I know about your power,
and I know you're not a killer,
you're a healer.
You're staying here?
How long?
Until I know you're all right.
I'm Becky Taylor.
Open rush starts today at the house.
What don't you come by?
I'm missing bid night, uncle Samuel.
Checking on your work
with Claire Bennet.
You're doing everything
to isolate her,
push other people away,
push her in our direction?
I remember flying.
I flew jets in the military, maybe.
- What name pops into your head?
- Call me Nathan.
I have a crush.
Please accept this bid
to join the Psi Alpha Chi sisterhood.
You need to undo what you did.
Give me back my body
and I will be happy...
You're a killer, I'm a cop.
If I have to keep you trapped inside
for the rest of my life,
so be it.
That was amazing.
You are amazing.
Forbidden fruit.
My favorite kind.
Subtitles: Rebel (1.0)
www.sous-titres.eu
Sheriff?
- You can't do this.
- Is that right?
You say you're a family friend.
Now, you're a lawyer?
- Jeremy lost his parents.
- My point, exactly.
You saw the broken heater.
You can't lock him up like a killer.
- You know this was and accident.
- What I know...
is that two people are dead.
And that boy...
Let's just say...
it's not the first time
he's made some trouble in my town.
- He's building up quite the rap sheet.
- Are you pressing charges?
That kid ain't going anywhere
until I finish my investigation.
And if and when that happens,
I'm not releasing him
to anyone who's not the next of kin.
And that is not you,
friend.
You have yourself
a nice evening now.
It's me.
I need your help.
I can get a latte here
no problem, right?
I saw a cow about a mile back.
Get some espresso, we're in business.
Thanks for coming.
I didn't know if you'd show.
- Who is your fallback?
- Don't have one.
Then I'm honored.
So, you found a kid with abilities?
I thought you were done
with the bag-and-tag business.
This is more of a rescue mission.
His name's Jeremy, 17 years old.
He has...
a dual ability.
Life and death.
He got into an argument
with his parents, and...
- He killed them?
- An accident.
His emotions got the better of him.
We all know that can happen.
Is that why you called me?
Not entirely.
They won't release him,
I'm not family, but it turns out...
that the kid is very fond...
of his ant Tracy.
Just go in,
talk to him, sign him out.
- I don't know.
- He's got nobody.
You've been there.
You awake?
- You?
- Yep.
You're afraid I'm gonna kiss-attack you
in your sleep?
Maybe.
We should talk about this.
Yeah, I guess we should.
It was stupid and impulsive and bad.
It wasn't bad.
I mean,
you're a good kisser.
I just...
I don't want to mess this up.
Mess what up?
My new totally ordinary life.
You know, the one I'm still chasing?
You're the first real friend
I've had since I left Texas, and...
that's a big deal for me.
And I really like you a lot.
Just... not in that way?
Jeez, Claire.
You don't have to go all Buffy on us.
We're just kidnapping you.
I am so sorry.
Do you want to be
an Alpha Chi or not?
Is that a trick question?
- Where are you taking us?
- Well, if I told you,
that wouldn't be a very good
kidnapping, would it?
Cannot believe that they shoved
us in the trunk.
So lame.
Look at us.
All tied up in the dark.
You know, they have entire
websites devoted to this.
Sorry.
So, you were saying
how you didn't really
like me that way?
You were saying that.
I was saying that you've been
a great friend.
So, which way is it?
I don't know.
What does that mean?
It means I don't know.
Awesome.
Good morning.
Welcome to hell week.
All right, ladies, listen up.
This is what we call
a screaming scavenger hunt.
There's a big Alpha Chi treasure
close by.
Whichever team finds it first
gets to sit out hell week.
Trust me, you want to sit out.
We've got goldfish.
Good luck!
But remember, ladies,
someone's got to win
and someone's got to lose.
Oh, my God!
Where are we?
Thank you.
My name's Tracy.
I'm a friend of Mr. Bennet's.
How'd you get in here?
We told them that I was your aunt.
My aunt?
I don't have an aunt.
You do now.
Mr. Bennet fixed some paperwork
and here I am.
Mr. Bennet said that
everything would go away...
That the cops would buy the story.
Mr. Bennet...
said they'd let me go.
All I have to do is sign you out.
That might not be such a good idea.
Why not?
I killed my parents.
I'm a murderer.
You can't control me.
You've never been able to do that.
I had a compelling reason.
Let's face it.
- Your wife is kind of hot.
- Enough!
That is the second Parkman
I made scream today.
If you want, I can give you
some pointers later.
Crazy psycho!
What are you gonna do?
Hit me?
Defend your lady's honor?
We both know it's not about that.
It's about all those other
things I can do to her...
And Matty, next time
I take over your body.
That's when the real fun begins.
Cozy.
Oh, my God.
Do you smell that?
It smells like something died in here.
- What is this place?
- Oh, my God.
Slaughterhouse.
Oh, my...
Please, don't say that again.
Hey, guys?
Super-cute puzzle over here.
"What you find
will help you survive."
"When we were found
will keep you alive."
"When we were found"?
Okay, let's just open one,
so we can get out of here.
Wait!
Oh, my God.
Relax. It's not real.
They're just trying to scare us.
Open 24.
How do you know?
"When we were found," 1924.
That's when the sorority was founded.
You know that?
My mom's a former sister.
Remember?
Thank God.
I am so thirsty.
One bottle per team.
No problem.
Come on, Ash.
They won the first round.
Now we are going to bring it.
Can I just stay here?
What happened with your parents...
I understand.
All you did was touch them.
The day that I discovered
my ability,
I killed a man.
He was threatening me.
I grabbed him and...
something took over.
Something inside of me.
And no matter how hard I tried...
You couldn't let go.
Your emotions took over.
You got mad.
For most people,
that's not a bad thing.
We're not most people.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
His next of kin is here.
What reason do you still have?
Well, we got plenty.
Is this Jeremy's?
Gil, show him what we found.
"I feel the darkness surrounding me.
"I am the bringer of death."
He's 17 years old.
The songs in his iPod sound like that.
I should read you the part
about killing animals.
Any kid at school will tell you
he does it, for fun.
So now we're taking gossip
as evidence, is that it?
There's something wrong
with that boy.
Far as I'm concerned,
this proves it.
He ain't getting away
with killing his family.
He's staying right here.
No, they still haven't charged him.
Their evidence
is circumstantial at best.
Yes, right now.
I'm calling in a favor, Denis.
Thank you.
All right, I'll see you then.
Sounds like you're shaking
things up in there.
From the looks of the place,
they could use it.
- Is that right?
- Tell me something.
How's a girl like you end up
in a place like this?
- You have to do better than that.
- The name is Samuel.
I'm here to ask you one question.
If you're here to save young
Jeremy's life,
then what's next?
You gonna take him
to a place just to live?
Or where he belongs?
- What did you do?
- It's all right.
- Stay back.
- I'm a friend, Tracy.
- How do you know my name?
- It's all right. You're safe here.
I'm like you.
We're all like you.
Where is this?
Home.
Slaughter floor or operation center?
Should I even ask?
Have a nice hell week.
After you.
- So, how long have you known?
- Known what?
That I really don't want
to be in this sorority?
That you like girls.
You make it sound
like I have to declare,
like, it's my major or something.
I'm actually jealous.
First year of college
and you've already figured yourself out.
I don't know about that.
Truth is I've had
more boyfriends than girlfriends.
Really?
How many more?
Six or seven.
That's not a lot, right?
Sounds about right.
You're not...
No, you couldn't be.
You were a cheerleader.
Not what?
A virgin?
We could not be more different.
Maybe we're strange attractors.
- Strange attractors?
- It's a physics thing.
Everything in the universe
has a magnetic charge.
So strange attractors are particles
that end up together
that don't belong together,
but together, they're super-powerful.
Sort of like we could be?
Or not.
What?
Hold on.
Come on.
Don't tell me you're freaked out now.
I mean, look.
See?
Nothing.
Just more lameness.
What the hell was that?
I'm starting to think
this isn't a game.
This is the life Jeremy could have.
What?
Working at a carnival?
Surrounded by family.
His true family.
Do you remember the first time
you experienced your gift?
"Gift" might be a little generous.
Like the entire universe
coursing through you all at once.
That wasn't just your ability,
Tracy.
You were tapping into something
greater than yourself.
We're all connected.
- I'd like to believe that.
- Believe it.
Every time someone
joins this family,
I get a feeling in here.
It's an energy, I guess.
It gets stronger every day.
This is where Jeremy should be.
What, living in trailers,
drifting from town to town?
What would you do?
Give him a false name? A false life?
This is a boy who can work miracles.
Why should he be invisible?
Bring him home!
You could join him.
I know you've been lost too.
It's your nature.
That's enough.
Just take me back now.
Fair enough.
Look, I'm never out the hard sell,
but please take this
to find your way back here.
This is Lydia.
She'll take you from here.
I know her. I helped her.
She came to me when she was sad.
I held her in my arms.
We were flying.
We've talked about this.
Those memories are not yours.
Then whose are they?
And if the real me isn't in here...
Where am I?
Matt, what are you doing?
I have to leave.
It's not safe for you and Matty.
Why?
Because...
Someone else can control me.
- My body.
- Someone else?
Why do you always do this?
Come on.
We're getting close.
We're going on 15 years
and you blow everything up again?
Look, I did a terrible thing.
- This should be good.
- I used my ability
to push one man's memories
into another man's head.
Yeah, my head.
There is somebody
using my body without my permission.
- I didn't know you could do that.
- It was wrong. I know that.
But I had to do it to get rid
of this really bad criminal.
- That's not very nice...
- Or at least just his mind.
And now his consciousness
is rattling around up in here.
- There's so much space.
- Shut up!
Look.
I can get rid of him.
- The answer's out there. I'll find it.
- Good luck.
- I need you to trust me, okay?
- I'm gonna give you guys a moment.
- You trust me, right?
- Do your thing.
You said it yourself.
Fifteen years are worth something.
I can fix this.
You need a place to work things out.
You should stay here.
I insist.
It's safer for you here.
I'll take Matty
and we'll go and stay with...
Don't!
Don't tell me.
I don't want him to hear.
All right.
- I love you.
- That's good.
That was pretty smart even for you,
not letting her tell me
where she's gonna be.
But you still haven't figured out
how to get rid of me, genius.
Mohinder.
I have no idea where you are.
Will you do me a favor?
Call me back, okay?
When you get this, just call me.
Mohinder?
How's he gonna help?
He's probably working
on his father's research.
Why don't you try your old lady?
See if she picks up.
Forget it.
It is time to give me back my body
and just...
Accept it.
I'm... gaining ground and I...
I can...
make you do whatever...
- I want.
- Yeah?
This is hurting you a little bit?
You wish.
You know, you're right.
I mean, you slept with my wife.
You can control me
at any time, right?
All right.
Control me.
Stop me from drinking this beer.
Come on.
Come on!
Stop me!
Why don't we see...
how you do...
Against the heavy artillery.
Wait.
I think I've finally
found a leash for this dog.
There you are.
Your guy came through.
- He made all the arrangements.
- That's great.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Let's just get him out of here.
Thanks.
Jeremy, they're letting you go.
But who am I gonna live with?
You'll be a few doors down from me
in my apartment building in D.C.
I've set up a new identity for you.
Your name is Jarod Mitchell
and you attend
Georgetown high school.
So nobody will know what I can do?
You'll learn to control
your ability with Tracy's help.
But you're gonna keep it to yourself.
It's the only way.
What if something happens?
Nothing's going to happen.
You'll be safe.
You'll be invisible.
What, you think a sorority
brought us out here to kill us?
That's ridiculous.
It's just a game.
It didn't just move itself.
There was no one else there.
How else would you explain it?
- In my world, there's a million ways.
- Name one.
Telekinesis.
I've seen it.
Heck, I know someone who has it.
So wait, you're saying
there's another one of you here?
It's very possible.
And what?
They're playing a college prank on you?
Not a prank.
You think that they're
trying to kill you?
Not me.
Then who?
Me?
Come on.
Think about it.
My first roommate committed suicide
with a mysterious note that
wasn't there, but then it was.
Maybe you almost
getting gutted wasn't a coincidence.
Claire, that is a little out there.
Sounds like some crazy-ass
conspiracy theory.
Which pretty much describes
your entire life.
What was that?
I don't know.
Ash, cut it out.
Come on.
You guys all right?
- You find another clue?
- Like I'm gonna tell you.
Look, your roommate's freaked out
and we don't care about the treasure.
Let's stick together,
get the hell out of here,
and once we find it,
you can have it. Deal?
- Okay, can we just go?
- Deal.
Lead the way.
Take my car.
Straight ahead.
We know what happened
to your parents!
We know what you did!
We know what you did.
You're getting away
with murder, you...
Don't hurt him!
Jeremy, stop.
Let him go.
Get the hell away from him!
Jeremy, you can save him!
- Everyone back! Back!
- Listen to me.
- You can help him. You can save him.
- Everybody stand back!
Now listen, son.
You're going back in there.
You know what you did
to your mama and your daddy.
Save him.
You can do it.
You have no idea
what's happening here.
Three people are dead.
I understand that.
And that boy, whatever he is,
is responsible!
Do you want it to happen again?
Let me talk to him.
Talk to him?
You're through talking to him.
Both of you.
You think killers go free?
Not in this town.
Gil, where's the boy?
Gil, do you read?
The boy is gone.
Gil, do you read me?
Are you there?
Not so tough now, are you?
Go ahead.
Take your best shot.
Give me a reason.
You're not normal.
You don't belong here.
Go.
You like that?
You know what this is?
I bought this...
with Janice,
on our anniversary trip to Ensenada.
And it is so poetic
that I am using it to bury you.
Bury me or drown the truth?
The truth, what?
That you...
you're nothing?
You're just a figment of my imagination.
Let's quiet those voices, shall we?
Your wife walked out on you.
You think she wanted
to give you your space.
She can't stand the sight of you.
Pathetic.
You know what she said to me,
in front of the fire last night?
"Why can't you be more
like this all the time?"
When you're gone...
Janice and I are gonna have
a beautiful life together.
You're so desperate
to fit in.
Why can't you accept your power?
Why do you insist
on being... so forgettable?
Man.
You're afraid.
You're afraid of dying.
And you just passed out.
You just passed out.
Yes!
Honey, I did it.
I really did it.
"Kill house."
"Prep room."
"Kill house" sounds more dangerous.
We're taking that one.
I thought we were gonna
stick together.
No way.
Let's just check this real quick.
We'll catch up to them.
Well, we won.
Kind of.
I'm gonna go get Paris and Nicole.
- I get it, by the way.
- You get what?
You wanting to run
from your freaky world
and live a normal life.
I shouldn't have put you on the spot
and gotten all relationship-y on you.
- The last thing you need right now...
- I need you.
Trust me.
What?
What's going on?
Oh, my God!
Claire!
Oh...
My...
God!
Becky?
Grab her!
A little help, please?
Oh, my God.
Don't do it!
Stop!
No, stop!
- What the...
- What?
How did you...
What's happening?
What are we gonna do?
We could have saved him.
He needed a home.
A real home.
Tracy, I'm sorry.
You know,
this was supposed to be simple.
Just go in and sign him out.
I thought I could manage.
By hiding him away
for the rest of his life?
I stood on his porch and I told him
that I wouldn't let him down.
But you did.
We did.
I did what I thought was right.
And I was wrong.
I've been wrong all these years.
Do we have to be invisible?
You ever think we could just live,
Noah?
Out in the open?
Not after today, no.
Don't ever call me again.
You gave us quite
a scare there, brother.
I know.
I'm sorry. I just...
I had to see if...
If I could...
I'm much better now.
Not quite.
We start over...
from the beginning.
You hear me?
Thanks.
Both of you.
I love you.
You'll love me a lot more
after I take a shower.
Let me guess.
You want your body back?
Did you think
you were actually winning?
The second you blacked out,
I slipped right in.
Now I'm in the driver's seat.
You'll never get away with this.
I already have.