Previously on heroes...
You had to go and be the detective,
Didn't you, matt?
Now that you know, you can't be here.
No!
This girl found me,
Said I should go to this company, pinehearst.
There's a chance
That these people at pinehearst can help us.
You don't have your powers anymore, peter.
Because I have them now.
I'm sorry, peter. this is something I have to do.
You help him, you're proving
All the worst things I've ever said about you.
Just kick his ass, and let's get out of here.
I'm not going anywhere, peter.
You are.
You can't heal.
How did you fall that far and not die?
Now that they think we're dead,
We have time to get away.
No. I told you. I'm not running.
There's a company, primatech--
They know how to deal with situations like this.
If anybody can help, they can.
It worked.
He thinks I'm on his side.
Hello, angela.
You can see the future.
I can't have that.
That's too dangerous.
Dad's dead.
He's not. he's alive.
I need to know where he is.
Pinehearst.
Pinehearst, the biotech firm?
How do you know about pinehearst?
I've been taking a consultant fee from them
For over a year.
I can open doors.
I don't need any doors opened.
I plan on kicking 'em down.
I'm ready to begin my spirit walk.
I understand you've been dreaming about me.
When the moon passes
Between the sun and the earth,
A strange fascination
Takes root in the heart.
And suddenly, anything is possible.
Its power is undeniable.
Its beauty mesmerizing.
Its lure biblical.
Its meaning unknowable.
And as quickly as it comes,It disappears,
Leaving us to dwell on our own insignificance
In the face of god.
I understand you've been dreaming about me.
I can't have that.
That's too dangerous.
I will completely wipe out your memory.
Hiro!
Leave my friend alone!
You had one job to do,
And now I have to come clean up your mess.
That's what I get for sending a boy to do a man's job.
Still hard to believe peter survived that fall
Without his powers.
Yeah, I was just thinking that myself.
Come. I have something to show you.
Where are you taking me?
It's time I started acting like your father, gabriel.
That hunger you've got, it's not about killing,
It's about power.
You can take all the abilities you want
Without killing.
I can teach you.
How?
By accessing your empathy,
That part of your heart I know is there.
You've had this power all along.
Empathy.
What makes you think I'm capable of that?
Because I know you're the one
That saved peter from that fall.
You.
-We have to get out of here. -I know.
But you're not coming with me.
What?
I'm gonna go someplace where they can't find me.
And you're gonna go home.
Peter, I have to protect you.
I can protect myself, claire.
How? you don't have your powers.
Your father's trying to kill you.
Look, this isn't your fight.
I need you to stay...
Stay what?
Innocent.
Fire escape. run!
-I'll hold 'em off. -claire.
I have a plan. go.
You're never gonna find him.
Aw, that's cute. she's protecting him.
Don't you know?
I'm the defensive player of the year.
Come on!
Told you I had a plan.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
They're coming. come on.
We should keep moving.
Any luck yet?
If you call this luck?
What went wrong?
I don't know.
I'm beginning to think it's impossible
To give people abilities without an adverse reaction.
He's a human being for god's sakes.
I see we share a fascination.
It seems most of the powers I've documented
Took place during the last total-annular eclipse.
It's probably just a coincidence.
I thought I had successfully combined my findings
With yours.
I mean, theoretically, this formula is sound,
But the serum is triggering a mutation
Because something is missing.
Something?
Some kind of catalyst that allows the proteins
From the serum to bond with the enzymes
Produced by each individual's adrenals.
Then you'll just have to keep looking.
It's not that simple.
The key component of this catalyst would be something
That couldn't be stored or created synthetically.
Meaning what?
Meaning it would live in a human host.
You're saying this catalyst isn't something.
It's someone.
Kaito.
I'm sorry?
My former colleague, kaito nakamura.
He hid it.
Just not well enough.
I will kill you, you son of a bitch.
You murdered my father!
Yes, I did.
How could you do that to me?
I'm not gonna insult you by saying I'm sorry.
You deserve so much more than that, elle.
You deserve vengeance.
I'll take whatever you've got.
I thought you said
there were people who could help us here.
There were.
Where'd they all go?
It's like a ghost town.
Who is that?
Her name is, uh, angela petrelli.
Petrelli.
-What's wrong with her? -I don't know.
Mrs. petrelli.
What is it? what did you see?
I gotta help her.
I better get a nurse.
Didn't expect you so soon.
Matt parkman's at primatech.
He's trying to help your wife.
Did you do that to her?
Mrs. petrelli will be fine.
Can we leave matt out of this?
You know, if you're unhappy,
I can always arrange for you
To go back to your previous life.
Just tell me what I'm supposed to do.
Stay with parkman.
And if he tries to help your wife?
Then I'll be waiting.
Okay, we'll go and then we'll separate.
Separate?
I told you. you have to go home.
I'm not going home, peter.
You still have a chance, claire.
I left home so I could fight these people,
And I have.
I can protect myself now.
I can protect you.
That's the problem.
What's this all about?
Look, that alley back there,
That's where you kill me.
What?
In the future, you find me,
And you shoot me.
Twice. right in the chest.
What are you talking about? why would I do that?
Because what you're becoming is a killer.
And I'm trying really hard to make sure
That future that I saw does not come true.
And I don't know if I can do it.
Because everything that happens,
Everything, you're still becoming this woman who--
Who what?
Who kills you?
Stop saying that.
Claire, just go home.
Please.
No.
It's not gonna happen.
And it's all your fault.
You should have never come to odessa to save me.
You should have never become my friend or my hero.
And now I can't leave you
Because I have a favor to return.
Run.
Go.
You want him, you're gonna have to go through me.
You can't fight it, claire.
How do you know my name?
Oh, 'cause we didn't come for peter.
We came for you.
No!
Get off of me!
No! let me go!
superhero?
I couldn't find anyone.
There's no one here.
I gotta try and get inside her head.
See if I can unlock what's holding her.
Is that safe?
Can you get hurt?
I've only done it one other time.
With my dad.
How'd that work out?
What do you need me to do?
Just stay here and keep an eye on me, okay?
I might disappear for a while.
In there.
But I'll be back. I'll be okay.
Just knowing that you're here's gonna help.
Matt?
Can you hear me?
Murderer!
I didn't want to kill him.
I didn't want to kill any of them.
You know that.
You saved my life. remember, elle?
You know the pain I feel over this.
The urge. but I'm not gonna let it control me.
Not anymore.
I'll kill you, I swear to god!
I'll kill you, I swear to god! I will kill you!
I understand.
You need to let it out.
The anger.
The betrayal.
You can take it out on me.
I can take it all.
Go ahead.
Kill me.
Please.
There was a wide spot up in the road.
In the berkshires.
My father used to take my brother and me fishing there
When we were kids.
It was called pinehearst.
Nathan, are you sure
You want to do this?
If he's alive,
Maybe there's a reason he hasn't contacted you.
I need to know the truth.
Everything I've ever done in my life
Has been because of my father.
I went to law school to be like him.
I married the girl he wanted me to.
I ran for office
Because he couldn't.
If he's alive, I've gotta see him.
My god.
Good to see you too,
Nathan.
Come give your dad a hug.
You must be miss strauss.
I must be.
You have any idea
What you've done to this family?
What you've done to me?
Hindsight being 20/20, I should have told you sooner
What your role was in all of this.
My role?
Would you excuse us, please?
My son and I need to talk alone.
Absolutely.
Take a hard look at the last couple of weeks
Of your life, and you will see that role
Coming into focus.
The assassination, linderman,
The senate seat.
All part of your destiny.
That was all you.
You were born with a talent, nathan.
A talent to lead a nation.
This is the same crap linderman spouted.
I'm not falling for it again.
Because...last time, it was new york
That was destroyed, and this time,
It would be the world, right?
Look around you.
It's already happening.
And I've got the formula that will stop it.
You're insane.
I am not afraid to admit
That you have always been my favorite son,
The one most like me.
The strong one.
We can save the world together.
This can be our legacy, nathan,
For the petrelli name.
I am offering you this chance.
As your father.
Kill me.
Take my power. that's what you want.
Kill me, and make the pain stop.
I wanna make it stop, elle.
But I'm not gonna kill you.
Please just do it.
I'm sorry.
I wanna be a good person.
You're a monster.
Like me.
No, your father made you this way,
Just like my mother made me.
We we never good enough for them, elle.
You never meant to be this way.
You wanted to be normal.
You just didn't know how.
You saved my life once, elle.
You gave me the will to live.
Don't you see I owe you?
I only saved you so we could use you.
Like a lab rat.
You were just following orders.
But I forgive you.
Now you need to forgive yourself.
The pain.
It's gone.
Oh, my god.
Let me go! no!
You've got two choices.
Let her go, or you die.
You and what army?
Peter, what are you doing?
I don't need an army to kick your ass, flint.
I can do that all by myself.
Don't even need my powers.
Stop!
Gas.
Claire, run!
No one's ever done anything like that for me before.
You forgave yourself, elle.
We're all at war with ourselves.
That's what it means to be human.
The trick is figuring out how to be on the winning side.
You wanna try?
Clearly, I don't have it figured out yet.
Let me show you a few tricks.
You aim.
Then go like this.
That's good.
This time, loosen up.
You know? give it some attitude.
Some english.
That's really good.
Keep it up, you'll be a gunslinger in no time.
Thank you.
It's amazing.
Hiro!
He wants to give half the planet superpowers,
So that we can save the world together with me as president.
And you believed him?
I don't know what to believe.
Nothing makes any sense.
I thought the man was dead.
I don't even know what to do with my life
Now that he's alive.
Hold on a minute.
You are a u.s. senator.
You've got an entire constituency riding on you
Having a clear vision of what you believe in.
Good luck with that.
No, you need to listen to me.
You gotta snap the hell out of this.
You have to get yourself together.
Do you understand?
We should go back to washington.
We'll get the justice department involved-- no.
Let's keep the lid on it.
But people have to know.
No.
Last time I tried to tell anybody anything like this,
My brother came back from the future and shot me.
Twice.
I'm gonna go to primatech,
See what else my mother knows.
You go to washington.
Cover for me.
I'll be back in touch when I know
What our next move is, okay?
Let me guess.
You want me to take away your power.
No.
I'm actually getting used to it.
I'm here because I think
That you and I can help each other.
Can we now?
And all I ask on my end
Is that you look out for me once the dust settles.
See...
I believe that you have a p.r. problem.
I pride myself on knowing how the tides turn.
I know how the world works,
And for your plan to succeed,
You need a public face.
Now, normally, that would be you.
Problem is, the world thinks you're dead.
A thorny issue,
I admit.
But I think nathan can be that face.
The bad news, he's on the fence.
The good news...
I can push him over.
You scratch my back,
And I will make sure he lands on the right side.
Matt?
Can you hear me?
Angela!
You okay?
I'm here to help you. I'm gonna get you out of here.
You shouldn't have come.
He's too dangerous.
Don't you understand?
There's no escape.
Even if you get them off,
Arthur's locked all of the doors.
These doors are open. I can get us out of here.
Daphne.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to help you, matt.
Aah! daphne, don't!
No.
Matt.
No. no.
You gotta come back.
Daphne, don't.
Matt.
Matt, wake up!
Matt, you've got to wake up! wake up, matt!
Matt, matt, wake up. bring me in there.
Matt, you have to take me in there.
Matt, we gotta go. matt.
Get away from me.
I came to help you.
Ugh, you stabbed me.
That wasn't me. don't believe her, matt.
Take it from me.
A woman will betray you at every turn.
You're lying.
Really? how do you think I knew where you were?
She told me.
She betrayed you, matt.
Like angela betrayed me.
You told him?
I was afraid.
I thought I had to. he said he'd take it all away from me.
What are you talking about?
I can't go back to being the way that I was, matt,
But I couldn't let you die either.
I'm sorry. I just--i didn't know.
Didn't know what?
How much I cared about you.
Matt, you're bleeding.
I don't know how arthur's doing it,
But you've got to wake up, or you're going to die.
You can't trust her, matt. she lies.
They all lie.
Send her away.
No. no, don't. matt, please.
I made a mistake.
I trusted the wrong people, but I can't lose you.
I love you.
We were once like that, arthur.
Remember?
You loved me.
And there's a part of you that still does.
So now you're going
To let me go.
You understand?
I said, let me go, arthur.
We gotta go, fast.
We did it.
You were there.
Was that really you?
Yeah, you brought me in.
And those things that you said--
Yeah, that was me too, and I meant every word of it.
Detective parkman.
Are you okay?
I'm gonna get a doctor.
Parkman?
Peter.
She can't be trusted.
You're the one who can't be trusted.
You shot your own brother,
And then you sent me out in the middle of nowhere!
It wasn't me. it wasn't me.
Matt, you gotta believe me. I'm telling the truth.
Where's angela?
She's awake.
Test subject was injected with batch 38
At 0634 hours.
Heart rate rose to 164 beats per minute.
Sustained at that level for two hours.
I am so sorry.
Please kill me. please.
Mom. thank god you're okay.
Your father. he's alive.
I know.
I talked to him today.
He's got the formula.
Both halves.
They were supposed to be hidden away forever,
But someone's stolen them
Right out from underneath us.
Now peter and I have both seen the future,
And trust me, it's not one that any of you want to face.
Make that three of us.
And she's right.
Arthur's probably figured out by now
That there's a third piece of the formula.
It won't work without it.
What kind of piece?
It's a catalyst.
Hidden away in the blood of a human host.
Kaito nakamura was the only one who knew the identity
Of the host, and kaito, as we know, is dead.
So how do we find the host?
We don't have to.
We just have to make sure that he doesn't.
When sylar attacked me, he saw something.
He took off the top of my head.
He said I was different from everyone else.
Special.
I didn't understand what that meant until today.
I think I'm the catalyst.
It starts with light
And ends with light.
And in between, there is darkness.
Nothing there is beyond hope.
Nothing that can be sworn impossible.
Nothing left unimagined...
Since zeus, father of the olympians,
Made night from midday...
Hiding the light of the shining sun
And raining dark fear down upon men.
It's coming.