I must have gotten
your ability on the street.
Ability?
Peter Petrelli?
Hiro.
- You're the man with a plan.
- I'm not sure I'm that guy anymore.
Well, it's just, you know,
kind of sad when you...
look back on your life,
you realize it hasn't amounted to much.
What are you talking about?
Your life is about helping people.
But I don't remember
actually helping... anybody.
The guy don't know his name,
what day it is, nothing.
I'm gonna help you.
You're a watchmaker from queens,
who murdered your own mother.
No!
What are you waiting for?
A broken vessel.
An empty shell.
What is a man without mind,
without memory?
A ghost?
A body in search of a soul?
With no compass to guide us,
how can we know if our destiny
is to seek the good...
Or obey the demons
that whisper in our ear?
The blank slate hungers
to be written upon.
The body thrives
when the heart has a mission.
How you feeling, hiro?
You collapsed in my apartment
last night.
You remember?
And you brought me to the hospital?
I spoke to the doctors.
Hiro, you're very sick.
Yes, I know.
Brain tumor.
I'm dying.
I guess I didn't want to believe
that I would end up
in a hospital bed so soon, but...
Here I am.
Look, I know about dying.
I've helped a lot of people
through this transition.
And I'm gonna help you
with whatever you need.
Maybe that's why you came to me.
Maybe.
But maybe not.
Destiny has been sending me
to different places, different times,
to right many wrongs before I die.
Maybe destiny has brought me
to you, Peter...
To fix a problem in your life.
No, my...
my life is fine.
I really don't need any fixing.
What if, you didn't come here
so that you can fix me?
What if I could fix you?
I've seen the best doctors in japan.
- There's nothing that can be done.
- Maybe not by doctors.
The faster I can go...
The faster I can get back.
Go... go where?
Just sit tight, okay?
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Did you send a cello to my apartment?
A cello? No.
Something is wrong with my ability,
or whatever you call it.
There's nothing wrong...
It's confusing, at first.
I know.
It's difficult for everyone
in the beginning.
And I want to talk about it
with you, but I can't.
- Right now I have to leave.
- Leave?
My friend is dying, and it can't wait.
You know what...
You have questions about abilities?
You should talk to him.
He knows everything about abilities.
His name is Hiro.
Talk to him, and I'll be back soon.
Where are you going?
To save his life.
He's not what you expected.
For years I've heard rumors, stories.
Sylar, the most powerful one of all.
But that man seems beaten.
Afraid.
What happened to him?
I'm not sure.
It's like there are two sides
at war within him.
Good morning, Sylar.
How'd you sleep?
You called me Sylar.
Who's Sylar?
That's you.
That's your name.
The police told me my name is Gabriel.
You don't even know your name?
What happened to you?
I don't know.
I can't remember.
You know what I think?
I think a great damage
has been done to you.
And you've come to us to heal.
Walk with me.
Spend the day among us,
and with time,
your memories will return.
What do we call you...
Gabriel?
Sylar?
Take a deep breath.
What's the first name
that pops into your head?
Call me Nathan.
Subtitles: Rebel (1.0)
www.sous-titres.eu
Why are you doing this for me?
Taking me in, hiding me.
- You don't even know me.
- Of course I do.
You may not realize it,
but you're a man of great powers.
Powers?
At the police station,
I raised my hand and somehow
threw a man across a room.
What's wrong with me?
There's nothing wrong.
You're special.
Take a look around.
Here, everyone is.
Hey, Teddy, show him what you can do.
- You mean everybody here...
- Is like you. Like us.
Lydia!
Come meet our new friend.
Show him around a bit, will you?
I think you are gonna like each other.
My pleasure.
What is it?
I remember shaking a lot of hands.
Like a I was a politician or something.
Is that possible?
I suppose anything is possible.
Come on.
Hi.
Laundry day.
Is this a bad time?
No...
come on in.
How goes job hunting?
Unproductive.
Well, hang in there.
It'll work out.
Thank you.
Can I have some quarters?
I need, like, 12 of them.
Yeah, sure.
Over there in the jar.
Help yourself.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but have you ever thought about
doing a little volunteer work?
Oh, wait...
Peter?
How did you get in the bathroom?
It's been a long time
since I've teleported.
I need you to deliver some tickets.
"Captain Lubbock, Baltimore P. D."
Isn't this the guy who was
hunting Sylar last night?
Something is very wrong.
The memories are returning,
but they're the wrong memories.
There's someone else inside his head.
We need to jump-start the real Sylar.
Wake the sleeping lion.
If the real Sylar sees
this cop coming at him,
he might kill him.
Indeed, he might.
Hiro's dying?
He doesn't have to
if I can find a healer.
That's why I came over here.
I want you to help me locate one.
What about my blood?
Can't we give him a transfusion?
That won't work.
A tumor is living tissue.
Your blood's regenerative powers
would only make it grow faster.
But there was a kid,
bag-and-tag of three
to four years ago.
How long does he have?
It could be a couple months.
Could be a couple hours.
That's him.
Jeremy Greer.
I found him when he was 13.
I was getting a report of a kid
that was bringing
- squashed bugs back to life.
- Back from the dead?
Not exactly.
But if just a leg still twitching.
All he had to do was touch them
and away they would fly.
We studied him for four days
and, of course, erased his memory.
He was a good kid.
Or he wanted to be. He couldn't decide
if his power was a gift or a curse.
Well, if he can save Hiro,
it's definitely a gift.
Cainan, Georgia.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Samuel's brother, Joseph,
began the tradition of morning chores.
He believed that hard work
helped bind a community together.
I'm certainly looking forward to getting
my hands dirty.
I haven't done
an honest day's work since...
Since I can't remember when.
It's nice having you here.
We don't see a new face
among us that often.
Especially one so handsome.
How you doing?
That Lydia...
always had a thing for bad boys.
- What do you mean?
- I've heard about you, Sylar.
How you steal powers
from other people.
How I...
I'm sorry, I have
no idea what you're talking about.
I'm sure you can do
some fancy tricks.
But you know what,
I have some tricks of my own.
Excuse me.
Those are kind of in the way.
Are you gonna stop this?
Boys will be boys.
Why don't we let the others
finish up here?
There's someone
I'd like you to meet.
It's so strange when that happens.
My hand rises up and can suddenly do
incredible things, like motor memory.
Memories don't only exist in the mind.
The body retains everything.
I remember flying.
- You mean flying in a plane.
- No, I mean, like piloting a jet.
I flew jets in the military, maybe.
A politician's life, jet pilot.
It all sounds like a very exciting life.
But it isn't yours.
Someone's done something to you.
Polluted your mind somehow.
I thought your memories would return
on their own, it's just not happening.
You want to know who you really are?
Of course I do.
Then it's time
for stronger measures. Damian.
This is Damian.
He has a powerful gift.
In his hands, your true memories
will be returned.
Are you ready to know the truth?
Take him to the house of mirrors.
Go away.
I have no more blood left.
No more blood.
Blood?
I'm sorry... I...
I read lips,
but yours move differently.
Sorry.
Japanese accent.
- I'm Emma.
- I'm Hiro.
Peter Petrelli said
I could ask you questions
about my... Abilities.
You have a power?
How can I make it stop?
No, manifesting a power
is a wondrous time.
A hero never refuses the call.
I'm deaf.
I can't hear the call.
You must have many questions.
Just one.
How do I turn it off?
It's not a light switch.
It's part of who you are.
Sorry to have bothered you.
Dead plants, dead bushes.
Not exactly what you'd expect
from a healer, huh?
- What do you know about this kid?
- Not much.
You know, I tested him.
I wrote up a report,
threw it in the file. But...
The kid was coming into his ability.
He had a lot of questions, so...
Naturally we wiped his memory,
Sent him back to his messed up family.
And I went on to my next assignment.
The company wasn't a support group.
- It's the powers, not the people.
- It's right.
But you saw him heal, right?
Yeah. Bugs.
Dog that got hit by a car.
Day four I slashed my arm pretty bad.
The kid touched it, it was good as new.
Guess his power doesn't work on birds.
- That smells like...
- Death.
Hello?
Is anybody home?
Oh... Noah. Noah.
- The parents.
- What the hell happened here?
There was a case in china.
This woman manifested as a healer,
But as time went on,
it evolved into something
very different.
There was a flip side.
She could control
the flow of life... give it...
Or take it away?
Yeah.
Jeremy?
Jeremy, is that you?
Gabriel.
- Hello, Gabriel.
- Mom?
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god, no!
No, this isn't me.
This isn't me.
Why are you doing this to me?
Make it stop, please!
Make it stop!
So tell me about your ability.
I have an ability too.
I am the master of time and space.
Well, I was.
Lately, time and space has been
the master of me.
Oh, is that my brain scan?
No. Mine.
I see sounds.
They make colors.
A new ability can be frightening.
But you must not turn away from it.
I want it to stop.
- He's not shooting to kill.
- He's just warning us to stay away.
Still, we're talking about a scared kid
with a small cannon in his hands.
- I'm going up.
- No.
I need to talk to him.
- There's a staircase out back, though.
- I'm on it.
Jeremy, I'm coming upstairs.
Unarmed.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Talk to me.
Say something.
Stay away, all right.
I'm warning you!
I'm coming upstairs,
If you're gonna shoot, lock and load.
I told you to keep away!
Why?
What happens if I don't?
Everything I touch ends up dead.
Captain Lubbock.
I'm Samuel Sullivan.
Glad your family could make it.
I appreciate you sending
those tickets over this morning.
But a gotta ask.
Why me?
We always try
and do something special
for local law enforcement.
I heard about you on the news.
Out chasing down
some escaped prisoner?
You'll indulge me.
I'm showing this to everyone I can.
- A lot of people on the hunt for him.
- Don't think I've seen him.
But I could be wrong.
A lot of folks come and go around here.
If you spot him, call me right away.
I absolutely will.
Enjoy the carnival.
Mrs. Lubbock.
Stop. Make it stop.
Please... Please.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God!
Oh, my God!
This isn't me!
Please make it stop!
No, this can't be me.
Please make it...
- What happened?
- Don't come any closer!
Okay, I'm right here.
Your parents?
I killed them.
I was angry.
I just touched them, and they died.
- I didn't mean to do it.
- I know you didn't.
You know, what's happened
to you, Jeremy, it's not fair.
You never should have been left
to suffer through this alone.
And who are you?
You don't remember me.
But we've met.
I know all about you.
I know about your power.
I know that you're not a killer.
You're a healer.
I used to heal things.
And then it turned.
And now I kill!
No, you're still a healer.
- You can do both.
- Stop.
If you come one step closer,
I swear to God I will shoot you!
Stay with me.
- Oh, my God.
- He's bleeding out.
He's never gonna make it
to the hospital.
You need to heal him.
I can't.
Yes, you can.
I've seen it with my own eyes.
You need to come over here
and lay your hands on him now!
- If I touch him, he'll die.
- He'll die if you don't.
You can do this.
Listen to me.
My power is understanding
people like you.
That's what I do.
What happened to your parents
never has to happen again.
You can control it,
and you can heal him.
Everything I touch dies.
I'm touching you right now.
You can do this.
You can give life.
Come on.
Focus, Jeremy.
Visualize Peter healing.
Imagine what it's gonna look like
when the wound disappears,
his eyes open again,
and he is healthy and alive.
Picture it, Jeremy.
Keep that thought in your mind.
Welcome back.
And now,
to assist Hiro the magnificent,
please welcome to the stage
Emma the...
also magnificent!
- Hiro, what are you doing?
- Magic.
And we are going to need
much applause
for the next feat of magicalness.
I will make Emma...
disappear!
- It's like time is...
- Standing still.
It's all so beautiful.
There are no bad powers Emma.
You just have to understand them.
And when you do,
you will learn to use your powers
to do good things in the world.
But please, for now,
our magic trick.
Hide behind the curtains.
Over there.
Where did she go?
Where is Emma?
Where are you?
There she is!
A big applause
for Emma the magnificent!
But we have to give applause
in a different way.
Like this.
All those murders...
All those memories in my mind...
But I cannot believe that they're mine.
How many did I kill?
A dozen?
Two dozen?
I'm sorry for your pain.
- Truth can be difficult.
- Difficult?
I am a monster!
I stalk people
and slash open their skulls.
Has it ever occurred to you
to question
what brought you here?
Why providence has seen fit
for our paths to cross?
This place is a safe,
protected womb.
Out there's a cruel world filled
with people who persecute our kind.
They made you what you are,
turned you into a monster.
- That makes it okay?
- It makes it the truth!
You wanted to know who you are.
And now you do.
The question now is:
Where are you gonna go from here?
Do you wallow in self-pity,
or do you learn to use the gifts
God gave you and command fear.
And respect, and defend against
those who would do us harm?
All in the embrace of a community
who loves you
for exactly who you are.
You just met me.
You would take me in here...
Knowing what I've done,
and who I am?
We're family.
Family accepts.
Family forgives.
There's a problem.
That policeman who was hunting you,
he's here.
It's not just about you anymore,
we're harboring a criminal now.
- What do you want me to do?
- I can't make that decision for you.
But your presence here
puts all of us in jeopardy.
Something has to be done.
Where is he?
One of my men saw him
going into the house of mirrors.
I don't know what to do with him.
A leash?
A cage?
Maybe a cattle prod.
Now...
You keep your Japanese tush
in this bed!
I'm not a pet.
She's right, Hiro.
You're sick.
You need to stop using your power
before it kills you.
But my power isn't killing me.
It keeps me alive.
When I was stuck in my cubicle
every day...
wasting my life,
that's when I was dying.
How can you be so focused
helping others,
knowing what it might cost?
I had a friend once.
She knew she was dying but,
that didn't push her off her path.
She told me to keep joy
and dignity alive,
even in the face of death.
Her name was Charlie.
Oh, my god.
I can't believe I left her
off the list.
What?
What are you doing?
Paper and pen, stat.
I had a list.
A list of all the wrongs
I have to right before I die.
I can't believe I forgot her.
Promise me you won't leave
until Peter returns.
There's been an accident
at 2627 Otsego.
Please send the police
and the coroner.
Did you get his ability?
So what next?
There's an air field about six miles
south of here off the highway.
I called in a favor
and I got you a ride.
It's not as fast as how you came, but...
- You're not coming with?
- No.
All right, better hurry.
Hiro's waiting.
Okay, so, I jerry-rigged the heater.
And I backed up the vent.
It's gonna look like
carbon monoxide poisoning, OK?
You came home and you found them.
All right?
You're staying here?
- Yeah.
- How long?
Till I know that you're all right.
Jeremy,
it used to be my job
to watch over people like you.
But somehow I...
I lost my way.
I dropped the ball.
You may not know it,
but I let you down.
Come on.
Hands above your head... Now.
You need to leave here, now.
While there's still time.
I got a better idea.
You resist arrest,
then I have an excuse.
I'm just trying to save you.
What are you?
Don't just stand there, get a mop!
- That was beautiful.
- You promised you would stay in bed.
Joy and dignity
in the face of death.
Just like Charlie.
Come on, back to bed.
You're safe now.
Tonight...
We welcome a new brother
into our family.
He will live
and work among us...
And will be welcome here...
all the rest of our days.
There, there, Edgar, don't pout.
Good thing I followed that bastard.
I knew he wouldn't follow through.
He's just a baby
learning how to walk.
What use is he to us like this?
What use is a lion that can't kill?
Maybe it's better this way.
We just make a better sylar.
And when we do...
He'll be ours forever.
Emma, I'm sorry it took so long.
How is he?
- Gone.
- What?
He disappeared.
Just disappeared.
"Save Charlie."