previously on heroes...
i'm not gonna
let you manipulate me.
i'm the one
making the decisions.
mr. petrelli.
you're playing yourself?
i'm obviously playing mr.-
she can't see me, nathan.
no one can.
except you.
you're different.
you're special.
my name is daphne, and why
are you two following me?
i want my father's
formula back.
there's supposed to be some sort
of exchange going down
at this theater.
and i'm waiting to intercept.
you were right.
i am just a killer.
i guess you were
wrong about me.
we'll see.
you wanna tell me
that's not you?
it's not me.
you can't run this story.
hey!
my name is tracy strauss.
do you know me?
know you?
i created you.
i came to find you.
get you outta here.
i need to show you.
the whole world is in trouble.
reflexes, blood pressure,
balance.
they're all normal.
i am completely
the same in every way.
just different.
my god.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
英雄 第三季第4集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：个人id
校对：个人id
时间轴：加饭的菜猪
this is dr. mohinder suresh,
journal entry 12.
three days after injecting
the genetic
modification formula.
my reflexes are sharper.
my strength, off the charts.
it's a dream come true.
who among us hasn't wished
for strength?
to fly?
and now it's all possible.
there are few
adverse reactions.
the one exception being
an unusual rash.
a byproduct of the formula,
an allergy-
oh, no, please don't!
stop it!
hello, is everything
all right?
i'm sorry to intrude,
but i heard shouting
and i wanted to make sure
everything was-
everything's fine.
thanks.
are you sure?
'cause it looks
like your wife-
she'll be fine.
now back off, sahib.
stop it!
stop, please.
just leave us alone,
all right?
god, don't hurt him.
you were one of three
identical triplets.
tracy, niki, and barbara.
perfect test subjects.
when your birth
parents died
we separated you.
we-
i just need some answers.
what did you do to me?
dna manipulation.
a formula that would
make you incredible.
speed, strength.
is it something like that?
why?
why would you do this?
what gave you the right?
we had no right.
we were arrogant
and selfish and...
human.
who?
who wanted this?
i think i've said
too much already.
they would not like that.
give me a name.
someone!
there was a company.
a company that-
um, i don't remember.
i can't remember.
you're lying.
they made us forget.
well, then you have
to take it away.
this... thing that i can do.
i can't.
no, you don't understand.
this ability...
i've hurt people.
it is part of you now.
no, i never asked for it.
you need to take it away.
i can't.
tell me how to take it away.
ah!
tell me.
i'm so sorry.
what have you done?
who is she?
what happened to her?
it's your future, parkman.
not mine.
yeah, it is, okay.
so that means i can stop that
from happening, right?
do you really want to know?
this stuff is supposed
to show me my future?
i don't think this is working.
here.
try this.
come on.
where are we?
when are we?
this is the future
i came back to stop.
why?
it looks just like today.
with one big difference.
how is this possible?
an injection.
abilities are available
to anyone.
for sale if you
can afford it.
for grabs if you're
desperate enough.
now all these people
with abilities
are gonna destroy the world.
how could you know that?
how would you?
i painted it.
dreamed it.
it's going to happen-
here, look.
all the crime, murder,
all abilities.
people can't be trusted.
we're weak,
jealous,
violent.
there's always
good people, always.
how could i be so naive?
when abilities are
the new weapon of choice-
people will
control themselves.
it's not safe for me
to be out in the open.
they'll be looking for us.
i needed you to see.
who are "they"?
what did you do?
they think i'm an extremist.
a villain.
i had to stop it.
maybe they're right.
you shot nathan.
you killed him.
he was gonna tell everyone
the truth about us.
but he d didn't die.
and now he
doesn't have to.
so why hasn't
everything changed?
someone from your time
is putting together a formula
that gives people abilities.
you have to stop him.
why me?
why can't you do it?
because i made
terrible choices.
stepped on
too many butterflies.
what does that mean?
you can't make
the same mistakes as me.
we need to find sylar.
with his ability,
you won't make
the same mistakes.
sylar, what the hell
are you talking about?
i wanna see nathan,
claire, suresh.
they're not the people
you think they are.
why not?
not all of us were born
with abilities, okay?
some of us were made.
a line was drawn.
sides were chosen.
it tore us apart.
well, you actually did it.
you killed peter.
no.
he's still alive.
looks plenty dead to me.
there were two of them.
this one and a younger one
from the past.
this is bad, right?
bad-bad.
yeah, we have orders.
kill petrelli.
it's obviously easier said
than done.
we need to use molly.
she can find peter
anywhere in the world.
you know i can't
just do that.
it's not that simple.
it is.
if you won't ask her,
i will.
i'm not afraid of you.
no, but you are
afraid of peter.
and you know he won't stop,
not ever.
until we find him...
and we kill him.
let me out!
i must save the world!
the future depends on it!
we have to get  out
of here,ando.
there must be
another way...
ah! the vent!
but, it's too high.
ando,come on and give me a hand.
i'm not talking to you.
what?
what did i do?
you said you
didn't need me.
you said you don't know
why you take me along!
you're so powerful.
help yourself.
i followed you
around the world.
risked my life for you because i
believed we were friends.partners.
you know what i think?
i think you're still upset that
future me murders future you.
and what if i am....?
i knew it!
i can't help it.
every time i look at you i see it
over and over again.
how could you kill me ?
i would never hurt you.
but i'm starting to
understand why i might.
senator petrelli?
senator, you need
to make your choice.
there are a lotta
historical desks available.
where's tracy?
isn't it her job
to make these decisions?
well, ms. strauss
isn't answering her cell.
take the john foster dulles.
it sends the right message.
which one
would you pick?
uh, robert kennedy's.
kennedy it is,
thank you.
you know, i thought you'd
be enjoying this.
you're a senator back
in the seat of power
where you belong.
able to do god's
work here on earth.
god's work?
i'm picking out desks.
what's the real
problem here, nathan?
you.
you're the real problem.
y- you don't trust me?
i'm hurt.
i'm the only one
who can see you.
that's a problem.
don't play me, okay?
i've been around people
who can do amazing things.
what are you?
what, are you a telepath?
no.
nothing that obvious.
you know what it is?
it's brain damage
from the shooting.
the shooting that you so
miraculously survived.
come on, nathan.
i mean, healing, flying.
i mean, isn't that
the work of angels?
you saying you're an angel?
you're a murderer.
you wanted to destroy
new york city.
kill millions
of people.
if i remember correctly,
you did too.
what exactly do
you want from me?
i want to help you.
first, a senator.
then president.
president.
the greater the fall,
the grander the ascension.
isn't that what
you've always wanted?
trust me.
this is the path
to salvation.
it's not my path.
not if you're
leading the way.
this place is disgusting.
the milk's gone bad.
didn't you notice?
look, i don't need you
cleaning up after me.
well, obviously you do.
ugh.
you don't look well.
i'm just tired.
no wonder.
working all hours.
no food, no fresh air.
i have lots to do.
come on,
let's get outta here.
i can't.
but it's a beautiful
day outside.
and you've been
cooped up in here-
working for you.
trying to find some way
to take away your ability!
isn't that
what you want?
i came because
i care about you.
you want me to go?
fine.
wait.
i- i-i didn't mean to yell.
i- i'm just tired.
i will find the answers...
for you.
i promise.
journal entry 13.
the rash is spreading.
i don't know what it is
or its connection
to my aggression.
the formula is
transforming me, and i fear...
i fear what i'm becoming.
the formula is transforming me.
the formula is transforming me,
and i fear...
i fear what i'm becoming.
mohinder?
what do you want?
i need your help.
i need you to tell me
everything you know about sylar.
sylar?
i have to find him.
he's supposed to...
help me.
but why?
why sylar?
mohinder, are you okay?
what happened to you?
what's going on?
mohinder!
do not repeat my mistakes.
what happened to you?
i wanted abilities.
impetuous.
selfish.
i got the formula wrong.
so wrong.
let me help you.
tell me about sylar.
sylar's power is dangerous.
you don't understand it.
i need to understand.
where is he?
where's sylar?
costa verde, the bennet house.
don't go!
hey, uncle peter.
dad's making waffles.
what's up, champ?
how you doing, man?
good to see you.
raa!
who wants some waffles,
huh?
who else should
get some waffles?
mr. muggles.
okay, a little piece
of waffle.
but just 'cause
you're such a good boy.
yes, you're so good.
always such a good dog.
yes, you're a very good doggy.
peter, it's so good
to see you.
i haven't seen you
in so long.
if you told me you were coming,
i would've made extra.
what's the magic word?
abracadabra.
well, that's a magic word,
so that's close enough.
where's your scar,
uncle peter?
you know what?
grown-ups need to have
a little chat in the other room.
so i'm gonna get you
started on your waffle.
all right,
there you go.
you gonna be okay?
yes.
yes, i know you are.
we're just gonna be
in the other room, all right?
you're not from
around here, are you?
no scar.
the past, right?
which means, to you,
i'm the boogeyman.
it's a hell of a thing.
you coming here to find out
that you and i
are brothers.
brothers?
oh, i'm sorry that you've come
all this way, peter,
but i can't help you.
can't?
i won't.
why?
i'm not gonna give it to you,
my ability, i'm not.
then i'll just take
what i need from you.
as if you could.
peter is dead.
they killed him.
and now they're after me.
i am not leaving
without your ability, sylar.
my name is gabriel.
and you don't realize...
my ability is not just
understanding how things work.
there's a hunger
that comes with it.
to know more,
to have more.
i couldn't control it.
it had turned me
into a killer.
a monster.
every day is a struggle.
every hour.
but i fight it...
for him.
and i am not...
going to willingly
condemn you to hell.
if i have your ability-
if i can understand
the variables, then i-
can save the world.
the world always
needs saving, peter.
you're all gonna die.
your family.
your son.
this world is gonna end.
you don't believe me?
here.
paint it.
see for yourself.
paint the future.
don't let him see me.
not like this.
do you understand?
no, no way.
no, we're not dragging
molly into this. what?
well, we're both
raising her.
yes, to be
a normal little girl.
not to be your bloodhound.
no, it's just this once.
we use her ability
to find peter.
peter petrelli is a murderer
and a terrorist and-
and he's the villain,
not me.
this is our chance
to stop peter now.
forever.
i just-i-
i don't understand
why you would risk your life
when you've got
this beautiful baby girl
waiting for you at home.
you are beautiful.
this is everything to me.
you, this family-
and this is the part where
the "but" comes in, daniella.
but i was a cop.
and i know what it's like
to have a spouse who's worried
if you're ever gonna
come home alive.
i'm gonna be fine.
nothing can touch me.
right.
you're a wife and a mother.
it's time for you
to slow down.
we find peter.
we catch him and then
you can consider me settled.
you're not gonna
let this go, are you?
and miss a chance
to stop peter
and all the pain
and misery he's caused?
we have to.
molly.
you guys done arguing?
uh, we-we weren't-
your mother needs
to talk to you for a second.
everything's gonna be fine.
peter's in costa verde.
sylar.
sylar, yeah.
you're afraid.
don't act like i don't know
what i'm talking about.
you stink of it.
so what if i am?
so claire bennet
isn't afraid of anything.
i just killed my uncle
and i have to do it again.
give me a second
to be a human being.
you see, the problem is,
claire,
unlike you,
daphne and i can die.
so get your
head on straight.
sylar?
it's a scar.
a reminder of what i was.
of what i can be.
fix it.
i don't know a thing
about watches.
if you wanna learn how
to access my ability,
fix the watch.
listen to it.
like a symphony,
every piece has its part.
all coming together
in perfect harmony.
if you can understand
the complexities of a watch,
you can understand anything.
everything.
cause, effect,
action, reaction.
how to change the future.
you have it now.
i'm so sorry.
daddy!
not now, noah.
yes, now.
noah, stay where you are,
buddy.
noah.
it's gonna be okay, buddy.
let's not make
this any harder
than it already is, peter.
just come quietly,
and we'll leave them alone.
don't do it, peter.
teleport out now.
i'm not leaving you.
i brought this
into your house.
no.
this was my house.
you took everything from me.
claire, i never meant
for you-
shut up.
what's it gonna be?
the boy or you?
you don't want anyone
to get hurt, do you?
just, first,
let the boy go.
not until you're dead.
you're gonna kill me?
one bullet in the back of
the head should do the trick.
then i'll let the boy go.
i'm not the guy that you killed
this morning, claire.
look, this is me.
you're not gonna kill me.
yes, i am.
what happened to you?
how'd you get this way?
i learned how
to take care of myself.
noah!
daddy!
go hide over there.
go now.
i understand your power.
you get stronger with fear.
i'm not afraid of you.
but he is.
noah, run!
run!
daddy!
they killed him!
gabriel!
let me try.
i've got it.
what?
you afraid i'm going to
strangle you with it?
let go.
i don't want to let go
what are you doing?
you always sucked at tug of war.
enjoy  your escape
you're not coming?
you've made it very clear you
don't want me around.
ando.
i need your help one more time.
almost there.
i can't push any harder
just two more inches.
ando
you have only ever been by my side
i don't know how i ever
doubted you. i'm a terrible
friend. i'm soryy.
maybe now is not
the time for apologizies.
you must know. i can change.
the future.and myself.
i swear it!
we did it,ando!
we did it!
ando?
metropolitan police department.
detective russick, please.
this is detective russick.
are you the detective
working the jim mccann case?
yes, i am.
i have some information...
about him.
who is this?
i-
hello?
i killed him.
damn it.
journal entry 16.
i cannot reverse the process.
cannot remove the ability.
not from maya.
not from myself.
it's a part of me now.
yes?
you stuck your nose
where it didn't belong.
so did you.
and the glory
forever and ever.
amen.
please, show me my path.
you picked the kennedy desk.
good choice.
hey.
you're back.
did you find what
you were looking for?
my resignation.
i know i dragged you
into this.
and i'm sorry.
i just can't
do this anymore.
nothing i can say
to change your mind?
no.
i know what
i have to do now.
you must pray for guidance.
this is your path.
you're just gonna
have to trust me, nathan.
you must help her.
drink?
yeah.
you okay?
no.
so, uh...
you can fly?
yeah, mm-hmm.
i can't believe
this is happening.
yeah.
i have to show you something.
your hands aren't even cold.
costa verde is gone.
the single greatest tragedy
in american history.
the first lady and i mourn
this tremendous loss.
we urge all of you
to find your families.
find your loved ones.
and that we pray
together as a family.
and as a nation.
are you trying to teleport?
that's not gonna work
with my friend here.
200,000 people
died in costa verde.
i want you
to feel the pain
of every single death.
that's one.
i can save them.
everyone in costa verde.
this whole world...
doesn't have
to be like this, claire.
you don't have
to be like this.
i saved you once,
i can save you again.
no.
that's two.
stop.
i'd like a moment
with my brother alone.
is this the president
or my father speaking?
both.
i know what you're doing.
i've seen it.
the world splitting in half.
i'm not ignorant.
i've seen the paintings.
and i've heard the dreams.
i know what's going on.
you're strong, pete.
but one man cannot
save the world.
it's everybody's
responsibility.
everybody with abilities.
yeah.
an army with abilities.
congress has agreed
to full proliferation...
because of costa verde.
because of you.
now, i know you think
people can't be trusted.
that we're all greedy.
power hungry.
but we were created
in god's image, pete.
there is a goodness to man.
pete...
you don't trust me?
you've been manipulated
before by linderman.
you were gonna blow up
new york city.
you can read minds.
read mine.
peter?
i understand...
your intentions.
your emotions.
you believe that
you're doing the right thing,
but you're wrong.
peter, stop.
it hurts.
i need-
i need to-
i need to...
understand.
i need to-
your intentions.
mr. president!
mr. president,
are you all right?
peter.
what are you doing?
i went to the future.
the world ended.
i took your ability so i could
understand how to stop it.
you took my ability?
you have the hunger.
you're like me.
i will never let myself
become you.
you already are...
this was the scene above
costa verde just hours ago.
everything
within four miles
has been completely
incinerated.
the sky is dark
with smoke and debris.
we can only imagine...
it's my fault.
i told her
to go to costa verde.
daniella needs her bottle.
come on.
but i-
go take care of your sister.
now.
...danger of radiation
poisoning.
any search for survivors
is going to take time.
but it's hard to imagine
anyone still alive in there.
the army
and national guard
are only now
beginning to assess
the extent
of the destruction.
daphne.
i wasn't fast enough.
no. no.
no, no, no, no.
come on.
come on, you'll be fine.
you're gonna be just fine.
welcome back.
what happened to me?
i was in the future.
did i time travel?
no.
you never left.
you were asleep.
dreaming.
dreaming?
no, no, no.
no, it was real.
it was.
i was there.
she was there.
everybody had abilities.
the bomb.
the baby.
it was real.
her name's daphne.
i gotta find her.
it's a big world.
lots of people.
you sent me
on this journey.
come on.
you must find your totem.
a spirit guide that attaches
to your subconscious.
it will lead you
on your journey.
what is that, some african,
mystical, mojo thing?
carl jung.
analytical psychology.
you don't read much, do you?
all right.
what is this totem supposed
to look like anyway?
usually an animal.
think about your dream...
and you'll find your guide.
where is kaito's
part of the formula?
what's so important
about this formula?
it can turn people like you
into people like us.
and that will lead to disaster.
so the formula is gone.
stolen.
there were two parts
to that formula.
they have both
and we have lost.
your father
loved you dearly, hiro.
he had faith you would grow up
to be a great man.
but he was mistaken.
and his folly will be
the downfall of us all.
i am sorry.
no, you're not.
i'm not?
don't apologize to her.
this is hiro nakamura.
he will not rest until
that formula is safe.
what he said.
someone is manipulating us.
someone powerful.
hidden.
and they must be stopped.
i will find them
and stop them.
actually,
you're the only one who can.
you have the key to unlocking
this entire mystery.
i do?
hmm?
if i knew i had the key--
i wouldn't have buried it so deep.
are you sure this is a good idea?
no. but there's no turning back now.
hiro, you son of a-
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入