Previously on Heroes
This is the last posthumous issue.
But it's not the last story.
The day that he died,
Isaac mendez bequeathed his sketchbook
To a humble bike messenger.
You find that messenger,
You find your story.
It's got nothing to do with dad.
I'm going to pinehurst.
His idea,
Giving people abilities,
The right people.
It's wrong. it's not wrong.
It's so right.
We're taking claire with us.
That's what we came for in the first place.
Well, I've read your files, gabriel.
You're not their son.
They're just leveraging your mommy issues
And turning you into their weapon.
And I understand now
That I'm never gonna change.
Theoretically this formula is sound,
But something is missing,
Some kind of catalyst.
The key component of this catalyst
Would live in a human host.
I think I'm the catalyst.
That's claire, and that's hiro hiding behind the ferns.
I think hiro has to take claire here
To get his memory back.
I must go, right now.
Hiro!
Save the cheerleader
What did you do?
What the hell is going on?
We think she died in the fire.
Dad?
Once again. Not a request.
That baby's me.
You're hiro nakamura, aren't you?
Hiro Nakamura! Yes!
Peter told me about you.
You're a time traveler,
So you brought me back in time.
Why did you bring me here?
I don't understand a word you're saying.
You don't speak english?
Less talking. More watching.
Don't get too close.
Oh, look.
Is that you?
Am I here for you?
Sorry. I only had one semester English.
All I know is...
Where is train station?
I must use toilet.
More waffles, please.
Hiro.
Mommy!
Mommy?!
My mother is here! I have to see her!
Hey, where are you going?
Should I stay with me, or should I go with you?
Hey, what am I supposed to do?
Hiro, not so rough.Your mother is ill.
It's all right.
How are you?
Our son can hear us.
Speak english.
Are you feeling better?
We must face the inevitable.
I am dying.
I think it will happen tonight.
We must make arrangements
For the catalyst
Before it is lost forever.
The catalyst.
Catalyst?
What are they saying?
I hate it when they speak English!
Are you sure?
Nothing will ever be the same.
You must think of the future, kaito.
I will have noah return with the baby.
She is the perfect candidate.
I wanted to keep it in the family.
Absolutely not.
Our son couldn't possibly.
Mommy! Look!
Yes, my Hiro...
A dove is sick.
This conversation isn't over yet.
What is it, Hiro?
Wil he die?
Let's see.
My mommy is a healer.
-I know what I have to do. -I know what we have to do!
-I think I can stop the catalyst. -I think my mommy can heal my brain!
-Before they put it in me. -Restore my memory!
-I can be a hero. -I can be a hero.
-I don't understand what you're saying. -I don't understand what you're saying.
I have to follow my dad, protect that baby,
So they don't inject the catalyst into me.
I'll meet you here tonight.
Stay out of trouble, okay?
Okay.
What are you doning here?
You should be in the kitchen.
My wife's been waiting for breakfast all morning.
Aren't you the new chef?
Hurry up, then!
She wants Tamagoyaki.
What?
You were supposed to be here by now.
Where's claire?
Gone into thin air.
What happened?
Don't know, don't care.
I'm not helping you anymore, arthur.
I'm not helping anyone.
I talked to bennet. he told me everything.
He told me you're not my father.
I want the truth.
And I know exactly where I'm gonna find it.
I've got a whole new list of people with abilities.
It's gonna be very useful.
Don't do this.
Come see me.
Don't worry, I will.
Very soon.
Good-bye, elle.
One shot to the back of his head
And it's done.
You want me to kill him?
Why do you think I sent you and your brother
To find the haitian?
He makes arthur vulnerable.
And now that nathan
Has switched his allegiance,
It's all up to you.
Your father is far too powerful.
He won't be contained.
If the tables were turned,
He would not hesitate to put a bullet in your brain,
Or nathan's.
Why do you think I poisoned him,
The man I loved,
Father of my children?
He tried to kill your brother.
And if you get in his way, he will destroy you.
You don't know that.
I know that he will stop at nothing
To get what he wants
By any means necessary, no matter who gets hurt.
There's no other way.
So d.o.d. is on board. we're all set.
Well done, tracy.
Nathan, nice to see you.
What are you doing here?
It's my job, senator--
Finding opportunities for you.
Have you reconsidered my offer, son?
I agree with what you're trying to do.
The world's a dangerous place and it's not getting any better.
We need a leader, somebody with vision.
And that somebody isn't you.
Is it you?
I'm taking over pinehurst,
The complete program.
I'll work out of my office.
We can use my resources.
Who do you think you're talking to?
I made you.
You wouldn't have gone
To all this trouble to make me
If you didn't need me.
You wanted a legitimate face for pinehurst,
A person with authority.
Senator nathan petrelli.
All right, nathan. you win.
Brief him on what we've done.
You're angry.
What do you expect?
You went behind my back.
You're supposed to be working for me.
That's exactly what I was doing.
We're on your side, nathan.
Your father sees the problems in this world--
War, terrorism.
He wants to make it a better place.
You have no idea who my father is.
I know he's crossed some lines,
But he has a vision for the future,
And you're in it as president of the united states.
That is where you belong, nathan.
And I belong there with you.
We'd like to call it "intelligent design."
Until now abilities have been random,
Given to good people and bad,
Whether they deserve them or not.
When we perfect the formula,
We get to choose who gets what power.
And we have chosen the best.
Meet the future.
Fall in!
A-ten-hut!
Okay, almost there.
Hang in there.
Oh, gosh.
Come on. hang in there.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, my gosh, let me help you.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, my husband bailed on me.
Our first day with an adopted baby,
And he had to go back to work.
Oh, my gosh, thank you. no worries.
I'm bonnie, by the way.
I'm staying next door with the monacos.
I'm their niece.
Hi, bonnie. I'm sandra.
Thank you so much. put 'em anywhere.
Thank you.
Come on, baby girl.
Here we go.
We made it home.
Nice place.
She's probably just wet
And doesn't know how to tell you yet.
Let's see.
Up we go.
There we go.
Yeah, she's definitely wet.
You want me to change her? sure.
There we go.
There we go, little one.
I'm so glad I ran into you.
To be honest, I'm a little overwhelmed.
She's so little.
And I'm completely unprepared.
I don't have a clue about how to take care of a baby.
Well, I have a feeling you'll do just fine.
Besides, I have major babysitting skills.
I could teach you a thing or two if you want.
That would be great.
What about your husband, is he good with kids?
Not really.
Noah's very busy at work.
He just got a promotion.
Apparently he is, um--
He's very good at what he does.
I'll bet he is.
All done.
There we go.
Thank you.
Oh, it's so strange.
I've only known claire a few hours,
And I'm so in love with her.
I think she knows that.
Yeah.
Don't let her out of your sight, okay?
What do you mean?
Oh, I just mean that
She's gonna grow up really fast.
Believe me, I am gonna watch her like a hawk.
Hi, baby girl.
Hey, sue, is it really your birthday?
Hey, birthday girl!
Sue landers?
Special delivery.
You're lying.
You're not here to make a delivery.
Impressive. how did you do that?
What do you want?
To understand what you do.
Human lie detector, how does that work?
When someone tells a lie, does it tingle?
How did you know about me?
Who are you?
Someone who covets your ability.
I have to find out the truth about something.
No, you don't.
Trust me.
I'm sure it's hard,
Seeing the ugly truth at every turn.
It must make it hard to trust anyone.
It's not gonna hurt a bit.
Got me.
That's a lie.
I almost forgot how good this feels.
Happy birthday!
Cake.
Tell me what you know about this program.
It's gonna make us better marines, sir.
Yeah. but how?
Not exactly sure.
Some kind of drug. I'm told it's safe.
Sergeant, I want you to know
Exactly what it is you've signed up for.
The drug that we're developing,
It'll change your life
In ways you can't possibly imagine.
Forever.
I get it, sir, but I have my reasons.
I did two tours in iraq.
In the last mission, last tour,
Rpg took out our humvee
Three klicks south of kirkut.
Boatload of hadjis has us pinned down,
And we fought as best we could.
End of the day though,
12 of us went in, only 2 came out.
That's tough.
The trip back to stateside,
I couldn't help thinking,
"why couldn't I have been better?"
You're being too hard on yourself, marine.
Everybody says that.
You're only human.
If only I was more than that,
Maybe they'd still be alive, you know?
Yeah, I think I do.
I like teleporting better.
Less windy.
I don't care where you are. hey.
It should been there an hour ago.
They're ready. get it to them.
Excuse me, we're looking for a messenger.
Sure, pal, what do you need delivered?
We need to find something, someone.
Yeah, a messenger picked up a package
From an artist at a downtown loft,
Isaac mendez.
We need that package.
Sorry, can't help you out.
Johnson, 57th and lex!
The messenger picked up this package last year.
If you just--
Wait, last year? you're kidding me.
I can barely keep track of what we delivered last week.
You have records, right? receipts.
Just look it up.
His name was isaac mendez. m-e-n-d-e--
Look, I would like to help.
City regulations prevent me from talking about deliveries.
There's no city regulation about that.
What are you, a cop?
-He knows something, matt. -right.
Sorry to do this to you, buddy.
He does know about the sketches.
Wait, how do you know that I know?
I also know that you're skimming off the top.
What, $5,200 already this year.
Give us the sketches now.
Okay, fine. I got it in the back.
It's in the safe. I'll go get it.
That's a great idea.
We found them.
Hey, you've been a good friend to hiro, nemesis.
How come?
Well, it's kinda my fault.
I mean, I started this whole mess stealing the formula--
No, no, no, it's more than that.
You're doing it because that's the right thing to do,
And that's who you are.
Guys.
He's getting away.
He's got the sketchbook. we have to stop him.
Allow me.
Hey, watch it!
Watch out!
What the--
Fine, I give.
Remember, fifth grade a boy named danny.
He's cute, but he'll break your heart,
So whatever you do
Do not share your juice with him.
Don't do it.
Don't do it, okay?
Who are you?
I'm, uh--
I'm bonnie.
I was just watching the baby
while sandra set up the nursery.
Hi, hon.
I thought I heard you come in. how's work?
You left the baby alone with some strange girl?
She's not strange.
Bonnie, this is mr. bennet.
She's a potential new babysitter for us.
Is there a problem?
You can't let a stranger come in our home
Under any circumstances.
Don't worry, claire.
I'm here to protect both of us.
Something wrong?
Tell me who you are again.
I'm the monacos' niece.
The monacos don't have a niece.
So I'm gonna ask you one last time.
Who are you?
And what the hell do you want?
You don't understand.
I'm here to protect her and this family.
Who sent you?
What's going on, noah?
Nothing; just go on back in the bedroom.
Does this have something to do
With how we got the baby?
No questions. that was the arrangement.
Please, just go sit in the bedroom and wait.
I'll take the baby.
No, everything is fine, sandra.
Please, just go.
I know you're scared.
You're a company man.
And this little baby is your assignment.
You're thinking, how can she possibly
Be your daughter when they could
Take her away from you at any moment?
You're trying so hard,
But you can't let yourself love her.
What is this? are you one of them?
Are you a mind reader?
Something like that.
Believe me, this little baby
Will be in your life for at least 16 more years.
And many more hopefully after that.
She's gonna need you to protect her
From so many things,
Terrible things.
But you're gonna love each other so much.
How do you know all this?
No, don't answer that.
Why not?
It's the company, okay?
They want to take her back just for a minute.
But they're going to do something to her.
And it's gonna change everything.
This little baby, your clair-bear,
She's fine
Just the way she is.
Trust me.
Claire-bear, huh?
Thank you.
We are both here, my son.
Now is our chance. Tell me about your life.
I became a master of space and time.
And I have saved the world...twice.
I always knew you were meant for greatness.
Did your father see this?
Yes. My father and I grew to
He saw me become a great hero.
And now I have the chance to save the world again.
Give me the catalyst, Mother.
Give me the light. I will defend it.
Your father wants me to give it to a baby.
He is calling Noah Bennet now--
I am strong enough to protect it.
I can keep it safe.
Believe me.
I've always believed in you, my son.
I am so proud of you, Hiro.
You are the one who did it.
You showed me what it means to be a hero...
Mother?
Mother!
Please...don't go!
Mother...
Mommy.
Farewell.
Present day.
Your silence betrays you.
What? no, I'm fine.
You know, I was just thinking
It's too bad the eclipse had to end.
The world be a lot simpler without powers.
To kill one's own father is a horrible thing.
He tried to kill my brother.
He took away my powers.
He'd kill me if he had to.
But he didn't.
You and I both know
The world isn't safe with my father in it.
But I also know you, peter.
You want to save the world.
You always have.
It's that part of you that wants to save your father.
Give the gun to me.
I'll do it.
No.
Just like your brother was your responsibility.
This one is mine.
Something wrong?
No.
Does kind of tingle.
I found it in some guy's locker
After he got canned.
I had no idea how much it was worth.
Every fanboy in the city's been trying to grab it.
My life's been a living hell.
I don't understand.
This is how it ends?
What's happened to hiro?
Maybe it's not so bad.
Right.
Maybe this is just the cover to get people to buy it.
Hiro will come back.
He has to.
16 yeas ago.
Cheerleader, it's over.
We can go home now.
Hey, you speak english.
-I thought that--  -it's a long story.
Just know that I have taken the catalyst.
The light is in me now.
We have saved the future.
Wait, you put the catalyst in you?
Guess I showed up just in time.
Keep away, arthur petrelli.
I will save the cheerleader again.
I don't think so.
I'll take the catalyst and your powers too, hiro.
You're a dead man.
No!
Hiro.
As for you,
I need you to deliver a message for me.
Tell angela it's over. I've won.
Cheerleader!
Hello?!
Anybody there?
Help!
Help.
Please.
I can't believe it.
Hiro's stuck back in time 16 years ago and no powers.
Maybe it isn't all bad news.
Arthur petrelli has the catalyst.
He could perfect the formula.
Yeah, wait, he-- he can give people powers.
So that means that there could be another time traveler.
Someone to save hiro.
Maybe it could be me.
I can go back in time
And save hiro.
We've got to find the formula.
How do we find the formula?
Doctor.
Ready to change the world?
I.d. please.
We'll need 50 doses to begin--
One for every marine?
We'll just try it on one first.
Let's make sure this thing works.
No offense.
What is it?
Nothing.
Just a minor inconvenience.
Call your first marine.
I'll be back.
Peter.
I'm glad you're here.
Nathan and I have just been--
Don't be ridiculous.
So...
You're here to kill me.
I'm here to stop you.
Creating abilities like this,
Giving them out,
It'll destroy the world.
In your opinion.
I've seen it. this ends now.
I don't think you have the nerve to kill me, peter.
I like your choice.
Very all-american.
We could put him on a poster.
Where's my father?
We don't need him.
You're in charge, remember?
All right, let's do this.
What the hell happened to you?
A mistake.
Hopefully this formula will fix all that.
What's in there?
It's all right, scott.
Who is this guy?!
What's happening?
I'm not sure.
He's too strong.
I cannot hold his powers back.
Listen to me, son.
There is another way.
The formula is ready. nathan is here.
I can give you your abilities back.
- We can start over. - No.
Peter!
- Wait. just wait.- Shoot now.
That your problem, son.
Too much thought. not enough action.
How could you be my son?
Hello, arthur.
Gabriel, you're here.
I am.
No place I'd rather be than with family.
Are you really my family?
Of course.
I'm your father.
No, you're not.
Now I know the truth.
You're not a killer, peter.
I am.
There'll be no need for that.
I'm not gonna kill you.
You don't have anything I need anymore.
I'm sorry, peter.
Your father was the one who had to die.
Go after sylar.
It's over.
How do you feel?
I feel good.