People think I collect art,
but I really collect
our lives fixed in paint.
A perfect moment
capturing an entire existence,
made immortal.
What you've done is not evolution,
it's murder.
What I am doing...
is revenge.
A monster's fight to survive...
and live to kill again.
A mother willing to fracture
her own soul to protect her child.
Don't lie to me anymore.
You told me she was gone.
Now which one of you is in control?
Niki, Jessica?
I'm not so sure.
Youth struggle for innocence,
despite life's cruelty.
Who are you?
I'm your grandmother.
The double-edged lies
needed to sustain a double-edged life.
He is going to be a problem.
Why don't we do it right now?
Sorry.
- What do we think?
- He's telling the truth.
He doesn't know where Claire is.
A wandering hero's pure joy at success.
And his darkest hour,
when all the world seems lost.
All perfect moments frozen in time.
Alone, each tells a single story.
Together they can tell the future.
Daddy, I'm so sorry.
It's all my fault.
I tried to do what you said,
but they caught me, and now...
I'm so scared.
What is it?
You.
You're not...
Not what?
Not you.
Why don't you leave us alone, Candice?
Are you sure?
I can show him things
that would make him tear his eyes out.
You've got more important matters
to take care of.
Things okay in here?
Do you need anything?
I just got through
with this Graham Greene I was reading.
I'll bring it.
How was it?
Ended bad.
I don't know where Claire is.
None of these games can make me
tell you what I don't know.
I'm going easy on you.
The only reason we haven't...
taken it up a notch, is...
because of friendship.
Friendship?
I brought you in, vouched for you.
And how do you repay my kindness?
Attempting to destroy the company?
You asked me to betray my daughter.
You got too close.
And then you got sloppy.
I saw what your girl Candice can do.
Maybe you're the one who got sloppy.
Maybe I'm exactly where I want to be.
You're on death row.
If you were gonna kill me,
you'd have done it by now.
I'm just waiting for the order.
That's how we do it here.
We follow orders.
I'll see about getting you that book.
Japanese feudalism.
Renaissance, Baroque,
Mayan, Persian.
20th century.
You must bring
all your first dates here?
What do you do with all this?
I protect it.
I shield it from a greedy
and dangerous world.
You push the cultured facade
long enough,
people forget you're a criminal.
When my day of judgment comes, Nathan,
I'll be remembered as a humanitarian.
I care about the world.
I just want to save it.
To heal it.
And to do that, I need you.
What could you possibly know
about healing?
A few things.
Subtitles: swsub.com
Parkman.
Parkman, wake up.
- They're just waiting...
- You gotta be kidding me.
They're coming for you.
They're just waiting for the order.
And then you're never coming back.
Not to your wife,
or anyone else you care about.
They'll never see you again.
We don't have much time.
If you can hear me,
and if you can trust me,
bang on the pipe.
Good man.
If you follow everything I say,
you might not die.
You may want to argue,
but luckily
this is a one-way conversation.
Can I count on you?
I hate him.
Yes or no?
I know this man.
Well, great. If you see him,
tell him I want my sword back.
He said he needed it to save the world.
A lot of people
seem to be saying that these days.
Well...
we all have our roles to play
in the events to come.
You know,
this isn't just a collection of art.
This... is a road map.
These artists
envisioned a brighter future.
Peace, prosperity.
That's your idea of a brighter future?
What if I was to tell you that it was?
I'd say you were a lousy humanitarian.
I was a lot younger than you
when I discovered my power.
And there were others too, like me,
who discovered theirs.
We were all confused.
And we found each other.
Together,
we tried to make a difference
to the world.
And for a while, we did.
It was beautiful.
And then, some of my...
friends...
they lost their way.
They used their powers
for personal gain.
And all the good that we'd done was...
Well, it amounted to nothing.
And I learned
that healing one person at a time
was just not enough.
We needed something...
something to pull it down on course.
Something big.
And that's what you think this is?
People need hope, Nathan.
An explosion of that magnitude
would destroy half the population
of New York City like that.
There's six and a half billion people
on the planet.
That less than .07%.
Come on, that's an acceptable loss
by anyone's count.
- By anybody's count?
- Look,
I said people need hope,
but they trust fear.
This is crazy.
This tragedy will be a catalyst
for good.
For change.
Out of the ashes,
humanity will find a common goal.
A united sense of hope
couched in a united sense of fear.
And it is your destiny, Nathan,
to be the leader
who uses this event to rally a city,
a nation, a world.
Now you look deep into your heart.
You'll know I'm right.
I don't mean to toss a wet blanket,
but if you haven't noticed,
I'm down in the polls.
I'm not gonna get elected to Congress.
Let alone the White House.
Do you think I'd leave that to chance?
If you know all this,
then you also know
that the exploding man
is my brother Peter.
As I said,
we all have our role to play.
Peter's curtain call will come
the day after you're elected.
You're insane.
You know that?
Now, all that banging
has alerted the guards.
What?
You told me to signal you!
Don't worry, it's a good thing.
Now look for the rusted pipe.
Pipes.
It should be the one
closest to the window.
A couple of hits will loosen it.
Hurry up! A guard will be there.
You've got three minutes.
Come on!
By now you should have removed the pipe.
The guard will be coming
through the door any second now.
Signal when you've knocked him out.
Yeah, I'm working on it.
Come on!
Grab his pass, and head into the hall.
Suresh?
It's Peter Petrelli.
Mohinder?
Sylar.
I remember you.
You're like me, aren't you?
I'd like to see how that works.
Not now.
I'm not done with him yet.
Interesting.
I can't wait to try that one.
My God.
My two boys actually getting along.
Nathan's wedding.
He has two boys of his own now.
And that handsome man is Peter.
But you've already met him now,
haven't you?
He saved my life.
He forgot to mention
that we were related.
Oh, he didn't know.
He didn't even know you existed.
But you did?
Since you were a baby.
Nathan's folly in Texas.
And you kept me a secret?
I cared about you a great deal.
Perhaps not in the traditional sense...
oatmeal cookies and school plays...
but I did what I could.
My husband and I
made arrangements for you.
Arrangements?
Then that fire happened, and...
Nathan just assumed you were gone, so...
So you let him.
It was the right thing to do.
You need to be protected.
Trust me, I don't need protecting.
Because you can grow back your bones
and spit up bullets?
You have no idea, Claire.
The life your abilities
would bring you...
You deserve better.
And that's why you have to go.
Get you away, like we planned.
I haven't seen Peter,
or met my father yet.
Neither of them is in a position
to be anything to you right now.
Be sensible.
By shipping me off to Paris?
For now, yes.
I'll be taking you there myself.
You'll have a chance to grow up
and develop
into someone
who can make her own choices.
And then if you choose to come back
and join this madness, like I once did,
at least
I will have given you the option.
So you're like me?
I regret a lot of the choices
I've made in my life.
You're getting the benefit
of my experience.
Whether I want it or not.
You get that mouth from me.
The list... no!
My editor needs these pages right away,
so I called my best messenger.
Oh, man, the new 9th Wonders.
I've been dying to find out
what happens to Hiro.
The latest, and the last.
Last?
Looks that way.
Why, what do you mean?
Never mind.
So what happens to Hiro in this one?
You promise you won't post any spoilers?
The future?
How do you come up with this stuff?
It's a gift.
Speaking of which...
Your sketchbook?
Are you serious?
Hold on to it.
It might be worth something someday.
Thank you.
Working for a gangster like Linderman,
pulling triggers for him.
Everything I've done,
I've done for Micah.
You keep telling yourself that.
Hey, if it wasn't for me,
Niki would still be in prison,
Micah wouldn't have a mother,
and you'd be all alone.
I don't remember you complaining.
Niki, Jessica,
whoever the hell you are, I'm done.
- I'm taking Micah, and...
- Careful how you finish that sentence.
He's not safe as long as Linderman
owns our lives.
Not as long as you're around.
Look at what you brought into our house.
What, money?
Rent?
Poor me!
Nobody wants to hire a black ex-con.
Everywhere you go, people die.
Cash, cars,
hurting people for the fun of it.
Hell, you didn't turn into Jessica.
You turned into your old man.
Don't you dare.
I'll die before I'll let you do to Micah
what he did to you.
Miss Sanders...
Mr. Linderman has asked to see you
right away.
If this is the life you want,
you need to get Micah out of it.
You can say good-bye tonight.
The first door on the right
is the supply room.
Steal something less conspicuous.
Keep moving.
You'll see an exit door before the hall.
Orders came down.
We're moving Bennet,
Sprague, and Parkman.
Now make sure you gas Sprague's room
before you put the IV in him.
I don't want that man
so much as dreaming.
What about Parkman?
Put some tape on his mouth.
I don't want to hear any more
about his pregnant wife.
You want to do what?!
We gotta go.
Quickly!
Go... how did you even get in here?
Bennet, he's got a plan.
Bennet?
Were you listening to him?
He told me to come get you.
He could be leading you
right where he wants you to go.
It can't be worse than the alternative.
Mrs. Petrelli?
Yes.
I'm so sorry. It's Peter.
What about him?
I found this address in his wallet.
I didn't know where else to go.
I couldn't leave him.
He's dead.
He was killed... murdered...
trying to save my life.
I was in over my head and...
Get out of here.
I'm sorry?
Please leave... now.
Mr. Linderman will see you now.
Linderman? You're kidding.
Linderman doesn't see anyone.
Not if I can help it.
Fearsome Jessica, finally.
Sweet Niki, yes,
but you... I never had the pleasure.
You were due.
We've both certainly
come a long way, haven't we,
since you borrowed that $30,000
and conveniently forgot to repay.
Oh, by the way...
I've had to have that room repainted
since your last assignment.
What is this?
I need a small favor.
You're Linderman.
When you need something,
you send your boys.
When it's something big,
you send lawyers.
This must be off the charts.
It's all a matter of perspective.
I need to borrow your Micah briefly.
Borrow?
Yeah, that is, his talent.
I want to help Micah achieve
something monumental in his life.
I had a plan in place
that, until recently, began to unravel.
I need your son to help me repair it.
Micah wasn't part of our deal.
I don't want him involved in all this.
Understand,
Micah is involved
by the mere fact of his birth.
Now, I've been,
I think, more than fair to you.
I mean,
I helped you out of a tough spot.
Spared you that long walk
to the gas chamber even.
So...
a chocolate milk,
all the cookies he can eat,
and I'll tell you what.
I'll even make him
a fresh sandwich myself.
If you need something from me,
point and I'll shoot.
Micah's off limits.
The request was a courtesy, dear.
Send anyone you want...
you're not touching my son.
We'd better take out
an insurance policy on Miss Sanders.
The power grid!
Why does he want me to do, melt it?
No, no, he says you've gotta...
- What the hell's an E.M.P.?
- I don't know!
It's an electromagnetic pulse
that causes a high-intensity
photoelectron surge.
I don't know what he's saying,
but he says it's not radioactive!
- He says it's clean.
- But I don't know how to do that!
He said you'd say that. He says...
You have no concept of your potential!
You can focus all your energy
into one burst.
He says don't burn hot, burn bright.
Does that make sense?
Did he say anything else?
I shouldn't stand next to you.
The power's out, let's go!
- No. We've gotta get Bennet.
- That guy is why we're in here!
He got us this far, we owe him.
- I'm not going back in there.
- They'll kill him!
- Yeah, well...
- They're after his daughter.
He's just trying to protect her.
He is the one person
who can take them down.
This is our only shot
to get our lives back.
I don't have a life.
Hey, you're always talking
about how you want to die,
yet you fight like hell to stay alive.
Some part of you wants to live,
and for that, we need Bennet!
That went better than I expected.
Ma?
Where is he?
He's gone, Nathan.
He isn't supposed to die this way.
He's not supposed to die this way.
He was wrong.
What do we do?
We hide it.
What?
'Till after the election.
Last thing he would have wanted
was to bring you down with him.
Why does it matter anymore?
Peter's dead.
I'm not having this conversation.
I know you don't want me here.
I just want to see him.
I came all this way.
Let the girl have her moment.
I didn't even get to know you.
You're the only one
that made me feel safe.
I thought you were like me.
You saved my life.
Guess we're even now.
What do you do with something
that killed you?
You could put it underneath your pillow.
I don't know what I would have done.
Don't think about it.
- I didn't die.
- Yeah, but if you had...
I don't know who I am without you.
Of course you do,
you're Nathan Petrelli.
Top of his class, valedictorian,
most likely to...
You're that guy with me or without me.
Who's to say I'm not all that
because of you?
Most of what we are
is what people expect us to be.
I mean, if you take them away,
nothing means anything.
It's a good thing I can't die then.
- What?
- Oh, I got that from Claire.
She can regenerate.
No matter what happens?
I think so.
What about that painting?
You explode.
If that happened, you could survive it?
Doesn't really matter, does it?
Think about it for a minute.
If I go nuclear...
if I blow up New York,
do you know how many people
are gonna die?
.07%.
Talk to her, Nathan.
She wants to know her father.
I can't deal with that right now.
She's not just some girl,
she's your daughter.
You know that Mom wants to send her
to Paris? You can't let her go!
Don't you get it?
Claire's the girl that I saved...
in Texas.
- Save the cheerleader...
- save the world. I get it.
And she turns out to be your daughter...
your daughter!
Look around.
Everything I said is happening,
is happening now.
It's real.
Maybe if Claire's here,
I don't blow up.
Maybe she's here to save us.
Talk to her, Nathan.
We need her.
About what just happened,
Nathan and I need to talk to you.
It's okay, I know.
I knew long before either of you did.
I recommend the cherry pie.
Shouldn't we keep a lower profile?
They won't come after us
in a public place.
- They wouldn't risk it.
- How can you be so sure?
Point taken.
Eat up. It's a long road ahead.
Forget it,
I'm getting the hell out of here.
They will find you.
As long as they have
that tracking system,
you'll never be safe.
Neither will Claire.
Look...
the system is well-protected,
but we can get to it, destroy it.
No more bagging and tagging.
No more looking over your shoulder.
We can end it all.
Where is this tracking system?
New York City.
We're leaving on the next bus.
Is this where Linderman is?
Where did you get that name?
From your boss, Thompson.
He was thinking about sending us
to go see Linderman.
I just figured that must be
who you're working for.
Wait a minute...
You didn't know that?
You're trying to take down
your organization,
you don't even know
who signs your checks?
My God!
- You're middle management!
- So what's that supposed to mean?
What it means is he's a schlub,
just like the rest of us.
Linderman isn't in New York.
He's in Las Vegas.
So this is really Linderman Linderman,
the mobster who owns all those casinos?
- What does he have to do with all this?
- Apparently more than I knew.
I say we go to Vegas.
We take the fight to Linderman.
We stick with the plan.
We take out the tracking system.
And then whoever's left standing
can go after Linderman.
New York.
I've always wanted to go.
You boys ready to order?
But why'd you have to pick me up
so early today from school?
Today's a special day.
Mom?
The man we're gonna meet,
well, let's just say
he changes all the rules.
And he wants to meet me?
He knows
that you do the most amazing things.
I told him
he doesn't know the half of it.
My son the genius.
So I don't have to pretend
about what we can do, like dad said?
That's all right, gentlemen.
I want to greet this young man myself.
It's a great pleasure
to meet you, Micah.
Thank you.
How would you like
to save the world today?
Cute car.
You know why Peter Petrelli came here?
He wanted my help.
Instead, I got him killed.
You did the right thing calling us.
I tried to stop Sylar...
but I couldn't.
I'm a scientist. I can't fight someone
who defies the laws of physics.
You can.
You just need help.
You're not the one I called.
Glasses, tall fella?
He's no longer with the company.
You know,
you've been going about this
all wrong, Professor.
Trying to take on the science
and the killer all on your own?
What you're dealing with,
no man should face without friends.
Now, we can provide you
with the resources...
I didn't call about my research.
The man who murdered my father
and Peter Petrelli is still out there.
That takes precedence
over any academics.
A person that dangerous must be stopped.
I can assure you
we have similar priorities.
The best way to stop Sylar
is for us to work together.
You really can paint the future.
Just like the professor said. Fantastic.
You're late.
I guess you know why I'm here.
You're the one who's gonna kill me.
That's true.
This is usually the part
when people start screaming.
I tried fighting the future.
It's too big for me.
Maybe you can do better.
Why me?
Do you see some special future for me?
They stop you...
and you die.
You painted all that too?
Show me.
Show me!
Now, now.
It's already gone.
Why don't you tell me all about it then?
I've seen enough of the future.
I don't need to watch it happen.
I've wasted my life,
destroyed everything good
that ever came to me.
At least I did one good thing
before I died.
You can't fight the future.
Neither can you.
It's all right.
I finally know my part in all of this.
To die here with you.
But not before I show them
how to kill you...
and stop the bomb.
I finally get to be a hero.
Your mom said you wanted to talk to me.
I did... I do. Come in, please.
This should have happened
a long time ago,
under better circumstances.
It shouldn't take someone nearly dying
for the two of us to finally meet.
You know, you don't have to do this...
pretend to be nice to me.
I'm not pretending.
Claire, most people...
they think the worst of me,
and I've probably given them
good reason to. But I want to do better.
I want to be there for you.
But I can't.
Not now.
Of course.
I'm sorry, but there are things
happening right now
that I can't expect you to understand.
I barely understand them myself.
I got into politics
for the chance to... do something good.
I have a chance to help.
To be a part of something big.
- But in order to do that, I have...
- The election.
You can't have
some illegitimate daughter
popping up and waving at the cameras.
I need to win.
You need me to leave.
Paris, with my grandmother.
She warms up.
Sort of.
It's just one week.
And then what?
And then you come home to your family.
Okay?
You!
Me?