Previously on Heroes...
This is a good bye.
I love you dad.
I love you, Claire bear.
I care about the world.
I just want to heal it.
What could you
possibly know about healing?
A few things.
The company has devellopped
a new tracking system
that doesn't relly on isotopes
and satellites, it just finds you.
Wherever you are.
We go to New York,
we wipe out the Walker system.
There is someone you need to meet.
Molly Walker.
I hear you have an amazing ability.
They ask me where people are,
and I find them.
Molly is the only one
who can stop Sylar.
I must stop you.
Then, do it.
Do it!
Kill me!
You can't.
Now, I'm gonna have to kill you.
Your destiny, Nathan,
is to set the course of history
after this unspeakable act has occurred.
Can you be the one we need?
That's my boy.
I explode!
I wipe out this whole city.
You, Nathan, everyone.
You explode?
Like a nuclear bomb.
If I lose it, you're the only one
who can get close enough to stop me.
Me, Ted...
it doesn't really matter.
But you have to do this.
I just miss my family.
I hope I can make them proud.
Dad!
What's he doing?
He's absorbing your ability.
He's gotta make it stop.
Claire, you know what you have to do.
Do it.
Wait!
I'm okay.
Sword repair...
Yes. Do you fix ancient Samurai swords?
My name is Hiro Nakamura,
and the fate of the world
is in your hands.
So Peter Petrelli is your uncle.
You didn't know that?
There are a lot of things
they never told me.
I thought Peter was the only
person who could protect me.
Now you're here.
Why did you come here?
With them?
The people I used to work for
have a tracking system.
They can find anybody
anywhere in the world.
We came here to destroy it.
That's the only way
we can ever start over.
And build a normal life.
Is that even possible?
I mean, I'm not normal,
and they're not normal.
Everything that's been happening to us
has been so monumentally un-normal.
I mean, maybe Peter's right.
Maybe we all have a destiny.
And it's to save the world...
together.
I just rode 26 hours from Texas
to take down the evil bastards
who want me dead,
and you're saying I should go back
because of a painting that you saw?
That and a dream.
He might be nuts, but he's not lying.
He believes every word of it.
They'll take out the tracking system,
- then you're gonna be free.
- Free?
I killed people with my powers, okay?
I didn't mean to, but it happened.
And now the FBI thinks I'm a terrorist.
But you're not a terrorist.
You need to get out of town
before you become one.
There's a town in Nebraska.
Windy Fork.
Population 15.
Go there and wait for me to contact you.
He gave me directions.
You're sending
your daughter with them?
Claire tells me she has a destiny.
She stopped Ted
from melting down once before
and saved all our lives...
she could do it again.
She could stop both of you.
You coming?
I'm in.
Me too.
Subtitles: swsub.com
We can do the photo op
outside the polls.
Yes, Marty... Marty!
I know we're still behind.
That's why every vote counts.
Exit polls have me five points down.
I never listen to polls.
Be ready, Nathan.
Today you will become
a congressman.
In time, you will lead the country.
As long as I let this city
become a nuclear wasteland.
And let my brother explode.
You can't stop that.
No one can.
But it's what comes next.
And that... that is entirely up to us.
Your father would be very proud.
Pop would have me committed
for even considering this nonsense.
Clearly, your mother didn't tell you.
Tell me what?
Your father was one of us,
someone with great power.
He tried to make
a difference in the world.
He did all he could,
and when that wasn't enough...
he just gave up.
Your father was weak.
My father was my hero.
And when I win...
I thought you were gonna see the boys
before they went to school.
They wanted to wish you good luck.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were here.
That's all right.
I'm just on my way out.
Mrs. Petrelli, your husband
is about to become a very powerful man.
I would like to give you both a gift
to honor his forthcoming victory.
Something to make the days ahead
a little easier.
What is he talking about?
I don't know.
I can't believe you let
that man into our house.
Honey...
he's my largest campaign contributor.
He's a thief and a liar
and God knows what else.
And if I win this election,
he'll be the reason.
Why?
Because he gave you money?
Nathan, don't forget who you are.
I know exactly who I am.
I'm a man who's being asked to make
a hard choice for the greater good.
And you will.
And you're gonna do great things.
But you don't have to sell your soul!
What?
What is it?
Your foot.
It's moving.
What?
Oh, my God!
It's a miracle.
I've been thinking
after we save the world,
I might go on patrol.
You know, jumping in front of bullets
and dragging people
out of burning buildings.
Not gonna catch me wearing a cape,
zipping around with my underwear
outside my pants.
Why do we have to rent a car?
Can't we just fly to Nebraska?
In a plane.
FBI's got my face
all over wanted posters.
- I wouldn't get very far in an airport.
- Ted's a fugitive.
I can use that to get his power.
What is it?
It's Sylar.
He's here.
He's watching us.
Right now?
He knows what Ted can do.
We need to get off the streets.
Who's Sylar?
Would have been nice
to have Heidi for the photo op.
Something happened back at the house.
- She all right?
- She's fine.
She's better than fine, actually.
We'll make an announcement
after the election.
What's going on?
Miracles, Marty.
No, I need to speak to Nathan.
It's all right.
Mr. Hiro, how are you?
Fine.
Thank you very much.
We are trying to stop a bad thing.
The bomb.
Big boom.
You must help.
Or bad future will come.
Bad future?
Yes, we went there.
But I was already dead.
You become a... bad person,
But you can come with us now,
help us stop bomb...
together!
Sorry, Hiro.
I can't stop it.
Nobody can.
It's a pleasure to see you again.
Thanks for your support.
You already bad guy!
You are villain!
Villain!
Thank you all.
That's Petrelli?
Yep.
I don't see Micah.
Or Linderman.
We know they're in town.
Nathan can tell us where.
He'll never see us coming.
Mr. Claremont?
It's me. Hiro Nakamura.
I spoke to you on the phone.
About my problem.
My God.
The Kensei.
What happened?
It got cold.
Frozen.
Then... snap.
Can you fix it?
Depends.
On him.
I have a cousin who eats like you.
He's huge.
So am I.
You said you like comic books, so...
I bought you a stack.
Anything good?
The original Silver Surfer number one?
This must have cost you a fortune!
You're nice. Even when you're scary.
I just don't understand
why you're working for such a bad guy.
You could use your power to be a hero.
You're just too young to see
how much the world sucks.
How people can be
so mean to each other
just because of where they were born
or what they look like.
Mr. Linderman's gonna change all that.
He's gonna heal the world.
I didn't know it was sick.
- How are you?
- Good.
And how is our boy?
Good, sir.
I wanna see my mom.
After today, you can go home.
I don't believe you.
I'm sure other grownups
talk down to you, Micah.
I'm not gonna make that mistake.
I'm gonna look you
straight in the eye
and tell you one simple truth.
What you do here today
with your incredible ability
is going to save many lives.
What do you want me to do?
What comes naturally.
Talking to machines.
And after that,
you'll take me home?
I'll tell you what.
I'll do better than that.
You do as you're told,
and I'll make sure
that you and your parents
have enough money
to live happily ever after.
So this guy Sylar,
he kills people like us?
Yeah, to take what we can do.
How does he manage that?
He rips your head open.
I say we stick with the plan,
get out of the city.
Get out of here!
Go!
Federal agents. On your knees!
Now! Now!
Let's go!
There were two others!
Find them.
You're under arrest.
Agent Hanson?
I've been chasing you
all across the country, Ted.
You know I'm not a terrorist!
Do I?
You blew up a van full
of federal agents in Los Angeles.
But I didn't mean to hurt anybody.
Good. Your next stop...
Guantanamo Bay.
I'm gonna need
a concrete cell lined with lead.
So everyone is safe!
We got him,
thanks to your tip, Mister...
Mendez. Isaac Mendez.
I thought I recognized Sprague
from his picture in the post office.
I knew it was my duty to call.
Especially with it being
election day and all.
You helped us capture
a very dangerous man.
Most people wouldn't take the risk.
I'm not most people.
A few things.
Welcome, Ms... Baker.
Do you mind if I take my son
into the voting booth with me?
I'm trying to teach him
about democracy in action.
What a lovely thought.
Follow me.
I've been thinking about
how you make yourself look like that.
You must bend light or something.
How do you know this isn't the real me?
Okay, Micah,
it's time to boot up.
What do you want me to do?
You can tell computers what to do.
So I want you to tell this one
and all the others here
to vote for Nathan Petrelli.
After this, we do the same thing
in 12 other precincts.
We don't have to go anywhere else.
It says that they're all networked.
So from here, I can change
every one in the city.
It says that?
How many votes does your boss
want him to win by?
Make it a landslide.
Can I go home now?
Sorry to interrupt your big day.
How did...
I didn't think I'd be seeing you again.
I thought after you
tipped me off about Linderman,
I figured you'd be dead.
And Niki thought
that you were gonna take him out.
Let me guess.
He made you an offer
that you couldn't refuse.
Something like that, yeah.
We came here to find Linderman.
- Who are you?
- He took our son.
Why would he do that?
Something to do with you
and the election.
Kidnapping.
That's a serious accusation.
I hope you have evidence.
Cut the crap, Nathan.
We both know that you hate
Linderman as much as we do.
You were gonna kill him.
Let us finish the job.
Whatever you think
you're getting from this man,
he's gonna take back
ten times more from you.
And he ain't never gonna stop
until everything you care about is gone.
If I tell you where Linderman is...
I have to know
that he's not gonna come after us.
The man took my son.
He's gonna pay for that in full.
Takezo Kensei longed to unite Japan.
He went to the dragon
of Kiso Mountain
and asked the dragon
to teach him the secrets of the sword.
The dragon taught him
to become the Kensei,
the sword saint.
He fought his enemies and won,
saving his people.
Then the dragon came to his palace,
demanding the life of the princess.
Kensei drew his sword
and plunged it into his own heart.
He handed it to the dragon and said,
"My love is in here. Take it. "
And then he died.
Tracking system's on the 42nd floor.
Get a read on someone.
You sure there isn't another way?
The reason I brought you here, Parkman,
was so that you could get us to those
elevators without raising a ruckus.
If you can't do that,
you might as well give up
on your wife and unborn child right now.
Because no matter how far you run...
they will find you.
A simple "no" would have done the trick.
- Good morning, Stanley.
- Okay, I got it.
Stanley, hey, man.
I just took my buddy to lunch,
I forgot my ID.
Can you buzz us through?
I don't know you.
It's Matt from accounting on 3-6.
What are you talking about?
We just went to Ray's for an egg parm.
I'm gonna need to see your ID, buddy.
Stan, come on, buddy,
you don't remember?
Remember on the weekend,
I ran into you at the...
At that restaurant.
Where did I take Tanya, Shopsins?
Shopsins.
Right? You introduced me to Tanya.
I did? Drank and, God,
I hope I didn't...
You okay, Stan?
Remember? You were really drunk.
And you were worried about
people finding out about the...
you know...
the porno.
Yeah, don't worry about it! Here.
You guys go ahead. Have a good day.
- Thanks, Stan.
- No problem, sir.
The password doesn't work.
They changed the protocol.
We have to wait until
you can pick it out of somebody's head.
We gotta move. Right now.
That blonde works for Linderman.
Let's go.
Linderman could be on any floor.
Then we'll search them all. Come on.
Mr. Hawkins. Ms. Sanders?
Relax.
My friend can hear your thoughts.
He says we have similar goals.
Didn't I throw you out a window?
You're responding well to the treatment.
The important question is
how are you feeling, Molly?
Good, I guess.
As long as I don't get any more shots.
The antibodies in my blood
are a cure for the virus.
I'm afraid we will need
to continue the treatments.
I'm all better.
Look what I can do.
Just like before I was sick.
I think about someone,
and I know where they are in my head.
Right...
here.
How do I know you're not playing a trick
just to get out of more shots?
Now, you've put that pin
in this building.
Is that supposed to be me?
No. It's my other hero.
If he's here, can I see him?
Your other hero?
The police officer
that saved me from the bogeyman.
If your power has returned,
we can stop the bogeyman
so he never hurts anyone else.
Can you think about it?
Show me where he is?
You sure you wanna know?
And how's our favorite
patient, Dr. Suresh?
Much improved.
Molly says she can locate Sylar.
We should go after him immediately.
We will, soon.
Right now, you need
to go away with Molly.
We have a helicopter on its way
to take you both to a safe location.
You'll find Linderman on 51.
Good luck finding your son.
Right. Nice to see you too.
How do we take out this tracking system?
Erase a hard disk,
destroy a satellite link?
You did your part. This is mine.
Surveillance picked 'em up
in the elevator.
What does he want?
Molly.
Good night, Bennet.
It was Thompson.
I heard him waiting for you.
- Anybody else?
- No. He's alone.
All right, stay here!
What? No! I don't have a gun!
What am I thinking now, Parkman?
Your last thought.
How'd you know he was gonna
come up on me?
We were old friends.
I thought I heard a noise.
It's nothing.
Go back to your room, okay?
Good girl.
Look, whatever happens in here,
you gotta know
this is the only way our
families are ever gonna be safe.
Why? What do you mean?
What's here?
Where's the tracking system?
It's in there.
That's the tracking system?
A kid?
We came here to kill a little girl?
No.
I knew it was a person,
but I had no idea.
Lower your gun.
As long as she's alive,
my daughter will never be safe.
None of them will.
Lower your gun, or I will kill you.
Shoot me, and she dies.
I'm hurt!
I think it's bad!
Here, let me help.
Where is my friend?
He bought one of my Nagamakis and left.
He bought a sword?
He said if you weren't
going to save the world, he would.
Hey, move the car!
Come on, get moving!
- Is this the only way out of the city?
- No, but it's the fastest.
This is the sickest thing
I've ever seen.
Did this happen in the accident?
The top of the guy's head came off!
How else does that happen?
You don't wanna know.
Sylar got him.
He killed Ted.
Does that mean Sylar
can do what Ted can do?
He's the one.
He's gonna wipe out the entire city.
You've gotta stop him.
I don't think I can.
The last time I fought Sylar,
he killed me.
Come on. Come on.
Yes, we'll send a helicopter
to retrieve the Petrelli family.
Just make sure they're not late.
I must admit,
I'm quite surprised to see you here.
Where's Micah?
She asked you a question.
You wouldn't even have Micah
if it wasn't for me...
arranging your relationship.
Crafting your opportunities.
What gives you the right
to ruin our lives,
take our boy from his home,
your money?
You think being rich
makes you better than us?
Well, social Darwinism
did play its part.
I believe destiny to be intrinsic.
Your destiny...
is to give me back my son.
He's in the building.
42nd floor.
I'll go look for Micah.
Watch him.
You'll never see him again, you know.
How's that?
Jessica's gonna kill you for me.
Open the bag.
You just caught me preparing for a trip.
Yes.
Well, consider this a deposit
with more to follow.
How much more?
- You can't be listening to this!
- Of course she is.
Like most women whose lives
have been ruined by men,
all Jessica really wants is security,
and money buys that.
Money's all she's ever
really cared about.
She cares about our son.
How much?
5, 10 million?
Think about Micah.
You saw that painting.
You came here to save him.
Alright.
$20 million to kill your husband
and walk away.
He's right, D.L.
I wanna take the money.
I really do.
I would even kill you for it.
But Niki wouldn't.
You don't love him.
Everything I've done...
I did for them.
You should have taken the money.
I don't care what he said.
Me and you getting together...
that was real.
Jessica wasn't the strong one.
It was you.
Baby...
I feel so stupid sitting here.
I wanna jump out of this damn chair.
People don't believe in miracles.
When the time is right,
we'll tell everyone.
We're ready.
Thank you all.
Thank you very much
for your amazing support.
A landslide.
That's what they're calling it.
I'm sorry my brother
couldn't be with us tonight.
But I know that Peter cares
about this city more than anyone.
You know, our father always said
that we had a responsibility
to use what God gave us
to help people.
To make a real difference.
Pop always made the hard choices
for the greater good.
He believed in that.
And so do I.
Our children deserve that.
They deserve a better future.
A future where they don't have
to face their fears alone...
but can look into the darkness
and find hope.
I challenge everyone in here
to inspire by example.
To fight the battle,
no matter the cost.
Because the world is sick
and spinning out of control.
But we can help.
With our help, it can heal.
With our love, with our compassion,
and with our strength
we can heal it.
Let's put aside our differences.
Let's embrace our common goals.
Let's do it for our children.
Let's show them all exactly
what we're capable of.
Thank you all.
Thank you very much.