Hey, Murray.
Nice shorts.
Okay, guys, time for the
interesting buildings tour.
This week
it's band rotundas.
Ugh. It should be called
the "boring buildings tour."
- Why?
- Because it's boring.
It's not boring.
There's a real buzz about it.
- Everyone's talking about these tours.
- Who's talking about it?
Bret, you were talking
about it last week.
- I was saying it's boring.
- Oh, were you?
Well, you were still
talking about it.
Murray, I can't go this week.
I'm going on a date.
- What? A date?
- A date with a girl from work.
- What are you gonna do?
- I think we're gonna watch a DVD.
Bret, I've had this
organized for ages.
You knew about that.
I was gonna tell you the difference
between, you know,
gazebos and band shells.
Yeah, Bret,
you've got to come.
Why don't we just postpone the tour,
just go next week?
It's not as easy as that!
I've got the schedule.
Look, it's all time-tabled.
I made those for you.
"Friday, 4:05 P. M: Bret, Jemaine and
Murray leave Dave's shop."
Well, I guess I'll just have to go
with you, Jemaine. Just the two of us.
Ah. Except
I just remembered
that I also can't go.
Why? I suppose you've
got a date as well, have you?
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah?
- Where'd you meet her?
- At... at the library.
Library?
What library?
- Video library.
- Ha-ha-ha!
Video library.
No such thing.
Gotcha.
No, that's fine.
I'll go on my own.
That's fine.
Enjoy your date, Bret, and your
pretend date, Jemaine.
All right? The video library...
that's fine.
I won't say goodbye,
I don't feel like it.
See you, Murray.
- Bye, Murray.
- Bye. You gonna say "bye"?
No!
The carrots
were really nice.
And the broccoli was
really nice as well.
Yeah.
It did turn out
really nice.
Yeah, really nice.
It was really nice.
Yeah, it was
really nice.
Like your eyes...
I could look
at them for ages.
The eggs were really nice
like your lips.
So... your lips
look delicious like...
as delicious
as the eggs.
Probably more delicious.
Do... do you want
to kiss me?
Oh yes, please.
Are we gonna watch
a DVD or what?
I think it might be a bit late for
a DVD, man.
No, it's okay. We just have to keep
the volume down
because my roommate
is sleeping.
No, well, we should
probably get home.
It's pretty late.
Well, maybe I'll stay
a little bit longer.
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah.
Do you wanna... you could stay over
if... if you want?
No, I don't
want to stay over.
No, we should
get going.
I don't know... why don't
I stay and you go?
No, it's okay, I don't mind.
I'll stay here.
Whatever you want.
Hey, Jemaine, I've written this
love song for Coco.
- Oh yeah?
- Would you be able to have a listen?
- Give me a bit of feedback?
- Yeah.
It's good,
it's good.
# I'd climb
the highest mountain #
# I'd swim
the deepest ocean #
# I'd walk along
the longest path #
# To be with you #
# If you want me to... #
# I'd solve
the hardest puzzle #
# And read
the boringest book #
# I'd hold
the hottest substance #
# Solve
the hardest puzzle #
# And race
the fastest animal #
# Eat the biggest meal #
# To be with you #
# Co... co. #
It's a bit long.
- Okay.
- It's two hours long.
Yeah.
Anything else?
Um, yeah.
Let's see...
Okay.
Okay. "I'd climb
the highest mountain."
- Would you actually do that?
- Probably not.
Well, you're sort of
promising that you would.
- That's a metaphor.
- Oh, is it? Oh okay.
- Yeah.
- What's it a metaphor for?
For... that I'd do
anything for her.
Would you climb the highest
mountain for her?
Oh God.
I see.
No. Pass me that?
No, I wouldn't do
a lot of this stuff.
Would you swallow
a whole sword?
A sword... okay, I probably wouldn't
do that one either.
Yeah, maybe you should
make it more realistic things you'd do,
- some other things.
- Like what?
Uh, "I would
hang out with you."
- Oh, that's good. That's really...
- That's not bad.
That's a lyric of mine.
You can use that.
Just "hang out
with you."
What about making it
more personal?
Things about her that... what do you
know that's specific to Coco?
She has a rash that she
doesn't tell anyone about.
What... what else?
- She likes food.
- Yeah, okay.
Her flatmate
is called Stuart.
Yeah.
This is all good stuff.
All right, let's
get started, shall we?
Can I just say it's good to have
a lady's touch in the office?
Doesn't happen
very often.
All right, second annual
fan-club meeting.
- President.
- Present.
- Secretary.
- Treasurer.
- Present!
- Maybe we should make that one title?
- Sure.
It's all... it's quite convoluted.
You're all three.
- Sure.
- And Murray, present.
All right, item one:
Any more fans?
No. Sorry, Murray.
- Really?
- No.
All right,
let's move on.
Item two:
The new newsletter.
Really good idea.
Like it.
- Thank you.
- Really good.
In fact, I've got
some photos here.
I took some of Bret...
well, actually I found them,
I... when I was
round at his flat.
- Oh-ho!
- That... he's asleep there,
and so you could
put those in the newsletter.
Mm-mm,
mm-mm-mmm! Mmm!
Oh my God.
- What's this one?
- Mmm?
- God, how did that get in there? Sorry.
It must have slipped
in with the...
- do you want to hold onto that?
- No.
- No. So...
- So...
It's...
All right.
Item three.
Now if one of the band members was
to have a girlfriend...
Mmm.
...would you find that:
A) very positive;
- B) positive...
- Why do you... why do you ask?
- No reason.
- Has Bret got a girlfriend?
Yes, he's seeing
a girl from work...
Coco.
Oh.
Wow. Well, that's great
that Bret has a girlfriend.
- That's really great.
- You don't think Bret's
- any less available now that he's?
- Well, no!
No. Is she pretty?
You're still interested
in the band then, even though it's?
Yes, it's nice for Bret to have
a girlfriend.
- Good.
- Yes.
- All right. You sure?
- Yes!
- Is she stupid?
- You've still got Jemaine anyway.
- He's always available, isn't he?
- Yeah.
He's not gonna...
not gonna get a girlfriend anytime soon,
- so...
- Does, um...
- Try your chances with him, can't you?
- Mm-hmm.
Does... does Bret's girlfriend look
anything like me?
- Little bit?
- A little bit... around the eyes.
Oh yeah?
Big eyes, huh?
Well, she's...
she's got eyes.
Yeah.
- You want some more macaroni?
- No, I'm okay.
You sure.
I was gonna have some
fruit salad or something.
- Do you want anything?
- No, I'm fine.
Um, actually, I've...
I've written you a song, Coco.
Really? You didn't
need to do that.
Well, Jemaine helped.
That's so sweet.
It's called
"If You're Into It."
Okay.
# If you want me to #
# I can hang round
with you #
# If I only knew
that's what you're into #
# You and him,
him and you #
# If that's
what you're into #
# Him hanging round,
around you #
# You're hanging round...
yeah, you're there too #
# And if you want me to, I will
take off all my clothes for you #
# I'll take off all
my clothes for you #
# If that's what
you're into #
# How about him
in the nude? #
# If that's what
you're into #
# In the nude
in front of you #
# Is that what
you'd want to view? #
# If it's cool
with you #
# I'll let you
get naked too #
# It could be
a dream come true #
# Providing that's
what you are into #
# Is that what
you're into? #
# Him and you
in the nude #
# That's what
he's prepared to do #
# Is that the kind of thing that
you think you might be into? #
# And then maybe later we'll get hot by
the refrigerator #
# In the kitchen
next to the pantry #
# You think that might be
what you fancy? #
# In the buff,
being lewd #
# Doing stuff
with the food #
# Gettin' lewd
with his food #
# We heard that's
what you are into #
# Then on our next date #
# Well, you could bring
your roommate #
# I don't know
if Stu is keen to #
# But if you want
we could double-team you #
# How about you
and two dudes? #
# Him you and Stu
in the nude? #
# Bein' lewd with
two dudes with food #
# Well, that's if Stu's
into it too #
# All the things
I'd do #
# Things I'd do
for you #
# If I only knew #
# That's what
your into #
# Ooh. #
Thank you.
That was great.
- Thank you too, Jemaine.
- Oh, it was no problem.
So, what are we
gonna do now?
Well, we were gonna
go cycling.
- Yeah.
- Oh, were we?
Oh, great.
Kiss her, Bret.
Kiss her.
Hey Bret, I've been thinking
about these dates.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah, actually, I was gonna say...
I was thinking that maybe...
I've been thinking,
you know, they're a bit...
- they're a bit girlie.
- Well, Coco's a girl.
Yeah, but I'm not, though. It's not just
you and her going on these dates,
I'm there too. So what about thinking
about something I might like to do,
like paintball? We could watch
a kickboxing championship.
- Um, yeah.
- You know, that sort of thing.
- Maybe...
- Or we could go to a strip bar?
She doesn't like... she doesn't
want to go to a strip bar again.
- I was actually wondering...
- We could go to just a topless bar.
There's just
topless bars as well.
But I was thinking
maybe her and I like...
Or she doesn't always have to come
as well. That's another option.
Me and you could go on
one of these date... oh, that'd be weird.
Yeah, I was thinking maybe just her
and I would go on a date without you.
Maybe.
- Why?
- Oh no, don't worry about it.
- No, come on. You brought it up, so...
- Well...
just 'cause I never get to
hang out with just her.
You hang out with her
all the time.
- Yeah, but you're always there.
- Oh, so are you.
You're always there.
I always see you there.
Yeah, I'm always there,
but she's my girlfriend.
Yes. Good point.
Yes, good point.
And, uh...
Coco said that the other night when
I went to the bathroom
that she felt like you...
- like made a move on her.
- Yep. Yep, guilty, I did.
But you weren't doing
anything, so I thought...
Yeah, but that's 'cause
you were there.
- Ah! Of course I was there.
- You can't do that.
You're definitely not coming
on my next date.
Okay. Well, that's fine.
That's all you needed to say.
Okay.
- Good night.
Look at that.
Classic
Robert Moses design.
See the band shell,
Jemaine?
Where's your
fact sheet?
You should be
checking this out.
I don't know,
I left it at home.
"Julius Caesar" was
done here in 1957.
- Really?
- Joseph Papp's.
- Oh.
- Amazing.
- You think this is good?
You missed some of
the best band shells
and some awesome rotundas
when you were on all those dates.
Where's your
date tonight?
Uh, Bret asked me not to
come on his dates anymore.
- What? You were going on their dates?
- I know. Yeah.
You don't go on
other people's dates.
I thought you had
your own date.
No, I was dating them.
You don't do that.
- That's crazy.
- It's not crazy.
Are you okay?
Are your feelings hurt?
No.
- They must be. Are they?
- No.
- A little bit?
A little bit, eh?
- A little bit.
- Yeah, a little bit.
I knew it. Bret shouldn't have
a girlfriend. I told him.
- Did he listen?
- No.
No.
He doesn't listen.
I just hope we don't
have a Yoko Ono situation.
- Do you know what I mean?
- Yeah.
Is she trying to
split up the band?
She hasn't mentioned anything.
I don't think so... she's nice.
- Is she an artist?
- Don't know.
Does she like, you know,
staying in bed a lot?
I haven't
really noticed.
What about peace?
Is she into peace?
I don't know.
Look into that.
Now, Stuart Vaughan was
the director here.
Imagine that!
"Julius Caesar" in 1957.
I mean, the whole place
would have been full.
Come down and
touch it, Jemaine!
Hey, Bret,
is, um...
is Coco into art?
Yeah. Why?
- Uh, no reason.
- Mmm.
# Black-haired
lady queen #
# Dabbling in art #
# I won't let
the she-wolf #
# Tear us apart,
because I... #
- What's that song?
- Nothing, just a new song
called "She-wolf."
# Cold-hearted bitch #
# Diggin' a ditch... #
All I'm saying, Bret, is it could bring
unnecessary tension
to the band's dynamic.
Like this pencil...
Iook.
Jeez, that is a...
That's it... that's
your band. Broken.
It happens to
all the best bands.
All right? Girlfriends and music
just don't mix very well.
Jemaine's nodding
in approval.
By the way,
how is Coco?
- She's great. We're really in love.
- Yeah?
- It's... yeah, it's awesome.
- She seems really nice.
- Yeah, she's amazing.
- Yeah.
Hold onto her.
Okay?
It's a rare thing,
what you've got there.
- Hi, I'm not disturbing you guys, am I?
- Hey, Coco.
- No, come in.
- We're busy at the moment actually.
Oh, okay. I just popped in to
bring you some lunch.
- Oh good.
- Favoritism.
- Here's yours, Jemaine.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Murray.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Bret.
- Thanks, Coco.
You didn't need to do that.
That's great.
While I'm here, I thought I would
show you this.
Um, I had some spare time
last night, and...
I thought it might be useful.
Whoa,
that's awesome.
- Well, it's really arty.
- It's cool.
We've already got
a poster that I did.
Oh, okay. Oh, that's... that's all right.
That's cool. That's great,
it's... it's better.
Um, I just thought...
that's no problem.
Um, well, I should
let you guys...
I should go, let you
guys get on with it.
- No you should stay, you should stay.
- Oh no no no...
- Yeah yeah.
- I should go.
- You should stay.
- I insist.
Look, take a seat.
You've brought us lunch.
All right, we'll only be
five minutes, all right?
- At least.
- Yeah, sit down, sit down.
Okay okay okay.
Okay.
Right,
"slight delay."
And also present,
Coco.
Yoko.
What did you...
what did you say?
Oh nothing, just had
a bit of a cough.
Mmm, okay.
No, it wasn't a real cough.
I said "Yoko."
- Yeah, I thought so.
- Oh, I should go.
Why did you say that?
'Cause she's nothing like Yoko.
Oh-no, she isn't.
Jemaine, you're putting
"oh no" together to sound like "Ono."
- Oh-no, I didn't.
- You did it again.
- Oh-no, did I?
- Did you pick that up?
- He's doing it.
- All right, I'm gonna go.
Yeah. I'll throw this sandwich in your
face if you say that again.
Bret, don't you dare.
Not in my office.
Coco, sit down.
Let's resolve this.
Jemaine,
what's the problem?
Well, Yoko's trying
to split up the band.
- Bret?
- Jemaine's upset
because I asked him not
to come on our dates
and he's misinterpreting his feelings
about being left out of the friendship
- as being about the band.
- Oh, as if.
It's the one I said about Yoko trying to
split up the band.
Sorry, guys, I just realized
I'm late for work.
Um, it was
really cool seeing you.
What are you working on?
Splitting up another band?
- Oh! Here!
- A sandwich hit my face.
Yeah, well, I said I'd throw
a sandwich at your face.
I've never seen such bad behavior
at one of my meetings!
- Don't be such a... a dickhead.
- Yeah well, I'm quitting this band.
- Yeah.
- Well, you quit last week.
- Yeah well, I'm quitting again.
- Don't be a quitter! You can't!
- Yeah, you quitter.
- Right, well, go on then.
You've never been interested
in bands anyway, Bret.
You only came to one
of the band rotunda tours.
Yeah, I'll see you later,
dickheads.
You're the dickhead,
Bret!
Sorry, everyone.
It was a visa
application denied.
It took a long time
to try and get resolved.
I think the guy's
a criminal.
Sorry.
Just carry on.
It's looking good.
Good riddance,
eh, Jemaine?
I've got tomato
on my sleeve.
See? I told you.
Girlfriends and bands
just don't mix, Jemaine.
You'll never have
a girlfriend, will you?
No.
All right, let's just
move on. Item two:
Band uniforms.
I want all the band
to wear the same unif...
oh, that's...
Do you miss Bret?
A little bit.
Do you?
Same.
I miss him.
Can you ask him
back in the band?
Okay.
Bret? Bret?
Dear Jemaine,
by the time you read this,
I will be far far away
at Coco's house
and I will no longer
be residing...
and that is just one of the reasons
why I'm moving out.
You didn't seem to
understand that...
And the most important
thing for me to say is that...
Do you remember
the time that seagull...
Yours sincerely,
Bret.
# Lives are like
retractable pencils #
# If you push 'em too hard,
they're gonna break #
# And people are like
paper dolls #
# Paper dolls and people,
they're a similar shape #
# Mm-mm, mm-mm #
# Love is like
a roll of tape #
# It's real good for
making two things one #
# But just like
that roll of tape #
# Love sometimes breaks off
before you are done #
# Another way that love
is similar to tape #
# That I've noticed #
# Is sometimes it's
hard to see the end #
- # You search on the roll #
- # You're searchin' round the roll #
# You search
with your fingernail #
# Again and again
and again and again #
- # And again #
- # Whoa-oah #
# Brown paper,
white paper #
# Stick it together with
the tape... the tape of love #
# The sticky stuff... #
- Bret.
- Hey, man.
What are you doing here?
Murray and I miss you and we want you
to rejoin the band again.
Really?
Yeah.
On one condition.
That you...
I'm not gonna
kill her, man.
No, just leave...
just leave her, not...
Oh no, I'm not gonna leave her.
I told you that.
You know, I like the band,
but no, I'm not leaving Coco.
I wouldn't mind,
- I mean if that's what you really want.
- Shush, baby.
- I don't really see us a long-term...
- Shush.
So what's it
gonna be, Bret?
The girl
or the band?
Well, it's gonna
be Coco.
Oh. Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Oh, I thought you...
I was sure you were
gonna say the band.
No, I'm staying
with Coco.
I guess you can still
be in the band.
Okay. Great.
- Okay.
- Cool.
- Okay, well I'll see you later.
- I'll see you at band practice.
Actually, I'm gonna wait
till the bus stops,
and then I'll get off.
# Brown paper,
white paper #
# Stick it together with
the tape... the tape of love #
- # The sticky stuff #
- # Ooh #
# Ooh-hoo! #
# People people, paper paper,
paper paper, people people #
# People people,
pencil pencil #
# Pencil pencil,
paper paper #
# Put the pencil
to the paper #
# Give the paper
to the people #
# Let the people read about the
cellotape, oh, baby baby, yeah... #
You know, Jemaine,
I've been thinking about love,
and I guess it's the very strongest
adhesive.
Oh, sorry, Bret, were you talking to me?
I was humming.
- What did you say?
- Oh, doesn't matter.
# Brown paper,
white paper #
# Stick it together with
the tape... the tape of love #
# Oh, the sticky stuff #
# Yeah!
Oh, brown... #
# Brown paper,
white paper #
# Stick it together with
the tape... the tape of love #
- # Stick... stick it together #
- # Ooh-hoo... #
# Stick stick stick it
together, yeah. #