In a land of myth and time of magic,
the destiny of a great kingdom rests of shoulders on a young boy.
His name...Merlin.
Run run!
It's gone.
You saved my life.
I'm Merlin.
Lancelot.
The wound is superficial.
The fever will pass.
He should be fine by morning.
What creature could've done this?
We found no tracks in or out.
What the villagers say must be true.
It has wings.
and
what?
..and it took no livestock - only people.
Whatever it is,  it has a taste for human flesh.
Post sentries at all the outlying villages.
Put the lookouts on full alert.
If this thing should make for Camelot,
we must be ready.
Ever since I was a child, I've dreamed of coming here.
It's my life's ambition to join the knights of Camelot.
I know what you're thinking. I...I expect too much.
After all, who am I?
They have their pick of the best and bravest in the land.
Lancelot.
Yes.
They're going to love you.
They are?
I've seen you in action.
You could shame Arthur himself.
I hardly think so.
In fact, you know what I'll do?
I'll talk to him right now.
Yo know Arthur?
Oh, yes.
Right, you jumped-up dung beetle,
this is it final test.
Pass this and you're knight at Camelot,
Fail, and you're no-one.
You face the most feared of all foes, the ultimate killing machine.
You face me.
Your challenge - the last one minute, free combat.
Grimond, second son of Wessex.
Your times starts now.
Take him away.
He's the third to fail this month.
How can I defend Camelot with rubbish like that?
I think I might be able to help.
You, Merlin?
You have no idea what it takes to be knight
courage, fortitude, discipline.
No, of course I don't. But I do know someone who dose.
Yeah?
Save my life.
That's blown it for starters!
He's really good, honestly.
I'm sure he's terrific.
You forget Camelot's first code.
What?
The first code.
Only noblemen can be knights.
So unless your friend is a nobleman...
He is ... a nobleman.
- Is he?  - Absolutely.
Very well. Bring him to the training ground tomorrow.
Make sure he brings his seal of nobility.
Thanks, Arthur. You wont't regret it.
Well? Did you speak to him?
I spoke to him.
And?
And...
He'd like to meet you.
Yes!
Thank you. Thank you.
Hey, it's no problem, really.
It was nothing.
You're not a nobleman by any chance, are you?
A nobleman? No. Good lord, No.
Why do you ask?
It's just that...
The first code of Camelot states that
only those of noble blood can serve as knight.
Uther created the knights to protect this kingdom
from those who wish to destroy it.
He knew he'd have to trust each of his knights with his life.
So he chose those who'd sworn allegiance to him.
The nobility.
Thus the first code of Camelot was born.
And ever since that day, only sons of noble families
have served as knights.
That is not fair.
Fair or unfair, that's the way it is.
I'm sorry, Lancelot.
Truly I am.
Why do you want to be a knight so much?
When I was a boy, my village was attacked by raiders from northern plains.
They were slaughtered where they stood -
my father, my mother, everyone.
I alone escaped.
I vowed that day that never again would I be helpless in the face of tyranny.
I made swordcraft my life.
Every waking hour since that day I devoted to the art of combat.
When I was ready, I set forth for Camelot.
And now it seems my journey ends.
Everything I've fought for - wasted.
I give you my word,
whatever it takes, I will make this right.
Homework.
(spell)
Come on, come on yes!
It's, um, a real page-turner.
What's that?
This is your seal of nobility.
I don't understand.
Ladies and gentlemen, I give you Lancelot,
fifth son of Lord Eldred of Northumbira.
No, Merlin, no.
So you don't want to be knight then.
Of course I do!
What? The rules don't allow it?
Damn the rules. The rules are wrong.
But it's a lie. It's against everything that stands for.
You have as much right to be a knight as any man. I know it.
But the rules, Merlin...
We're not breaking the rules.
We're bending them.That's all.
You get your foot in the door.
After that, you'll be judged on your merit alone.
And if you succeed, if they make you a knight,
it'll be because you have earned it, noble or not.
I can't change the way things are done here,
but you can... if you let me help you.
This is very kind of you, uh...
Gwen.
Short for Guinevere. Ah.
Then thank you, Guinevere.
Don't thank me. Thank Merlin.
Merlin would do anything for anyone.
Sorry, can you raise your arms?
Thank you. Sorry.
I think it's great that Merlin's got you this chance.
We need men like you.
You do?
Well, not me personally but, you know, Camelot.
Camelot needs knights.
Not just Arthur and his kind,
but ordinary people like you and me.
I'm not a knight yet, my lady.
And I'm not a lady.
Sorry, I...
Ok, we're done.
I should have these ready in no time.
It's nice to meet you, Lancelot.
She seems lovely. Guievere.
Oh, yeah, yeah, she is.
And the best seamstress in Camelot, I promise.
Are you two...you know?
No. No, no.
Just friends.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
One.
Two.
Three.
You certainly look the part.
Doesn't he just?
I dont feel it.
That'll do for today.
Well done.
Here's your chance. Go for it.
Yes? Lancelot, fifth son of Lord Eldred of Northumbria.
Lance-a-lot?
My servant mentioned you.
Got your seal?
Sire.
Sluggish reactions.
On a battlefield, you'd be dead by now.
Come back when you're ready.
I'm ready now, sire.
You are, are you?
Fine. You can start by cleaning out the stables.
I'm sorry about Lancelot.
I could see you were upset.
Oh...you know, that's life.
You win some, you lose some.
You're taking it very well.
I have to say. Very mature.
Thank you, Gaius.
How'd it go?
He found work at the stables.
I see.
And the truth, before I lose my temper.
He's, uh... trying out for the knights.
The first code of Camelot has never been broken for any man.
What have you done, Merlin?
I bent the rules a little.
But they're wrong, they're unfair.
You bent the rules using magic?
It was nothing, honestly.
It was more of a trick than actual magic.
Your magic is not toy for you to use or abuse as you see fit.
I know. Then why did you do it?
I owe Lancelot my life.
I am paying for that debt the only way I can
by giving him the opportunity he deserves.
If you want to punish me for it, go ahead.
Not bad.
Would you like me sweep the guardhouse agian, sire?
It certainly needs sweeping.
First, I'd like you to kill me.
Sire.
Come on. Don't pretend you dont want to.
Hell, if I were you, I'd want to.
Come on.
Come on, Lancelot.
You're not beating a carpet.
Congratulations, Lancelot.
You just made basic trainning.
You're safe now. I promise.
How is she? OK.
What happened to these people?
Their village was attacked by a winged monster.
I'd hunt this thing, but I cant track a creature through the air.
You dont have to track it.
First Greensward, then Willowdale.
It's heading south towards the mouth of the valley.
To Camelot.
You must prepare your knights, Arthur.
Have faith, Father. We'll be ready.
The wings of an eagle and the body of a lion.
The beast is heading for Camelot.
It's fast and agile,
but big enough to hit and to hit hard.
Starting today on training routines,
we'll concertrate on an attack strategy.
We dont have much time.
Dismisssed.
Yes Lancelot.
Is there anything I can do, sire?
I knwo in the event of battle, only a knight may serve.
That's correct and you are not yet a knight,
which is why I'm bringing your test forward.
You can face me in the morning.
Well, here we are - your final challenge.
Succeed and you join the elite.
Fail and your journey ends here.
Lancelot, fifth son of Lord Eldred of Northumbria...
...your time starts now.
I'm sorry.
Shame.
Do you submit, sire?
On your knees.
Arise, Sir Lancelot, Knigh of Camelot.
Who is this man?
He seems to have come out of nowhere.
I know. He's been a bit of a surprise to all of us.
You do us a great honour, Sir Lancelot.
The knighthood is the very foundation of Camelot.
The honour is all mine, sire.
You father would be very proud.
Yes sire.
I've not seen Lord Eldred for many years,
longer than I'd imagined it seems.
Last time I saw him, he only had four sons.
Well...here I am.
Indeed you are.
And I've kept you too long already.
Enjoy the celebrations.
Sire.
Take this seal to Geoffrey of Monmouth, the court genealogist.
I want his opinion by morning.
Look at him, Gaius.
Dose Lancelot not deserve this moment?
I never said he didn't.
But destiny and deserts are not the same thing.
You played God, Merlin.
You set him on a path of your choosing.
You brought him triumph but the future is uncertain.
I dont know what it said in you invitation,
but in mine, it said celebration.
Point taken.
Don't come back too late.
All right.
Here's trouble.
Tell me, do you think her...beautiful?
Yes sire, I do.
Yeah, I suppose she is.
You know what? I think our Sir Lancelot might have eyes for you, Gwen.
Dont be silly. What if he did? Would it be so bad?
He's not really my type.
Well, there's a surprise.
Sometimes I wonder if you'd know your type,
if he was standing right next to you.
You're probably right.
Oh, thank you.
So come on - just for the sake of argument,
if you had to, Arthur or Lancelot?
I don't have to and I never will.
Oh, you are no fun, Gwen.
Ladies and gentlemen, please join me in a toast to our new recruit,
our new knight of Camelot, Sir Lancelot.
Two yards of ale? Two miles, more like.
Good morning gentlemen.
Dont look at it. Dont smell it, just down it in one.
Better? Good.
Can't have you nodding off first day on the job, Lancelot.
Sir Lancelot, if you dont mind.
What are you doing?
King's orders.
Stop!
Tell him what you told me.
These credentials are faked.
The seal itself is faultless.
Forgery of the highest possible standard,
but a forgery it must be.
There is no record of
a fifth son of Lord Eldred of Northumbria.
-Therefore, he... -Lied.
Do you deny it?
No, sire.
You've broken the first code of Camelot.
You've brought shame upon yourself and upon us.
You're not worthy of knighthood.
You never were and you never will be.
Get him out of my sight.
Sire...
Do you contest my judgment?
His deception was inexcusable.
But he meant no harm, sire. I'm sure of it.
He only wished to serve.
The first code is a sacred bond of trust.
It is what binds the knights together.
How can you trust a man who's lied to you?
I don't know what to say to you, Lancelot.
-You're not to blame. -Yes, I am.
I pushed you. I made you lie.
The choice was mine.
My punishment is mine to bear, and mine to bear alone.
I wish there was something I could do.
There is.
You can stop blaming yourself.
Merlin?
Whatever you do, you don't say I told you so.
I have no wish to gloat.
What's done is done.
Here, come and take a look at this.
I've realised my mistake.
I've been looking for the creature in the wrong place,
The records of all known living things in the kingdom.
Then I thought,
What about creatures only recorded in legend? In myth?
And I just discovered this.
That is it! That's the monster!
On me! On me!
Defence!
What's happening?
Charge!
You said your knights were the best in the land.
You proved that today.
All I know is it's still out there.
Let's not wait for it.
The kingdom has been menaced by this creature for too long.
We finish this now.
Sire, if I may?
Gaius?
I've researched this creature, sire.
I believe it to be a griffin.
A griffin?
What's in a name?
Griffin is a creature of magic.
I don't have time for this, physician.
It is born of magic, sire,
and it can only be killed by magic.
You are mistaken.
It's a creature of flesh and blood like any other.
Arthur proved that today.
I'm not so sure, father.
I think there may be some truth in what he says.
What truth?
The griffin was unharmed, sire.
Our weapons were useless against it.
Useless?
I think not.
No. It's tasted our steel once.
The next time will be its last.
When will your knights be ready to ride again?
An hour, maybe two.
Good. We finish this tonight.
Is it true...
that the griffin can only be killed by magic?
Yes, Merlin. I'm certain of it.
If Arthur rides out against it, he'll die.
Then he must be stopped.
Uther must see reason.
Where magic is concered, our king is blind to reason.
And yet,
magic is our only hope.
You're not suggesting...
It is your destiny, Merlin.
The true purpose of your magic.
You saw it, Gaius. I can't go up against that thing.
But if you do not, then Arthur will surely perish.
No, no. This is madness.
I don't have magic that powerful. There must be another way.
This's the only way.
Do you even care what's happening to me?
Do this Merlin! Do that Merlin! Kill the griffin, Merlin!
I just sit here warm my feet by fire
Merlin!
Merlin... you are the only thing I care about in all this world.
I would give my life for you without a thought.
But for what? I cant save Arthur.
It is not my destiny. You know.
I am sorry.
I dont know what else I can say.
Then I'll say it for you.
We have two hours to find a way to kill that thing.
I should have known. How could I have been so stupid?
You don't look like a knight!
-I'm sorry. -I'm sorry too.
Because you fight like a knight.
And I need... Camelot needs...
-The creature...-We could not kill it.
I have never faced its like.
I faced it myself, sire.
Some days past. I struck it full square.
I wondered how it endured.
There are those that believe this creature, this griffin,
Is a  creature of magic, that only magic can destroy it.
Do you believe this?
It doesnt matter what I believe, the use of magic is not permitted.
The knights must prevail with steel and sinew alone.
Sire...
There's a horse waiting outside.
Thank you. Thank you, sire.
Lancelot...take it and never return to this place.
No.
No, please, it's not my freedom I seek.
I only wish to serve with hornour.
I know.
Then let me ride with you.
I cannot.
My father knows nothing of this. I release you, but can do no more.
Now go before I change my mind.
There. You must do this for Arthur.
I've never cast a spell of enchantment this powerful.
Nothing less will kill it.
Here. Try.
You have it within you. I know you do.
Don't worry Merlin. We've plenty of time.
Sorry to disturb you, my lady.
Lancelot, What are you doing here?
There's no time, I need weapons, armour.
What's it about?
Arthur's in peril.
I must do what I can to protect him.
It's my duty, knight or not.
You really believe that, dont you?
Yes my lady.
Lancelot, I don't believe I've ever met your like before.
Guinevere, if I should not return...
Don't go Lancelot. Please.
But go I must.
It's time.
Dont worry, Merlin, I know you're trying.
And failing. If Arthur dies because I'm not good enough...
Merlin!
Merlin! Lancelot's ridding out to kill the griffin!
He's what?
Merlin!
I'm coming with you.
No, you're not.
Try and stop me.
You're not a soldier.
Suit yourself
Arthur needs all the help he can get. Now let's go.
For Camelot.
For Camelot!
Arthur!
Arthur
Well?
He's alive.
Ok, Merlin. It's now or never.
Bregdan anweald gafeluec.
Yes!
Lancelot.
Sire.
Yo did it!
You killed it. Lancelot!
You did it?
I did it.
Thank God!
You did it, my son. You did it!
Not I, Father. It was Lancelot.
What's he doing here?
Father, I can explain.
You! Wait outside.
You have no right to...
What are they doing?
Deciding my fate.
I confess it, sire. I released him. I'll take the consequences.
But surely Lancelot's actions change things.
They change nothing. He broke the code.
He laid down his life for me!
He served with honour.
I see you feel strongly about this, Arthur.
Under the circumstances, a pardon, perhaps.
No. Not good enough, Father.
You must restore Lancelot to his rightful place,
As a knight of Camelot.
Never! The law is the law. The code bends for no man!
Then the code is wrong!
They'll restore your knighthood, of course they will.
You killed the griffin.
But I didn't kill the griffin. you did.
That's ridiculous.
"Bregdan anweald..."? I heard you. I saw you.
Don't worry. Your secret's safe with me.
But I cannot take credit for what I did not do.
There'll be no more lies. No more deceit.
What are you going to do?
The only thing I can do.
What is this?
Let me speak!
Wait! I'll hear him.
Forgive me, sire.
I've come to bid you farewell.
What is this Lancelot?
I lied to you both, and now there is conflict between you.
I cannot bear that burden, as you should not bear mine.
I must start again, far from here.
Then maybe one day fate shall grant me another chance,
To prove myself a worthy knight of Camelot.
But, Lancelot, you've already proved that to us.
But I must prove it to myself.
Your Highness. Prince Arthur.
Gwen? Guinevere?
Lancelot?
Yes!
Come, Gwen. Busy day ahead.
Yes, my lady.
Perhaps you were right, Gaius.
I should never have got involved.
No, Merlin. I was wrong.
Lancelot needed you and you needed Lancelot.
Your destinies were entwined.
Will he ever return?
That I cannot say.
Till next time, then...
Sir Lancelot.
My name is Edwin Muirden and I have a remedy to cure all ills.
We cannot preserve her life for much longer.
She has hours, maybe less.
You have magic? I wonder what Uther will do. Probably have him burnt.
Find Edwin!
www.tvsubtitles.net