In a land of myth
and a time of magic,
the destiny of a great kingdom
rests on the shoulders
of a young boy.
His name...
Merlin.
Halt.
What are you saying?
Bandits.
Always watch your back.
Didn't they teach you that?
Won't you beg for your life?
A Knight of Camelot does not beg.
Indulge me.
I'd rather die.
Who am I to deny a man
his last request?
We must go
if we are to make Camelot by nightfall.
Arthur's Knights
Merlin - 2x11
The Witch's Quickening
All clear.
Carry on.
Take the north door.
Straight ahead.
Keep going.
Come on...
Hurry!
Halt!
Keep going. It's not much further.
It's not much further now.
Wait in the forest of Brechffa
by the fork on the north ridge.
Ready?
We're nearly there.
At the end of the corridor.
Morgana's chamber is next.
What do mean, you lost him?
He could be dangerous.
Morgana's...
You are...
Sorry.
Morgana's...
They're in Morgana's chambers.
- I thought I'd never see you again.
- I found him wandering in the woods.
Lost and alone.
Hunted by Uther's men.
- Who are you?
- My name is Alvarr.
I too have been hunted by Uther
since I was a child.
- You have magic?
- Yes, my lady.
As did my parents.
And their parents before them.
They were fortunate
to live in a time of peace.
Before your king declared war
on sorcery.
I too have known Uther's cruelty.
Magic...
is not a crime.
It's a gift.
I wish to walk free
and without fear.
The boy said you would understand.
What are you doing in Camelot?
You take a great risk in coming here.
We came to see you.
Are you sure about this?
Definitely.
I saw them with my own eyes.
- What were you doing there?
- I heard voices in my...
- In your?
- In my chambers.
I thought I should investigate.
Frankly, it's hard to believe.
For once, you've shown
some real initiative.
I will not stand by
and watch innocent people destroyed.
And I am not alone.
Many have already joined me.
Many more join every day.
This is a war you cannot win.
- Uther has an army at his disposal.
- It does not matter how many you are
if you wield
a weapon powerful enough.
When I was a child,
my parents told me of a crystal.
It was taken from the sorcerers
in the last days of the Great Purge.
Taken?
By Uther?
It is here...
in Camelot.
Locked in the vaults beneath us.
The vaults are impregnable.
You'd never get it out.
No, I could not.
But you could.
- Me?
- You are the king's ward.
No-one would suspect you.
You are our only hope.
What are you doing?
I'd reason to believe
there was an intruder in here.
Right now, the only intruder is you.
Camelot has been infiltrated.
Did you hear the warning bell?
Of course I did.
I was hoping I'd be safe in my chambers.
- Permit me to search the room?
- You'll do no such thing!
Did you really think that if someone
was in my room I wouldn't know?
Please accept my apologies.
I don't understand.
I'm sorry, Merlin.
Which bit didn't you understand?
The making a fool out of me
or making a fool out of yourself?
There was someone in there.
- I know there was.
- Word of advice, Merlin.
In the future,
stick to what you do best.
Nothing!
We owe you our lives, my lady.
You are safe for now.
Uther won't rest 'til he has killed you.
You will help us?
Please, Morgana.
We need you.
Yes. I will.
Of course I will.
- Late night?
- You could say that.
I hear there was a disturbance,
an intruder in the city.
Yeah, I heard talking...
in my head.
They had magic?
I recognised the voice.
It was Mordred.
The druid boy?
What's he doing here?
He was guiding someone
to Morgana's chamber.
You're sure?
- She and the boy had a kind of bond.
- Yeah, but this...
- is more than that.
- What do you mean?
What if they'd been caught?
Whatever they were doing,
they were prepared to die for it.
Merlin, I was looking for Arthur.
He's out training.
- Of course.
- He trains every day.
Same time, same place.
I just wanted to apologise
for last night.
Another time, perhaps?
I'm starving.
You know what they say.
Good food takes time to prepare.
And this taste sensation
took exactly how long?
Nearly five minutes.
Really? Five minutes.
You need that long, you see,
to let it thicken.
Thicken?
The Crystal of Neahtid.
The locks... are not damaged.
What does that tell you?
It tells me
that somebody stole my keys.
Was it precious this crystal?
Of course it was!
It wouldn't been down here otherwise.
Right.
Whoever it was they knew exactly
what they were looking for.
Apparently.
Apparently?
Is that all you've got to say?
Tell me, Merlin,
whose job is it to ensure
my chambers are locked at all times?
Whose job is it to ensure
that something like this never happens?
Sorry!
You're sorry?!
That's not good enough.
- Did they force their way in?
- No, Sire.
How did they gain
access to the vault?
- They stole the keys.
- How is that possible?!
Someone broke into my chambers.
This is a grievous loss.
The Crystal of Neahtid
was locked away for good reason.
- Why is it so important?
- It is an instrument of magic.
In the days of the Purge,
sorcerers died trying to protect it.
Whatever it is,
it's important to them.
I'll search the town.
Find out what I can.
This crystal cannot fall
into enemy hands.
Yes, Sire.
- Thank you.
- For what exactly?
Lying to my father
to save your worthless hide?
If you put me in that position again,
I'll clap you in irons myself.
You'd better hope
we find that crystal.
- Morgana stole the crystal?
- I'm certain of it.
I caught her in Arthur's chambers.
She must have taken his keys.
- Can you prove any of this?
- Not exactly, but...
But she did it.
I'd bet my life on it.
You go accusing the King's ward
without proof, that's you'd be doing.
I know. You're right.
It doesn't make sense.
Why would Morgana
steal such a thing?
Uther said
it's an instrument of magic.
There are many legends
about the crystal.
Is it some kind of weapon?
That I don't know.
- You've heard of it?
- Indeed.
The sorcerers of the past believed
it held the secret of time.
- What did they mean by that?
- I'm not sure.
The crystal is an artefact
of the Old Religion.
There is only one
that could tell you more.
I need your help.
I am sure you do, young warlock.
But first you must honour
your promise.
I said I would set you free
and I will.
When?
When I know that Camelot is safe.
Please, trust me.
Why?
Because you don't have a choice.
What is it...
that you wish to know?
What is the Crystal of Neahtid?
To those who know how to use it,
the crystal holds great knowledge.
What kind of knowledge?
The knowledge of what is,
what has been
and what is yet to come.
Do you mean
it can show you the future?
Amongst other things, yes.
The crystal has been stolen.
By whom?
The Lady Morgana.
That witch does not have the power
to wield the crystal.
- Does the druid boy?
- Mordred?
It is possible. Why do you ask?
I believe that they are involved
in this together.
Once before I warned you
of the druid boy.
It is his destiny
to bring about Arthur's doom.
It may be that time is upon you.
What?
The ancient prophecies
speak of an alliance...
of Mordred and Morgana
united in evil.
But this union must be stopped...
whatever the cost.
- Thank you, Gwen. That'll be all.
- Nearly done.
- It's fine, Gwen. You can go.
- It won't take a moment.
I said you can go!
... My lady.
It is my hope,
that with time,
Mordred will master the crystal.
When he does,
we will strike Uther down.
Uther and all who serve him.
All who serve him?
If we are to win this war,
there can be no half measures.
I can see this troubles you.
Yes, it does.
We fight for our very survival.
As do you.
The boy, he told me you have magic.
You need not be afraid.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I have become so used
to concealing the truth.
Believe me,
I understand what that feels like.
Every day I must look Uther
in the eye knowing...
that if he were to discover
who I really am, he'd have me killed.
You have been very brave.
I don't want to be brave.
I just want to be myself.
I don't want to be alone any more.
You are not alone.
You are here with us.
You need never be alone again.
I must be heading back.
The castle will be waking soon.
Farewell then...
my lady Morgana.
Where's Morgana?
She could not stay.
- Will we be seeing her again?
- Yes, Mordred.
You can be sure of that.
Nicely done.
- You played her well.
- It was not hard.
She is very beautiful, after all.
Alvarr has a fearsome reputation.
- You know of him?
- He is a sorcerer.
And he and his band of renegades
have threatened to overthrow the King.
- He sounded pretty determined.
- He is a fanatic.
And his supporters
follow him unthinkingly,
- blinded by his charisma.
- Well, it worked on Morgana.
So it would seem.
And the druid boy.
Alvarrthinks the boy can harness
the power of the crystal.
We can't let this happen, Merlin.
What can we do?
We can bend the truth a little.
You know the whereabouts of it?
I believe so.
I see.
How did you come
by this information?
In my capacity as physician
I have dealings with many people.
They hear things, Sire,
and they see things.
Last night,
I was confronted by one such man
who told me that the crystal
had been stolen by a band of renegades,
led by a man called Alvarr.
- Who exactly was this informant?
- I think...
it would be only fair
to protect their identity, Sire.
If news of their betrayal
reached the renegades,
it could indeed endanger their life.
Very well.
Where is Alvarr hiding?
He was last seen
in the Valley of Chemary, Sire.
Summon the guards, Arthur.
I want this investigated without delay.
Thank you, Gaius.
Once again, I'm in your debt.
You're not seriously thinking
of going on this mission?
No, I'm not thinking about it,
I am going on this mission.
But you're chasing a rumour.
True. But for now it's the only lead
we have to go on.
You'll be wasting your time,
I assure you.
- I never knew you cared.
- What?
I can look after myself, you know.
It's the combination of raw talent
and hard training makes me...
Yes, I know.
That makes you so utterly obnoxious.
Gaius had better be right
about this.
What brings you here?
Arthur's been sent to capture
the crystal.
The Knights of Camelot
are almost upon us.
- How has this happened?
- I don't know.
I only know
that we've been betrayed.
- How much time do we have?
- An hour. Maybe two.
I cannot say for sure.
- Then we must be prepared for them.
- What can I do to help?
You can flee
while you still have the chance.
I am grateful
for all that you have done
but a battlefield
is no place for you.
I don't know why I bring you.
You spend the whole time terrified.
- I am not terrified.
- Yes, you are.
- I can tell you are.
- No, you can't.
If not, you'd be talking rubbish.
Well, I am talking rubbish as usual!
I mean,
I am talking as usual.
So, clearly, I'm not scared.
- Where now?
- No idea.
I thought Gaius gave you directions.
He did.
He just didn't tell me
about this part.
Merlin, this is your fault.
They're coming.
Warn the others.
The crystal.
They're coming.
- The renegade camp...
- They're coming! Hurry!
That way.
- And you know this because?
- I know it because...
Because of...
I give up.
Because of this!
It's a footprint.
Who says it belongs to a renegade?
There's more.
Follow me.
I told you.
Didn't I tell you?
What are you doing?
Well, whoever was here,
they're not here any more.
Yes, they are.
Take cover!
Run, Mordred!
I shall never forgive this, Emrys,
and I shall never forget.
- Give me the crystal.
- Why?
What use is it to you?
You are a fool! How many lives
have been lost this day...
for what?
You cannot wield the crystal.
You do not have the power.
None of you do!
Check the horses
are fed and watered.
Sorry?
- Not the right answer.
- What?
Something on your mind, is there?
When we entered the camp,
it was a trap.
They knew we were coming.
- Yeah, so?
- How did they know?
Well, they're sorcerers,
aren't they?
Probably used magic or something.
I need you to guard this with your life.
Why me?
- I can't guard it while I'm asleep.
- Neither can I.
Who said anything
about you sleeping?
So you admit to stealing
the Crystal of Neahtid?
I do.
You admit to plotting
against your King?
I do.
And you acted alone?
You were not aided or abetted
by any citizen of Camelot?
I acted...
alone.
I find you guilty of treason.
You are an enemy of Camelot, Alvarr.
You are sentenced to death.
Then I die with honour.
To be an enemy of Camelot
is no crime.
Take him.
You are the criminal.
How many more must you kill
before you are satisfied?
He was guilty.
He confessed his crimes.
- You heard him as well as I.
- His only crime was to defy you.
Why are you defending this man?
He was a sworn foe of Camelot.
You know this.
Is it any wonder he wanted you dead?
You who have persecuted his kind,
day after day, year after year.
I will hear no more of this,
Morgana.
Because you are an arrogant fool!
You are deaf and blind to the people
you profess to serve and protect.
- They will tolerate it no longer.
- I said "enough"!
They are rising up against you.
From this day forward,
I do not know you.
From this day forward, I disown you.
You will go to your chambers!
And you, Uther...
You will go to hell.
Is something interesting in there?
Sorry.
- What's the matter?
- It's the crystal.
It harbours a terrible power, Gaius.
But it's locked away now.
It can do no harm.
Unless the damage
has already been done.
I held it.
I knew I shouldn't.
I knew no good would come of it but...
it compelled me to look.
I couldn't resist it.
I saw things.
Terrible things.
Then you've already paid the price.
What I saw has not yet come to pass.
And I am scared, Gaius. I am...
really scared
of what the future may hold.
There is nothing on this Earth
that can know all possible futures.
- Even the crystal.
- But what I saw...
- It was so real.
- And it was real.
But it wasone reality.
The future is as yet unshaped.
It is we that shape it.
It is you....
the decisions you make,
the actions you take.
Remember that.
Eat your soup before it gets cold.
Could I have my sleeping draught?
- I didn't think you needed it any more.
- Last night the nightmares returned.
Sleep well.
Please,
this is not an official visit.
I'd like to see the prisoner.
Sorry, my lady,
the prisoner is to see no-one.
- The King's orders.
- That doesn't apply to the King's ward!
Thank you.
This might help to ease
the long night ahead.
My lady.
I was not expecting you.
I have come to say goodbye.
It was gracious of you
to think of me.
It will not be easy...
but you must prepare yourself
for what lies ahead.
I am prepared.
I have done what I can
to ease your passage.
I could not ask for more.
Good luck.
My thoughts will be with you.
Thank you...
my lady.
We've searched the citadel,
the town and every corner of Camelot.
- But he's gone.
- Yes, father.
How?
How has he escaped?
It appears
that the guards were drugged.
That means he had help.
Someone...
here in Camelot.
I'm afraid it looks that way.
Let this be understood...
whoever has done this,
they have betrayed me.
They have betrayed the Kingdom.
If I ever discover who it was,
they will rue the day
they were born.
I'm waiting, Merlin!
You gave your word!
Now set me free!
When the fires of Idirsholas burn,
the Knights of Medhir
will ride again.
It must be the work of magic.
Camelot's end is nigh
and there's nothing
you can do about it.