In a land of myth
and a time of magic,
the destiny of a great kingdom
rests on the shoulders
of a young boy.
His name...
Merlin.
Here is some extra blankets,
you might be cold...
Arthur's Knights
Merlin - 2x03
The Nightmare Begins
I came back in with some blankets.
- There was a candle, but I put it out.
- Are you sure?
I blew it out, I swear.
Gwen's been Morgana's servant for years.
If she says she did it, I believe her.
She could've been burnt alive.
Lightning that struck the castle roof
last night, could've started the fire.
Perhaps.
What other explanation is there?
Someone started the fire
deliberately.
- How did they reach Morgana's chambers?
- I don't know. There are many guards,
- it shouldn't be possible.
- Yet they managed to do so.
- I can't explain it.
- Well, I can.
They used magic.
Arrest all those under suspicion.
That's gonna take time.
My ward has been attacked.
Time is something we do not have!
What I don't understand, Morgana,
is how the fire started
in the first place.
It happened so quickly.
- It was terrifying.
- It's all right.
You're safe now.
You're the only person
I've told about my dreams.
I know I can trust you.
Yes, of course you can.
It was me.
I set the room alight,
I started the fire.
I don't understand.
Did you knock a candle over?
No. That's not what happened.
I did it just...
by looking at it.
The flame leapt higher.
It could've been a gust of wind.
It wasn't. It was me.
It was magic.
- My child...
- I'm not a child!
Last night was an accident.
It had nothing to do with you.
How could it have?
I am going to draw you up
a fresh remedy that will
make you feel better. I promise.
You must trust me.
I was helping clear up
Morgana's chambers earlier.
The window was blown out
into the courtyard below.
That's odd, isn't it?
If lightning struck the window, glass
would have fallen inside of the window.
It was magic. You know it was.
And, more importantly, so does she.
- Morgana knows nothing for certain.
- It's even worse.
She isn't sure what happens to her
and it's tearing her apart.
What would you have me do?
Talk to her.
Tell her she'll be OK,
tell her that her powers aren't
something to be afraid of.
I can't.
- Maybe I could speak to her.
- No, Merlin, you can't!
I know what she's going through.
You must never tell your secret,
not to anyone.
- If not me, then someone else.
- Who?
This is against the way.
Magic is outlawed.
- You forgot it?
- Some still practise it.
What about the druids?
They help people like this.
Uther's vowed to destroy them.
The druids cannot help her,
it would be suicide.
Then who can?
I will,
as I've always done.
You need to be honest with her.
Are you so certain
that you know better than me?
Because I went through
the same thing!
I know exactly how
she's feeling right now.
You cannot get involved in this.
No good can come of it.
I mean it, Merlin.
Stay out of it!
I need you... to...
- What are you hiding behind your back?
- Nothing. See?
What are you up to?
Nothing, honestly.
I would never lie to you.
I respect you too much for that.
- You wanted me to do something?
- My chainmail needs cleaning.
Well... I'll see to it right away.
How is she?
I've never seen her
like this before.
- I'm scared to leave her on her own.
- Is there anything I can do to help?
I'd better get back to her.
I'll make sure
she knows who they're from.
I can stay, if that would
make you feel better.
You've done so much already.
I don't mind.
I'll be fine.
Really.
Take the candle.
Is Gaius here?
He's not here,
- he should be back soon.
- I must speak to him! Where is he?
He's gone to see the King.
What's wrong?
You can trust me, Morgana.
You know you can.
I'm scared.
I don't understand anything
any more.
I need to know what's happening.
Please...
Gaius will be back soon.
He'll help you.
He won't. I don't want any more
remedies! They won't do any good.
It's magic.
- What?
- I'm your friend, I don't make this up.
Of course.
Then you believe me?
You think it's magic too?
Please,
I just need to hear someone say it,
so I don't feel like I'm imagining it!
I really wish
I could say something...
Wait!
I need your help.
Do you know where the druids are?
First you must tell me
why you seek them.
- That doesn't matter.
- It does to me.
I need to ask them something.
I've lived
more than a thousand years,
seen civilisations rise and fall.
Do not believe
that you can lie to me.
I need their help.
Someone I care about
needs their help.
You speak of the witch,
the Lady Morgana.
She's not a witch!
She's my friend.
She cannot be trusted.
What makes you say that?
It would be better if the witch...
Stop calling her that!
It would be better if the witch
never knew
- the true extent of her powers.
- You're wrong.
I know her. She has a good heart.
You failed to heed my advice in
the past
and it brought grave consequences.
I won't abandon her!
I will not give you
the help you seek.
If you pursue this course of action,
you do so alone.
- Are you sure this is all of them?
- Names and last known dwelling places.
My father suspects the fire
was started by sorcery.
Indeed, Sire.
I included details of everyone suspected
of consorting with sorcerers, witches
or druids.
Gather the men.
We'll arrest them immediately.
I told you to do that yesterday.
I didn't have time,
I was cleaning the stables.
That's strange.
Cos a little bird told me
you were somewhere else.
Mucking out the stables is strange
and a talking bird isn't?
- What we said about you being funny?
- I shouldn't.
So where are my flowers?
Your flowers?
I heard Morgana got some.
I assumed you'd be putting them
in all the rooms.
Or is she the only one to receive
a token of your affections?
What? It's not a...
token of anything,
affection or otherwise.
I see.
Why trying to hide them
from me yesterday?
I wasn't. I was just... I didn't want
you to get the wrong impression.
What's the right impression?
That... I was trying
to cheer her up after the fire.
Pick them yourself?
Maybe.
I was only trying to be nice.
Sword.
That'll be all.
- Move and I kill you.
- Forridel?
Who are you?
There is no time to explain,
we have to get out of here.
- The King's men are coming for you!
- Check in there!
- How did you know this was for me?
- I'm Prince Arthur's servant.
You took a great risk. Thank you.
I'm just sorry
I couldn't help them all.
- We'd better go.
- Wait. I need your help.
I want to contact the druids.
- I know nothing about them.
- Don't lie to me.
- I'm not lying.
- I need it, else you'd be under arrest.
You know I'm not a spy for Uther.
I'm a friend of the druids.
I need their help.
What do you want to know?
Gaius asked me to deliver this.
I don't need any potion, thank you.
Ignore what I said last night.
I had a nightmare. I was upset.
I know.
I haven't said anything to anyone.
I'm sorry. It's usually Gwen that has
to deal with me when I'm like this.
I don't mind.
Maybe I could help.
I doubt that.
You'd be surprised.
I understand.
I realise... how frightening all this
must be for you. Especially for you.
Why especially for me?
You're the King's ward. You know
his hatred of magic better than anyone.
That's what you think
has been happening to me?
The dreams, the fire.
You think it was magic!
- I'm not saying that.
- But it could be, couldn't it?
I really wouldn't know.
- But there are people who do.
- Who?
What about the druids?
They help people like you.
None of their kind would dare
show their face in Camelot.
But I know where you can find them.
The guards have completed
their search. No trace of her.
Encircle the city.
No-one gets in or out.
- You sent for me, Sire.
- Yes.
What time did you deliver
this sleeping draught to Morgana?
The guards said that Merlin delivered it
after she retired to her chambers.
So she was safe, then?
I suppose she must have been.
I didn't ask you to take
this to Morgana last night.
I used some initiative.
Those warning bells are ringing
because Uther thinks
that Morgana's been kidnapped.
- You don't seem overly concerned.
- She can look after herself.
- What have you done?
- What you refused to.
I helped her.
This ends now.
People's lives are at risk,
Morgana's included.
Where is she?
She's gone to the Forest of Ascetir
to find the druids.
I told you not to get involved!
I had to. You wouldn't even acknowledge
she had magic!
- For good reason!
- No, you don't understand.
You don't understand what it's like.
The years before I came here
were the loneliest of my life.
Morgana is the king's ward.
Her situation
is completely different.
I've got you, she hasn't.
I've always taken good care
of Morgana.
It's not the same.
Everything that's good and right
about magic,
I've learnt from you.
I'd be lost without you.
Like she is now.
Do you understand why I did it?
I do.
But that doesn't mean
I don't fear the consequences.
- Have the suspects been arrested?
- Nearly. A few have gone to ground.
Issue a proclamation.
"All the prisoners will be executed
"unless the Lady Morgana
is returned to Camelot."
I'll see to it, sire.
Come on, Merlin!
Out of your bed.
You'll be late for work.
I'm not going to hurt you.
You've hurt your leg.
Try not to move it.
- What happened?
- You were stung by a Serket.
I came to help.
My name's Aglain.
Relax, Morgana.
You're safe now.
Who told you my name?
I did.
You.
When the Serket attacked last night,
Mordred was able
to sense your distress...
with his mind.
Hello, Morgana.
Did you hear that?
- How did you do?
- We don't always need words
to speak to one another.
Now I can take care of you...
like you did me.
There's some confusion
as to how it was broken.
- By the looks of these...
- There is no confusion.
It was magic.
The same one that was used
to start the fire in Morgana's chambers.
- Where does the trail lead?
- The Forest of Ascetir.
We've long suspected
that the druids have hidden there.
The trail will lead us
straight to them.
Take no prisoners.
It's time we rid ourselves
of these druids once and for all.
Where's Merlin?
He's not well.
- He's still upset about Morgana.
- We all are.
Tell him to stop pining,
pull himself together
and get back to work.
Is anybody there?
... aren't something to be
afraid of...
... now I can take care of you...
... a great risk...
- ... like you did me...
- ... in time you will learn...
What would you like to know?
Any word from Arthur?
No, sire, not yet.
But they haven't been gone long.
Yes. Of course.
Why are you so certain
that she's been kidnapped?
What other possibility?
She was upset after the fire,
she could have gone of her own accord.
That's not her.
In all her years, I've never known her
run from anything.
Takes after her father too much
for that.
You haven't let Gorlois down.
You've looked after that girl
as if she were your own.
That is what she's become.
If she were to die,
a huge part of me would die with her.
- I trust you slept well?
- Better than I've done in days.
Here, this might make you feel
more at home.
They're surprised to see you here,
if not a little afraid.
Your King would have us killed.
They have nothing to fear from me.
I do not share
Uther's hatred of magic.
I imagine you wouldn't.
These forests are dangerous.
What brings you so far from Camelot?
I'm searching for answers.
I hoped the druids
might be able to give them to me.
Come.
Keep moving!
This way.
What would you like to know?
Why I can see the future
in my dreams.
Why I'm able to start fires
with my mind.
People who are able to do this
are few and far between.
You have a gift.
Is it magic?
Of a kind, yes.
But it will be many years
before you're able to understand it,
let alone use it.
Isn't something to be afraid of.
It is if you have Uther
as your guardian.
- If he found out he'd have me killed.
- He won't.
But if he did...
We won't let that happen.
You're safe here.
You shouldn't be scared of Uther.
You should pity him.
Pity? Why?
Because he's a broken man,
consumed by fear.
His hatred of magic
has driven goodness from his heart.
I've always been taught
that magic is evil.
That it corrupts your soul.
Uther told you this.
Just because he decrees it,
doesn't make it so.
In time you will learn
that magic isn't a dark art
that must be shrouded in secrecy.
It can be a force for good.
Remember the King's orders.
No prisoners.
- What are you doing here?!
- I've come to take you back.
I'm afraid
you've had a wasted journey.
- I'm never going back.
- You have to.
Why? You're the one
who said I should seek out the druids.
I never realised
what the repercussions would be.
What repercussions?
The King thinks
you've been kidnapped.
He won't stop.
He's arrested dozens of people.
He's gonna execute them all.
If I return,
the same fate awaits me.
Uther doesn't need to know about this.
I won't tell a soul.
I'm sorry.
I'm never going back.
These are my people.
They're like me.
I don't feel so alone here.
Do you understand?
Better than anyone.
We must go.
Who are you?
It's all right, he's a friend.
What's wrong?
Arthur is coming.
Your friend has led him
straight to us.
Hello, Emrys.
This way!
- Keep moving.
- My leg, it's too painful!
- I'll try to create a diversion.
- No, you can't!
You carry on,
it's my fault they're here. Go.
- Go!
- I'll never forget this.
There!
Over there!
- I can't go on!
- We're not leaving you behind.
Please...
They're coming!
We have her!
We have the Lady Morgana!
I was so, so worried about you.
You were right.
The druids kidnapped her.
My lady.
I wanted to check you were OK.
I'm fine.
- What was said at the woods...
- You can trust me, I won't tell anyone.
Thank you, Merlin.
I know now who I really am.
And it isn't something
to be scared of.
Maybe one day people will come
to see magic as a force for good.
It's good to have you back.
Thank you, Merlin.
Sleep well.
This has to stop.
The King would have your head
if he found out,
and there's no point denying it.
Denying what?
Your affections
for the Lady Morgana.
Right...
Take a bit of advice from someone
who knows about women.
If such a person existed, I would.
Stick to girls who are more...
How can I put it?
- ... on your level.
- Thanks.
She can't be your friend...
let alone anything else.
I know.
You can't hide anything from me.
Wouldn't dream of it.
I'm sorry, Gaius.
- I thought you'd be angry with me.
- I was.
Right up to the moment
you walked in.
Then I was just grateful
that you're back safe and sound.
Morgana knows the truth.
The druids told her she has magic.
Sorry.
It's not your fault.
You were only doing
what you thought was right.
We both were.
- What happens now?
- You must take care of her,
and hope Uther never discovers the truth
about her powers.
Morgana's party hasn't returned.
There's no sign of her.
Where's Guinevere?
How can I admit that
I think about her all the time?
Lancelot!
I would die for you 100 times over.
Release the wildereon!