myth and the time of magic,
the destiny of a great kingdom
rests on the shoulders of a young boy.
His name...
Merlin
Do you have my supplies ready?
We must leave the
city without delay.
Everything you asked for -
it's all here. I'm sorry.
Seize him! Stop there!
Run! Run, run!
Help!
Help me!
Please.
'Please. '
'You have to help me. '
'Help me. '
Search in there.
Take the other side.
You, did you see a boy run in here?
'They're searching for me. '
'Why are they after you?'
'They're going to kill me. '
Guards!
In here.
'This way. '
'Run. Run!'
Hey. There he is!
Alert the rest of the guards!
In there.
Quick, down there.
We've got 'im.
Have you forgotten
how to knock, Merlin?
The guards are after him.
I didn't know what to do.
My Lady?
In there.
Sorry to disturb you, My Lady.
We're searching for a young Druid
boy. We believe he came this way.
I haven't seen anyone.
It's just me and my maid.
- Best keep the door locked.
- Of course. Thank you.
The Druid was only in Camelot to
collect supplies. He meant no harm.
- Is it necessary to execute him?
- Absolutely necessary.
Those who use magic
cannot be tolerated.
The Druids are a peaceful people.
Given the chance, they would
return magic to the kingdom.
They preach peace,
but conspire against me.
- We cannot appear weak.
- Showing mercy can be a strength.
Our enemies will
not see it that way.
We have a responsibility
to protect this kingdom.
Executing the Druid
will send out a clear message.
Find the boy.
Search every inch of the city.
People of Camelot,
the man before you is guilty
of using enchantments and magic.
Under our law, the sentence
for this crime is death.
We're still searching
for his accomplice.
Anyone found harbouring the boy
is guilty of conspiracy,
and will be executed as a traitor.
Let this serve
as a warning to your people.
You have let your fear of magic
turn to hate.
- I pity you.
- I can't watch this.
No!
Do you know much about the Druids?
Very little.
They're very secretive people.
Especially now they're
being hunted by Uther.
Merlin, please tell me you haven't
got yourself mixed up in this.
Me? No. Mixed up in what?
For someone with such a big secret,
you are a terrible liar.
Well, I haven't done anything.
Merlin...
I heard the boy calling out.
He was nowhere to be seen,
but I could hear him...
like he was inside my mind.
Yes, I've heard of this ability.
The Druids look for children with
such gifts to serve as apprentices.
While they're searching for this
boy, you must be especially careful
otherwise it will be your head
on the block.
- I'm always careful. You know me.
- Yes, Merlin, unfortunately I do.
- How is he?
- He's sleeping.
He's very pale.
I worry he may have
lost a lot of blood.
- Has he said anything at all?
- Nothing.
He won't even tell me his name.
You know, er, for a moment there
earlier,
I thought you were going
to hand us over to the guards.
I'm glad you have
so much faith in me, Merlin.
No, no, sorry. Erm,
I meant, you're the King's ward.
You're taking a huge risk
helping the boy.
I wouldn't see an
innocent child executed.
What harm has he ever done anyone?
Uther believes he has magic,
and that makes him guilty.
- Uther's wrong.
- You believe that?
What if magic
isn't something you choose?
What if it chooses you?
- Why're you looking at me like that?
- Nothing.
Why are you helping him?
It was a spur of the moment decision.
What d'you think we should do
with him? He can't stay here.
We have to find a way to
get him back to his people.
You seem troubled, Morgana.
Is something wrong?
No, My Lord.
I am sorry I'm not better company.
I was merely concerned
for your welfare.
Thank you, My Lord. All is well.
What news of the hunt
for the Druid boy?
We have conducted
an extensive search.
The boy is nowhere to be found.
- You mean you failed to find him?
- Perhaps he's already left the city.
You're telling me that a wounded boy
is able to escape the city?
Nonsense, someone's hiding him.
I want him found.
He's just a boy.
What harm can he do?
He is a Druid, so he's dangerous.
The Druids would see your
father's kingdom destroyed.
I had no idea you were
such an authority on Druids.
Morgana is right.
Double your efforts.
Yes, father.
Keep searching until you find him.
- How long has he been burning up?
- Since early this morning.
I think his wound may be infected.
We need Gaius
before it gets any worse.
We can't involve Gaius.
It's too dangerous.
If he finds out,
he'll execute me himself.
We need to get him out of Camelot,
and we can't while he's sick.
We need a physician.
I'll treat him.
treat an infected wound?
Not exactly, but I'm a fast learner.
Arthur! To what do
I owe this pleasure?
It's not a social call.
I'm looking for the Druid boy.
- You're not searching my chambers.
- Don't take it personally.
I have to search the entire castle.
It will only take a few minutes.
I'm not having you
mess up my things.
I'm not interested in your things,
I'm just looking for any evidence
that the Druid boy's in the castle.
Perhaps he's hiding in your chambers.
They're such a mess,
you'd never know.
It's hardly my fault I have
such a lazy idiot for a servant.
If you can't even find your own
servant how can you find the boy?
I'm touched
by your confidence.
But the sooner we get started,
the sooner we'll be finished.
Well, I'll save you the trouble.
Trust me,
if I could find him, I would.
The Druid boy's hiding
behind the screen.
I'm sure your father would love to
know how you wasted your time
by rifling through
my things. Go on.
So you can have the satisfaction
of making me look a fool?
You don't need any help
looking like a fool.
What are you waiting for?
Take a look.
Why don't you go back
to brushing your hair,
or whatever it is
that you do all day?
Bye, Arthur.
Good luck with the search!
Bites, bruises, burns, wounds...
Infections...
Ah, there you are. I need you
to pick some heather for me.
Can I do it later?
I was just going out.
Who's had this book out?
It was me. I was doing some reading.
Oh? I'd given up hoping you might
take more of an interest in my work.
No. It's fascinating.
Merlin, you are riddle
wrapped inside a mystery.
That's me. I was getting
some cleaning supplies.
Arthur's been complaining
about the state of his chambers.
We're not missing the chance
to begin your education.
- Really. I should go.
- Sit.
We'll start
with some basic anatomy...
What took you so long?
Sorry. Once Gaius gets talking about
anatomy, there's no stopping him.
- Sure you know what you're doing?
- I'm doing my best.
I'll get you some more water.
'Thank you, Emrys. '
'Emrys? Why do you call me that?'
'Among my people, that is your name. '
'You know who I am. How?'
Speak to me.
I don't know if he can't speak,
or... he's just too scared to.
Hello?
Do you have to do that?
You scared the life out of me.
The young warlock. No doubt you're
here about the Druid boy.
- How did you know?
- Like you, I hear him speak.
Why does he call me Emrys?
Because that is your name.
I'm pretty sure my name's
Merlin, always has been.
- You have many names.
- Do I?
How does the boy know who I am?
I've never even met any Druids.
There is much written about you
that you have yet to read.
You should not protect this boy.
Why?
He has magic. He's just like me.
You and the boy are as different
as day and night.
- What do you mean?
- Heed my words, Merlin.
Why should I not protect him?
Let me care for him for a while.
You need to sleep.
You'll make yourself sick
if you go on like this.
- His fever's getting worse.
- 'Morgana. '
- Did you hear that?
- What?
- He said my name.
- Did he? I didn't hear anything.
It's Merlin.
- How is he?
- He's getting weaker.
What you did yesterday hasn't worked.
We have to ask Gaius for help.
After all you've done,
you can't give up now.
Please!
If he doesn't receive
treatment, he'll die.
OK.
The search for this Druid boy
is becoming a real nuisance.
With all the extra security
around the castle,
it's taking me
twice as long to do my round.
Is that everything?
Morgana's hiding the
Druid boy in her chambers.
When you say that Morgana's
hiding the Druid boy,
- I take it you're helping her?
- Sort of.
You promised you
wouldn't get involved.
I know. I'm sorry. I had no choice.
Every guard in Camelot
is searching for this boy,
and you're harbouring him
under their very noses.
Can't you see how dangerous that is?
What were you thinking of?
- Was I supposed to hand him over?
- You think you can save this boy?
Who's going to save you?
You're saying it's wrong
to harbour a young magician?
The difference is, Merlin,
that your magic is still secret,
although it's a wonder how,
considering how careless you are.
The boy's hurt. He's really sick.
I've tried to treat him.
We need your help.
So now you want me
to risk my neck, too?
I wish the boy no harm,
but it's too dangerous.
If you don't, we may as well
hand him over, cos he'll die anyway.
You didn't turn your back on me.
Please don't turn your back on him.
I will treat the boy, but as soon
as he's well, get him out of Camelot.
And woe betide anyone
caught helping him.
Well, one thing we know for certain.
What's that?
You're no physician.
Halt there.
The guards are searching
everyone leaving the town.
There is another way out.
There's a secret door in the armoury.
It leads to the lower town.
No. It's too dangerous.
I'll do it.
I'm good with secret
doors and things.
If you are caught,
Uther will execute you.
The boy's my responsibility.
I'll smuggle him out of the castle.
You'll need a key for the door.
- Who has it?
- Arthur.
Is there any bread? What was that?
- What?
- There was a sound.
Was there?
What is that?
Can't you hear it?!
- I can't hear anything.
- Are you deaf?
It's like a jangling sound.
- There!
- What?
I thought I saw something.
- What was that?
- What?
A different sound, like a splash.
Bread?
It'll have to do.
I fear I've put you in danger
without asking how you feel about it.
I'm sorry.
I know how it feels
to face the threat of execution.
It's Merlin.
We're going to get you
out of Camelot.
I won't let anything
bad happen to you. I promise.
Are you ready?
Did you get the keys?
Yeah. The door is behind the
shield at the far end of the armoury.
I'll pack you some food
and water for the journey.
Be careful.
I hope they're OK.
Morgana really cares about the boy.
I've never seen her
this way with anyone.
I'm sure
she just wants to protect him.
Hmm.
A servant saw someone entering.
They had a boy with them.
Sound the warning bell.
They're coming.
There's enough food for three days.
Your horse is fed and watered.
I'll take you to it.
- No point in us all risking it.
- What about you?
- I'll take my chances.
- Morgana...
I couldn't live with myself if
anything happened to either of you.
We must go.
'Goodbye, Emrys. '
Fan out.
Halt, or I'll run you through.
Show yourself.
Let him go. I beg you.
He's just a child.
Restrain them.
All this time, you've been
hiding the boy in my own palace.
- How could you betray me like this?
- I would not see him executed.
I've treated you like a daughter.
Is this how you repay me?
I did what I thought was right.
To conspire
with my enemies against me?
He's just a boy.
- He is a Druid.
- Is that such a crime?
His kind would see me dead
and you would help them.
Then punish me... but spare the boy.
I beg you.
Make arrangements for the boy
to be executed tomorrow morning.
No! Please. He's done nothing.
Let this be a lesson to you.
You don't have to do this.
Do you hear me?
I want him executed at dawn.
Yes, father.
What have these people done to you?
Why are you so full of hate?
Enough!
I will not hear another word!
Do not speak to me until
you are ready to apologise.
I promised that I wouldn't
let anything bad happen.
- You tried your best.
- It's not enough.
He's in jail now.
There's nothing more we can do.
I will not let him die.
Can I count on your help?
Thank you.
Perhaps imprisonment is a more
suitable punishment for the boy.
It would allow him to grow
until he strikes against us.
We don't know he's gonna strike
against us. He's yet to do anything.
It is enough that his people
conspire to overthrow me.
This is harsh, but necessary. I
take no pleasure in killing the boy.
Then spare him for Morgana's sake.
If you execute him
I fear she will never forgive you.
I do not seek her forgiveness!
She has betrayed me.
Yet you're sparing her.
She has the promise I made her
father to thank for that.
The boy enjoys no such privilege.
He will be executed at dawn.
Is that clear?
Make yourself at home
You can't let your father
execute the boy.
You're lucky he's not executing you.
Was he really behind the screen when
I came to search your chambers?
I know you believe your
father's wrong to execute him.
What I believe doesn't matter.
My father's made up his mind.
He won't be talked out of it.
- I tried.
- Then the time for talking is over.
Whatever you're thinking,
it's not going to happen.
We have to get the boy back
to his people.
No. Forget it.
You'd let an innocent child die?
It's too late. He's been caught.
I have no choice.
And is this how you will rule
when you are king?
You're not like your father.
- I will not betray him.
- If I know you at all,
you won't stand by
and let this happen.
Please.
If you won't do this for the boy,
then do it for me.
Sorry. Was I interrupting something?
Nothing you need
concern yourself with.
Make yourself useful,
muck out my horses.
I trust Merlin.
We're going to break the Druid boy
out of the dungeons.
You can't do that.
We have to. Uther's going
to have him executed him at dawn.
I mean...
it's too dangerous.
if the King catches you a second
time he'll never forgive you.
- I'm not worried for myself.
- Merlin's right.
When my father finds out the boy's
escaped, he will suspect you.
It's suicide.
You must go to my
father and apologise.
Dine with him, so you're with him
when the boy escapes.
You need me if the plan is to work.
You can't do this on your own.
- Merlin will take your place.
- Me?
I'm going to take the boy
out through the burial vaults.
There's a tunnel
that leads beyond the city walls.
Get my horse from the
stables and meet me there.
There's a grate that covers
the entrance to the tunnel.
- Bring a rope and grappling hook.
- No, I can't.
Merlin. Do you understand?
If you're not there to meet us,
we will surely be caught.
I need to know why you
told me not to protect the boy.
You seek my counsel
and yet you choose to ignore it.
Just tell me why.
If the boy lives,
you cannot fulfil your destiny.
You said it's my destiny
to protect Arthur?
Then you have the answer you seek.
You're telling me that little boy
is going to kill Arthur?
It seems that is up to you.
No.
You can't know that for certain.
You have it in your power
to prevent a great evil.
There must be another way?
The future isn't set in stone.
You must let the boy die.
the plight of the Druid boy
that's causing your forehead
to wrinkle like a lizard's elbow.
Would you let
something terrible happen
if it meant you'd stop something
even worse happening in the future?
I suppose it depends
on what the 'terrible'
and 'even worse' things were.
One of them's bad,
really bad.
And the other... it's unthinkable.
It sounds as if you've already
made your decision.
You can only do what you believe
to be right, Merlin.
I just hope it doesn't involve you
putting yourself in terrible danger.
For once, you don't have to worry.
I'm going to do nothing.
Thank you.
What is it? What's wrong?
You're risking so much for this boy.
You don't know anything about him.
- You don't even know his name.
- There's a bond between us.
Stronger than the bond
you have with Uther?
It's like nothing
I've ever felt before.
Perhaps I was always
meant to help him.
How can that be?
I don't know.
I can't explain it.
I must go to Uther.
Good luck.
I have come to apologise, my Lord.
You have been generous,
kind and fair.
And I owe you everything.
I truly don't know
what came over me.
I acted without thinking
of the consequences.
My behaviour was unforgivable.
I am glad you have seen sense.
Dine with me. Let's put this
unfortunate incident behind us.
Don't be scared.
I have sent word to your people,
I'm taking you to them.
You must come with me.
This way.
It's the Druid boy. He's escaped!
Merlin... Merlin!
Don't worry, he'll be here.
Guard!
Find out why they have sounded
the warning bell.
Yes, my Lord.
Damn it, Merlin!
'Emrys?'
'Emrys?
Where are you, Emrys?
'Emrys. '
'Help us. Please!'
'They're coming. '
Look down here.
'I'm scared, Emrys.
'They will kill me. Don't do this. '
'Don't ignore me. '
'I know you can hear me.
I thought you were my friend. '
'We're the same.
I don't want to die. '
'Emrys! Emrys,'
'Emrys!'
Hey!
Where the hell have you been?
I had trouble getting
out of the castle.
Get this grate off, they're coming.
If my father asks where I am,
I've gone on a hunting trip.
You'd better make yourself scarce,
or they'll execute you in his place.
'Goodbye, Emrys. I know that
someday we will meet again. '
My Lord. I regret to report
that the Druid boy
has escaped from the dungeons.
- What!? How?
- My Lord.
He was assisted by some accomplices.
The guards are searching
Camelot as we speak.
Find him and his accomplices
and kill them.
Yes, my Lord.
If I discover that you were somehow
involved in freeing this boy,
will be extremely severe.
My Lord, you know I respect you too
much to ever betray you like that.
I made a promise to your father
that I would protect you.
But if you cross me again,
I will break that promise
without a second thought.
We are forever indebted to you,
Arthur Pendragon
for returning the boy to us.
You must not let it be known that
it was I who brought him to you.
We will tell no-one.
You have my word.
Wait, I don't even know your name.
At least tell me your name.
It's all right.
My name is Mordred.
Good luck, Mordred.
- Tristan's tomb is empty.
- Dead men do not return.
Single combat. To the death.
He's been conjured
from the dead.
This will be your death.
I need to find a weapon
that will kill the dead.
AAAAGH!
www.tvsubtitles.net