In a land of myth
and a time of magic,
the destiny of a great kingdom
rests of the shoulders
of a young boy.
His name...
Merlin.
- Yes, Sire?
- Are you deaf?
I wish.
I want you to go down there
and tell them to stop.
But they're working
under the King's orders.
And you're working under mine.
Hello?
Arthur's Knights
Merlin - 2x01
The Curse of Cornelius Sigan
How do you think he died?
Do you know whose tomb is it?
I'm not sure.
Do you think it might be cursed?
You've just saved my life.
- Thank you.
- ... guarded at all times.
Idiot.
Were you born clumsy
or do you work at it?
It's just one of my many gifts.
Well, this is quite a find.
You see, guys, I was right.
There is treasure to be found
under Camelot.
Which of my predecessors
do I have to thank for all this?
I'd have to look into it, Sire.
How did he die?
He seems to have unwittingly
triggered a trap here.
To deter grave robbers.
There's plenty in here
people would want to steal.
Have them secure the tomb. Guarding
it is your responsibility, Arthur.
Yes, Father.
So this jewel...
What size did you say it was?
- About that size.
- My word, really?
About that size. Well, I never.
Here you are. Drink up.
And this tomb...
I bet they got that locked up
nice and safe, haven't they?
Tighter than the King's coffers.
Must be a way in, though?
Only with the keys...
Right, right. Right.
And who's got the keys?
You must think I'm stupid.
I'm not telling you that.
Course not.
A bright lad like you knows what
that sort of information's worth.
We don't want everyone to see.
Believe me. This place is
full of thieves and fingersmiths.
Put it inside your tunic
And careful of that fellow
over there.
Which one?
Far end of the bar.
See him?
- He keeps on watching you.
- Yeah, yeah, the one with the beard.
That one.
I got my eye on him.
Thank you.
So who's got the keys?
Only the prince.
But don't get your hopes up.
He keeps them
in his private chambers.
And there's only one person
allowed in there:
his servant.
- Hurry up, Merlin.
- Sorry.
- I don't understand.
- Well, there's a surprise.
- I did that girth up myself.
- That might have been a problem.
It wasn't my fault!
Would you like me to fit the girth
properly for you, Sire?
Thank you.
It's an honour to be of service
to the prince.
An honour.
Do you hear that, Merlin?
Allow me the honour
of brushing your clothes down.
The honour.
Is there anything else
I can do for you, Sire?
You can give Merlin, here,
a kick up the backside.
I wouldn't wish to deprive you
of the pleasure, Sire.
What's your name?
Cedric.
I've come to Camelot
in search of work.
Good.
You can be a beater on the hunt.
We're short of a man or two.
You're too kind, Sire.
Here, you'll need a beater.
Oh, sorry.
Who threw that?
Was it you?
You've just saved my life.
Honestly, Sire, it was nothing.
I shall be forever indebted to you.
You must be rewarded.
No. I couldn't possibly...
Come on.
What do you wish for?
- I desire only one thing, Sire.
- Anything.
- A position in the royal household.
- Bien.
Consider it done.
You can have that back now.
Sorry.
What's wrong?
I saved Arthur's life.
Someone else got the credit.
Just the usual.
What are you doing?
I found this inscription
on the sceptre.
What language is that?
I don't know.
Sigan would have known
many languages.
- Sigan?
- It's his tomb.
Who's he?
He was the most powerful sorcerer
to have lived.
Really?
You didn't grow up in Camelot,
but for those of us that did,
Cornelius Sigan
was a figure of nightmare.
Why?
Sigan's pass.
He could change day into night.
Turn the tides, and legend has it,
his spells helped
to build Camelot itself.
What happened?
In the end, he grew too powerful
and the King at that time
ordered his execution.
If he's dead,
why are you so worried?
Sigan couldn't bear the thought
that his wealth and power
would die with him,
so he became obsessed
with finding a way
to defeat death itself.
You think he might have succeeded?
Let's hope not.
For all our sakes.
What is it you want?
To seal up the burial chamber
and all its contents.
Don't be ridiculous.
The insignia on this ring,
belongs to Cornelius Sigan.
I believe it to be his tomb.
In the old religion
the name Sigan means "raven".
- No wonder the riches are so great.
- Then you're aware of the legend, Sire.
I have always enjoyed the tale
of the arrogant sorcerer
who came to an untimely end.
According to the story,
Sigan cursed Camelot.
He said he would one day return
and raise the city to the ground.
Gaius, you've long been my ally
in the war against sorcery.
You, more than anyone,
should not give into these...
irrational fears.
Thank you, Sire.
Do not spray panic
amongst my people.
This is foolish superstition,
nothing more.
My lady!
My lady, what's the matter?
It's all right, it's all right.
I'm here.
There's nothing to be frightened of.
- Is that lunch?
- No, it's breakfast.
This is lovely, Cedric.
Is there anything else
that you need doing, Sire?
No, I think
Cedric's got it all covered.
I regret, Sire, there's one thing
I've failed to do.
Muck out your horses.
Off you go.
I'll get the door for you.
What was this dream about?
A bird.
What kind of bird?
- A raven.
- A raven?
It was terrifying.
What do you think it means?
Probably nothing.
It's happening again, isn't it?
One raven certainly doesn't mean
that your nightmares are returning.
Are you taking the sleeping draughts
I prepared for you?
I'll get Gwen
to give you something stronger.
Like a blow to the head?
I'm sure she wants to.
Go on and have fun.
Go on. Go and have fun.
Sire!
Sire?
What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- I can see that.
I wasn't sleeping.
I was...
I was just bending down.
Looking for something?
- We may be looking for the same thing.
- What?
I don't know. The horses!
The horses?
One mistake I can understand,
everyone has a bad day,
but this is one thing after another!
I don't know what happened.
Sire?
Please, Sire. Don't be too hard on him.
He is a good servant, it's just...
- He's tired.
- I am not.
Maybe...
- if he had the evening off...
- I don't want the evening off!
- A good night's rest.
- I did not fall asleep!
I'm more than willing
to take over his duties tonight.
You're right.
- Shut up, Merlin.
- Can't you see what he's doing?
He's trying to get rid of me and if you
weren't such a clotpole you'd see that.
A what?
Clotpole. He said clotpole.
Cedric's right.
He can look after me tonight.
You can go home.
And think about whether you want
to be my servant or not. But... go!
- What's that on your face?
- Nothing.
- What's wrong?
Here.
I am not an idiot.
What happened?
I just want Arthur to trust me.
And to see me for who I really am.
One day he will.
When?
Everything I do is for him
and he just thinks I'm an idiot.
Not everyone thinks you're an idiot.
Although, looking at you now...
Now is not the time
to be questioning these things, Merlin.
I believe that you and Arthur
are destined for greatness,
and that your calling
is to serve and protect him.
- It's hard.
- I know it's hard,
but Camelot is in grave peril.
I've translated the inscription.
He who breaks my heart
completes my work.
What does it mean?
Do you remembered the stone
in the tomb, how it glowed?
- I've never seen a jewel like it.
- That's because it's not a jewel,
it's the soul of Cornelius Sigan.
- You think he's alive?
- His soul is.
But in order to truly live,
a soul needs a body.
So if the stone
is removed from its setting
then the heart is broken
and the soul is released.
That's what I fear.
I'll be right outside
in the anteroom should you need me.
That'll be all, Cedric.
Sleep well, Sire.
Hello, ladies.
Sound the warning bell.
Whoever did this got more
than they bargained for.
I don't understand how they got in.
The gate's not even damaged.
- They must have used a key.
- Arthur's got the only key.
Where does he keep it?
- On his belt with the others.
- Does he ever take it off?
Only when he's asleep.
He keeps it next to his bed.
- Who get into his chambers last night?
- Just me and...
Cedric.
Cedric is possessed
by an evil spirit.
What?
He tried to steal the jewel.
But it wasn't a jewel. It was the soul
of an ancient sorcerer, Sigan
Merlin, have you been on the cider?
Please... Listen to me.
Camelot is in mortal danger.
Sigan is using Cedric's body
to take his revenge.
This isn't helping you
keep your job.
You are not listening to me!
If you're going to shout anyway...
Will you escort Merlin
from the palace?
You've gone too far this time.
You can spend a few days
cooling off in the cells.
Guards!
He's going to destroy Camelot.
I am returned.
What this creature is,
where it's come from!
There's more than one.
There are several.
There's panic in the lower town.
People are fleeing the city.
You must hunt the creatures down
- and kill them.
- Yes, Sire.
- Have you seen what's happening?
- It is as I warned you, Sire.
- This cannot be Sigan.
- It is his revenge.
You do not understand, Sire. You can't
kill a man who has conquered mortality
Don't tell me what cannot be done.
Camelot will not fall to a sorcerer
while I am king.
Hello?
Regroup!
Form a phalanx.
We need more bandages, Gwen.
- You shouldn't be doing this.
- It's exactly what I should be doing.
- You need rest, Morgana.
- I'm likely to get it with all this?
That thing could have killed you.
And it still might.
Sorry, Sire.
No, my pleasure.
I'll get you something
to stop the bleeding.
I wanted to say...
Just...
You always surprise me.
- Is that it, Sire?
- That's it.
And...
Thank you.
It's nothing.
- Have we driven the creatures out?
- They have control of the lower town.
The market has been
all but destroyed.
How many dead?
Too many to number.
I'm sealing the citadel.
- You can't.
- I have no choice.
I have to protect
those who have a chance.
If I don't, we will all fall.
- Where are you going?
- There are people
trapped on the drawbridge.
I'm not leaving them to die.
It's suicide.
It's my duty to Camelot
and to myself.
- What are you doing here?
- I have to help Arthur.
- Sigan's power is way beyond yours.
- I don't have a choice.
But Sigan is immortal and you are not.
If you face him, he'll destroy you.
There must be a way.
There is only one alive who is old
enough to give us the answers we need.
What do you mean?
The Great Dragon.
You knew, then.
- that I used to visit him?
- Yes, Merlin, of course I knew.
You're a creature of magic,
just as he is.
- I hope that he could help you.
- He helps no-one but himself.
- For Arthur's sake, you must go to him.
- I can't.
We have no choice.
Check for survivors.
On me!
Charge!
Hello?
Please, I need your help.
You told me
I would not see you again.
I'm not here for myself,
I'm here for Arthur.
Arthur's path lies with yours.
You have made it clear that
you do not walk in step with me.
You cannot want Cornelius Sigan
to win, you're not evil.
At least Sigan knows
where is loyalties lie.
You have shown that you do not.
So you will let Camelot fall?
I did not say that.
Then you will help me?
To defeat Sigan,
you will need a spell more powerful
than anything you know.
Please. I have to try.
Very well.
But you must give me
something in return.
- What?
- A promise.
- A promise?
- That one day
you will free me.
If I release you, what will you do?
- That is not your concern.
- I don't trust you.
Nevertheless, you must promise,
or Camelot will fall.
I promise.
Now, please, give me the spell.
Close your eyes
and open your mind.
Few men have ever been gifted
such knowledge.
Use it wisely.
I will.
You made a promise, young warlock.
And one day...
I shall keep you to it.
Retreat!
Regroup in the square!
Save yourselves! It's an order.
Retreat, retreat!
Seal the doors!
What's that?
Where is he?
You can't leave him out there.
He'll be torn apart.
You can't go out there, Sire!
If you open that door, you will die,
we will all die.
Who would have believed it?
You, a sorcerer.
And a powerful one.
I won't let you hurt him.
And you're going to stop me?
I'll stop you.
He does not deserve your loyalty.
He treats you like a slave.
That's not true.
He cast you aside
without a moment's thought...
- It doesn't matter.
- But it must hurt so much.
To be so put upon, so overlooked,
when all the while
you have such power.
- That's the way it has to be.
- Does it?
You are young Merlin.
Look inside yourself,
you have yet
to discover your true power.
I can help you.
Think, Merlin,
to have the world
appreciate your greatness,
To have Arthur know you
for what you are.
- That can never be.
- It can.
If you join me.
Together we can rule over this land.
Arthur will tremble at your voice.
He will kneel at your feet.
I don't want that.
You'd rather be a servant?
Better to save a good man
than to rule with an evil one.
So be it.
If you will not join me,
I will become you
and your power
will be harnessed to my will.
Well done, my boy.
We must learn our lessons
from these terrible events, Gaius.
Indeed, Sire.
They prove beyond that
that I was right.
Magic is evil,
it is our greatest threat.
I have grown complacent, Gaius.
I wouldn't say that, Sire.
We must renew our efforts.
We must ensure that all sorcerers
and their followers
are eradicated from this kingdom.
Of course, Sire.
You know you won't get
any thanks, Merlin.
I'm not a complete idiot.
There you go. It's not much,
but you deserve something.
I've come to see Merlin.
I've not forgotten about your lazy,
insolent ways, or the fact
that you called me a "clotpole",
but I do have to admit
that there was some truth
in your accusations against Cedric.
Does this mean you're admitting that
on this occasion I was actually right?
Not exactly, no.
It means that I have a knighthood
to bestow first thing tomorrow
and no-one to clean my armour.
All that?
Clotpole?
- And what would you know about magic?
- Nothing.
Today you will fight for glory
and for honour.
That has got to hurt.
Nothing can ever happen between us!
When you're king,
you can change that.
You do realize your wife
- is a troll, Sire.
- What?
How could you resist such beauty?
Send for the witchfinder
Your magic is a secret
to be guarded with your life.
I won't sacrifice
a friend to save myself.
Gaius is already doomed.
My name is Lancelot.
Do not believe that
you can lie to me.
We're going to kill each other.
The boy: Merlin.