In a land of myth
and a time of magic,
the destiny of a great kingdom
rests on the shoulders
of a young boy.
His name...
Merlin.
Quick, my potion.
Lady Catrina is not
all that she seems to be.
- She's a troll.
- She's not that bad!
Trolls are greedy, and Lady Catrina
is like the rest of her kind.
- She lusts after wealth and power.
- Uther's wealth and power.
There's more than one way
to enchant a man.
I want you to have it.
I shall wear it always.
You may possess some magic, wretch,
but you are no match for me.
I now pronounce you to be
husband and wife.
Arthur's Knights
Merlin - 2x06
Beauty and the Beast (2/2)
You look positively
foul.
Does the enchantment hold?
It works a treat.
Uther is like a puppet on a string.
What about the boy?
He knows your secret.
Leave him to me.
My Lord.
Darling.
We are alone at last.
- What's wrong?
- I'm sorry.
It's not you.
I want this more than anything.
This has been the happiest day
of my life.
Then what is it?
When I was forced to flee my home,
the one thing I was able to take with me
was my family seal.
You showed it to me
when you first arrived.
It's the only surviving link
I have to my father.
And now it's gone.
Stolen from my chambers.
Who could have done such a thing?
Oh, no, please.
I don't want to cause any trouble.
Not on a day
that should be filled with such joy.
Who took your seal?
It was Arthur's servant.
Search the stables.
You, check the kitchens.
Alert the guard on the South gate.
- What's in there?
- This way. Hurry up.
- Where's Merlin?
- Where he always is at this time.
Working for Arthur.
What's this about?
We've come to arrest him,
by order of the King.
You need to get out of here.
The King's ordered me to arrest you.
Catrina's accused you
of taking her seal.
- But I didn't.
- I don't want to know
and you haven't got time to explain.
If you value your life,
you'll leave Camelot now.
But she is a troll.
She's trying to set me up.
- We've been through this.
- I'm telling the truth.
I saw her.
I don't care. You need to leave.
- Sire?
- Go.
Go!
I fear he may have slipped
through our net.
You're very quick
to give up the chase.
That is because I know
my quarry is long gone.
- How can you be so certain?
- Well, despite appearances,
He isn't stupid. He must have got wind
that we were looking for him and left.
Outwitting your army in the process.
It appears so.
I thought your men aspired
to the same high standards
that my father instilled in you.
When I led the army, they did.
We don't even know if he's still
in Camelot. He could be anywhere.
And that's a good enough reason
to give up?
I'm not.
- I believe our resources would...
- I've heard enough of your excuses.
We both have.
I want the boy found.
Sire.
My Lady.
My plan to undermine Arthur
is under way.
Soon Uther will detest
the sight of his own son.
What's that, then?
What is that smell?
A treat.
To celebrate.
Fresh from the stables.
You do know how to treat a lady.
Alert the rest of the guard.
Come with me.
They've found Merlin's trail. They say
he's heading for the Northern Borders.
I'm sure he'll outrun them.
What if he can't?
- Uther won't show him any mercy.
- Try not to worry, Gwen.
That was comfortable.
A necessary evil, I'm afraid.
They've picked up the trail that we left
but it won't fool them for long.
- Then I'd better get busy.
- Be careful.
The guards are still
searching for you.
Mistress, it is time.
- Do I have to?
- You must keep up the pretence.
I hate being like this.
So clean. It's revolting.
I can't keep it up.
This skin,
this face.
I just want to claw it off.
Think of all the money
and the power.
Soon it will all be yours.
There is something important
that I...
We... wish you to address.
For too long,
the people have had it easy.
They've grown fat
off our indulgence of them.
How so?
We provide peace, protection, food.
They give us very little in return.
Our people are poor. They survive
on the few crops they're able to grow.
That's what they want us to think.
- It's what I see every day.
- We're introducing a new tax.
The people must pay for the sanctuary
that Camelot provides.
You can't.
The majority are barely able
to get by as it is.
Those who refuse to pay it will
be arrested and publicly flogged.
We've lived this way for years.
You've never suggested
anything like this before.
Maybe not to you,
but the King confided in me
that he has been considering this
for some time, haven't you?
I have.
You are to begin the collections
at once.
I saw her drink some of this potion
and a patch of troll skin
on her arm disappeared.
It must be pretty powerful magic
to physically change her like that.
Could you make a potion
that looks and tastes
the same as this?
I don't know.
Yes, I suppose so.
But without the troll magic,
it wouldn't have the same effect.
Exactly.
If I can replace this potion
with one that isn't magical...
So Catrina will keep taking it,
- but it will no longer work.
- And she'll turn into a troll.
- Think you can do it?
- I don't know.
We have to make the switch
before morning or Jonas will notice.
Then it's going to be a long night.
My Lady.
My Liege.
I brought you flowers.
Picked from the royal garden.
They're...
They're lovely.
Not as lovely as you.
Are you all right?
No. I'm sorry.
I can't keep this up any longer.
- Keep what up?
- The lie.
I can't keep pretending like this.
I'm beginning to wonder if you're really
the man I thought you were,
the man I fell in love with.
The man I married was firm,
strong,
in both mind and body.
Trust me, I am all of that,
and more.
I fear for Camelot.
Arthur has not taken
after his father.
He is too weak
to make the hard decisions.
Then it's lucky
I'm in such rude health.
Lucky indeed.
But what if some tragedy
were to befall you?
Let me worry about Arthur.
No, I can't.
Your love for him
has made you blind to his faults.
I judge Arthur
the same as the rest of my men.
If he excels he is rewarded.
If he fails, he is punished.
Well...
as long as you're sure of that.
I am.
Now let me take your mind off this.
I promise our first night
as husband and wife
will be one to remember.
- What's in it?
- Nothing too potent.
- Rat's guts.
- Nice.
Toad paste.
- You take two toads, grind them up...
- I get the picture.
Horse dung,
- crushed sheep's eyeball.
- Lovely.
Pond scum, three wolf spiders,
and what potion isn't complete
without a dash of sheep's brain?
Sounds... delicious.
Good.
Because you're going to taste it.
No way.
It's completely harmless.
That is disgusting.
To you, but not to a troll.
I can't even believe
you let me put that in my mouth.
Now...
Try the original.
Just a small amount,
and be sure to spit it out.
- Does it taste roughly the same?
- Yes, it's horrible!
You sure? Because if there's too big
a difference, Catrina will notice.
It tastes exactly the same.
Let's hope she thinks so too.
- What do you think you're doing?
- He's refusing to pay the King's tax.
You ask for too much.
- I've given all I can.
- It's not enough.
Let me see.
- Release him.
- The King said...
Release him!
Give them back their money.
All of it.
- I gave you a direct order.
- People cannot afford to pay the tax.
Don't tell me you're naive enough
to take them at their word?
We have their loyalty,
their goodwill.
Do not forsake that
by making unreasonable demands.
Is it so unreasonable
for a king to expect
- his subjects to obey him?
- They'll starve.
Nonsense.
You've grown too soft.
Remember, these are your subjects,
not your friends.
Why can't they be both?
Because we rule the people,
not the other way round.
I think you're wrong.
I beg your pardon?
I said you're wrong.
Without the people,
there is no Camelot.
We're as much their servant
as they are ours.
You allow him to address you
in this manner?
I do not.
It will not be tolerated.
You will take your men
down into the town, and go
to every house
collecting the payments I demand!
I will not.
Get out of my sight.
How can he do this to me?
My own son!
After all the sacrifices
I've made for him.
- You're tense.
- Is it any surprise?
The lack of respect he shows... me!
- I'm sorry. Did that hurt?
- No, of course not.
Your hands are surprisingly strong
for one so delicate.
Arthur carries a heavy burden.
It can't be easy holding all that
responsibility at such
a tender age.
I'm afraid
that's the way it has to be.
After all,
I cannot rule Camelot alone.
You don't have to.
You married me, remember?
How could I forget?
I'm sorry, I can't.
I'm too worried about you.
With Arthur letting you down
the way he has. How will you cope?
Like you said,
you can't rule Camelot alone.
I have you by my side.
I may be your Queen,
but I have no power.
Why not?
The people wouldn't respect me
as they do Arthur.
I'm not heir to the throne.
Would it put your mind at rest
if you were?
It would.
- It most definitely would.
- Then you shall be.
The ceremony will take place
this afternoon.
It's time for my potion.
Are your plans progressing
as you'd hoped?
And not a moment too soon.
I must admit, though,
that crown
will look rather fetching.
All that gold
and them lovely jewels.
Now, would you care
to accompany your Queen?
Come in.
I saw what you did earlier.
The people owe you
a debt of gratitude.
The people owe me nothing.
My father is still going
to impose the tax.
- Will he not be persuaded?
- Not by me.
- He can't stand the sight of me.
- That's not true.
- The King loves you.
- Have you heard how he spoke to me?
I'm sure he was angry
but you're still his son.
Everyone appreciates what you did.
They know you tried
and they won't forget that.
Maybe he's right.
One day I will be
the King of Camelot.
I cannot be a friend to the people
as well as their ruler.
That's not true and you'll prove it
when you become King.
You've a kind heart, Arthur.
Don't ever change.
Not for anyone.
The King has sent for you.
Father.
I'm relaxing your duties,
revoking your title.
- What?
- We live in dangerous times.
I cannot allow you
to undermine my authority.
You've always welcomed my counsel.
You stood against me
for all the people to see.
I'm sorry. Any future grievance
I have will be held in private.
Too late.
You are to be disinherited
with immediate effect.
You are no longer
Crown Prince of Camelot.
Sire, Arthur is your son,
you natural heir.
You've taught me to be true to my heart
and that's all I've ever tried to do.
To be the man you wanted me to be,
someone you were proud to call your son.
My decision is final.
Queen Catrina will be named
as rightful heir to the throne.
Ceremony will begin forthwith.
We've done it.
Catrina's drank the fake potion.
What's wrong? What's happened?
Uther has disinherited Arthur...
and made Catrina his heir.
So if Uther dies,
she will rule Camelot.
We are gathered here to bear witness
to the naming of Queen Catrina
as the rightful heir to Camelot.
Are you willing to take the oath?
I am.
Do you solemnly swear to govern
the people of Camelot,
to uphold the laws and customs
of the land?
I... do.
Will you, to your power,
cause Law and Justice in Mercy,
to be executed
in all your judgements?
I will.
Will you,
to the utmost of your powers,
- maintain the laws...?
Yes.
I'm sorry, you must let me finish.
The wording must be
exactly right to be binding.
Well, get on with it then!
I mean really,
where did you dig up this old crone
from?
Right, get on with it.
Will you,
to the utmost of your powers...
- ... maintain the laws and customs...
- I will.
... of the land and serve
the people of Camelot?
Just shut up and give me the crown!
Will you just hurry up!
- Whatever's the matter?
- I'm sorry.
I don't know what came over me.
I just suddenly felt so hot.
I think I need to be on my own.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, I'm fine.
Really. Thank you.
Come on!
Open!
Let me.
What's that!?
What's up?
Somebody help her!
You're a troll!
How dare you speak
about her like that?
What is wrong with you?
Look at the state of her!
I don't believe it.
She just ripped a door
off its hinges...
- Doesn't that tell you something?
- Enough!
She's a troll!
A giant, grey...
- Stinking.
- ... stinking troll.
Stop it!
Haven't you hurt her feelings enough?
Insult my wife again,
it'll be the last thing you ever do.
I'm so sorry that you had to hear
those terrible things.
He's just taking time to adjust.
He'll soon get used
to having his stepmother around.
How could he compare
such beauty with a troll?
Search me.
I washed my face and everything.
What is it?
It's just your scent...
It's so...
fragrant.
It's mostly... dung.
Such a sense of humour.
I was so blessed
it was my castle you came to...
That I may look
upon this vision every day.
Beauty is in the eye
of the beholder.
I shall behold it.
I wasn't aware
we were due to convene the council.
What's this about?
Come on. Someone speak up.
I'm afraid it's your wife, Sire.
What about her?
It's a rather delicate matter, Sire.
Gaius, you've been my trusted adviser
for many years.
You can speak as you will.
I don't suppose it's escaped your notice
but we just...
Just wanted to make
absolutely certain.
You do realise your wife
is a troll, Sire?
I beg your pardon.
At least that's the way she looks to us,
what with the...
warts, and the...
- nose...
- And the smell.
Smell?!
What...?
She also has what appears to be...
- a set of fangs.
- What?!
I wouldn't really say they were fangs...
More like tusks.
Yes, they are more like tusks.
Not that we're saying
that's a bad thing.
Thought I ought to point it out to you,
in case it had passed you by.
The next person to insult
Queen Catrina...
... will be charged with treason
and beheaded
according to the laws of the land.
Uther must be enchanted.
It's the only explanation.
- Which is why we must find a way.
- You won't find anything in your books.
Troll enchantments are too strong.
Then what are we going to do?
You must speak to the Dragon.
If there's a way to break Catrina's
hold on Uther,
he will know it.
But be careful.
Dragons and trolls
have been close allies in the past.
Is everything to your satisfaction?
This thing's got to go for a start.
It's made for midgets!
Too hard, too clean!
Not my taste at all.
What can I get you instead?
I was walking
through the grounds this morning
and I couldn't help but notice
that your stables
have just been mucked out.
It seems such a waste to throw away
all that lovely dung.
This isn't funny.
It is!
The thought of Uther
marrying a troll!
- Was it a very public affair?
- Public enough.
Don't laugh.
If she can't be stopped,
Arthur won't become King.
Albion will never be born.
I'm sorry.
You are right, of course.
How can we break the enchantment?
These are not trifling tricks...
Troll magic is very powerful.
- There has to be a way.
- The only way you could break this
is if Uther were to cry
tears of true remorse.
- How do we make him do that?
- That I can't answer.
Uther's heart is cold as stone.
He's never been sorry for anything.
Thanks. I think.
Young warlock!
It was some time ago
you promised to set me free.
The help I give
is not unconditional.
That is for you.
Now, tell them about our plan,
beloved.
- Plan...
- We are introducing further taxes.
Sire, we can't.
The people have given all they can.
You told me that before.
And yet our coffer is full.
Your people
are already going hungry.
- Are you questioning my orders?
- It's just...
If we take more, they'll starve.
Who are you to tell me
what's best for my people?
You will collect more taxes
or you will lose your head.
Lose your head! Lose your head!
I understand Bayard of Mercia wishes
to honour our marriage with a visit.
Good! Now, tell this Bayard
we expect gifts.
Lots of lovely shiny gold.
I think at this time,
it might be wise to...
- to respectfully decline his visit.
- Whatever for?
I'm still not sure
that we can trust Bayard.
Nonsense he is a friend of Camelot.
You will send our reply.
- It'll be an honour to feast with him.
- Honour.
The Dragon said he had to cry
tears of true remorse
- to break the enchantment.
- That's not going to be easy.
Uther's heart is closed to everyone.
Not everyone.
Then there's only
one course of action we can take.
Uther must see his son die.
Who's there?
- You're back.
- I never left.
You mean to say...?
You've been under there
this whole time?
- Course not. No.
- Because if you were...
I wasn't, I swear.
Your stepmother is a troll, then.
- If you say, "I told you so..."
- I wasn't going to. I wouldn't.
But if you had listened to me
earlier...
Sorry.
Gaius and I believe
your father's been enchanted.
Now we've found a way to break
the spell, but...
we need your help.
So your great plan is to kill me?
Not exactly.
Gaius has made a potion
that gives the appearance of death
without the actual dying bit.
It's fine.
There's nothing to worry about.
It'll only bring you
to the brink of death.
- Only to the brink.
- We haven't got a choice.
- We have to make your father cry.
- He doesn't care about me any more.
Nonsense.
That's Catrina's influence.
I've known your father
for many, many years.
There's never been anyone or anything
he's treasured more than you.
It's perfectly safe -
a single drop of the antidote
will reverse the effects immediately.
Antidote. What antidote?
- You didn't say anything about it.
- I didn't think it was important.
The potion will lower
your heart rate and breathing.
To all intents and purposes,
you will be dead.
The antidote reverses the effects?
If it's administered in time.
If it isn't?
You will be dead.
You just said it wasn't important!
I suppose it is a bit important.
Merlin will have the antidote.
Once I've administered the poison...
The potion...
he'll have half an hour
to get it to you.
Don't be late.
Am I ever?
You sure you wanna go through this?
It's the only way to save Camelot.
Time to break the bad news to Uther.
My boy...
It was my fault.
I pushed you away.
My son.
Come away, there's nothing
you can do for him now.
I killed him.
I killed my only son.
What kind of trickery is this?
How I've suffered these last weeks.
Allowing you to touch me,
having to share a bed with you.
- It's repulsive.
- I know the feeling.
- I've been looking forward to this.
- Guards!
Seize... it!
Is that any way to treat
your dear old stepmother?
I'd like to thank you
for exposing this attack
on our state.
Once again, magic was used
to strike at the heart of Camelot.
You mean, your heart.
How many nights did you
share a bed with a troll?
Obviously, I was under its spell.
I did many things that I...
- regret.
- Father,
I don't want to know the details.
I want you to know
that I never doubted you.
All right, maybe I did,
but it's your own fault.
You've got a suspicious look
about you. Shifty.
Like you've got something to hide.
- I'm an open book.
- Don't believe that for a second.
However, I know that without your help,
I'd still have a troll for a stepmother.
Thanks.
- What?
- Thought you were going for a hug.
It was sorcery you saw. You certain?
- Send for the witchfinder.
- Your once noble Camelot is rotten.
Can you prove that it wasn't you?
My methods are infallible,
my findings incontestable!
The facts point
to one person alone...
The boy!
- You're a liar!
- You've got to stop this.