Subtitles: www.swsub.com
Hey! Slow down!
Will!
Will, you're in here?
We're still waiting for a report
on casualties
and details are hard to come by,
- but police are not ruling out...
- Jay!
Two men were seen fleeing the scene.
- Thank you, Heather.
- She's talking about us.
Your call cannot be completed
as dialed...
- She's talking about us, Jay!
- I know, Tyler!
I think I'm gonna puke.
- Where the hell is Will?
- He's dead!
We don't know that.
- He was in there!
- We don't know that!
We haven't done anything wrong.
So let's just take a breath
and go to the police, okay?
They can handle this.
- A guide book.
- Guide book?
Jack Kerouac wrote the great
American novel in less than 3 weeks.
The guy didn't need to invent
the adventures of Dean Moriarty
and Sal Paradise.
He lived them.
They teach that at chemical engineering?
I'm not a chemical engineer
for the next two months.
And you are not a venture capitalist.
And you are definitely not a lawyer.
For the next two months,
we are professional vagabonds,
Moriarty and Paradise,
living between the East of our youth...
- and the West of our future.
- Exactly.
- That's from the book.
- Yeah. Right. I know.
Well, looks like
it's time to say goodbye to the Castle.
Shotgun!
You suck!
Every damn time...
What, are we 12 years old or what?
Come on.
We're good.
Quit playing games.
Welcome to New York.
You booked us here?
It's our last night to live like kings.
After this,
it's all motels and camps all the way
- to San Francisco.
- Catch!
You guys check in.
I'm gonna go park the car.
They've got valet.
I know a garage in 51st.
It's half the price.
I'll meet you guys up in the room.
Are you gentlemen in town
for business or pleasure?
Definitely pleasure.
You're on a road trip?
I can tell by the bags.
I like to guess where folks are headed
based on their luggage.
- It's a cool trick.
- Yep.
And we plan to start this trip off
with a bang.
So, if you could arrange a limo for us
this evening, we'd be in your debt.
Of course, sir.
Concierge will have a car waiting.
Thanks.
You don't have to pay
for everything on this trip.
We said Will
would be in charge of planning,
I would cover major expenses
and you will keep us out of trouble.
Of the three....
I'd say you have the hardest job.
Wake up, Jay! It's just the beginning.
Suit yourselves, ladies.
Go ahead.
Hey, act like you're having fun.
You take that thing
everywhere on this trip?
You'll thank me for this someday.
Excuse me. Ladies,
we didn't come to the most exclusive
club in Manhattan
for you to play wallflower, ok?
Now, I've got 3 interns from Vogue
over there looking for dance partners.
But if we don't act fast,
they'll gonna be taken off the market.
Hey man, some of us have girlfriends.
No. You, Jay, have a girlfriend,
but if you take advantage
of your time with me tonight,
We might just make that girlfriends.
Careful Tyler!
Give it back, man.
Hey, hon, Jay will call you back...
in like 2 months.
- Why?
- I'm just looking out for you.
We'll be there in a minute. One minute.
I'll be waiting.
It's the 3rd time
she's called you tonight.
Doesn't want you to go?
She's not the only one
having second thoughts.
Got to see the world before
you can change it, right?
Yeah, I've also to pay
80,000 in loans, too.
Jay, come on, look.
You're doing the right thing, here.
A trip like this,
you take time to step off the path
and really see
what makes this country tick.
It'll change your life.
- Alright?
- Alright.
Good. Now,
you do whatever damage control
you need to do,
and you come out here
and get your groove on.
Can I see that move again?
- It's call fun.
- You are so horribly white.
Wake up call!
Rise and shine,
we've got a lot to do today.
If you're done,
I've an unforgettable way
to start our trip.
Will, can I just say how proud of you
I am right now?
Rumor is Kerouac
streaked this place back in 47
as a "screw you"
to New York establishment.
This is genius.
My grandma used to drag me here
like once a month.
I figure we race from the top,
whoever gets out first
doesn't drive till Chicago.
Like that med-school prank?
It was 2 years ago.
Here we go again.
Look, you said it was my job
to keep us out of trouble, all right?
Things are a little different now.
We're not in grad school anymore.
Jay, it's a prank.
So what if we get
in a little bit of trouble?
Tyler, there's a difference between
getting hired by a major law firm
and going to work for your dad.
You know what, Jay?
Wake up.
Cause that law firm is gonna run
your life in about 2 months.
And this trip is your last chance
to actually have a little bit of fun.
No, and actually do something memorable.
If we do this thing,
we're gonna do it together,
we said that from day one in this trip.
- So you're putting this on me, now.
- If you're out, we all are.
I win, Tyler keeps his mouth shut
about Kim for the rest of the trip.
Oh, it is on, my friend,
it is on!
Let's go!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the special Docents tour
will be beginning in five minutes.
I haven't done this since hockey season.
Don't make excuses.
It's like riding a bike.
OK. You guys head down first, I'll be
right behind you taping the whole thing.
And if we get split up?
We meet outside North/East corner.
Amen.
Good luck.
Sorry.
What happened, man?
- Where is Will?
- You two!
Hold it!
- Go. Let's go!
- Attention, this is a fire alarm.
Please follow a docent
or a security guard to the nearest exit.
No, you can't do that in here!
Coming through! Thank you,
thank you guys! Sorry!
- This was not bad.
- Not bad!
By the way,
you're driving to Chi-town.
- No, there was blatant interference.
- I was first to the door.
- Calling Will?
- Yeah.
Did you get out?
- Did you get out?
- Yeah, we're at the corner.
Where are you?
- I'm sorry I had to do this.
- Do what?
President Shears
personal art collection
was on display at the Drexler.
It may have been the bomb's target.
New York's counterterrorism units
are taking no chances.
All public transportation
has been suspended.
The East wing of New York's
oldest Art Museum is still burning.
3 guards have been rushed to Bellevue
Hospital and are in critical condition.
- But no fatalities...
- All of Will's stuff is gone!
I mean there's no way
he could have beaten us back here.
... it clearly shows
2 men fleeing the museum.
They appear to be using rollerblades.
The suspects are Caucasian,
in their late 20s.
The authorities are asking
anyone with information
to call the city's terrorism hot line.
They're calling us terrorists, now!
The Drexler is an invaluable part
of this city...
- What are you doing?
- Get changed.
- My dad had a great lawyer downtown.
- We got a lawyer right here.
- A real lawyer!
- I'm a real lawyer!
Stop pretending
this is not happening, Jay!
Will apologized right before
the museum exploded.
By the time we get back here,
all of his stuff is gone
and our faces are on TV?
What are you trying to say?
Do you think Will framed us for this?
There's no reason that our best friend,
a guy we lived with for 2 years
would do this!
Well, I'll be happy to ask him
what he was thinking,
but he's not here, now, is he?
Then we call the cops
and let them look for him.
Come on!
This is Will we're talking about!
This is special agent in charge
Fred Chambers.
I understand I'm speaking with one of
the men from the Drexler museum video.
Yes. This is Jay Burchell.
I'm sorry, who am I talking to?
Start the work up.
Thank you for calling, Mr. Burchell.
You're doing the right thing
by contacting us.
This can only help your case.
I want to make it clear upfront that we
had nothing to do with the bombing.
But we think a friend of ours was
in  the building when the bomb went off.
- You think?
- His name is Will Traveler.
We spoke just before the explosion.
If he's alive,
he might have seen something useful.
So you're saying
there is a third suspect.
Yes. No!
Listen, I know how this must look,
but we're not involved.
All right, it was just a prank.
We were rollerblading
through the museum...
- You needed to get somewhere quickly?
- I told you it was a prank.
You pulled
right before the Drexler exploded.
It was an innocent joke.
And I'm pretty sure that FBI procedure
does not allow you
to put our faces on TV
without reasonable bases for suspicion.
I suggest you calm down, Mr. Burchell.
Bingo. Triangulation...
Got them at Park Avenue
between 49th and 54th.
Mr. Burchell,
this is special agent Jane Marlow.
I was curious if you might be a lawyer?
Yes. Well, not technically, but...
Then you understand that in cases
of national security,
standard protocol takes a back seat.
Son, what the hell
did I just see on TV?
Dad, listen to me, I can explain, OK?
Are you still there, Mr. Burchell?
Look, I called to help, to tell you
our friend was in the building.
Just please, check the security footage.
He's 5'10'', he's wearing--
a dark blue track jacket.
Swallow it.
Got them. Burchell, Jason.
Room 509 Worcester Park Hotel.
Ordered 5 pizzas
from room service last night.
How far out are our nearest units?
Less than 2 minutes.
We'll check the footage again.
How does that sound ?
Good.
Yesterday, over ten million shares
of Holloway Insurance
were sold on the stock market.
Do you know what they cover ?
Yeah, they're specialized in fine Art.
The Drexler foundation to be exact.
That means that somebody, somewhere,
knew this was gonna happen.
- It's all we have ?
- The rest was destroyed by the fire.
Do you see him now ?
I'm afraid the rest of the footage
was lost, Mr. Burchell.
There's no sign of your friend.
Jay wants us to go to the cops.
That is not an option.
If you're on TV, it is not an accident.
But dad, we weren't involved !
That hasn't stop the authorities
from screwing this family before.
You need to get out of there now.
Son ?
Jay...
Are those cars for us ?
Burchell, this is Fred Chambers.
You should come in.
We can talk about this in person.
I told you. You got the wrong guys.
It's time to go.
My dad just called, OK ?
This is bigger than Will.
People, in very high places, knew
that something was gonna happen today.
Now, we have to get out of here,
out of the city.
- If we run, we look guilty.
- It's a little too late for that.
Someone put our faces on that TV.
Someone wants us
to take the blame for this.
You of all people know that
this can happen.
We find Will.
He's the only one
who can back up our alibi.
Whatever gets you out of this room.
Hold it !
Come back here !
Where'd they go?
Hey, you!
Cover that exit!
Suspects on either 3 or 4.
On 3 !
Come on!
Any more ideas ?
Yeah. But you're not gonna like it.
- We're running out of options.
- We call in a bomb threat.
You're right, I don't like it.
If they think it's the truth,
they'll clear the hotel.
You two are a long way
from the luxury suite.
We ran out of shampoo.
Don't worry.
I ain't no fan of the police.
Look, a friend of ours is in trouble
and unless we get out of here
- we're not gonna find him.
- And we can pay.
You ain't got enough.
But I do like that watch.
It is all yours.
- NYPD. Open the door!
- One minute!
This leads to the basement.
Take the hall to your right, it leads
to the building next door.
I'm changing. Be right there!
Don't worry. You'll be fine.
You got three seconds!
Come on guys! Gimme a break!
Jay Burchell, 26. Graduated Yale Law
last week, top 5 in his class.
UCLA for undergrade,
grew up in Romington California.
Rough neighborhood.
What about parents?
Mother, Felicia Cruz,
holds multiple jobs in Los Angeles.
- Mainly housework.
- Father?
That's where it gets interesting.
Sergeant William Burchell,
served in Iraq, 1992.
He's court-martialed
for a friendly fire incident
that killed 5 men.
He took his own life a year later.
It's a potential motive.
It sounds like payback.
So far we haven't found any matches
for the name he gave us, Will Traveler.
We checked DMV, NCIC, Credit bureaus.
We're looking in the old records.
- It sounds like a decoy.
- I don't think so, sir.
He was panicked but his speech pattern
didn't suggest he was lying.
Come on people, talk to me!
They got out.
We were on the phone with them
five minutes ago!
The room was registered to Tyler Fog.
Calvin Fog's son?
We compared Fog's DMV picture
with the Drexler footage
and got a positive match.
So Tyler Fog's our number two.
OK, I want a profiler running point
in the field.
- That means you, Marlow.
- Me sir?
Richardson's still in DC.
That makes you my senior profiler.
So take Boris and check out the Drexler.
No problem, sir.
Cheyenne, I want you
and every available SOG
looking for contacts.
Captain Fitz!
I want port authority transit
and MTA to lock up the island.
These guys do not leave Manhattan
unless I personally walk them
across a bridge.
Let's go.
- Your car is not here.
- Are you sure?
Look, man, I checked three times.
Now you need to leave.
A lot of people coming here to get cars.
Cops are shutting down the subways.
Wait, they're what?
The subways, man.
Looking for two guys on that bombing.
White, not Arabic if you can believe.
It's not here Tyler let's go. Thanks.
They're shutting down the subways.
Great. Just keep walking.
- Dad.
- Tyler, what's happening?
They took the car.
Minor setback.
You need to get to Queensborough bridge.
That's the quickest way for you to get
out of town and get to Elysium.
We're heading there now.
Good. You still have my black card,
- the one I gave you for emergencies?
- Yeah.
Albright, listen. The Pin number
is your birthday.
Find an ATM, get out as much cash
as you can.
Go to the bridge directly,
and walk across.
Call me when you get to Queens.
- And son?
- Yeah?
Good luck.
OK. We're 20 minutes
from getting out of here.
Then he states a two hour drive.
We'll be safe, there.
That's off the grid.
I'm not going.
- What?
- I left that room
so we can find Will,
not to run.
Will is a part of this, man!
He's the one who parked the car
so they could take it.
Maybe he was set up too.
Did you ever think about that?
Maybe he had a gun to his head
when we talked to him on the phone.
We get his picture, take it to the feds.
- Let the system find him.
- But he doesn't want to be found!
Tyler!
Look, I know you and Will were closer,
that you knew him better.
But things are different now.
We are the ones out on this sidewalk,
not him.
- Then run, Tyler.
- Don't do this, Jay.
It'll be easier for you to get out
on your own.
I don't want to go without you.
All right, fine.
But I'm gonna wait for you
on the Queensbourough bridge footpath.
And if you're not there in an hour,
I'm gonna leave without you.
But Jay...
for both of our sakes,
I hope you're there with me when I go.
You're the tenth person who's called me.
I'm just getting home.
I'll call you later.
...were able to salvage
some of the artwork inside.
Along with Burchell,
police are looking for this man:
Tyler Fog.
He's the son of Carlton Fog,
one of the richest man in America
and convicted conspirator
for the Iran contract scandal
in the late 80s.
- I don't have a lot of time.
- Are you alright?
Are these all the pictures
that you have?
Calm down
and tell me what the hell is going on!
I've been calling you all day!
Come on, tell me so I can help.
We're not terrorists.
You know that, right?
Yeah, of course.
Why are they saying you're involved?
'Cause someone...
is trying to make it look like
it's our fault.
Look, Will was in the museum
when the bomb went off,
I need pictures,
just something to take to the cops.
Alright then. We'll look together.
Come on, Will!
Every photograph...
He never wanted his picture taken.
He'd try steeling my camera at parties.
Come on!
There's gotta be one!
It's okay, we'll keep looking.
It's not okay.
How could I live with him for two years,
and not have one picture of him?
Tyler was right.
Will was a part of this.
Ground zero.
My team found traces of aluminum,
naphtaline and palmitate.
Napalm.
Highly compressed
to get this kind of dispersion.
You think a law school grad
could do this?
Yeah, if he's Ted Kazinsky.
This is some pretty complex engineering.
I want a copy
of Burchell's and Fog's transcripts.
Sure thing.
Lucky that people got out.
Such a blast should have caused
more casualties.
Not everybody got out.
Burchell mentioned a friend
in a blue track jacket.
What about the idea
that this might somehow be
an act of retribution
for what happened to their fathers?
Perhaps, but if Fog and Burchell
have ties
to terrorist groups overseas,
they will be considered
enemy combatants
and remanded
to the military...
Alright. Then we get a lawyer!
A whole team of lawyers!
- This is not over!
- It is!
Tyler's dad said people knew
this was gonna happen.
You're gonna believe a man
like Carlton Fog?
Listen to what they're saying about us!
Enemy combatants!
Alright? If we go in now, they will
ship us out to Guantanamo Bay.
I'm sorry.
Will was my best friend.
I told him things, I trusted him.
What if everything he did and said
was a lie?
Then we...
- fight this!
- No, I have to fight this.
I don't want you to get involved.
You know,
half the city is on the streets.
By now, those people
are trying to get home
They haven't seen the news yet,
They're not focused
on what we look like.
But they will be soon.
Wait...
Somehow, I'm gonna see you again?
Do you remember
the first time we met?
Will did everything he could
to keep me from calling you.
He probably knew
it would complicate his plan.
But he didn't keep us apart then,
and he won't keep me
from coming back to you now.
You can't run from this.
My father died because someone
in the government betrayed him.
It didn't make me hate my country,
it made me want to fix it
but if I'm gonna fix this,
whatever is really going on,
I need to figure out
who Will Traveler really is.
- We got something here.
- What is it?
I've got Carlton Fog making
six $500 withdrawals
near 59 and Lex.
Carlton Fog is not in the city.
I want Burchell and Fog
wrapped up tight
before President Cheers
returns from Tokyo.
That means today!
Sir?
We found Tyler Fog.
- Can you hurry up, please?
- Have a little patience.
All units look for Tyler Fog.
White male...
12-9 to Central,
I've got the Drexler suspect
heading East to the tramway path.
What's your 20?
We're on it.
- Cover the block.
- Marlow!
FBI! I will fire!
Keep your hands up and turn around.
There's nowhere to run, Fog.
Cover me.
Look...
the guy you want left hours ago.
You can tell me all about it
when this is over.
Marlow, this is Chambers. Copy?
Take him.
Go for it, Marlow.
A call coming through
on your cell. Answer it.
- Who, sir?
- Jay Burchell.
- Okay, you're on, Mr. Burchell.
- Who am I talking to?
Mr. Burchell,
this is special agent Marlow.
- I'm glad you called.
- Stay down.
We're taking your friend
into custody.
Any chance you'll come in too?
I'm afraid I can't do that.
I won't tell you
how the law works.
If you don't cooperate now,
you'll go away for a long time
when we catch you.
I've got another bomb in the city.
I want you to call of your men
or I will have to detonate.
What if I said I think you're bluffing?
We found your friend Traveler
in the museum...
dead.
I'd say you'd never really know
what someone is capable of.
And you still have to take my deal.
I've got Burchell on hold.
What do we have ?
Cell tower put him
within a 3 block radius.
I'm working on video from dock cams.
- Marlow, I'm pulling you out.
- What?
- I want you out of there now.
- We can't negotiate!
We're not.
Tell him what he wants.
Let him see what he wants.
But I am moving undercover agents
in the area.
So give the word for your men
to stand down.
Yes, sir.
Put Burchell back on line.
It's your lucky day,
you can have your friend.
It's gonna take a minute to clear.
All units, pull back.
All units, pull back of the area.
Pull back!
Get him up!
- Uncuff him.
- What?
Come on, uncuff him!
Burchell, we're leaving Fog now.
Pull back !
The bomb. I want the location.
Brooklyn Bridge,
North West abutment.
- Jay, what did you tell them?
- I gave up a 2nd bomb.
- You did what?
- No, it worked.
Just like you said
it would, they're clearing out.
I didn't think you'd come back for me.
You'd do the same for me.
They'll still be watching the building.
Be careful getting out.
Okay, you too, pal.
That's enough, Mr. Fog.
It's a hell of a way
to start a road trip.
I should have listened to you
this morning.
Not Will.
Will's dead.
I know.
You were right about him.
Look, I know we've been at each other...
Shut up back there!
Get out!
On your feet!
Come with me.
Now!
Who are you?
I'm the only person who believes
your side of the story.
Wait a minute!
You just killed two FBI agents.
Get up!
What happened to Will?
If you know what's going on, tell us.
You'll need this more than me.
Once you get over the bridge,
the only people you trust
are each other.
Now go.
Go!
Dad, it's Tyler.
We just got out of the city.
If all goes well,
we'll be there by 7, maybe 8.
You must be Will.
- Oh, actually I'm Jay.
- I thought I'd take a chance.
Tyler Fog.
Wait, you're a Cubs fan?
I thought you were from L.A.?
My dad was from Chicago.
I was actually at the game
when Barber went for the foul ball,
- cost him a pennant, total heartbreak.
- Yet again.
And the circle is complete.
Hey, you must be Will Traveler?
- Yeah.
- Tyler Fog, school management.
- This is...
- Jay.
Jay Burchell, law school.
I read the housing ticket.
Looks like we've got a nice place.
Yeah, well, wait till you see upstairs.
I'm sorry, guys, I have to take this.
Hey, dad, can I call you back?
So that's Tyler Fog?
I wonder what he's doing
in grad housing.
I'm sure he'll be happy to tell us.
You're kidding me? You're a Cubs fan?
Yeah, we just went through this.
Wait. You too?
I am loving this house already.
Wait. What are the chances that 3 guys
from L.A, Maine and the Hamptons
all like the same team?
Must be fate.
I know a garage in 51st.
It's half the price.
I'll meet you in the room.
You take time to step off the path
and really see
what makes this country tick?
- It'll change your life.
- If you're out, we are.
Good luck. I'm sorry I had to do this.
My dad knows a used car dealership
2 blocks away
and they take cash.
Can he help us track down
and phone Will?
- He's the only lead we got.
- He's already looking into it.
- Dad?
- Okay, son, listen...
Call from the road
if you have any problems.
We'll see you soon.
I've done as you asked,
they'll be here tonight.