David, I still believe in your presidency,
and if Milliken threatens your ability
to lead this country, he will be stopped.
Milliken was driving the car
that killed your daughter 12 years ago.
Yeah. I saw Milliken driving the car that night.
Kelly was the only one who saw it,
then Milliken got to him.
- He'll swear to this?
- Yes.
Mr Kelly?
(gasps)
- (Adam) What is that?
- A baby.
I can see that it's a baby. Whose is it?
- Chloe's.
- Chloe doesn't have a baby.
Adam just told me you're not the mother.
I think she's delusional.
She's the only one capable
of filtering Chase's audio strains.
- If Chloe is unstable...
- We've no alternative. We've got to keep her.
Amador will be here in 15 minutes.
Confirm that he has the virus, give him
his money and bring the virus back to us.
Good job. I don't need you any more.
He's gonna kill him.
Delta teams won't get there.
- Ram Ãn, we had a deal.
- (gunshot)
- Chase!
- (Chase) Tony, Delta's here.
All we want is the virus.
Just put the cylinder down slowly.
We do not have the virus.
The cylinder was rigged with a bomb.
Amador switched it. Do we have his position?
(Tony) Delta has a team on him.
He won't get far.
(man) Hands in the air. Get on the ground.
(Tony) Amador ambushed Delta Three.
It was a setup.
- (Jack) What about his position?
- We lost his signal.
Son of a bitch. Delta Three's been taken out.
They don't have a position on Amador.
- What do you wanna do?
- We gotta find Nina.
- Jack.
- This is Bauer.
- I have an area lit past the road. Is that you?
- Negative.
- I'll check it out.
- Be careful.
(Nina) Stop right there.
Drop your gun.
Drop it! Put your hands on your head.
- You on a two-way with Jack?
- Yeah.
Give him a code six.
I'm gonna reach in my bag
and I'm gonna pull out a two-way.
Slowly.
Jack?
- Yeah?
- Code six.
What about the light you saw?
It was nothing.
Off, not standby. Throw it over here.
(beep)
- Who is on the grid?
- Just me and Jack.
- You're lying. I saw a Delta team.
- They went north.
- What about Amador?
- He escaped with the virus.
He ripped off everybody.
Son of a bitch.
All right. Move down the hill.
- Where are we going?
- Just walk.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Contact Delta.
Tell them to meet us at the airfield.
- What are you gonna do?
- lnterrogate her.
- No, he's not.
- Shut up!
Chase, please, just trust me.
I'll meet you at the airfield.
Jack, Amador still has the virus.
I can help you track him.
He chose here cos it's close to the border.
He needs to get back to LA.
Once he does, he'll meet somebody,
unload the virus and disappear.
I can help you find him.
Jack, I don't want to die.
Let me help you find him.
I can help you.
(beep)
- CTU.
- This is Bauer. Patch me through to Almeida.
(phone rings)
Almeida.
I've got Nina Myers. Alive.
Any sign of Amador?
No. Once the satellite comes around,
we'll do a sweep.
- Nina says he's headed to Los Angeles.
- Do you believe her?
I think she knows something. She wants to
cut a deal. We gotta bring her back to CTU.
OK. I'll get a Delta plane ready.
Copy that.
Get up. Slowly.
Tony, I'm coordinating too many comms. I
need to off-load some of it to Adam's group.
- You have everything?
- Yeah.
Look, Chloe, uh...
you need to go talk to Chappelle.
For what?
You know what for.
(phone rings)
- Kim Bauer.
- Did you update the logs?
Most of them.
What's going on with Dad and Chase?
That's why I called. They're headed back to
LA. They lost Amador. We're looking for him.
- What about Nina?
- They're bringing her with them.
- Thank you, Tony.
- All right. You got it.
(baby gurgles)
I'd love nothing more,
but we have to prioritise.
- (man) I understand. Keep me posted.
- All right. Yeah. All right. I gotta go.
- Tony said you wanted to talk. Here I am.
- Sit down.
If you want me to talk about the baby, you're
wasting your time because I'm not gonna.
So sit down. Tell me what the hell's going on.
What?
All right. First you told us the baby
was yours. We found out that was a lie.
Then you say you and your boyfriend took it
from its mother because it was being abused.
I did say that and I'd like
to correct that right now.
I don't have a boyfriend.
You're unbelievable.
- Who does the baby belong to?
- I can't tell you.
You brought in an unauthorised person.
That's a federal offence.
- It's just a baby.
- I don't care who it is, you're in violation.
- Fine. I'm in violation.
- Who does the baby belong to, Chloe?
Do you want me to take it to the lab
and run blood tests to get an lD? Cos I will.
I'm not gonna talk about this baby.
It's not because I'm an evil person.
It's just because I can't do it. Just
please don't start sticking needles in her.
- Eileen?
- Yes, Mr Chappelle?
Send security in. I want Chloe O'Brian under
guard while we run some tests on the baby.
Right away, sir.
Tony Almeida from CTU has just informed us
that they were unable to confiscate
this Cordilla virus in Mexico.
I thought they located the seller
and had the area surrounded.
The seller, a man named Michael Amador,
he never intended to give up the virus.
In fact, it was a well-planned rip-off.
David, we lost six men.
Members of a Delta team.
We lost a Delta team?
This man, Amador, where is he now?
The theory is that Amador has this virus
- and is headed back here to LA.
- To release it?
We don't know, but he has no history
of implementing terrorist strikes.
He's an arms dealer with no known ideology.
The bottom line is
we just don't know what his intentions are.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
I finally reached Sherry Palmer.
- Is she on the line now?
- Yes, sir.
Continue here, Wayne.
Sherry?
I'm sorry I couldn't call back.
I had to leave Kelly's in a hurry.
- Did you talk to him after we spoke?
- That's just it. When I got back, he was gone.
- Gone? Do you think he ran?
- No, I don't.
He was more than ready
to come forward against Milliken.
- Someone obviously got to him first.
- But you didn't see anyone?
No. I ran back to my car and got out of there.
I was, uh... I was pretty there scared, David.
Milliken must be on to you. Get back here.
It's not safe for you out there any more.
I really need to do something first.
- What?
- I've got to go see Julia Milliken.
No. No. I don't want you to go
anywhere near her or Alan tonight.
I have to. Milliken had to move fast in order to
kidnap, maybe even kill, this Kevin Kelly guy.
I must take advantage of that
before he covers his tracks.
Sherry, I do not want you confronting Alan.
I told you, David,
I'm just going to talk to Julia.
I promise, I'll stay away from Alan.
- Sherry...
- David.
You asked me to help you, right?
Please, let me do that.
- What happened?
- She wants to help find Amador.
Agent Bauer? Mike Murphy, Delta Four. The
navy was good enough to reroute a C-130.
- Tell them we said thank you.
- We're taking you and the prisoner to LA.
- Any movement on Amador?
- No.
Air Tactical's been monitoring the area.
So far, nothing.
- Jack, you sure you want to leave?
- Secure her.
Amador's already gone.
He's planned this thing well.
We need to find who wants the virus
and where and when they're releasing it.
We need to leave.
- (man) Hello.
- Marcus, it's me.
- Where are you?
- I'll be there in an hour.
- You got the virus?
- Yes. Just be ready.
I will be.
(cellphone rings)
- Hello?
- Julia?
- I'm almost there. Where's Alan now?
- He's in his room.
- Is he asleep?
- No. He just got off the phone with someone.
- Do you know who was he was talking to?
- No, no.
How do I get to you without him knowing?
The gate code is 41-32.
Park off to the side and walk up
to the service porch. I'll be there.
- All right. What's that number again?
- 41-32.
- OK. Are there any security cameras?
- Yes.
- Make sure they're disabled.
- I don't know if I can.
Find a way, Julia.
I'll be there in a few minutes.
(TV in background)
You're up late.
Ken called from Singapore.
He still hasn't figured out
how to calculate the time difference.
- You should be in bed yourself.
- I will.
I just put on some tea.
I'd like to settle my stomach.
- All right, then.
- All right.
- Good night.
Julia?
I know you felt demeaned earlier.
That's behind us now.
I know it is.
I let you live. Tell me what you know.
When Amador does business on the West
Coast, he washes his deal through Alvers.
Alvers. What's his first name?
All I is know "Alvers".
- How does Amador contact this Alvers?
- I don't know. I've never met him.
But I did check out Amador before our deal
and I kept coming across the name "Alvers".
It was a connector to a lot of his past deals
and Los Angeles was always the hub.
- Chase, you on with CTU?
- Yeah, it's Tony.
- Tell him I want to speak to him.
- Tony, Jack wants to talk to you.
- Tony.
- Hey, Jack.
I want you to run a check on the name
"Alvers". Cross-reference it with Amador.
- Is that it?
- Yeah. Just the name - "Alvers". A-l-v-e-r-s.
- You got this from Nina?
- Yeah.
- All right. I'll work it up. I'll get back to you.
- OK. Thanks.
Keep it.
- How's the hand?
- Don't worry about it. It's fine.
You and I have been through a lot today.
We should move past it and do our job.
You don't trust me, Jack. Why didn't
you tell me about your deal with Hector?
It couldn't go beyond Gael, Tony and myself.
What did you think? That I wasn't
going to come after you and Ram Ãn?
- I didn't know whether to save or kill you.
- I expected you to follow my orders.
But I probably would've
done the same thing myself.
You put a gun to my head.
And you pulled the trigger.
I made a judgment call that Salazar would not
give me a loaded weapon, that it was a test.
And if it was loaded?
- Then what?
- I'd have finished my mission.
You do this job long enough,
you're gonna have to make choices,
and you don't know you've made
the right one until the scenario plays out.
The only thing that matters is that if we don't
stop this virus, the world will change forever.
And that fact alone
is the only thing that you have to keep
in the front of your mind, and you know that.
- Yeah.
Keep pressing her.
She probably hasn't told you everything.
No, she probably hasn't.
But we're gonna have to wait.
Make sure Alvers is a real lead.
Over a 1,000 "Alvers"
showed up in the database.
I did background checks and consistency refs
with Amador. Only one red-flagged.
Marcus Alvers.
Born in Austria. Moved to England.
Met Amador in Cambridge,
where Alvers studied biology.
In 1994 they were suspected
of manufacturing weapons-grade anthrax.
- But there was no evidence.
- Sounds like our guy.
The dossier's sketchy, but they've
definitely crossed paths over the years.
The ClA had these on file.
Over the past three years there have been 14
sightings of Alvers and Amador together.
All right. So, how do we find Alvers?
We have some threads.
We'll need manpower from Division.
Michelle, hook 'em up.
(cellphone rings)
- Bauer.
- We got a match on Alvers.
Now we gotta find him. It'll take some time.
Yeah. I'll see what we can do from here.
We're on.
Looks like the information
you gave us is real.
Of course it is. CTU's not going to
find him before his meeting with Amador.
- But I can help you.
- How?
I know a little more than I said I did.
I know there's no time for a signed deal,
so I'm gonna trust you'll support my case
with the Department of Justice if I help you.
You've got my word.
His name is Marcus Frederick Alvers. He's
an amateur biologist and wannabe terrorist.
Raised hell from Vienna to Los Angeles,
with a two-year stop in London.
I have a number for him.
Dial a Felco prefix, then you reach him
through an internet socket.
Give me the cold line.
What's the number?
It's 1775531.
You're gonna get a fast busy signal,
but don't hang up.
- I've got the busy signal.
- Hit nine and hold it for three seconds.
- Did you get a tone?
- Yeah, I've got a tone.
Hit 95731-star-6.
It's ringing.
When the ringing stops, you're gonna get
a series of numbers. That's your lP address.
It's stopped ringing.
- I'm not getting any numbers.
- It's OK. Just wait.
- (phone rings)
- Yeah?
The tech room is spiking all over the place.
Can you reset it?
I don't know. I'll have to get back to you.
Adam, what's going on? My system's locked.
- Division. Tech.
- It's Adam in CTU.
Adam, look, we don't know what's going on.
We're locked up here too. I'll get back to you.
(dials)
- No need to dial it again. Once was enough.
- What are you talking about?
You just triggered a worm that's going
to bring down agency connectivity.
My God, what have you done?
What have you done?
Until I say otherwise, your antiterrorist
computer network is jammed.
We got a self-propagating code
leaking into the system.
Shut down your sockets. Save everything
you can. We gotta find where this came from.
- (Tony) Nina did this?
- She knew our system better than anyone.
She embedded a worm where
she knew we'd never upgrade.
She told you this? What does she want?
- I don't know. Can you stop this thing?
- We're doing our best, Jack.
Pull Chloe out of my sector.
She's been asked to step aside.
- What are you talking about?
- It's a long story.
This is not the time to take Chloe out of play.
You know how many terrorist cells
try to hack into our system.
If this eats through our fire walls,
agents will be targets.
What about Nina?
Will she tell us how to neutralise this?
- I'll start working on it. I'll get back to you.
- All right.
- What do you want?
- Turn around and head back to Mexico.
Once you do, I'll slow down
the spread of the worm.
- When I'm safe, I'll give you the kill code.
- That'll never happen.
How many terrorist cells are waiting
for a window like this? 200?
In 30 minutes they'll all have access to CTU
files everywhere. Turn the plane around.
- You're assuming we can't stop this thing.
- I invite you to try.
Ryan, I know.
But Chloe's the only one who knows enough
about this section of code to stop the worm.
- Fine. Steve, you can go.
- Yes, sir.
- What's happening?
- There's a worm in our network.
Nina Myers somehow launched it remotely
and it's running rampant.
Tony says you can stop it. Is that correct?
- If it hasn't destroyed the routing data.
- Good. Do it.
- Did you close the gateways?
- Yeah.
- Reopen 12 and 14.
- What for?
They won't leak
and they get us to the kernel.
Dalton, ping the nodes in lT. If you stop
getting packet loss, freeze the process.
- I'll be in the tech room.
- All right.
I'm not comfortable with you being here,
so just tell me what you want.
Come on, Julia, I told you earlier. I know
about your marriage, I know about your life.
I know you'd rather be with a man you love,
but you stay with Alan
because of his money and the security.
I don't need a drive-through shrink,
so unless you have a real reason to be...
How about murder?
What are you talking about?
A man named Kevin Kelly has information
on Alan that could hurt him very badly.
An hour ago, Kelly disappeared.
- Disappeared?
- It's possible he was killed.
- And you think Alan is involved?
- Sweetie, I know Alan is involved.
And you're gonna help me prove it.
Even if I could do that, why would l?
Because it's your ticket out of here.
If Alan goes to prison,
you get everything, Julia.
What would you need me to do?
First, I need you to find out what phone
calls he's made in the past two hours.
- He makes his calls behind closed doors.
- Does he use the house phone?
His cell. He keeps it with him.
It makes things easier with his wheelchair.
- Where's his cellphone now?
- In his room.
- I need you to get that phone.
- No.
Alan just went to bed.
I'm not sure he's asleep yet.
Well, then, why don't you find out?
I can't.
Don't you want to be free of him?
- I'm afraid.
- Well, I'm not.
Where's the bedroom?
(creak)
Set the group permission on the beta node
to 577 and make it recursive down the tree.
I want anyone who's on the cipher volume
to stay off until I'm done.
- Adam, are those gateways open?
- Of course.
I'm trying to see the virus definition.
- I hope you have enough to go on.
- We'll know in a minute.
It's sad that I have to do this knowing
that you and Kim stabbed me in the back.
What do you want me to do? You're breaking
rules and lying about it all the place.
- Tell me what you'd do.
- I'd have faith in my fellow worker.
No, you'd follow protocol.
You're the biggest rule freak of anyone.
I've done a good job at breaking the rules,
trying to protect a friend and that baby.
What friend?
(bleeping)
It's done. Dammit.
- It didn't work?
- The worm's speeding up!
- How is that possible?
- We triggered something. Open 1 and 4.
- Won't that expose the kernel?
- Yeah, but we have no choice. Do it.
- (man) 07?
- No. 47.
Yes. And the last one on here
has a 206 area code.
- Washington?
- Yeah. That's 555-0191.
- That's it?
- Yeah.
OK. And, Brian? Thank you so much.
- You OK?
- Yeah. Just call me. All right.
What are you doing?
I have someone who can track
the calls made from this phone.
If any of them can be connected to Kelly, we
have evidence that we can use against Alan.
- What should I do?
- Nothing. Absolutely nothing.
Just go to bed and, as far as you're
concerned, nothing happened here.
Julia. Why aren't you in bed?
And who are you talking to?
Sherry?
Hello, Alan.
- Julia, I'm disappointed in you.
- I didn't ask her here.
But you let her in
and you took my cellphone as well.
No.
I took the phone.
So, what do you think you're going to do,
Sherry? Stop me? That's not likely.
All right.
You want to talk about this in the open? Fine.
What happened to Kevin Kelly?
- Kevin Kelly. The name rings a bell.
- Well, it should ring a bell.
He's the man that saw you run over
his daughter and kill her 12 years ago.
The man you paid a considerable amount
of money to keep quiet.
And the man you made disappear tonight.
So, why don't you chew on that a bit?
And maybe we can talk about it
a little more tomorrow.
Or we can end it now
and you can back off David.
(phone rings)
- Bauer.
- (man) Chloe O'Brian for you.
- Fine. Patch her through.
- Yes, sir.
(Jack) I understand the system's going down.
Have you tried all the security codes?
What do you suggest?
Nina, I've heard all about you.
I know what you've done,
and how you've stayed alive is impressive.
But if you try to play Jack one more time...
he's going to kill you.
Is that so?
Yeah.
I'm going to put you on speakerphone.
In three minutes our system will be down.
If you want any leverage,
tell me how to stop this thing now.
- It doesn't move that fast.
- You're wrong. Chloe, put it up on the screen.
You're running out of time to cut a deal.
Explain it to her, Chloe.
When I tried to separate the routers,
the worm speed tripled.
- Who is this?
- Chloe O'Brian.
My network monitor's up. What do I do?
Log in with user lD: ClS 27 A.
- It's asking for a security level.
- Hit Escape 6.
- That's it?
- Yes.
- (Jack) Chloe, did that stop it?
- No.
Wait a minute.
It didn't stop, but it's slowing down.
- How much time do we have?
- Our simulation says 20 minutes.
- I'll get back to you.
- OK, I slowed it down.
Now turn around and head back to Mexico.
If you don't, you can expect your undercover
agents to start dying within the hour.
You're going to LA. You're gonna help me
find Amador and then go to prison.
That's what's happening here.
You come into my house
after everything I've done for your family?
I made your children's father
the president of the United States!
Wait a minute. Whatever you did to help
David was not for the benefit of my children.
You're just a small man, who lords his money
over his friends because that's all you have.
That's all you are. Why do you think your wife
had to go out and find another man?
- Don't talk to me like this.
- Because you're not one!
Not one woman in her right mind would
find you attractive without your wealth, Alan.
That's what people want from you.
That's all Julia wants from you.
I'm supposed to be afraid of you? You think
I'm scared of you? You're just a little boy.
A pathetic, scrawny, sickly little boy.
(wheezing) Julia! My pills, my pills.
- Don't.
- What are you doing?
- Sherry?
- Don't.
- (gasping) Julia. Julia.
This is your way out.
Julia!
Julia! Julia!
All right. We can't stay here, Julia.
- We killed him.
- No, no. No one killed him.
- We watched him die.
- It's over, Julia.
- We watched him!
- It's over! Shh!
Now, Alan was a sick little man
and his weak body gave out.
Nobody was around to help him and
you were in your bedroom. Understand me?
You're free of him, sweetie.
That's all you need to think about.
But there's one thing
you're gonna have to be clear about
when the authorities
come around questioning you.
This was an accident.
- I don't think I can do this.
- You don't have a choice.
Unless you want to spend
the rest of your pretty little life in prison.
Oh, God.
All right. You go into your bedroom.
You stay there for about an hour.
Then you're gonna come out
for a glass of water,
and then you're gonna see the body.
Now, that's your story.
Who do I call?
911.
That's what you would naturally do, right?
OK.
- What about you?
- No, no. You listen.
You listen real strong
because this is very crucial.
If anyone suspects that I was here,
there will be an investigation,
and both of us will go to prison.
I was never here.
You understand me?
Julia, you tell me right now
that you understand what I'm saying.
I understand.
OK.
(computer alarm signal)
Stop that process. It's making it worse.
- What is it?
- I'm not getting it.
- What'll it take?
- I don't know.
If you can't stop this worm,
I have to tell Jack to reroute that plane.
Tony, please let me work.
(dials)
- Bauer.
- Jack.
- Tell me you've got a handle on this thing.
- We don't.
Nina's not gonna give us the kill code until
we turn the plane around back to Mexico.
We don't have a choice. Tell the pilot to
reroute now. We have to do whatever it takes.
- That's not an alternative. Tony? Tony?
- (interference on line)
Son of a bitch.
Once the damage is done, you won't be able
to cut a deal. Give me the kill code.
Jack.
Think about it.
You should give her what she wants now.
It's not worth it.
We'll deal with her later.
If you turn the plane around,
I can slow this thing down even more.
But I'm not giving you the kill code
until I'm safe in Mexico.
(engine noise)
- What's going on?
- We're going back up.
Son of a bitch.
- What are you doing?
- I got orders from Almeida not to land.
- He said to take the plane to Mexico.
- Land the plane now.
I got my orders.
Don't even think about it.
Land the plane!
What the hell is he doing?
Lieutenant, why aren't you turning around?
- Bauer won't let me.
- What do you mean?
- He's got a gun on me.
- Put me on speaker.
- Jack, can you hear me?
- Yeah, and we're landing in Los Angeles.
We need that kill code. Tell the pilot
to turn around. That's an order from Division.
- We can't keep giving in to her.
- Wait. I think I'm getting something.
I can't take that chance. We have to stop this
or agents are gonna wind up dead.
- Our people are gonna have to stop it.
- We're trying. We don't have the time.
Turning around won't help. It'll take us
farther from where we need to be.
- Chloe.
- Please shut up. Dalton, bring it back to 50.
- OK. I'm clear.
- What branches?
- 14 through 20.
- Dalton?
- Yeah. The routers are coming back up.
- Are we OK?
- I can't tell.
- Yeah. Here, here. It's coming back up.
(beeping)
- No, stop the process.
- It's cycling through. It's almost back up.
It's a defensive ploy built into the worm.
It's a simple back-pop virus.
- I've tripped out the resource fork.
- The CPU is almost 100 per cent.
- Stop. What you see on the monitor isn't real.
- Do what she says.
All right. It's stopped.
- Wait. What's going on?
- I think it's resetting itself.
We got it.
Jack? We're back up.
- Fully functional?
- Fully functional.
We're resuming our approach. Good work.
You can file a report
with your commanding officer.
All our systems are up and running.
I don't believe you.
I don't care what you believe.
- Check your directories.
- I'm on it. What about the network volumes?
Let's remount those six at a time
until they're all on.
- OK. These all look good. Dalton?
- There's some drop-out.
But it'll self-adjust in ten minutes.
Great work today. You averted
what could have been a major loss.
- I know. Are Jack and Chase back soon?
- Yeah. Where are you going?
- Back upstairs.
- No.
This whole thing with the baby
isn't going to just go away.
What you did will certainly bear well
on your case, but the charges still stand.
We're handing you over to LAPD
and, no matter what happens,
you'll have to tell them
who this baby belongs to.
- Where are they taking Angela?
- Child Protective Services has custody now.
- No, they can't do that.
- Of course they can.
- Child Services, hold on!
- What are you doing?
I'll tell you who the father is.
Don't ask me who the mother is, I don't know.
I was doing a favour. I swear it's the truth.
Barb.
We're gonna hold on to her a little longer.
We just got some more information.
Why didn't you tell me this earlier?
He didn't want me to tell anyone.
I was trying to be a friend. Sorry.
Chloe. I heard you stopped the worm.
Yeah. Your dad and Chase are back in LA.
You must be relieved.
Yes. Thank you.
Look, Chloe, what about the baby?
- What?
- I thought they were pressing charges.
- No. That was a misunderstanding.
- Chloe, wait.
- What?
- So, they're not pressing charges?
- No.
- Why not?
I told them who the father was
and everything's OK.
Everything's OK? Why?
Who's the father?
Chase.
Visiontext Subtitles: Katherine Appleby
ENGLlSH SDH