previously on despertae housewives
If you're trying  to come between me and my husband,I will take you down
bring it on
Gaberille threat the nun
you good to go
Susan hit on her doctoer
so you came to ask me out,cause i'll say yes
bree's daughter let her intention being known
it's amazing how far we're willing to go
Andrew,give me one  good reason  why shouldn't  call the police
because i'm your son
all in the name of love
If there is one thing Eddie Brit understood,it was nature of war
after two fail marriages and countless rocky  romances
She had learned love was a  battle field
it is the easiest way to survive the carnage was total surrender
i was thinking a vacation of roma will be so romantic
Vegas is cheaper
could you put yor underwear in the heper
can you do it   you standing right there
i got a hankering for chinese food tonight
i'm so over rice  Let's do pizza
but the day comes for every assaulter  when she must take a stand
what do you think you're doing?
and fight
it's time for my game
i want to watch my movie
Eddie,this is important to me
fine
i have stuff to do anyway
You see when it came to man,Eddie had a battle plan of her own
you have five minutes for Eddie?
that's some knot  you tied
yeah? that's no fun it's not tight
you know what would be hot,whipped cream
you're so bad
you have no idea
yes,eddie brit understood the nature of war
Eddie it has been ten minutes
Where 's the damn whipped cream
She also know to the victor go the spoils
Eddie!
the guest bedroom on the second floor of  Whiteapples' house  had the best view in all misteria lane
from it's windows one could see Mike Delfino's house one down the street
all the way to old huber's place one on the other
but unfortunately for the room's newest guest
the view is about to change,dramatically
What on earth is he doing here?
matthew,go to your room
mom and i gonna have a talk now
he has a room ?have your lost your mind
relax I take newpapers set to the windows people can't see him
kela£¬get back down there
nono we had a talk it's fine he understand what could happen  if he was discovered
for five sec he understand and forget
you know that ?
we can protect him without treating him like an animal
I'm keeping him safe from the police from the fosters from him themselves
he is not going back downstairs
Since when do you talk to me like that
Since i share the risk
i have a few annoucement
I would like to acknowledge Mrs harber for  holding the potluck dinner
for hard working
she is adorable ins't she
she is okay
next saturday the woman's ministration...
she's gorgeous
knock it off
baby's baby'
sound  like a broken record     i just had miscarriage
it will take some time befor i get ready for  get pregant  again
any idea you'll be ready£¬you know
stop it
i just enjoy it the here and now
we're together,we have just backed on track  life  is good
before we wrap up,we have a dear friend back form her missionary trip to tell us  about her experiences
Sister mary Bernard
son of a bitch
Daniel
Honey are you in there
i'm doing homework
really because i'm holding your backpack with all your schoolbooks
hold on
thanks mom i  was just doing a lttle research on line
I m here mess and grab some  laundry
pleas not right now
honey stop complaining
one day you will wish someone offer  to do your laundry
Daniel,question  is there a black man hiding under your bed
what is going on ?
i just thought you should know i came home to find your song hiding underneath my daughter's bed
it just seems to me
inside,right now
i apologize  for my son 's behavior it won't happen again
for the house we sell and we're moving
now,if you excuse me
how is it going?
not good
i'm trying to salvage the pitch from the black frozen yorghout  campaign
you know what kills me
yeah?
here we are  T-minus 9 hours  eleven minutes from the biggest pitch  in our company's history
and i have nothing even vaguely presentable
- i will get the coffe
- thank you
you wanna go over it   and toss some ideas around
no that's okay
i know you're exhausted you should go to bed
come on honey let's do this let's nail this sucker
what do we got
we got nothing
okay
black frozen yoghourt let you taste bud come in from the cold
you know whatever i  just knock the rust off  i know i can do better
blacks the froe-yor the make you go wow
come on i'm sorry i just really need focus here
black frozen yoghourt  beacuse our cows are better
or froghourt
froghourt  it's fun to eat fun to say
That 's actually good
really?
no,the cow part that can work
we'll make them characters  we'll humanize them
Oh! i know  i know  celebrity cow spooks people
yes that's exactly what i was thinking you know like famouse characters
like  reworen  Moo
what do you think of that
thank you i have fabulous time
me too
I guess i'd better get going
julie is staying in her father's house and i'm all alone here
sometimes it actually make me a little nervous
turn the TV on that 's what i do
oh that's a good idea
I forgot i have a bottle of wine
it's already chilled in the refrigerator
i don't know it's just really relax me
that's good
so we still good for thursday
yeah
thursday is great
good night
do i just repulse you
no why
we've been on three dates and you just keep acting like a perfect gentleman
getting a little odd
Susan,you make no mistake  i'm like inches away from  ripping off  you clothes right now
and you stopping why?
I'm still your doc,it's not quite ethical,yeah
why are we dating
it's only temporary  once you 're well  i'm done treating you   all bets are  off
okay
what the hell
okay that's sorta feel unethical
thank you for meeting with me
sure  i didn't invite you to the house  but  the place's real pick site
carlos i'm a nun not a moron
i know gab despise me
she is just jealous that's all
of me,oh,isn't that silly
she refuse to believe that i can  connect with anyone on a spiritual  level
we do have an amazing connection
that's why i want to talk to you
when i saw you at the church
i can tell instantly you're unhappy
okay,maybe i have been a little  down lately
tell me
this whole have no kids thing
sister mary i want them so bad
gab still refuse to give them to you
to be fair,she did have  miscarriage recently
what if  she decide to agaist kids
what if this just all stalk tacted
that i'm screwed
sorry
you're right
you're screwed
unless?
unless what
american  catholics guide to annulments
sister mary what is exactly what are you saying here
I'm saying god help those who help themselves
hey,i got great news
we just landed the black frozen yorghout  account
really they love the pitch ?
The talking cows rocking their world
how do they like my bull clinton idea
well i rewrote some of  stuff we work on
but you know essentially it'sthe same  and they eat it up
that is fantastic
finally we can afford hire another executive
terrific,tell me did they like the promtion plan about a bounch of cow eating  contest
the pitch was running long so we cut off a few things
I'm just glad they love my idea
to be fair
do they like the hugh  play cows
they're calling in for meeting  i gotta go
i love you bye
so this is your spleen
normally it would over here because your missing ligament structure
it has wander under over there right  next to the liver
we discuss about this aftermeaning
every one  thinks you should remove it immediately
okay
i guess you guys have all sorts of  new exciting  technians  you don't even cut open the body
no not really
no?
so we're talking surgery
well i guess i can handle that
people got cut  open everyday
so i assume you will let me do the surgery
you ?
it seems natural  i know the most about your case  i promise you will be in very good hands
what?
the first time you see me naked  i will be on an operating table
i promise i will be a perfect gentleman my eyes will be strictly on the spleen
docter mrs baker is here for her follow-up
we need to schedule susan for splenectomy,with me
Oh,congratulations!
So I will call you later?
Oh,I am so happy for him.He's such a doll.
I'm curious. Um...
why were youso congratulatory?
Oh,the spleen surgery--
it'll be his first!
Hey,honey.
Can we talkabout something?
Sure.
So I've been thinkingabout the whole baby thing.
And how ever long it takes for you to feel ready,I am fine with.
Okay.
But here's the deal--
I need to knowthat this isn't a maybe.
I want a promisethat we will have children.
I'm sorry.I can't promise that.
Why not?
Because I can't saythat I'm gonna wake up tomorrow
and suddenly wanna do somethingthat I swore my entire life
I would never do. "Maybe" isa very big step for me.
Yeah,well,it isn'tbig enough for me.
Well,I'm sorry,but you'rejust gonna have to accept it.
There's nothing else you can do.
That isn'tnecessarily true.
Excuse me?
Annulments
You are threatening mewith an annulment?
That conniving little bitchput you up to this,didn't she?
Didn't she?
This fight could beover right now
if you'd justmake me a promise.
The only promiseI am making you
is that this isso not over.
hi!
Hey.
Hi.
How's the search coming forthe new ad exec? Any luck?
Oh,the pickings are slim.
So far none ofmy top choices are available.
Hey,um,do you have someonefrom your old company
that you could,you know,maybe recommend?
Daddy!Well--
I can't find my toothbrush.
I'll be upin a second,buddy.
Hi.
As a matter of fact,
there's this one guy who would be perfect.
Yeah?
Yeah,hard-working,smart as a whip. Total package.
Really? What's his name?
Tom.
Tom? Tom what?
Tom scavo.
no! No!
I do not think thatthat is a good idea.
Come on,honey,I mean,the other nightdoing those pitches--
it just gotthe old juices flowing.
I remembered how muchI miss having a real job.
You have a real job,right herestaying home with the kids.
With two incomes,we couldafford a top-notch nanny.
What about penny?
You're the one who fought foroffice day care. Let's use it.
What about the two of us workingand living together?
I think that could bea recipe for disaster.
Why? The last timethat we worked together...
we fell in love.
Oh,it's just...
I'M...
I'm not sure that you would findthis job that satisfying.
You don't thinkI'm good enough,do you?
I'm not saying that.
Daddy,I stillcan't find my toothbrush!
- I'll go.
- I got it.
Come on,buddy.Let's hunt it down.
So who won the fight?
We weren't fighting.
Mommy's just lettingdaddy know where he stands.
Oh,hey! Hey!
- thanks for coming in,mr. Gainey.
- We'll be in touch.
Thank you. Bye.
What did you think?
Well,honestly,I wasn't blown away.
I know the pickingsare slim,
but we can't hold outmuch longer.
We need to hiresomeone this week.
I know! I know! I know.
So who's up next?
Tom cavos.You ever heard of him?
Just... uh...
could you excuse mefor just a minute?
Sure.
- Tom cavos?
- Yeah,it's an anagram.
It's deceptively simple,don't you think?
What do you think
you're doing?
I'm going overyour head.
I mean,you mightnot think I'm good enough,
but maybe ed will bea little more open-minded,
since,you know,he's notconstantly competing with me.
You want the truth,tom?
I think you're good.You have moments of brilliance.
But I also thinksometimes you coast.
And I thinkif i were your boss
and had to ride your assevery day,
you would come homeseething with resentment.
Come on! It's hard enoughkeeping a marriage together.
If you're at all concernedabout saving our marriage,
you better let metake my shot.
What does that mean?
It means that a little partof me has been hating you
ever since you tankedmy promotion at petersen.
Tom...
but I could let it all go ifyou'll give me this one thing.
Excuse me.Ed's waiting for you guys.
Great! Great!
Just let my résuméspeak for itself.
Uh,just let your résuméspeak for itself?
Yes.
okay!
Oh! You workedthe poncer cheese accounts?
Those "angry mouse" spots?They were hilarious!
I was on thatfrom the beginning.
warning,do not eat the cheese!
The cheese is evil!
I love that!
You've got a great résum?Thank you.
Yeah,gosh,it is.It's quite impressive.
Oh,wow,I see you workedfor bellfore and barrasso.
That's a great shop.
Yeah,I put my time in.
Uh-huh,and when were you there?
Because you forgot to list your dates of employmentfor that one.
Um,that wasa few years back.
Uh-huh. And how longdid you stay?
Just about five months,actually.
What,did you getrecruited by another firm?
Did somebodycherry-pick ya?
No,I was fired.
Yeah,but honestly,I was happy to leave
because they didn't getmy sense of humor.
I actually pitched a version of the "cheese is evil"there first.
They hated it.
Idiots!Well,their loss,right?
Yep.And I see you won a clio for the thompson's salad dressing spot.
That was very cool.
So did you do that solo?
Actually,no. My wifehelped me on that one.
Um,she's inadvertising,too.
But if you were to ask her,
I'm sure she'd tell you she did the whole thing all by herself.
credit hog,huh?I know the type.
You know what,tom?I like you.
Ed...
and I'm not usually onefor hiring in the room.
No,no,no,no,we never hire in the room.
But we're in a time crunch,and we need someone now.
I think you're the guy.
Lynette,you got any issues?
Well...
um,let me just call ina few references
before we makeanything official.
Sure! Sure!We'll be in touch,okay?
the cheese is evil!
Oh,god,I love that.
Oh,um,I'm lookingfor father crowley.
Do you know where he is?
Um,he's inthe confessional.
How long has it beensince your last confession?
Who cares?
Father,it's me.
Gabrielle?
Yeah.
Look,I need youto do something for me.
I need you to get rid ofsister mary bernard.
What? Why?
Because she's ruiningmy marriage.
- Sister mary?
- Yes!
At first it startedwith the love letters while he was in prison,
and the next thing I know,
they're spendingday and night together--
sneaking offto private bible study,
- and one-on-onespiritual consultation.
- Gabrielle--
and if that wasn't enough,he issaying her name in his sleep.
"hold me,sister mary,hold me."
it's disgusting.He's like a lovesick puppy.
do you have reasonto believe that your husbandand sister mary are...
having sex?
Speak from the heart,gabrielle.
This is just betweenme,you and god.
Yeah... yep.They're having sex.
Carlos confessedeverything...
right beforehe asked for an annulment.
forgive me,father,for I have sinned.
How long sinceyour last confession?
Mm,not that long ago.
Look,I sorta told a fib,so...
how many "hail marys"is that gonna set me back?
- oh,honey.
- Go away!
Oh,honey,what happenedwasn't my fault.
There's no way I could'vepredicted how betty would react.
Oh,please,you knewsomething bad would happen.
You wanted all thisto blow up in my face.
Oh,honey,why would I want that?
Because you're jealous thatmy life's just getting started
and yours is over.
Danielle,that's ridiculous,sweetheart.
Daddy's dead.
You drove your boyfriendto suicide.
You're getting olderby the minute,
and soon you'll beso dried up and bitter
that no man will ever wantto touch you ever again.
Danielle...
and now you're determinedto ruin my life
so I have to stay with you hereand keep you company
while you turninto an old fossil.
All I ever wanted wasfor you to be happy.
Don't just want it.Make it happen.
danielle,I don't feel muchlike cooking tonight.
I'm thinkingof ordering a pizza.
I want canadian bacon.
Please.
All right.
He's mad at you'cause you hit him.
Well,I feel bad about that.
But when I considerthe risks he was taking...
it's a shamehe can't see that girl.
She's so pretty.
What did you sayabout danielle?
I said that she...
you know I don't want youthinking about things like that.
I'm sorry.I didn'T. I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
Go on and run upto your room.
Read the comics I got you.
And,caleb?
If I ever catch you lookingat that van de kamp girl,
I'll hit you twice as hardas I hit your brother,
and I won't feel bad about it.
Okay?
Okay.
So this wholesplenectomy thing--
you feelgood about it,huh?
Yeah,yeah,I told you.It's a routine surgery.
You're gonna be fine.
Right,right.
Actually,I sort of meant,um...
do you personallyfeel confident?
What do you mean?
Well,you know,you're gonna be...
hacking into me,
and I just wanted to make surethat you feel ready.
I've never taken outa spleen before.
But believe me,it's no big deal.
Spleen,gallbladder--it's all the same.
Okay,red flag! See,I didn'tgo to medical school,
but I'm thinking--not all the same.
Susan,I know what I'm doing.You're gonna have to trust me.
I would like to.But I gotta be honest--
the fact that you can't evencut that steak isn't helping.
That's not fair.You overcooked it,
and,frankly,it's not the freshest meat.
Well,neither am I.I've got 35 years on that cow.
Wait,susan,are you saying you don't want meto be your surgeon?
I'm sorry.
I don't mean this to soundthe wrong way. I just...
I would be more comfortablewith an experienced surgeon.
That's okay. I understand.
Thank you.
I should really be going.
What?
I didn't evenserve dessert yet.
You said you understood!
No,I do,I do.I respect your decision to see another doctor,
but you know what?
You need to respectthat my feelings are hurt.
What? You want me to putmy life on the line to service your ego?
I save lives every day.I cut. I save. I cut. I save.
That's what I do,and if that gives me an out-of-control ego,
well,maybe I need that to cut intoanother human being.
jim...
hey.Hey.
Dinner's ready.
So did you call around?Check on my references?
I told edyou were my husband,
and he was cool with that.
He really wants to hire you.
So who am ito stand in the way?
Really? So I got the job?
On one condition.
If you take this job,
you are never allowedto bring up
what happened beforewith your promotion.
That's it? Deal.
No,it's not a deal.I need a solemn vow
that you will never throwthat in my face ever again.
Because if you do,you will unleash demons
that you do not wanna meet.
I get it.
And what i really need from you...
is to be forgiven.
Actually,I already haD.
This dinner is really good.
Thank you.
- Hi,betty.
- Hello.
I wanted to talk to youabout what happened the other day with the kids.
I told you,we will be moving soon.
There's nothingto worry about.
Well,my fear is thatif we keep them apart,
they'll try that much harderto be together.
I mean,you knowhow teenagers can be,and,
well,a lot can happenin a couple of weeks.
I'll make a deal with you.
If you control yours,I will control mine.
Well,how about someold-fashioned chaperoning?
That way they can,um,still see each other,
and we won't have tobe the villains.
When it comesto my son's best interests,
I'm not afraid of beingthe villain.
I assumed that you wouldfeel the same way,bree.
Now that you mention it,I guess I do.
I have to go. I have some,um,muffins in the oven.
Mom,what's wrong?
It's the applewhites. I don't want you to go near them.
What?!
Do you remember the manthey arrested--
the one that brokeinto gabrielle's
and escapedfrom the mental hospital?
He's there.
I saw him in their window.They're hiding him.
You're kidding.No,I'm not.
And I forbid youto go over there.
Lynette,hi,it's bree.Uh,listen,
call me when youget this message,
and please cometo poker tonight.
I have some big newsabout the applewhites.
All right,bye.
Who was that?
Sister mary.
They just transferred her toa parish in fairbanks,alaska.
You're kidding me. Why?
She doesn't know.
The diocese wouldn't evengive her a reason.
Ah,vatican politics.
What's wrong?
I think I'm just coming downwith a migraine.
Oh,well,maybe youshould go lie down.
I'm gonna be outfor a while.
All right.
Uh,I'll see you there.
Susan?What are you doing here?
We need to talk.
Okay,all right,but,look,I just got out of surgery.
I've been waitingfor three hours.
After you stormed outthe other night,
I started to doubt myself.
I started to think,
"gee,you know,maybe I shouldjust ignore my better instincts,
and I should let dr. Ron gut me like a fish."
- Susan--
- I mean,why not?
'Cause all my life,
I have jumped through hoopsto keep men from leaving.
But I'm not doing it anymore.So tough luck,pally.
You just missed outon a good thing.
Susan...
you've been herefor three hours?
Yeah.Well,two hours ago,
flowers,champagneand an apology note were deliveredto your doorstep.
Really?
Look,I put our relationshipat risk,all right?
And it was stupid.
I haven't felt this wayabout somebody in a long time.
Susan,I really like you.
And because of that,I...
I can't be your doctor,let alone,your surgeon.
I mean,there's a pretty good reason why they make those rules.
Listen,I hopeyou forgive me,all right?
Because I'll hate myselfif I lose you.
I wouldn't want youto hate yourself.
No.
And I am so sorryabout that... snap thing.
I was just tryingto be theatrical.
I got your note.What's going on?
Are you hidingsomeone in your house?
What?
My mom saw someone inyour second-story window.
She thinks it's the guywho broke into mrs. Solis'.
Damn it,caleb.
Is that his name?
Has she told anybody else?
She left messageson her friends' machines.
They're coming oversoon to get details.
We're gonna have to leave tonight.
- This is--
- why? What's going on?
I would loveto tell you,believe me,I would.
But I can'T.
If you trust me,I could help you.
My familyhas secrets,too.
What my brother did--
it's bad.
Last year my brotherdid something really awful,
and my parentscovered it up for him.
If anyone were toever find out,
andrew and my momcould go to jail.
So you don't have to worryabout me judging you.
Tell me your secrets.I'll understand.
Okay.
But you tell meyours first.
What are you doing here?
I heard you werebeing transferred so I cameto say good-bye.
Come to gloatis more like it.
No,we've hadour differences,
but that doesn't meanI'm happy to see you shipped off to alaska.
Brr.
You had something to dowith this,didn't you?
Me? Oh,I'm justa humble sinner.
You're the one withall the power around here--
all the... annulment mojo.
Is that why you did it?
Well,getting rid of meisn't gonna change anything.
Carlos will do what he wants.
The problems in your marriagearen't going away.
Maybe not...
but you certainly are.
You missed a spot.
That was a mistake.
There.I think we're all done here.
Oh,my god!Oh,my god! Hold on!
Are you okay?
Stop fighting!
Stop fighting! No!
What the hellwere you thinking?
Uh,depends.What have you heard?
I got a callfrom the church.
They said you attackedsister mary.
Yeah,that's about right.
What are you thinking?
I wasn't,but I was thinkingabout it on the way over here.
And I realized the assI should be kicking is yours.
- Mine?
- Yes!
Sister mary manipulated youinto threatening me,
but you're the idiotthat fell for it.
I was notthreatening you.
I was asking for a promise.
You made me a promise,carlos,
a long time ago--till death do us part.
And one day you just come homeand start throwing words around like annulment.
How do you thinkthat makes me feel?
Okay,I'm sorryabout that.
I need to have a child.
And I need to knowI'm the woman you want to spendthe rest of your life with,
not just some uterusin high heels.
Gabrielle,please--
no,carlos,I am sorry.
I am not gonna be blackmailedinto giving birth.
You have to choose.
And I wish you would do itso I can move on with my life.
Well,of course I choose you.
I think that'sthe right decision.
You know,I made a decision,too.
The answer to your questionearlier is yes.
Yes...
I wanna have a baby.
I wanna havea baby with you.
betty.
What a surprise.
Can I talk to youfor a moment?
Uh,now is actuallynot a good time for me.
I think it is.
I wanted to chat with you before you didsomething foolish.
I don't knowwhat you mean.
The person you sawat my house today
is my other son.
His name is caleb.
He didn't harm gabrielle,
and he didn't hurtthe man in the car trunk.
That's all you need to know.
He's your son?
He's my dear sonwho happens to be slow.
Sometimes he makes mistakes.
But,betty,the policeare looking for him.
He escaped from that facilitythey sent him to.
He had help,trust me.
I've always thoughtthe maternal instinct
is one ofnature's most amazing gifts.
I mean,the length thatsome mothers will go to to protect their children--
it drives ordinary womento do extraordinary things,
women like me,bree,and like you.
What are you talking about?
If you breathe one wordof caleb's existence to anyone,
I will tell carlos,gabrielle and the police
that it was your sondriving the car
that killed juanita solis
and that you have been coveringup his crime ever since.
We're going to begreat friends,bree.
We have so much in common.
So is that all she said?
Yeah,something aboutthe applewhites.
I'm dying of curiosity.
it's rude to keeppeople waiting.
Hi. Come on in.
So,spill it.
What's the scoopon the applewhites?
Um,about that... um...
oh,bree,come on,dish already!
Well,perhaps I gotmore excited than I should have,
but I recently found outthat betty applewhite
is quite the poker player,
and so,uh,I have invited herto join our weekly game.
Hello,everybody.
I hope you broughtyour checkbooks because I am feeling lucky.
Everyone understands the nature of war.
I raise.
We also understand that victory depends on the cards
that we have been dealt.
Some,when faced with a bloody battle,
simply give in.
But for some,surrender is unacceptable.
Well,bree,what are you gonna do?
Even though they know it will be a fight...
I'll raise you.
...To the death.