-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:YTET-fisherchen
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Desperate Housewives
to make those dreams come true.
Aah! Oh. Watch it,susie.
Mom,why don't you
just go see a dressmaker?
Wait.
I have the perfect idea.
You get in the dress
and I'll pin it.
We wear the same size.
- Since when?
- Since forever.
You have to leave,though.
You can't stay.
You can't see susie
in a wedding dress,
not until your big day.
Mom!
No,it's not a problem.
I can see her in it.
- You can?
I assume you wanna pick out your own wedding dress when we get married,right?
that sounds like
a proposal.
Did it?
Yeah,it did.
Huh. What do you know?
Are you planning
to pop the question?
Well,if she knows it's coming,
the question won't really pop,
now will it?
He's right,mom. I want it
to be just like you do--
you know,on your own terms,
and you get down on one knee
and the whole production.
That's the plan.
Well,then I can wait.
I can wait.
I'm a good waiter.
Good.
I'm just wondering if there's
a ballpark of how long
I will have to wait--
a week,a month,after lunch?
Again,you're not waiting
for the pop.
Right,right. I'm sorry.
Oh,mom.
So the hives occurred
right after you kissed george?
Yes.It was the strangest thing,
and so inconvenient.
To be honest,
I think we were about to
make love for the first time.
Bree,have you considered the idea
that your subconscious mind
was trying to sabotage
your evening with george?
Actually,
I have not considered that
because that's idiotic.
You don't think being with george
made you feel a bit guilty?
Why should I feel guilty?
Perhaps you felt you were
about to commit adultery.
Dr. Goldfine,rex is dead.
You can't cheat on a corpse.
Well,maybe that's not how
you really feel deep down.
Oh,so you think I'm crazy?
You say you got
a case of hives for no reason.
I think there is a reason,
and it's probably
a psychosomatic one.
You can think
whatever you want,
but to be honest,I don't
believe in the subconscious.
Every time you've said "rex"
in this session,
you've stroked the place where
your wedding ring used to be.
Why did you do that?
Let's talk about monday.
We are re-pitching
to the kamarov people.
Lynette,you'll be on point.
Great. Great. No problem.
And can you do me a favor
and maybe not wear the green suit?
Um...
I... wasn't planning to,
uh,but... why?
The fabric. It just has
this quality to it,
like you could--
I don't know--
wipe it clean
with a damp cloth.
I'll just wear
a different suit,then.
Great.
Like what,you think?
Another suit.
I have other suits.
And if by other suits,you mean the gray one,
then of course you do.
No,actually,I have quite a few others.
Uh,the blue one
and,uh...
what's wrong with the blue suit?
Stu,would you liketo tell lynette
what's wrongwith the blue suit?
No. That's cool.
Stu... come on.
Do the thing--
the thing that you didat lunch.
"Look at me. I'm lynette.
"I've got food stainseverywhere."
All right. So if I getmy blue suit dry-cleaned,
will that be acceptableto everyone?
The pants also havea split seam in the back.
Excuse me.
Hello,david.
What the hell is this?
I thought i told you
to dress maternal.
Yes,you did,and i considered
it for about a second.
What happened?
David,i know you're
the lawyer and all,
but trust me,it's never a smart
strategy to cover this up.
We've got 40 minutes
before the pre-trial hearing.
- Let's go home and get you changed.
- What?
You want to get your husband
out of jail?
You gotta dress like
a pregnant,suffering wife,
- not the cover of "vogue."
- David.
- Louis,what are you doing here?
- I need a favor,david.
If this has to do with lifting
my client's restraing order,
the answer's the same one
you got last week.
You don't understand.
I love crystal.
Yeah,we all love the pretty
ladies at the stop n' shop,
but now you' gotta love her
from 50 yards away.
You turned her against me
If it wasn't for you,we'd be together.
Louis,crystal hired me to keep you away from her.
She doesn't want to see you.
Oh,yeah,then why did
she ask for my phone number?
She's a cashier.You paid by check.
It doesn't make you special.
Don't walk away from me.
We're having a conversation!
Louis,this is your problem.
You're creepy!
Nobody likes you.
What you call a conversation
the rest of us call harassment.
You want a friend,
get a hamster.
David!
call the police!
stay there!
That's right,you better run,
'cause i'm gonna get some bullets for this thing and come after y!
Freeze!
Hey,everything's cool.
Are you okay?
weeds are a common annoyance
of life in suburbia,
and no matter how hard
we try to get rid of them...
they always tend to crop
back up.
A-are you seeing this?
I don't believe him.
He is so brazen.
He's just mowing the lawn
like nothing ever happened.
What should we do?
Should we call the police?
Well,susan did say that he murdered mrs.
Huber,so my vote would be yes.
Oh,my god,susan's home.
Has she seen paul yet?
I think so.
Hello,susan.
Oh,my god. Paul.
Need some help
with those bags?
Why... are you doing here?
This is where i live.
I came home to find my son.
- Here you go.
- No,don't come near me.
- I'm just giving you back your pie filling.
- I don't want my pie filling.
- oh,come on. Just take it.
- No,stop!
Put that pie filling down.
Slowly.
- I'm calling 9-1-1.
- You don't want to do that.
Oh,i think i do.
You're a cold-blooded murderer.
Susan,how can you believe that?
We've been neighbors for years.
Ladies,good to see you.
Paul,
we've called the police.
You didn't really need
to do that.
We know what you did
to mrs. Huber.
Wonderful. I see you've all turned
into susan while i've been gone.
Oh,thank god.
They're here.
Hey,what's going on?
Oh,mayer's convinced that
paul young murdered martha huber.
Oh,my god.
I live right behind him.
I know. I gave him
my house keys to feed my cat.
I win. I made out with him.
Here you go. There's no warrant
here for a paul young.
Why don't you ask mike?
He overheard everything,right?
- Who's mike?
- Uh,he's my boyfriend,
and he told me that paul
confessed everything to him.
Oh,and mike has
martha's journals,
which clearly prove
that paul had a motive.
All right,all right,
where do i find this mike guy?
Uh,he's... follow me.
You mind if i stay here?
I've got a lot of raking to do.
Let's go.
Hey.
What's going on?
Mike,paul young is back.
Look.
Your girlfriend said mr. Young
confessed a murder to you?
Um...
no. No,not to me.
And i don't suppose you have a journal
that belonged to a martha huber?
No. I hardly knew her.
Besides,you ever known a woman
who'd loan out her diary?
Mike,what are you doing?
I'm sorry,susan. I don't know
what you're talking about.
But i've got a job to get to.
Is there anything else?
No,no,
that pretty much covers it.
Well,someone might as well
say it.
Susan,what the hell
have you been smoking?
Okay.
Wow!
Nice.
Oh,my god.
Okay,don't be distracted
by that. Look at me.
Here i am tomorrow,
making my presentation.
You see?
You see how it moves with me?
That's where the magic is.
$900?
Yeah,well,this one was
the most expensive.
The other ones aren't as nice.
But look.
Look,look,look,look at me,
look at me. Watch.
I don't walk in it.
I glide.
Um,honey,you know what?
There's gotta be like
$3,000 worth of clothes here.
Yeah,well,i haven't bought
a new suit in six years.
So? When i was working,
you don't think i would have
loved to have a designer suit?
I wore wash-and-wear so that
we could live in a nice neighborhood,
so we could take the kids
on vacation every summer.
- I mean,i made sacrifices.
- I'm willing to make sacrifices.
Great,well,let's start here,because
this should cover
a math tutor for parker.
- Whoa,hold on a sec.
- Six months of preschool for penny.
All right,
now you're being ridiculous.
You know what? And the twins...
they're gonna need braces.
That oughta make a dent.
Oh,no. Come on,tom.
Not this one.
Strip.
You saw the walk,right?
You wanna see
the walk again?
- I'll tutor parker myself.
- Honey,that'd be great.
You also gonna take up
home dentistry?
Fine. I'll take them back.
Could you step out
for a minute,please?
I want to be alone with it
for a little while.
Hi,it's bree.
Hi. I was thinking
about calling you.
I just got some new
antihistamines in at the store.
I think they're really gonna
help with your rash.
Well,great.
how would you feel about the two of us
checking into a romantic hotel tomorrow?
What? Uh,l-i'd like that
very much.
I will let you make
all of the arrangements.
Something out of town
would be nice.
Good night.
- We need to talk.
- Where did you come from?
I'm sorry.
I've been waiting for you.
I'm just a little upset because
everybody thinks i'm crazy.
Can i at least get out
of the truck first?
Yes,definitely.
I mean,i can understand why you wouldn't want the cops to know that you kidnapped paul.
- I mean,that definitely looks bad.
- Since i was on probation.
Well,right.
I mean,there's that.
And in possession of a gun...
- well,okay...
- which i held to his head.
So i violated my probation,
committed a felony and coerced a confession.
If the cops found out about that
i'd be looking at 10 to 15 years.
But why don't you want 'em to know about martha huber's journal?
I mean,she says right in there that she was blackmailing paul's wife.
She also says right in there that she was blackmailing you for burning down edie's house.
Oh.
I forgot about that.
I just can't believe it.
I mean,there he is,
a murderer,
just living
right on our street,
and there's nothing
we can do about it
because you're a convicted felon and i burnedown that stupid house.
It's not fair.
I want paul young gone
as badly as you do,
and he will be,
but i also want to find zach.
I think ce zach finds out
paul's here,
i got a feeling he'll be back.
Well,that's comforting to know
there's a silver lining.
hi.
What are you doing here?
Well,you protected me
from a hail of gunre,
so i thought i'd stop by
and give you a card.
You're my first visitor.
What do you mean,i'm your first visitor?You've been here two days.
My office sent me flowers.
Oh. "dear david,
"who knew you could
actually bleed?
"Sincerely,
your stunned co-workers."
Yeah,well,i'm a lawyer
who got shot.Everybody's cracking wise.
You're not gonna eat.
Uh,can't really cut y.
Well,i'm not gonna let you
starve to death.
Besides,you're gonna need your strength to get my husband out of jail.
You know,when i was waiting for
the ambulance the other day...
i seriously thought
i was gonna die.
I was scared.
Of course you were.
Thanks.
For what?
For not making any jokes.
Sure.
Now... open up.
- Here.
- Thank you.
I'm glad that you could all make
it here on such short notice.
Just follow this hallway
straight down there
and make yourselves
comfortable.
For the good of their family,
lynette had made a promise
to her husband...
and within ten days
from the date of purchase,
she intended to keep it.
Oh. That's a fantastic suit.
Oh. Thanks.
I'm flattered,really.
I mean,who knew that you cared
so much about what i think?
I don't follow you.
Well,i make
a few innocent comments,
and you go out and buy yourself
a gorgeous new suit.
Dance,puppet,dance.
Well,actually,this was
already in my closet.
I just forgot about it.
Forgot? You forgot
that you had that suit?
Good morning. Hi.
I'm lynette scavo.
Now is everyone taken care of
in terms of coffee
and whatever else they may like?
Great.
Well,then let's get started.
I will show you how kamarov vodka can expand its customer mindshare
while still holding the line
on marketing costs.
It's something we here
at parcher and murphy
like to call
"persuasive engineering."
Lynette...
just hold on one second.
You have a...
They put the price tags
on the skirts these days,too,
just so you know.
Look at that,everybody.
Lynette just bought herself
a beautiful,brand-new suit.
Doesn't she look great?
Go on.
Okay.
You may be seated.
Good to see you back
on your feet,mr. Bradley.
Whenever you're ready.
Thank you,your honor.
The defense moves to dismiss this case immediately on the grounds that the defendant...
are you all right,mr. Bradley?
I'm sorry,your honor.
I just can't.
Mr. Bradley,
do you need a recess?
What the hell's going on?
- David,where are you going?
- I'm sorry. I quit.
You can't just quit
in the middle of a hearing.
I'd love to get
your idiot husband out of jail,
but i just can't do it.
I'm sorry.
- Yeah. Why not?
- Because i'm in love with you.
What?
The other day in the hospital,
i started to feel something.
I don't know.
Maybe it was there all along.
But when i look into your eyes,
i know y feel it,too.
We belong together.
Okay,david,if you don't get back in there right now,
i will go get a gun
and shoot you myself.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Come in!
We need to talk.
paul,you... you can't just
waltz into people's houses.
Susan,you told me
to come in.
Well,that's 'cause i assumed you were someone i would let in my house.
What do you want?
I was looking through my mail,
and i found this.
I was surpriseto discover that you were looking for my son.
You didn't happen to find
anything out
about where zach might be,
did you?
No. No,i didn't.
Sorry i can't help you out.
I'm asking because
if you remember,
zach hid here
in this house before,
and now i learn that
you've been searching for him.
Well,he's not here.
Well,maybe we should
double-check.
But he's not here.
I swear.
What are you grabbing for?
A kne.
I just want to slice
some tomatoes.
I don't know how
i know this,
but l-i think
that he's in utah.
He... he took a bus
to bountiful.
You have family there,
right?
Okay,i gave him
the bus fare.
You might want to be
careful with that.
You seem a little jittery.
Look,
i know the timing is bad.
- Pretty bad.
- I feel terrible.
How was i supposed to know
that he would take a bullet
and suddenly realize
he's in love with me?
Okay,look,i know i pushed you
into hiring that creep,
but i promise i will do
anything i can to fix this.
All right,go have sex
with bradley.
What?
Well,that's what you want me
to say,isn't it?
God,you guys are good.
I mean,you set me up perfectly.
You think david and i planned
this so we could sleep together?
Let's see. The guy tells me
to my face that he wants
to get into your pants,
quits a week before my trial,
and now you can't wait
to do anything to get him back?
Yeah. I'd like to goack
to jail now.
How dare
you think that of me?
I have been nothing
but faithful to you!
Since you've been in here.
Save it.
I know when i've been outfoxed,
and please don't pretend
that you're doing this for me,
'cause i'd rather rot in here.
And you know what?
A lesser woman
would let you rot in here,
but i'm not gonna do that.
I'm not gonna give you
the satisfaction.
So you better start
packing up your shanks
or whatever you people
make in re,
because you're coming home
with me!
I don't have any shanks.
Good afternoon.
Checking in?
Yes. Reservations in the name
of williams... george williams.
Let me get your paperwork.
So what do
you want to do first?
I don't know. I thought maybe
we could go antiquing.
I hear you have
some lovely museums nearby.
Do you have any brochures?
Right over there,
mrs. Williams.
Oh,uh,she's not my wife.
I'm so sorry.
So i hear they have a terrific
farmers' market nearby.
We shoulpick up
some nectarines.
George...
- i can't.
- What?
- I can't stay in a hotel room with you.
- Why not?
Because i am starting
to get that rash again.
Well,i brought
the antihistamines.
Oh,please.
It's not gonna help.
George,clearly,
this is psychosomatic.
We need to go home.
Bree,we just drove
three hours to get here.
I know,and you have
every right to be mad,
but,george,i am really
starting to itch.
Is there a problem?
Uh,no,there's no problem.
Everything is fine.
Okay,okay,okay,okay.
Uh,uh,
i'll get you your own room.
George...
no,no,no. We can still
have a nice weekend.
We'll just shift the focus
to... antiquing.
Please. I mean,clearly,
you didn't come here to shop.
No,i came to spend time
with you...
time that does not need
to be spent in a bed.
Really? You mean that?
You wouldn't mind?
- No.
- You know what,george?
We're gonna have
a great time,
because there's tons
of fun stuff we can do
that doesn't involve sex.
You betcha.
While i take care of this,
why don't you go get
those brochures?
George,you won't believe it.
I just stopped itching.
How about that?
- Nice suit.
- Just hear me out.
I was gonna take it back,
i swear.
But?
But then i started thinking
about it,and you know what?
I'll be damned if i'm gonna
pitch to a roomful of people
who are all wearing
armani and vera wang
while i'm standing there
with 2-year-old breast milk
- crusted on my lapel.
- Lynette...
and you know what else?
I kicked ass in that meeting
because of this suit.
Lynette,it is a suit.
Why are you so obsessed with it?
You can't explain obsession,
tom.
It just... is.
No,we are parents.
We can't afford
the luxury of obsessions.
See? That's where i think
we have been making
a terrible,terrible mistake.
What is this?
Sometimes we just need to get
something that makes us happy.
I know that sounds selfish,
but i've been thinking.
It might make us
better people
and maybe
even better parents.
No. No,lynette,no.
This is wrong.
Carbon... fiber... shafts.
Wow.
I feel like a better parent
already.
Oh,yeah.
So i was talking to one
of the bellmen,
and he said there's a place
not far from here
where we could go
horseback riding.
Doesn't that sound like fun?
George?
Wh-what? What? I'm sorry.
I was saying i think
we should go horseback riding.
Oh,sure. That'd be great.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
L-i just don't think
that we should risk
you getting another rash.
We,i'm not gonna get another
rash just by holding your hand.
You never know.
Oh. Well,okay.
Hey,uh,i brought
those antihistamines with me.
Maybe you should take a couple,
just to see if it works.
Oh,i'm drinking wine.
I don'think you're supposed
to mix pills with alcohol.
That's for people who are...
who are about to use
heavy machinery.
You don't plan on operating
a forklift tonight,do you?
Well,you're the pharmacist.
If you think it's okay...
i do.
George,i can't feel my legs.
I know,sweetheart.
Don't you worry.
I'm gonna take you
to your room,
and then we're gonna get you
into bed.
Is she going to be okay?
Yeah,she's just had
a little too much wine.
i don't think
it was the wine,george.
I think it was
the antihistamines.
she doesn't know what
she's... we're good,thank you.
Oh.
No,no,no,no,no.
I'll get those.
You just relax.
I love you very much,bree.
You know that,right?
i know.
And i want
more than anything
for you to love me back.
Do you understand
what i'm saying?
Bree?
Hey there.
How you feeling?
Oh,okay.
Have you been sitting there
all this time?
I wanted to make sure
you were okay,
so i stayed
and watched you sleep.
Did i do anything embarrassing?
Sometimes i snore.
No. No,
you slept like an angel.
In fact,you were
so beautiful and peaceful,
i actually started
to feel guilty.
Guilty?
Um,well,you know,
'cause i told you
take those pills.
That chair looks
so uncomfortable.
Why didn't you sleep
next to me?
Well,you made it pretty clear
that you don't want me
in your bed.
George.
I know what you want
from me,
and i thought i wanted
the same thing,
but i keep getting
those rashes because...
i still feel married.
Makes sense,i guess.
Can't you just be patient?
Can't you wait
just a little bit longer?
I've already waited
my whole life for you,
and i can wait
a little more.
But let's be honest.
There's no guarantee
that you'll ever be ready.
There's only so much rejection
i can take.
So...
i'll do my best,
but... don't be surprised
if one of these days
you wake up and...
i'm not here.
Well,i should get back
to my room,
try to get a little sleep.
The antique stores
open at 10.
George,wait.
Please don't go.
Stay here with me.
But what if you get
another rash?
Well,i'll just...
have to get over it,won't i?
Gabrielle?
I got your call...
wow.
Does this mean
what i think it means?
There are
some ground rules first.
I'm not leaving my husband.
Carlos is looking at
spending eight years in jail
because of my lapse of judgment
with the gardener.
I can't let him rot in there.
I'd be filled with guilt.
You could get him out
and then divorce him.
Not an option.
I'm catholic,hence the guilt.
So what are our options?
This,us,stolen moments,
seeing each other
whenever we n.
Carlos never needs to know.
No.
I thought this was
what you wanted.
I want all of you.
All or nothing.
Then it's nothing.
So you won't get a divorce,
but you'll have an affair?
I said i was catholic,
not a fanatic.
You know,david,
you could tell me to stop.
Just tell me to stop,
and i will,
or you can have me
right now...
on my terms.
All right.
Ow! What are you doing?
Making my point.
- You don't love me.
- Aah! Yes,i do.
No. You just agreed
to an affair...
a cheap,illicit affair
with the woman you"love."
Carlos would never share me.
He's looking
at eight years in prison
because the mere thought of it
sent him into a violent rage.
That is love.
This is... this is just lust,
mixed with posttraumatic stress.
I will see you in court
tomorrow at 10 a.m.
And don't be late,
or else i'll have you disbarred
for sexual harassment.
i'd take it easy
with that snail poison.
It's hell
on your agapanthus.
Thanks.
I'll keep that in mind.
Is that why you stopped by...
share a few gardening tips?
Nobody wants you here,paul,
especially me.
I'm just a father
looking for his son.
Oh,i know what you are.
First,your girlfriend
tries to run me off
with some crazy story
about sending zach to utah.
Now you're he
trying to scare me away.
So much for
"love thy neighbor."
Anyway,thanks for the advice.
About my agapanthus,i mean.
I'll make sure
i send you some.
What did susan tell you?
You look beautiful.
Oh,you should really
consider wearing this
when you marry mike.
We could make it
a family tradition.
Why don't we both stop
getting divorced?
That would be
a nice family tradition.
I need to ask you
something important.
Oh,my god!
Aah! This is it!
Oh! Let me get my camera.
Oh,no,mom,stop!
What is it?
Did you give zach money
to go to utah?
What?
Yes or no.
He was talking so much
about julie.
I tried to get him
to come home with me...
i mean,to... to you,
but he just kept going
on and on about her,
and i got scared.
Yes or no.
Yes.
Mike. Mike,i didn't do it
to hurt you.
You've gotta believe me.
L...
i should have told you
right away. I know that.
But you know now,
so can we please talk about it?
(mike) no.
Mike,stop.
Susan,you said you wanted to
help me,and i believed you.
That's it. We're done.
No...
No,no,no,no!
I screwed up,okay?!
I want to fix it!
Please let me fix it!
Tell me how to fix it!
mike... i love you.
Please,no,please.
No,mike! Mike,please!
Come back!
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:YTET-fisherchen
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Yes,every little girl
dreams of a big white wedding.
But some dreams
just don't come true.
Desperate Housewives
-=The End=-