Previously...
Edmond Hayes, Agent June Stahl.
I am willing to look past
all these illegal guns
because I want James O'Phelan.
Can't tie anything to Jimmy,
but my dad can.
That's the four dozen AKs.
Beating was from the League.
This is from me.
Mr. Weston does a lot of things
very well,
but understanding the need for this type
of relationship evades him.
This is the third delivery
you haven't let me pay for.
I am investing in the future
of your organization.
The night of Bobby's party,
I was attacked.
- Girl says her baby's choking.
- Please help me.
Goddamn doll in the car seat.
I came to handcuffed
to a chain-link.
There were three of them.
When he spoke, I knew his voice:
Zobelle's right hand, Weston.
They raped me,
all three of them.
This retaliation needs to be smart.
How do you want to handle it?
We kill them all.
Are you going to protect SAMCRO?
I'm going to help a friend.
Now, you do whatever you need to do.
Consider yourself acting chief.
Cliffie, Duke.
What the hell is this?
I'm their father.
See your kids have taken
that little trip I arranged.
Son of a bitch.
I'll kill you for this.
At least I didn't gang-rape them.
You want to kill me? Time and place.
Timberland, 8:00.
AJ Weston,
you're under arrest for arson,
burning down Caracara.
- Where's your father?
- I don't know.
Polly?
Deputy Chief!
My daughter and I are
in possession of illegal narcotics.
- Arrest us.
- Come on. Let's go.
We're going to kill you.
What?
Stahl's been locked in a room with FBI,
two hours now.
No idea what's going on.
What about Weston?
Still waiting to hear from the DA.
I'm sorry.
You should go on back to the clubhouse.
They going to need you there.
All right.
You come home to me.
- Sack, stay with my mom and Tara.
- Absolutely, man.
Thanks, bro.
All right?
Our two-fingered witness,
Chuck Marstein?
He's a felon,
history of fraud.
Unreliable witness.
Weston walks.
I am not handing
this guy over to Clay.
I need to talk to you.
Talk to my deputy. He's in charge.
Right this way.
What the hell happened in there?
The FBI is cutting Zobelle loose.
Jesus Christ.
He had a key of heroin.
Copped to trafficking.
This is bullshit.
Welcome to my life, Wayne.
Please, please.
Zobelle is not just dealing
guns and dope.
That scumbag
had Gemma Teller
beaten
and gang-raped.
Jesus Christ.
I need something to tell the club.
To tell Gemma.
This guy just skates away.
Ethan Zobelle...
is an FBI informant.
A rat?
For three years now.
He can tie the dirty deeds of his
organization to the rich and mighty.
Judges, clergymen, a few senators.
As well as naming
the Aryan shot-callers.
He's a gold mine, and he knows it.
He keeps churning a profit
while the feds fatten their case.
No wonder this guy struts around
like King Farouk.
He's untouchable.
And the wheels of justice
keep turning.
Don't they?
Comfortable?
What?
Bad news for law enforcement.
Weston and Zobelle are both walking.
How?
Chucky's testimony don't hold up.
And Zobelle
has been working for the FBI
all along.
A rat?
Trading senators
and A.B. shot-callers.
Thanks.
Get to Otto.
Have him send word up the ranks.
Gets us protected inside again,
stops any Aryan backlash
once we drop Weston.
- Weston's mine.
- I know.
My guys will escort you
wherever you need to go.
That won't be necessary.
Holy shit.
Alvarez.
Brown's protecting
their investment, huh?
There's not going to be
another battle in Charming.
Too late.
War's already started.
Riding through this world
All alone
God takes your soul
You're on your own
The crow flies straight
A perfect line
On the devil's bed
Until you die
Gotta look this life
In the eye.
Episode 213: Na Triobloidi
Not gonna wash your hands?
Ain't you wondering
why your boss was locked up?
Why he ain't now?
He's not my boss
or my concern.
I'd probably feel the same way,
if I found out I was working
for a rat.
Guy in the suit
that walked them out of here?
He's not a lawyer.
FBI handler.
Informant?
Three years.
We can't touch him.
Why are you telling me this?
The hate you got
in your heart for color,
multiply it by ten,
point it at yourself and Zobelle,
and hang my name on it.
I hope you rip each other to shreds.
We were just saying our good-byes.
Eyewitness was unreliable.
DA is not pursuing the charges.
You're free to go.
I can't prove what you did
to Gemma Teller.
And handing you over to Clay
would be a satisfying consolation.
But fortunately for you,
I'm a cop actually bound by the law.
You stay local,
SAMCRO will kill you.
I can't leave without my boys.
Maybe I can arrange a visit.
How you getting by?
10% vision.
It's lightened the work detail.
Resigned to
books on tape.
It's time for retribution, bro.
We got some intel the Aryan shot-callers
are gonna wanna know.
Who was that?
Weston.
He knows you're working
with the FBI.
Said you're a dead man.
What do we do, Dad?
Adjust and adapt
like we always do.
When I became...
obliged to the FBI,
it was inevitable
that my shift in alliances
would be exposed.
We're prepared.
Witness protection?
WitPro is a fantasy.
It was never an option.
We'll go home,
we'll regroup.
God will lead us
to the next right place.
Home?
- Budapest?
- We'll be safe and comfortable there.
I'll have a chance to rebuild.
It won't take long for this news
to get out on the streets.
When it does, our Mexican cohorts
will not be compelled
to give us assistance.
We should leave now.
I will charter a jet
out of Sacramento.
Today?
We have no choice.
- I have to go back to the house.
- Why?
Pack.
All my stuff is here.
I just can't leave.
You're going to see him.
I have to.
You're smarter than that.
I have done everything
you've asked me to. Everything!
I believe in you.
I love you.
But I need to do this.
I'll be back in an hour.
So where we at?
I cleared out Floyd
and everyone else
in the potential line of fire.
Look,
helping SAMCRO, it's about Gemma.
I get it.
But if these guys open up
on Main Street,
I gotta call the sheriff.
This is Charming business.
Look at this.
If this goes south,
we can't contain it, all right?
It's the goddamn Wild West.
You put me in charge. I'm calling.
Downloaded Otto.
Weston out yet?
Hale's got Eglee to give him
an escort out of town.
Making a stop to
see his kids first...
Sanwa CFS.
I'll catch him at Family Services.
No harm to my officer.
Let's go, brother.
And me.
I'll handle the rest.
Stop right there.
That's far enough.
Just want a discussion, man.
He's clean.
Don't know
what the drama's all about, ese.
Just buying a few cigars.
Our truce?
Null and void.
You need to buy cigars
someplace else.
I'm not staying long.
Just showing
a new friend out of town.
Your new friend...
he hurt my club
and my town and my family.
You got no idea
who you crawled into bed with.
Send your crew home, Clay.
Let me do what I gotta do.
Or I'll call in another charter
and we can turn Main Street
into Dia de los Muertos
Why didn't you tell
him Zobelle's a rat?
'Cause he'd kill him...
and that's mine.
Intellect throws each man
back upon himself
into a solitude from which he looks out
with absolutely strange eyes on society.
And if the spectacle touches him,
if it arouses interest
and compassion,
his feeling will be for those
tender ones of the great human flock
whom the shepherds shear
and starve and sell
and do not feed.
Imperfect education makes
the rank-and-file of revolutionists,
but from time to time,
a leader steps down to them
out of the highest circles:
a Mirabeau,
a Rochefort,
a Prince Kropotkin.
The desire of the Sons of Anarchy
is indeed
to dispense with leaders;
for since all men
in the formula are equal,
it is unreasonable that one
should lead rather than another.
The beating was from SAMCRO.
This
is from me.
You've reached the end of side one.
Please turn over the tape.
Here we go.
What the hell's he doing
with the kid?
Shit,
he's taking the kid with him.
Call Unser,
find out what's going on.
Your cell's ringing.
Get out here.
- Come on.
- I'm coming.
Go.
Hello.
Eddy, it's Da.
- Da, where the hell have...
- Just listen, boy.
Picked up a tail.
Got to be feds.
Probably on you, too.
Meet at the place.
We'll talk safe.
One hour.
No trace.
Wants to meet at the wharf.
Let's go.
It's time.
Let's make the Mexicans
feel welcome.
You and the Nomads keep an eye
on things. Rest of us, clubhouse.
Call you when they get restless.
Would be a good time to take our ride.
We have to wait for Polly.
I'm all about family,
but Clay ain't the kind of guy
that rolls over.
May not get this window again.
We wait.
Okay, cool.
So they gave Weston
a supervised visit with his kid...
Unser's cop as chaperone.
And he took them for ink.
Perfect.
Guess little Cliffie couldn't go.
He's in a psych eval.
Go figure.
Weston, two inkers, two customers,
the kid, and the cop.
Freddy a friend?
I think so.
We got to get Weston
away from his kid.
Make the call.
Can you get that, baby?
- This is Freddy.
- It's Opie, SAMCRO.
Need a favor.
Guy on your table, club wants him.
Raped a member's mother.
Need to get him clear
of the kid and the cop.
In five minutes,
give him a reason
to go to the bathroom.
Think you can do that, Freddy?
I got no problem with that.
Club will owe you one.
Come on. Let's go.
Good?
- Come on.
- Sorry, man.
We're okay.
You should go rinse that off though.
You got to piss?
Shit.
Jesus.
It's okay, Dukey.
Get rid of him.
Head back, Dukey.
I got to talk to these guys.
Say nothing,
no matter what happens.
Understand?
You don't ever talk to the cops.
I love you.
He never sees this.
Da.
ATF has me.
Go.
Said they're gonna tell Jimmy
I was a rat. I didn't help!
Listen to me, boy.
Got to convince Jimmy you'd do
anything for the cause.
- What do I do?
- Kill that ATF bitch.
Don't care how you do it.
Just get it done.
How do I...?
She's a fed.
This is the call, boy.
This is you being a man.
Figure it out.
Do it.
Let me know when it's done.
Very, very sneaky, Eddy.
Very sneaky and very stupid.
It's the only way
I could get him to come in.
Told him the safe house was clear.
Gonna meet me there, one hour.
Good boy.
My Da's smart.
He's got scanners, detectors.
He sees anyone, hears anything,
he'll know it's a trap.
I can't exactly trust you alone,
now can I?
Then just you.
No one else.
Let's go.
It's done.
I am so proud of you.
Me, too.
Where we at?
Puerto Rican's watching Zobelle.
Where's my mom?
Her and Tara are getting supplies.
Sack's with them.
You're a good son.
Sons.
Give me those.
I'm driving.
That blonde.
She's the one you chased.
Who is she, Gemma?
Zobelle's daughter.
She's the one who told me
her baby was choking.
Hit me over the head.
Where are we going?
Forward, sweetheart.
You take milk?
Think I might be sick.
Go.
What are you going to do with that?
Box you put me in...
you give me no choice.
Put the gun down.
Jesus!
What the...?
Blanks.
We knew the gun was there.
Knew that the cell phone
was at the wharf.
We've been one step ahead, Eddy.
And now
I'm going to send Daddy a text
from your phone,
telling him that I am dead
and that it's safe
to come round and pick you up.
Why'd you let me take it this far?
Could've just told me,
sent the text.
I was curious.
Wanted to see if you had the balls.
But you didn't.
I guess Da raised a little Irish pussy,
didn't he?
Shit.
We heard shots on the wire.
Need a status update.
Over.
Those were the blanks.
I guess old Edmond here
had the nerve after all.
I sent a message to Cameron,
so keep the streets clear
and disengage the wire.
Go radio silence.
I don't want a scanner
or a $20 RF detector
tanking this operation.
We got to go.
Now.
She'll be back soon.
I got guys out there
with outstanding warrants.
Those sheriffs start running plates,
you're going to lose half your escort.
What are we doing here, Gemma?
That rape
would have destroyed most women,
but it made you
stronger, wiser, compassionate.
Whatever it is you think
you have to do, you're past it.
My son.
My husband.
Their brothers.
They're out there
risking their lives,
their freedom
for me.
This is how I do my part.
God's put her in my path,
so I can...
fix that part of me
that they ripped open.
I'm supposed to do this.
Jesus.
- Do you even hear what you're saying?
- Get my grandson home safe.
Love you, Tara.
I'm glad you're with my boy.
- Gemma, please don't do this.
- I'll be okay.
I'll be okay.
Where's she going?
Stay here.
She may need to get out fast.
Edmond?
Eddy?
It's me.
Edmond, are you here?
Where are you?
Oh, God.
Put down the gun.
You're the one that killed him.
Turn around.
Turn around!
Bloody day for both of us.
Push the gun on the floor.
Was she involved in the rape?
I'm sorry that that happened to you.
And now what happens?
Go.
I'll give you some time
to slip away.
Why would you do that?
At least see your family
before we pick you up.
But head out the back.
Avoid my guys in front.
I'm giving you a chance.
Go.
What are you doing?
You need to put down the gun.
Goddamn.
You are a smart bitch.
Clock's ticking, darling.
This is Stahl.
Status update.
Cameron Hayes never showed.
The girlfriend, Polly Zobelle, did.
I told Edmond to get rid of her,
but before he could,
Clay Morrow's old lady followed her in,
armed.
She sucker-punched me,
took my gun,
shot the girl in the chest.
Edmond panicked, ran for the door.
Gemma shot him in the back
with my weapon.
He's dead.
She took off.
I couldn't stop her.
Oh, Mother Mary...
My boy!
No sign of any suspects in the yard.
We're going, with or without you.
I'm ready.
Can you please
leave one of your men here?
In case Polly shows up.
It's ready and waiting.
Wayne.
I need a little help.
What's the matter, darling?
Where are you?
I'm on the lam.
We've got company.
Alvarez, take off!
Or we finish this.
Let's go.
Go get King Whitey.
Okay, kids. Go grab a snack.
Behave yourselves.
That's his car.
Check it out.
Hey, kids.
He's in there. He's surrounded
with a busload of kids.
Probably calling for backup.
Maybe the sheriffs.
- Who gives a shit?
- Those kids clear...
we kill him.
It's just me.
- Where's Gemma?
- I don't know.
Feds raided the house.
I had to leave.
You better call Jax.
I didn't want
to bother you with this...
What?
It's Gemma. She followed
Zobelle's daughter in the...
What...?
- What?
- Something's wrong. I got to go.
- I'm with you, brother.
- Yeah, me, too.
Weapon.
What are you doing?
What do you want?
Gemma killed my Eddy.
Figured maybe,
I kill an old lady, even the score.
Don't get brave, boyo.
Sit.
Here we are.
Son for a son.
Seems about right.
Please, no!
Wait.
Line 1, Chief.
Clay and his men attacked me.
I am trapped.
Deli Mart, Tyler Creek and Stallion.
Bad day for the Zobelles
to leave Charming.
Feds found your daughter
shot to death
in some shithole in Galt.
I'll get the sheriffs
right out there.
You want the Sanwa Sheriff?
That's it.
Kids are finishing up.
Convince the locals
to buy their snacks someplace else.
- Tell the deli clerk to take a break.
- Done.
My baby!
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Are you okay?
He took Abel.
What?
- Who took him?
- That Irishman I patched up.
Cameron.
Everything all right?
I need you.
We got to go.
What are you talking about?
Zobelle's unprotected.
Irish took my grandson.
Son of a bitch!
I got this.
Is it just you, then,
this afternoon?
My... daughter
will not be joining me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well...
We...
adjust
and adapt, yes?
Local police struck out.
Looks like Gemma's in the wind.
Any idea where we're headed?
Far dock!
He took my son.
He took my son!
Santiag Team
.:: La Fabrique ::.