Previously...
Shit!
You really got 400 thou
stashed away, Chucky?
Lin was real sloppy with his money,
so I cooked his books for about a year.
- The hand on the dick, what's the deal?
- I have this condition.
I'm not even aware of it.
I want to talk to Lin.
I'll throw in the door prize.
I do not accept this!
Ethan Zobelle.
Cammy Hayes. My boy, Edmond.
- Glad we finally get to meet in person.
- Someplace private we can talk?
Why don't you keep me company?
Otto says some guy's
giving you trouble.
Shitbag's threatening my girls
they don't join his company.
- Wait a minute, hang onto that.
- Look what that asshole did to her.
- This was Caruso?
- Who do you think?!
Georgie!
Get the hell out!
This is a closed set!
Shit!
Think they know where Zobelle is.
Christian Center, Morada.
AKs and shotguns. Let's go.
We got to get the hell out of here.
Out!
Drop the guns, now!
No, they need this.
I finished it.
What do you want me to say?
Keep saying
you want to change things.
But you keep repeating old behavior.
Can't have it both ways.
Is there anything you love
so much,
you'd protect it no matter the cost?
The damage it did to you?
Yeah, a child.
That's how I feel about this club.
Since I was five, all I ever wanted
was a Harley and a cut.
Look, change won't happen quick.
Or without blood.
But it'll happen.
It has to.
See you later.
You get any sleep?
Not much.
- That fight with Jax...
- It's my problem.
Donna?
Don't matter why.
Had to happen.
- What?
- Him challenging me.
It's in his DNA.
Maybe you're right.
Ghost of his old man haunting him.
And how does that play out?
I guess we'll find out.
I want to do a dinner tonight.
Everyone.
- It's not a good time.
- It's the perfect time.
We need it.
Do what you gotta do.
What did you tell Stahl?
- There's nothing to tell.
- Bullshit!
ATF's looking into Zobelle
and the Irish.
She's not digging into Sam Crow.
She's doing her job.
She wants the supplier.
I got no delusions
about us being on the same side.
But we both know that Zobelle
and this ATF bitch
are bad for Charming.
You were right.
Zobelle doesn't make mistakes.
He's protected.
My god.
ATF can't touch the league.
FBI's looking into white hate.
Right.
That's why Stahl needs us.
Now why would the feds need you?
Sons just being mechanics and all.
Big picture, deputy. Look at it.
It's a little bit painful
when I ride.
Sometimes I feel it when I walk.
Other than that, back to normal.
Is it gay
- that I want to see it?
- Gay curious.
Come on, drop 'em.
Show time.
Is it supposed to be that swollen?
Think so.
They look uneven.
One nut's always bigger
than the other one.
Really?
I think mine are equally huge, man.
I shouldn't have to see that.
- The new ball.
- I gather.
Congrats.
What's up?
We need to take a look
at this thing with Clay and Jax.
Heard they got into it at county.
It was brutal, man.
Shit's been brewing for months.
Since Donna.
You think Donna's death's
got something to do with their beef?
Started way before.
What do you think
they're fighting about?
Jax pushing for change.
That kind of beef is good for this club.
It keeps us current.
What's going on between them
is much uglier.
And if it keeps going,
it going to hurt us,
worse than Zobelle and the ATF.
We got to dig into them.
- We got to get to the truth.
- I can talk to Jax.
You two been bumping heads.
He'll tell me.
He knows I want to help.
All right.
Tigger,
you should talk to Clay.
We've find out what's going on.
We bring it to the table
and we get past this shit.
It's on us to fix this.
What?
Just downloading to the prospect.
And his new swollen nut.
Welcome back, shithead.
Chinese just called.
They want a sit-down.
I got to head up to Caracara.
Where's Clay?
I appreciate you helping us out.
You got my word.
Ain't gonna burn you on the bail.
Thank your wife.
Reminded me we're just a couple
of kids from a small town.
I might need your help
protecting our small town.
- From what?
- Jacob Hale.
He's been using his clout
on city council.
In the last year,
he's changed three city charters,
giving more power to the mayor.
Mayor gig's pretty much ceremonial.
Not anymore.
The post has full veto authority
over town policy,
including eminent domain decisions.
Guess who's running for mayor?
Hale.
Wants your timberland.
I've got to run against him.
It's the only way to protect this.
I need your help.
Sam Crow has sway over this town.
You in my corner, I got a shot.
There's something I need from you.
Piece of land, access road,
power.
- Something off the radar.
- Guns.
You don't ever need to know.
Show of good faith.
It's a knife
with your fingerprints on it
we used to kill the scumbag
raped your little girl.
I know what it is.
I ain't got nothing on you now.
From here on out,
we got to trust each other.
Just the good word
of two honest men.
Riding through this world
All alone
God takes your soul
You're on your own
The crow flies straight
A perfect line
On the Devil's bed
Until you die
Gotta look this life
In the eye.
Episode 208: Potlatch
- Can you call Opie?
- What happened?
Someone broke in.
Stole our HD camera and my laptop.
Had three rough cuts on it.
Shit!
What happened to the guard dog
I bought you?
See for yourself.
It's okay, sweetie.
No one's gonna hurt you.
Oh, man.
Lyla's scared.
She wants Ope.
Hungry?
- Dim sum's better than good head.
- What do you want, Lin?
Last time we visited your restaurant,
we were throwing shots at each other.
Why I wanted to see you.
We need guns.
Our distributor
is temporarily offline.
If it was the feds that shut
your guy down, we're not interested.
Wasn't ATF. INS.
He's having a little trouble
getting into the country.
We know you deal AKs.
We'll pay double,
all you can get us.
As a show of good faith,
a gift.
Shit.
What the hell happened to his hands?
My sexual proclivities,
they took their toll on Mr. Lin.
Can't grab it, can't pull it.
I accept that.
Jesus Christ, man.
Turns out, you only need
two fingers to work a calculator.
He paid off his debt, but...
my new son-in-law's an accountant.
Told my daughter
I'd give him the job, so,
Chuck is all yours.
We'll pass.
- Thought he was a friend of yours.
- I am.
Otto and me are best friends.
We'll let you know about the guns.
Please, Clay, if you don't take me,
they're just gonna kill me.
You're already dead in my book.
Come on, Clay. Lin's a psycho.
We'll take him.
What?
He can do the books at Caracara.
It'll free Bobby up.
Get up.
Come on.
Are we really going to the Irish
for the AKs
knowing that Stahl's onto them?
We don't know anything
Stahl says is true.
She'll tell you
anything to get what she wants.
We'll go to Edmond's.
We'll feel it out.
If he's got the guns, we figure out
a safe way to make the transaction.
If he doesn't,
then we know he's selling to Zobelle.
That was Jax. Got to go to Caracara.
I'm gonna need you guys.
You stay available.
Take Chucky. Go on.
What?
Come on, open the door for him.
Fiona?
Mornin'.
Jesus.
What the hell you doing here?
I heard about what happened.
We were worried.
That's from Kerrianne.
You alone?
Doesn't matter.
Came to see you.
How are you feeling?
Like I was blown up.
Doctor says I'm healing.
I'm glad.
Bad idea you coming here.
My life's a series of bad ideas,
lovey.
Sleep.
Mo ghr.
That dog cost me four grand.
And that was a $10,000 camera.
Camera's insured. The rough cuts
are worth ten times as much.
This had to be Georgie, right?
Of course it was.
They look pretty cozy.
I think they're kind of cute.
Reminds me of me and Otto.
She okay?
I think so.
Who did this?
The shit that's missing,
it's got to be Caruso.
Let's go.
See you later?
What time does Gemma
want us for dinner?
8:00.
Gemma's having a potlatch.
Wants us all there.
Sounds like a good idea.
I got Kenny and Ellie.
Bring 'em.
Lyla?
She's been helping me out.
You serious about it?
I don't know.
Kids like her.
- You hitting it?
- Come on, Bobby.
- We're just hanging out.
- Dude, she's a porn star.
Your point?
My point is she's a porn star.
You gotta hit it.
What do you know
about hooking up with porn stars?
Just what I heard.
You know, it can get, like...
I have been around, you know?
I mean, it's like,
it gets crazy sometimes, you know?
You should bring her
to dinner tonight, man.
Gemma won't mind. Come on.
- What the hell, dude?
- Forgot. Shit.
It's a gift from the Chinese.
He could help with the books.
Nice to see you.
They chopped them off?
That is deep shit, man.
- I'm still adjusting.
- That mean you can't...?
I'm very thick.
So, yes,
masturbation is pretty much impossible.
That's gotta suck.
I'm very indebted to all of you.
Lin's been out of his mind.
- Why is that?
- He's losing turf to the Mexicans.
Heroin?
Mayans took over everything
south of Water Street.
- That's why they need the guns.
- That's pushing it on niners' turf.
What does that mean for us?
Georgie's studio's halfway
to Oaktown.
Maybe we should check in on Laroy.
Come with us, chucky.
- We'll put you to use.
- I accept that.
Late night at the pub?
In the future, I'd appreciate a little
heads-up before you fellas drop in.
Where's the russian Aks, man?
Sold them.
To who?
Guessing you wouldn't want us telling
other customers who you were.
Our deal was,
we move your handguns,
you sell us the aks.
When we get more,
you'll be the first to know.
Bullshit.
You don't mind if I take
another look around?
- Don't take kindly to your suspicions.
- It's okay.
We just got an unexpected order,
and we was hoping to fill it is all.
Next time.
- Those guns are in that house, man.
- I know.
- Means they're selling to Zobelle.
- We keep eyes on them.
Zobelle's crew shows up,
we take our guns back.
Sack, you got the first shift.
Right.
They were pissed.
Clay backed them off,
but he knew something was up.
We sure about this, da?
We haven't even cleared it with Jimmy O.
I'll let you know.
Morning, lovey.
Your dad?
Who's Jimmy O?
He's no one you'd ever want to meet.
You're a long way from home,
sweetheart.
Yes. I am.
Why?
I was worried about him.
Could've sent flowers.
Just needed to see him, Gemma.
We are in a shitstorm here.
The last thing we need
is you turning him inside out.
Hello.
Dr. Knowles,
Fiona Larkin.
Nice to meet you.
I'm afraid
icu is for immediate
family members only.
She is family.
I'm his wife.
Pardon me.
What do you need?
I called Mr.
Caruso about watching my reel.
Mutilation fetish.
Wait here.
He's here.
Not interested.
I got something else.
Mother...!
- Get out.
- Now!
How does that feel, you dead bitch?
Come in, "OJ."
Get us the camera
before my boy here
crushes his throat.
Get the goddamn camera.
I'll cover him.
I'm guessing this one's ours
but maybe we should
take both just in case.
All my shit's on that one!
This one?
You son of a bitch.
Don't!
That's for killing the dog,
you psycho piece of shit.
You think this is how it works?
You idiots could just crash in here
and take stuff from me?
You got no idea.
You white trash morons,
you got no...
Lyla's with me now.
You touch her,
call her,
even think about her,
I'll kill you.
Come on, chucky, boy.
I think we owe you a drink.
Yeah, two fingers of tequila.
Humor's very healing.
I think Georgie could
use a drink and a laugh.
What do we do here?
I didn't know Chibs was married.
They never got divorced.
It's been a long time
since they were together.
Sounds like she's not a favorite.
There's only been three women
I'm afraid of...
My mother,
my third grade math teacher
and that irish bitch.
Where's Chibs at...
his insurance shit?
He'll be off critical
in a day or two.
He'll have to finish
his recovery at Stockton.
That can't happen.
Not with her around.
He can't be out of our sight.
- There's nothing I can do.
- There's always something we can do.
You see that redhead?
Margaret Murphy,
chief administrator.
She has been up my ass
about the club.
I try anything,
she'll be all over it.
It can't happen.
Going down?
Yes, ma'am.
Where's the van?
Jax and the guys took it.
This thing with Jax, man,
you haven't said much.
Is it that Donna thing?
That's part of it.
Anything I can do?
I doubt it.
That shit already's
got you spun around.
Wh-what does that mean?
Killing Donna...
it's flipped some switch in you.
Not even sure
that patch makes sense.
You think I can't make
the hard call?
With all the shit that I've done
for you and this club?
It's not about the shit you've done,
it's about the shit you may have to do.
I can do my job.
Good to know.
Weston just got here, one other guy.
- Follow the guns.
- Right.
Call everybody.
What do you want?
Laroy won't mind us dropping by.
Wait here.
We know the way.
Pardon me.
Orange fanta, please.
Shit,
new owners.
We should go.
Weston has the guns up
ahead at the rest stop.
Looks like they're waiting
for a pick up.
Where is everyone?
Get them on the phone.
- I want them here!
- All right.
Probably should've called ahead
and made sure Laroy was home.
That would've been the smart play.
It's gotta be Clay wondering
where the hell we are.
Heard things got pretty
out of hand in county.
You and me always been able
to talk about shit.
Not lately.
Think maybe it's got something to do
with this beef you got going with Clay?
- Maybe if I knew what it was...
- It's about keeping shit contained.
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
You getting in deeper with Clay.
I don't know.
I feel like I'm losing
all my friends.
Laroy don't live here no more, ese.
- We put that together.
- Where'd you get the russian hardware?
New friends,
new opportunities.
You got a point to make,
make it quick.
My mom's expecting us for dinner.
So I'm not invited?
I might need someone
to bus a few tables.
Hijo de puta!
You tell Clay that bullshit truce
we had is off the table.
Every state, every charter.
Mayans are no friends of...
Get 'em out of here.
And take their cuts.
That ain't gonna happen.
You will lay it at my feet,cabrón.
Pull the trigger, man. It's the only
way this leather's coming off my back.
Summer of love may be over,
jefe, but
killing the mother charter's vp?
You might want to think
about that move.
Next time a son walks
into mayan territory,
they don't walk out.
Shit.
What do we know?
We know she's dead.
Beaten to death.
Saw some wood slivers.
Probably a bat.
Call for a body wagon.
What the hell is this?
- Right there.
- Do not move!
Easy.
Think you may have accidentally
picked up our order.
Yeah,
these are definitely our cigars.
Something funny, white boy?
It's just amazing
how bad your timing is.
Shit!
Drop 'em! Drop em!
Shit, want the guns!
Cover him.
Come on, let it go.
Jesus christ!
How the hell did that happen?
They follow you?
Not sure.
We whole?
Load 'em.
I'll follow you to the delivery.
Zobelle wants to do this personally.
You should head back
to the cigar shop
before something else goes wrong.
And you should adjust your attitude.
- Thought you were bringing a salad.
- I've been busy.
What?
This is a hostile work environment
claim filed against me and myproxy
by Margaret Murphy.
Are you kidding me?
- What a bunch of pussies.
- You threatened her.
I had a passionate conversation
with her in the elevator.
This is my livelihood!
Do you have any idea how hard
I've worked to get to where I am?
I get it.
Do you?
This could cost me my goddamn job.
The club is the club,
my life is my life. Stay out of it.
Perfect.
Serving hand jobs for dessert?
That's real nice
in front of the kids.
- Where you going?
- Home.
I am tired of taking abuse.
That doctor's an arrogant bitch.
Sorry.
Thanks, brother.
Jesus christ, here we go.
Dinner with mom.
Weston almost lost
the guns to Sam Crow.
He got all bent out of shape
when he couldn't deliver them to you.
Mr. Weston does a lot
of things very well,
but understanding the need for
this type of relationship evades him.
That's not necessary.
This is the third delivery
you haven't let me pay for.
It's not the way business is done.
I'm a venture capitalist,
Mr. Alvarez.
I'm investing in the future
of your organization.
Talk to your associates in,
Stockton and Pelican Bay.
They'll assure you,
I'm a fair player
and a good friend to have.
I will.
Can you ease up on Lyla?
- She's just...
- I know...
doing her best.
I keep hanging out with this family,
I may be sucking cock
to pay my bills, too.
What the hell's the matter with you?
Ask your mother.
- What happened?
- Come on, everybody.
Come on, let's sit down.
- Where the hell were you?
- What are you talking about?
Two guys are at the hospital,
and you decide not to pick up the phone.
We were neck-deep
in our own pile of shit.
We almost got killed
trying to take back our guns, man.
Club business.
Not here, asshole.
- Come on!
- I mean it.
Hey, they were helping me, Clay.
We had some payback
to deliver at Caracara.
Hopefully, it went a little bit better
than the trammel task.
- Blow me, shithead.
- Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt.
I figured I should tell you
this in person.
We just found Luann Delaney
off county 18.
Beaten to death.
There's no other details right now.
I'm sorry.
Did you cause this?
- What are you talking about?
- Payback
- at Caracara.
- This is on me, Clay.
- And me, too.
- What did you idiots do?
I'm not talking to you, asshole.
You see what you're doing
to this club?
Do you see what you're
doing to this club?!
I was risking my ass for this club.
Bullshit.
You're as blind as you are crippled.
The blind guy's in jail with no wife
'cause you just got her killed.
I'm not the one murdering women!
Santiag Team
.:: La Fabrique ::.