Hold it, hold, it, hold it!
Holy shit.
Appreciate the lift.
No problem.
Where's the Cutlass?
- It's at the hospital.
- Still not running right?
It's running okay.
This worry I'm getting here.
Have anything to do with that car
that's been following us?
The compact parked
halfway down the block.
What the hell's going on?
That ATF agent
that's been looking into you guys.
I think he's here for me.
- What are you talking about?
- I was with him in Chicago.
It got violent. I tried to end it.
He started stalking me.
- Don't. He's dangerous.
- Go back inside, Tara.
Lock the door.
Vandalism, deadly weapon.
That's six months in County, asshole.
Violating a restraining order.
You'll be in the cell next to me.
They teach you
how to suck a dick in ATF school?
Badass biker.
You guys gave it your best shot.
You got nothing on Sam Crow.
And you harassing Tara.
That ends here.
Or next time it won't be your piece
of shit car I'm draining fluid from.
You threatening a federal agent?
I'm threatening you.
Go away.
It's my last warning.
You'd better rein
in your ATF boyfriend.
Agent Kohn isn't on my payroll.
I don't keep tabs.
Well, maybe you should.
He's not here for Sam Crow, Hale.
He's here for Tara.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- This guy was stalking her in Chicago.
Thinks she came back to Charming
to be with me. I'm telling you:
this guy is nuts
and he's going to hurt her.
Jesus Christ.
That's who she had
a restraining order against.
You knew?
No, but it makes sense now.
Hale.
Let's go, hotshot.
Water and Power just dug up
some old bones out on 44.
Be there in a minute.
Kohn is my problem.
I will handle it.
You'd better, man,
or I'm gonna.
Half-Sack, bomaye.
Get in there, kid.
- My money's on Lowell.
- Now you're getting cocky.
Anyone can beat up a junkie,
prospect.
Doesn't mean shit.
Where'd you learn
to fight like this?
I was Junior Lightweight Champion,
- Armed Forces Boxing Competition.
- That's so hot.
Things all better
with the little missus now?
My balls are still attached.
Shit, Lowell, get out of there.
- Whose idea was this?
- Bobby's.
I don't I don't mind it, Clay.
- I'm just... helping Half-Sack train.
- Well, you killed enough brain cells.
Come on, come on. Back to work.
Thanks.
- How's he doing?
- The latest round of rehab
seems to be sticking.
He hasn't missed any work.
If I could get AA to kick up a vig,
Lowell could make us all rich.
He's always been a freak.
He's a damn good mechanic.
I guess you taught him that.
How's Sugar Ray One-Nut looking?
He's wicked fast.
He's got a great right hook.
How much money gets thrown around
at these bare-fist things?
The purse is okay,
but it's the betting that's gone crazy.
I know a couple of guys last year,
made six figures each.
- Really?
- The prospect could knock
those lightweights out
any day of the week.
Absolutely.
What'd we pull together for McKeavy?
120.
You ain't thinking about betting
on the prospect?
You know, if Half-Sack
takes his first five fights
and looks strong
going into the finish,
we control how it ends.
Could be a huge payday.
What do you think?
I don't know.
But I do know there's no way
we're raising 80 grand
in the next four days, so...
Might be our only shot.
- I'm in.
Done.
All right, I'm in.
Take 50 grand.
I want to see it triple.
You're going to train him.
No booze, no weed, no pussy.
That include the Nevada sweetbutt?
Until I'm up a hundred K, ***the Nevada
sweetbutt*** can cool on the counter.
Bobby.
Do me a favor.
Push up on that thing, will you?
- Really?
- Really.
Halfy-Sacky's all about that now.
I want to see
if she's all about him.
And go at it hard.
- I ain't mad at that.
- Half-Sack's going to lose his mind.
Well, that kind of anger
we can really use.
Call Unser, see if he wants in
on some of this fight action.
Clay, he's out on the job.
Water and Power dug up
some old bones this morning.
- Where?
- Out on 44.
What?
Wheeling out two bodies.
Should be three.
- I'm afraid to ask.
- Don't be.
There it is.
Was this us?
Shit.
Episode 107: Old Bones
All three of them were Mayans?
Back in '92,
Mexicans tried to expand
their Oakland dope base.
Set up a charter in Lodi.
We couldn't let that happen.
Was a bloody two years.
Bodies dropped.
I remember.
That was right around
the time my old man died.
That's right.
We got to stop the PD
from IDing those bodies, man.
I mean, if they flag the Mayans,
we're their next stop.
We can pull teeth to stop the ID,
but they can still DNA test.
Forensic tests on three bodies?
That would blow half
of Unser's yearly budget.
But if Hale thought
it would hurt us,
he could get his new fed buddies
to float the cost.
Shit, man, that was pre-O.J., right?
I mean, we weren't thinking
about DNA,
right, back in '93. What kind of clues
we got buried with those Mexicans?
If they don't know they're Mayans,
they won't take it any further.
We stop the identification.
We stop the investigation.
There's a $15K purse on the line...
and a lot of ringside action.
I'm ready.
This ain't no Army boxing, kid.
This is street brawling.
No, it's cool.
Cherry Pie.
- What?
- It's time to go.
What are you talking about?
Go where?
- What are you doing, Bobby?
- Relax, prospect.
She's going to stay with him
till the fight.
No, I'm not.
- Oh, yeah, you are.
- Why?
No booze, no dope.
No pussy.
- You'll love my place. Very cozy.
- Get your hands off me.
- Quarantine.
- Back off!
Clay, you know, no...
sex before a fight's like
an old wives' thing, man.
Did you just insult
my old lady again?
Jump him.
Why didn't you tell me it was Kohn?
Jax told you?
I did not know that Kohn
was the guy that was stalking you.
- I could have...
- I tried getting help in Chicago.
Complained to his superiors.
Made things worse.
I went through three precincts
before someone'd even
give me that restraining order.
Doubted you could do anything.
Kohn's boss doesn't even know
that he is here.
This guy is in deep shit.
He is done.
Really?
He is leaving Charming.
I promise.
And I am sorry.
Town's talking about the skulls
that rolled out of that hole.
I'm sure they are.
You thought about damage control?
Tig's the only one
who knows the truth.
Everybody else thinks
all those bodies are Mayans.
And how do you stop that truth
from spreading?
I got it covered.
All right? Don't worry.
This shit stays in the rearview.
I talked to Trammel.
Sanwa County Coroner's
clearing space,
but bones stay local tonight.
Good.
Now I have to get into
the lower level of the hospital.
You...
think the old squeeze
might be able to hook a brother up?
- I'll see what I can do.
- Alright.
Sorry, Clay.
I just asked Gemma,
just wanted to make sure it was okay
that I have Moby here
only during my break.
He likes to watch me work.
Sure. That's fine.
You're doing good work.
Thanks, man.
All right, Tara's not here.
- What do you want to do?
- Lab coat on the chair.
You distract the doctors.
Yeah, not a problem.
Excuse me, ladies.
How you doing?
You're doctors, both of you?
Thank God.
Doberman pinscher,
you know, took a chunk...
- Jesus Christ. No, hang out.
- Took a chunk out of my ass.
- Can we...
- You need to go to the ER.
Distract them. I said distract them,
not scar them for life.
No, shit, I'm serious.
Man, I think it's infected.
***A man *** just steal
a key card from an intern.
Hopefully it gets us below.
Me and Tig'll take care of this.
Why don't you stay here
and run interference.
Why?
Kid looks strong, huh?
You have a good night, all right?
You, too.
Nurse said you wanted to see me.
I was just checking in.
You okay?
I talked to Hale.
He assured me Joshua was leaving.
Thanks for...
handling that.
You're welcome.
You won't have to worry
about that guy anymore.
H, I, J, K...
L, M, N, O, P...
Q, R, S...
T, U, V...
W, X,
Y, and Z...
- I'll find us some gloves.
- Okay.
Freako.
- We ain't here to find you a date.
- I know.
I know, it's just... you know.
You ever...?
What?
- Cold-pack?
- Yeah.
No. Not my thing.
I know
it's a little bit creepy at first.
But then something happens, man.
I'm telling you.
This soothing coldness,
the stillness,
I mean, it's really a beautiful thing.
Please, please,
stop.
Goddamn it.
It's all right.
I thought I told you
to wait upstairs.
There's no interference to run.
And I figured you could use
the extra pair of hands.
Is that all right?
I got 'em.
All three.
Hold the head.
Tight.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
It's already been ID'd.
Lowell Harlan, Senior.
This is Lowell's old man.
Cookie time.
I made 'em.
Especially for you.
No, thank you.
Stop. Please.
Come on, girl.
You ain't no old lady yet.
You...
do this for me...
I'll make sure that you get
the thumbs-up from Clay.
- Stop, okay? Please.
- Come on.
Stop!
I'm not a sweetbutt!
- Yeah, you are.
- No, I'm not. I came here for Kip.
I'm not gonna be passed around anymore,
all right?
I'm done with that.
- Come on.
- Seriously!
Jesus!
Okay.
Okay?
I said... "Okay."
Relax. Have a cookie.
Why was Lowell's dad
buried with the enemy?
Casualty of war.
Mayans took him out.
- He worked at T-M. He wasn't patched.
- Mayans went after everybody.
Family, friends, didn't matter.
Lowell thinks his dad just split.
Poor bastard's convinced
he's still out there.
I know.
So, why the same grave?
A disrespect.
I know.
It was a crazy two years. I didn't have
time to think a lot of shit through.
Is that why you didn't want me
in the morgue?
Protect that secret?
I got no secrets from you.
You know,
with the Mayans ID'd, too,
I can only imagine the poison
Hale's gonna pour on Lowell's ear.
I'll handle Lowell.
Sounds good.
Is it cool if I work on it
before my shift?
Is everything okay, man?
I want you to hear this from me.
What?
Something happen to Moby?
- I left him with Neeta...
- No, your kid's fine.
Those bodies
they pulled out of the hole on 44.
One of them's your old man.
My dad?
That don't make sense.
I'm sorry, son.
No, he ran off when I was like, 15.
He just split.
Everyone told me that.
You told me that.
I know.
Well...
son of a bitch
was already dead to me, right?
What...
what happened to him?
Mayan war.
Wrong place, wrong time.
The other bodies
they found in the hole
was two Mexicans
who killed your dad.
Vengeance was meted out.
The cops...
They're gonna try to lay
all those bodies at Sam Crow's feet.
- That's bullshit.
- I know.
It ain't a matter of true or false.
Hale is gonna try
to screw with your compass.
I don't want you losing true north.
Inside the club,
there had to be truth.
Our word was our honor.
But outside,
it was all about deception.
Lies were our defense, our default.
To survive,
you had to master the art of perjury.
The lie and the truth
had to feel the same.
But once you learn that skill,
nobody knows the truth,
in or outside the club.
Especially you.
My God...
Holy shit!
The two bodies were Mayan captains.
It had to be Sam Crow.
Yeah, well, 15-year-old Mexican
bones give us nothing.
Even with DNA,
there's no murder weapon
so it's ancient history.
The US Attorney's Office won't touch it.
Look at this.
Dead mechanic
worked for Teller-Morrow.
History of drug abuse, domestic
violence... his kid's on the way in.
Following his old man's footsteps,
close to Sam Crow.
- How close?
- Not sure.
Any word on Kohn?
Checked out of his hotel,
turned in his rental car.
He may already be gone. Here we go.
- You, wanted to see me?
- Yeah.
Have a seat, Lowell.
I'm June Stahl, federal agent.
I'm here helping out
the deputy chief.
Yeah?
Helping out with what?
We have some sad news
for you about your father.
Yeah, I know.
They found him in that hole off of 44.
Well, you don't seem
too surprised by that, Lowell.
- You live by the sword, you know?
- He was a mechanic, not a gangster.
- Why was he buried with outlaw bikers?
- I don't know.
Your old man worked
for Teller-Morrow, right?
Yeah.
So the Sons of Anarchy
must've trusted him.
He was a friend.
Did Clay tell you that?
It's true: he was a friend,
and I'm a friend.
Right, just like your dad.
You're just a chip off
the old spoon.
Let's just hope we don't find you in
a ditch on a county road somewhere?
Who do you think killed him?
You know they found
three bullet holes in his head.
Now, what could a mechanic do
that would incite such a gruesome death?
- I don't know.
- He was buried with the enemy, Lowell.
He was not a friend.
He did something to piss off Clay.
No.
He was in the same grave
because he had the same killers.
Use your head, Lowell.
- Sam Crow killed your father.
- That is not true!
Yes, it is.
What's going on in here?
Who the hell are you?
- ATF.
- Just what we need.
- You guys want to rent a goddamn wing?
- Aren't you spunky.
You done with him?
For now.
Get out of here, Lowell.
Go ahead.
Go on.
Pleasure.
It's bad enough I got to see the other
one every time I get a hot shave.
Now, I gotta deal with Mrs. ATF
chewing on my last nerve?
- When did you last see Kohn?
- I just left him, at Floyd's.
- Who did this?
- ATF.
Why?
Tara.
- That stupid bitch.
- How is this her fault?
- This guy's dead.
- At least.
Yeah.
Kohn's still in town.
I know. He's at Floyd's.
I'm taking care of it.
I'm really going to miss this, Floyd.
You want to go to war with me,
you sick piece of shit?
This is bullshit.
He attacked me.
No one backs your version, Kohn.
He put me through a goddamn window.
Right.
Apparently after
you stabbed him with some scissors.
No.
Don't think Jax is pressing charges.
Shit! Great!
Thank you.
But you will be facing
charges in Illinois
for violating a restraining order.
I'm not stalking Tara.
I'm protecting her.
Come on.
We all know what happens
if she hooks up with Teller.
You know I'm right.
We're all on the same team here.
No, Josh.
Not anymore.
You're in breach of about
a half dozen federal statutes.
You've been stripped of your creds
and OPR is going to meet you at O'Hare.
I hope that the stalk
was a good rush 'cause,
it just killed your career.
Wait.
She came back here
because she was afraid of me.
I pointed her at Sam Crow.
I can't fix that mistake,
but you can both of you can.
Please?
Barber says you came in
for a haircut.
Agent Kohn attacked you
with a pair of scissors,
so you pushed him
through a plate glass window.
Self-defense.
That's what Floyd saw.
I guess that's what happened.
That's fantastic.
Tell me.
Are they all just afraid of you
or convinced
that you are a necessary evil?
You charging me?
No charges.
Why does Kohn have
a hard-on for you?
You know why.
You're right, I do.
Tara Knowles.
The charming ingenue.
- High school sweethearts, right?
- Yeah.
She fears for her life,
so she comes back home
to the only man
she knows loves her
enough to protect her.
A guy who would have no problem
putting a fed through
a plate glass window.
That's beautiful.
Really, it is.
I wish I had that kind
of pull for someone.
You're a lucky man.
You done?
Yeah, she's done.
She's getting under his skin.
I can feel it.
It's bad for us.
I'm keeping an eye on him.
Not gonna let anything turn Jax
away from Sam Crow, especially pussy.
Tara's not pussy.
He loved her.
Probably still does.
Neeta just called.
Lowell, MIA.
She just found Moby in the apartment
crying, locked in the bathroom.
Shit.
Yeah, he probably went
to Lodi looking to score.
It's not your fault, baby.
Been taking care
of Lowell since he's 16.
You've done everything you could.
Just some shit you can't escape.
It's like father, like son,
- Yeah.
- It looks like it's going that way.
Gotta to rember what's important.
Big picture.
I'll call the Vista.
See if he checked in.
No one blames you
if Lowell don't come home.
Come on, Lowell.
Open up. I'm taking you home.
It makes no sense.
It's no sense that my dad
was buried with them wetbacks!
How long have you been
taking care of me, Clay?
Why are you here now?
I made a promise to your dad.
What, before you killed him?
You killed him, Clay.
Why would you do that?
I lied to you, son.
Don't you call me that.
I am not that.
Your father wasn't
killed by the enemy.
- - He was the enemy.
- No. He was a friend.
He was a loathsome piece of shit.
Treated you and your mother like dirt.
Cared more about the crank than
he did about his friends, his family.
- Sound familiar?
- I'm not that.
No?
Then what the hell are you?
You can't stay clean!
You abandoned your kid.
Moby.
I killed your old man.
I killed him 'cause he was a rat.
A weak, unkie rat.
I'm not a rat.
Look at you.
Ten minutes with Hale,
you turn inside out.
You run away.
You don't give a shit
about your kid!
I'm sorry, Clay.
Next time maybe Moby
drowns in that bathtub.
Or maybe you tell Hale and the feds
all those secrets you've been
hearing at Teller-Morrow.
I can't deal with it anymore, Clay.
My point.
Shit.
I'm my old man.
I'm Lowell.
God.
I'm sorry, Clay.
I know that you tried to help me.
You help Moby.
You save him from me.
Do it!
Please.
You help my little boy.
This is it, prospect.
The final fight.
- How you feeling?
- I'm good, man.
- This asshole looks half dead.
- Yeah, well, he's had a tougher climb.
- It's a beautiful thing.
- It is a beautiful thing.
You're looking like a champ.
Everybody's betting on you.
Except for us.
What do you mean?
You want me to lose?
Come on, man. I can beat this guy.
I can win this whole thing.
If you win this, we get 15 grand.
You lose, we walk home with
ten times that much, so you lose.
You're gonna take
a dive for the club.
Go get him...
sort of.
Why aren't you at the fight?
Had my share for today.
Yeah.
Your leg okay?
- Where's the doctor?
- I don't know.
Where you going with that, Jax?
Nowhere.
I don't believe that.
I've seen the two of you together,
see how you act around her.
She's still got ties in you.
You know what?
I don't give a shit what you think.
What I do, what Tara does...
It's not your business.
No, cleaning up piss and broken cribs...
that's my business?
No one asked you to take this on.
This house, this kid.
It's not your burden; it's mine.
Shit.
- You deal with that Lowell problem?
- Call Neeta.
Tell her she's gonna be
watching Moby for a while.
All right.
Give it one more round.
Then he falls.
I understand you...
declined Bobby's
request for some comfort.
Yeah, I did.
I'm not about that anymore.
And if I was to ask
for some comfort...
would you be about that?
No.
Sorry, but your old lady
would turn us both into chum.
You make a good point.
If, Half-Sack patches in,
which is a big if,
it's all right with me
if you stick around.
That is, if he wants
you as his old lady.
Shit!
Half-Sack, don't!
What's he doing?
What is he doing?
Gonna KO this guy.
Shit, I'll kill him.
I'm gonna kill him.
No, no, no.
My bad. My bad.
Get him out of there
before we got to bury another Mexican.
Come on.
Hey,*** relax
Clay, I'm really sorry.
You know, I just lost it... I'm
You owe the club 35K.
- Really?
- Yeah.
At least you got the girl?
Go on, get out of here
before I rape both of you.
- Ick. Hey!
- Come on, come on.
It's just an expression.
A term of endearment.
We're gonna need the 115 by Friday.
It's gonna be a busy week.
You said it.
He's a good mechanic.
Jesus, are you okay?
Yeah.
Hale told me what happened.
Kohn's gone.
I watched him leave town.
Thank you.
What is it?
You left Chicago 'cause you were afraid
this guy was gonna hurt you?
One of the reasons.
Did you come back here
'cause you knew I would hurt this guy?
- Do what the cops wouldn't do?
- God, no.
And I had no idea
he would follow me.
I didn't know
you'd even still be here.
That doesn't sound like you, Jax.
Sounds like your mother.
Well, you're safe now.
How'd it go, baby?
Where is he?
Sam Crow rehab.
What did you tell Jax?
About the bodies?
Some of the truth.
And Lowell?
A little more.
The rest stays buried.
Yeah.
It rests in peace.
Subtitles: Santiag Team
michvanilly, Tagne