Previously, on Sons of Anarchy
- I thought we agreed to meet alone.
- My son Esai.
I don't travel far from home
without family.
How'd you like to take over
Sam Crow's gun business?
Their Irish gun supplier.
Part of an ATF file on the Sons.
You hit Clay first.
Then you kill the rest.
I get Charming.
You get the gun intel.
Got to put down two dogs
making my life miserable.
- Just tell me who.
- Sam Crow boss.
And that greedy cracker shithead.
Let me and my boys do it.
Michael McKeavy.
- Good soldier, good friend.
- Hear.
He's hurt real bad.
We got to get him back to the clubhouse.
That ATF agent, I was with him.
It got violent. I tried to end it.
He started stalking me.
Not this way.
You stupid bitch!
They're gonna patch him up.
He'll do a few years for assault.
Then he's gonna be out.
Free to do this again.
Once a biker slut, always a...
Where is he?
Relax.
Don't tell me to relax.
Called his cell phone a dozen times,
Tara's house. No answer.
I can't just sit here.
Till we see where this lands,
you stay put, understand?
- What if they got to him?
- Jax can take care of himself, Gem.
I'm going to the hospital,
see if he's there.
I'll go with you.
Take care of my boys.
Always.
We got to get the slugs out
of this guy's ass.
Infection's spreading.
He may even have sepsis.
Just do the best you can, all right?
I can't find the damn slug!
Unser at the back door.
Let him in.
Shut those doors.
- Me arse!
- Keep him quiet.
What can I do for you, Chief?
I need to bring you down
to the station house,
ask a few questions.
Why? What happened?
Someone went after Darby last night,
killed one of his guys, two women.
At his house.
In Charming.
You think it was us?
Lodi also found two dead Mayans
in a ditch off 18,
half mile outside of town.
Last time
I looked at the scoreboard,
Nords and Mayans were the away team.
Glad you're rooting
for the home team, Chief.
I see you for a minute?
It's okay. Don't worry.
This ain't funny.
At all.
Five DBs.
Know what heat that brings?
Jesus Christ.
- Who the hell is that?
- A friend.
With two bullets in his ass
that were meant for my head.
The Mayans went after me, too.
Goddamn it.
We didn't have nothing
to do with Darby.
And the dead Mexicans were
the result of their own stupidity.
But I made sure that didn't land
in Charming.
Barely.
My office still got
the stink of ATF.
This body count's gonna bring
that haughty bitch circling back.
I need you to come with me.
All right? Due process.
I got nothing to hide.
You do not go alone.
- I think I could keep him safe.
- I'll be all right.
You hold it together here.
- I'll meet you down there.
- No.
You stay put.
I'll watch her.
I got it! I got it!
- Jesus!
- Shit! Shit! Shit!
Come here! Hold that!
- What the...?
- Hold on.
We got one slug out.
This is insane.
- What the hell are we gonna do?
- Just keep your finger in his ass.
This is way beyond my wheelhouse.
This is way beyond it!
Just stay.
- Where you going?
- Find Jax and Tara.
You heard what Clay said:
family stays put.
You got two choices, Tigger:
tackle me or tag along.
I got nothing but adoration for you.
Why do you got to give me
such a hard time for?
It's my nature. I'm a giver.
This is why I beat hookers.
Jesus Christ.
You scared the shit out of me.
Where you been?
I'm sorry. I got caught up.
You been here?
This whole time?
We been waiting
for those medical supplies, man.
I know.
That's it? You know?
Someone tries to kill Clay,
and you decide
it's a good time to get laid?
It's not like that, Mom.
If you want to resurrect old trauma
with this bitch,
you do it on your own goddamn time.
She's not there.
Don't go looking for her either.
Mom!
Leave her alone.
Don't ever forget
your first priority.
I didn't.
Take your foot
off my bike.
Episode 109: Hell Followed
It wasn't Sam Crow.
- It was Mayan filth killed my guy.
- We have your statement.
We'll look into your accusations.
Accusation?
You arrogant piece of shit!
Get this asshole off me!
You okay?
The shithead caught me off guard.
- Put him in holding.
- That's right. Arrest the white guy,
let the wetbacks and coons shoot up
whoever they want to shoot up.
You do know that I'm married
to a dark-skinned woman, right?
Yeah, I know that.
Just making sure.
How you feeling?
What the hell's going on?
There were some...
complications.
- Where's the Scotsman at?
- He's gonna be right back.
Where the hell's your hand?
It's...
Okay.
Well...
my finger is...
plugging up
one of your bullet holes.
You got your finger
jammed up my ass?
Well, technically, yes. Okay.
But my finger's not
jammed up your ass,
'cause, you know, that would be gay.
It's kind of jammed in your ass.
Which I guess is still kind of gay.
- Jesus...
- But I...
Am I gonna die or not?
I don't think so.
Scotsman.
I need you guys to do me a favor.
Brenan Hefner.
Port commissioner.
He's got to be dealt with.
- There's plenty of time for that.
- No!
It's got to happen before Monday.
He's gonna sic port dogs
on our shipment.
You got to take him out.
You promise me that.
Don't worry.
Promise you.
It'll get done, I swear.
Have a drown. There you go.
Take him out?
That means, like, kill him?
No, I think what he means
is dinner and a movie.
Jackie boy, where have you been?!
I'm here now.
The bullet in this guy's ass
has hit a major femoral artery.
He needs a doctor
and he needs it now.
All right.
Where's Clay?
Unser took him in for questioning.
The Mayans tried to hit Darby, too.
Holy shit.
The other charters are on their way,
all right?
Clay wants to bounce out
this Mayan problem with them
- before we decide on any retaliation.
- Okay, makes sense.
Let me know if anything breaks.
Where are you going?
To find a doctor.
Don't ride alone.
I'll go with him.
- I've been calling you.
- Shit.
What the hell is going on, Ope?
Something came up. Clay needed me.
The mill called.
if you're not there
to pick up the 2nd shift,
- your ass is canned.
- I'll deal with it.
Deal with it? How?
You're not there,
you're out of work.
We got something goin' here, Donna.
You lying piece of shit.
Your promises were just smoke,
weren't they?
No, I never lied to you.
I said I'd find a way to earn straight.
They're gonna fire you.
The club is more important
than taking care of us?
It's more important
than spitting sawdust ten hours a day.
I'll figure it out.
I'm not gonna live this way anymore.
I'm done with this shit.
Look, I'm fine.
- You should go after her.
- I can't keep doing this.
Half our goddamned fights
are about money,
and I can't get ahead
without the club.
I need back in.
Guns, protections runs, all of it.
- You still gotta talk to Donna.
- I'm done talking.
I want back in, Jax.
I'll talk to Clay when I see him.
I didn't see this coming.
Us and the Mexicans...
it's been kinda quiet.
I'm not an idiot.
I know it was the Mayans
torched your warehouse last month.
Yeah, but coming after me,
and Heir Darby?
That's a new kind of boldness.
Me and you,
whatever the hell this is now,
always had one thing
we played out together.
Keeping blood and greed away
from our front door.
We've done that.
Until now.
And my fear is,
knowing the amount of pride
stuffed into that cut,
it will not end here.
Don't get involved in my end game,
okay, old friend?
I'm not an old friend, remember?
I'm an old cop.
And this old cop is telling ya
the tit for tat can't go on.
Fine.
We done tittin' and tattin'?
You take out that Mayan boss,
and you will trip a wire
that sends this town
into the history books.
The bad guys will leave the ghetto
and bring their filthy game to Charming.
And next time it won't be a few
of Darby's scumbags who go down.
It'll be one of your guys
or Floyd or some kid or something.
See where I'm going with this?
Deal always was
outlaws live in Charming,
shit beyond the borders.
You can't change the rules
or it all goes to hell.
And that, my old friend,
is exactly what Captain America
out there wants:
hell to break out in Charming,
followed by all the things
that put the devil in place.
It's for my cancer.
I got a card.
What the hell's this?
A little family reunion.
Holy shit.
- Did you hear anything that I just...?
- Enough, enough, all right?!
You goddamn angst
is giving me cancer.
I heard your plea
loud and clear.
There's only one thing
that's gonna make this work.
Have the sheriff pick up
Marcus Alvarez and bring him here.
Oh, sure!
Should I dress him in a lamb suit?
Listen to me.
Bring in Alvarez, I talk to him.
I'll talk to Darby.
We figure it out.
An hour from now,
there's gonna be a dozen guys
sitting around a redwood table
planning a kill.
If I were you,
I would take my request
and put it at the top
of that old cop to-do list.
How's he doing?
Good.
It's a strong-willed little guy.
Thought you were gonna take
a personal day?
I tried to. I had to get out of there,
you know?
It's a light day.
You okay?
I don't know.
What'd you do with him?
It's done.
What did we do?
When Kohn showed up at Charming,
he knew this could only end
one of two ways...
Either him dead or you dead.
It ended the right way.
Maybe I came back here
knowing the same thing.
And this was the only place
I felt safe.
It was survival.
You did what you had to do.
Is that how this works?
You make up...
your own moral code for everything?
I never killed anyone
like this before, Tara.
I don't know what the code is.
I'm sorry.
I've been waking up
every day since he was born
with this sick feeling,
wondering who was gonna die today.
It scares the shit out of me.
And then, I woke up this morning,
and it was gone.
I think that scares me more.
You're in shock.
I don't think anything
can shock me anymore.
What do you want me to do?
How can I help you?
Don't go anywhere.
I'm not.
I need you to come
to the clubhouse with me.
Those medical supplies I needed?
Bullet wounds.
The guy's got a bad infection.
We're gonna lose him.
I'll borrow some things.
What happened
with you and the Mayans?
I know you and Alvarez made
a deal in Chino. What went south?
That spic name don't ring a bell.
Ring a bell now?
We can keep going
cage fight if you want.
How many punches
you got left in that hand?
Okay,
Stupid question.
I gave up the 20
on your gun warehouse.
The Mayans were supposed to provide
muscle for my crank push
into Charming.
Alvarez double-crossed you.
I'm gonna slit
that wetback's throat ear to ear.
No, you're not.
- Neither am I.
- What the hell you talking about?
The murder rate tripled
in my town last night.
If we kill King Beaner,
Charming becomes a war zone.
- So, what, we sit back and do nothing?
- No, we do something.
And it will be satisfying.
But Sam Crow handles
the retaliation.
You got it?
My God.
Took two slugs.
I got one.
Little Dutch boy's keeping
the blood dike from bursting.
Have some Vancomycin.
This'll kill anything.
Give him two now
and then one every four hours.
Got to wake up.
Wake up here.
Come on. Wake up.
- What's going on?
- Take these.
Doc's here.
She's going to fix you up.
Here you go.
How's it look?
It looks like you got shot.
The doctor is a friend of the club.
You're in good hands.
- You Irish, Doc?
- Half.
The half that's a doctor?
I'm not sure.
You should find that out.
It's good to know.
Me?
Where should I put it?
Careful.
I'm going to have...
- Juice.
- ... Juice. Pull his finger out.
I want you to stuff
that gauze into the wound,
and then I'll close it off
with this clamp, okay? ***
Sure you know what you're doing?
Guess we'll find out.
Ready?
One...
two...
three.
Holy shit.
Great job, Doc.
Can I go and wash my hands now?
Yeah.
Hey, you did...
you did great, Juice.
You helped...
you helped save his life.
That was very sweet.
No, I mean it.
That guy's not used to good feedback.
I'm a little out of my element here.
I'm not quite sure
how all this works.
For now, you keep him alive.
Beyond that...
I got no idea how this works.
What the hell is this?
The sheriff said I was being
brought in for questioning.
I'm sitting here...
trying to think
how killing me and the dirty white boy
is a smart move for you guys.
There's got to be a piece
of the puzzle I ain't seeing.
Or maybe you're just really stupid.
Which...
looking at how
you botched both hits,
as a theory, ain't too far-fetched.
You got something you want to do here,
let's get to it, man.
What do you mean, like shiv ya?
Make you suck my dick?
That's a little obvious,
don't you think?
You and me, Marky,
we're going to have
our own little MC summit.
Yeah?
We're just going
to figure it all out, are we?
I don't know, man.
Mayans and Sons...
- that's some real Arab-Jew shit.
- We got a little history,
but why don't we talk
about the present.
You guys need guns, right?
Half-ass gats
you're buying off the street
barely scare the clerks
at the 7-Eleven...
- We arm up just fine, ese.
- Bullshit. You're packing toys.
You need real guns;
I need real money.
Maybe it's time for me to...
expand my customer base.
Sounds smart.
What I really need...
is that nigger's heroin trade.
Can't take it
if their guns are bigger than mine.
I said expand, not exchange.
I'm still going to sell to the Niners.
You guys want to play Operation
Ghetto Storm, knock yourselves out.
What I'm offering you is the same
hardware at the same price.
What's your end?
Peace of mind.
Charters up north, they settle
all their beefs with the SOA,
and I don't care what it costs you.
It all ends up in our favor.
And Nevada...
your charters leave my new crew
in Indian Hills alone.
And the first bullet
out of one of my guns
that hits a Son or friend of,
ends the arrangement, followed by a hell
you don't even want to know.
What about ATF?
Non-issue.
They know about
your Irish gun hook-up, ese.
Ship from Dungloe, oil drums.
Got intel on all of it.
And that puzzle piece
you couldn't see...
some ATF agent you guys
pissed off sent Darby a file.
Gave him all the info
on your gun business.
Let me guess.
Darby used it as currency?
The guns for my head?
I hate that white boy.
Let my emotions
get the better of me.
The hits... bad planning,
sloppy work.
I guess God had a bigger plan.
I mean, here we are talking about peace.
Ain't no peace yet.
Don't forget, you tried to end me.
That doesn't go unanswered.
Salt Lake to Tacoma...
my crews going
to want your head on a stick.
I got a compromise
I think will satisfy everyone.
I never made a conscious decision
to have the club
become one thing or another.
It just happened before my eyes.
Each savage event
was a catalyst for the next.
And by the time the violence
reached epic proportion,
I couldn't see it.
Blood was every color.
- Doc's looking for you.
- Okay.
One two three...
Takin' easy, we ***got***
How is he?
I got the slugs out
and stopped the bleeding.
If the penicillin kills the infection,
he should make it.
How is she?
Can't stop that bleeding.
She still wants me dead,
you know that, right?
I'll handle my mother.
What happened last night...
can never happen again.
Not just someone trying to off me,
but bodies dropping in Charming
'cause of us.
We had nothing to do
with the hit on the Nords.
Mayans went
after me and Darby, all right?
Different targets, same war.
We fire back...
we can't stop the blowback
from hitting home.
- I sat down with Alvarez.
- What?
What, just the two of you?
- Where?
- Unser's cage.
We...
we discussed
our outstanding issues...
made a deal.
What kind of deal?
We sell them guns,
they settle all their beefs
with all of us.
Any territory hassles,
any business disputes,
- it all lands in our favor.
- You made that call
without a vote?
I set it up.
We vote on it now.
If this thing passes,
you all sit down with the Mayans
in your own territories,
you work stuff out.
- Take the win.
- What about Laroy and the Niners?
We've had a deal
with them for years.
That we don't sell to the wetbacks.
Juice, Laroy don't have
no loyalty to us.
He's been buying from other dealers.
He reneged on the AK sale.
Ain't no reason at all
we can't branch out.
But the peace
we make with the Mayans
could start something
a lot worse with the Niners.
We'll deal with that fire
when it catches.
You know,
these assholes tried to kill you, man.
We're supposed to just pretend
that didn't happen?
That debt gets settled.
But not by us.
It's got to be some outside charter.
You up for it, Hap?
I'll do this thing.
It'll be perfect.
Of that I have no doubt.
Everybody in favor
of the Mayan deal...
Anybody opposed?
Cameron was supposed to kill
that piece of shit Hefner before Monday.
Hefner's squeezing the Irish
for more payoff cash.
- So he's gonna intercept the cargo.
- How is that our problem?
It ain't a problem.
It's a gift from the Irishman.
Look, we take out
the port commissioner...
he's going to give us back
the 200K that we just forked over.
Plus a month of free guns.
Our warehouse rebuild
is crushing us.
It's the cost of raw materials.
Free guns and cash...
we could be seeing black
before we put a roof on it.
Murder for hire?
- That's a dirty business.
- It's not about money.
That asshole killed McKeavy.
Michael was a friend of mine
and yours and your dad's.
And he went back
a long way with Sam Crow.
What do you think, V.P.?
I agree with Piney.
McKeavy was a friend.
I think we owe it to the Irish.
How was Cameron gonna do it?
Hefner's got a Sunday ritual.
Church with the fat wife,
sex with the black girlfriend.
She lives in a shitty hood,
right outside his nice Oakland suburb.
And that's where we take him out.
Black-on-white hate crime?
Who gives a shit?
- Who does it?
- I do.
Been a while
since you suited up, brother.
I'll do it.
I can do this.
Get Cameron to confirm the payoff.
No mistakes.
Allright.
I want Ope pulling the trigger
on this.
I want to make sure
he's really back.
We all do.
That's a good look for you.
You think?
Are we crazy?
I'll answer that later.
- You look like shit, man.
- Donna took the kids to her mom's.
I can never sleep
when the house is empty.
This gig doesn't make
sense for you, Ope.
Why do you keep
trying to push me off this?
You're the one who keeps saying
I can't live half in and half out.
'Cause you need it too much.
It becomes about money
and shit gets sloppy.
This is not about money.
I'm doing this
the same reason you are.
To prove I'm Sam Crow.
- I got nothing to prove.
- That's not what I hear.
Look, I'm ready for this, brother.
Let's just get it done.
Fine.
Good morning.
Thanks for saving the Irishman.
He'd be dead if it wasn't for you.
You're welcome.
Can I ask you a question?
I'm tired.
I'm not really up for a fight.
I'm not gonna fight.
I'm just trying to...
figure out what's going on.
You and Jax are
obviously reconnected.
Honestly?
I don't know what we are.
That's what concerns me.
You're clearly not one of them.
- I'm glad that's clear.
- So what happens next?
I don't know.
You become his old lady?
What's that look like?
Operating on kids during the day,
- patching up bullet wounds at night.
- Okay, I get it.
I know you hate me,
but this isn't me being
some overbearing bitch.
This is someone telling you
the truth.
You and Jax is a bad idea,
and someone'd
better start thinking clearly
before both of you get hurt.
Well, it wouldn't be my first bad idea.
Seems to follow me wherever I go.
You know...
you are smarter
and more strong-willed
than anyone I've ever met.
You need to shine some of that
on this thing with Jax.
He's not smart enough right now
to do what's right.
You have to be
the one to break this off.
Save both of you
from something bad.
That is his green Mercedes
in the garage.
Which apartment?
Unit nine. It's the top floor,
third from the right.
Cameras cover the garage.
Should do this on the upper level.
If this guy's got half a brain,
he's going to be cautious and armed.
Look, anyone walks into this,
has an eye line, we abort.
No risks.
Opie, you take the front steps.
I'll take the back.
- You stay, in case he gets by.
- No.
I'm gonna take the front.
This is the way Clay wanted it.
It's about Ope jumping backin.
I know.
All right.
Watch him.
All right, I got your back
in case he gets by you.
The second this goes down,
I'm in the car, motor running.
Hey, relax?
Shit happens, man.
Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry, Pop.
Because of your mistake,
I had a sit-down with Sam Crow.
Made a deal with him.
He's going to start selling us guns.
- That's good, man.
- That happened because of you, okay?
It's okay, man.
Let's go get a churro.
Catch you up on what we got to do.
Shit.
I love you, mi hijo.
Subtitles: Santiag Team