You okay selling
these guys five AKs?
Natey just hangs out
with these survivalist cats,
bunch of crazy old guys playing...
I don't know,
capture the flag or something.
I wanted to thank you
for peeling a few free so I could...
- let this happen, huh?
- No problem, Piney.
Those Russians make a hell of a gun,
I'll give them that.
Looks like you're about 5,000 light.
I thought we were getting
a family discount.
You are. $10,000.
I know damn well these guns
go for a grand on the street.
When was the last time
you were on the street, junior?
Russ, we had a deal.
Give the man his goddamn money.
Pay him.
Here. Sorry.
Thanks, Piney.
- I'll be seeing you.
- Yeah, Nate.
You take it easy, brother.
You're too...
You got to get me
a little wet, baby.
Shit.
Wait a minute. Where you going?
How is this my fault?
Jesus.
Half-Sack.
What?
Get in here.
Jesus Christ.
- What the hell is this?
- Oh, man.
Who do you think would be flushing
panties down the shitter?
That's weird.
You think?
How'd this morning go?
Those jarheads are dicks,
but it made Piney happy.
- I think it's cool.
- Any tails?
Doubled back three times.
No one followed us.
- The rest of the AKs are here.
- Call the Niners.
I'm sure Leroy will be thrilled that the
Russian firepower appeared a day early.
I'll be right back.
We okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sorry I...
I just...
It was a strange morning.
I'm fine.
Okay.
Do you have the number
for the septic guy?
Piney filled the tanks already?
Yeah,
and someone's been flushing
lace panties.
I don't even know
what to say to that.
Here you go.
Thanks.
You look real nice today, Gemma.
Thank you, Eddie.
- It's good to be...
- What the hell is she doing here?
She told me she was getting out
in Bakersfield.
It's not his fault, okay?
I know I'm not supposed to be here.
Let me go talk to someone.
You talk to somebody in some
other charter, you got that, sweet butt?
- Get her the hell out of here.
- Let's go...
What are you thinking, man?
What was I supposed to do?
Just throw her out of the cab?
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Get me out of here.
Who's that girl?
I don't really... I don't know.
I saw your heart
skip a beat from here.
Who is she?
Just a Tribe hang-around.
Clay hit that tart, didn't he?
I don't really know
who Clay's hitting.
Except for you.
I'm sure he's hitting you
'cause you're his wife and all.
Get out.
I'm looking for Good Shepherd
Junior High School.
My grandson's in a play,
and I can't find it.
It's supposed to be out here
on County 18 somewhere.
You missed it.
- It's about six miles back.
- Over there?
- Truman exit...
- Don't you move!
Don't move.
Hey, open the back.
- Get Frank out of the van.
- Stay still.
Pull right there!
Don't move! Don't move!
- This way. This way, let's go!
- Move, move!
Let's go!
Jesus...
Who'd McKeavy see up north?
Few gun brokers,
some Irish expats,
and fat, black hookers.
Where's he now?
He's greasing the palms
of the Port Authority contacts.
All right, we got a week,
maybe ten days,
then he wants his 200K.
We're working on it.
Clay, he made it very clear.
We got to have the money up front
for the IRA to keep them flush.
Otherwise,
he'll sell to the Russians.
And we lose
the Irish pipeline to our guns.
Laroy's gonna take
the three dozen AKs off our hands.
At a deep discount.
It's either that or spend
a month finding a better buyer.
At least this way,
it puts 50 grand in our pockets now.
Plus the ten I got this morning
and the Chinese money.
Gets us more than halfway there.
Clay.
You better get out here.
Now you're either feds
or limo drivers.
Agent Stahl, ATF.
I'm looking for the owner
of Teller-Morrow Automotive.
That's me.
Come on.
Let's go, Clay.
You gonna bother
mentioning a charge?
No charges yet.
I just need to discuss your relationship
with a Nate Meineke.
Who?
Nate Meineke.
He's one of the men who held up
a prison transport vehicle
this morning.
Killed three people with AK-47s.
We found Mr. Meineke's cell phone
at the scene.
Last call he received
was from your garage.
Preference?
Lady's choice.
Tattoos and chivalry.
Delicious combination.
Ride into this world
All alone
God takes your soul
You're on your own
The crow flies straight
In a perfect line
On the Devil's bed
Until you die
Gotta look this life
In the eye.
Episode 106 - AK-51
I was in the garage waiting for you.
I just called Nate
to confirm the meet.
I never thought anything like this
would happen.
You had no idea
what they were up to, Pop.
I don't get off that easy, though.
I let friendship interfere
with business.
I know better.
Gotta reach out to 'em, Piney.
We need to find these guys
before the feds do.
Nate will not rat on me.
No, but his dipshit kid
sure as hell would.
It's just a matter of time
before the feds connect you
to Nate and come after you, too.
You know, Opie.
I don't give a shit. How's that?
You know, well, I do.
Take him to the cabin.
So you're calling
the shots now, huh?
Till Clay gets out.
The VP patch means this shit
lands on my back.
The backs of children.
He's just pissed at himself.
The old dude saved his ass in Khe Sanh,
but the rest of that crew?
Killed cops and innocents?
We'll find 'em.
You call Trammel?
Trammel called us
looking for Clay.
All right, good.
No way we're getting those guns
to Laroy with the feds there.
I see
you haven't called your lawyer.
My lawyer's $1,200 an hour.
When I got a problem
worth that pay scale,
I'll give him a call.
And you don't think that
aiding and abetting a murder
and a triple homicide is a problem?
I don't know nothing
about that crime
or the guys that did it.
Homegrown terrorists.
***ber-right-wing fanatics.
Not the brightest figs
in the Newton,
but dangerous enough
to clock a watch.
This 'cause somebody from my garage
called one of those assholes,
that doesn't make me
an accessory of murder.
But your association
with an organized crime syndicate
and your rap sheet for gunrunning
flags you as a source
of their illegal AKs.
Sons of Anarchy
is a motorcycle club,
and, just for you information,
I haven't been charged with a crime,
gun-related or otherwise,
in over seven years.
I'm a mechanic
and a motorcycle enthusiast.
You are a criminal
and a gunrunner,
and in my book, you are responsible
for the deaths of three innocent people.
Now, in a couple of hours,
I will have a warrant
to search your garage
and your little clubhouse,
and we'll see how enthusiastic
you are then.
Maybe I should call that lawyer of mine
after all, huh?
I'll set that up...
in a couple hours.
Look at that.
I just saved you 2,400 bucks.
Jesus.
Yeah, don't spank her.
Let's rehearse one.
Can you believe the balls
on that little whore
showing up at the goddamn clubhouse?
- Clay couldn't have known.
- So what?!
The rules got broken.
What happens on a run
stays on a run.
It does not show up and slap me
in the goddamn face.
That does not happen to me!
She's so young.
And dumb.
And before she knows it,
she's gonna be old and wise like us.
How am I supposed to handle this?
I just want to rip
his goddamn heart out.
Estrotol.
Solution 15. It's magic. I'll get my guy
to write you a prescription.
I didn't come here for a diagnosis.
Sure, you did.
You're lucky, baby.
My walls went dry at 45.
I'm only 51.
I'm not ready for this.
Stop!
You know,
me and Saunde came up together.
I known him 15 years.
I'm sorry.
Those were your AKs, weren't they?
I think so.
Goddamn it, Jax.
Feds picked up Clay.
Traced a call from one of the shooters'
cell phones back to TM.
Jesus.
Need you to find out how real it is,
who else they have.
Can't let them find these guys.
Your guns kill a friend of mine
and now you tasking me
to protect the shooters?
It's not about protecting them.
It's about getting to them first.
Gotta get Clay clear of this shit.
I was supposed to help you
get your guns to the ghetto
and run a little interference.
I didn't sign on for burnt bodies...
- Dead sheriffs.
- I know.
This is over.
Hey, Trammel,
it's too late for "over," man.
You know all about us,
and we know all about you.
Look, only way this relationship works
is two of us together...
or one of us dead.
I'll be waiting for your call.
All right, let me call you back.
Any luck with the warrant?
Sacramento says cell phones
aren't enough.
- No warrant.
- Shit!
Maybe I can help. Agent Kohn.
I guess Chicago doesn't have
a dress code, huh?
What brings you here?
I can't discuss the specifics
of my investigation.
Give me a break, Sparky.
This is Stockton's jurisdiction.
Who's your superior, Gainslay?
I can share these.
I followed Sons of Anarchy
to Indian Hills, Nevada last week.
War broke out with a rival MC.
Those are fully automatic handguns.
That truck was in their lot today.
Are these oil drums?
Well, it is illegal to transport
petroleum products
over state lines now, isn't it?
This is Piney Winston,
SOA's founding elder.
Did multiple TODs in 'Nam.
Guess what two guys were
in his platoon
for every re-up.
Nate Meineke and Frank Cison.
The father of that guy
they freed from the prison transport.
Mother's little helpers.
Get me my goddamned warrant.
Nothing's coming up under Meineke
other than discount mufflers.
What's going on?
Thought I told you
to go underground.
Nate, reached out.
They're in some survivalist bunker
outside of Woodbridge Forest.
Great.
- You gotta set up a meet.
- And then what happens?
They killed three people
in cold blood,
and there's a straight line
back to this club.
What the hell you think happens,
Piney?
I just talked to Trammel.
The feds got a warrant
to rip this place up.
Shit!
Cabin now.
Who the hell do you
think you're talking to?
- Relax, relax, relax!
- All right, get out of here.
You'll never be able
to get these guns out of here.
Yeah, well, the feds open up them
oil barrels, we all got a new charter:
Stockton State Prison.
Yeah, go meet with Laroy.
Pick up our money.
Tell him he'll have his guns
before the end of the day.
You gonna Houdini
this stuff out of here, brother?
I'll figure it out.
Mrs. Teller, Estrotol
doesn't make Solution 15 anymore.
It's called "Menopause Plus" now.
Same amount of estrogen,
same formula, do the same thing for ya.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Skinny-ass bitch.
My God, my nose!
My God!
Who are you?
Why'd you do that to me?!
The older I get,
the more I realized that age
doesn't bring wisdom.
It only brings ***wearity***
I'm not anyhow smarter
than I was 30 years ago,
I've just grown too tired
to joggle the lies
and hide the fears.
Self-awareness
doesn't reveal my indiscretions.
Exhaustioned us.
What are you doing in here?
I was...
curious.
This incubation chamber is for medical
personnel and family only.
It still hurts me.
Be at Sam Crow in 45 minutes
if you want to see his future.
And yours, too, maybe.
- Well, Niners do not want the Aks.
- What?
Nobody's gonna touch them,
not after what went down this morning.
Man.
We'll worry about a buyer later.
Right now,
it's all about the shit.
What the hell is she doing here?
She's got nothing to do with this.
Assaulted some girl,
hit her in the face with a skateboard.
What?!
- What's he doing here?
- The feds are grilling him.
- What the hell did you do?!
- Same thing you did:
- nailed some little tart from Nevada!
- Like I don't have enough shit
oozing out of my ears!
You got to go and do this!
Should've thought of that before
your dick went on a cheerleader hunt!
- I didn't tell her to come here!
- But she's here!
- Well, that's not my fault!
- And it's not my pussy!
And that's why I'm single.
You hungry?
I'll take a smoke.
What?
When you were our paperboy,
you had that same goofy haircut.
That was a long time ago.
Last time I was in here,
I was 18 years old.
What'd they get you for?
Disorderly conduct.
I was piss-drunk.
Think there might have been an,
an assault charge involved, too.
Yeah, well, go figure?
What do the feds want with Clay?
What do you think they want him for?
Thanks for the smoke.
We're heading out.
Okay.
Get on the ground!
Hands where I can see them!
Come on. Let's go!
Face on the pavement.
Spread your legs.
Check the bar license also.
Gullies are clean.
Clear for storage unit.
You smell nice.
Nate called.
Wants to make a deal
on the rest of those Aks.
Russell knows nobody will touch them.
Ten grand for all 36.
Shit. Those guns are worth
ten times that.
All right, set it up.
Me and Ope will make the run.
Now, you can't go without me.
They won't trust you.
You okay tying up this loose end?
You know,
you don't have to ask me that.
All right.
This is the one.
Step back, boys.
Jesus!
Get the guns!
Found six of these in his garage.
I'm guessing this is how they're getting
their guns into the country.
Dungloe, Ireland?
True IRA territory.
Outlaw Irish.
This could be huge, Deputy.
If the Sons of Anarchy are running guns
through a known terrorist organization,
well, then that puts
your little motorcycle club on
at least a half a dozen
federal watch lists.
My nipples are unbelievably
hard right now.
I'm gonna pull
in Homeland Security, Treasury.
We might just shut
this Harley Mafia down for good.
I'll be in touch.
Did you brief Agent Kohn on this?
You know, I called Chicago,
and, Kohn's supervisor seems to think
he's on vacation in Oregon.
Let me know if he stirs anything up
with Sam Crow,
and keep this inside your khakis.
Clay Morrow's free to go.
Hale says
you don't want bail posted.
That's right.
Just need a little me time.
Well,
I'll stay at the clubhouse.
I don't want you in here.
I don't give a shit what you want.
Right.
I can't take back what happened.
Should never have gone down
like this.
I'm sorry.
Won't happen again.
I promise.
What are you doing?
You're staying?
So am I.
I'm going through menopause, Clay.
You know what that means?
Means things are changing.
Yeah.
You know what doesn't change?
The love I got for you.
Go home.
Just pick me up in the morning.
I'm really sorry, Kip.
I'm really sorry
if I got people in trouble.
Can't let a club president
have a time with you, and then
you show up a week later, you know,
especially with his old lady
on the lot.
I know,
but I'm not here for Clay.
You have any thoughts about
pressing charges against Gemma?
Never.
I'm not going to.
Anybody asks, you don't know anything
about what went down in Indian Hills.
Nothing.
I know the way it works.
Good.
Why the hell did you get
in that cargo truck?
You know why.
No, no,
Jesus, that...
that can't work, you understand.
Look, look.
Okay, look, that can't work, okay,
not after what went down.
Just give me one more dance.
I can take it from there.
I don't think that's a good idea.
- No?
- No, 'cause you know...
Welcome home.
Welcome back, bro.
The dough is here.
Feds trashed the clubhouse,
but the search turned up nothing.
- We got the guns out.
- No, wait a minute.
Jackie Boy got all the guns out.
Good.
ATF's got shit.
It's all smoke.
Yeah, they're onto the oil barrels.
Yeah, well,
we'll just have to find a smarter
way to get the guns in is all.
By the time the warehouse
is rebuilt,
we'll be a distant memory
for the AT&F.
Mom home?
She wouldn't let me post bail.
Shit.
She is pissed.
Yeah, that she is.
Well, we're handling
Meineke and his crew.
Piney set up a meet for tomorrow.
- We're gonna clean this up.
- Yeah, well, I'm tired
and my head hurts,
and you'll handle it.
I'm just going to crash here
tonight.
We'll talk in the daylight.
In the daylight.
We're not idiots.
We weren't followed.
That smells like shit.
Long story.
They're all here.
Three dozen.
Cut open the bags and you can
check for yourself if you like.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Sorry about how this went down.
I wanted to tell you,
but Russ thought it best not to.
That Russ,
he always was a big thinker.
He's a good kid, just a little nervous.
Believes in the cause.
And this is your retirement plan?
Hiding out in some bunker?
You got anybody up there with you?
Family,
women, kids?
No. Frank and Russ' boys.
We're gonna lie low
till the heat dies down.
We got some big boy
waiting for us in Mexico.
Mexico.
Gonna be running
this revolution from Acapulco?
Yeah.
You,
take care of yourself, friend.
Well, there...
ain't no innocents with 'em.
All this shit landed on your back.
Handled it pretty damn good, kid.
Thanks, old man.
I heard Clay
got clear of everything.
Yeah.
Thanks for the heads-up.
There's a little gratitude
bump in the envelope.
Okay.
The guys that killed your friend--
that's been taken care of.
Shit like that won't happen again.
We together here?
Yeah.
One big happy family.
- Hey, you okay?
- Yeah. Why?
I was going past the clubhouse
yesterday. I saw all these cops.
That was a bunch of bullshit.
We got this ATF agent harassing us.
Following me. Showed up here.
The guy's nuts. He's looking for
dirt that doesn't exist.
I'm, I'm just finishing up my rounds.
Do you mind giving me a ride home?
Sure.
What's going on?
Shitty day.
My nerves are kind of shot.
Well, I'll be with the kid.
Thanks.
- You been waiting long?
- All my life, baby.
Jesus.
This stupid bitch.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no, I got it.
No skateboards.
Promise.
I just want to say I'm sorry
if I caused any problems.
Why the hell are you here?
You and him.
I want that.
- The prospect?
- Yeah.
He's the right one.
What if that doesn't hook up?
The others want a taste?
Then I'm gone.
I'm not here for anyone else.
You so much as flash
a pretty grin at him,
I will jam my fist
so far up your bony ass,
your cup size will double.
Is that how your rack
got to be that size?
- Not a good time to be clever.
- Yes, ma'am.
I promise: I'm clear of your man.
Not even a smile.
You'll heal okay.
Yeah?
And you?
I'll be fine.
Work everything out?
Relax.
A threesome ain't gonna happen.
- Did I say anything about a threesome?
- You are so transparent.
Take me home.
Yes, ma'am.
You allright?
Santiag Team: michvanilly, Tagne.