MENTALIST
/'men-t3-list/ noun
Someone who uses mental
Acuity, hypnosis and/or suggestion.
A master manipulator of
Thoughts and behavior.
Go!Go!
Get down on the floor!
Get down on the floor now!
One Year Later
Thank you for coming.
You said you had
information about red john.
Yes, I do.
He killed your wife and daughter?
I've heard a lot about you.
They say you can tell
when people are lying.
Do you have information
about red john?
I have dynamite
information about red john.
Enough to catch him.
How do you come by this information?
Red john is a friend
of a friend of mine.
Is that friend of
yours in prison, too?
I have friends from
all walks of life.
Tell me.
I am currently doing 25 years to
life for a crime I didn't commit.
My last appeal just failed.
You get me out of here, and
I will give you red john.
You raped and murdered your
family housekeeper's daughter.
If you do know a lot about me, you
know that I'm not a real magician.
I didn't do it.
I read the case file...
The physical evidence, the
testimonies of all the witnesses,
Including your own
family, says you did.
I didn't kill her.
What happened?
I don't know.
We were partying.
I did some blow, some meth.
We had sex. I fell asleep.
Then it's morning. Undine's dead.
The cops are busting in...
The door was locked from the inside.
- There were bars on the windows.
- Yes.
How is it physically
possible that anyone
else could've committed the murder?
I don't know, but I didn't.
Ergo, someone else did.
Someone you can find.
You see me.
Am I lying?
You seem to be telling the truth,
But you're a very clever, unprincipled
narcissist In a desperate corner.
Even if you are innocent, it doesn't
mean You have information on red john.
Yeah, it's a tough call.
I'm gonna have to say no.
Your wife... Red john
painted her toenails. Yes.
Painted them with her own blood...
The police didn't make
that public, did they?
She's the only instance he did that?
A touch of elegance
for you alone.
How do you know that?
I told you, Red john is a
friend of a friend of mine.
What is this friend's name?
His name is "get me out
of here and i'll tell you."
That and much more.
I'll sing like a bird.
Okay.
No. I said no,
and I mean no.
It's not that I don't want to
help you. I want to help you.
It's just... It's not
physically possible.
Jared renfrew was tried and
convicted. It's a closed case.
I have no authority To
reopen it witho cause.
- There is cause.
- For you, there's cause.
Not for the state of california.
We can't touch it.
- But we could touch it if...
- Closed case. Nothing to be done.
The justice department
doesn't go about...
Undoing its own work.
I understand.
No problem.
If we can't touch
it, we can't touch it.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
The law's the law.
My desire for revenge
doesn't outweigh the rules.
I have to accept that.
- I'm glad you understand.
- Thanks for your time.
He's lying through
his teeth, isn't he?
Yes.
Jane.
I know better
than to try and stop you
From doing what you
think you have to do.
No, i-I'm fine about it.
I can see minelli's point.
I can't be chasing every
nutbag with a good story, can i?
Yeah. Sure, you're fine with it.
Just do me the favor
of listening to me for
a minute,
So I can say "i told you so" later.
Sure.
Jared renfrew was found
hugging the corpse
of undine kopecki in a room
locked from the inside,
Holding a bloody butcher
knife in his hand.
His semen was inside of her.
He had been stalking her for weeks.
He's got a history of
violence going back 15 years.
What's your point?
He's guilty. You're being conned.
Possible, but I don't think so.
I gotta find out one
way or the other.
Even if he's telling
the truth about the murder,
he could still be
lying about red john.
Also possible.
But I gotta take the
chance. What else can I do?
Minelli wants me to
keep a watch on you.
- What are you gonna do?
- I'm not gonna follow you around.
Let's compromise.
When you get into trouble,
call me first.
- So I can try and minimize the damage.
- Deal.
And don't use your cbi card.
If the bureau finds out you used it
without authorization, you're done.
I hear you.
Hello?
My name's patrick jane.
I'd like to speak to gardner
renfrew about his brother jared.
One moment, please.
Mr. Renfrew says,"no, thank you."
Tell mr. Renfrew I can prove
his brother is innocent,
And I know who really
committed the murder.
Thank you very much.
Is that your father?
Yes.
What's this all about, mr. Jane?
Who are you, and what
do you mean by this?
Do you think
your brother is innocent?
You said you could
prove he's innocent.
You said you know who really did it.
No. Just... That was just
to get inside the house.
I have no idea
who might have done it.
It might've been jared.
I hope not.
He seems to be telling the
truth. What do you think?
I think you had better
leave right now, mr. Jane.
I don't have the... The time
or the patience for tomfoolery.
So you think he's guilty?
I'm wasting my time.
We're done talking.
Suppose I could prove he was
innocent. Wouldn't you want that?
Wouldn't you want that
blot on your name expunged?
Of course he would.
Nothing would make me
happier, but my brother's guilty.
He violated that poor girl. He violated
this house. He violated this family.
That's all I needed to know.
Thank you for your time.
Your, mother lives here in
the guesthouse, doesn't she?
You leave my mother alone.
Well, that's not
your call to make, is it?
Breck, call the police.
Be sure and tell 'em I'm unarmed.
Go inside, mother! Go inside!
My name's patrick jane. I want to
speak to you about your son jared.
I'll deal with him, mother. The police
are on their way. Just go inside.
Don't order me about, and
don't be so hysterical.
What's your interest in jared?
I'm a friend of his, trying
to prove his innocence.
- Come and sit down.
- Thank you.
Mother, you're being childish.
Go away, gardner.
- Mother!
- Go away!
Tell me why you wish to
prove my son's innocence.
I can promise you I'm not
up to anything sinister, ma'am.
My motives are pure.
Tell me about jared.
He was a troubled child,
charming and bright, but...
a bully and a liar.
Something of a sadist.
Qualities you rather
liked in him, I expect.
Yes, I did.
I found him rather amusing...
At first.
One doesn't want a wimp for a son.
But there must be
a sense of proportion
and moderation.
As he got older, he got worse.
Got in with bad people.
It was one scandal after another.
In and out of prison.
A common criminal.
But he turned himself
around, didn't he?
He gave up the drink and the
drugs and the gallivanting,
Made peace with his brother
and came home to help run
the family businesses.
- The prodigal son.
- Yes.
George, his father, was overjoyed.
I was skeptical.
Pleased, of course, but skeptical.
As my mother always
said,"you are what you are."
- I guess she's right.
- Yes.
Poor george dropped dead
a week after the murder.
Broke his heart, people said.
George didn't really have
a heart, in that sense.
He died of embarrassment.
A renfrew in the pokey
for murder. Quelle horreur.
Can you show me where it happened?
Who else was in the house?
I had a small dinner party,
Probably ten people all told.
After they left, it
was just family...
Gardner and breck, george
and i and jared, of course.
Not mariska the housekeeper?
No, she lived out.
Undine was only here to help
the cook with the dinner party.
She was a lovely girl.
Full of life and promise.
Her mother and mariska had
been with us 20 years...
Part of the family.
Jared told me that he and
undine were having an affair,
That he loved her and
he'd never hurt her.
She told her mother
that he was stalking her,
that she was scared of him.
She didn't go to the police
out of respect for the family.
I'd like to speak to her mother.
She left our employ, I'm afraid.
It was too difficult,
for both of us.
Where is she now?
I have an address somewhere.
Can you get it for me now?
- As you wish.
- Thank you.
- Sir, would you come with us?
- Why?
- You're trespassing here.
- No, I'm not.
Okay, sir, this man here
says he's the homeowner
And says you're trespassing, so
let's go, partner.
Officer, it's the other way
around. I'm the homeowner.
- That man is the intruder.
- Well, that's a lie! He... he's lying!
Listen to the madness in his voice.
Will you please take him
somewhere he can get some help?
Here you are. I don't know that
she'll still be there, but...
Thank you so much.
For heaven's sake, gardner.
Policemen?
How ridiculous. Send them away.
Ma'am, this man here is...
Yes, yes,
it's quite all right, officer.
You can go.
Thanks.
Well, good-bye, mrs. Renfrew.
I expect we'll speak again soon.
Good day to you.
Gardner renfrew is a
player in this town.
You can't go to his house
and screw around with him.
Why not? It's a free country.
I didn't use my I. D.
I didn't even mention the cbi.
- You gave your real name.
- It's my name.
Well, you should've
lied as you so often do,
Because now I have to give
you an official reprimand
And order you in the strongest possible
terms to leave the renfrew family alone
- And... and drop the matter.
- Sorry, can't do that.
You have to. This is straight
from the A. G.'s office.
Jared renfrew didn't
kill undine kopecki.
- Do you have evidence of that?
- Not yet.
I have pieces... That
I'm piecing together.
He's innocent.
Wake up, dorothy. You're
not in kansas anymore.
There are innocent men
in jail. It happens.
Is he one of them? I
don't know. I doubt it.
In any case,
we can't reopen his case.
If I'm dorothy, then who are you?
It doesn't matter who I am.
We will find other ways of
making renfrew talk to you.
There is a lot that can be done
to make a prisoner's life easier,
- If he cooperates.
- It's not gonna work.
- He's innocent.
- Okay, here it is.
If you pursue this any further,
I'm gonna have to throw
you out of the cbi.
We can't take the liability.
I very much do not
want to have to do that.
I know you don't.
So...
Well, i'll spare
you the trouble. I quit.
- Don't do that.
- Oh, it's okay. It's best this way.
You are the good witch
glinda, obviously.
Thank you.
I learned a lot.
CBI HQ Sacramento, CA
Don't bother, I know. I feel the
same way. Nothing to be done.
So now when he really needs our
help, We're letting him down.
I wanna help him just
as much as you do.
Our orders state that we
must stay away from this case.
I don't care what our
orders say. It's not right.
We closed cases before he came.
We'll close cases after he's gone.
Just not so many.
The cases are not the point. It's
not that we need him. He needs us.
He needs us on a fool's
errand. Renfrew's a con man.
He doesn't know
anything about red john.
Suppose we found a connection
between renfrew and red john.
It would...
Wait.
What's in the file? Let me guess...
A connection between
renfrew and red john?
Seven years ago, Renfrew was serving
time on a narcotics conviction.
He shared a cell in lompoc with
a man by the name of orval tanner.
Tanner claimed in his
1998 trial for murder.
That he had only been an accomplice,
That the real killer was a
man by the name of red john.
Nobody believed him.
'98. That's the beginning
of red john's career.
Where's tanner now?
He died of heart disease
in a prison hospital.
- Of course, our luck.
- It's a connection.
Slim. Likely, nobody
believed him for a reason.
But it's a connection.
Okay.
Check out tanner's background, find
the autopsy reports,
See if there's any
credibility to his story.
I mean, obviously, we can't do that,
But that's what
I would tell you to do.
If we weren't ordered to
stay away from this case.
Okay, then let me speak To the
assistant to the deputy records officer.
Why do people say "eureka"
when they do something good?
It's, greek for "bingo."
Well, so... Eureka.
I found the autopsy reports, And
they back up orval tanner's story.
The body of the alleged
victim... Cut up, red john style.
Which means renfrew's
telling some kind of truth
- about his red john connection.
- Yep.
Van pelt.
What's that you're working on?
- Sir, I asked her to...
- I'm talking to van pelt.
Sir...
I'm doing research
for jane. No excuses, sir.
You, too, I suppose.
Hey, boss.
I gave this unit a direct,
written order.
And they have flagrantly
disobeyed that order.
Did they do that with
your knowledge?
I ordered them to do it.
I told them you countermanded
your earlier order.
They had no knowledge whatsoever.
That they were doing
anything irregular.
Nice try, mother teresa. They
already gave themselves up.
We never said a word...
I stand by my story.
They didn't know
they were out of line.
Sir, the opposite is true. We forced
agent lisbon to let us do this.
Very touching.
My ex-wife would love
this scene in a movie.
I'm giving you all formal notice.
Any further infractions will
result in immediate suspension.
Sir...
You might as well suspend me now,
because there will be
further infractions.
Jane needs our help, and
he's gonna get it.
I'm not gonna lay off
because some fat cat's
putting on the pressure.
- Me, too.
- And me.
Moving, eloquent, two thumbs up.
You shall have your
wish. You're all suspended,
Starting right now, For
gross insubordination.
I'm sorry.
Lisbon.
Still here?
That was more of a rhetorical
stand we were taking back there.
You take it back then.
Well, no, but I wanted to talk to...
This... The...
The suspension paperwork right here.
Look...
I have to go and visit my sister
in hawaii for a week. She's sick.
Meanwhile,
this paperwork is gonna sit on my desk.
For a week, is that clear?
- One week.
- Yes, sir.
- Yes...
- Thank you.
Be very grateful.
Do not contact me.
I do not want to know anything.
And please...
Do not dig the hole
that you are standing
in any deeper than you
have already dug it.
No, sir.
That hole is the grave of
your very promising career.
You should put
a flashlight underneath
your chin just to
complete the effect.
I'm not kidding.
I know.
Hey, lisbon.
Oh, yeah, I'm fine. Just...
Out investigating stuff.
Sure.
Yeah.
Pepperoni or plain?
Okay.
Hey, lisbon...
Thank you.
Renfrew couldn't dispute
the physical evidence.
The core of his defense was
that he loved undine deeply
and he would never hurt her.
Undine's mother
testified that was a lie.
I went to go speak with her,
but she moved,
left no forwarding address.
- Mariska kopecki, right?
- Yeah.
How does the brother look?
He had motive. There's a moral
turpitude clause in the family trust.
Once convicted, all jared's shares In
the family business went to gardner.
But he would've also got
the shares if jared had died.
So why not just kill
jared? Why kill undine?
Exactly.
Why kill undine?
He wanted to see jared suffer maybe
Or had a thing for undine himself.
Eureka.
I input mariska kopecki into
the secure search engine.
I get an i. M. link
to a health care database that documents
mariska kopecki's notification
That she's changing her
name to vanna clooney.
I input the new name and get a hit.
Four months ago, someone named v. K.
Clooney Bought a condo in marin.
Nice work.
Yeah, weird thing, though...
The original i. M.
Came from a civilian.
A dr. Joe in new hampshire.
He couldn't have been logged
on to the d. O. j. Secure network.
So how did he know
what i was asking about?
And how did he have access
to the health care database?
Nobody's allowed to do that.
When you say "dr. Joe in new
hampshire," Do you mean d-r-j-o-e-n-h...
Yeah.
Oh, my god.
Ask,"who are you?"
Is Jane there?
Yes.
This is Jane.
"Keep up the good work."
Why?
I.M. source locator
He's gone.
What the hell was that about?
He somehow tapped into
the d. O. j. Secure network.
He's been spying on us.
Can we find the source of the i. M.?
There's a self-destruct
code built into the uplink.
It dead-ends at
the secondary server.
There's no way to trace it back.
He wants us to succeed.
He wants renfrew out of jail.
Out where he can get
at him... to silence him.
Yes. Which means renfrew
is telling the truth.
Which means he has
the goods on red john.
Slow down.
We don't have anything yet.
Yes, we still have to get
renfrew out of jail first.
Oh, that's all.
And we will, and then red
john will go after him.
He has to break cover. He has to.
And we will waiting for him.
Damn.
How are you gonna get us in
there without your magic badge?
- You do the talking.
- No, you try.
Don't be childish. I'm not...
I thought it was harry.
Who are you?
- Vanna clooney?
- Yes.
- I'm teresa, and this is patrick.
Can... can we come in for a moment?
What do you want?
- It's to do with harry.
- What about him?
Well, it's best not to
speak out here in public.
Okay, i lied just now.
We're here to talk about
your daughter undine.
- Get out.
- Sit down.
Who are you?
Listen to me,
or your guilt and pain
and shame won't ever go away.
It won't go away until
you tell the truth.
What truth? What, are you crazy?
You don't know me. You
don't know what i feel.
I do know you.
When you first came to this
country as a young woman,
you dreamed of such great things,
What a life you'd have.
And what did fate bring you?
25 years of drudgery, a
servant's life.
You hated every day of it.
Who wants to be a servant? Nobody.
You did it for her, for undine.
So that she would
have a better life.
- Yes.
- And then she was gone,
taken from you.
In a flash,
your whole life...
All those days of drudgery
and humiliation... Wasted.
What a joke?
Yes.
A joke.
What do you want from me?
I want to know who killed her.
What's it matter who
killed her? She's gone.
Well, you didn't say jared. That
would be the obvious answer.
Okay. Jared killed her.
I don't care.
It's true.
There's nothing you can do
that will bring her back.
So if you get paid to lie about what
happened, then, where's the harm?
What paid?
Nobody paid me anything.
Don't lie to me. Tell me the truth.
You took your 20 pieces of silver
and bought the life you always wanted,
didn't you?
- No.
- It's what you always wanted.
- It means nothing.
- Jane.
Look at me, mariska. Look at
me, And tell me i'm wrong.
You think you know
everything! You know nothing!
I know that jared and undine
were lovers, weren't they?
And you were paid to
say that they weren't.
Say it out loud.
Yes.
They were lovers.
Who paid you to say
that they weren't?
I don't know.
A what you call a...
A private investigator.
He came to me, and he
offered me a lot of money.
A lot of money! But i said no.
He offered more.
- I took it.
- What was his name?
Samsa.
Austin samsa.
Okay, cho,
thank you.
- Austin Samsa's dead.
- What?
- Hit by a bus.
- Damn.
We could get a court
order for his records.
Remember, you're on suspension.
If we don't get this closed up
before minelli gets back, We're done.
- Plan "B" then.
- What's plan "B"?
Well, you're not gonna like it.
We need to speak with
your husband, ma'am.
Who's the agent in charge here?
I'm agent lisbon.
This is agent rigsby.
And i believe you've met
my colleague patrick jane.
Hello.
I expect you're wondering
why i gathered you all here?
- Breck, go call the police.
- Mr. Renfrew, wait.
Unless you want your family ruined
In a deluge of sordid scandal,
- You might want to listen to me.
- What are you talking about?
Someone,
i don't know who,
paid mariska kopecki a lot of money
to lie about jared and undine.
They were lovers, as
your brother said.
So what?
The fact is,
they were found in a locked room.
It's not physically possible For
someone to have gotten into the room
to commit the murder.
Yes,
there's the rub.
The key was in the door.
Watch closely.
Rigsby.
Would you please go
inside and lock the door?
Suppose jared and undine
are inside sleeping.
It's all very clever, but
how do you get out again?
Can i borrow your lighter, please?
Thank you.
And that is how jared was framed.
- Cool?
- It doesn't mean jared's innocent.
And it certainly doesn't
mean someone else is guilty.
- It's a party trick.
- A party trick a jury will love.
Put that together with
mariska's testimony,
and i think we have a pretty good
chance of winning a new trial.
Then the truth will come
out somehow.
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless we can make some
kind of financial deal here
That would make it worth
our while Dropping all this.
You want money?
You're blackmailing us.
- We call it leverage.
- But you're state agents.
Ex-state agents. Thanks
to your son here,
Jane was tossed out, and
we're going with him.
We need to look after ourselves now.
We won't be unreasonable.
You people are a disgrace.
- Get out.
- We're going.
We'll give you until 4:00
to call us with an offer.
After that, we're gonna
make some calls of our own.
I'll tell you who i'm
calling. I'm calling the fbi!
Am i wrong, Or did that go
down not quite as you'd hoped?
I've had better responses, but
i think we made a sale.
- You never can tell.
- We're doomed.
Patience.
If you say "patience"
one more time...
Hello?
I'll be right there.
Who was it?
I confess,
I thought it'd
be gardner who called me.
Gardner?
He hasn't the gumption.
I will not see our family name
dragged through the mud again.
How much do you want to keep quiet?
How much did you give mariska?
I don't say i paid her anything.
You needn't be evasive.
Only a guilty person would respond
this way to such naked extortion.
I know you're guilty.
I'm just not sure why.
Your suspicions are
neither here nor there.
I asked you your price.
Your late husband
was a handsome man.
Yes, he was. What's
that got to do with it?
Domineering, though. Had
to have things his way.
He died how long after the murder?
A week.
Aortic aneurysm.
And mariska... She
left your employ when?
At the same time.
After he died, though.
Yes.
May i?
Thank you.
So you got rid of her as soon
as you could after he died,
Because undine
was your husband's child,
Wasn't she?
Yes.
And you never confronted
him or mariska?
No.
I decided i liked my life as it was.
I didn't want a drama, and
i didn't want to be lied to.
They never knew i suspected.
18 years of secret anger.
How did you stand it?
Nobody's life is perfect.
And then when you found out
about undine and jared's affair,
you must've been enraged.
It's practically incest.
It is.
It is incest.
When i found out, I...
I told jared that he was
not to continue the affair.
He refused...
Said he was in love with her.
He refused to stop seeing her.
Didn't you tell him
why you objected?
Certainly not.
I couldn't tell him.
It was too sordid,
too humiliating.
Instead, you killed undine,
paid off her mother
and sent your son to jail for life.
No.
I wouldn't do that.
Undine's blood.
It's proof... I did it.
I took it so i could confess
And get jared freed when i chose.
- Just as soon as he learned his lesson.
- What lesson?
Everything in moderation.
And...
- Listen to your mother.
- Can't argue with that.
Two Week Later
- good?
- Yep.
Okay.
We're ready to go get renfrew.
- Is the safe house all set up?
- Yeah.
Good.
I guess i'll see
you over there later.
Jane, please be careful.
Remember, this is playing out
just like red john wants it to.
This is playing out
just like it has to.
He has no choice but to
try and silence renfrew.
He has to show himself.
We're getting close. I can feel it.
You can feel it.
- Like a psychic thing?
- No.
I am quietly confident
that we will get a bite.
You think you're playing him, and
he thinks he's playing you.
One of you is wrong.
Thank you.
I kept my side of the
bargain. Now it's your turn.
- Tell what you know.
- Absolutely.
All will be revealed.
But here?
Give me a chance to catch
a breath of fresh air,
And then we will sit and
talk as long as you like.
And i got a lot to tell.
And i owe you...
Big-time.
I owe you my life.
In the meantime,
I would kill for
a cheeseburger and fries.
Drive-through.
Put this on.
Can't you say "please"?
I'm a free man now.
Put this on... Please.
Sure.
MEAT IS MURDER
FUR IS EVIL
What is this?
Oh Jesus, come on!
Relax
Damn it!
He vanished five hours ago, and
we've heard nothing from him since.
The town was on
pretty good lockdown,
So we're guessing he had friends
get him out of the area fast.
Planted in advance, probably.
Would you stop that?
It's not your fault.
Well, whose fault is it then?
It's mine. I have to accept that.
Actually,
it's... it's my fault.
Okay, everyone? My fault.
What's done is done. Focus on now.
We need to get to renfrew
before red john does.
Where is he now? Who are his
friends? What are his options?
- Hello?
- mr. Jane.
I just wanted to call and
apologize for letting you down.
Hello, jared.
It was dishonorable, i know, but...
Crossing red john just...
Seems too dangerous.
You've already crossed him.
You need our protection.
I haven't given you a thing.
- How is he to know that?
- Oh, he'll know.
He'll know.
Like i said, i have friends, and
they'll put in a good word for me.
Friends? What friends?
Who?
Wouldn't you like to know?
Jared, listen to me. You can't trust
them. They're not your friends.
Vaya con dios, amigo.
Jared.
Damn fool. Red john probably
already has his location.
- Did you trace the line?
- Yes, i'm tracking the call now.
He's in tijuana, mexico,
in a motel room with a hooker.
Because?
He wouldn't call if he didn't
think he was out of our reach.
I could hear latin music
and sirens and horns
and a whole neighborhood
in the background,
Which suggests thin
walls and a city.
- Hence, tijuana motel room.
- And the hooker?
He needs to use somebody's phone,
and he has been in prison for a year.
Hence, the hooker.
The phone belongs to
juana porfiria braga...
Calle rojas 65, tijuana, mexico.
Five arrests on
prostitution charges.
Let me get a location on the call.
I'll go reach out to the
federal police in tijuana.
- You boys come with me.
- Yes, sir.
Go ahead. Say it.
- Say what?
- You told me. You warned me.
You get the privilege of
saying,"i told you so."
That's all right. Not now.
This isn't over yet.
We're gonna find renfrew, And
he's gonna tell us what he knows.
Got it.
Motel carona del norte.
He is...
Well, you can say it now.
Well, i don't really
feel like saying it.
- Let me take a rain check on that.
- Sure.
What do you think it means?
It means red john is far more
powerful than i ever thought.
He's been way ahead
of me this whole time.
I mean the writing on the wall.
I have no idea.
It's a good clue, though, isn't it?
Jared was trying to tell
us something important.
Maybe.
Next time,
we'll get him.
Next time.
Hello?