Jason Sands' .....
Mind running it for us,inspector?
Not sure why you all were called in.
We could handle it.
Place belongs to jason
sands,big-ass political contributor.
Been missing since last night.
That's why we're here.
Attorney general likes to stay
on top of these kinds of things.
Mr. Sands' wife jennifer arrived home
last night with their daughter about 9:00.
She found her husband gone and this...
Thanks,guys.
There's been no ransom demand yet,but
i expect we'll get something soon.
If you want our tech guys to
set taps,i gotta let 'em know.
That's okay. We can handle it.
Do you know where his family is?
Uh,with friends.
Mrs. Sands thought it would be best
for the little girl,and we agreed.
Any sign of forced entry?
No,it must have been a front door job,someone
posing as a courier or what have you.
He's still here.
Not unless he's
invisible,he's not,agent jane.
He's not an agent. He's a consultant.
No badge. No gun.
They don't even give me dental.
Oh,yeah. You're the one they were
telling me about--the psychic.
Sorry,gandalf. In our own bumbling
way,we did look around pretty good.
He's not here.
He's here,and there's no
such thing as psychics.
He was tortured in this chair...
To give them a pass code...
Pass code to what?
Could you humor me,inspector?
Could you try and pick
up that sheet of paper?
- All right.
- Thanks.
That's--that's
it.
Well,the bookcase must have moved.
After these papers were
spread all over the floor?
It's a door. To a safe?
- Or a safe room.
- Yes.
The intruder must have been distracted by
something,left sands alone for a moment,
Sands punches in the code,and
before they can stop him,
Goes into the safe room and
shuts the door behind him.
Which will open if you
press the buttons a lot?
I'm entering the top
ten pass code choices.
But if it is a safe room,wouldn't it have a
silent alarm connected to a security company?
Not if you're the
paranoid,secretive type.
You make a safe room
only you know about.
I guess we need a locksmith.
Hang on a minute.
Farewell and adieu to
you,fair spanish maidens
farewell and adieu
to you,Ladies of spain
for we've received orders
for to sail back to boston
And so never more shall we see you...
Again.
The Mentalist
Par J. J. Team
- = Syncro et Transcript = -
YDY.com
Season 01 Episode 04
Ladies in Red
I look around.I don't see anyone here who could
torture a man to death with pliers and a lit cigar.
Picture them naked rr
and ravenously hungry.
You know,strictly speaking,he
wasn't tortured to death.
He bled to death on his own
in his little hidey-hole there.
Kind of has himself to blame then,huh?
Mm,kind of.
How does the widow check out?
The night of the murder,she and her daughter
were at a concert-- "peter & the wolf."
- She have stubs?
- Yep.
Who's the suit hovering around her?
That's michael claymore
bennett iii,sands' lawyer.
What about him?
The widow's scared of him or...
Or?
Or,uh,he's reassuring her of
something else that she's scared of.
- Which is it?
- I don't know. Could be both.
Well,we can't question 'em here.
Let's go get started on
sands' computer files.
- You guys stay here till this thing's over.
- Yes,boss.
You never know. Somebody might confess.
Van pelt,you're killing me.
- Can i ask you a personal question?
- Nope.
Have you told her how you feel?
She's a co-worker. It's against
the rules. That's how i feel.
That's not how you feel.
I sent out the vibes. I got nothing
back,okay? So i'm leaving them alone.
Vibes. Really? Vibes?
That's where he stares at the back of her
neck for several hours. Women love that.
Oh,shut up,cho.
You gotta go get her,man.
You gotta seduce her.
Yeah,well,seduction's
not my strong point.
Man,seduction's easy once you know the
basic principles. There's nothing to it.
Oh,really? Well,i don't see a
crowd of women following you around.
Why would i want a crowd of
women following me around?
Okay. I'll bite.
What's the basic principle?
- Cost you a dollar.
- For what?
So you pay attention.
- Love and affection.
- What?
- Give me my dollar back.
When you're seducing someone,what
are you offering them?
Love and affection.
Who doesn't want love and
affection? It's that simple.
Seriously,give me my dollar back.
Let me demonstrate.
I will bet you 100 more of these
dollars that i can seduce any woman here.
Okay. The widow.
Wait a minute. What
are you-- J-j-jane!
Good job.
Hello,sweetheart.
Mrs. Sands,my name is patrick jane,cbi.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Up close,you're really very beautiful.
That's...Totally
inappropriate and--
listen to me,jennifer.
I don't know what kind of
hold this man has over you...
- Excuse me.
- Back up now.
And i'm not exactly sure what kind of trouble
you're in,but i'm confident that i can help you.
- Call me,and i'll come.
- Excuse me,sir. You have to leave.
No problem. Sorry. Sorry
about that. Come on. Come on.
I'm so sorry.
Looks like you owe me 100 bucks.
Early days,rigsby. Early days.
CBI HQ Sacramento
I'm disappointed. I-i'm--i'm very
disappointed,and i'm embarrassed.
How could you do this me?
I told the mayor of san francisco that
i was putting my best people on this.
Holy mother!
Who takes off the freakin'
labels? I mean,what is that?
Is this--is this
real or is that decaf?
I mean,how am i supposed
to know which is which?
Mix 'em both half and half
and drink twice as much.
What kind of idiot drinks
decaf anyway? What is the point?
And what were you thinking,leaving
this man alone at an event like that?
No excuses.
I mistakenly treated him
as a responsible adult.
- I do have a plan.
- Which is?
Uh,first win the
widow's confidence--
Aside from her lawyer making an official
complaint at the attorney general,
How is that going for you?
She's playing hard to get.
Jane,you close cases.
You--you close like a fiend,so i
tolerate you,and i--and i protect you.
And i let you make
lisbon's life a misery.
But th-there is a line.
There is a line,and when you cross
it,i will protect myself and this unit,
- and i will throw you to the wolves.
- Okay.
As long as we're clear.
Yes?
Yeah. It's the A. G. 'S office.
Um,mrs. Sands is willing to drop the
matter if jane will apologize to her.
Great. I'll make the call.
She wants to hear it
in person,at her house.
Do you want to see my trolls?
I'd love to.
This one's a boy. His
name is woody sands.
Yeah. Come.
You have a very nice room.
Thank you. My daddy made it for me.
This one's a girl.
Her name is wanda sands.
This one's a
girl,too. Her name is--
I bet i can guess her name.
- Warren moon.
- No.
- Wiley post?
- Wendy sands.
- Yes.
- Bye.
Thank you.
- Are you married,mr. Jane?
- Was.
- She's dead.
- Oh,i'm sorry. What happened?
It doesn't matter.
You have a very strange
way about you,mr. Jane.
Do i?
After the memorial service,i don't
know why i simply don't have you fired.
Are you usually so forthright?
What's on your mind,mrs.
Sands? Why am i here?
You know why. I want an apology.
No,you don't.
Here you go,julie.
You told me if i was ever to
need your help,i should call you.
Yes.
- And here i am.
- You were right.
Bennett did upset me at the service.
- He told me the truth about jason.
- Which is?
His investment business was
a sham,went broke ages ago.
Our bank accounts are empty.
He left me and julie with nothing
but massive debts,penniless.
We're gonna have to sell the house
and--and--and--and everything else we own.
I'm so sorry.
The I. R. S. And the S. E. C. And i don't
know who else were investigating him for fraud.
- He told you nothing?
- Nothing. Nothing.
Turns out our--our
marriage was a lie.
Our--our whole life
together was a lie.
- Perhaps he was ashamed in his failure.
- No.
Ashamed? Jason? No.
I always knew he had a-a
secretive,mistrustful side,but this?
Every couple has secrets.
There are rooms in this house
i didn't even know were there.
Mrs. Sands,you asked me...
- To help you.
- Yes.
How can i do that?
If i know jason,he--he--
there's something left.
He would have hid a nest egg somewhere.
Don't you think it's possible?
Whoever killed him certainly thought so.
Sheriff's department.
What is this? Who are you?
Asset seizure. No trouble.
- Start upstairs,boys.
- Cbi. Department of justice.
Hang on a second.
Yeah,this is in order,but,uh,where's
your lethal toxins immunization papers?
Excuse me?
Did they not tell you the score here?
Did you get your shots?
Shots? What are you talking about?
Shots. There was a murder here.
- Yeah,i know.
- Excuse me a minute.
Suspected poisoning.
Anthrax.
Come on. Let's,uh,let's go,guys.
Get your shots. We'll talk.
Shots.
Looks like sands was bust all right.
He used to be huge,but he made
some really bad calls in I. T.
Over the past five years,his business
has dwindled down to almost nothing.
No clients. No income.
There were indictments and injunctions and
the whole nightmare coming,just down the road.
The strange thing is,until
a couple of weeks ago,
There was $10 million in his personal
accounts in cash and bonds and stocks,
Most of it deposited over the last year.
His business is dead for years.
Where do you get $10 million from?
More importantly,where is it now?
That's what his killers wanted to know.
Are you sure the widow
doesn't know where it is?
No,she's genuinely broke
and genuinely scared.
- You're not soft on her,are you?
- No.
Maybe a little.
We need to talk to
the lawyer.What's his--
bennett? We need to talk to him.
You need to stay well away.
Did you say maybe a little?
She's a gorgeous,grieving
widow. Of course maybe a little.
Don't worry. It's not
going to affect my work.
I'm a law enforcement
professional. Jeez.
My sincere apologies for our
operative jane,by the way.
Unconscionable.
Supervising agent minelli
gave him a severe reprimand.
Well,think nothing of it.
I can't tell you how sad i am
about all this. How can i help?
I'll try and be brief.
You were sands' lawyer.
You had to have known
he was in ruinous debt.
Yeah,i knew there were difficulties,but
i had no idea how deep he was in it.
I don't deal in his business affairs.
I'm his family lawyer,so i look
after his personal financial matters,
Which until recently,were
in pretty good shape.
Yeah,two weeks ago,he converted a
$10 million pension account into cash.
It's pretty much all he had.
Which is his right. I learned about
it after the fact from his accountants.
It's a huge withdrawal,but,uh,of course,i
figured he had much more in reserve.
Did you ask him what he
was doing with the money?
I did.
He told me he needed
it to surprise his wife.
He did that all right.
I believed him.
What do you believe now?
I think he was looking at jail time.
I think he grabbed as much cash as
he could,and he was gonna run away.
Thanks for your help,counselor.
We'll be in touch.
Okay. Whatever you
need,i'm at your service.
We found out where that
money was coming from.
Sands owns an office supply company that supplies
this happy landings entertainment with copy paper.
Over the last 2
years,$55. 2 million worth.
Who owns happy landings entertainment?
It's a shell company hidden in a swiss
trust wrapped in a dummy corporation.
It'll take a while to untangle.
But sands' company?
It's the only one of his businesses
under a separate corporate address.
In sausalito?
- Odd,huh?
- Nice work.
Are we gonna have a look?
We are. You're gonna stay
here and keep digging.
Who owns happy landings entertainment?
Sau......
Doesn't look like a copy
paper business,does it?
Uh,no.
This is it. You coming aboard?
Why not?
If sands lied about this,what
else did he cover up?
The place is trashed.
Cho.
I'm--i'm just gonna
wait on--on the jetty.
Who are you?
Patrick jane,cbi.
Don't shoot.
What's that,cbi?
Police. Lay the gun down.
- Show me the badge.
- Put the gun down!
Okay,police. I make
no trouble. No problem.
Who'd you think we were?
Nobody.
Who are you? What are you looking for?
This is my boat. I can do what i like.
Yeah,it's very nice,very put together.
This boat belongs to jason sands.
Yes,and jason sands is my fianc\.Y
***********With burglary,vandalism,assault
with a deadly weapon.
That's 10 to 15 right there.
Wouldn't you rather talk
to us about your situation?
From you,i buy cookies.
I don't talk about situation.
Listen. We
have enough--
The handsome one.
Gay,yes?
This is a murder investigation.
You've got no alibi for
the time frame in question.
We're looking at you as a suspect.
You should take this a
little more seriously.
You know,when i was this big,
i was in a detention camp for two years.
- You understand?
- I understand.
No,you don't.
That was
serious. This--no.
What do you do for a living?
I dance,model,acting.
Is that a good living?
What's good?
How long were you and
jason sands lovers?
Two years. We were-- we
were more than lovers.
We were engaged to be married.
He was already married.
No,he was divorcing her.
- She doesn't know that.
- Oh,sure,she does.
Why would she tell
you? It's embarrassing.
He doesn't want her
anymore. It is embarrassing.
What were you looking for?
And we loved each other.
You loved each other. We hear that.
What were you looking for on the boat?
Jason bought $10 million of
diamonds for when we would run away.
I was looking for them.
When did he buy them?
A month ago.
Once he showed me them.
They are beautiful.
And then he hid them
somewhere. I don't know where.
You were gonna run away?
Jason knew that it was
the end of the road here.
He was going to jail or going
to get killed,so we make a plan.
We are going,to,uh,run
away in the sailboat.
You and him on a sailboat.
No,he was a good sailor. He teach me.
If,um,those bastards didn't kill him,
maybe me and him and
julie would be in tahiti,
Rich,instead of here with you.
Y-you were gonna take julie?
What bastards. You know who killed him?
- Yeah,sure,i know.
- Tell us.
If i tell you,i leave here now.
You drop this burglary stupidness.
I don't testify. Nothing.
I give you names. That's it.
Deal.
These,um,scum pigs run nightclubs.
Jason cleans their,uh,drug
and,um,girl money for them.
It's this money he uses
to buy the diamonds.
Did they have a company called happy
landings entertainment out of oakland?
I don't know. They live in oakland.
These people have names?
Dieter webb and carter lewis.
Scum pigs.
Dieter and carter-- started
out as college deejays.
Nightlife impresarios is
what they say they are.
They own clubs,restaurants,boutique
hotels up and down the west coast.
Drugs and prostitution started as a natural
sideline,then became their core business.
Did we find 'em?
These guys like to
glide under the radar.
According to official records,they
own no property and live nowhere.
Their only address is a P. O.box.
Working with san francisco
and oakland P. D.as we speak.
You're letting her go?
She gave us dieter and carter.
I could charge her with waving
a gun at jane,but what for?
I don't know,boss.
If ever i saw a woman who could use
pliers and a lit cigar on a man,that's her.
Miss jonovic,a moment.
Jane,tell her not to leave town.
You said you and jason were
planning on leaving with julie.
Yes.
- You didn't mind taking the kid?
- No. I love julie.
Me and her are good friends.
You were gonna take her
away from her own mother?
Yes.
Oh,that seems a cruel thing to do.
Depends.
She is a cold
person--jennifer.
She doesn't care so much about julie.
She pretends,but she doesn't really.
Tell me something.
Do you think,uh,jennifer
has my diamonds?
I don't know. Maybe.
Maybe? Did you ask her?
Don't leave town.
As you like.
So love and affection,huh?
That's it.
Where you going?
- To speak to the widow.
- Oh,yeah?
I want to know if she
knows about the mistress.
This is delicious. Thank you so much.
Do you have children,patrick?
No.
They are the greatest gift.
Yes,they are.
Put a little bit of ginger in it.
Hey,it's been bothering
the hell of out of me.
Peter & the wolf-- is the duck a
flute or a bassoon? I cannot remember.
Oh,um,a-a bassoon,i think.
Never mind. Trivia.
Listen,i have good
news,and i have bad news.
Dieter webb's grandmother is 93 and lives in
a seniors' assisted living center in tucson,
- Has for a decade,but
she-- - Let me guess.
She's leasing a high-end vehicle and
recently bought a nice house in oakland.
You're good.
Get rigsby and van pelt on it.
$10 million?
Yes,just as you suspected,a
very healthy nest egg.
Oh,that's wonderful. We have to find it.
Wouldn't be a bad idea.
Where should we start?
I don't know.
You found the safe room in a moment.
You must be terribly clever at
that kind of thing,finding things.
I could try.
But,jennifer,that was the good news.
Okay. Bad news?
We talked to a woman who appears
to have been jason's mistress.
I knew it.
I knew it. I knew it.
I'm sorry.
You didn't know about her?
No. What's she like? H-how old is she?
Mid '20s,eastern european,tough.
Good-looking?
Not bad.
Does she have the money?
Strong possibility.
Life is so complicated.
Patrick? Will you hold me?
I need someone to hold me. Please.
I'm sorry,jennifer. I wish i could.
O...
Where's the entry team? They were
supposed to be here 20 minutes ago.
Relax. Guys like these probably
aren't even out of bed yet.
Could be up from the night before.
Maybe went out for some breakfast.
We can deal with 'em.
Suddenly she's steve mcqueen.
They're on the move.
Come on. Let's take 'em.
Police! Get out of the car!
Hands up!
- Get out of the car!
- Get out!
Take it easy,man.
Come on. Nice and easy.
Up against the car.
Ven aqu^.
Freeze!
Hands behind your head.
Hands. Give me your hands!
Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
You don't want to talk to me,dieter?
I've got nothing to say. Call my lawyer.
What do you know about jason sands?
I know he's dead.
How much did he take from you?
How much what?
We estimate he stole around $10
million from you. Is that about right?
Me and my partner,we host parties.
I'm doing good,but not that good.
$10 million.
Jason didn't steal anything from me.
You and carter broke into his house,and you
tortured him to death because he stole from you.
Look,dude,i know people that know how to
do that stuff. You know what i'm saying?
If it was us that tortured him,we'd have
the money right now,and he'd have his life.
- I wouldn't kill him.
- What money?
Oh,you caught me there.
The imaginary money you
said he stole from us.
Somebody got there before us.
An imaginary somebody.
You want my opinion?
Now this isn't snitching.
It's just an opinion.
Write this down. Adrianna jonovic.
She's a crazy armenian
dancer that jason was tapping.
Why?
She's a mercenary bitch.
She made jason's life
misery and made him like it.
She used to work for us,so
i know whereof i speak.
You should check her out.
The other one,lewis,has the same line.
There were class "a"
drugs all over his house,
So we can hold him as long as it takes.
And jonovic?
I think she's clean on this one,but we
can bring her back in just to be safe.
Well,don't let up on 'em.
We need a result here.
Mrs. Sands.
Patrick,she's gone. She's gone.
Th-they--they took
her! My baby is gone!
It's okay. It's okay.
W-we'll be right there.
YOU KNOW WHAT WE WANT TELL THE
POLICE AND SHE DIES.WAIT FOR OUR CALL.
***********
They are.
Look,you have to find
my little girl. Please.
What are you talking about,steal a kid?
I've been locked up in this place.
You have friends,remember?
So you think that i'd be ass enough to
hire somebody to do it while i'm in here?
Dieter has a point.
He and carter are bad
guys,but they're not mafia.
They don't have that kind of reach.
- Or those kind of stones.
- We're up.
The kidnappers just i.
M.'ed jennifer's cell phone.
I have your dauthter,do
you have what i want?
Say yes. Say yes and tell
'em i'll bring it to them.
What? No.
It's okay. I know where the
money is,honestly. Say yes.
Yes,i have it.
- Still awake?
- Wide.
Jane,be careful.
Don't try and get them to
say anything or stop them.
All we need is their phone.
Just sent us the number. We'll
track the kidnapper's address.
Oh,here comes someone.
Jane,just do your mind games
and get out of there,okay?
Don't worry,mom.
This better not be a trap.
I will kill you. Give me the diamonds.
Oh,adrianna,you're going down
the wrong road.Kidnapping is--
i'm not a kidnapper. You
think i want to do this?
I have to do this. I
don't want julie to die.
Tell me what's going on.
I can--i can help you.
I don't know you. I don't trust you.
Just give me the diamonds.
Okay.
Where's julie?
I call a number,tell them i have
the diamonds,they give julie.
Call them.
How do i know those are real diamonds?
They look real to me.
Here. Why don't you have a look?
You've seen them before. Here.
Oh,i'm sorry.
It's okay.
Scan's working.
No,this--this... This
is not the diamonds.
No,plastic. Forwarding
the last number dialed.
You son of a whore.
Signal on that phone is coming from
an apartment building in the presidio.
All units move in.
They will kill julie now.
Who is "they"?
I don't know. They call me.
They send pictures to my
phone of--of julie tied up.
They say i must give them
jason's money,or she dies.
I don't have jason's money.
Did they ask for jason's money
or did they ask for diamonds?
For money.
Then they're not gonna hurt julie
if you're telling me the truth.
No if. I am telling the truth.
Get back.
- Police!
Freeze!
- Drop the weapon!
- Drop the gun!
- Drop it right now!
- Put down the weapon!
- Drop the weapon!
- Watch the kid!
So far what i know is you guys shot
and grievously wounded a prominent
And a very well-liked member
of the san francisco bar.
What's going on?
In simple,declarative sentences.
Bennett's our man.
He killed jason sands for $10 million in
diamonds,kidnapped julie sands for the same reason.
Either the widow or the
mistress acted as his accomplice.
Which one?
We're trying to nail that down now.
If bennett makes it,he could tell
us,but it doesn't look like he will,
so we're gonna need a
confession from his accomplice.
- So,um...
- What?
Jane has an idea.
But if we generate any complaints as to how
we go about this,you've got our backs,right?
Well,that depends.
Obviously,we need a win here.
But i-i won't sanction anything
underhanded or actionable.
That's kind of vague.
The whole point of this unit is--is
subtly and discretion and judgment.
I expect you to do what's right
without dragging me into it.
Really?
Yes,yes,lisbon. Of course.
If i'm forced to it,i have your back.
I'm insulted you need to ask.
Where is she? Where is she? Is she okay?
Yes. She's a little in
shock,but physically she's fine.
Not a scratch. Doctors
just want to make sure.
Hello,jennifer.
Adrianna?
This is a surprise.
What's she doing here?
Shouldn't she be in jail?
Uh,out on bond,ma'am.
So quickly?
I screw better lawyers than you.
You've obviously led a very sad
and difficult life to be so twisted.
Truly,adrianna,you have my sympathy.
********
Cho,let's move.
- What was that name again?
- What name?
The one that jane
thought was so important.
Wendy.
Right,wendy. Do either of
you know a woman named wendy?
- No. No?
- Shame.
She'd be worth knowing.
- Cho.
- What?
Excuse his levity,ma'am.
This wendy person--
she has the diamonds?
It's a possibility.
Diamonds?
By the way,your friend mr.
Bennett is coming along nicely.
I expect we'll be
talking to him shortly.
So if there's anything
you want to pass along...
But this other police said
that he was a dead man.
- Yeah,they said he was dying.
- No.
No,he'll live.
- How'd it go?
- I think we sold it.
- Are you kidding?
- We killed. Yeah.
Well,jane says give it a
moment,let it play itself out.
It's empty. They're both gone.
Really? Both?
Jane,nobody's there. Come on.
It's okay,baby. Everything
going to be good now.
- Everything's good.
- Where have you been?
Damn! Damn! Damn!
What are you looking for?
You know what i'm looking for.
I'm pretty certain wendy
sands had purple hair.
- You may want to call a lawyer now.
- Why? What for?
Don't make this difficult,jennifer.
Bennett told us everything.
Nicely done.
You made me think adrianna had the
money,and you made her think i had the money.
Clever.
Thank you.
Coming from a fine actress
like yourself,i'm...
I'm flattered.
Is it really in diamonds,or
is that just part of the trick?
No trick. Diamonds.
Do you know where?
I do.
Tell me.
Tell me what happened,and
i'll tell you where they are.
This whole time,you
were just playing me.
Not the whole time.
That's so sad. I... Thought
we had a real connection.
We did.
- We can again.
- No,we can't.
You know,i...
I never meant for this to happen.
I know.
It was bennett.
He forced me into this.
He--he planned the whole thing.
No,bennett is an idiot
that thinks he's in control,
But you played him like a violin,with
those big eyes and those trembling lips.
It's a dynamite act.
You had me buying it.
If only you'd told me
the duck was an oboe,
I probably would've told
you where the diamonds were,
And we likely never
would've solved this one.
The duck was an oboe?
Yeah. "peter and the wolf."
The duck is played by the oboe.
The wolf is a bassoon.
The flute is the songbird.
Anyone who's seen it knows that.
But you didn't.
You didn't go to "peter and the wolf."
You stayed home and tortured your husband
to make him give you his running away money.
Running away with my daughter and
$10 million and that dirty whore.
And leave me with nothing?
I don't think so.
How do you think it feels that my daughter
prefers her father's whore over me?
That she loves her more
than her own mother?
How do you think that feels?
I'm sure it hurts.
I always knew there
was a safe in that room,
But he would never tell me where
or what the combination was.
And i had a real breakthrough insight.
I realized...
That was our whole
marriage-- withholding.
Withholding,always withholding.
Whatever it was that i
needed most from jason...
That's what he refused to give me.
Tell me. Where are they?
The diamonds.
- Very nice room.
- My daddy made it for me.
When did you first suspect it was her?
Oh,i had an idea at the funeral service.
- No,you did not.
- I did. I did.
She,uh,she was looking way too good.
No wife should glow at
her husband's funeral.
So you made that bet with rigsby that you could seduce
her with the deliberate intention of snaring her?
I wanted to win the bet,too,and,uh...
I couldn't.
Just because i lost doesn't mean
you shouldn't take my advice.
Yeah,yeah,hush.
I'm serious,man. Go for it.
What's he talking about?
Nothing.
J. J. Team
Pour U-Sub
- = Syncro et Transcript = -
YDY.com