so you leaving the beanie baby's
earring tree and the butt master?
It was late at night.
Couldn't sleep. Infomercials.
That's how I ended
up with a rotato.
You know, this is the good
thing about moving in with a man,
starting a whole new
grown-up relationship,
is that you can leave your
embarrassing stuff behind.
It's like leaving your lesser self.
Starting fresh,
clean slate-I love it.
Just one beanie baby
- the dolphin.
I want you to keep this for me.
I
- is it somebody's ashes?
It's a getaway box.
Get away from what?
You know, living with
luke isn't going so hot.
I, uh, need to get out in a hurry.
I don't have to
stop and pack stuff.
Ruins the whole dramatic exit.
So if it doesn't work out with
luke, you're living with me?
No, I'm just gonna
come pick up the box.
Maybe I'll spend one night.
Oh, so romantic.
I've never lived
with anybody before.
It makes me nervous.
You, of all people,
should understand.
Just because my relationship went down in
flames doesn't mean that yours is going to.
And if it does, at least you know there's
no chance luke will end up being your boss.
Hey, I am totally okay with the
"my ex is now my boss" thing.
Tom is professional.
I am professional.
It's all very professional.
Seriously.
We are both very okay with this.
But since you brought up the subject of work
- no, no.
She didn't bring up work.
She brought up tom.
We're taking a work break.
Which means no discussion
of the kiss me not killer.
I never 100% agreed to that.
What's left to discuss?
We have nothing
- no D.N.A., No fingerprints, no fibers.
We don't even know who
she is, the poor girl.
We're missing something.
No killer is that good.
They always make a mistake.
Not this one.
Not yet.
Lindsay, I'm not saying you shouldn't do everything
in your power to bring this son of a bitch down.
You should.
We all should, and we will.
But you need to be able to put it
away sometimes, like, for example, now.
Let's just try...
and be in the moment.
You're the one with
the getaway box.
ah, this can't be good.
Boxer.
Bernhardt.
Washburn.
We're in the process of disconnecting the
car, so the electricity had to be turn off.
I don't know how much
we can do in the dark.
somebody's working on a generator.
Watch your step.
I wish I had a
getaway box for this.
3 dead, 6 gunshot wounds
from what appear to be a. 38
My guess is one killer with
good aim and coordination.
"noreen davenport.
" Looks like she was running
for the door, but her heel broke.
She might have made it.
Never run in jimmy choos.
She's still holding her blackberry,
but her wallet's stripped of cash,
and the tan lines say she
was wearing a lot of jewelry.
Oh, look.
A sock from before
socks were invented.
Hey, put this in evidence with the four
condoms and the calcified raisinets.
Tell me that leg
was already missing.
I think he left it in iraq.
"Carlos fuentes, "
from his dog tags.
He fought hard here, too.
The shot through his
hand is a defensive wound.
And then there's rodney boyce.
Never knew what hit him.
"go green" t-shirt, hemp bag.
Kid was fighting
for a perfect world.
He's there now.
All right. By the size of that boot
print, safe bet is our killer is a man.
What are you
thinkin', spree killer?
No, a spree killer doesn't
boost things from a crime scene.
This guy's organized and precise.
The boot print is
all he left behind?
That and the forensics from the last
50 people who passed through the car.
all right, subway is
shut down indefinitely.
Mayor's on his way.
I got a press conference.
What do you got?
We don't even know yet if
there was an intended target.
The victims all seem unrelated.
Get unis to search the other subway cars for
a rder weapon, trash receptacles, anything.
Jacobi's on it.
We have to disconnect this
subway car, move it downtown.
It's in the works.
What's claire got?
Well, what doesn't she have?
There's too much information.
All right.
the politics on this
are gonna be endless.
I want you to find me when
you have anything at all.
Of course.
I can't talk about
the case, but it's big.
I don't know when
I'll be home again.
Honey, let me, uh,
let me call you back.
Hey, what are you doing down here?
- I'm with lindsay boxer.
She's expecting me.
Excuse me, where do
you think you're going?
Hey, jill, it's great to see you.
What a circus. Huh?
- Yeah, how did you get by the uniforms?
I told them I have a
relationship with lindsay.
You have a very loose
definition of a "relationship.
" Not according to
my last boyfriend.
Hey, you have to leave.
No, this happened very quickly,
so I didn't have time to alert you.
I am on the crime desk
at the "register" now.
You should be behind
that desk as we speak.
You'll get all the details at the press
conference along with everybody else.
Jill, I need to talk to you.
Denise kwon.
Cindy thomas from the "register.
" As criminal division chief, how
does your office plan to proceed?
A reporter on the crime scene?
I am a crime reporter.
She was just leaving.
Look, sorry to throw you intohe deep end here,
but you were the only one to answer the phone.
Obviously I'm gonna
reassign this in the morning.
Just take good notes.
Why would you reassign it?
You've never handled
anything of this magnitude.
I have a 98% conviction rate on
every case where I was lead counsel.
If you take me off of this, I'll
have to challenge that decision.
From hello to over my head, and
it feels like I just got here.
Okay. I'll give you a shot...
but you might wish I hadn'T.
All right. Okay, bring her in, art.
just need you to confirm
this is rodney boyce.
My god.
Yes, it's rodney.
He's a, uh, temp worker, but we
were gonna offer him a position.
So much promise, thakid.
First in, last out every day.
We've been unable
to locate his family.
The only I. D. He had on
him was his employee card.
I think he was from wisconsin.
I'll check my records.
Okay.
What, uh, was the nature of
his work at lazar software?
Whatever needed doing.
He was there to learn.
About?
Oh, small business- in my case,
software- inventory and billing systems.
I could tell you more, but it
usually clears dinner parties.
If you could get us the personal information,
we'll handle notifying the family.
Thank you for coming in, mr. Lazar.
So I just subpoenaed the personnel
records of 250 bart employees.
If any one of them so much as threatened
a subway rat, I'll know about it.
Where are you guys?
Buried, but I can tell you that the shoe
print is a rubber outsoled army boot,
which doesn't exactly
narrow the field.
I also pulled a court
record on carlos fuentes.
Nothing much. Some gang
activity in his youth.
Um, he chose army over
prison when he got busted.
Where he performed well
and got glowing reports.
I spoke to his company commander.
I have yet to notify
his next of kin.
god, it's so sad.
He survived gangs in hisouth,
survived I. E. D. S over there-
talk about life's not fair.
What about noreen davenport?
Some really good work on her face, easily 50,
000 bucks worth, and that's just above the neck,
and the blouse costs as much
as the extension on my house.
So why is she riding the train?
Who I. D. 'Ed the body?
Her sister, who mentioned an ex-husband,
and it did not sound like an amicable split.
It's worth checking out.
And speaking of ex-husbands, tom is hoping that
we can eliminate the spree killer idea A. S. A. P.
Is there any way that you
can help me out with that?
Well, sure, if you don't need, I
don't know, facts to back it up.
The bart is up and running, but
people are too scared to ride it.
The city is shutting
down from gridlock.
Department of transportation
is having a meltdown.
Well, I can't give
you what I don't have.
I know.
Okay, thanks.
Come on, where'd
you get the address?
Tom has a snitch in los
santos, carlos' former gang.
Say fuentes has a brother
living here-alberto.
He's the only next
of kin I could find.
And don't look at me like I'm
cheating on you 'cause I talk to tom.
Well, have I not said
that tom and I are good?
Your turn.
Oh, god, I hate notifying family.
I don't even deal
well with my own pain.
Mr. Fuentes?
Anybody home?
Let's check around back.
A canine welcoming committee.
door's open.
Mr. Fuentes?
San francisco police department.
Can we talk to you?
get down!
there he goes.
stop!
Police!
Dinero cuando no hay de que reírse.
stay down!
Stay down!
You don't run from the police!
Don't shoot! Don't
shoot! Don't shoot me.
I'm guessing he already
knows about his brother.
Lindsay, the point is, why would he kill
his brother, not to mention two strangers?
Carlos left los santos three years
ago, but you were still active.
what's she getting at?
we know what happens when
someone leaves a gang.
They're marked.
I've been to a few
of those funerals.
I know you're still mad about the gun thing
- the gun thing?
You me where my partner and I
were almost killed, that gun thing?
Alberto is not your subway killer.
Did you not tell everyone in los santos
that your brother was dead to you?
Look, they hated
him for getting out.
Me, too, maybe.
But it was righteous what
he did, going to iraq-
kicking ass over there,
coming back all busted up.
You don't mess with
a guy like that.
He's still booked for
attempted murder...
for "the gun thing.
" Don't worry, alberto.
I'll be your lawyer.
hey.
Take it.
It's for you.
okay, don't attack. It's me.
I need another reason.
Information in the subway killings.
Look, I figure-I figure we
could work out a quid pro quo.
I give you this.
You give me, uh...
uh, you know, whatever.
I'm open.
Okay, listen, my editor is screaming at me to write
a 2-page spread entitled "spree killer on the rampage.
" It's not a spree killer.
Hey, you know that for a fact?
My gut does.
See, the thing is, "spree
killer" sells papers.
If, uh, if you were to give me something
else, I could help with the spin.
Rodney boyce, the temp at lazar
software, had a-had a police record.
I didn't get a hit on him.
Canada.
He was arrested for
assault on a police officer.
Well, okay, technically, a mountie.
What was he doing in canada?
Fun place to go when you're
in trouble with the law?
Plus the beer.
Anyway, it's a lead.
It's a bribe.
You're gonna miss me
when I stop coming around.
Give me a chance to find out.
Om) this is obviously top priority.
We've got 15 additional officers in the bart,
and I've got my best inspectors working on it.
What's going on?
I think tom's getting a
taste of being lieutenant.
The chief and the mayor,
not just their people.
Now do you want tom's job?
I don't even want mine.
I just spent hours with the surveillance
tapes from the bart atform and got nothing.
How's it going with
the fuentes kid?
I don't like him as the killer.
He emptied a clip on us
and didn't hit a thing.
I like that in a shooter.
Well, I finally pulled all the info
from noreen davenport's blackberry.
The woman could talk
a lot about nothing.
But this transcript is good.
It's to her ex-husband,
threatening to sue him
for having the 7 series towed from her
driveway the night before the murders.
That explains why
she was on the train.
What are his responses?
Uh, I don't know.
He, um, tends to ignore her.
I know how that feels.
You busy?
Overwhelmed.
What can I do for you?
Well, I was just in the building, you know, trying to get
the fuentes kid off on a bogus attempted murder charge.
And you want me to talk to lindsay?
Well, yeah.
But I, uh, also think
the two of us should talk.
hanson, be a guy.
The guy never wants to talk.
Look, I know your situation.
I don't expect you to dump
your E. R. Doc over me.
But if you were to dump him for some other reason,
like he's a workaholic with a god complex...
hanson.
Then come find me.
Listen, we're not gonna deal on the
fuentes kid, so you can just forget it.
Now if I were you, I'd leave, unless you want
to stick around to meet denise's dark side.
Trust me, I've seen it.
I can't believe that she
called the cops on me.
I mean, I-I admit I shouldn't have towed
her car, but noreen keeps stonewalling.
mr. Davenport, that's not
why we called you to come in.
Noreen was killed.
She was one of the victims
in the sway murders.
Wh
- I'm sorry.
Oh, dear god.
I did this to her.
I didn't mean that.
I...
she was on the subway because
of me, because of the car.
Mr. Davenport, the language of her e
- mails to you is, uh, pretty extreme.
Yeah, well, that's
- that was noreen's way of keeping a relationship going.
She couldn't accept
that I moved on.
When you say moved on,
you mean you're remarried?
Uh, yes, almost a year.
So you have no strong
feelings for your ex-wife?
Am I a suspect?
Understanding the victim
helps us understand the crime.
No, I didn't have any
strong feelings towards her.
But I didn't want her to die.
Hey!
bart shootings,
oakland commuters...
hey.
Didn't know if you'd be home.
Uh, yeah, tag teaming.
Marin county sent some
people to help out.
Where are the kids?
Homework, upstairs.
Has anybody eaten?
There was talk of pizza.
Have a bad day today?
You don't want to know.
Is that why you're not
at physical therapy?
I can't predict when I'm
gonna feel like this, claire.
And even when you do feel this
way, you have to keep going.
The doctor said there was-
look, this whole "one foot in front of the other"
thing is easier for some people than others.
You're telling me?
I've been staring at the
body of a disabled vet
who fought like an olympic
warrior to save his own life.
And you can't make dinner.
hey, can it wait?
We got the murder weapon.
Unis found it in a storm drain four
blocks away from the bart station.
I'm on my way.
yes.
So-yeah, as soon as we confirm it is not a
spree killer, I will give you a call back.
Yes, sir.
No, sir, I-hello?
Damn!
Grumpy mayor?
Turns out that man has a silver platter, which
he just handed me with my ass all over it.
I'm sorry.
Part of the job.
Can't take it personal... ly.
Is that what I think it is?
Do you think it's
the murder weapon?
I do.
Then it is what you think it is.
You know what this means?
That you can call the mayor back.
And give him what?
Good news.
Very...
good news.
Come on. Come on.
We are gonna solve this case.
The city is gonna
get back to normal.
Things are lookin' up.
Come on. Give me a little shimmy.
This is so not professional.
is that the mayor again?
It's the chief...
calling to make threats on my
job if we don't solve this case.
We are gonna solve
this case, right?
I'm workin' on it.
hello, chief.
Uh, no.
Actually, we have
found the murder weapon.
Yes, sir.
Claire says it's a match
on all three victims.
The bad news is it's
unregistered and untraceable.
Did you go home last night?
No. Can you tell?
You look fine.
The good news is I spent the night
running all the stores that sell army boots
like the ones our
killer was wearing.
I found one that's been busted twice in
the past year for selling illegal firearms.
Seriously, am I, like, haggard?
Is it dark circles, what?
You're fine. It's a solid lead.
Have you told tom?
Well, I was on my way.
That should keep the mayor off
his back for at least an hour.
How's that going?
It's, uh, still professional?
Oh, yeah. He's moved
on. I've moved on.
It's-it's all good.
But it's clean, though.
Yeah, this is
- hi.
Oh, do you need tom?
No.
Not at all.
Uh, lindsay, this is heather.
Heather, lindsay.
Well, I assumed.
It's nice to finally meet you.
Yeah, you, too.
She brought me a fresh shirt
since I worked all night.
It's
- it's a beautiful shirt.
Italian.
She's trying to upgrade me.
Just your clothes.
Just...
Uh, did you need me?
It can wait.
Nice to meet you.
Okay.
I'll talk to you later.
Thank god I've moved on.
Because if I hadn't moved on,
that would've been awkward...
seeing him...
half-naked...
in front of his fiancéE...
heather.
Do you need me for
this conversation?
Surplus store.
You comin'?
Yeah.
Were you up all night?
I'll meet you the motor pool.
I don't sell gunS.
Not legally, anyway.
Listen, you sell guns,
you don't sell guns.
We're just trying
to find the murderer.
Long as you're not
him, you're good.
Really?
'Cause one more citation,
A. T. F. Shuts my store down.
I will not call A. T. F. On you.
I promise.
Is that the marine corps?
You were in the marines,
weren't you, jacobi?
Yeah, um, trained in parris island.
Yeah?
Me, too.
Well, different decade, though.
You deployed to nam?
You're hilarious.
One of the victims was a vet.
He lost his leg in iraq only to die at
the hands of some lunatic on the subway.
It's not exactly a
hero's end, right?
You really not gonna turn me in?
Biker guy came in looking
for a. 38 Nice enough guy.
Kind of a camo freak.
He said he needed
it for protection.
He calls himself "mad dog.
" Biker named mad dog, yeah.
That narrows it down, yes.
Mad dog vinny.
That's all I know.
You got an address?
Tenderloin district...
maybe.
You were good.
Look, who would ever
buy me as a marine?
I have a titanium hip, and i
was a kid when the war ended.
I was.
You ll A. T. F. On that guy?
Well, you can'T. You promised.
Hey!
This is where the
murder weapon came from?
You know, there is a fine line
between investigating and stalking.
Hey, look, this isn't
just a police matter.
You're aountable to the public
whose tax dollars pay your salary.
Now you can keep stonewalling me, or
we can find a way to help each other.
Off the record?
Of course.
A biker named mad dog, and if I see that
in print, you'll be held accountable to me,
which is much worse than being
held accountable to the public.
You won't be sorry.
We're going on day
three with nothing, jill.
Tell me why I shouldn't
pull this from your desk.
Because you'd have
to start from scratch.
Because I have a far better working relationship
with the detectives than anyone in our office.
And yet I still have
nothing to report to my boss,
who in turn has nothing to
report to his boss the mayor,
who in turn has nothing to report
to the people who elected him.
I get the whole chain of command.
Then act like it.
Girl talk?
here's your warrant.
This better be the right mad dog.
Let's leave it at that.
Listen, this guy's been hauled
in multiple times for possession.
The store owner I.D.'Ed his
mug shot off of a six-pack,
oddly enough, right before
A.T.F.Raided his shop.
I met heather.
You did? When?
In tom's officE.
She brought him a shirt.
He was half undressed.
And here's the wrd thing
- walked in, and he didn't even flinch.
Why would he flinch?
You've both moved on.
I would still expect a flinch.
Go get mad dog, then we'll talk
about heather. I want details
Smells like vinny's
having meth for lunch.
Vincent morelo. San
francisco police.
Mr. Morelo?
Vincent?
Oh, this doesn't look good.
Jacobi.
mad dog's been on a drug binge.
Damn it, he's O. D. 'Ing.
Call it in.
Come on, vinny.
You don't die without
giving me some answers.
What do we got?
30-year-old male,
meth overdose.
He's in a lethal arrhythmia,
hypertensive and diaphoretic.
All right, let's check breath
sounds, get a monitor in him.
All right?
Draw my labs.
I'll take it from here.
Okay. I-I want this guy,
luke, alivand talking.
That's the bart killer.
Yeah, okay, well, linz, right
now, he's my patient, okay?
So just go wait in the chairs.
Did you get anything out
of him in the ambulance?
No, he never regained
consciousness.
You both need to leave.
We both need to leave.
Whose side are you on?
Let me get back to you on that one.
This is when I call denise
to tell her we got our killer,
and she manages to
take all the credit.
Remember when I wanted
to buy a motorcycle?
Your subconscious
post-divorce death wish?
The good ones are expensive,
like 30 grand easy.
Mad dog had a brand-new bike
parked outside his trailer.
The thing had to cost way
more than what he would
have made pawning the stuff
he stole from the crime scene.
Meth heads aren't
known for their savings.
He must have had a windfall.
Somebody paid him to
commit those murders.
Yeah, one of them, anyway.
The othetwo he killed just to spin us
sideways, or just because they were there.
If mad dog dies, we may never know
who he was paid to kill or why.
Mad dog's in capable
hands, believe me.
Yeah, luke is pretty
amazing in action.
'S kind of sexy, actually...
except for the part when he
kept telling me to get lost.
Nah, that was kind of sexy, too.
yeah, he's great.
You say "he's great" the way
people say green tea is great.
Like we're supposed to drink it,
but we really want to drink coffee.
Oh, you heard all
of that in my voice?
Is there someone else?
Someone a little more coffee?
This is not about
green tea or coffee.
I just haven't told him I
sleep with a wave machine.
You do know cops are
like human lie detectors?
it happened once.
It's not an affair.
Who?
I'm not gonna tell you who.
You're so telling me who.
Hanson.
Hanson north?
Again?
Are you nuts?
Luke is crazy about you.
He's a crusading
doctor that saves lives.
Hanson is an arrogant P. D. Who
lives to make our lives difficult.
Yeah, I heard you the last two
times I got involved with him.
And what happened to starting
over and a clean slate?
That's what I'm doing.
Clean slate starts now.
No wonder denise hates you.
What?
You know about her and hanson?
You don't know
about her and hanson?
They got together the
first time you split.
Wait, or was it the second?
Do you know how I
heard about mad dog?
On the scanner, with every
other cop and criminal hobbyist.
I'm sorry.
I got distracted by our suspect
almost dying on the way here.
You get a solid lead on the killer,
and it just doesn't come up
when we're passing in the hall?
Is this anger I'm
detecting in your voice?
You didn't tell me about
this guy on purpose.
You're withholding-
I didn't tell you because when I
walked into your office to tell you,
you and heather were playing dress
up, and it didn't seem apppriate.
Is mad dog our guy or not?
He pulled the trigger.
All right.
I am gonna call denise and
schedule a press conference.
But someone paid him to do it.
You know that?
Call it a strong hunch.
and if I'm right, a press conference will
send that somebody straight into hiding.
Just...
trust me.
If you can't trust her, trust me.
I didn't withhold anything.
no press conference, tom.
So this is it.
The inner sanctum.
can't believe I got in here.
Inner sanctum? Hardly.
They're just hiding
from their bosses.
Not hiding, just seeking shelter
from their constant interference.
Plus we'd rather
not be seen with you.
I had unis in pawn shops all day.
How is it they found nothing, but you
managed to find rodney boyce's laptop?
Uh, unis were showing the
pawn shop guys his mug shot.
I, on the other hand,
had this-candid mad dog.
I, uh, figured out that mad dog
vinny was vincent morelo eventually.
What did you do, go to a biker bar?
I went to seven.
They're a little scary.
Oh, but the people are surprisingly helpful
once they figure out that you're not a cop.
Bikers are not fond of cops.
Anyway, one of the bars
had that on the wall.
Martha, cut it out.
Little defensive about
the dog's affections?
At least I'm not
playing with other dogs.
don't make a person
sorry she confided.
clean slate, got it.
Just don't use up all
your chances like I did.
Rodney sure wrote a
bunch of boring e-mails.
He also watched a lot of youtube.
Wait, wait. Open that one right there
-"discrepancies.
" He named a file "discrepancies.
" Not very subtle.
It's a full rundown on the
books of lazar software.
Pretty detailed for a temp.
Projected earnings of the last year compared to some other figures
- I'm guessing his.
So the numbers weren't
adding up for him.
He was going to somebody
with the information.
Oh, he already went, and whoever he
went to didn't like what rodney found.
Enter mad dog.
Bet he was supposed to destroy the
computer after he killed rodney.
Never hire a meth head to do
a professional hit man's job.
I knew that the
laptop was important.
Otherwise why would mad dog take it and
leave behind a blackberry and an ipod?
I just suddenly became very
interested in digital software.
Yeah.
You know what?
Let's, uh, let's get
down there and, um...
right.
I'll hang.
Catch you on the "b" side.
inspectors.
Talk us through this, mrlazar.
Well, let's see.
It's, uh...
my company's private
financial records.
How did you get these?
Rodney boyce's computer.
Look closer.
Rodney?
I don't understand.
You never mentioned that your company
was going public in a few months.
It's a big deal for
a family company-
big enough you started cooking the
books so you could get a bigger payday?
No. I've always emphasized the fact tt our
numbers have to be aboveboard, especially now.
Emphasized it to who?
My son artie.
I'm grooming him to take over.
He runs our accounting team.
He would never
- is this him?
Yeah.
bit of a weekend warrior.
You know, I think a little talk with
artie would help us figure all of this out.
Artie jr. 'S on his way in.
Chips, candy, cupcakes.
Is an apple too much to ask for?
Aside from driving his truly obnoxious motorcycle
55 through a school zone, his record is clean.
And here I was hoping he had a
prior for solicitation of murder.
Get the dark chocolate.
It's healthy...
You realize we've
got jack on this guy.
Well, that's why god
invented lying to suspects.
That's also why I asked tom, no
press conferences about mad dog
till after we've smoked out whoever hired
him to kill rodney boyce, I. E., Artie jr.
It'll work.
You always say that.
And I'm always right...
usually.
More often than not.
Inspectors!
Hey, I need to talk to you.
Come on.
Please?
I'll pass.
I told your lawyer no deal.
I just want to know what's going
on with my brother's killer.
I can't comment on an
ongoing investigation.
That's bull.
That's protocol.
Hey, cho just called.
Artie jr. Has entered the building.
When there's news to be had,
I'll make sure you have it.
Best I can do.
Thank you for coming in, mr. Lazar.
Artie, please.
We're happy to do anything we
can to help find rodney's killer.
Well, the thing is...
I think I'm looking right at him.
I told you, artie was
in portland on business
when the murders happened.
- Dad, dad, it's okay.
Anyway, didn't you guys
already catch the subway killer?
Rodney came to you with his concerns about the
discrepancies in your company's finaes, didn't he?
Sure, he came to me.
We talked throh it.
He knew everything was aboveboard.
You know, the only problem
with what you're saying is that
we got a guy who says you
hired him to murder rodney.
That's ridiculous.
What? Let me guess. Mad dog.
I heard the name on the
radio on the way over here.
Mad dog vincent something, I think.
Right?
Big press conference?
Subway killer apprehended?
They said he O. D. 'Ed, though.
Sounds like he won't make it.
You can't trust
everything you hear.
Either way, I think we'll head out.
You all set, dad?
Stay close to home, artie.
Hey!
Is that him?
You get the guy who
killed my brother?
Hey, I know it was you who
killed my big brother, man!
When I get out,
I'm-a get you, man!
I swear, I'm-a get you!
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Just
take it easy. We're...
lindsay?
What my partner is trying to say,
if she weren't too furious to speak,
is that your little press conference just got
artie lazar off the hook for rodney boyce's murder.
How could you?
I didn'T.
Denise was just filling me in.
The call came from on high.
Don't you dare defend this.
Artie heard it all on the radio.
He knew mad dog was never going to
be able to say a word against him.
It's very simple.
The mayor heard through the grapevine
that we had somebody in custody.
He didn't want to sit
on it one mite longer.
I really didn't have a choice.
You always have a choice.
I'm sure you'll make
the case another way.
So you can screw it up again.
That is enough, inspector.
Pardon me?
You cannot, no matter how
personally aggrieved you feel,
yell at the deputy district
attorney in the middle of my bullpen.
Your bullpen?
You heard me.
Uh, e-excuse me.
I was told that you have
noreen's personal effects.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Uh, yes.
Here you go.
Thank you.
We will get him someday.
Someday is not good enough.
It's not a good plan
Who sprayed my partner
and I with bullets.
You said yourself he
was a terrible shot.
That was luck.
His intentions were clear.
Look, his brother was getting
his life back together.
This kid could turn it around, too.
Didn't you give me a speech
about using up your chances?
It wasn't a speech.
It was more of a quip.
Come on.
We can still get some
good out of this day.
If I see that kid in here for so much as a
parking ticket, you're both gonna regret it.
I'll make that clear.
This is your lucky day, alberto.
I caught inspector boxer
in a warm and fuzzy mood.
So...
does that mean I get to go?
There are conditions.
First, you're finished with the gang,
and believe me, we will follow up on that.
Ll, he's gonna need protection.
We can do that.
What do you say?
Make your brother proud.
Artie...
remember me?
What you doin', homes, huh?
I told you we'd meet again.
Look, I have, uh, credit cards.
I have A. T. M. Cards,
little bit of cash.
What do you guys want?
I want mi hermano back alive.
I don't know what those cops told
you. I didn't even know your brother!
Carlos got his leg blown off fighting for
everybody's right to ride around in big cars
and work in fancy offices.
He finally gets out of that
hole and dies because of you.
This is all I got left.
Look, I didn't mean to do anything
- you didn't mean what?
I didn't mean to do anything!
It was just supposed
to be the one guy!
That was the deal, I swear!
That guy went nuts!
He went nuts-I just- I
wanted rodney boyce dead!
That was the deal.
- That's it. Let's go!
That was the gig!
I'm telling you the truth!
Look, your brother wasn't my fault.
Please believe me.
Artie lazar, you are under arrest for the murders
of carlos fuentes, rodney boyce and noreen davenport.
thank you, officers.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will... Be used
against you in a court of law... are u right?
you did a good job.
You got us everything we need.
Now isn't that more satisfying
than shooting at cops?
You're a lot better at it, anyway.
whatever.
I think I kind of like this whole
clean slate/ fresh start thing.
And now is where you want me
to tell you it was a good plan.
No.
Maybe later.
It was a good plan.
"Exam room three.
Insomnia and bouts of withholding"?
Hey!
What's going on?
We closed our case tonight.
Congratulations.
How's mad dog?
Ohh.
Remember that poster
of your brain on drugs?
Yeah.
So what's with the dinosis?
I need to tell you something.
I'm glad we're together.
Well, I'm glad we're together, too,
but that can't be keeping you awake.
I wanted to give you this.
It's a getaway box.
It was a getaway box.
Now it's just a box of my stuff
that's gonna be in our apartment
with all the rest of my stuff.
A getaway box.
Let me guess.
The getaway box was for a quick
getaway if it wasn't working out.
You're kind of smart
for a handsome guy.
Yeah.
Is there anything else while
you're feeling confessional?
I sleep with a wave machine.
I can live with that.
who dining here
Um,
n-n-no one.
Yet.
See, it's been a long time since I've
made dinner, and I forgot about splatter.
And then...
I, uh, I forgot about
the part where, uh...
I really can't reach the splatter.
And, uh, so I guess I just...
created more work for you.
you haven't even tasted it yet.
Don't need to.
hey!
Hey!
Uh, can I officially
release artie lazar's name?
How are you always around?
I'm good at what i do.
Yeah, sure.
We're on the record.
So, um, am i in the club?
There is no club.
Oh, yeah.
I am in.
Hey.
Good work today.
Thanks.
I didn't mean to freeze you out.
I didn't mean for you
to meet heather that way.
No matter how I met her, I
wouldn't have liked it, so...
is that your dinner?
don't start.
I was gonna offer you some of mine.
Heather dropped off a casserole.
Of course she did.
What is it, tuna surprise?
Cassoulet.
Really? My favorite.
I know.
Ironic.
it's delicious.
eating dinner together is nice.
We never did it
when we were married.
We should have.
anyway, um, at least the
mayor will sleep well tonight.
The city will sleep well tonight.
Ooh lindsay, we got a hit on the prints
from the kiss me not killer's latest victim.
Her name was elaine lewis.
Her parents reported her missing from
silver springs, nevada, two weeks ago.
I'll call claire.
He took her across state lines.
That makes it federal.
The fbi is taking over the case.
It's not my call.
you could fight for me.
And it's not open for debate.
This is not personal, lindsay.
It is to me.
Tell heather thanks for dinner.