little some times she
falls asleep on my pillow
all those number37 not to get die
what cute
i already told to know
that's dangerous
the practise for the k word
cats?
kates ? more ? sex
once a month
are you talking to someone
about this ? issues
you can't even commit
a date!
because she'd rather be here
with sexy old me.
what do you got?
death amst the jacarandas.
neighbor heard a gunshot
about midnight and called it in.
was the shot
preceded by, say,
shouting or the unds
of a struggle?
only the lonesome call
of the whip-poor-will.
you were at the opera
again tonight, weren't you?
he gets in these moods.
ew. somebody meant business.
well, we can gather it wasn't
a carjacking. that's his car.
god, he's young.
yeah, 21.
already married.
ethan williams.
his driver's license says he
lived a half mile up the road.
he's a security guard
at pacific modern art gallery.
carried a gun--
all the good it did him.
employer probably
didn't bother to train him
how to use it.
so the killer disarmed him,
took the gun with him. smart.
you think he was shot
with his own gun?
well, we won't know
what kd of gun
he had on him.
retrieve bullet, and ?
(lindsay) are those
blood stains on that scarf?
yeah, i was gonna ride by the labe
and see if the blood
belonged to the victim.
or our killers.
what are we thinking?
ethan came here to meet
somebody and got ambushed?
or he was followed--
they ? his car
? following hime
pulled his gun...
things went south from there.
there was a scuffle.
killer lost his scarf.
maybe he was wounded. ethan got
a clean shot to the forehead.
uh, i'll be right back.
okay, we know nothing
fit to print,
so don't bother asking.
i wasn't going to ask. i was
going to offer information.
well, in that case,
offer away.
this park used to be totally
evil-drug-dealer infested.
then there was this whole
save-the-park campaign, a-and--
it got caned up, i know.
who do you think
did the cleaning?
oh, right, the police.
do you think
the dealers came back?
could be another one
of our ten possible theories.
maybe his cell records
will shed a little light.
i'll get rolling
on a subpoena.
looks like another
?
i love my job.
y at the hall.
i've gotta go notify
a very young widow.
yes?
good evening.
i'm inspector boxer.
this is inspector jacobi.
we're looking for
ethan williams' wife?
beth?
well, she's with ethan.
they went out for a walk
when he came home from work.
we're ethan's parents.
is everything okay?
i'm very sorry
to tell you,
uh, your son
was found dead.
he was shot and killed.
what about beth?
where is she?
oh, my god!
the baby.
they had a baby with them?
beth is
nine months pregnant.
±¾׳צה»½צ¹©ס§ן°½»בק£¬סן½ףדףתילעµףדם¾
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
womens.murder.club µת1¼¾µת5¼¯
-=זזאדנ׳צה»׳י=-
·­עכ£÷עאדמ
נ£¶פ£÷f.o.g.
ך±¼הצב£÷d&כיךף
found a scarf
at the crime scene.
ethan's parents said
that beth was wearing one
when they left.
it had blood on it.
search the whole park?
there was no body.
it looks like an abduction.
the car was abandoned,
and we found beth's purse
in her bedroom with 200 bucks
and credit cards inside.
so she didn't take off
on her own.
whoever killed him--
most likely took beth.
and there's only one reason
people are gonna abduct a woman
who's nine months pregnant.
somebody wants that baby.
beth williams, white female,
20 years old.
we believe she was taken
from hawthorne park
at approximately 11:00 p.m.
now until we find her
and her baby,
they are all you care about.
baker, martinez,
i want you guys to hit
the art gallery
where beth's husband worked.
you guys work the neighbors,
see if there was anybody
suspicious hanging around beth
or ethan in the last few days.
miller, recanvass
the park area,
and you look for video cameras
in a 10-block radius.
now this girl is stickin' out
to here. she'll be hard to miss.
inector boxer's gonna be
in the thick of things,
so i'm command central.
everybodgets o.t. tonigh
let's find her.
(officers speaking indistinctly)
you contact
the girl's parents?
they're both dead. she moved
here out of high school.
outside of her in-laws,
she's got nobody.
which is probably why
she was in such a hurry
to start a family of her own.
at least she's young,
white and pretty.
the media will help us.
what was that?
what?
that.
well you got married
soon.
you knew that.
well, yeah,
but th is really soon.
you know...
i liked
our invitations better.
they were less fancy.
gee, thanks.
make sure you notify
all the divisions.
our place is kind of small,
so ethan and beth would drive
to the park to take a walk,
you know, get...
get some privacy.
is it possible
they were buying drugs?
no. how can you
even ask me that?
have you seen
anyone unfamiliar
hanging around
the neighborhood lately?
had either of them
made any new friends?
i don't think so.
i mean, ethan was always
out working, you know,
either at the art gallery
or at the mall.
you know, they were trying
to save up for their own place.
how about beth?
was she working?
doctor told her  take it easy.
she had some bleeding early on.
but she wants to go to college
after the baby is born,
maybe be a nurse.
was beth already pregnant
when they got married?
uh-huh. they were married almost
a year when that happened.
it wasn't planned.
but they got used
to the idea real quick.
they were so excited about
that little baby girl.
find beth...
and my granddaught.
please.
just find them.
how's he doing?
eh. it's a hell
of a thing to lose a kid.
i told him to go home
and try to get some sleep.
you should grab
a couple of hours yourself.
this thing could drag on.
yeah, maybe later.
well,
i'll go make the coffee.
ethan called a bunch
of discount stores
looking for a good deal
on a crib.
okay. what's this call
at 10:00 last night?
somebody named consuelo ?.
she hasn't called me back.
okay, well, i need more
than that. i need a full name.
i need an address.
yeah, phone company couldn't
get us complete records
till start of business.
they're on their way over.
meantime,
i'm doin' the best i can.
hey, it's  a i
situation.
what did jacobi find out?
well, everyone at the gallery
seems to think that
ethan walked on water.
i'm sure jacobi will hear
the same story at the mall.
yeah, people have such nice
things to say about a dead man.
yeah, maybe this time
it's actually true.
yeah, what else you got?
was there anything useful?
okay, thanks for calling.
i set up a hotline
at the "register" web site.
goabout  calls so far.
let me guess--
beth was abducted by aliens.
either that or arab terrorists.
the crazies can't decide.
perfect timing.
here's the bullet.
how can you have such
a gross job and still be
more emotional stable
than the rest of us?
speak for yourself.
what's that, a .38?
i'm betting
it matches the .38
his company issued him
a few months ago.
make sure
you get it tested.
yeah. always do.
the preliminary
x screen came back.
our boy's clean.
he would've made a good papa.
you didn't check
for alcohol.
page three. he was sober.
somebody's snippish today.
did you check
under the nails for d.n.a.?
already at the lab.
i put a rush on it
how could anybody want a baby
so badly they'd kill fort?
god, you're young.
hey, i'm with her--
midnight feedings
and babysitters
or clubbing with my girls
and noisy sex
with my boyfriend.
when's the last time
we went clubbing?
we could.
you do realize that
if you don't have kids,
you'll have  grow old
without a lifetime supply
of funky homemade
ceramic pencil holders.
you love those pencil holders.
more than life itself.
what about you?
you want a little boxer baby?
i just want to find theirs.
they were married and in love,
their first baby on the way.
whole life was in front of 'em.
ethan was pretty nervous
about the baby.
poor guy barely had
any fingernails left.
chewed 'em to the quick.
but  w ay
into the dad thing.
their lamaze teacher's
business card.
it's pretty worn
around the edges.
looks like it's been in and out
of his wallet a lot.
"consuelo sanchez."
ms. 10:00-p.m. phone call.
did they have lamaze classes
when you were having kids?
you'd have to ask my ex-wife.
which wife--
one, two or three?
(laughs) i forget. what i do
remember is working overtime
for five years ?
i bet you were
a good father.
eh, i was a cop.
so do you think the kidnapper's
planning to keep
this baby for himself,
or is he planning
to sell it?
i don't know.
i just hope he waits
for beth to go into labor
before cutting her open.
hi, we're looking
for consuelo sanchez.
(woman) they were
a real sweet couple.
ethan would take off work
so he didn't miss any classes.
why did they call you
last night?
oh, beth was having
braxton hicks contractions.
i said take a walk.
it...
oh, god.
if they hadn't
gone for that walk,
this never would have happened.
it's not your fault,
but we do need to know
where you were last night.
uh, i was at my cousin's.
i can give you her number.
it's like there's
a black cloud over my class.
last week, one of my girls
gave birth to a stillborn.
she was nearly full-term.
did she know beth?
they always sat together.
what was her name?
i don't think she's up
for talking to cops right now.
tell me her name.
melanie topor.
she was gonna be
a single mom.
melanie topor?
what is that sound?
melanie?
san francisco police department.
we need to talk to you.
(woman) come in.
what do you want?
is there a baby here?
i don't have a baby.
my baby died.
i'm very sorry.
do you, uh, mind
if we look around?
i still have milk.
when i feel better,
i'm gonna take it
to the hospital
for the sick babies.
it shouldn't go to waste.
i have 15 bottles
in the freezer.
melanie...
we're investigating
the disappearance
of beth williams
and the murder
of ethan williams.
oh.
do you know anyone
who could have hurt them?
well, the tv said
beth was kidnapped
by somebody
who wanted her baby.
your lamaze teacher said that
you and beth were good friends.
she was, uh,
she was pretty lonely.
why do you say that?
well, she was cooped up
with ethan and his parents...
and then he found out
about her boyfriend.
beth had a boyfriend?
what was his name?
i don't know.
i met her after they split.
you don't think that
he was the one tt--
melanie, can you remember
anything she told you
about him?
this is very important.
i'm trying.
i think she said
that he was--
he was from saramon.
such a stupid thing
to remember.
th-that's fine.
can you remember
anything else?
she said that
he was handsome and exciting--
a lot more fun than ethan...
at first.
but then she got pregnant...
and did an amnio
and found out
that it wasn't his,
and he started
screamin' at her
for sleepin'
with her husband.
she said it was the first
and the last time
he ever hit her.
oh.
excuse me.
yeah?
hey. the blood work ? came back
it's placental blood
mixed with amniotic fluid.
okay, thanks.
beth's water broke
at the crime scene.
that was 11 hours ago.
if she's still alive,
she's in labor... now.
her husband works two jobs,
goes to lamaze classes,
and she goes cheatin' on him?
she got married too young.
she didn't have
her head on straight.
one day she's into safe.
next day she's into sexy.
she es her whole life
all mapped out for her
and decides
she doesn't like it.
so no perfect couple award
after all.
just once before i die
i would like to see a marriage
that really was
what i thought it was.
you know,
my first child,
i was only in labor
six hours.
that baby could be out
in the world already.
i'm not gonna accept that
as a possibility.
why?
because if the baby's
been born,
there's a chance we're not
looking for beth anymore.
we're looking for her corpse.
as long as beth is in labor,
she's probably safe.
yeah, why risk cutting
the baby out of her
when it's already coming out
the natural way?
there is another possibility.
beth and romeo
got back together.
they whack hubby and ride off ?
(lindsay) with hubby's baby?
i can't see boyfriend
raising another man's child.
?
she didn't meet him on the job.
she didn't have one.
there are other places
to meet men.
yeah, the hotline
got a couple of calls
that beth shopped at the market
on 7th and walnut--
a prime hookup spot.
do you know how many
of those hotline tips
actually lead somewhere real?
and yet i am checking out
each and every one of them
that don't involve martians
or o.j. simpson.
i'm gonna schedule
another press conference,
keep beth's face out there.
i'm gonna go torture
the in-laws some more.
something is up with her.
is something up with her?
baby cases.
cops hate baby cases.
ohh. yeah, that's right.
press conference is set
for half an hour.
here's a couple more
pictures you can use.
let me know if you need
anything else.
how's she doing...
with everything?
i worry about her.
she doesn't want
to be worried about.
yeah, i know, but...
why'd you take this job?
it's a big step up for me.
you had other opportunities,
better ones.
i hear you could have gone
and worked for the chief.
i wanted to work homicide.
you wanted an excuse
to be near her again.
i am marrying heather.
if you say so.
i can't believe
beth had an affair.
how could she do that
to our son?
did ethan know about it?
we believe so. he never said
anything to either of you?
he always protected us
from the bad stuff.
when he was a boy,
he didn't go to the hospital
till his appendix almost burst.
he didn't want to complain
about the pain.
techs found this
in the trash can
and put it back together.
to "beth williams."
return address "sam johannes."
i remember that.
you hardly ever get
handwritten letterthese days.
i asked beth who it was from.
she said an old friend.
you think that's the guy?
if he hurts my granddaughter,
i'll make that
son of a bitch pay.
no, i will.
according to jill,
sam did three years
for almost killing
a guy with a pool cue.
any chance
he's from san ramon?
you want everything.
so beth is one of those girls
who wants to marry mr. clean
but likes doing the nasty
with the nasty bs.
the story of my life.
who are you, clean or nasty?
(chuckles) sam johannes?
where is he?
(man) no, no, that was fine.
you can mark it.
hey, hey, hey, hey.
oh.
merry christmas.
nice.
(jacobi) sam johannes?
what?
you sam johannes?
where's beth williams?
i don't know
who you're talking about.
your girlfriend.
where is she?
where's the baby?
i need to talk to my lawyer.
he could be holding beth
prisoner somewhere.
we gotta talk to this
slimeball's coworkers...
got people on it.
and get in touch with his wife.
baker has people on that.
wellget him some help and go
through his credit cards.
who's this, his lawyer?
lindsay, lindsay, i need you
to take it easy, okay?
we're no longer married.
you're not allowed
to give me inane advice.
sure i can. i'm your boss.
you have to understand,
my client got screwed
by the cops once before.
we have a missing girl
whose water broke
at least 14 hours ago.
i can assure you sam had
nothing to do with it.
how do you know beth?
last time i talked
to you people,
i got three years in san q.
how long were you
sleeping with her?
(scoffs) that wasn't the nature
of their association.
what werthey doing,
playing parcheesi?
if this baby dies while
you're jerking me around,
i will make san q.
look like club med.
we got enough
to hold this guy?
sure, except for that
whole probable cause thing.
inspector jacobi?
sam's wife sachiko.
uh, ma'am, why don't we
go back to my desk?
beth williams was not
my husband's girlfriend.
then who was she?
you wanted
to adopt beth's baby?
before we go any further,
we need assurances that--
we met her on
an internet adoption site.
it's kind of an informal place
where pregnant women
can connect with people
who want to become parents.
beth didn't have a computer.she ?
we've been trying
for years to adopt
or even be foster parents,
but--
when you have a felony on
your record, no one wants you,
even if you've got
ten years sober,
and you've completely turned
did ethan know that beth
wanted to give up the baby?
yeah. we met
the both of them over coffee.
they were getting divorced.
i don't think either one of them
wanted to become
a single parent.
why'd she choose you?
she said she liked my e-mails.
and you offered them money,
too, right? how much?
don't answer that.
and that's why
you weren't talking,
because baby buying
is illegal.
it was only $15,000, and it was
to cover maternityxpenses.
totally legal.
depends on the contract.
which you sent beth
in the mail.
and she i.m.'ed us yesterday
that she'd signed it
and that ethan would, too,
as soon as he got home.
but then we never hed
from her again.
maybe you did.
maybe beth told you that they
had changed their minds,
and you weren't getting
the baby after all.
see? what'd i tell you
about cops?
is my client under arrest?
it would be better for you--
okay, let's get the hell
out of here. come on.
come on.
good luck.
sachiko, is there
anything else you could--
come on.
dale peterson.
beth and i were i.m.'ing
one day,
and she said she had a boyfriend
named dale peterson.
dale peterson from san ramon.
i'll start hunting him down.
meanwhile i'm gonna need--
computer hard drives
from beth's local library.
i'll draw up a subpoena
and track down
our resident geek.
(cindy) here we go.
somebody at the library
logged in to pacificbaby.net.
talk about creepy. any old
pervert could log on here
and say he's
an adoptive couple.
find some
vulnerable pregnant woman
and invite her to some...
who knows.
this job is bad for my head.
okay. sam johannes
chatted with "bw20."
beth williams, 20 years old.
this is from 9:30 last night.
bw20 says,
"we'll bring you the contract
first thing tomorrow."
(jill) "i can't tell you
how happy this makes us."
so sam the man and sachikoko
were telling the truth.
(telephone rings)
wait a minute. why didn't beth
tell her good friend melanie
that she's putting her baby
up for adoption?
(ring)
jill bernhardt.
she probably felt weird
about giving up the baby ?
you know, salt in the wound.
wa a minute. is there
anything from what's his name--
dale peterson?
uh, not yet.
got it. gotta move.
what is it?
that was lindsay.
dale peterson
is not from san ramon.
he lives onthe "san ramon."
it's a boat.
i have about five minutes to
push through a search warrant.
(typing)
(lindsay) this place
is certainly a step up
from her in-laws'.
yeah. she meets an adventurer
who lives on the high seas...
hell, i'd run away
with him, too.
dale petson?
san francisco p.d.
we have a warrant.
you smell that?
yeah. bleach.
(lindsay)
somebody's been cleanin'.
not a very good job.
mnh-mnh.
lindsay... we got a knife.
you think we're looking
at another homicide?
i think either way,
beth had her baby.
still no leads
on dale peterson.
no permanent place
employment.
what do you think he did
with beth after...
we're sending down divers
just in case.
i'm gonna hit the marina
and see if anybody saw dale,
beth or a very newborn baby.
all right, keep me posted.
how could anyone do this?
actually, homicide is
a leading cause of death
of pregnant women.
oh, my god.
if you want to kill someone,
at least shoot them.
don't slice them open
with a fish knife.
it's possible he just
used the knife to cut
the baby's umbilical cord.
why go to all that trouble
for a baby that isn't even his?
maybe dale thought beth lied
and the baby really was his.
we found the placenta.
that's it. no kids.
i mean it.
you don't have to
give birth on a boat.
ugh.
was the baby born alive?
no way to know.
what?
(cindy) hey, i got
a hotline tip that a--
forget the damn hotline.
that a pregnant girl
used to hang out
at some bar by the pier
with a guy who lived on a boat.
so i've been making
the rounds, and, uh,
guess who's trying
to pick up a young hottie
at the lucky badger?
dale peterson. you wait.
i'm on my way.
i'll keep saying it.
i have no idea
what happened to this baby.
you want me to say it
in french, spanish...
she was born on your boat.
if i could help you guys,
i would.
i've got nothing against beth.
i think she's a great girl.
a little screwed up,
but who isn't?
when's the last time
you saw her?
i broke up with her...
must be months ago.
we hear she broke up with you
because you like
to hit pregnant women.
that's not my style.
okay, she kicked me in the nads
when i told her it was over.
but i never touched her.
you were pissed
the baby wasn't yours.
are you kidding?
i was thrilled.
look...
beth was a small-town girl
that i met on the pier one day
listening to street musicians.
i invited her to my boat.
we had a good time
for a few months there.
i figured she was looking
for a little break
from her boring life.
i am sorry if she
was hoping for more.
her blood is
all over your boat.
great. i haven't been home
in three days.
i never go there on
the weekends,
and she knows that.
maybe i should go in there.
hey, she's doing great.
she's a pro.
where were you last night
from 9:00 p.m. on?
that's my business.
my partner is still
on your boat.
i can just give him a call
and tell him
to tear the place apart.
i was with a friend.
i travel in a lot
of different circles.
this one's a little more,
uh, pacific heights.
uh-huh. what's your
lucky friend's name?
all right, see, that's where
i'm kind of stuck.
um, she provides me with the
wherewithal to
maintain my lifestyle.
and unfortunately, she's,
uh, she's a little shy, so.
shy because
she doesn't exist.
we've got you cold on
beth's murder, and you know it.
whatur main concern is
right now is this baby girl.
so if you could just
tell us where she is
and ease
her grandparents' minds,
i'm sure we can
work out a deal.
i'm a pretty laid-back guy...
but i don't like it
when chicks try to hustle me.
is that what beth did to you?
even chicks as sexy as you.
what did you do
with the baby?
honey, if you want a baby,
i'll give you one.
whoo!
get up!
you want to mess with me?
wow.
boxer. boxer!
you're not gonna tell me
where this kid is?
you gonna hit me?
get the hell off me!
boxer! lindsay, hey!
back off. back off.
where is that baby?
i can handle it. back off!
back--back off!
you back--come on. come on.
where the hell is that baby?
boxer? is that your name?
yeah, i want the videotapes,
'cause i'm pressin' charges.
you just made me
a millionaire, baby!
get off me!
what the hell
did you do that for?
are you kidding me?
i was about to break him--
in half, which doesn't help!
now we still don't know
if the baby is alive or dead.
lindsay, calm down.
calm d--god, i am so glad
i'm not married to you anymore.
you and me both.
maybe jacobi ought to take
the lead on this one.
maybe jacobi should take the lead
on the entire department!
lindsay.
how could you--
lindsay?
what?
luke just called from the e.r.
somebody droed off
a baby girl.
you're sure nobody saw
the baby being dropped off?
are we sure
it's beth's baby?
uh, shwas found
in a fishing tackle box
by the back maintenance door.
i don't suppose anybody was
careful about fingerprints?
i didn't think so.
here's
your little princess.
is she okay?
yeah. her attending says
she's doing great.
oh, she's actually
kind of beautiful.
???
you can touch her.
no, thanks.
stop! sir, ma'am, i--
thank you.
you can't come in here
dressed like that.
is that her?
you're not dressed properly.
please, we just need
to see our child.
i'm sorry.
you don't understand.
we're the family.
we'd like to see
our child. thank you.
please don't interre.
sam.
uh, why don't we just
go in the hall?
let's just
go out in the hall.
that baby
is legally ours.
actually, she's not.
her mother agreed to it.
r lawyer says
the birth mother's wishes--
you don't have
a signed contract.
the grandparents' claim
is preeminent.
how'd you know
the baby was here?
um, we read it
on the internet...
on some tv station
web site.
when?
maybe a half an hour ago.
my boss gave the media
the information 15 minutes ago
before that, no one knew.
okay, so it was
15 minutes ago.
you want
another trip downtown?
some woman
called my cell phone
about an hour ago
and told us the baby
was at the hospital.
you didn't recognize her voice?
no.
give me your phone.
we just didn't want things
to get complicated.
give me your phone. now.
i didn't call anybody.
you used t payphone
right down the block.
that's not too bright.
i-i didn't.
what happened to beth, melanie?
what'd you do to her?
nothing. that's crazy.
tell me why we shouldn't believe
that you killed beth and ethan
and stashed the baby
somewhere.
these weren't for
sick babies, were they?
they were for beth
and ethan's baby.
but you panicked,
and you dumped
the baby at the hospital.
no, you got it all wrong.
that's not what--
you're under arrest.
that not why i took
the baby there.
i...i don't know
what happened.
she was scared.
she asked me for my help.
she said it was best
for the baby.
she?
no!
beth!
get back.
get out.
just calm down, all right?
nobody has to get hurt today.
out! out of the room!
all right. all right.
now just calm down.
you, too. get out.
it's okay.
i got it.
i said get out.
drop your gun.
a lot of people
have been looking for you.
shut up. drop it.
okay.
god. don't make me
shoot you.
okay. just calm down,
all right?
look. see?
is that your husband's gun?
oh...
is that the one
you shot him with?
i was just trying
to scare him.
the gun went off.
you were mad at him.
he said that he would sign
the adoption papers.
he promised me,
but...
then he wouldn't do it.
and then your water broke,
and you knew
the baby was coming,
and you didn't know
what to do.
i just--i just.
i just wanted to be free,
go somewhere, you know?
like, start all over again
without--
without ethan or dale
or the baby or anybody.
why not just give ethan
the baby and go?
why give him anything?
he was breaking up with me,
and i needed the money
so i could start fresh.
so the gun went off,
and you panicked.
and i couldn't go anywhere.
i didn't go
to the hospital.
they'd find me.
and you delivered that baby
all by yourself?
i was so scared.
then the baby
started crying,
and i had to get her
to the hospital.
i knew melanie would help.
she's my only frie.
are they coming here?
my partner
probably called them.
beth, why don't you
just give me the gun?
no.
no. i'm leaving.
beth--
i'll shoot you.
do you want to know
how your daughter is?
doctors say she's doing fine.
beth, you could've dropped
that baby into the ocean.
it certainly would have been
a lot safer r you.
but you didn't.
you took her to the hospital.
you did a great job
of bringing your baby
into this world.
no! no!
you okay?
i'm fine.
???
you know the media's
not allowed to take pictures
up here.
shh. shh, shh, shh.
i'm just saying...
don't let us stop you.
luke never sees
that picture.
oh, come on.
you look adorable.
hey.
this little girl looks like
she's about ready to go home.
shh.
wherever that is.
she belongs
with her grandparents.
hey.
sweetie.
oh.
oh, my gosh.
oh, look at her.
oh, sweetie.
oh, my gosh.
excuse me. would you mind
if i took a picture?
no.
you are so beautiful.
oh, sweetie.
shh, shh, shh, shh.
you done good.
oh, sweetie.
a murdered father,
mother in jail...
she's gonna have a lot
to deal with growing up.
well, she's got two people
in her life
who care more about her
than anything in the world.
i'd say that's a good place
to start.
oh.
i'm guessing
you need a drink.
i just want to go home
to my dog.
hi.
hello, tom.
lieutenant.
whatever.
i got some good news.
i got that slimeball dale
to back off.
he's not gonna sue.
thanks, tom.
that is good news.
not the brightest bulb.
told him i'd arrest him
for obstructing justice,
and he bought it.
thanks, tom.
that is good news.
but you could have called
and told me over the phone.
uh, i just thought
i would...
come by and see
if you were okay.
i'm fine. how are you?
you lookin' forward
to the b wedding?
okay.
okay, i just thought--
all's well that ends well?
linz, i'here
if you want to talk.
i don't.
okay.
look...
lots of first pregnancies
don't work out.
ours didn't.
and that's nobody's fault.
nobody is a failure.
it just happens.
yeah, i know.
and it was four years ago.
yeah, and we both went back
to work three days later.
sure as hell
beats staying home.
i need
to take martha for a walk.
working this case
with you today--
i don't know--
i'm--you think that you've
put something away,
and then you realize...
that it's still with you.
i'm goa go.
you know...
i read
in a magazine somewhere that...
the japanese
have a ceremony...
when what happened to us
happens.
there's, uh, music
and--and toys...
and, uh...
hey, hey.
pretty little umbrellas
and...
the, uh, the parents
ask for the spirits
to take their baby
to a better world.
a better world.
that sounds nice.
tom...
זזאדנ׳צה»׳י
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
»¶ף­¼ףטכ