Previously on "Battlestar Galactica":
l have a message for you.
The fruit borne of two peoples
is alive.
A child named after the wife and sister
of the all-knowing Zeus.
Hera lives.
That's not true.
l don't suppose you'll tell me what this is
about. What's so important about this kid?
She may very well
be the shape of things to come.
The Cylons knew
where we were gonna be.
(both talk at once)
This is the map that l drew for you.
l gave this to you in your tent.
You were gonna burn it.
She offered to do it for you.
I... l want to explain.
He said he'd kill you.
- Who said it?
- One of the Brother Cavils.
This is Kacey.
Kacey, this is Kara.
Your mother.
Our people attack the air base,
detention centre, power station.
The plan is to sow chaos
the moment Galactica and Pegasus arrive.
No Pegasus, just Galactica.
These are your orders. Take the civilian
fleet and wait for me for 18 hours.
If l'm not back in 18 hours
then find Earth.
You know the mission. You should also
know there's only one way that it ends,
and that's with the successful rescue
of our people off of New Caprica.
Good hunting.
Hoshi's working on updating our map
coordinates for the search for Earth.
Civilian captains want to meet with you.
They have questions, problems.
Talk to me, Lee.
l'm having trouble...
accepting this.
l know.
But we have to push forward,
keep the fleet together,
find Earth.
- That's our duty.
- There's still a chance they'll come back.
Your father has pulled off
more than a few miracles in his day.
l know that.
And l haven't given up hope.
Yes, you have.
l saw the look on your face
when you came back from Galactica,
like you were
never gonna see him again.
Am l that easy to read?
Just to me.
He's taking on too much
for one half-strength battlestar to handle.
That's not opinion,
that's military fact.
He's not coming back from this.
None of them are.
All we can do
is make plans for the future.
We have to survive.
We have to find Earth. If we don't, there'll
be no one to remember William Adama,
or a battlestar named Galactica.
That is our charge to keep.
To keep humanity going,
no matter what the cost, no matter...
no matter who we leave behind.
You can do this.
You can get us there.
You are commander of this fleet
and you will guide us to safety.
And you will do it,
no matter the cost,
because you're an Adama.
Did l say how proud l am
to serve with you?
Not in so many words, no.
Well, l am proud to serve with you,
Lieutenant.
And to call you my wife.
Now, let's talk about map coordinates,
meeting with ships' captains.
l lost three men. If that sergeant wasn't
on her game, they'd have killed us all.
l know, godsdammit! You don't have to
keep running your mouth about it. l get it.
Get this. If Sharon had been killed, not
only would we not get the launch keys,
but the Cylons would know
we were in direct contact with Galactica.
This whole plan - the fate of
this whole city - would have fallen apart.
- Do you understand that, Colonel?
- l get it.
Good.
Hey.
You know
what has to be done here.
You don't want to do it. l understand.
But believe me, someone is gonna do this.
Now, it would be better
for her sake if it was you.
l had to do it, Saul.
l had to.
It was all for you.
And l want you to know
that l would've done anything to save you.
l know. It's all right.
Everything's gonna be all right.
No, you don't understand.
l got you out of detention, Saul.
It was me.
l got you out.
l went to see them - the Cylons.
l finally got to the one in charge.
And l got him to notice me
the way men notice me.
l slept with him.
l felt like puking every time
he put his filthy hands on me,
but l smiled and l faked it
to save you, Saul.
But you listen to me.
l'd do it again.
Frak anybody, do anything.
Even give them the map.
l didn't want anybody to be killed.
l could use a drink.
You've always been there for me
when l need you.
Oh, l'm exhausted.
l feel like l could just curl up here.
l should have listened to you, Saul.
l should have stayed on Galactica.
Don't worry about any of that now.
You just...
- You just go to sleep.
- l'm sleepy.
l love you,
do you hear me?
(sobs)
l mean, l've told you and l've told you,
but to what end?
Too secure
in your smug superiority to listen.
Too comfortable
in your predictions of success
to even consider
the possibility of defeat.
And where are we now?
More to the point,
where's Laura Roslin?
Where's Tom Zarek?
At large.
Whereabouts unknown.
Free, at any rate.
Probably with Colonel Tigh, solidifying
the insurgency's hold over the public.
What would you have us do, Gaius?
Leave.
Pack up your Centurions...
and go.
Please. Go.
And then what? What would you do
if we really just left you here?
Live your lives in peace and never trouble
yourself with thoughts of us again?
Or would you raise your children
with stories of the Cylon?
Mechanical slaves who once
did your bidding, only to turn against you.
Killers who committed genocide
against your race.
And occupiers of this city
until we just ran away.
Would you tell them to tell the story
to their children?
And to their children's children?
Nurse a dream of vengeance
through the years,
so that one day they could just go out into
the stars and hunt the Cylon once more.
Blood for blood.
It has to stop one day.
(distant explosions)
Oh, my gods.
Nice job, Anders.
Come on. Come on.
(siren wails)
OK, that's our cue.
You know what to do.
Rally your people
and get them to the evac points.
Remember the drills and you'll do fine.
Go with the gods. Go! Go! Go!
- Tory, tell Laura l can't thank her...
- Tell her yourself when this is all over.
l wish we were all
as calm as she is.
- Get them to their ship. Go!
- (man) Yes, ma'am.
Come on!
Quick, quick!
Let's move!
Let's move! Let's move!
This is it. We get to the detention centre
and we do not stop until everybody is free.
Everybody knows the rescue points.
Let's load up and we move, right now.
Let's move! Let's go!
Decoy squadron
approaching launch point.
(Kat) OK, this is it, guys.
Stand by.
All Vipers, break...
now, now, now!
Deploy drones on my mark.
Three, two, one.
Mark!
The drone signatures match.
The Cylons should pick up their drones on
DRADIS and read them as two battlestars.
Hey.
For nothing.
- All for nothing.
- We'll start over, Gaius.
A new city
to rise out of the ashes.
It'll be buried.
Buried like the cities of old,
consumed by the wrath of God.
Two battlestars
just jumped into orbit.
Adama's back.
Kat, Racetrack. Two baseships
on DRADIS, bearing 002, carom 015.
- They're launching Raiders.
- Red squadron, Kat. We've done our part.
Kick in the turbos
and let's get the hell out of here!
- (Starbuck) What's going on?
- Insurgents. l'll be back.
- You cannot leave us here.
- It's safest here.
No!
Let's go! Let's go!
- Tom, head to the shipyard.
- You're coming?
My ship's up there.
You sure have a sense of the dramatic.
Hey, wait. Laura. Wait.
You're on Galactica, right? Keep an eye
on her. Don't let her out of your sight. Go!
- See you up there.
(man) Jump preparation complete.
My board is green.
Ready to jump, sir.
- Stand by to launch blue squadron.
- This is the admiral.
All hands,
brace for turbulence.
Baseships just closed on the battlestar
targets. There's no Galactica, no Pegasus.
Drones.
Decoys.
- The whole thing's a trick.
- Where's Galactica?
Altitude 99,000,
falling like a rock.
- Launch! Launch them all!
- Stand by, FTL.
- (man) Clear for launch.
- Well, this ought to be different.
- They're clear!
- Stand by!
Jump!
Vipers!
Everybody, hold! Hold!
Hotdog, Redwing, l see friendlies
pinned outside the shipyard.
Roger. Redwing, target the tower.
l've got the gate. Pulling in hard.
(Chief) Incoming!
That's it! Let's go!
Let's go! Go! Go!
Let's go! Go!
Move! Move!
Godsdammit.
Come on! Move! Move, move!
Move! Let's go! Come on!
Move! Move, move, move!
- Fire in the hole!
- (woman) Fire in the hole!
Everybody, let's move!
To the shipyard!
Move! Move! Hustle!
Kara. Oh, gods!
No, no!
l'm gonna get you out of here.
Make damage report to Combat.
Batteries, report weapons status.
DRADIS?
Back online.
Cylon baseships
are coming out of the nebula.
Just as we expected.
Cylon Raiders are still scattered.
They're coming after us
without fighter cover.
If we draw the basestars away from
the planet, the Colonists may escape.
Hang on. Two more baseships
just jumped into orbit.
We got four baseships out there,
Admiral.
We can't hold off four.
Pass up the cord!
- Hold still.
- Connect the other side right away.
We lost thrusters.
We can't take more hits to port
or we're looking at decompressions
in sections 36 to 48.
Jump drives?
Then that's it.
It's been an honour.
Galactica, Pegasus. Let us take
some of this work off your hands.
Get your FTL ready
and we'll take care of the rest.
- Fire up that main battery!
- (man) Roger that!
Damn you, Lee.
Keep working on those FTLs.
Get 'em online!
The Cylons will redeploy
as soon as they recover.
Thank you, Lee.
(Dualla) They're coming about
to bracket us.
Steady as she goes.
Take us right into the centre.
- We won't last long in there.
- No.
(Starbuck) Put me down!
Put me down!
- Stop, stop! Put me down.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Shh! Shh!
Kara, shh.
- Is it really you?
- It's really me, but we don't have time.
We're going to the ships and we're
gonna get off this frakking planet.
- Where's Kacey?
- Who's Kacey?
- Kacey. She's my daughter.
- Kara, who's Kacey?
- She's my daughter!
- Kara, no! Kara!
Godsdammit! Kara, no!
Out of the way!
Come on!
Godsdammit, Kara, no!
We've lost control of the situation
on the surface.
There's a Heavy Raider standing by
ready to evacuate us.
We're agreed.
Evacuate the entire facility.
l'll stay behind
and set off the nuke.
(explosions continue outside)
You should go as well, Caprica.
And you.
l don't think you'll want to be here after
we've gone. There's a place for you too.
For me?
Well, you were right and we were wrong.
There should be some reward for that.
Gaius, we should go.
l just want to sit here and die.
You're gonna get your wish, Gaius.
The ships are getting off the ground.
They're jumping away.
Only a few left now. FTL's back online.
Pegasus is taking a hell of a pounding.
l don't think she has a plane in the air.
Lee left all his planes
to guard the civilian ships.
He knew this was a one-way trip.
He'll evac before the end.
- You sure?
- Land our birds!
Let's get the hell out of here.
(Helo) All wings, Galactica. Come home.
Landings authorised. Repeat, come home.
All hands, all hands,
get ready to jump.
- l believed in you.
- Whoa, whoa. Gaeta.
l believed in the dream
of New Caprica.
- Gaeta, we all did.
- No! No.
Not him. He believed in
the dream of Gaius Baltar.
The good life - booze, pills,
hot and cold running interns.
He led us to the apocalypse and...
and l turned out to be...
(Baltar) An idealist.
There's no sin in that.
Everything you say about me is true.
Every word.
But you have to listen to me.
The Cylons have a nuke
in this complex.
Nobody, and l mean nobody, is getting off
this planet alive unless l stop D'Anna.
- She'll kill you.
- Then she'll kill me.
Or it can be down to Mr Gaeta.
Either way,
the human race dies with me.
(Number Six) Gaius.
Go ahead, shoot.
What are you waiting for?
Please.
l'm begging you, please.
You have one chance to put things right,
do you understand me?
Get the frak out of here!
Stop that nuke!
- Go!
- Gaius, let's go!
(Apollo) Set main batteries to autofire,
cycle B. Lock engines ahead flank.
This is the commander. Abandon ship,
abandon ship. All hands, abandon ship.
Report to evac Raptors
and jump to rendezvous point.
Good work
and l'll see you on the other side.
All right, people, let's move.
Out! Let's go!
You too, Commander.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Kacey!
Kacey, honey,
where are you?
Kace...
l knew you'd be back.
l saw it.
Come here, Kacey.
- Say the words.
- Let me take her.
- Say them.
- What words?
You know what l want. l want to hear you
say them. And l want the rest of it.
Just like l told you.
Fine.
You win.
l love you.
Say it again.
Now the rest.
Was it everything
you thought it would be?
That and more.
l'll never forget this moment.
Neither will I.
l'll explain later.
Let's move.
- Are you sure she's in here?
- Positive. l saw her go in.
(baby cries)
Frakking liar!
(baby continues to cry)
It's her, Gaius.
The first of God's new generation.
Hera.
Shh, shh, shh.
It's a miracle.
God spared her.
- (baby cries)
- Shh.
Hera.
Can l hold her?
(Number Six) No.
She won't set off the nuke,
not any more.
Come on, Gaius.
We have to go.
Let's go.
- (man #1) All aboard.
- (man #2) Check up front.
All right.
l'm ready to go.
People, let's go. This way. Stand on the
deck until we can get you to new ships.
Come on, people, all the way down.
All the way down, people. Let's go!
Oh, my gods.
Captain?
- l thought you were dead.
- Yeah, so did I.
- Who is this?
- Yeah, l was gonna ask that myself.
- (Starbuck) This is...
- Kacey?
Kacey!
Oh, my little girl!
Mommy missed you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
When the Cylons took her,
I... l thought...
But you saved her.
Gods bless you.
- (man) Thank you, sir.
- Welcome aboard. Welcome.
Welcome aboard.
- l guess you didn't understand my orders.
- Never could read your handwriting.
(Tigh) Permission
to come aboard, sir?
Hey.
Permission granted.
You did it.
You brought 'em home, Saul.
Not all of them.
- l'm sorry.
- (crowd chants "Adama")
(crowd continues to chant)
We're still double-checking
the fleet's manifests, but...
it doesn't look like Maya
made it off of New Caprica.
What about the baby?
l was there when the two guards left
to take them to their ship.
l don't know what happened.
l'm so sorry.
l let you down and l know that.
No, you didn't.
It's not your fault.
This is bigger than us.
This is life.
(PA) All procedure support teams,
stand by for ship assignments.
All procedure support teams,
More religion.
Your soul is mine.