Previously on "Battlestar Galactica":
(Adama) Leoben's a very clever Cylon.
He's gonna try to get into your head.
We haven't been properly introduced.
l'm Leoben.
(Starbuck) l want
the Cylon interrogated.
Do it.
This has happened before.
And all of it will happen again.
Your destiny has already been written.
Assaulted, Miss Thrace.
A lot of old fractures from childhood.
Children of abusive parents often fear
passing that abuse to their own children.
Get out!
l'm trying to help you, Kara. l only want
you to see the truth of your life.
The reason you suffered.
The reason you struggled for so long.
Was there something to what Leoben
said about you and a special destiny?
Kara Thrace and her special destiny?
That sounds like
a bad cover band, Sam.
(Adama) l think the nova does look like
the mandala inside this temple.
Maybe it was a road sign. Show
me the direction it's headed to next.
(Helo) l'm curious about something.
Those paintings you did
from your apartment on Caprica.
This... was on the temple.
Where did you get the idea to paint yours?
That's something l've been doodling
since l was a kid. l liked the pattern.
(Helo) Well... they built the temple
4,000 years ago.
- What is it?
- Just something Leoben said once.
That l had a destiny.
That it had already been written.
What's up?
Nothing. Go back to sleep.
You're up early.
You too.
Yeah.
Hera gets these nightmares.
Wakes up crying and shaking.
By the time we calm her down
and get her to sleep, l'm wide awake.
All that crap she went through on
New Caprica really left its mark on her.
l know how she feels. l wish you'd never
shown me that picture of that mandala.
l dream about it and that bastard Leoben
every godsdamn night.
l feel like l'm losing my mind here.
You know, Kara, there's a, um...
psychiatrist aboard Inchon Velle.
We've made an appointment for Hera.
Think about seeing her.
Are you kidding me? Most shrinks are
more frakked up than their patients are.
You know, you might want to check out
that Oracle camped in Dogsville.
People say she interprets dreams.
Sees things in them. Predicts events.
Hey.
You OK?
l don't know.
Hello? (clears throat)
(woman) The goddess Aurora.
Take it. It's yours.
- What the hell am l gonna do with this?
- You'll know when the time comes.
Sit.
I, uh...
l can't sleep.
- Having these nightmares.
- About the Cylon.
The one who held you captive
on New Caprica.
Leoben.
He was just...
He knows you better than
you know yourself... Kara Thrace.
He sees the truth about you.
About your destiny.
You don't...
Enough of that.
The only destiny l have
is as a world-class frak-up.
Who hurts everyone
she cares about.
That was your mother's gift to you,
wasn't it?
You were born to a woman who believed
suffering was good for the soul,
so you suffered.
Your life is a testament to pain.
You want to believe it because
it means that you're bad luck.
You're like a cancer
that needs to be removed.
Because you hear her voice every day.
(Leoben) And you want her to be right.
Somebody told you
what Leoben said to me.
Did you ever tell anyone about that?
You learned the wrong lesson
from your mother, Kara.
You confused the messenger
with the message.
Your mother was trying
to teach you something else.
You don't know crap
about my mother.
Leoben does.
He sees the patterns,
sees how it all fits together.
- Shut up.
- He's coming for you.
Soon.
Shut the frak up.
You can't stop him.
And he will show you the way.
l'm on a shuttle in a half an hour.
Ask for your leave, come with me.
You could use the downtime.
It sounds tempting.
So do it. No strings, OK? We don't even
have to talk about our relationship.
l'll think about it.
Which means no.
(sighs)
You know, l hate to say this, but that
whack-job oracle... she's got a point.
Your mother frakked up your head
long before Leoben ever got to you.
She was dealing with a lot, Sam.
She told me that l was
different from other kids,
that l needed to be a warrior, like her.
Taught me that fury gets you killed.
And anger keeps you alive.
Well, she gave you plenty
to be angry about, didn't she?
Split your head open with a broom
because you didn't make your bed.
- l ever tell you how l got back at her?
- No.
In the first Cylon war, she was stationed
with the first marines on Medra.
Stinking jungles you wouldn't believe.
Had this phobia of insects
for the rest of her life.
Hated the damn things.
So l go out and l buy a bunch of
rubber bugs and l slip into her closet...
and l put 'em all over her shoes.
And?
She screamed her frakking head off.
l go in...
and she's trying to smash them
with her shoes.
But that's just making 'em
bounce around even more.
You must have caught hell for that.
She grabbed my hand, held it in
the doorjamb, and slammed the door.
Frak me.
It was worth it, though.
(Hotdog) lt's "Galactica". We had some
valve failures. We're restarting the unrep.
(Dualla) Great. Hotdog, settle in. We're
gonna be out for another three hours.
Hotdog, what the hell are you doing?
Enjoying blue skies again. About
the only thing l miss about New Caprica.
Galactica, Starbuck. Showtime.
Bogey. My right one,
in the soup at 45. Committing.
Starbuck, Hotdog. No joy. Press.
Abort the unrep.
Unhook those fuel lines immediately.
Refuelling ships, Galactica. Immediate.
Cease all under-way replenishment ops.
We've got both Starbuck and Hotdog
on DRADIS, but no contact on the bogey.
We're lucky we can see anything.
That planet's synchrotron radiation
has been kicking the crap out of every
DRADIS in the fleet since we got here.
Price you pay for a good place
to hide and refuel the fleet.
Looks like it's also a good place
for hiding a Cylon Raider.
Starbuck, Apollo.
What have you got?
Apollo, we got one turkey playing
hide-and-seek in the clouds. No sparrows.
Engaging offensive.
One heavy Raider.
No fighter escort.
(Gaeta) Still no bandits on DRADIS.
If that bastard jumps,
the Cylons could be all over us in minutes.
Alert the fleet to stand by for a jump.
Starbuck, Hotdog.
No visual on the Raider! l'm losing you!
Dammit. Starbuck, blind!
l say again! l lost you in the clouds!
(Hotdog) Starbuck, we have no DRADIS
on your bogey. Do you have visual?
Affirmative.
He just ducked into the storm system.
(Hotdog) Do you see him?
Do you see him?
Galactica, Starbuck.
Tally. Weapons hot.
Took a hit but still flying.
- (Hotdog) Starbuck, where did you go to?
- l'll be on him in a few seconds.
- Where the hell is that Raider?
- (Gaeta) Sir.
Starbuck's close to the hard deck.
The atmospheric density could
keep her from reaching orbit again.
Then the pressure will crush her
like a cheap soda can.
(Apollo) Starbuck, you're getting too low.
Break off and climb.
l repeat. Starbuck, you're getting too low.
Starbuck.
Pull out before you don't have
to smash to regain orbit.
You got to come in.
Where the hell is she going?
Get outta there.
(Apollo) Starbuck, come in. Do you read?
You're getting too low.
- Get up.
- (Apollo) Have you a visual on Starbuck?
Starbuck, come in! Do you read?
Starbuck! Pull up!
That is an order. Pull out!
Apollo, Starbuck. Wilco!
Come on!
- Where'd l take the hits, Chief?
- Looks like nowhere, Captain.
What? l felt the impact.
Damn Viper felt like
it hit a brick wall.
Well, we'll keep checking,
but so far not a scratch.
(Starbuck) It has to be there.
Run it again.
- We've watched it twice.
- Then this isn't my film.
(Sharon) No one else
pulled a trigger all day.
We checked Galactica's DRADIS records.
There was no paint on your Cylon.
And we all know that DRADIS
can be wonky near this planet.
Maybe the Raider jumped away
before you fired.
Or maybe it never existed
to begin with.
It was there.
Gonna ground her?
Karl says she's physically fit,
but an emotional basket case.
In peacetime, he'd ground us all.
So it falls back on you.
Yeah.
Even screwed up,
she's still the best Viper driver l've got.
Sometimes it's hard to admit
that the best of us... can burn out.
Do you think she has?
l don't know.
l think her identity as a steely-eyed Viper
jock is the only thing holding her together.
So if l ground her...
Everyone gets rattled sometimes.
But the bottom line is...
when the bullets start to fly...
can she handle it?
So where do you want to go
when you bite the big one?
l want to go right there.
Next to Kat.
A water-walking Viper jock.
A royal pain in the ass,
but a hell of a stick to have on your wing.
You can put me right here.
Next to Duck and Nora.
Good card players.
Nice way to spend eternity.
Whoever croaks first, the other one makes
sure their picture goes in the right place.
Deal?
Deal.
So what did the old man have to say
about my combat report?
"Starbuck's finally gone off the deep end.
Unfit for duty."
He said l'm the CAG.
It's my call.
Ah.
And what do you say?
l say l trust your eyes over DRADIS
any day of the week.
Something could have been there,
vanished in the cloud cover.
So you don't think l'm nuts?
l didn't say that.
You're a raving lunatic.
As demented and deranged
as the first day l met you.
And you're a bastard.
Look, um...
stress has made us all twitchy.
After what that Cylon put you through
on New Caprica,
you've had more than your share.
Get some rest...
or you will start seeing things.
Yeah.
(Adama) That leaves
six civvies in line to refuel.
- (Roslin) In another ten hours we're done.
- Yeah.
Starbuck?
- What do you hear?
- Nothing but the rain.
Well, then grab your gun
and bring in the cat.
Wilco, Admiral.
- Madam President.
- Captain. How is it out there?
- Hell of a view.
- (Adama) We're almost to the finish line.
Then we can jump the hell
outta this system.
So say we all.
Um... Actually...
Sorry. Boss.
l have something for you.
l thought that it would be a nice
figurehead for your model ship.
Aurora. Goddess of the dawn.
Yeah. She brings the morning star
and a fair wind.
A fresh start.
Thank you.
- Good hunting.
- Thank you.
(Chief) Harness assembly?
Lap and shoulder retaining pins installed.
Retraction reel correct.
Disconnect block locking indicator,
yellow flag visible.
(gasps)
You all right, Captain?
Uh...
Give me a minute here, Chief.
(screaming)
(Chief) Major.
She's just sitting there.
Did you talk to her?
You talk to her.
Feeling sorry for me?
Kara.
Everyone gets rattled.
Even the best.
l'm not going back out there.
l don't trust myself.
Hm.
So trust me.
l'll fly your wing.
The CAG flying my No.2?
Whatever it takes.
How are things with you and Dee?
Uh...
You know. Good.
No.
Better than good.
Best they've ever been.
l'm happy for you.
Really.
It's funny, though,
after all we've been through...
we are right back where we started.
You're CAG and l am
your hotshot problem pilot.
l guess that's all
we'll ever be now, huh?
Starbuck, Apollo.
How we doing?
Copacetic.
Another 30 minutes
and we head back for the barn.
Dammit. Apollo! One turkey, my right.
Level and ten, ducking in and out
of the clouds. Engaging.
Starbuck, Apollo. No joy.
Starbuck, Galactica.
No DRADIS contact on your Cylon.
Apollo. Starbuck.
Weapons hot. Committing.
This time l'm gonna drag him back and
dump his sorry ass on the hangar deck.
Set the fleet at condition one.
Uncouple the hoses.
Starbuck, Apollo.
l've lost you on DRADIS. l'm blind!
Starbuck, Apollo. l repeat.
l got no sign of you or the Raider.
Starbuck! Report!
Starbuck, report!
This is Apollo.
Can you read me?
Starbuck, we're falling.
Starbuck!
Starbuck, l have zero visibility.
Starbuck, are you out there? Kara!
(beeping)
(beeping continues)
(radio) Good morning.
Got another hot one in store for you today.
It's time to head for the beach.
Weatherman says we can exp...
Rise and shine.
We have a big day ahead of us.
Come on.
l'm not here.
l'm out cold, or on a Cylon ship,
and you dragged me
to play your frakking mind games.
No games, Kara.
This is about your destiny.
l write my own destiny.
l didn't paint that symbol, Kara.
You did.
You saw it again.
In the clouds.
Didn't you?
But you didn't tell anyone else.
Because you're drawn to it.
You feel its pull.
You want to fly into it.
You want to cross over.
But you're afraid.
Afraid of what?
A frakking cloud?
Of the unknown.
Death.
All of your high-wire stunts
have been an act.
Time after time...
you skip to the edge of the abyss,
then dance away again.
But you never really
conquered your fear.
You've been afraid.
Ever since that day.
What day?
All this has happened before.
And will happen again.
(knocking)
- (woman) It's open.
- (door opens)
Hello, Mamma.
It's hard to believe
it's only six years ago.
You look so much younger.
l was.
(mother) So, you really did it. First person
in the family to become an officer.
What is the world coming to?
Kara, they tell me that you're
the best natural pilot they've ever seen.
First time l got in that cockpit, l just...
felt like l belonged.
All that natural ability, and still
you only graduated 16th in your class.
16th out of 117 cadets, Mamma.
Why are you proud of that?
You should have been No.1.
They tell me that you have left a trail
of demerits from here to Aerelon.
- You have no respect for authority...
- It's none of your business any more.
You have a gift, Kara.
l've always known that in my gut. And
l am not going to let you piss that away.
- You're special. Don't you understand?
- No, l'm not.
Would you let go of
that stupid dream of yours?
Look, l am sorry as hell
that you never made officer,
and all you have to show for a life
of dedication is this crappy apartment
and that frakking medal on the wall.
But l will not make up for it all. l can't.
Yeah, because you're a quitter.
You always have been.
You went to an oncologist?
Hey! Put that down.
Don't touch that.
- What are you gonna do about this?
- Nothing.
There's nothing to do.
It's metastasised.
Game is over.
- l'm sorry, Mamma.
- l don't want your pity.
- You haven't got it.
- You want to feel sorry for someone?
Feel sorry for yourself.
You have to find another way to motivate
your ass. l'm not gonna be around to do it.
Oh, don't tell me
you're gonna cry about it now.
You know what? l don't need this.
l'm gonna... l'm gonna walk out that door.
And you can look at it every frakking
miserable day you have left
and know that l am never
gonna come back through it again.
Kara!
(door opens)
(door slams)
You kept running, didn't you?
For blocks.
(Leoben) She waited here.
Five weeks.
Hoping you'd come back.
She died alone.
l was afraid l couldn't watch.
It's not too late.
She's waiting still.
Mamma.
You came back.
l can't believe you kept all this.
Everything.
Always.
Mamma.
Something's about to happen.
You know that thing that
you were trying to prepare me for?
l don't know if l can do it.
Oh, yes, you can. You can.
How can you be sure?
You're my daughter.
(Leoben) See? There's nothing
so terrible about death.
When you finally face it...
it's beautiful.
You're free now.
To become who you really are.
You're not Leoben.
Never said l was.
l'm here to prepare you
to pass through the next door.
To discover what hovers
in the space between life and death.
(beeping)
Starbuck, Apollo.
l lost you on DRADIS.
l say again... l've lost you.
Switch idents.
l'll try and get a fix on you.
Kara!
(Starbuck) Lee.
l'm not afraid any more.
Say again?
She should be afraid.
She's damn close to the hard deck.
The pressure will crush them both.
- Lee, get her out of there.
- (Gaeta) 90 seconds to hard deck.
All right, Kara. Listen to me.
Forget the damn toaster.
Climb now or you're dead.
We can still pull out. We haven't
gone past the point of no return.
Kara!
(Gaeta) 60 seconds to hard deck.
D vector red section to Apollo's last
known. Set alert Vipers to ready one.
(Dualla) Hotdog, Hex, divert to 7.5.
Gods, Starbuck, where are you?!
Visual. Visual.
OK. Kara, l'm coming to get you.
(Starbuck) Lee...
l'll see you on the other side.
Kara, please!
Listen to me! Come back...
Just let me go.
Godsdammit, Kara.
You come back!
Come back!
It's OK. Just let me go.
They're waiting for me.
No!
Apollo! Get out of there!
Abort! Abort!
Lee, do you have her in sight?
Can you see her?
Negative.
She...
she went in.
She went in.
We're sending in the
search and rescue birds. We'll find her.
No, Dad. It's no use.
Her ship's in pieces.
No chute.
We lost her.
- l'm a Ronnie monster.
- What's a Ro?
(giggles)