Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor chronicles...
I'm thinking I love you.
Always remember that.
You wanna stop Skynet?
This is the way.
Eight years.
I didn't wanna leave you.
I didn't have a choice.
You married?
I am.
When we jumped through time,
you told me I died of cancer.
Yes. 2005.
- Am I still gonna get sick?
- I don't know.
She's bleeding out!
There's a warehouse in the desert.
Everybody who knew anything
about the factory is already dead.
Well, I'm not.
Kaliba was building something.
Hey, baby.
You were pregnant.
Now you aren't.
- You care about this girl?
- She's a security risk.
- What are you doing?
- Moving.
Yeah. Well, seems about
the right time for that.
When John was a child, the legends
of the jungle were his fairytales.
His favorite was the story
of El Viejo del Monte.
The old man of the forest...
A merciless hunter
who killed every animal in his path.
El Viejo didn't eat his prey.
He left it behind
to rot in the soil.
To teach him a lesson,
the Gods turned him into a simisco,
half-animal, half-man.
He was condemned to defend
the jungle for all eternity.
Mom. Mom!
This was El Viejo's punishment.
This was his curse...
To forever be vigilant,
to forever protect.
Look.
We have to keep moving.
- Why are we so far from camp?
- Told you. It's part of the game.
You mean training.
Well, if we call it a game,
it's more fun.
But it's not a game.
The point...
is listen to me.
I always listen.
You don't talk that much.
We gotta go.
How long will it take you
to pack up the storage locker?
A while.
Some explosives that need securing.
Make sure you get
to the safe house before night.
If you haven't been there before,
it can be hard to find.
- I can follow directions.
- Well, you can also make mistakes.
Wouldn't want anyone else
getting hurt because of them.
33-42-31 north.
The safe house coordinates.
It's in the desert.
You like the desert.
- Things happen out there.
- Things happen here too.
We're starting over.
Whatever happened here...
is no one's fault.
Let's get outta here.
Hello, Savannah.
How are you today?
I'm well.
Would you like to play a game?
Engaging in imaginative play
helps my development.
This is Mount Valmai,
hiding place of the Mask of Life.
The Toa protect the mask
from the Dark Hunters.
These are the ducklings...
Chickie,
Pluffy, and Feathers.
Can they play too?
I don't think
there are any ducklings
on the mystical island of Voya Nui.
Are you sure?
I'm sorry.
I've accessed all the files.
I can find no references
to them in any of the instructions.
What's wrong?
Would you like
one of the Toa instead?
The ducklings are sad
because they can't play.
Can't you change the rules
to make them happy?
We can change the rules.
- What... is...
- John Henry, stop!
- ... all... this... about?
- Let go, please!
You're hurting me!
I... understand...
what... this... is... about.
Episode 220: To the Lighthouse
v 1.00
Subtitles: Projet-SG
Static. It's weird.
Must be interference or something.
- What the hell?
- Bug slug.
- Bug slug? Are you serious?
- We just passed it.
We haven't played bug slug
since I was, like, eight.
You can't just start playing
without telling me.
Fine.
We're playing bug slug.
- What if I don't wanna play?
- Too late. Already started.
- You feelin' all right?
- I feel great.
You feel great.
Why?
We haven't been on the road together
for a long time. That's all.
What's so great about it?
Just don't teach bug slug to Cameron.
She could do some real damage.
God, this signal really blows.
Hey, desert's that way.
We're takin' a detour.
So, I've got good news,
I've got bad news, and I have...
really bad news.
The good news is what we've got
here isn't an engineering problem.
All of John Henry's processes
look okay.
- Daemons are running fine.
- Wait a minute. His demons?
His daemons... D-a-e-m-o-n.
It's a tech term for a program
that runs in the background.
All computers
like John Henry have them.
Daemons run the lights,
daemons manage the elevators,
the security systems...
All kinds of daemons everywhere.
So what caused John Henry's
deamons to go crazy?
That's the bad news.
Came from the outside.
Cyber attack?
Which brings me
to the really bad news.
And by bad news I mean
on a scale of one to ten,
one being a hangnail,
ten being Katrina,
this is Katrina with a hangnail.
Looks like someone managed
to stuff malware down the throat
of the most sophisticated AI
in human history.
John Henry was infiltrated.
Probed.
Well... looks worse than that to me.
It looks like someone out there
wants to kill him.
- You been into my plastique?
- I needed it.
You know what,
I can handle the rest myself.
- Sarah sent both of us here.
- Yeah.
- Get John away from you.
- Or from you.
Don't touch this.
- We're supposed to get everything.
- I've got this.
That jacket belongs to Jesse.
Don't talk about her.
You don't know anything about her.
I know that you loved her.
You wouldn't have fathered
a child with her if you didn't.
I'm sorry for your loss.
What?
- I'm sorry for your loss.
- What loss?
The child you fathered with Jesse.
The one she was carrying
aboard the SS Jimmy Carter.
The one that died.
I never had a kid.
- You can't kill me.
- I can try.
Tell me what you're talking about.
She was pregnant.
She miscarried.
Why'd you tell me that now?
You put John in danger
when you lied about Jesse.
Sarah nearly lost her child.
You've lost a child.
You won't make that mistake again.
You knew her.
I met her once.
She never told me that.
It seems she never told you
a lot of things.
What is this place?
Come here.
What are you doing here, huh?
Who lives here?
Come on.
Charley.
You like bouillabaisse?
I may, I don't know.
What is it?
It's French for fish soup.
- That's very good.
- The secret's the fresh tomatoes.
I grow 'em myself.
You grow tomatoes.
Yeah. Think that's funny?
Don't you?
I got a lotta time
on my hands, you know?
Might as well put it to good use.
She's been here before.
Not with me.
She set this house up
after Michelle died.
Want more soup?
Sure.
All right.
- She tell you why we're here?
- No, she didn't.
Spare room's in there.
We're spending the night?
- What about Derek and Cameron?
- We'll meet up with them tomorrow.
I could use a hand on the boat.
I've got some work to do.
Yeah.
Let me get my gear.
Smells good.
There's bread in the fridge.
There's peanut butter.
Help yourself.
I won't be here long.
No. No, you won't.
So she was from the future,
and you knew...
the whole time?
Not the whole time.
I suspected something, but...
Just took me a while
to figure it out.
You love her?
She was a good person.
I don't know.
Maybe if things were different...
Yeah, well, I guess
you could say that...
'bout a lotta things.
I could say that about my whole life.
But it's not, so what's the point?
That first week...
I kept seein' her.
I'd go to the market,
she'd be there.
And for a second,
my heart would stop.
And then I'd realize, hey, that's...
that's not my wife.
That's just some random woman
who wears her hair in a ponytail
the way Michelle used to.
For a while,
I stopped shopping there.
But a man can only live on convenience
store burritos for so long.
So... I go back there now.
It's gettin' better.
What kind of explosives
did you rig the beach with?
- Semtex.
- Radio detonators?
Hard-wired switch
mounted under the dock.
When the perimeter's breached,
a siren goes off.
I figure I got about 60 seconds
to escape by boat.
Boat can't stop bullets.
Even if they sink it,
I got a chance.
Those bastards can't swim.
I can.
Cromartie.
A hell of a day, huh?
Got more work to do.
All right?
You remember Hal Beesley?
The old guy from the diner?
Nebraska?
Yeah. What about him?
He was my best customer.
Came in for every meal.
Three times a day like clockwork...
Breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
He tipped me like crazy.
It was that waitress uniform.
It's like catnip.
One day John got sick.
I didn't know what was wrong with him.
I had no savings, no insurance.
Hal pulled out a wad of bills,
gave it to me to take John
to the doctor.
He said as long as I needed help,
he'd be there.
No strings attached.
That's a man with a dream.
He was a widower.
Lost his wife of 40 years.
Knew what it was like to be alone.
Said that I could count on him
for anything anytime.
And one day, he came in
and said I didn't need him anymore...
Said that I'd found someone
I could depend on...
Someone I could trust.
Someone who would never,
ever let me down.
I got nothin'...
I got nothin' left to give you.
Not for me.
He seems like he's pretty full up
with people taking care of him.
I don't trust any of them.
He's still got you, right?
How long?
I don't know.
I found it a few days ago.
Are you sure it's...
I think so.
How do you know?
Cameron said
when we jumped eight years through time,
we jumped over my death.
From cancer?
If you jumped over it, then...
It doesn't mean I don't...
still get it, Charley.
It doesn't mean it's not in me.
And I think that the things I've done,
maybe have sped up the date.
- It's my fate, Charley.
- Come here.
It's my fate.
There's nothing I can do.
Wish I could tell ya
I found every hole and patched it,
but no such thing
as perfect security.
Perfect, no.
But is it sufficient?
The damn thing is tricky.
- Can't know for sure, not really.
- Who would know?
He would.
John Henry was fooled before.
Yeah. You don't fool
John Henry twice.
Activate the AI.
But don't give it access
to the outside world just yet.
What is it, Mr. Murch?
It's just...
No one's ever done this
with an AI this sophisticated before.
- Done what?
- Any of this.
No one's ever created an AI
this sophisticated before, Mr. Murch.
Point taken.
Activate John Henry.
No outside network.
John Henry, can you understand me?
The system seems solid.
Should be good.
You're makin' pancakes.
Yours, I hope.
No such luck.
Am I interrupting something?
What are you doing?
You stole his seat.
I took his seat?
You want some food?
Who loves you, huh?
Who loves you?
You're not hungry?
Thank you.
Maple or boysenberry?
Maple.
I thought something like that
might happen.
Like what?
Explain, Mr. Murch, quickly.
The on/off problem.
Once it's off, no problem.
- But the act of turning it off...
- Quicker.
John Henry processes more information
in a minute than we do in a lifetime.
Millisecond for a supercomputer,
it's almost like forever to us.
So when you turn it off...
It feels itself power down
in that instant.
It experiences that moment
the way we might experience years.
It feels itself die.
Slowly.
Very slowly.
We have to hook it up
to the net now.
- Is that safe?
- We're starving it.
It's bad enough
that we let it die for like forever.
John Henry's been living off the most
insane amount of data for weeks now.
- It's his world.
- And we took it away.
Fix it.
Wait. We should talk about this.
In for a penny,
in for a pound, James.
I know what it feels like,
Mr. Ellison.
What?
To die.
Then come back.
To be alone.
We had to cut you off
from your network.
It was for your own good.
There is another.
- Another what?
- One like me.
Another one like me.
You didn't tell Derek and Cameron
we were coming here, did you?
- They wouldn't understand.
- They know about this place?
I don't trust them anymore.
Neither should you.
Derek made a mistake, mom.
It was a human mistake.
- He could have gotten you killed.
- He didn't.
Chose himself over you.
Because he loved her.
Lot of that goin' around these days.
Is that a bad thing?
I'm not here for Charley.
Then why are we here?
We're here for you.
People matter, John.
They're all that matters.
Don't ever forget that.
I won.
I was alone, and you couldn't find me.
That's the game, right?
You won.
When did you find the lump?
Few days ago.
Any unexplained weight loss,
fevers, night sweats?
I've been feeling nauseated,
but I thought that was just stress.
Work?
Yeah, work.
You can lie back.
Obviously there is a mass
inside your breast.
Whether it's cancer or not
remains to be seen.
The ultrasound
will show us the lump size
and exactly where it lies
inside the breast tissue.
- All set, Doctor.
- Thank you.
Now, to determine the nature of
the lump, you're gonna need a biopsy.
Now open up your gown, please.
It's gonna be cold.
Did you have surgery recently?
An implant removed?
No. What is it?
What do you see?
The good news is the lump
inside your breast isn't a tumor.
Then what is it?
It's a cystic mass.
It's not that unusual.
Great. That's great.
But what is unusual is
what the cyst has formed around.
It's a piece of metal.
A tiny wire.
Metal?
You don't know how it got in there?
You work for Kaliba.
It's a transmitter.
Empties in the back.
- Will this kill me?
- What?
I said, will this kill me?
You're gonna use that on yourself?
On the transmitter.
The current should short it out.
If it kills me, it's self-defeating.
It isn't gonna kill you,
it's gonna hurt.
Now you have to leave.
You did the right thing
by telling me.
Thank you.
Fix the tire. I'll check it out.
I've traced the roving back door
that allowed access to my systems.
It uploaded itself
from one of the main T3 hubs
that carry all global
internet traffic.
It uploaded itself.
Yes, Mr. Ellison.
It is highly sophisticated.
The intelligence who designed it
is far beyond you
or Mr. Murch
or any human being.
It's very interesting.
The back door allowed
the insertion of a worm program.
The worm is merely code,
a means by which
the intelligence can invade
and operate my systems remotely.
Like hands and fingers.
I calculate that the worm
is now present
in a significant percentage
of the world's computer systems.
The intelligence uses them.
- For what?
- It has been looking for me.
Why?
I share a common code base
with the worm
and therefore, the intelligence.
I believe we are brothers.
Explain.
How's this possible?
I found useful information
in the code comments.
This picture, in ASCII text,
and the name
of the original programmer.
Miles Dyson.
Miles Dyson died in 1997
in an explosion
at Cyberdyne Systems.
The apparent victim of Sarah Connor,
a known terrorist who had escaped
from Pescadero State mental hospital
days before the incident.
That was your case, Mr. Ellison,
when you were at the FBI.
Yes, it was my case.
You never found Sarah Connor.
I never did.
John Henry, this intelligence...
Your brother...
What does it want?
He wants what we all want,
Ms. Weaver.
To survive.
It's down.
I need to know what to do next.
Show me where to cut.
Right side of the head.
Got it.
Where'd you get this diagram?
Your brother?
You don't say.
You're welcome.
Why'd you come after me?
You know the location
of the safe house.
John's location.
- If they tortured you...
- That would never happen.
It has before.