There are those who believe that a child
in her womb shares his mother's dreams.
Her love for him.
Her hopes for his future.
Is it told to him in pictures
while he sleeps inside her?
Is that why he reaches for her
in that first moment
and cries for her touch?
But what if you'd known since he was
inside you what his life held for him?
That he would be hunted.
That his fate was tied
to the fate of millions.
That every moment of your life
will be spent keeping him alive.
Would he understand
why you were so hard?
Why you held on so tight?
Will he still reach for you
if the only dream
you ever shared
with him was a nightmare?
Would he know my love
runs through him like blood?
John, now.
Now!
- The cops make you at the diner?
- I don't know.
Maybe.
Yes. Definitely.
Sarah Connor! John Connor!
Drop what you're carrying.
Put your hands on your head
and kneel on the ground.
Now!
Do me a favor, will you?
Fix it.
Drop your weapon!
Move!
You run! Run!
John!
John. John.
John.
John?
Do it!
Do it! Kill me! Nothing matters anymore.
Kill me!
You're right.
Nothing matters anymore.
Only the boy.
The future's ours.
And it begins now.
Did you scream or something?
Scream? No.
Go back to sleep.
I can't. Got an early shift.
Are you all right?
I'm good.
- Yeah?
- I'm great.
Well, you damn well better be.
You know, the guy down at the store
told me any woman would be lucky
to have this ring.
He doesn't know the giver like I do.
You wanna know a secret?
I don't know. I don't like secrets.
No? This is a good one.
- Really?
- Yeah.
All right.
John picked it out.
Sort of.
You know I'd been looking
and looking and I...
kinda starting freaking myself out
with the whole color
and cut and clarity...
So you turned the job over
to a 15-year-old boy.
You think I'm a jackass, don't you?
I'm thinking I love you.
Always rember that.
Early shift.
- Better get going.
- Right.
Early shift.
Bye.
Season 1 Episode 1
Pilot (v. 1.00)
http://Projet-SG.net
Mom, how many times have I told you
it's freaky when you do that?
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
We can't stay here, John.
What?
It's not safe.
Not safe from who?
No one knows us.
No one asks questions.
It's been almost two years.
School starts in, like, three weeks.
- We need to go.
- No, you need to go.
You're scared. He gave you a ring
and now you're freaking out.
I know you like him.
So do you, mom!
So do you. You love him, I know you do.
Listen to me.
The cops will never find us. We're safe.
Don't you think that, John!
Don't you ever think that. Look at me!
No one is ever safe.
Half an hour.
One bag.
Plus the guns.
I'll make pancakes.
Every family has rules.
And we had ours.
Keep your head down,
keep your eyes up,
resist the urge to be seen
as important or special.
Know your exits.
I mean, she's not
exactly missing, right?
- The way you explain it.
- Right.
The way I explained it,
she's not missing.
She left.
Happens more than you think.
You don't know her.
I can say the same to you, Mr. Dixon.
FBI?
Been together long?
Six months, maybe. Bit of a whirlwind.
You have no idea, the whirlwind.
Tell me,
does the Skynet defense system
mean anything to you?
No.
How about this guy?
Miles Dyson.
No.
Never seen him before.
That's because he's dead.
Your fiancee, freshly escaped
from the pescadero mental hospital,
blew him apart two years ago.
Leveled a four story
research lab along with him.
But since there's no lethal injection
for the destruction of property,
let's just stick with the murder of
one of our county's brightest
computer scientists. And...
dedicated family man.
That's... it's just not...
Why would she do that?
Well, you know, Mr. Dixon.
It's the robots.
The ones from the future.
The ones Skynet sent to kill her son.
Which makes total sense.
Because, in the future,
John's not only her son, but...
What does it say here?
"The leader of the resistance
fighting artificially
intelligent machines
determined to annihilate
the human race."
Did he strike you that way?
Leader of a scrappy band of rebels?
Luke Skywalker type?
He's just a kid.
He's a great kid.
He was like a son to me.
I came down here for help.
You can't really be asking me this!
No.
I'm not.
This is just my patter, Mr. Dixon.
This is just me impressing upon you
that I'm not here
because you lost your fiancee.
Love of your life
and all-around good time girl.
I'm here because my boss,
the United States of America,
thinks Sarah Connor is a deluded...
Dangerous grade "A" whack-a-mole
who killed a man because she believes
that in the future he'll invent
a computer system
that declares war on the world.
So let's begin with her name.
I understand it's not Connor.
You'll be responsible
for three chapters a week.
You have a quiz each friday.
You're allowed one make-up test
with a parent's note.
What's your name?
John.
Cameron.
And no talking...
while I'm talking.
John?
I haven't seen you around here before.
- Did you just move here?
- Yeah, I did.
Sucks for you.
My dad sells tractors.
- What about yours?
- Insurance.
Really? What kind?
The boring kind.
Those are the kind of tractors
my dad sells.
What about your mom?
My mom stays home.
You know, I really gotta get
to the next class, so...
So...
maybe i'll see you later?
Sure, yeah.
Bye.
This is a hick town, mom.
We've been in worse places.
A lot worse.
Well, my clothes are all wrong.
I need, like, some different shirts.
You know, here everyone wears boots?
Like, cowboy boots.
I hate cowboy boots.
I'll see what I can do.
Their computers are like,
from the frigging '50s or something.
Their computers?
I thought we agreed...
It wasn't my fault
they switched my class.
I don't need you to be caught hacking.
I'm not hacking, mom.
God, I know the rules.
They're, like, written on the inside
of my eyeballs, all right?
Hey.
You meet any pretty girls?
No, I'm telling you, it's a hick town.
Come on.
Agent Ellison.
Welcome to New Mexico.
The sheriff's detachment'll hustle you
around on your business here,
whatever that is, he wouldn't say.
He doesn't know.
I lied to you yesterday.
My dad doesn't sell insurance.
He's dead.
He was a soldier.
He was killed on a mission.
I'm sorry.
It's all right. My mom was
pregnant with me when it happened.
I never even knew him.
So it's all right.
My mom,
she's kind of uptight.
Actually, no, she's
really uptight.
She likes me to come home
straight after school
and hang out with her and
that kind of thing, you know?
I'm all she's got.
Thank you for explaining.
It'll be our secret.
Mr. Ferguson is ill today.
My name is Cromartie.
This that your only name? Like madonna?
Madonna?
Why? No.
Let's take attendance, then.
Mary Booai.
Here.
Donald Chase.
- Franklin Lane.
- Here.
Cynthia Nolan.
Here.
Wayne Parker.
Cameron Phillips.
Cameron?
Here.
Reese?
Do we have a John...
Excellent.
Class dismissed.
Witnesses are reporting gunfire
just minutes ago
at Crestview High School in Red Valley.
Police are...
Come with me if you want to live.
Sarah Connor.
Where is he?
What have you done with him?
You don't know.
You don't know...
Killing yourself is the best strategy.
If you're alive,
I can use you against him.
- John?
- Mom, mom.
- I tried to call you.
- Mom, I've been trying to call you.
Listen to me, okay? They're back.
- It's back.
- John, slow down.
- Where are you?
- I'm going to the house.
- I'll be right there.
- Mom!
I love you, John. Stay right there.
Let's go.
John?
John!
- Are you okay?
- Mom?
- John?
John!
No!
Neat trick. You like?
Next time you do
what you're trained to do.
You run. Go!
- Did you stop him?
- 120 seconds and the system reboots.
- I was sent here to protect John.
- Not now. Not yet.
You might wanna put those
back in the holster.
We should be good here two more hours.
Hit the border at lunchtime.
What year are you from?
2027.
How long have you been looking for us?
73 days.
And the war?
The Skynet missile defense system
goes online april 19th, 2011.
Declares war on mankind
and triggers a nuclear apocalypse
two days later.
Miles Dyson.
Someone else builds Skynet.
Who?
- We don't know.
- You don't know who builds the computer
- that blows up the world?
- I wasn't sent here for that.
No, you were sent here to keep my son
from being assassinated.
Your fiance went to the police.
You should have changed your alias.
Go to hell.
They'd have found you anyway.
They always do.
There's Kevlar in that chair.
APB's statewide, but it's been...
19 hours.
What the hell happened here?
22 witnesses, Deputy Ridge.
22 of your good townfolk.
That's a whole football team.
Guess what 19 of 'em saw?
A shooter with some kind of robot leg.
A shooter...
with some kind of robot leg.
Hey.
Why is this happening again?
I don't know.
You stopped it.
I guess I didn't.
Well, you can.
You changed the future.
You just didn't change it enough.
So you can do it again.
- I don't know, John.
- I can't keep running.
I can't.
I'm not who they think I am.
Some messiah.
You don't know that.
I know.
I can't lead an army.
Maybe that's you, but it'll never be me.
So you've gotta stop it.
Please.
Mom.
All right.
All right what?
I'll stop it.
We're not going across the border.
Where are we going?
To find Skynet.
Chip?
Back at school,
you apologized for lying to me.
So I should apologize for lying to you.
It's all right. I get it.
You needed to get close to me.
It's just the way you're...
programmed.
Like some hot girl is really gonna try
and make friends with the new weird kid.
If I'd have thought about it,
I would've known something
was messed up, you know?
In the future, you have many friends.
What model are you?
Are you new? You seem...
different.
I am.
Let's go.
Mom, pizza's here.
Mom, the pizza!
Mom.
You.
We need to talk about Miles, Tarissa.
Danny, go to your room. Right now.
How dare you come here.
I know what they told you,
but it didn't happen that way.
Get the hell out of here.
- Now.
- It didn't happen that way.
I can't let you do that.
- Let go!
- Listen to me!
I didn't kill Miles.
All right, I didn't do it.
I would never.
Miles was a hero.
Then why are you here?
We're back.
You told me there'd be no more machines.
Look, it's happening again.
Everything we fought to stop.
Miles' work at Cyberdyne
is the only link we have.
Is there anyone, anywhere
who's shown an interest in his work?
Anyone he could've told.
Someone he forgot.
There's nobody. It's all gone.
You destroyed it all.
You and Miles destroyed...
You destroyed everything.
We have to go.
Now.
Help me.
Help my son.
Mom! Mom!
Oh, god.
Bandages, rubbing alcohol.
- Mom, you need a doctor.
- Go!
We'll find cover out back.
First aid kit on the floor.
Get it done before he gets back.
I'll get some ice. It'll numb you,
slow the blood loss.
Needle and thread
to slow the blood loss.
Do it now.
We can't keep running.
I'll lose my boy.
He'll leave me.
What time is it?
7:52.
How you feeling?
Better.
Good.
- We need to go.
- Where?
I'll show you.
So do you have, like, an account here?
Safety deposit box.
When'd you open that?
1963.
Everybody on the floor!
Please.
Keys to the safety deposit boxes.
Get inside. Keys.
Lock us in, and then get away
from the door.
I'll know if you don't.
You said you had a safety deposit box.
I do.
Open these boxes.
Put everything you find on the table.
Carefully.
Hey, James! You gotta see this.
The alarm tripped seven minutes ago.
Camera autodumps a digital copy
to the LAPD servers.
Don't you know 'em?
Less and less all the time.
Is that from the future?
You can't bring anything
through when you come.
Not weapons, not clothing.
Nothing.
You send someone back to build it.
What is it?
Hope.
Is that the police?
No. Get away from the door.
Why?
That's why.
That better be what I think it is.
One of our best engineers.
Took him eight months
to scavenge the parts.
When the isotope solution
turns red, then fire.
Isotope?
Is this nuclear?
No, not really.
I still don't get why you locked us in.
We didn't have to get trapped like rats.
We're not trapped.
What is that?
The engineer got a job
building the vault
so we'd always have a way back home.
What have you done?
You wanna find Skynet?
You wanna stop Skynet?
- This is the way.
- You don't know who builds it!
No, but we know where and we know when.
We can go kill it before it's born.
You can stop running.
Stay in one place.
Fight.
Mom, we've gotta go now!
Mom!
Do it!
Where are we?
Same where.
Different when.
Check this out!
Good day, baby! I got something for ya!
So this is where it all starts?
This is where Skynet begins?
Somewhere in there.
And nobody knows we're here.
You're safe.
- No one is ever safe.
Come on.
It is said that the death
of any one person
is the death of an entire world.
Certainly for parents,
the death of a child
is no less than a holocaust.
In the case of my son,
these words are literally true.
And finally tonight, amateur video
of what we can only assume
is a college prank gone wrong
as three streakers cause chaos
trying to cross the 105 freeway.
Honey, did you hear me? We're late.
Yeah,
I heard you.
And even though
we've traveled through time,
bent the rules of nature,
they will keep coming for him.
Keep trying to kill him.
But until that day...
It's gonna be one hell of a dogfight.