In the future, my son will lead mankind in a war against skynet...
A computer system programmed to destroy the world.
It has sent machines back through time.
Some to kill him, one to protect him.
Today we fight to stop skynet from ever being created.
To change our future.
To change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
Previously on terminator: the sarah connor chronicles: i haven't seen you around here before.
Did you just move here?
Yeah.
Sucks for you.
We can't stay here, john.
No one knows us.
We're safe.
Don't you think that, john!
No one is ever safe.
Fbi.
Your fiancee killed a man because she believes that in the future,
you'll invent a comput s stete that declares war on the world.
Cameron phillips.
Here.
Do we have a john reese?
Come with me if you wanna live.
I'm not who they think i am.
You changed the future, you just didn't change it enough.
So you can do it again.
You wanna stop skynet?
This is the way.
Mom.
We gotta go, now!
Do it!
Where are we?
Same where.
Different when.
A wise man once said "know thyself.
" easier said than done.
I've had nine aliases, 23 jobs, spoken four languages,
and spent three years in a mental hospital for speaking the truth.
At least when i was there,
i could use my real name.
Through it all, i've always known
who i am and why i'm here.
Protect my son.
Prepare for the future.
But lately it's gotten harder to control.
Even as i try to help john find firm ground in this new world,
the battlefield shifts beneath our feet.
Maybe it's all catching up to me.
Maybe if you spend your life hiding who you are,
you might filallenend fooling yourself.
Hey, how's it going?
All right.
You bought me the wrong needle nose pliers though.
I did?
You said red handles.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I, uh...
I guess i'm still...
I don't know.
I've been calling it time-lag.
What?
It's like jetlag, but for time travel.
Time-lag.
Yeah, sounds about right.
Hey, you kw what would really help with time-lag?
Some fresh air.
John.
I've been cooped up here for three days.
I know.
No, you don't know, because you keep going outside.
And so will you when we get new ids.
So let's get them already.
We will.
Can you be patient, please?
It's not just a name.
It's a legend.
A life.
A whole new you.
We go through this every time.
This is different.
New ids today?
It's been three days.
I want my new name.
I want that whole new me.
Can't you track down enrique?
All right, i'll track down enrique.
Old friend.
Ten years ago he was the best fake paper guy around.
John sent back better ones.
You cannot walk into the living room after three days-- three days--
and now after three days, now you tell me there are other people here?
Resistance fighters.
Humans.
Sent back from the future by john.
And what?
Are they manning some kind of apocalyptic paramilitary
convenience store filled with fake ids, and guns, and money?
Yes.
You done yelling at her yet?
I'm not yelling.
Right.
So look, mom, there's no turkey.
Turkey.
It's in there, john.
No.
Just move the food around and the turkey will reveal itself to you.
Mom, i already looked.
There's no-- oh, yeah, there it is.
Thanks.
And stay inside.
No id means-- yeah, i know what no id means.
How many guys are we meeting?
Four.
These resistance fighters, they know you?
They've seen me before.
I've seen that before.
Kyle reese had one.
Skynet work camp.
Prisoner.
Please remain calm.
Oh, my god.
You told me we'd be safe!
Safe!
Was that safe?
Three days and we're at war.
Why jump at all?
Why not stay in the past?
I had seven more years to get ready.
To get him ready.
No, you wouldn't have.
Why not?
Because you died two years ago.
December 4, 2005.
You died.
So what i'm getting is these things, they're here.
All over, i guess.
And they some of them, all of them,
are programmed with specific missions.
The one at the safe house was sent there for those fighters.
Skynet doesn't know you're here.
There's no directive to hunt you.
So if i was to walk right by one...
They'll walk right by you.
They don't know what you look like.
That's really awesome.
And what if they found out who he was?
Would they all know what to do then?
They do.
Awesome.
So school registration is at 3:00 tomorrow.
Do you think we can have all this sorted out by then?
Can't you just be happy being yourself for a little while longer?
Just sit still?
It's not so bad being a connor.
That's easy for you to say.
Is it?
You all put back together, tin man?
Tin man?
You ready to go?
Thank you for explaining.
You stay here.
Still like a statute.
Enrique?
Statue.
Yeah, i've been a statue for the lasthree days.
We'll be back.
I did paramilitary training with enrique outside of oaxaca.
He taught john to shoot rifles.
So what you said before.
Is that why we're really here?
Did john, the future john,
did he send you back to help me jump over my death?
Is everything else a lie?
No.
He sent us here to fight.
You're the best fighter he knows.
I'm sure that's not-- the best.
So if i'm such a great fighter, how was i killed?
Cancer.
We're here.
Hey, it's john.
I'm not here right now.
You know what to do.
Hey, sorry i misd you, but leave a message
and i'll call you back...
Probably.
You've reached the future leader of mankind.
It may take me a little while to get back to you,
but leave a message anyway.
818-555-0147.
Leave a message.
Statue.
Screw it.
I'm not surprised.
I know i looked surprised
when i saw you in that first moment.
But i am not surprised.
Do you know this woman well?
It's rhetorical.
If you don't, you don't.
But if you do, an you're anything like her,
you'll lie and say you don't.
But if you do, then i know that you,
like me, are not surprised.
And john.
He's a man now.
He's grown up.
He misses you.
I need three sets of papers.
I can pay.
Not a lot, but some.
Why not?
I'm finished with that life.
What?
Are you familiar with ricardo lopez?
The boxer from cuernavaca.
He is very famous in my country.
His nickname is el finito.
Finisher.
Yes.
He fought 52 fights.
51 victories, one draw.
And no losses, zero.
I don't understand.
I wanted to be el finito.
To retire undefeated.
I lived my wild life.
I fought the wars i wanted to.
And a few i did not.
But i lived every day free.
Not one day behind bars.
Nor in the hands of the enemy.
So now i am finished.
El finito.
Happy for you.
Sorry for me, but happy for you.
Hey, don't give up so easy!
I did not say i can't help.
My nephew, carlos, has, how we say,
taken over the family business.
His operation is very good.
But he is not a believer.
Few believers left, i think.
You're a very quiet girl.
Hey, are you there?
who's charlie dixon?
You shouldn't surf with the demo.
People get in your business.
Clear your history too.
My history?
Your history of what you've been looking at.
Snoopy people, dude.
Snoopy people all over.
Got a special on those.
, no, maybe later.
Thanks.
Carlos?
Enrique sent us.
What the hell?
Pipe their crazy asses down.
Wait at the car.
Something about your friend i should know?
Cat person.
Heh.
Want a soda or something?
I'm good.
We got the old-fashioned soda machine.
Little bottles.
It's a collectible now.
Jose!
Soda, por favor.
* * my uncle, he's very good at keeping secrets.
When i was young, i'd see him at family barbecues,
and i'd try to get him to tell me his secrets.
How did that work out for you?
Not so good.
Except one day, about eight years ago,
i find him in the kitchen.
A bottle of patron and the times.
You know whose picture's on the front page?
Only time i ever see my uncle cry.
He's a good man.
Not for me to say, but he's my uncle.
And you're as close as i'm gonna get to one of his secrets.
So i'm gonna give you what you need.
Thank you.
What?
I don't have that.
That's a family discount in these hard times.
Especially for someone who's been dead eight years.
That's extortion.
War on terrorism makes this the front lines, lady.
Some raghead gets fake papers down here,
we're all going to guantanamo.
9/11 doubled prices overnight.
9/11.What's that?
Hey, baby girl.
What did i tell you about hanging around?
Who's your new friend here?
She someone i need to know?
'Cause the longer you stand around,
the more i think she's someone i need to know.
You got a name?
Um, no.
Hmm.
This your car?
No.
It's definitely not my car.
See, i know just about everyone in this neighborhood,
and you are not one of those everyone.
So now you got me wondering not just who you are that you won't say,
but why you're here.
And that you won't s.
You know, it's not uncommon in these neighborhoods for a gang
dealing in drugs to store their drugs inside of a stolen car.
That way no drugs can be found on their property or
on any property belonging to them.
But they also like to leave a lookout,
sometimes a pretty girl, to watch their stash.
Now you don't mind if i call this license plate in, do you?
Jenny!
Jejennif!
How many times have i told you to stop seeing that little punk ass?
I swear to god.
Is he meeting you here?
Ma'am?
Ma'am!
You know this girl?
Yes, i know this girl.
Do i have any choice but to know you,
you spoiled little bitch?
Do you do domestic complaints officer?
Can i make a domestic complaint against my spoiled little stepdaughter
for making me want to beat my own brains in?
It's her real mother's fault.
Can i tell you what she lets her do?
Ma'am, is this your car?
Why would i drive that piece of crap?
'Cause i will send you back to private school.
The one with the uniforms.
They will dress you like a flannel sock.
Ma'am, maybe you guys can have this conversation somewhere else,
like at home perhaps?
Out of gang territory.
Gang territory?
Of course.
Thank you, officer.
Come on.
It's 13 miles to walk home.
We need another car.
Were you gonna kill that cop?
Don't answer that.
Don't want to know.
We need rules.
Aren't you supposed to take orders or something like that?
I do.
From john.
So if i tell john to forbid you-- not this john.
Not this john.
Aren't they the same?
Not yet.
I cannot imagine the apocalypse.
No matter what kyle reece told me, or others who have come back.
I cannot imagine 3 billion dead.
I can imagine planes hitting buildings,
and i can imagine fire.
If i would've witnessed it,
if i would've been here,
i'm sure i would've thought the end was near.
I'm sure i would've thought...
We have failed.
John?
Johnny?
Is it really you?
It is you.
I--i saw a picture of your mother on the television
and i could barely believe my--
i can't believe this.
Don't come any closer.
Stop.
You came to my house.
You married?
Yeah, i am.
She's a nurse at the hospital where i work.
That's nice.
It's good.
Johnny, what happened?
Stop.
Johnny, it's okay.
Please stop.
No, no, johnny.
It's me, johnny.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
How'd it go with enrique?
El finito is a true believer,
but he is finished with the life.
What?
We need 20 grand.
It's a long story.
That taking you a while?
Yeah, it's taking me a while.
I gotta, you know, strip wires and...
John has a high level of stress.
Genetics are a bitch.
I did a brief analysis.
Surface skin temperature high.
Salinity high.
Pulse abnormal.
That's 'cause the kid snuck
out while we were gone.
Wouldn't look me in the eye.
His shoes are wet with grass.
Don't need to be a tin man to figure that one out.
Just a mom.
Where did he go?
Worry about that later.
Just need to make sure he doesn't do it again.
I didn't know that was something you could do.
The skin trick.
I should know about your skills or whatever.
Like can you analyze blood?
Can you scan someone?
You mean computed axial tomography?
Cat scans?
Yeah.
That.Can you do that?
No.
Get your shoes on.
Do you want your new name or what?
You sure there's money here?
Money, guns, anything they valued.
It will be hidden.
It's always hidden.
Yeah, well, whatever they had,
les hope the cops didn't get to it first.
Let's hope our metal friend didn't find it.
Our metal friend was only here to kill
that fourth fighter when he came home.
Nice to know we spoiled that.
It'll find him.
That's ridiculous.
People do like small animals.
Yeah, but...
I don't know how to explain this.
Some badass soldier is not gonna
have a kitty poster on the wall.
Mom.
Do what you do, girly.
What?
They rigged it.
What did she say?
120 seconds before the system reboots?
We gotta get in there, john.
We can't come back.
Mom, we'll find the money some other way.
No, whatever's in there, i want it now.
Numbers.
What are the numbers?
What can the numbers be?
Damn.Fingerprints.
It's a date.
Judgment day.
What are those?
Why are diamonds a girl's best friend?
What?
Where'd you get that?
John gave it to me.
He did, did he?
That was sweet of him.
We have a whole bag of them.Do you want one?
They're a girl's best friend.
Not this girl.
I know what the tin man is.
He needed a heart.
The wonderful wizard of oz, written by l.
Frank baum in 1900.First published in
-- i know all about the wizard of oz.
When john was little, i--
you read it to him over and over again in spanish.
He never told you, but it was one
of his favorite things that you did.
He used to talk about it a lot.
Okay, shoppers.
98 for this dvd/cd player with remote...
Hey, who-- who the hell are you?
What are you doing here, man?
This is my house, man.
"chet.
" what's with thtrespassing?
And the visor...
Chet?
Oh, chet-- aah!
they're exactly like you asked.
These ain't just forgeries.
This is full service.
You're in the system and everything.
Collect welfare with 'em if you want.
We might have to.
Didn't take you long to round that up,
so i'm feeling the price was right.
Maybe you'd have gone another ten gs.
Uncle enrique will be proud.
So i miss the next family barbecue.
Charlie...
You okay?
You've been a little, you know,
out of it all night.
No, i'm good.
I'm fine.I just-- i had a rough call.
Some guy on meth.
God, babe, want me to take a look at that?
No, no, i'm good.I'm goo.
-You sure?
-Yeah.
Love you.
Yeah, i love you too.
Carlos was right.
$20,000 wasn't that much money.
A new identity, a new life, a chance.
You can't put a price on that.
But unlike jn,n, i was never
eager for that new life to begin.
I liked having no name, no story.
It was the only time i got to be me.
Unfortunately, sometimes you have to pay for that.
And the price was getting higher every day.
Sarah.
You can either drinitit od mp it.
I say drink it.
Anything i should know?
Excuse me?
Anything you forgot to tell me?
Neglected.
Lied about.
First and last chance.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Please...
Put the gun down and explain.
El finito.
El finito.Yes, what about it?
Not a day behind bars.
Lived a life of freedom.
Yes!
That's not what carlos said.
[speaking spanis my nephew is a thief and a liar.
I told you-- he was speaking spanish to his crew.
He referred to you as a rata.
Slang for "snitch," isn't it?
You must have heard him wrong.
A rata.
Rat.
Denunciente.
Informer.
Certain words i know and don't forget.
Are you selling people out?
Are you selling me out, enrique?
Okay.
I was in lompoc many years ago.
On a federal gun charge.
You said you never--
three weeks.Only three weeks.
And you made a deal?You talked?
No, i gave information on my cellmate.
He had kidnapped a child and put her in
his trunk, and drove her from oregon.
He told me--he told me where he dumped her.
And--they dropped my charge, yes.
But that was all.
That was all i gave.
And yes, i lied to you.
But whe e i ew up, where we grew up,
a man doesn't-- you know--
it's another one.
It means the same thing.
Why would you do this?
Did you hear what he said?
We don't know.
He was possibly lying.
Possibly?
You just executed him on possibly?
He had a family!
Why would you do this?
Because you wouldn't.
How do you know what i would and would not do?
You don't know me.
You don't know me!
And you don't know my son.
Not john.
Not my john.
You don't know what i would and wouldn't do.
I don't even know what i would and wouldn't do.
I wake up this morning and you tell me...
I dot k ow anything anymore.
I don't even remember what my name is.
Sarah connor.
So where are you from?
Lawrence, kansas, actually.
It's a pretty good size city.
About 80,000.
Go to kansas city often?
Well, lawrence is about 50
miles east of kansas city.
25 miles west.
I knew that.
What about your father?
Your father.
Did you leave him behind in lawrence, kansas?
Your father's dead.
He was a police officer.
He died apprehending a criminal.
He's a hero.
Yeah, i know that.
My dad's always a hero.
And he's always dead.
Did you go out late last night?
No, why?
Motion detectors.
I thought i heard a beep.
Probably her.
She just walks and walks.
Look, if you want to hold me out another
few days until these stupid stories straight
-- you're going to school.
But--
at least that way i'll know where you are.
And who you're with.
Mom.
What?
Never mind.
Who do you think, agent?
Perhaps you think i was retired, yes?
That i did not have my ear to the street?
If you return my call, i believe i may
have something of interest for you.
Muy expensivo, but of great interest.
El finito will not disappoint.
Know thyself.
John once told me it's inscribed on
the front of the temple of apollo.
Then entire quote is, "know thyself "
and thou shall know all the mysteries
of the gods and of the universe.
" that's quite a mouthful.
My version is this.
Know thyself because what else is there to know?
People hide secrets.
Time is a lie.
The material world can disappear in an instant.
It has and it will again.
The doctor will see you in a few minutes, ms.Baum.
Our identities change.
Our names, the way we look, how we act and speak.
We're shape shifters.
There is no control.
No constant.
No shelter but the love of family
and the body god gave us.
And we can only hope that
that will always be enough.