In the future,
a computer program called Skynet
will declare war on the human race.
Machines has traveled back in time
taking human form
to terminate John Connor,
the future leader of the resistance.
Sarah Connor, John's mother,
teacher and protector.
Cameron, a Terminator reprogramed
to defend them at all costs.
Derek Reese, John's uncle
and a commanding officer
with the resistance.
Together, they fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created.
The battle for our tomorrow
starts today.
Episode 201: Samson & Delilah
v 1.00
http://Projet-SG.net
Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles...
Do we have a John Reese?
Come if you want to live.
You want to stop Skynet?
This is the way.
Cromartie came through.
He knows we're here.
We're programmed
to repair ourselves'.
We're programmed to blend in.
- There are other people here?
- Resistance fighters.
Humans sent back from the future
by John.
The machine's gotta go.
Don't let yourself think
that you can train them like a pet,
because it'll be the last thing
that you think.
Your fiancee, Sarah Connor,
killed a man because she believes
in the future,
he'll invent a computer system
that declares war on the world.
My Turk plays chess
at a level that could defeat
every human player that has ever lived
and probably ever will live.
Tech Industry spent billions
doubling chip power.
That's how we can go
from a chess computer to the apocalypse.
The Turk created Skynet.
Somebody killed him
and took the machine.
He was dead and the Turk was gone.
Got a good idea who has it.
Sarkissian.
Check the office.
See if he stashed the Turk.
Sarkissian's hard drive.
If you die, they win.
Agent Ellison.
Can I borrow you?
Pulled him from the apartment.
It's your guy, right? The shooter?
Yeah, that's him.
How does a mope like that
take out 20 of our HRT?
Zach wants you back home
for a full incident report.
You need a ride?
I can get a junior agent
to drive your car.
Come on.
They gonna believe a mope like this
took out 20 of your HRT?
And believe a machine from the future
stole his identity and did it?
They gotta believe.
This has to end here.
Sorry you gotta take the blame for it.
It's not your fault.
Just bad luck.
You all right?
John, are you all right?
Would you answer me?
Mom!
Can you move?
Are you hurt? You're bleeding.
- I'm fine. Are you all right?
- Just my shoulder.
We gotta go.
- Can you walk?
- Yeah.
Good, 'cause we gotta run.
Come back here!
All fire and EMT Personnel
advised to stand by.
Fire has destroyed a home
at 204 Laurel Avenue.
Number of dead or injured
is unknown.
- These the only two DOA?
- That's it.
- You check the whole house?
- House is clear.
What the hell's going on here?
Where is she?
Hell if I know.
Long gone if I know her.
- Who's out there under those sheets?
- We were doing a deal.
Went bad.
We stole this.
Guess they came back for it.
- What's on it?
- Records, names, transactions.
I don't know.
We thought we could use it.
- What are you looking for?
- It's a piece of tech.
It's called the Turk.
It's another computer.
It's a program.
- What's it do?
- Right now?
Plays a mean game of chess.
Couple years, it's gonna get
really pissed off. Blow up the world.
Units requested.
Possible stolen vehicle
involved in an accident.
Suspects fled scene. Injuries unknown.
- She could be anywhere.
- That's right, she could be anywhere.
Or she could be right there.
Maybe with your chess program.
The identification of these two victims
has not yet been released.
And it is unclear
how they are connected to this blaze
or to the car explosion nearby.
Mr. Walsh?
- Ma'am.
- Do you have it?
I do, Ma'am.
It's a modest little mouse,
if I may say.
It's not much to look at for 300,000.
Better be able to checkmate
Bobby Fischer for that.
Not for you to judge, Mr. Walsh.
- It's the last you'll hear of it.
- When will I see you?
I thought I'd tour the sights
with it for a bit, Ma'am.
- Make sure I was clean.
- That seems prudent.
An hour, then.
An hour.
And Mr. Walsh,
Bobby Fischer's dead.
Yes?
Call a meeting of the department heads
for tonight.
Tonight?
But Ms. Weaver, Justin Tuck
is in Palm Springs for a long weekend.
- I'll get him back.
- Thank you.
Witness saw a woman
and a teenage boy get out of the car
and move off to the south.
- Are they hurt?
- Either way, they're moving.
I'm okay.
It's just bruised. Let's go.
It could be broken.
How's your leg?
Is your head still bleeding?
We've gotta get off the street.
We need to find a safe place.
Has there been an accident?
We need sanctuary.
Can I ask for that? Please?
We need somewhere to hide.
Now.
Yes.
Of course. Come with me.
And they should leave.
Come on.
- What will you do when you find 'em?
- Do?
Join the team?
Think she's gonna go with you,
'cause it's not gonna happen.
She left you at the altar
for a reason.
- That's not what I want.
- Really.
- Yeah. I'm married.
- So you say.
- I love my wife.
Look, I just wanna know they're okay,
got it?
- What if they're not?
- Then I'll make 'em okay.
Like I did for you.
Your money'll be deposited
in the account within 30 minutes.
Please,
take all the precautions we discussed.
Of course, Ma'am.
So much for so little.
Again, don't mind me sayin'.
They flow from street to street.
At a particular speed
and in a particular direction.
Walk the block,
wait for the signal,
cross at the light.
Over and over.
So orderly.
All day I can watch them and know
with a great deal of certainty
what they'll do at any given moment.
But they're not orderly, are they?
Up close.
Any individual.
Who knows what they're gonna do?
Any one of them
might dash across the street
at the wrong time
and get hit by a car.
When you get up close,
we never follow the rules.
You give a computer a series of rules,
and it will follow them
till those rules
are superseded by other rules.
Or that computer simply...
wears down and quits.
Computers are obedient to a fault.
Do you know what's extremely rare
in the world of computers?
Finding one...
that'll cross against the light.
Thank you, Mr. Walsh.
Be careful out there.
Are you all right?
- You already asked me that.
- I'm asking you again.
I'm fine.
I think we need to talk
about what happened back at the house.
- No, I don't.
- Maybe I need to talk about it.
Maybe you do, but I don't,
so let's not.
Please.
Then we need to talk about her.
Whatever happened with the explosion,
it's flipped a switch.
She's reverted or something.
She knows everything.
I know.
Bank accounts.
Contingency plans. Weapons stash.
- I know.
- How we run, where we'll go.
Who we've been, who we'll be.
She's... stronger and faster.
- We have to kill her, John.
- I know!
I know.
I just read your incident report.
I wanna thank you
for filling everything out
so quickly...
It's a big help.
Of course.
So, Laszlo...
Did you ever think
that he had it in him?
Out-of-work actor, a civilian?
I did not, no.
But he was here before.
Suspect in multiple murders.
- We cleared him.
- But you had a change of heart?
I discovered he was impersonating
an FBI agent.
Yeah, I had a change of heart.
Do you have any idea whose bullet
was ultimately responsible
for taking Laszlo out?
No, I don't.
You know who threw the tear gas
into the residence?
And who fired into the apartment,
igniting the canisters?
- No, I do not.
- It's amazing you survived.
Do you know how you survived?
You wanna talk to somebody?
You need help?
You want a counselor? A pastor?
You're divorced. You have anybody?
I'll be all right.
Take six weeks paid leave,
special circumstances.
- I don't think that will be necessary.
- We insist on it.
So under possible penalty of perjury,
as it relates to case file
B1987004,
do you, Agent James Ellison,
today attest
that all that you've recorded
and said,
case file's accurate and factual
as far as your recollection can warrant?
Yes.
I do.
Good luck, Agent.
Yes? May I help you?
I'm looking for my family.
- Family?
- My mother and my brother.
We were in an accident.
I think they're hurt.
There is no one here.
I need to find them.
It's life or death.
Like I said,
there is no one here.
I'm going to look around.
It's life or death.
Now.
- Two minutes.
- I know.
- What are you doing?
- Stay away. Please.
I told you to go away.
You have to stay away.
Go!
70 seconds.
- The knife isn't sharp enough.
- Well, push harder.
- How much time?
- 55.
Wait, I see it.
Screwdriver, screwdriver.
- 35.
- Oh, it's not the right size.
20 seconds.
Okay, okay.
The knife, the knife.
- Damn it!
- We can't do this.
- Come on.
- She's waking up.
She's waking up!
Keys.
You have to go.
Do it.
- What?
- Go.
Move!
Call to him.
- You're making this difficult.
- He won't come back!
No. He won't.
You can't do this.
You don't know what you're about to do.
Yes, I do.
You're gonna kill me.
No, John.
You can't do this.
You're not doing the right thing.
This is not the right thing, John.
Things are good now.
Things are fine now.
I ran a test.
Things are good now.
I'm fixed now.
You can trust me now.
- What are you waiting for?
- She doesn't know, she doesn't.
I'm good now.
I'm good, I ran a test.
Everything's perfect. I'm perfect.
I'm sorry for what I did.
It wasn't me.
You have to understand. It wasn't me.
That wasn't me.
You can't let this happen, John.
You can't!
Please, listen to me.
Listen to me. I don't wanna go.
Please, John, please.
John, listen to me.
I don't wanna go.
Please, John.
Please. I'm good now.
Listen to me.
I don't want to go. I'm sorry.
That wasn't me.
I'm fixed now. I ran a test.
Everything's perfect.
You can trust me.
I love you!
I love you, please.
I love you, John,
and you love me.
We should get going soon.
You guys cut a pretty serious path
of destruction across the city.
Wasn't us.
- I'm sorry.
- Shoulda called earlier...
- We could've helped you avoid some.
- I doubt it.
How's this?
It looks trashed.
So I'm guessing Sarkissian
didn't tell you where he sold the Turk.
Wasn't that kind of conversation.
Did he see it all?
He saw it all.
Damn.
So Charlie told me that Cromartie
killed about 20 FBI guys today.
He's still out there.
He's here for me.
They're dead because of me.
They're dead because some people refuse
to accept the reality of the situation.
Which is what?
Which is that they carry death
with them.
She was different.
- No.
- I made her.
I sent her back.
- She's different.
- She's not different.
There's physical damage
to her chip.
Which means that she can be repaired...
I need her.
She saved my life.
She saves my life!
I know what you saw today.
I know what you did, and I'm...
so proud of you.
Maybe you could fix her.
I know you wanna try.
But I can't let you.
I just... I can't.
So burn her.
Let's get the hell outta here.
What she said back there...
Everything she said, it was a trick.
You know that, right?
They don't feel anything.
They don't have feelings.
They don't know love.
I know that, Mom.
You know,
I saw her do this with the last one.
The only way to be sure.
Especially this one.
John, chip.
The flare. Where is it?
I'm sorry.
John.
Don't do this.
- Don't do this!
- Back off!
- John, she'll kill you.
- There's only one way to find out.
Are you here to kill me, John?
Are you here to kill me?
No.
Promise.
I'll never lead you to her.
So if that's why you left me alive,
you might as well kill me right now.
I'll never do the Devil's work.
We'll see.
Thank you for joining me tonight.
I'm pleased to announce
the formation of a new division.
It'll cross disciplines,
draw from many areas
of expertise,
and require the highest level of work
from each of your groups.
Each of our groups?
How's that? Won't you be hiring...
I'll be taking team members
from each division
- and creating a new team.
- With all due respect,
and I can only speak
on behalf of the AI division
when I tell you
that I haven't a man to spare.
Your division will be hard-hit.
A list of new team members
will be on your desks after you leave.
The name of the new group is Babylon.
- It's from the Bible.
- And what does Babylon do?
I mean,
besides steal our team members.
Mr. Tuck,
it's going to change the world.
I got what I could.
Some smoke and water damage,
but you don't have to start over.
It wouldn't be the first time.
Thanks.
There's one too many.
Charley took off.
He said to say bye.
Guess he really does have a wife.
Have you seen John?
I think he's using the shower.
Do you believe in the Resurrection?
What?
The story of Jesus Christ.
The Resurrection.
Do you believe in it?
Would you if you'd seen
what I've seen?
Faith isn't part of my programming.
Yeah, well, I'm not sure
it's part of mine either.
Don't let him do that again.
If I ever go bad again...
don't let him bring me back.
I made you a sandwich
and brought you some clothes.
I'll be out soon.
John, I need you to know
everything that happened today.
Everything we did.
It was all...
It just happened the way it did.
And there's nothing we can do
to change it.
Whatever happened, we're alive.
Okay? We're alive.
I know you need more
from me today, but...
It's gonna have to be enough.
Can you hear me?
Are you listening?
Yeah, I'm listening.
Happy birthday.
That was something, wasn't it?
Wonder what she's got planned.
Who knows what goes on
in that brain of hers?
I don't know understand what the hell
she's talking about anyway.
Zen koans and Bible quotes.
It's all a bunch of bull.
Our options have tripled
since she took over,
so I wouldn't bite the hand
if I were you.
Well, that's easy for you to say.
She's not cannibalizing your division
for some top secret Torah study.
God, that bitch pisses me off.
Sorry I piss you off, Mr. Tuck.
The feeling's mutual.