Previously on terminator,The
sarah connor chronicle.
What did you want it to Show me.
We need to learn how they Work.
How to fight them
We are developing a human interactive AI
The name is babylon
It's going to change the World.
Dr. buoyed sherman.
He's on that wall for a reason.
Still fuzzy as to why you Called me.
The AI needs to be trained.
Do you care about this Girl?
Yeah.
Leave her alone.
You are pissed off because
I found someone I like spending time with,
and it's Not you.
-Jesse
-Hey, baby.
What does it mean to you?
I keep seeing it my dreams.
It means something.
Go back to bed.
Keep it running.
We'll be back.
You got it.
Right place?
Right place.
Should have brought john.
Don't need to know much
About computers to do this.
Get the ones over there.
Same as the rest.
It's vaporware
There is nothing there.
I didn't say that.
It's a design for an AI
Built to handle big problems.
You need a whole server farm To run it,
and they got zip, Less than zip.
after you lobotomize their desktops
But they have a design.
Yeah,it's like all those articles you read
how the Terrorists have
the plans for nuclear bombs
And all they are missing is the plutonium.
Another dead-end.
Chasing phantoms and
smudges On the wall again.
Artificial intelligence.
The company logo,with 3 dots
Our fingerprints left by
That poor bastard while
Bleeding out in the basement.
That's all.It's just blood.
Everything on that wall has Meant something.
It's all blood.
Cromartie's body is not in Ellison's yard.
Nobody is saying to stop Looking.
But this, it's not the turk.
You have been looking really hard, mom,
maybe too hard.
If you are going to start
In, too, don't, okay.
Good morning.
Good morning to you.
I did some digging on the drives
The systems is hunting for Start-up money.
Need investors for the server
farm they are going to build.
Big investors.
I made you an appointment.
Here's your cover.
I am a rich divorceee
Looking to put my money in Tech start-ups.
That's right.
I also made you a cheat Sheet
so you wouldn't sound Like a total moron
when you Are asking about networks.
I have no idea what you just said.
Yeah, that's my point.
Were you up all Night doing this.
A start-up, okay.
So Cyberdyne was
Andy good was building a chess Program,
barbara chamberland
Was trying to solve a traffic Problem.
It always starts small.
You got 30 seconds.
Go.
Funny Derek
25.
I'm not joking.
I was sent back to find him.
You could have told me.
You could have told me
you Were living with him,
with her, It. Metal.
Wasn't talking anymore.
Just her.
He is making questionable Decisions.
Getting people killed.
Good people.
Ten seconds.
She has taken over.
It's sick.
It's what it is.
Imagine if he spends the
next 20 years with her.
Imagine what he will become.
What she will turn him into.
Just try.
I'm here to stop her.
I'm here to save him.
I have got to think about this.
What the hell are you doing Here?
Why did connor send you back?
I love you.
But don't push it.
James Ellison,been a long time.
Heard you lost some weight.
Well, too much irony in a Diet is not good.
What've you got?
Heat wave blew a Transformer on sunday,
blacked Out half of downtown.
Single guy working the Weekend.
Spent eight hours in a sealed Room,
no ac, no ventilation.
Heated up until the heat baked Him to death.
Not a happy ending.
His name is dr. buoyed Sherman.
Consultant on a project here.
He worked downstairs.
Downstairs.
The basement.
We call the project babylon.
Sophisticated computer Program.
An artificial intelligence.
During the blackout,
The A.I. reseerve
generator powered for itself
In doing so shut down the
Building's other systems.
This ai, gas control over The building?
You make it sound like a Monster movie.
The facility and ai are Interconnected
to the extent That it needs
the facility's Resources to help it grow.
Does growing involve
Allowing to agonizing death
of an otherwise healthy man?
I don't know what his Intentions were.
Intentions.
Now that does osound like a Monster movie.
Which is why we need to Find out.
Thank you, colonel.
Good to see you.
Sarah Gail,Alex,Welcome to Dakara
Have to bear with us,
we Had a break-in last night.
They took our drives,
Industrial espionage for sure.
A lot of money in the ai.
A lot of money.
Aren't you worried they
got Your software know,
pass it Off as their own.
No.
My son built security measures Into the code.
Anyone tries to use the system
It will attack.
Is that why the airforce Wants it.
The airforce has been Interested in
ai applications For a long time now,
as par Back as the '80s.
Strange that you call the '80s far back.
I know,isn't it.
Are you a music fan?
That's how I mark the decade.
Always will be duran, duran.
I loved duran, duran.
Used to go dancing.
I miss dancing.
We would dress up.
Big hair.
it's the hardest thing to get right
-Hair
-Right.
So, the airforce?
Spreading money all over.
Rnd, industry cofinancing, Prizes.
I call her emma.
Ai, her name is emma.
Like my mom.
You never knew her.
She died in a car crash in 1984.
Coffee always helps me Think better. You?
Always.
Do you like chess?
I don't pretend to know what
goes on in that big Brain.
Operates in rounds that
you And I can't imagine.
He just has trouble with this One.
Needs you.
I bet sometimes it feels like He always will.
Do you have any kids.
Just one. Just my son.
Also challenging.
Yeah.
In his own way.
Well, then you get it.
Do anything for our kids.
Throw our lives out the window If we had to.
Tell me what you need.
Last night I would have
Said $100,000 and a little Patience.
This morning,
I need ten times That and a miracle.
A hell of a morning.
Design is so good.
How much time do you have?
Two weeks.
You need more than I have.
Call me alex.
Sorry, alex.
I'm sorry, too ms. gail.
Call me sarah.
Hi. I'm looking for riley.
Yeah, sure.
You must be john.
Hey, this is john.
Hi.
John, come in.
Riley's upstairs.
So your foster parents.
Not really what I imagined.
Yeah, they are nice.
They are too nice.
They are aliens.
See those kids down there.
They are not theirs.
They are just losers and
cast offs and rejects.
They run a loser camp here.
So what about my posters?
What's your favourite?
Ah, I don't know.
I went here so many.
I have been there with my mom.
What about you?
I'm going to guess the bear.
You seem like a good merit person.
Not a poster of a bear.
It's a poster of a fish
being Caught by a bear.
Swiped out of the water
Totally random.
Do the other fish even care?
Do they even notice?
No.
They just keep swimming
like nothing happened.
Nothing important did.
You know what, I think I'm going to go.
No.
Stay.
I mean,
you came here for a reason, right.
Stay.
Back in mexico,
I promised to explain everything.
The truth.
But the truth is there
is nothing I can explain.
Nothing I can say.
You don't have to say anything, john.
It's okay.
You can just sit here with me.
I would like that.
Sorry.
Okay, we got three dots, ai with a name.
Strong sense of self-preservation.
Plus the united states Airforce.
What does this add up to for You?
Not the turk.
Sandra doesn't play chess.
He prefers go.
It's a game.
Chinese invented it 5,000 Years ago.
Sandra said it has been calculated there more
Possible go games
In the all-atoms in the universe.
He offered to teach me how to play.
Did he offer to tell you about his ai?
It's not the turk.
I told you Sandra doesn't play Chess.
Can be a piece of the Puzzle.
We have seen that before.
Strange things happen at the one, two point.
It's go proverb.
Means the usual rules don't always apply.
Always the same rules. They always apply.
The car has no money.
Without this the airforce deadline.
They will find the money.
Everything they need.
Every penny.
They will get their miracle.
How do you know?
I know because it's written
In blood on my basement wall.
Cute top.
You wanted to talk.
You look tired.
Are you sleeping enough?
He came to visit me today.
And I thought he was going to
Tell me everything.
I think that's what he wanted To do.
And then nothing happened.
He just left.
Something's wrong.
Off balance.
Steady him.
He is reaching out.
He ran away from me.
He is a boy.
A lot of mirrors in this Room.
Did you notice that?
I don't think I can do this Anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's not easy, I understand.
Maybe you even have some
real Feelings for him.
You wouldn't. He is john connor.
A reason people follow him all over hell.
What if I want out?
How would you do that?
Where would you go?
There is no out.
You can do this.
You have to do this.
Take a look at this.
Do you see him?
The three dots on the belt.
If you are going to talk about my mother
when she is Not even here.
I'm talking about the
three Dots on this belt.
I'm seeing them everywhere Now.
Got me thinking how crazy this can make you.
You start seeing things in Every corner
and on every Wall.
Pretty soon you forget what it
Was you were looking for in The first place.
All of us, every one.
I remember. I always Remember.
Do you?
Are you sure?
Derrick, what the hell?
Nothing.
I just need to know that
you Are seeing clearly.
I need to know someone
is, but Especially you.
How old did you say your Son was?
I didn't, but he is 16.
Had our kids about the same Age.
Had mine when I was 21.
You?
19.
My wife, emma, was 19 when we First met.
The debut performance of pink Floyd the wall,
daily memorial Sports arena.
I remember that.
I wanted to see it so bad.
That was 1980, so you Were ...
Nine?
I was very young.
This morning I told you i Needed a miracle.
Did you get it.
Do you remember the chess Tournament,
airforce sponsored A couple of months ago.
A friend of a friend works for A company
that sponsored the Winners, the japanese.
They have a chip prototype.
Chip.
It's a super computer.
Small enough to fit on
the end Of your finger.
They want to license it to us.
We quietly put it through its Paces,
and they get a real World test,
and if it works,
We are all geniuses.
Very rich geniuses.
What do you need for this Chip?
A deposit.
Japanese friends are very risk Averse.
They want half a million to
Demonstrate seriousness.
You think it works.
This chip?
It's the future.
I have been in warmer morgues.
Got to keep the temperature not to go frozen
Towers would fry.
Computer is like everything Else.
Power it generates heat,
Requires cooling, needs more Power.
You know Babylon is a kind of a pig.
Babylon.
You know the story£¿
I minored in beer bang Engineering.
I didn't read a lot of Stories.
It was a marvel.
God destroyed it.
God have gave it a shot yesterday.
The blackout should have
shut it down completely.
Should it
Babylon routed every watt
From the generates to keep Itself running.
It broke the rules.
It invented new ones.
Mr Waiver said dr. sherman
Worked on the ...
Yeah.
Touchy feely, BS, if you Ask me.
How did it feel about him?
Sorry?
Babylon.
How did it feel about Dr. sherman?
I know how that sounds.
It's a computer.
I mean, how does a coffee
Maker feel about coffee?
You heard me.
You are asking if I knew
It was killing sherman
when it threw the switch?
Impossible.
Help.
It's not enough.
What would be enough?
Everything.
Everything then.
You are certain?
Certain as --
is a luxury.
The rules do not apply.
I guess it's enough.
Are you okay?
I'm still patient
Big prolong.
You have to use the full range
Of tools on a guy like him
Before you can close.
You are lucky you and your
Tech pair aren't as tight.
You are kidding?
A little bit.
Are you sure you want to do This in cash?
I don't like banks.
Return the toast, proper Etiquette.
Used to think that it was Impossible.
Circuits are so tiny you are
All but in the quantum realm.
It's the most sophisticated Process on earth.
If you could take your Memories,
your consciousness,
Everything that makes you a Person,
turn it into pure data
And download it on to a Machine.
That you could run it.
Are you going to eat that?
America.
I love it here.
No pressure.
No expectations.
Good sucker
So how long do you estimate
Before we stop screwing around Here
and you hand over the Chip?
Pleasure to do business With you.
Don't worry.
Didn't know you spoke Japanese.
I was into stix before Duran, duran.
My turn.
No, it's not, it's my turn.
Whatever. It's my turn.
Hand me the remote.
You missed dinner again.
Leftovers are in the Fridge.
All right.
Give it back.
The remote.
You took it, and I know you Did.
Riley saw.
I did not, you lier.
I'm going to tell mom.
Tell mom what?
Gina took the remote.
And she wants to watch.
I know you are upset.
We don't use those words in This house.
She started and riley saw.
Crazy.
What.
I said he is crazy.
You are all crazy.
Everyone of you.
Just sit here in your cozy Little house
with your cold Sewgas --
sodas and facebook Pages
like it matters.
Like it's real but it's not.
It's going to burn
and you Will be nothing but skulls.
Don't you get it.
You are dead.
All of you are dead.
Honey.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Look at them.
So many dreams.
About to burn those dreams to The ground.
Connections are up.
Drawing full power.
Loading the program.
What's going on?
Processor register error in The cp memory.
I'm sure it's just a Hiccup.
The data,
a post stamp on a Pool table.
Trying to push a watermelon
Through a garden hose.
our enemy is not 12.
This chip is not digned
This guy appears more advanced.
they screwed us.
My family used to run a
dry Goods store
for the second World war.
After pearl harbour
when they Were getting
rounded up for internment
neighbours offered to watch
our home and business For us.
Just sign this little piece of Paper.
What grandpa didn't know
While his son was fighting Across italy 442nd
the Neighbours were getting the
Property condemned and
deeding It to themselves.
You couldn't have known.
I will fix it.
Make it right.
I don't know how long it will Take
but I will pay you back Every dime.
This isn't important right Now.
I will talk to him.
You don't just talk to Someone like him.
It is old country.
You know what it is.
A gangster.
You hit him, he will hit You back.
Only he will hit you back Tenfold.
He will mail what's left of You
to your son one piece at a Time cod.
And you trusted him.
Most of these guys mobbed Up.
You didn't buy that chip.
You were paying him to steal It.
Now we know all the facts.
Means, opportunity, but Intent.
we can only guess.
Why did you ask him?
Ask the babylon ai, ask john Henry.
John henry.
It has a name.
Something dr. sherman did.
Gave it that name.
Not a person.
No.
But it's a mind.
talk to john Henry.
Communicates through images,
Symbol responses,
thought About using a
natural language Interface,
but decided against It.
Too creepy.
But it does voice recognition.
Just talk to him.
John henry, I'm James Ellison.
Okay.
You know who I am.
Good.
Do you know dr. boyd sherman?
That's a yes.
One is yes. Zero is no.
Did you work with him Yesterday?
Did you work with him today?
Why is that?
No operator.
No operation.
Could mean dead.
Could be waiting for input.
Rephrase it.
Show me what happened to Dr. sherman.
He was in the lab when the Power went out.
Biometrics showed normal.
Generators came on line.
Power went to the server Farms.
Dr. sherman tried to leave
but The electronic door failed.
His pulse increased.
There was only enough power
to run and cool the servers.
Security and biometric
Monitoring went off line.
John henry,
show me Security video
and biometrics For the lab
at the time External power returned.
His heart had stopped.
His body temperature had risen To the room
to almost double Standard temperatures.
Well above human Survivorability levels.
He was dead.
But john henry says medical
attention require it.
John henry,
was dr. sherman Alive at this time.
But you called the paramedics.
You thought they could help?
Am I alive?
Am I dead?
No operator.
Doesn't understand the Question.
John henry,
how did you Feel about dr. sherman?
Do you understand that
Redirecting the power to the Server farms
caused Dr. sherman to die?
What image do you associate
With that information?
John henry,
What image do you associate
With that information?
Has no feeling for what it Did.
Has no opinion.
That's what I was telling you.
Sure, you taught it Procedures.
You taught it rules.
But it has got no ethics, no Morales.
Whether it had any feeling
About dr. sherman shouldn't Matter.
If you had taught it to value Sherman's life.
Someone killed a man.
And it wasn't john henry.
Excuse me.
What would you teach it?
What would you teach it if you Could?
Teach commands.
Start with the first ten.
Get down on the ground now.
I don't have money
English got good. Real good.
please don't kill me.
If I were you I would
try To talk me out of it.
What do you want me to say.
I'm an actor.
I will say whatever you want Me to say.
I am just an actor
an actor. Who hired you?
Real.
I told you.
I want the chip. The real chip.
I just hand it back was handed to Me by him.
That's all I swear.
Don't lie to me.
Please.
He is not lying.
How the hell do you know?
I know.
You never saw my face.
Did you get it?
Something is going on here.
We have to dig deeper.
Guy's an actor.
You know who hired him and you Know why.
Someone going to fill me In.
The dots,
the ai, airforce, Chip
Nothing.
Listen to yourself.
First it's the dots,
then the Ai, now the chip.
Whatever you needed it to be,
That's what it is.
You got played. It happens.
Welcome to the human race.
zander? zander
Who are you working for?
zander and I
I don't know what you mean.
Don't lie to me. I hate liers.
Not working for anybody.
It's just me and zander.
I has been spent a Couple
of years in a nut House.
You want to know why.
Men like you.
It was me that blew the building sky high
so don't lie to me.
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for.
What did you do?
The money. I'm sorry about the money.
It's not about the damn Money.
Where is zander.
Tell me about the chip,
ai, About the three dots.
Don't hurt my boy.
Please.
Stop changing the subject
And making this about your Wife,
poor grandpa, your son.
It is.
It's all about him.
It's all about zander.
Three dots.
You crazy bitch.
- You want to see zander,
- Please.
Want to see your son.
Please don't hurt him.
I will kill you.
Tell him.
Tell him the truth.
Dad.
It's okay.
I won't let her hurt you.
Tell your son what you have Done
or will throw you both Through that window.
Don't think she can't.
there was no chip.
I made it up to get her money.
What?
No chip.
I hired a man to sell to us.
We couldn't make the airforce Deadline, zan.
No chance.
I had to make sure you were Taken care of.
I just couldn't take that Chance.
But it could work.
My design can work.
Daddy, I hope you are right. I do.
I have faith in you.
It's just sometimes I barely
Understand what you are Saying.
And I wonder if you understand Me.
The money is under my desk.
And it's just ...unlocked.
I'm going to regret giving You a key.
John connor is my nephew.
Three people know that fact.
You are the fourth.
I see
I came here to fight a war.
And do whatever it takes to Stop sky net.
Now today.
If we are going to do this,
There is no more room for Secrets.
If there is anything you Haven't told me,
I need to Hear it now.
Remember when we were Stationed at the point,
that Whole time
I was using your Toothbrush.
the one in my basket
I wasn't using that to brush my teeth.
Mom.
It's riley.
I'm okay.
Knocking.
How not like you.
Sarcasm, how not like you.
Oh, wait, that's exactly like You.
I just wanted to stop by to
Let you know that I reject Your rejection.
You want to go for a walk?
Mom, I'm going out for A while.
I thought about what you Said, about rules.
The ten commandments.
I'm not qualified to teach
John henry those things.
I don't know how.
That's why dr. sherman was Here.
I want to show you something.
In the folklore
John henry raced a
steam-drill through a moutain.
One man alone challenge the machine.
Armed with an iron hammer
Say he was born with it in his Hand.
His heart gave out, he died, I know.
John henry defeated the Machine.
But he couldn't stop progress.
Hello, mr. ellis.
My name is john henry.
How are you today?
www.tvsubtitles.net