Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles
- You've got a nuclear sub?
- Seawolf sub.
The Jimmy Carter. We've got a scrubbed
trip eight for a captain.
Damn it, Cameron,
you're supposed to burn the endos.
- What is happening with you?
- I've planted an explosive
in my skull, near my chin.
It's a small amount, but it's enough.
I saw the metal,
and she knows that I saw it.
Master your fear.
Remember the mission.
I can't go back there.
You are here to keep John Connor
away from her.
- I can get her to tell me the truth.
- Stay away from her.
Cameron was supposed to kill me!
You knew that was the only thing
that would turn John against her.
I rescued you from hell!
And I took you to paradise.
You don't need to be so dramatic.
It's a milk run.
A milk run across 8,000 miles
of metal-infested ocean.
Are you gonna be like this
every time I ship out?
Listen, Jesse,
I'm going on a mission, too.
I see.
One of those missions.
It's something else.
- It's different.
- Different.
How's it different?
What does different mean?
Different means different.
Just listen to me.
You're stuck in a can under the ocean,
with one of those things...
Don't worry about Queeg.
He's a good bloke.
He's not a bloke.
Jesse, he's not on our side.
Don't ever think that.
Aim for the chip.
Aim for the chip, they don't get up.
I love you too.
Means "I'll see you later."
What're you doing?
Moving.
Yeah, well...
Seems about the right time for that.
Get your stuff sorted.
I'm nearly done with the living room,
I'm gonna start on the garage.
Why don't you let me
take the garage?
I got a lot of memory cards
and flash drives.
I need to sort through. I don't want us
to save our Dakara Records
and torch my old copy
of Space Invaders.
It's all yours.
Thanks.
Great, it looks like
a robot serial killer lives here.
I guess one does.
I'm doing inventory.
Don't do it here.
We need to clear all this stuff out
before mom comes in and finds it.
Dig a hole out back.
Down below the retaining wall.
We'll bury the parts
and come back for them later.
We have to find a place
to burn them.
And we will burn them.
What you drinking?
I don't know.
You don't know what you're drinking?
There's booze in it.
Some sugary crap to cut the hell
outta the burning taste, and some ice.
'Course,
this one's pretty much empty.
Can you get her another one of...
whatever she's drinking?
How do you order it?
Just like you did.
But it's gotta start somewhere.
You can't just sit down and ask for it.
- What happened to your face?
- Lot of questions
for a guy
who wants to get in my pants.
- Do I?
- Yeah, see... there's another one.
That's a nice costume.
You thinking about a career
in the military?
Actually, I fly P-3S.
For the Navy.
- Brown shoe.
- Guilty as charged.
- You?
- Submarine.
- Bubblehead.
- A bubblehead!
They let women on subs in Australia?
Reprogrammed killer robots too.
Yeah, we don't discriminate.
Well, there's a coincidence.
I hunt subs, you drive subs.
Sort of like the wolf
and the sheep dog.
Not that I'm comparing you
to a dog, or anything.
That's a good point, actually.
In fact, I just remembered something.
- What's that?
- Sheep dogs hate wolves.
And I hate brown shoes.
I can't believe you guys are
just up and moving like this.
You could let me throw a party.
You know you never did come to dinner.
Tape.
It's okay.
It's not like you're moving to Mars.
We can still totally keep in touch.
Absolutely.
- Let me help you with that.
- I'm good. Sit down.
You know, I'm fine.
People say it takes a while
to get back to fighting trim,
but I snapped back
like a rubber band.
Yeah, mostly like a rubber band.
You look great.
I'm thinking if I can
breastfeed him till he's five,
maybe I can trick my body
into letting me keep these boobs.
Kidding.
Sort of.
- Who's got the baby?
- Trevor.
He's...
He's not back, he's just visiting.
He said he needed some daddy-time.
I don't blame him.
Not after the call
they got last night.
They found a girl
in the river.
Shot through the chest.
Trevor had said that it looked like
she'd been executed.
That's terrible.
Pretty little blonde thing.
Probably moved here from Iowa
or something to be an actress,
and fell in with the wrong people.
Dreams die hard.
Then Trevor said
all they have to go on are some scars
from an attempted suicide
and a tattoo on her wrist.
A pretty little star.
Right here.
Your mother's coming.
All right, quick.
Hide this stuff.
I need to talk to John.
Alone.
Goodbye, bird.
There's a 51% chance
I wouldn't have killed you.
I know.
I heard you.
Riley's dead.
Episode 2x18
v 1.00
Subtitles: Projet-SG
Was it you?
Did you kill her?
What if I did?
Don't play games with me.
I need the truth.
I didn't kill her.
- I wanna believe you.
- Believe me.
Sometimes you lie to me.
Yes.
I do, but I'm not lying now.
I am sorry.
You're sorry?
For what?
For your loss.
I really wish
I could believe that too.
So are you gonna say anything?
Thanks.
For bailing me out.
- I know you don't like police stations.
- Maybe that's because I'm a fugitive.
I know.
- So thanks.
- What happened?
I told you, I got in a fight.
With four naval aviators.
Really just three.
One of them went down pretty quick.
What's going on?
Nothing.
I don't believe you.
I need to know
what the hell's going on.
I told you.
Nothing.
- We crossed the line yet?
- Not yet.
Give it a tick.
Zero degrees north, heading
south-southwest over the equator.
Now we've crossed the line.
One nice thing about metal driving
the boat, a schedule's a schedule.
One nice thing.
- That mean we're done?
- Quiet, you.
Proclamation.
Know ye, that sonarman second class
Christopher Garvin,
on the 13th day of September, 2027,
aboard USS Jimmy Carter,
appeared at the equator
at latitude zero, longitude 180,
entering into our royal domain,
and having been inspected
and found worthy by my royal staff,
was initiated into the solemn mysteries
of the Ancient Order of the Deep.
I command my subjects
to honor and respect him
as one of our trusty shellbacks.
Now rise, shellback.
- Never gets old, does it?
- Never.
Depth charge?
General quarters, go.
Go!
Come and play hide and seek, mommy.
- I'm working.
- But you promised.
Patience is a virtue, Savannah.
To tolerate delay.
It implies self-control
and forbearance.
As opposed to wanting
what we want when we want it.
Something to think about.
Would you like
to play hide and seek?
My daughter, Savannah...
She's missing.
She's in the building, Mr. Ellison.
We just have to find her.
- There's 23 stories.
- Yes.
And there's someone who knows
what's going on in all of them.
John Henry, we're looking
for my daughter, Savannah.
- Have you seen her today?
- Yes, I have.
She wanted to play a game.
- Where is she now?
- She's hiding.
Tell us where she's hiding.
That's not how the game works.
How's the game work?
Hide and seek,
there are many variations.
The one we're playing,
you guess what I'm thinking,
I give you a clue.
Listen to me, John Henry.
You're gonna tell me where Savannah is,
and you're gonna tell me now.
I'm thinking of a country.
Come again?
Let's play the game.
This is ridiculous!
I'm not gonna bargain with a computer.
If I'm not mistaken, Mr. Ellison,
we've got no choice.
You hit him in the mouth,
didn't you?
Never aim for the mouth.
- What's that?
- Antibiotic.
You know, one time
when Kyle and I were kids,
we saw two tunnel trolls go at it
over a can of stewed tomatoes.
The loser got three teeth knocked out,
and the winner...
got a blood infection
from his split knuckles
and died a week later.
The human mouth is filthy.
You got that?
What?
Damn.
John okay?
All right.
Hold tight, I'm on my way.
John's... girlfriend is dead.
A cyborg did it.
- You know that for sure?
- Who else could it be?
- What are you gonna do?
- About the metal?
What are you gonna do?
Because you can't kill her, Derek.
- What?
- That's not something you can do.
He has to make that decision
on his own.
You've really thought this through.
No.
But I think about it.
Just like you do.
More depth charges.
Shook us up a bit, but no damage.
They want us to make a mistake.
Reveal our position.
A lot of metal
in the water, Captain.
Barrage.
- Getting closer.
- ASW bots.
- How many?
- Travel in packs, no way to tell.
Mister Gavin?
Not ASW bots.
Oh, man. Oh, man.
Kraken.
We got a kraken.
- You sure?
- Bet my life on it.
- Feed the sonar picture to tactical.
- Aye, ma'am.
You're a big fellow, aren't you?
And you're very far from home.
That can't be right.
- Where are we?
- Chief of the boat,
status of our torpedo stock?
Two, maybe three
I'd consider worth using in a fight.
Ready tube one.
Hold for my order.
Queeg.
You can't fight a kraken
with one torpedo. Or three.
We need to break contact
and find a way around.
Mister Garvin, active sonar, please.
One ping only.
One ping, aye.
Torpedo in the water.
Closing fast. Maybe... 40 seconds.
Status on my torpedo?
- Torpedo ready, but...
- Thirty second fuse.
Match our speed
and bearing after breakaway.
Fire.
You heard him. Fire.
- Torpedo away.
- Still closing, 55 knots.
You got us 20 degrees down bubble.
Ahead, full.
Queeg, you're tak...
Taking the boat to 729.8 meters.
- Crush depth.
- To the edge of crush depth.
The kraken won't be able to follow.
The sonar will reflect off
the thermocline layer.
- We'll be...
- Invisible. We're playing dead.
- Eight seconds to torpedo contact.
- Approaching crush depth.
If he's off by even a millimeter,
for even a fraction of a second...
He won't be.
This is what he does.
Two detonations.
Our torpedo and theirs.
1,100 meters to starboard.
120 on the Z.
And now we roll over,
stick out our tongue,
and hold our breath.
Skipper, we're at 729.8.
I'm aware, Chief.
Thank you.
729.8... and holding.
You may return
to your duty stations now.
You heard the Captain, people.
What, you've never been
20 centimeters from your maker?
Move.
Skipper, when we're done
skating over our deaths...
I got a question.
Why are we 300 miles off course?
We were using it for research.
- To find out what...
- Don't.
John, just don't.
Don't make excuses for her.
Don't cover for her.
- I knew about the parts.
- I'm not talking about the parts.
I'm talking about Riley.
Well, there's nothing
to talk about, is there?
Because Riley's dead.
How do you think that happened?
I don't know.
I'm gonna figure it out, though.
You know, John.
We both know.
Cameron didn't do it.
How can you say that?
How can you be so sure?
Because I'm sure.
And I know her.
And she told me.
She told you?
Just like she told you she destroyed
every part we ever captured?
Just like she tells us what she does
every night when we go to sleep?
When she comes back in the morning,
she's covered in cuts and bruises.
Just like she told you
she loved you?
You don't know anything.
I'm thinking of an herb.
Tarragon?
We're wasting time.
But it's working. His game.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you not angry?
Why should I be?
We have a way to get her back.
Tell me where the child is.
Look.
You asked me to teach him
ethics, morals, and rules.
What good is it
if he's not gonna follow them?
He will.
If we let him learn the rules
on his own.
Oregano.
Correct.
See there.
A lucky guess.
Lucky.
Give us our clue.
The sun is shining on Savannah.
Security.
Check near all windows.
Anyplace light is coming through.
Copy.
I'm thinking of an animal.
Antelope.
Lion.
Horse.
- Bird!
- Correct.
- Give us our clue.
- The answer is the clue.
What?
What does that mean?
Just what he said.
Bird is our clue.
I know where she is.
Security.
Meet us at the elevators.
Savannah, are you okay?
Go to your mother.
You found me, mommy.
Yes, darling...
I did.
Aaron?
I remember.
Is Riley around?
No, she didn't come home last night.
Riley didn't come home.
Thanks.
Foster kids...
That's the way it is
with them sometimes.
They drift into your life,
then they drift back out again.
Not always according to plan.
She's a tough one, too.
Good heart,
as I'm sure you know, but...
tough to know.
I really really needed
to talk to her.
I don't know if you could maybe just
take a message for me...
- See, last time that we spoke...
- Hang on a sec.
God, Riley!
Are you all right?
- Where are you?
- Everything's fine.
I'm in Riverside, it's a long story.
Everything's fine.
We've been worried sick.
We were about to call the police.
Please don't do that.
Everything's fine.
John, too... he's here.
Really? Can I talk to him?
Me?
You're in Riverside?
Listen... we'll talk...
when I see you.
I thought you'd wanna hear my voice.
You know you're really
freaking everybody out, right?
Am I freaking you out, now?
- So let's talk later.
- I'm sorry.
It's just...
I've been thinking
about my parents a lot.
And there are things
I can't get out of my head.
And I just thought if I came out
and saw where we used to live...
I know...
Stupid, right?
We'll talk about all this in person.
When you get back.
We're hanging up now.
Sure. That would be great.
I love you.
- What the hell was that about?
- What was what about?
What happened just now.
It was the plan.
No. The plan was
to call the foster parents.
The plan was
to let him hear her voice.
That's what I did.
That's not all you did.
What you did was not the plan.
The plan was to make
him think she's still alive...
So he wouldn't go to the police.
You became part of that plan.
Your reaction made it
more authentic.
Don't you think it was
more authentic that way?
Where are we going now?
We're not going anywhere.
I'm going somewhere.
And I'm gonna go alone.
- You shouldn't be alone.
- Yes, I should.
Did you have fun
playing the game, Mr. Ellison?
No, John Henry.
I did not.
Why not?
Because what you did
made me very, very angry.
- I don't understand.
- You kept a secret.
Is it wrong to keep a secret?
The secret you kept
could've harmed Savannah.
What if we couldn't have found her?
What if she'd fallen
from the roof and died?
Then she wouldn't be alive anymore.
And her life is important.
Human life is sacred.
If she had died...
it would've been your fault.
My fault?
Because you were the only one
who knew where she was.
And you made a choice not to tell.
That was the wrong choice.
I'm thinking about Riley.
What the cyborg did to her.
It's a terrible thing.
But...
if John realizes
what the metal is...
What it really does...
Maybe some good can come of it.
Maybe you can help him see that.
Good?
An innocent kid is dead.
Because that metal bitch
murdered her in cold blood.
No good comes out of that.
None. Not ever.
You're a good man.
Oh, yeah?
Don't let anyone tell you different.
- Hoo-roo.
We've been bearing 30 degrees
off course for four hours.
Into a major Skynet zone.
- What's going on?
- Our new mission required it.
What mission?
Where are we headed?
A deepwater oil platform
near the Indonesian Archipelago.
Lieutenant Dietz and his team will
board the rig and retrieve a package.
We will deliver this package
to Seranno Point.
We have important cargo
to take to Perth.
- Components. Vaccines...
- Our orders come from John Connor.
These orders from John Connor...
Do they say what we're after?
What it is?
Yes.
They say what the package is.
Right.
Please inform the crew.
Thank you.
Just stay sharp, you'll be fine.
I know I'll be fine. I got this.
I'm serious, Dietz.
I'm always serious about being fine.
You do me one favor.
You see anything you don't like,
you think before you pull that trigger.
I've been seeing things
I don't like since J-Day.
You don't get to be my age
without thinking first.
I swear, Mom.
We'll hold hands
before we cross the street.
ASDS has cut engines, Commander.
I think we're clear for comms.
ASDS, this is Carter.
Over.
Hey, Mom.
I'll say this much
about a deep-sea oil rig...
Second-worst thing I've ever smelled.
Dark as night out here.
We're gonna keep this channel open.
Maintain radio silence
till you've got the package.
Planning on it.
Connor sent me.
John Connor.
I've come for that.
That's for him.
I'm here to pick it up.
I had planned on waiting for you
with Derek's sniper rifle.
Pulled the trigger.
Solved about 50% of my problems.
One shot.
Do you know how bad I'd have felt?
Very bad.
Not bad at all.
But I know someone
who'd have felt bad.
Someone who'd have never forgiven me
if I'd have done that.
I don't know what to do with you.
You know what the stakes are.
You know why we're here.
You know what this means.
And yet, here I stand.
Burning what's left of an endoskeleton
I'd thought we'd burned months ago.
I needed spare parts.
I don't care what you need,
because this is not about you.
It's not about me.
It's about John.
You're concerned for his safety.
- You bet I am.
- From Skynet.
From me.
Maybe.
Maybe especially you.
We're all a threat.
We're all a threat to John.
He worries about us.
That makes him vulnerable.
He cares.
I am not John's problem.
John is John's problem.
Humans are the problem.
There's only one way for him
to be safe.
That's to be alone.
What kind of life is that?
John's life.
Someday.
I'm sorry.