You shouldn't nest in the chimney.
You're migratory.
You need to find a mate.
That's a window, bird.
What am I going to do with you?
A bird in a chimney
is a fire hazard.
I'm not supposed to kill you,
but you can't stay here.
Go.
I was wondering
when we'd see you again.
They make you rest a couple days.
Does it help?
Not really.
Is there any more somewhere?
Downstairs under the sink.
I just needed a minute alone.
Sorry.
She say something?
She asked me about it.
To be nice, I think.
Well, it's nobody's business.
Well, it shouldn't
have happened here.
Or not at all.
It's in the past.
People don't forget about the past.
I'm not saying "forget it".
I'm saying
it's in the past.
- Sight's off.
- Gimme.
It's nice being able
to waste bullets on apples.
Yeah. It's nice being able
to waste apples.
April 21st, 2011.
I never asked you for Judgment Day.
Your Judgment Day.
You're right about the sight.
April 21st, 2011. That's mine.
What's yours?
Whenever mine is,
it might not be any more.
So, don't forget about it, love.
We'll know it when it happens.
I want you to help me
with something.
Didn't I just help with something
this morning in the shower?
There's a guy.
He's got some information I need.
- So, ask him.
- Not that kind of guy.
Not that kind of information.
I'm not here
to stop the war, sweetie.
I'm here to win it.
You keep saying that.
But, I don't know what it means.
I'm the one living with him.
How's that working out for you?
Is the metal alive and well?
Sarah running you around?
I'm here.
I'm asking you.
Either help me with my plan
or show me some progress on yours.
Okay. What do you need?
There was a stack of research here
on that lawyer.
The one who set up
the drone shell company.
Derek took it.
- When?
- While you were gone.
So, he's chasing it down?
- I don't know.
- He should keep me in the loop.
It's my loop.
You've been distracted.
I was kidnapped.
Which is distracting.
Talk to me about Riley.
What happened the day
she tried to kill herself?
She was very upset.
John could tell.
- She had a bruise on her face.
- Who gave her the bruise?
John thought it was her foster dad.
She said it was a door.
Liar. Then what?
Riley cut her wrists like this.
She almost bled to death.
- Do you think it was her foster dad?
- It's hard to say.
We don't know much about Riley.
We should know more.
I know where she lives.
I'll go talk to her foster parents.
I'll go. My loop.
Episode 2x17
V 1.00
Subtitles: Projet-SG
I killed a bird.
Not the one in the chimney.
I thought you should know.
A bird did that?
No. I did that. Look.
The bird experienced
an involuntary movement of my fingers.
It was fragile.
Wiggle your fingers.
Yeah, there's damage,
but it's buried pretty deep in there.
I don't know how it happened.
It was probably during a fight.
You're not designed
to fight other machines.
Maybe I could swap this out.
But it's not like we just have
spare parts lying around.
- You're supposed to burn the endos.
- Not all of them.
Says who?
You.
What, future me?
Future you.
Yeah, why doesn't that surprise me?
I have damage to my hand
and now you're able to fix it.
Future John has better
information than you do.
- She's gonna kill me.
- What? Who?
Her. Cameron.
- What happened? What did it do?
- I saw something. The metal.
- The metal.
- She cut her wrists.
- Why did it cut itself?
- I don't know.
But I saw the metal.
And she knows that I saw it.
Sweetie, if she knew you saw,
you'd be dead.
- I can't go back there.
- I wonder what's wrong with it.
- Has it been acting strange?
- Strange?
Everything she does is strange.
Did you not hear me?
I can't go back there.
Course you can, dear.
You put one foot
in front of the other.
Master your fear.
Remember the mission.
- There's gotta be another way.
- Trust me. There is only one way.
I won't let Cameron hurt you.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
Here's one from my private stash.
Kay doesn't buy the kind
with sugar or caffeine
but what's the point?
I hear you.
Must've been a shock,
what happened to Riley.
What's John say?
Getting anything out of that boy
is like pulling teeth.
But he did say
that she seemed upset that day
and she had a bruise on her face.
Bruise?
I'm a patient person,
but I swear,
there have been times...
Kids. They know
how to push your buttons.
Just saying if someone
was to lose their temper...
- Get physical...
- If by someone, you mean me...
These things do happen.
But not the way you're thinking.
Not by a long shot.
That girl assaulted my wife.
Went absolutely nuts.
Started yelling
about the world burning up
and bleached skulls
or some such nonsense.
She said that?
I wanted to report it.
Kay wouldn't let me.
But now I wish I had with you
coming around here accusing us.
I'm not accusing anybody.
First your kid drops out of school,
then so does she.
Next thing you know,
we got a guidance counselor at our door.
Even she thinks
John's a bad influence.
A guidance counselor.
She had a lot to say
about you and your family.
I was willing to dismiss it
as gossip...
Until I met you.
Do you have her name?
Keep John away from Riley.
She's been through enough.
Okay, clench your fist.
And, okay, now, fingers straight.
You feel any different?
Yes.
Are you all fixed?
I don't know.
Just try not to kill any more birds.
You're ahead of schedule.
With what?
What you need to learn.
I know it's just recon, Derek,
but I can't have you
running off like that.
I gotta go.
- Miss Wilson, thanks for coming.
- Ms. Baum.
So your family's moved
around a lot, I take it.
Unfortunately, my job requires it.
It's been difficult on John.
Hard for him to make friends.
I can imagine.
That's why I was so happy when Riley
first came home with him.
I didn't realize
she was so troubled.
Foster kids like these,
it's hard to tell.
A lot of them come
from broken homes, abuse.
Where does she come from?
An orphan out of Riverside.
Her parents died in a fire
in a meth lab. It's tragic.
I met her foster dad.
He said you talked to him about us.
I was curious about
why it happened in your home.
In your bathroom.
I have no idea.
My main concern
is that the girl get help.
Of course.
I've only known her a short while,
but I've grown fond of her.
- Funny, she thinks you don't like her.
- It's not the case.
So you're the one who took her
to the hospital afterwards?
No. I was out of town.
So there was no adult supervision
in the household at the time.
John's uncle stays with us
sometimes.
Yeah, Riley's mentioned the uncle.
Uncle Derek.
John's uncle on his father's side.
We're not involved
if that's what you're getting at.
Not getting at anything.
Just trying to paint a picture.
Do you think it's wise
to have an unattached,
adult male hanging around
a pretty, teenage girl
who's obviously
so desperate for attention?
What, did she say
something about him?
She might have.
If she did, it's confidential.
Miss Wilson, look,
John's a good kid.
Whatever's going on with this girl,
he's trying to be her friend.
He's trying to help her.
Like by taking her to Mexico?
Mexico?
Riley said she and John
took a trip to Mexico.
Now, I don't have to tell you
that transporting a minor
across the border without her parents'
permission is a federal offense.
I didn't know.
Obviously, I will talk to my son.
Miss Baum, I'm not out
to get anyone here.
My sense is that you're a decent person,
a hardworking mom.
I'm a big believer in keeping
your own house in order.
So why don't I let you handle
this your way...
For now.
I'd appreciate that.
Consider it done.
Keep taking the antibiotics.
That's it?
Why? Is there something else
you need, sweetie?
- No.
- 'Cause we really could use the room.
What are you doing?
I'm looking up a restaurant address.
Are you hungry?
Yeah. But this is actually
for Derek.
That Kaliba lawyer
he's been tracking,
the guy's got a booth
reserved there.
Not an ideal location for Derek
to acquire his target.
It's underground, and according to this,
crowded with friendly people.
Hard to dispose of the body.
I don't think
that's gonna be necessary.
Derek's just gonna
follow him and grab him
and press him about Kaliba.
To see if it's connected to Skynet?
- Exactly.
- It's going to be necessary.
- I'll make you a sandwich.
- Wait. Why?
You're hungry.
Why don't we let hungry
be my problem?
Sometimes it's nice to have help.
How's the hand?
Not a problem.
Aren't you supposed to be really good
at self-repair?
But sometimes it's nice
to have help.
Well, I'll make my own sandwich.
This one taken?
You buying?
I could introduce you to Davy.
I'm here for business,
not pleasure, thanks.
My mistake.
That one, huh?
What's he do anyway?
Lawyer.
He ever buy you a drink?
Once or twice.
How'd the muscle feel about that?
They very much enjoy the show.
It's nice having an audience.
So you're coming over later, right?
Just watch a movie or something.
Okay, I'll see you soon.
I just had an interesting conversation
with a counselor from your old school.
I forgot to send in
the quarterly home schooling thing.
Actualy, that didn't come up.
The main topic of conversation
was Riley.
What about her?
She has a lot to say.
About you and me, and Derek.
And Mexico.
- A school counselor told you this?
- All those things.
From a stranger's lips
to my own ears, John.
No, that doesn't make any sense.
And I talked to her foster dad.
I would've talked to him longer,
but he asked me to leave.
He thinks we're the reason
she tried to kill herself.
Because of Mexico?
Because Riley had a violent
breakdown about bleached skulls
and the end of the World.
I haven't told her anything.
I don't believe you.
Well, I swear to God
I've said nothing.
I'll talk to her.
- Might be too late for that.
- Well, what do you want me to do?
To prepare for what's gonna happen
when Cameron finds out.
Do you think it's possible for me
to know something future John doesn't?
That's hard to know.
Seems unlikely.
Do you think it's possible for me
to know something you don't know?
Are you asking me
if future John kept secrets from me?
I'm sure he did.
Is John here?
You owe him an explanation
for all the things you said.
What I've said?
To your foster dad.
To your guidance counselor.
Guidance counselor?
You're a terrible liar.
You don't owe me.
It's him who put his trust in you.
People know things, Riley.
True things.
They know about Mexico.
Why would I spill
my guts to my foster dad
or to a guidance counselor?
I've never said anything
to anyone, I swear.
What would I even say?
Can we go somewhere
more private, please?
You expecting someone else?
Someone with a clipboard.
- May I help you?
- Hi, there. I'm Molly Malloy.
I'm with the department
of child and family services.
How can I help you?
I was hoping that I could speak with you
about Riley Dawson.
- She's not here, is she?
- No, she's not.
Are you John?
What's this regarding?
Would it be easier
if I came in for a quick chat?
Thank you.
This is your fault.
- What's my fault?
- You're the reason that person is here.
You're John's sister.
You can't keep me here.
They don't always like
the way I do things.
I've heard you keep guns
in the home,
which, of course,
is every American's right.
For security. We were robbed.
Have you ever carried a weapon
outside of the house?
Can I ask again what this is about?
I'm just clearing up
a few details about
what kind of environment you've got
for kids like Riley or even John here.
I did a little search
and couldn't find
a concealed weapons permit
in your name.
Check the state of new Mexico.
Well, out of state permits
aren't valid in California.
True, but we have 60 days to file
an ownership report with the DOJ.
Sharp kid.
I'll be on the lookout for that.
What am I going to do with you?
I don't understand.
I don't know what you mean.
Children and family services
respond to complaints.
Are you a complainer?
I never told them anything.
- What would I even tell them?
- You don't belong here.
John isn't right for you
and you're not right for him.
He can't see that.
Stop. Please.
You're freaking me out.
You're unreliable.
I don't know what you do.
I'm just John's girlfriend.
That's it.
You can't be John's girlfriend.
You're a threat.
You can't stay here anymore.
But I can't let you leave.
You're John's sister.
What am I going to do with you?
Nothing.
You can't do anything to me
'cause you're John's sister.
Get it through your head.
You're just his sister.
Riley, come with me.
All right.
You wanna wait outside for me?
Were you gonna kill her?
I don't know what I was going to do.
What do you mean{\ you didn't know
what you were gonna do}?
Since when do you not know
what you're gonna do?
I don't know.
I should've killed her.
She's a threat to you.
That is not your decision to make.
- It's usually not a decision.
- Obviously it is this time.
And it's not yours.
What's happening with you?
I don't know.
I didn't make that call.
I know that.
I believe you. Really.
Riley, is there anything
you wanna tell me?
About what?
About anything.
Is there anything
you want to tell me?
Because today is the day.
Today is the day where you tell me
whatever it is
that you might want to tell me.
Today.
Is there anything
that you wanna tell me?
'Cause you're right.
I think today is the day.
You're late.
Where have you been?
I was hungry and I hate room service.
What's all this?
Recon on our guy.
He's got security 24/7.
Two 12 hour shifts.
Four guys total.
Armed.
The place he's staying at
is up in the hills.
High walls. Lots of cameras.
Guys with guns.
- We should take this slow.
- No. No slow.
He's chartered a flight. We'll grab him
on the way to the airport.
It's a moving target.
But, you see, the roads up there
are narrow and isolated.
I'm not sure I can do this.
What do you mean you're not sure
you can do this? You're in.
I'm out of practice.
You've got your people.
My people seem distracted.
What about you?
20:30 tonight.
Bring a vehicle to block the road.
You pin down the guards,
I'll snatch up the lawyer.
Look, she didn't rat us out.
She trusted someone.
They sold her out.
Who?
She won't tell me who.
This is not good, John.
This could mean
a lot of very bad things.
I know, Jesse. I know!
Let go.
- What the hell are you doing?
What are you talking about?
Calm down.
- You wanted him to care about me.
- Of course.
- To like me.
- Even to love me.
- Of course, sweetie.
We talked about it 1,000 times.
That was the plan.
But that wasn't enough, right?
And you knew it wasn't enough.
She's supposed to kill me, right?
That's it. That's the real plan.
- That's absurd.
- No, it's not.
You knew that was the only thing
that would turn John against her.
She's supposed to kill me.
You called the DCFs.
You called my foster parents.
You called my school.
How could you do that to me?
I trusted you.
I loved you!
I rescued you from hell
and I took you to paradise!
I gave you a purpose.
A chance to be a hero.
You know how few people get a chance
for their lives to mean something?
For their deaths to mean something?
- I made you matter.
- Stop!
You could've been beautiful.
But you're just a coward.
I can't find her.
If she's out there, she'll call you.
Eventually, she always does.
Cameron, did you...
You know I didn't.
What have you been doing?
You've been out here for hours.
Making something.
For you.
What is it?
You tried to fix me.
Twice now.
- It's not working.
- And?
I'm not capable of self-termination.
- Suicide.
- I can't kill myself.
But you can.
Why would I want to kill you?
You might have to some day.
I've planted an explosive in my skull
near my chip.
It's a small amount,
but it's enough.
Enough?
All you have to do
is hit the switch.
What would future John do now?
Future John doesn't live here.
You do.