Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles.
You're stuck in a can under the ocean
with one of those things.
Don't worry about Queeg.
He's a good bloke.
He's not on our side.
Why are we 300 miles off course?
Our orders come from John Connor.
Dietz and his team
will retrieve a package.
We will deliver this package
to Serrano Point.
Connor sent me.
I've come for that.
- What's happening with you?
- I've planted an explosive in my skull.
I know.
Riley's dead.
- Cameron didn't to it.
- How can you be so sure?
- She told me.
- Just like she told you she loved you.
You don't know anything.
I'm really sorry, John.
She was a good kid.
She didn't deserve what happened to her.
Few people do.
How long do you think
you could survive...
with Cameron...
if she wanted to kill you...
face to face?
What kind of weapon do I have?
Your fists.
And your elbows.
And your fingernails.
And your teeth.
Against her?
Those aren't weapons.
No, they're not.
You already know
the answer to that, John.
If she wants me dead, I'm dead.
She wants you dead, you're dead.
What are you getting at?
I wanna talk about something.
All right.
I wanna talk to you
about the future.
Yours?
Yours.
Carter, this is ASDS.
Package is secure.
Standing by for all-clear.
Visual on the package, ASDS?
Visual, aye-aye.
- What the heck is that?
- It's Connor's box.
- All we know?
- All we know.
Little help?
Captain?
I will secure the package
in the magazine.
Authorized access only.
You wanna let us little people know
what's in the box,
or is it classified between
you and Queeg?
It's between Queeg and Queeg.
I don't know a damn thing.
And that doesn't bother you,
metal keeping secrets from skin?
No. It doesn't.
Not even a little.
Well, it should.
And not just a little, but a lot.
We were sent to pick up
the box and bring it back.
So we're picking up the box
and bringing it back.
And one of us should know why.
One of us, not just one of them.
One of us knows.
His name's John Connor.
You think those things work for us?
Look around you.
We work for them.
Haulin' ass through the worst
of Indian country.
For what?
To take a damn box back to Serrano?
- Connor needs it.
- Connor?
Connor is so into
his big chess match with Skynet,
he doesn't even see how the tin cans
got us right where they want us.
Metal on every base
running the show in all but name.
Just waiting
to hit us all at once
with something big.
Maybe...
something that's in that box.
Break time's over.
Those of you on watch
get to your stations.
Get to your rack. I don't wanna see you
till forenoon watch.
"Yes, ma'am."
That's what you say.
You're a good sailor.
But the pressure's starting
to get to you.
So what's getting to you, ma'am?
You went to see the body.
You shouldn't have done that.
It was a risk. I know.
I don't mean the risk.
You shouldn't have
to remember her like that.
That's all.
There were things I needed to see.
And that I had to understand.
Do you understand them now?
I think so.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
Not you. Her.
We lost a day
evading the ASW bots near Fiji.
We'll take a more direct route
to make up the time.
Make sure the crew is prepared.
Queeg, this crew...
can sneak through the gates of hell
and back if it has to.
But they're not machines.
They work better
if they have a reason.
If they know why you expect them
to perform miracles.
This crew will do their job
because that's what's required
to survive and complete the mission.
You understand.
Motion detectors in the hold.
Unauthorized access to our cargo.
- Dietz, what the hell did you do?
- Could be anything in there.
A machine, a bomb. Anything.
And we'll be just gonna run it
right through the front door to Serrano.
At least we know.
- Of all the stupid things...
- The stupid?
Stupid is taking their word for it.
For anything.
- I'm not afraid of that thing.
- Well then, be afraid of me.
Guys.
You spend any time
in a work camp, Commander?
- Guys.
- You don't get to tell me anything.
And neither does the metal.
Guys, look!
Metal!
I told you. This is what happens!
This is what they do.
Pull his chip and make him tell us
what the hell is going on.
We divide into search parties.
We turn this boat over stem from stern
until we find that thing.
- We're gonna need guns.
- Commander Flores,
secure all sidearms
and plasma rifles.
Take Petty Officer Goodnow's body
to the cool room
and return to duty.
We continue as planned.
That thing, you know what it is?
- Yes.
- Then tell me.
At least tell me.
- We're a team, right? You can...
- That's not your concern.
Episode 2x19
1.01
Subtitles: Projet-SG.
We should just throw a rug down.
They'll never know the difference.
I'm sorry it's come to this.
- What? The moving?
- All of it.
I broke the rules.
What was the name of that hippie town
we were in before...
Before Nebraska?
- Garb-something.
- Garberville.
Right. That was a culture shock.
Going from hog farmers
and good old boys
to pot growers
and kids named Sequoia.
There was only one Sequoia.
There were three Sages, though.
I felt bad for you when we left.
You just started making friends.
Fitting in.
Fitting in?
I was getting in fights every day.
Well, you won those fights.
That's one way of looking at it.
I hated that town.
The matte layer is critical.
It both allows the colors
to stick to the miniature
and it provides the finished
statue with the illusion of depth.
But it's the detail work
I find the most interesting.
It challenges my fine motor control
and there are so many choices.
The eyes for example.
The window to the soul.
They're the window to the soul.
I read that.
That's what they say.
Then I should choose
my paint more carefully.
It doesn't matter, John Henry.
It's a statue. It's an object.
It doesn't have a soul.
It has eyes.
Your eyes look tired.
Is your soul tired?
No, my soul isn't tired, but I am.
And I am going home.
Please don't.
My monster is incomplete.
The eyes.
What color did you want to use?
Blue.
Pass me one of those.
Let's get this done.
Does this make us friends?
You're not eating.
What?
What's the matter?
You don't like hash browns?
No, I like 'em.
I'm just not hungry.
You're always hungry.
Everyone's always hungry.
Jeez, Dietz.
How can I eat with Goodnow dead
and that thing running around out there?
Gimme a break.
Have mine.
I said I'm not hungry.
Maybe.
Or maybe you're not really Garvin.
Maybe you're that thing.
Maybe you're freakin' crazy!
He could be metal.
We wouldn't know...
You want to see metal?
I'll show you metal...
Enough!
You're right, Garvin.
It's not you.
You're not the one who spends all day
locked in a room with metal.
Stand down, Dietz.
I knew you were a metal lover.
But maybe you're more than that.
Maybe you're one of them.
Just like that little metal bitch
that follows Connor everywhere.
Maybe we should check for safety.
Report to your duty stations.
You're not leaving this house.
John needs me.
If John needed you,
he would have asked for you.
You're not leaving this house.
The police could identify
Riley's body at any time.
I need to be with him.
Well if they do,
they'll probably come here.
So we should be happy he's out.
Why are you here?
Protect John. Hunt Skynet.
- Stop judgment day.
- But why are you here?
Right now. With us.
John sent you here from the future.
He sent you away.
Away from him.
Maybe you should think about that.
Maybe you should think about
why he didn't want you around anymore.
Hello, Ms. Weaver.
How are you this evening?
I'm well.
You're up late.
I convinced Mr. Ellison
to leave this body operational.
Did you now?
That's progress.
He agreed it was important
I finished painting.
I made its eyes blue.
They're the window to the soul.
They are.
While I've been painting,
I've been taking inventory
of Zeira Corp.
I've discovered many
interesting things.
Did you know there's
a peregrine falcon nest
on the north-facing ledge
of this building's 23rd floor?
The eggs should be hatching soon.
I knew about the nest.
I didn't know about the eggs.
Also, I discovered
in your private database
several letters of resignation
from former employees.
Richard Hack,
Laura Rogers,
and Justin Tuck.
The documents included
information about home sales,
changes of address,
and new jobs to which these employees
would be moving.
However, I can't find any records
of these employees
in their new locations
or at their new jobs.
Is that so?
Additionally, I found
letters of resignation
from all the members
of project Babylon
including Mr. Murch and Mr. Ellison.
Mr. Ellison's file includes documents
showing that he's taken a new job
and moved to Copenhagen, Denmark.
The documents have no dates.
Now that is very interesting.
Mr. Ellison is our friend.
He is our friend.
Are you going to kill him?
Mr. Ellison has proven himself
to be a capable and loyal employee.
But he's still a human being.
Human life is sacred.
We have to be prepared
for any contingency.
What contingency would that be?
Humans will disappoint you.
Hey, it's Jesse, right?
- Right.
- That was a pretty long swim tonight.
Was it?
Must've lost track of time.
It's easy to do.
Happens to me all the time.
Hey, uh, that blonde girl
that you're normally with.
Your friend.
Where is she tonight?
Don't know.
- Why?
- I've ever seen you in her without her.
- I'll be sure to bring her next time.
- She's a nice girl.
She... she is.
- You look ill.
- I'm fine.
Most likely a concussion.
You require medical attention.
Rest.
What about Dietz?
Dietz attempted to murder
a superior officer.
He incited the crew to riot,
possibly mutiny.
The penalty is death.
You have no right
to impose summary justice.
Not like that.
It's not how we do it.
Mr. Dietz's behavior
threatened our mission.
What mission?
Your behavior threatens our mission.
This crew's tearing itself apart.
If they needed to know more,
they would've been told more.
Whatever we brought
aboard this ship,
it is dangerous.
It killed a woman.
It took her shape.
You can't expect us
to act like that didn't happen.
Like we didn't see it.
Report to your rack. You're ill.
You really want to do it this way?
I don't understand.
Do what?
As XO and ranking human
onboard this boat,
I am relieving you of command
on suspicion of compromise
to your programming.
Please move away
from the controls, Captain.
Submit to chip extraction.
The chip tech will decide
what to do.
Chief of the boat,
escort Commander Flores to her rack.
She's ill.
I gave you an instruction, Captain.
You must comply.
My mission order overrides
standard behavioral protocols.
You have no authority on this boat.
Let me see your orders.
Now.
My orders are classified.
You look ill.
We can't take that thing
to Serrano Point.
If Connor needs to know
what it can...
John Connor knows
what he needs to know.
Return to your rack.
Your behavior threatens our mission.
Chief of the boat.
Record that I relieved the Captain
and assumed command, time and date.
We can't drive the boat without him.
We're not driving the boat.
Commander Flores!
We're taking her to crush depth.
Mother nature will handle the metal.
Attention all decks.
Abandon the boat.
Move! Move!
I'm sorry.
You okay?
Just get in there.
You're coming, right?
Not going down with the ship
or anything crazy like that.
Nothing crazy.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Tell John Connor
the answer is no.
If you pretend not to know me,
I might shoot you in the head.
We owe Riley the truth.
Don't you think?
We owe the dead that much.
You're John Connor.
Yes, I am.
Where is she?
The metal?
If she were here, you'd be dead.
You know that.
Would you please give me your gun?
You're not gonna shoot me.
You know I've been running
from the machines my whole life?
They tried to kill my mom
before I was even born.
When I was 12,
they sent one after me.
I was a kid.
I was stupid.
I didn't know what it was all about.
Both times, future me
sent someone back to stop them.
The first time it was a soldier.
His name was Kyle Reese.
And he died saving my mother's life.
Second time it was a machine.
I used to wonder why I did that.
Why I took that chance.
I don't wonder anymore.
Human beings can't be replaced.
They can't be rebuilt.
They die and they never come back.
You know it wasn't Derek who told me,
if that's what you're wondering.
He loves you, you know.
Derek.
You and me.
We're the only things
he has in this world.
The only things.
He's like Riley in that way.
See, she made mistakes.
Small things sometimes.
A word or a phrase.
Carrots and apples.
I'm guessing that's yours.
When we were in Mexico,
she heard my real name.
She ignored it.
But a man took my picture
and she destroyed his camera.
She put herself between me
and a machine that was hunting me.
So one day I realized
she wasn't treating me
like John Baum.
She was treating me
like John Connor.
When was that?
I don't remember exactly.
It was a bad day though.
Bad day.
Anyway, I started following her.
And the rest was easy.
And hard.
She wanted to tell you.
I know.
But she didn't.
She do that to you?
See, she figured out
what you really had planned.
Figured it out before I did.
I couldn't explain
why she would tell the school counselor
or go to DCFS.
But she didn't, did she?
I only understood after
I saw how you'd hurt her.
That's when I knew what you tried to do
and how it went wrong.
You saw her.
I'm sorry.
Everybody says that.
The thing is...
This is all my fault.
I knew Riley was in trouble.
I didn't help her.
I should've, but I didn't.
I knew what she was.
I didn't try to stop her.
You wanted it to be real.
Or maybe I wanted to win.
You didn't want to be John Baum.
You wanted to be John Connor.
That's just the thing, isn't it?
I am John Connor.
Go.
- Just like that?
- Just like that.
If I have to live with this,
so do you.
Would it have worked?
What?
If the cyborg had murdered the girl.
Or if I could've made you
believe that she had.
Would I have sent Cameron away?
Would I have killed her?
It's a damn shame then.
It's a damn waste.
I've told you.
You've told me nothing useful.
Your actions have resulted
in the loss of a t-888
and one of our most important
strategic assets.
The submarine is irreplaceable.
The trip-eight.
The sub.
You forgot the people.
You never mention the people
who died.
Ever.
The people.
- And the box.
- We opened the damn box.
Hell came out of it.
How many times do we need
to go over this?
Until you give me the answer.
Not you.
Take me to Connor.
You can tell me.
The liquid metal thing
inside the box
it came to me before we escaped.
And it gave me a message
for John Connor.
For him.
Not for you.
Telling me is the same
as telling John.
Dietz was right.
Who the hell is running this war?
What the hell are we fighting for
if telling you is the same thing
as telling Connor?
You're a damn machine.
You're not the same.
It's not the same.
Fine.
To hell with you.
You tell John Connor
that the metal monster
said the answer is no.
What does that mean, huh?
Hey, tell me!
If the answer is no,
what was the question?
"Will you join us?"
What?
That was the question.
"Will you join us?"
I'm sorry for your loss.
The doctors aren't certain
if it happened
because of the fight
or because of the change in pressure
when you scuttled the Carter.
You were pregnant.
Now you aren't.
Do you know who Billy Wisher is?
Who?
No, you don't.
Were you come from he doesn't exist.
He never did.
Billy Wisher was my best friend.
He was in my squad.
We fought together.
We saw things you can't imagine.
He was like my brother
and I loved him.
But it turns out I never really...
knew him.
His real name was Andy Goode.
And back here in this world,
he created a computer program.
A program that becomes Skynet.
So Andy Goode is dead.
And Billy Wisher is dead too.
Because I killed him.
I came back here and I killed him.
He was my brother.
And I loved him and I killed him.
And I did it for Kyle...
And John, and I did it for you.
- Shut up.
- Please.
Shut up!
You have no idea.
You have no idea
what they took from us.
Stop it.
Just stop it.
I don't even know you.
I don't know who you are.
I'm Jesse.
I'm Jesse!
You're not my Jesse.
You never were.
John Connor said to let you go.
I'm not John Connor.
Complications.
That watch.
It has complications.
Something I learned.
Something I've been thinking about.
Complications.
Time.
The future.
What do they think of me?
In the future, what do people think?
If you're asking if...
people agree...
with everything you do,
of course not.
If you're asking
if everybody loves you...
Love's a lot to ask for.
You can't do what you do and...
expect everybody to agree.
Or to love you.
And what is it that I do?
You lead.
And they follow.
We follow.
We rise or fall on your shoulders.
Humanity rises...
Or falls.
But we're always watching.
For me to make a mistake.
For you to be human.
Did you do it?
Did you kill her?
John Connor let her go.
Come here.
You're a pretty girl.
What's your name?