Previously on Lost...
You stole my kidney.
You need a father, and I need a kidney.
Get over it.
I know you were raised in foster care.
I know you spent the four years
prior to your arrival
on this island in a wheelchair,
and I know how you ended up in it.
What if I told you
that somewhere on this island,
there's a very large box,
and whatever you imagined,
whatever you wanted to be in it,
when you opened that box,
there it would be?
I'd say I hope that box is big enough
to imagine yourself up new submarine.
Well, John, you've really gone
and done it now.
You're not gonna start talking about
the magic box again, are you?
No, John. I'm gonna show you
what came out of it.
Dad?
Save your breath.
Nobody's gonna hear you.
Dad?
What is this?
You tell me. You brought him here.
I didn't bring him here.
I'd be careful about getting
too close to him, John.
Well, where did you find him?
Why did you bring him here?
I've already said... We didn't...
You want me to ask him how he got here?
Be my guest.
I warned you, John.
Don't you know, John?
Don't you know where we are?
What did he mean?
I'm afraid we don't have time
to deal with that right now, John.
We're leaving
first thing in the morning, all of us.
Where are you going?
We're going to a new place.
Well, an old place, actually.
Would you like to come with us?
Yes.
Good.
We're holding Kate
a few buildings over from here.
Maybe you'd like to say good-bye.
Hey, where you going?
I can't sleep if I'm not in my own tent.
Fine. Let's go to your tent.
It's nothing personal. It's...
old habits, you know?
Fine. Scram.
You want me to walk you home?
It's five tents. I think I'll make it.
Are you sure? I gotta pee anyway.
That is so romantic.
What the hell y'all doin'?
What the hell you doing?
Going to take a leak.
Yeah, well, so are we.
Well, all righty then.
Hello, James.
Subtitles: swsub.com
You wanna zip your pants up?
What the hell are you doing here?
Looking for you, actually.
Okay, Tarzan.
Now that you're back from your
"blow up everything
that could get us off the island" tour,
how 'bout you tell me why
you joined up with the damn enemy?
I didn't join 'em. I infiltrated 'em.
- You're undercover with the others.
- That's right.
Now how 'bout you give me
one reason to believe that?
Because a few hours ago
I snuck into Ben's tent
and kidnapped him.
I tied him up,
dragged him off into the jungle.
And you came all the way back here
to tell me this because...
Because this is the same man
who tortured you,
beat you, humiliated you...
And I want you...
to kill him.
You want him dead, you kill him.
- I'm not a murder.
- Neither am I!
Except for the man you killed in Sydney.
They got files on us, James...
All of us.
Yeah, well,
their files got their facts wrong.
Then I made a mistake coming to you.
Please don't tell anyone
that I was here.
Hey, stop!
I said stop!
Damn it! Wait up!
There. That ought to do it.
Thanks.
That would've taken me hours
to do myself.
Glad I could help.
Don't mind them.
They're all just excited you're here.
Excited?
We've been waiting for you.
John, you got a minute?
Ben's asking for you.
Okay.
Ben, it's 6:00 a.m. on saturday morning.
Kwon is pregnant.
The fetus is healthy
and was conceived on island
with her husband.
He was sterile when they got here.
Hello, John. Thanks for coming.
What's that?
Juliet is gathering information for us
at your former camp.
She's determing
if any of the women are pregnant.
Then we're gonna go in and...
take them.
Take them?
This is not the first time
we've done this.
Trust me, no one will get hurt.
Could you pass me that, please?
Thank you.
I believe
I have you to thank for this, John.
- Me?
- A week ago, I couldn't move my toes...
But the minute you showed up,
I started to feel pins and needles.
And this is only the beginning, John.
I can't wait to show you
what this island can do,
but unfortunately,
you're not ready, John.
- No, I'm ready.
- No, John, you're not.
You're still crippled by the memories
of the man you used to be
before you came to this island,
and you'll never be free
until you release
the hold that your father has over you.
Why do you think you brought him here?
The magic box.
Okay, Ben, how about you show me...
"Magic box" is a metaphor, John.
I can't show you anything
until you can show me
that you're ready
and willing to be one of us.
When people join us here on this island,
they need to make a gesture
of free will, of commitment.
That's why
you're gonna have to kill your father.
When did you get back?
Last night.
Well, early this morning.
So... camping, huh?
What were you guys doing out there?
We...
figured we'd explore a bit, you know.
See what was further down the beach.
Male bonding.
Well, next time you go out, sign me up.
Yeah, next time. Sure.
Thanks, Jin.
We have to tell Jack.
Yeah, I mean,
shouldn't he check out her wound?
Can you give me your word
that Jack can be trusted?
That he spent ten days with those people
and that nothing happened to him?
And that woman
he's spending all his time with...
- Juliet.
- Aye. Juliet.
Two weeks ago,
she had your friends in cages.
Naomi...
Well, you heard
everything that she said.
If we keep her safe,
she's our way off this island.
So given that,
do you trust Jack,
or don't you?
Right.
So we better bring in
someone we can trust.
You should've put some shoes on.
You think?
So what else is in it?
In what?
The file they got on me.
Not much.
That your parents died
when you were very young.
But it doesn't say why
your father...
shot your mother...
or why he turned the gun on himself.
That must've been hard for you.
What else?
High school transcripts...
criminal record...
all the con jobs you were arrested for.
I guess that's why
you use an alias, huh?
Why did you choose the name Sawyer?
How stupid do you think I am?
I already been conned by Ben once.
Maybe you heard about it...
bunny with a number painted on it?
You think I'm just gonna follow you
through the jungle?
Please, you have to...
You have to trust me.
Where are you taking me?
Tell me the truth!
What do you want from me?
I'm bringing you there
to do exactly what I said...
- To kill Ben.
- Why did you come back to get me?
- I had to.
- Why me?!
Why won't you do it yourself?
- James, please...
- Don't call me James!
Why won't you do it yourself?
Because I can't! I can't!
I can't do it!
That's why I came back for you.
Get up.
I'll go to wherever you got him,
but then
we're bringing him back to our camp.
I ain't killing nobody.
You understand me?
Yeah. I understand...
But you'll change your mind
When you hear what he has to say,
you'll change your mind.
Hey, dude.
Hello, Hurley.
Can you keep a secret?
You've already spoken to her?
Yeah, but you're gonna want
to hear it for yourself.
And you haven't told Jack?
No.
Good.
My name's Sayid Jarrah.
I understand your helicopter
crashed onto the island.
Actually, it crashed in the water.
What's your name?
Naomi. Naomi Dorrit.
Naomi, from where exactly
did you take off?
A ship... freighter...
About 80 nautical miles west of here.
I'm part of a search and recovery team.
You told my friends the wreckage
of flight 815 was discovered.
Did you mean the partial wreckage?
No. They found the entire plane
off the coast of Bali,
in an ocean trench 4 miles deep.
They sent down cameras in these
little robots to survey the wreck.
The bodies were all there.
Well, obviously we're not dead.
Obviously.
So if you weren't looking for us,
then who were you looking for?
Him.
Desmond?
My company was hired by a woman
named Penelope Widmore.
I don't know why. I never met her.
She gave us a set of coordinates.
We've been conducting a differential
G.P.S. grid search ever since.
You knew about the island?
Island?
We were given coordinates
in the middle of the bloody ocean.
We thought it was a fool's errand...
till three days ago.
I was flying back for the ship,
when all of a sudden
the clouds cleared, and I saw land.
The instruments started spinning.
I realized I was going down,
so I grabbed my chute, and I bailed.
Did you actually see her helicopter?
No.
You think I'm lying, mate?
I take it you have no means whatsoever
of communicating
with that freighter of yours?
What was your name? Sayid?
Yes.
Remind me not to rescue you, Sayid.
So Ben...
You said I'd kill him
when I heard what he's got to say.
- That's right.
- Well, you wanna give me a heads-up?
It's not really my place to tell you.
Look, what you read in that file...
about the guy in Sydney...
I thought he was someone else.
I made a mistake.
I didn't mean to kill him.
Well, who'd you mean to kill?
Are we almost there?
Almost.
Wake up, John.
It's time.
I know it won't be easy,
but the quicker the better.
You're kidding me, right?
You expect him to kill me?
The hesitation that you're feeling
is just the part of you
that still feels like
he has a perfectly good explanation
for stealing your kidney,
throwing you out of an 8-story window.
Don't you wanna be free from him?
The hesitation he's feeling
is because he is a spineless...
Shut up!
- I gotta think...
- Don't think, John.
You're wasting your time, bug-eye.
Me and him have been through all this.
- All he wants is his daddy...
- Shut up! I said shut up!
You really haven't figured it out yet,
have you?
Let go of him, John.
Why are you doing this to me?
You're doing this to yourself.
As long as he's still breathing,
you'll still be
that same sad, pathetic little man
that was kicked off his walkabout tour
because you couldn't walk.
I'll be here the rest of the week, John,
if you change your mind...
I'm sorry.
He's not who we thought he was.
Son of a...
Nice place you got here, Locke.
Ben's inside in the brig.
You ready?
Yeah, I'm ready.
Friends of yours?
It's an old slaving ship,
mid nineteenth century,
My guess is they...
captured the slaves and brought them
here to try and mine the island.
What's in the boxes?
That'd be dynamite.
Son of a bitch.
You really kidnapped the little bastard.
We ain't killin' him, Locke.
Whatever you say, James.
Well, well, well.
What are you doing?!
Open the damn door!
Shut up!
Open up!
I said shut up!
Who the hell are you?
- It's like a radio?
- It's like a radio, yes,
but I've never seen
equipment this sophisticated.
But you can still make it work, right?
I hope so.
And what about the other part?
The part about they found the plane
and we're all dead?
One thing at a time.
There's not a single audible channel.
Whatever that interference is,
it's blocking our ability
to send our own transmission.
If we...
What's that? Is that a radio?
Where'd you get it?
Uh, the luggage.
What, you just found a radio
in the luggage?
Kate, if I explain,
I want you to keep this very quiet.
Keep what very quiet?
Locke! Open the damn door!
Open it up! I can hear you,
you bald bastard!
Rousseau?
Locke.
What brings you to "The Black Rock"?
Dynamite. And you?
Open this door!
Open up!
Crates are right over there.
Open this damn door!
Be careful. It's unstable.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
No matter how much time
you spend on the island,
you just never get tired of this view.
We haven't been formally introduced.
I'm Richard.
- You mind if I join you?
- Oh, sure.
He wanted to embarrass you.
I'm sorry?
Ben knew you weren't gonna kill
your own father.
He put you in front of
everyone in our camp
just so they could all watch you fail.
Why?
'cause when word got back here
that there was a man
with a broken spine on the plane
who could suddenly walk again, well...
People here began to get very excited,
because that...
That could only happen to someone
who was extremely special.
Now Ben doesn't want anyone
to think you're special, John.
And why are you telling me this?
Ben has been wasting our time
with novelties like fertility problems.
We're looking for someone to remind us
that we're here
for more important reasons.
What do you want from me?
I want for you to find your purpose,
and to do that,
your father has to go, John,
and since you're not going to do it...
I'm gonna suggest someone else.
Sawyer?
Why would Sawyer kill my father?
He doesn't even know him.
Keep reading.
Open this damn door!
Son of a bitch!
I'm pointin' my gun at you, John-boy.
You got three seconds to open this door!
You're not gonna shoot anyone, James.
One...
two!
If there were any bullets in that gun,
why would you hold a knife to my throat?
Son of a bitch!
Guess I didn't raise no dummies.
What the hell's that mean?
It means that "bald-headed bastard"
outside the door is my son.
Come again?
My son.
As in I'm his father.
You do speak English?
How did you get here... to the island?
Island?
I'm driving down I-10
through Tallahassee, when bam...
Somebody slams into the back of my car.
I go right into the divider
at 70 miles an hour.
The next thing I know,
the paramedics are strapping me
to a gurney,
stuffing me in the back of an ambulance,
and one of them actually smiles at me
as he pops the I.V. In my arm,
and then... nothing.
Just black.
And the next thing I know,
I wake up in a dark room
tied up, gag in my mouth,
and when the door opens,
I'm looking up at the same man
I threw out a window...
John Locke,
my dead son.
And he's dead 'cause you threw him
out a window?
No, he survived that,
but it paralyzed him, permanently.
He's dead because the plane
he was flying on crashed in the Pacific.
Well, I got bad news for you, pops,
'cause I was on that plane
with your son,
and he sure as hell wasn't crippled.
And we didn't crash in the pacific.
We crashed here on this island.
You sure it's an island?
Well, what else is it?
Little hot for heaven, isn't it?
Oh, okay, so we're dead.
They found your plane
on the bottom of the ocean.
One minute I'm in a car wreck,
and the next minute
I'm in a pirate ship
in the middle of the jungle?
If ts isn't hell, friend...
Then where are we?
Why did you throw Locke out a window?
He was becoming a nuisance.
I conned him into giving me
one of his kidneys.
He never got over it.
Conned?
Yes, sir.
Conned.
What's your name?
Your name?
A con man goes by many names, friend.
I've been Alan Seward,
Anthony Cooper, Ten McLaren, Tom Sawyer,
- Louis Jackson, Paul...
- Tom Sawyer?
I was young, and "Huck Finn"
was taken...
And the ladies loved that one.
Made me charming.
Well, how about that?
How about what?
Sawyer's my name, too.
Ben, what's going on?
- We're moving.
- Moving? Where are we going?
We are not going anywhere, John.
You are going to stay behind.
You both are going to stay behind.
What? You're not taking him?
He's your mess, John.
Why would we clean him up?
Ben, if you're trying to put me
in my place, or embarrass me...
Where would you get
a ridiculous idea like that?
Well, you can't leave me.
- After everything, you can't just...
- Don't tell me what I can't do, John.
But I thought I was... special.
Well, everyone makes mistakes.
We're leaving now.
We'll leave a trail...
one you can track. And, John,
unless you're carrying
your father's body on your back,
don't bother.
What's the matter with you?
You ever been to Jasper, Alabama?
Why?
Have you, or haven't you?
Yeah, I've been to Jasper.
Don't tell me I'm your daddy.
No.
You killed my daddy.
Read it.
"Dear Mr. Sawyer... "
- What is this?
- Just read it.
"You don't know who I am,
but I know who you are,
"and I know what you done.
"You had sex with my mother
"and then you stole
my dad's money all away,
"so he got angry,
and he killed my mother... "
"and then he killed himself... "
So what?
Is this supposed to be you?
You wrote this letter?
Hey, wait a second.
Did you take my name
because you were on some kind
of revenge kick?
- Keep reading.
- Easy, easy.
Don't get all worked up.
Look, I ran that con two dozen times.
- If your mother was one of the...
- Mary.
Her name was Mary.
Mary from Jasper, Alabama.
Yeah, I remember her.
She practically begged me
to take her $38,000
and to rescue her
from her sorry little life.
You finish the letter.
Look, I only took her money.
It ain't my fault your dad overreacted.
If he pulled the old murder-suicide,
then I'm sure he's down here
somewhere.
Maybe you could take this up with him.
Finish it!
You wanna go to hell?
You wanna go to hell?!
Thank you.
You missing those cheeseburgers yet?
Only every second.
I need to talk to you.
- In private.
- No problem.
Anything you wanna say to me,
you can say in front of her.
Not this.
- It's okay.
- No, no. You can stay.
Yeah, you know what? You should stay.
Seems only fair, considering
that she's the reason
no one wants to tell you
that there's a woman
in Hurley's tent who parachuted
onto the island yesterday.
- What?
- A woman.
She jumped from her chopper
before it crashed.
She says that the boat
that she took off from
is about 80 miles off the coast
and that if she can find a way
to contact it, we'll all be rescued!
Why didn't anyone tell me this?
I already told you...
because they don't trust you.
How?
How what?
How is she supposed to contact her boat?
Did you hear what I just said?
Hurley, Charlie, Sayid, your friends,
are afraid to...
How?
She had a phone-radio thing.
Sayid's trying to get it to work.
We should tell her.
- No.
- Tell me what?
- We should tell her.
- Not yet.
You can go back now.
Why did you do this?
He ruined my life,
and he ruined yours.
And he had it coming.
Juliet is a mole.
- What?
- She's working for Ben.
He sent her back to find out
which of our women were pregnant.
Three days from now,
there's gonna be a raid on the beach,
and they're gonna take them.
They say they don't want anyone
to get hurt.
Well, why are you telling me?
- So you can warn the camp.
- You warn the camp.
I'm not going back.
You're going back undercover?
No, I was never undercover, James.
I'm on my own journey now.
Even if Juliet is a mole,
they ain't gonna believe me.
I been saying that since she showed up.
They'll believe you now.
Is it true?
Is what true?
That he threw you out a window...
That you were a cripple?
Not anymore.