Previously on Lost...
Is that an helicopter?
It's how an helicopter suppose to sound?
Get away from her!
Desmond.
- What's wrong?
- What's wrong is I'm married.
Right.
You're pregnant.
Good morning, Jack.
You need a hand?
Thank you.
I came by your tent earlier.
Is Jin gone?
He went off with Charlie,
Hurley and Desmond.
Did you need him?
Actually, I was looking for you.
I wanted to see how you were doing
with your pregnancy.
I'm doing fine.
A little tired, but that's normal,
right?
Sure.
Any morning sickness?
Not anymore.
Any bleeding?
Why are you asking me
all these questions, Jack?
I'm just checking in.
I mean, now that I'm back, I just...
wanted to make sure
that you were doing okay.
Thank you.
I'm okay.
Great.
- Who is she?
- I have no idea.
She seems to know you, dude.
She just said your name.
I've never seen her before in my life.
She's waking up.
She's trying to talk.
We should get her some water.
Hey, give me a hand.
- What's she saying?
- I don't know.
- Spanish, dude.
- What, do you understand her, then?
She says she's dying.
My God!
It's a branch!
She must have hit it on the way down.
Get her pack. We haven't got much
in this first aid kit.
See if there's anything
we can use in it.
What if this is a rescue?
What if she came for us?
Is she gonna be okay?
- We can't let her...
- Just go and start looking!
We get Jack.
We have to get her to Jack
as soon as possible.
- She could be our way off the island.
- If we move her, it'll be worse.
We just let her bleed to death?
No, we need to bring Jack here.
It's an 8-hour walk one way!
Then I'll run.
You're out of your mind. It's not safe.
It's gonna be dark soon.
Who knows who's out in this jungle?
In case you have forgotten,
there're people on this island
- trying to kill us!
- Nobody knows we're here!
Subtitles: swsub.com
How's this?
That's perfect.
Thank you.
What do you think happened to Jack
while he was with the others?
Since he's been back,
he seems different.
He says that he was pretty much
a prisoner,
and the only reason
why he cooperated is 'cause
he thought
they'd let him off the island.
Do you believe him?
Why wouldn't I?
He came to me,
asking about my pregnancy.
- What would that have anything to do...
- What if...
What if the others want my baby?
He's been there alone for over a week.
How do we know
he isn't working with them?
He's not working with them.
Do you know something, Kate?
It's Juliet.
She was their doctor... their...
Their fertility doctor,
studying pregnant women,
and when Claire was sick,
she told me and Jack...
The reason the Others
wanted her baby...
was for research.
- Wait. You don't have to do this.
- Go away, Kate.
I want to know about your research.
What happens to pregnant women?
You're pregnant.
Are you sure? How do you know?
I asked you a question.
Everyone else might be all right
with you washing your clothes
and eating our food,
but I want to know what's going on.
I want answers.
What are you people doing?
Why are you taking children?
What happens to pregnant women
on this island?
- What happens... - They die.
They all die.
Sun, come on. Let's go.
What is she saying?
Chinese... not Korean.
Maybe we should just pull it out.
- You'll just make it worse.
- You forgot what's at stake?
Or is this another of your flashes?
Who's getting an arrow in the neck?
Unless you forget,
she said my bloody name!
She had a photo of me
and my girlfriend!
Do I understand?
I understand better than all of you!
Hey, guys, chill.
We've wasted enough time already.
Hey, you're not leaving us.
Just get out of my way, Charlie.
Who are you?
I said, who are you?
He's the guy who shot Sayid.
Kate told us he lived out
in that station that Locke blew up.
He's an Other.
I thought Locke killed that guy
with the electro-fence thingy.
You've got five seconds to talk,
or I fire this gun, brother.
That's a flare gun.
And how do you think it'll feel...
Taking a flare to the chest
at this range?
As your friend pointed out,
I already died once this week.
You understand her.
She's speaking Italian.
She said she's dying. She needs help.
I was a soviet army field medic.
I can offer you my services.
- Wait. What are you doing?
- I'm saving her.
This branch has punctured her lung.
It's filling with blood.
If it is not ventilated soon,
she's going to die.
Well, do it. Help her.
If I fix her,
you must let me walk away
as if I never came upon you.
What do you need?
Be quiet. Don't move.
You want me to help you and your baby?
I have answers to your questions,
but you have to come with me right now.
Just you and me, nobody else.
If what you said was true,
that means I'm already dead.
Why should I go anywhere with you?
Because there may be hope for you yet.
Where are we going?
There's a medical station near here.
They have an ultrasound machine.
Claire and Kate
told me about that place.
It was abandoned.
They found nothing there.
Well, that's because
they didn't know where to look.
What are you going to do to me?
I'm gonna look at your baby
and determine the D.O.C....
Date of conception.
The ultrasound will tell me
when you got pregnant,
give or take a day.
If you got pregnant off the island,
then you and your baby
will probably be okay,
but if you got pregnant here...
We'll cross that bridge
when we come to it.
When was the last time
you and your husband had sex?
I would rather not talk about that.
Look, I know that it's personal,
but if I know when,
then I can figure...
Isn't that what the machine will do?
Then let's keep walking.
What else do you know
about this woman?
Did she have anything on her
besides the flare gun?
Just a book,
a fancy radio/phone thingy...
Does it work?
Like I'd tell you.
One of you must help.
The rest, clear the way.
I need space.
I'll do it.
Wipe away as much of the blood
as you can.
We need to evacuate the air now!
Hold her steady.
- Steady!
- I heard you.
Is that... normal?
Gauze.
Tape it. Be careful.
The covering needs to be hollow.
The wound needs to breathe.
What did she say?
"Thank you."
She said,
"thank you for helping me."
It's right down here.
Why are you doing this?
What?
Helping me.
Once upon a time,
I told women that they were pregnant,
and their faces...
it was the best news
they ever got
in their entire life.
Then I came here.
I've lost...
nine patients in the last three years.
I'm helping you
because I want to tell you
that you and your husband got
pregnant before you came here.
I'm helping you because
I want to give good news again.
I slept with another man...
...before we got to the island.
Jin and I, we were having...
trouble.
We weren't...
and I had a friend.
It was a mistake.
We all make mistakes.
Which way?
Will you help me move this forward?
Good.
Why is this room hidden?
Don't worry about it.
What is this place?
Tell me!
It's where we brought
the women to die.
She's fine.
Keep the wound as clean as you can.
She should be better in a day.
A day?
Her lung was punctured.
On this island,
the rules are a bit different.
Maybe a day and a half.
I did as I promised.
She will live.
- You can't seriously considering...
- Just go.
Are you kidding?
He's one of them!
So what would you
have me do, Charlie?
We've got to make a stretcher
and carry her.
How are we gonna do that
and bring a prisoner?
Give me some rope.
I'll take responsibility.
Phone. Phone!
Wait, Jin!
- Jin, it's all right!
- No, let him!
- Come back here!
- Let him!
Jin, it's all right! Jin!
Let him go.
Jin, let him go!
Phone!
You stole this?
How could you respect me
if I didn't try?
How about I take your other eye?
Would you respect that?
Sorry. I...
Charlie, don't!
Charlie, let him go!
This is a mistake!
We can't keep letting these people go!
We gave him our word!
Go on.
Get out of here.
The baby isn't Jin's.
We tried to have a baby
back in Korea and couldn't.
And the doctor...
he told me Jin was infertile.
And then you came here.
What?
Did you know that
the average male sperm count
is between 60 and 80 million?
But on this island,
it's five times that.
We call that good odds.
You ready?
Yes.
You wanna lift up your shirt a little?
It's cold.
Will I see the baby?
Maybe. It's your first trimester,
so it's a little iffy.
If you don't see a heartbeat,
don't worry about it.
It's just early.
How does it work?
Well, I take a measurement of the fetus,
and that will tell us
when your baby was conceived,
and then we'll know who.
Are you okay?
I lose either way.
If I'm going to live...
that means the baby's not Jin's.
Do you still want to do this?
Yes.
Moment of truth.
There it is.
There's your baby.
Can you see?
I can see it.
Is it a boy or a girl?
It's... it's a little early,
but...
do you see that little flutter?
That's the heart beating.
It's very strong. It's very healthy.
You crashed here 90 days ago.
The baby was conceived
about eight weeks ago,
so... around 53 days.
You got pregnant on the island.
I am sorry. I'm so sorry, Sun.
I will do everything that I can.
It's Jin's.
So how long do I have?
Most of the women made it into
the middle of their second trimester.
Nobody made it to their third.
That gives me two months.
I am...
very happy the baby's Jin's.
You gave me good news, Juliet.
It was my pleasure, Sun.
I'm gonna go back inside and make sure
that I didn't miss anything.
I don't wanna take the chance
that we didn't cover our tracks.
Do you wanna wait out here?
All right.
Thank you.
Ben, it's 6:00 a.m. on Saturday morning.
Kwon is pregnant.
The fetus is healthy
and was conceived on island
with her husband.
He was sterile before they got here.
I'm still working on getting
samples from the other women.
I should have Austen's soon.
I'll report back when I know more.
I hate you.
You can't trust 'em, you know.
- What's that?
- The others...
The one you let go.
He'll be back tomorrow
with five of his mates.
Should've killed him.
Charlie.
- Tight.
- Okay.
You know, brother,
by my count,
you've killed more of them
than they've killed of you.
They started it.
Just 'cause one comes
traipsing back with Jack and Kate
doesn't mean that we can
trust them now.
Mom?
Where am I?
Take it easy.
You had a giant branch...
- Where am I?
- I don't know.
You're on an island.
Are you here to rescue us?
Are there more of you?
can you make your phone work?
Who are you?
Hugo Reyes.
I crashed here on Oceanic flight 815.
A bunch of us survived.
Is that why you're here?
Were you looking for us?
815?
Flight 815? The one from Sydney?
No. That's not possible.
Yeah, I know. It wasn't easy,
but we found food...
- in the hatch...
- No, flight 815, they...
They found the plane.
There were no survivors.
They were all dead.
What?