Previously on Lost...
You want me to save your life?
I want you to want to save my life.
Just made a small incision
in Ben's kidney sac.
Now if I don't stitch that back up
in the next hour, he's dead.
I would like for you
to go back in there,
put Ben under and finish the surgery.
And why would I want to do that?
Because I'm going to go
help your friends escape.
What, you wanna turn steering?
We have to go back.
What the hell are you talking about?
Turn the boat around, I mean it.
Have you lost your mind?
We just got away.
Just do it.
- You give me one good reason to turn...
- Because we can't leave Jack behind.
Yes, we can, Freckles...
'cause that's what he asked us to do.
I mean, think about it…
We go back there,
what do you think captain bunnykiller's
gonna do if he catches us?
He'll kill you.
God loves you as he loved Jacob.
Thanks for the input.
Sorry, kiddo...
Jack's on his own.
Time to get up.
We're moving you.
Moving me where?
Someplace else, Jack.
Why?
So this is it, huh?
"It"?
You just helped me save his life.
If you're gonna kill me, please,
at least show me the respect
of not calling it "moving."
Now why would we kill you?
Because you're done with me.
What kind of people do you think we are?
I don't know, Tom.
The kind of people that would take
a pregnant woman...
would hang Charlie from a tree...
would drag our people
out of the jungle...
would kidnap children…
That's the kind of people
I think you are.
You see this glass house
you're living in, Jack?
How 'bout I get you some stones?
Let's do this the easy way.
What do you say?
Sync by Sixe.
www.swsub.com
Dr. Jack? Hey, Dr. Jack?
Dr. Jack want soda?
You know I can't understand a word
you're saying, right?
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You're not from around here, are you?
No. No, I'm not.
I'm... Jack.
Hi, Jack. I'm Achara.
Achara...
Juliet grilled these for me.
Who's that woman?
That'd be the sheriff.
- You have a sheriff?
- Not literally.
Why are you moving Juliet into my room?
'Cause she's in trouble.
Now don't try anything stupid.
You stay put in this cage, okay?
You say that like you're not watching me
from that camera right there.
Oh, right.
Ben told me you got into
the surveillance room.
Let me ask you something.
You risk your neck to cut them loose,
and they run away
and don't ever look back...
Thanks for the sandwich.
Never thought I'd be glad
to get back to this rock again.
What are you doing?
What's it look like?
I'm heading into shore.
Why? If we just keep going,
we can circle round.
Sooner or later we'll get to camp
and tell Locke and Sayid what happened.
Oh, we will?
You got a map you ain't showing me,
Magellan?
We got no food, no water,
and I can't steer in the dark.
Then I'll steer.
You'll come ashore,
and we'll make camp.
You want to contribute?
You can build a campfire
while I carry the kid.
Glad we agree.
Sure you ain't hungry?
No, James, I ain't hungry.
You shouldn't fight.
When the hell did you wake up?
You shouldn't fight
because you're lucky to be alive.
Golly! I think he's got a point!
That island we were on...
Is that where your people live?
Just where we work.
Work on what?
Projects.
Oh, sure, like the "steal the kid
off the raft"
project?
That was a humdinger.
So you don't actually live
on that island?
Do you live here...
on this island?
Yes, ma'am.
And what did you do with the people
that you took...
- the kids?
- We give them a better life.
Better than what?
Better than yours.
There's not gonna be any moon tonight.
It'll be dark.
Me and Alex used to lie in my backyard
at night,
make up names for the constellations.
You can't see it yet,
but right there will be
"Ursa Theodorus"...
the teddy bear.
You have backyards?
Well, ain't that quaint?
Warning!
I thought you were locked up.
They let me out to examine Ben.
His vitals are low, and he has a fever.
I took this about ten minutes ago.
It's of his stitches.
They're infected, aren't they?
- Yes.
- Will you come look at them?
I'm not asking you for them... or him.
I'm asking you as a personal favor
to me.
You... want me to help him again?
Yes.
Are you sure about that, Juliet?
Yes... I'm sure.
And this is because he said
that he would let you go home?
It's because I'm in trouble.
- Trouble? For...
- I just killed someone.
That's why they put me in your room.
Who?
It's complicated.
Well, then, let me simplify it for you.
I'm not gonna help him...
and I'm not gonna help you.
Special Thai dish for you. You try.
Very brave, very brave.
My brother likes you.
Well, I'm a very likeable guy.
So, Jack...
tell me something.
Shoot.
Why is it you don't know
how to fly a kite?
Just never learned, I guess.
That's very sad.
Well, my dad worked a lot.
He wasn't exactly the kite-flying type,
anyway.
I mean, we never really...
I have no interest in your father.
Well, that's a relief,
because I'm pretty tired
of talking about him.
Some things are personal.
So you're in Phuket to...
"find yourself"?
Why would you say that?
You're an American.
I have... a gift.
Must be one hell of a gift.
I was just reading your tattoos.
The "five" and the stars are very cute,
But the Chinese I find...
a bit ironic.
You find what ironic?
What it says.
You do know what it says?
Yeah, I know what it says.
Are you sure?
Chinese is a very complicated language.
It's fairly common for some things
to get lost in translation.
I know what it says.
All right, then.
My name is Isabel.
If you'll come with me,
I'd like to talk to you and ask you
a few questions.
Why don't you check on your father,
sweetheart?
I know he'd appreciate it.
Please, have a seat, Jack.
As you may have gathered,
we don't live on this little island.
In fact, most of us
don't really even like coming here.
There's been an incident
that I'm investigating,
and I need to ask you some questions,
so I was hoping you may help me clear up
a few of the... inconsistencies.
Now correct me if I'm wrong, Tom,
but you said, in the midst
of a surgical procedure,
Jack made several comments indicating
that Juliet had asked him to kill Ben.
Yeah. That's right.
Is that true, Jack?
Did Juliet ask you to kill Ben?
The question's simple.
No, I was lying.
I would've done anything
to get my friends out,
and turning you people
against each other
was my best chance of creating chaos.
Why are you lying for her, Jack?
I'd like to go back to my cage now.
Who's there?
Who do you think?
What time is it?
It's late.
Salty.
I went for a swim in the ocean.
Washing the day off of you, huh?
Is there something
you'd like to ask me, Jack?
No, not at all.
I mean...
it might be nice...
after a month of you coming and going
whenever you want,
to find out something about you.
There are things that happen here
that you could never understand.
Like your gift?
Yes...
like my gift.
Are you having fun with me, Jack?
Oh, yeah.
Then stop ask questions.
Let's have fun.
What?
Do I...
do I know you?
815. You're...
you were the stewardess.
Cindy.
What are you doing here, with them?
I thought you were taken.
You were... You were captured.
They're not... it's not that simple.
What are they doing here right now?
What are you doing here?!
We're here to watch, Jack.
Watch what?
What is it, sweetheart?
She... wants to know
how Ana Lucia's doing.
- Are you serious?
- What?
If you've got something to watch,
Cindy, go watch it!
- What?
- Sawyer, wake up.
He's gone.
Karl's gone.
Where?
I got it.
No, let me talk to him.
No, I got it.
Boys only.
What the hell was that for?
So you'd cowboy up.
Crying in the jungle.
I thought you
people were supposed to be tough.
I am tough.
Sure you are, Bobby.
Bobby? "The Brady bunch"?
What the hell's "The Brady bunch"?
Anyway, look...
I’ve been with a lot of girls...
some of them worth the trouble...
some not.
Every now and again...
there's one...
one you name dumb stars with.
So this girl, Sally Slingshot...
Alex.
You love her?
More than anything.
Then go back
to wherever the hell your...
yards are, and get her back.
If I get caught,
they'll kill me this time.
Well...
at least it'll be worth it.
I wanna ask you something.
They're not watching anymore,
so you can tell me the truth.
Ben...
Why'd you save his life?
All this time...
After all he did to you
and your people...
you should hate him,
But you still fixed him up,
even after your friends got away. Why?
You're his daughter.
Answer the question.
I'll answer your question
if you answer one of mine.
Where's Juliet?
She's with the rest of them.
They're gonna read her verdict.
Her verdict?
And we all know what it's gonna be.
We're pretty strict
about killing one of our own.
Eye for an eye.
Who? Who did she kill?
The man who was gonna murder
your friends.
No wonder you're so worried about her.
If it wasn't for you,
she never would have done it.
That was three questions.
Your turn, Jack.
I saved your father
because I said I would.
Is he still in charge?
- What?
- Ben, your father...
Is he still in charge?
Will that woman Isabel do what he says?
Get me out of this cage.
I wouldn't do that.
The cavalry has arrived at last.
I'd be much more impressed with you
people if you had a good surgeon.
We had an excellent surgeon, Jack.
His name was Ethan.
You have a very serious infection, Ben.
That infected tissue
needs to be re-incised, debrided,
and you need to be very closely
monitored from here on out.
There might be nerve damage
or any number of other complications.
You might not walk again.
Your bedside manner
leaves something to be desired.
Well, then,
it's too bad you're stuck with me.
- Am I?
- You need a doctor,
someone to stay with you
bring you back to good health.
And here we go again.
I've already given you
a ticket off this island.
What's it gonna cost me this time?
Right now your people are in a room
deciding whether or not
to execute Juliet.
You're gonna stop it.
Juliet doesn't care about you, Jack.
Doesn't matter what she's done,
No matter what you think...
she's one of us.
Do we have a deal or not?
Does Isabel have a walkie?
They're already in the meeting.
Then get me something to write on.
You following me.
What is all this?
This is where I work,
and you shouldn't be here.
This is a...
a tattoo parlor.
This was your big secret?
The envelopes... your gift?
I am not a tattoo artist.
I'm able to see who people are.
My work is not decoration...
it is definition...
and this...
this is my gift.
So...
you see who people are.
Yes...
and I mark them.
So tell me who I am.
No.
- Why not?
- You are an outsider.
So you can sleep with me...
I'm not allowed.
Do you see who I am, Achara?
Yes.
Who am I?
You are a leader, a great man.
But this...
this makes you lonely...
and frightened..
and angry.
Good.
Now put it on me.
Put it on me.
No. This...
this is against my people.
There will be consequences, Jack.
There always are.
Wait. No,
you shouldn't be here.
Just stand back.
Don't say anything.
Alex, you...
What the hell
did you bring him here for?!
Let him go, Tom.
What's going on, Alex?
This is from Ben.
Ben has commuted Juliet's sentence.
Execution is off the table.
He says the rules don't apply.
He has, however,
ordered her to be marked.
Hey, where you going?
Hey, I know you.
I'm Achara's friend from...
...Chet's. Jack from the restaurant.
Let go of me, man.
You will get off our beach!
You leave this country!
Do you understand me?
I heard you only liked them grilled.
I missed the toothpicks, too.
Let me see.
They marked you.
Let me see it.
Break a branch off that aloe plant
over there...
Please. Please do it.
All right, turn around.
Why did you help me?
He told you he was gonna
let you go home.
He told me the same thing.
We're gonna make sure he keeps his word.
And how are we going to do that?
Together.
They'll be coming for you
in a few minutes...
All of them.
Your friends know where we are,
so we have to leave this island
to go back to where we live.
Go where?
Well, Ben calls it "home."
Where's Karl?
I let him go.
- You what?
- I let him go.
He could have led us back
to where they live.
What, you think I cut him loose
'cause I'm so damn sensitive?
The kid's a target.
Ben ain't never gonna stop
looking for him, so as long…
All Ben wants is that kid
as far from his daughter as possible.
Let's get back to camp.
Are you coming or not?
Should I walk beside you
or ten paces behind you?
You're so good at telling me what to do,
I can't think for myself anymore.
Don't take it out on me
'cause you feel guilty.
I don't feel guilty.
The hell you don't!
We had to leave Jack behind.
- I didn't have a choice...
- I'm not talking
about leaving Jack behind.
I'm talking about you and me.
I know you did it 'cause you thought
I was a dead man...
so don't beat yourself up
'cause the doc's left behind.
I'm not beating myself up.
'Course you're not.
So now that we got that out of the way,
let's go.
"He walks amongst us,
but he is not one of us."
Your tattoos...
That's what they say.
It's not what they mean.
www.swsub.com