Previously, on Lost...
You brought me here to operate on you.
You think, I trust you,
that I am gonna just...
do the surgery and hope
that you let me go?
You have to do it.
- How did they get you to ask me?
- Please--
- What did they offer you?
- Nothing.
- Then what are you doing here?
- They're gonna kill Sawyer...
Tomorrow morning, first thing,
we'll get it out,
and they'll keep you alive.
I'm ready.
Sawyer, please!
You get your hands off of him!
I just made a small incision
in Ben's kidney sac.
Now if I don't stitch that back up
in the next hour, he's dead.
Now get in here,
and bring that walkie-talkie.
3x07 - Not In Portland
I fell asleep.
With candles burning-- that's real safe.
We don't have to keep doing this,
you know.
Are you saying that
because you don't think it's gonna work
or because you're afraid he'll find out?
Lift up your shirt.
Some doctor you are.
I'm not doing this as your doctor.
I'm doing it as your sister.
I don't like you being here alone.
Come stay with me.
I like living on the beach.
This is Miami, Rachel.
Everything's on the beach.
You have about an hour head start
before they come after you.
Take the walkie, take Sawyer and go.
Wait. Where are you?
Kate, listen to me. Just listen to me.
You remember
what I told you on the beach?
Do you rember what story I told you
when you were stitching me up?
Do you rember it?!
Yes, yes, I remember!
When you get safe, you radio me
and you tell me that story.
Jack, please--
If I don't get a call from you
in the next hour,
I'm gonna know something went wrong,
and he dies!
I can't leave without you.
Yes, you are. Go.
- Jack, I can't!
- Go, now.
I can't!
Kate, damn it, run!
Juliet, stop the bleeding
and stitch him up.
She's not a surgeon.
She can't fix this.
He's right.
Let's go.
Warning.
Sawyer, let's go!
Then what the hell do you suggest we do?
Go get Danny,
then find Austen and Ford
and bring them back.
- No, you do that, and Ben dies.
- Go.
You think I'm lying?
Do you think this is a bluff?
- I will let him die!
- No, Jack, you won't.
Go. Get them back.
If you have to...
kill them.
Subtitle : www.sub-way.fr (V.1.00)
Transcript : www.swsub.com
- Dr. Burke?
- Yes.
This is Diana from Mittelos Bioscience.
I'm calling to confirm
your appointment tomorrow.
Uh, 2:00, right?
2:00. Dr. Alpert asked me to tell you
that he's very much looking forward
to meeting you.
Me, too. Thank you.
Good-Bye.
Stay here.
Hello, Juliet.
Why exactly are you here?
Oh, I, m...
today's lab work...
I got home, and I realized
that inverted some numbers.
And it couldn't wait till the morning?
Um... Edmund?
I'm sorry.
How rude of me.
Uh, Juliet, this is Sherry.
Sherry, this is Juliet,
My ex-wife.
Juliet's leaving.
I am.
Could you please turn off the lights?
You haven't thought this through, Jack.
Your plan's not gonna work.
Yeah? Why is that?
Your friends aren't going
to make it back to your side
of the island
because we're not on that island.
We're on a smaller island
2 miles offshore.
'Fraid so.
So why don't we see if we can come up
with some kind of peaceful resolution?
A peaceful resolution?
That's right.
Is that what you call
asking me to kill Ben
while on the operang table--
- Make it look like an accident?
- That's ridiculous.
- She wants Ben to die.
- He's lying.
She said if I did it,
that she would protect me--
Enough!
Get out.
Tom, he's lying.
You said you can't stitch him up...
then you don't need to be in here.
Go, Julie.
Don't let him fool you.
He'll never let a patient just die.
Can anybody hear me?!
What happened?
Open the cage.
- Where is--
- Just open the damn cage!
That's our island?
What, you didn't believe me
when I told you before?
We need a boat.
Yeah, a couple of towels
and a buffet lunch.
We'll follow the beach.
There's gotta be one
around here somewhere.
How else do they get back and forth?
Why don't we just stop
and ask for directions?
Jack, are you there?
- Yeah, I'm here.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Tell him I said "hi"?
- Get to the point!
- We need a boat.
We need some way
to get off of this island.
You heard her.
How do they get off this island?!
What's he doing?
Come on!
This way!
Jason, you all right?
Over there! There!
Come on! Get inside, get inside! Go!
Come on!
Be quiet, be quiet, be quiet.
What?
Where'd they go?
That way.
Nice to meet you, Sheena.
Is it true?
Is what true?
What you said--
Did Juliet really ask you to kill him?
Yeah...
and in about 40 minutes,
she's gonna get her wish.
That's... not... helping...
anything.
Now...
could somebody please get Juliet?
Edmund wants to see you in his office.
Do you work here?
I'm the new research assistant.
Of course you are.
I want in.
In on what?
I know what you're doing, Juliet.
I'm not really sure what--
I read your notes.
I know what you took from the lab.
The only thing I don't know is...
who's your guinea pig?
Ed, I've...
I've been doing my research
in my own lab, on my own time.
- I don't really see--
- It's your sister, isn't it?
Look, Jules,
there's two ways this plays out--
One is, your research is
potentially genius.
And the other,
you're raising
some very serious ethical questions,
maybe even criminal concerns...
but if you collaborate with me,
based on my reputation,
all this is viewed
as cutting edge science.
And we will win prizes
and drink Champagne
and do a lot of good for people.
Why don't I give you some time
to think about it?
Ben's awake.
How?
Shephard says he's a spinal surgeon,
not an anesthesiologist.
Ben's asking for you.
This a hobby of yours, underdog,
digging holes?
Yep, that and basket weaving.
Want one?
Happen to have a tunnel to the mainland?
No, but I've got a boat.
Can we use it?
Yeah, but we've got to hurry.
Hold on a second, sister.
You just happen to find us in the woods,
you just happen to have a boat,
and you're gonna let us use it, huh?
There's something we need to do first.
Oh, gee...
My boyfriend is being held prisoner.
If you help me rescue him,
I promise you,
I'll get you back to the other island.
Your boyfriend--
his name happen to be Karl?
Yeah.
Ah, come on.
I stopped the surgery.
I know.
I've been able to hear you
for a few minutes now.
It's very clever of you.
I should have seen it coming.
Are you in pain?
- I can...
- No.
But thanks all the same.
I'd like to speak to Juliet alone,
please, Jack.
No, I'm sorry.
Please, I'm asking you...
one gentleman to another.
It won't hurt you to give me 3 minutes,
will it...
Knowing I have only 27 left?
If you touch him,
- if you try to--
- I won't.
You've got three minutes.
I'm Tom, by the way.
They've got history.
I would like for you to go back
in there,
put Ben under and finish the surgery.
And why would I want to do that?
Because I'm going to go help
your friends escape.
Thank you for taking the time
to let us make our pitch, Dr. Burke.
Mittelos Bioscience is based in Oregon.
We're just outside of Portland.
These shots might seem a little,
uh, cheeseball,
but our people really are this happy.
Now why? Because we're privately funded.
Privately funded means freedom.
We organize trips every week
in and around the Portland area,
which is just awesome for hiking
and biking and river running.
Look, when you--
your company reached out to me,
I was flattered,
but I don't really know
why you would want me to--
Is it true that you successfully
impregnated a male field mouse?
It didn't carry to term.
Mind if I ask you something?
Sure.
What do you see?
It's a human womb, obviously.
Judging from the decomposition
of the endometrium,
I would say
that the woman was somewhere in her 70s.
No, actually, she's 26.
What happened to her?
What if I told you that you could have
complete freedom and money to find out?
We think you're special, Dr. Burke,
and we want you to lead a team
of highly trained people
because we think you're just that good.
I can't.
Why can't you?
My ex-husband wouldn't let me. I--
He wouldn't want you to have
this opportunity?
He doesn't want me to have anything.
He would never give the okay.
Maybe we could reach out to him
- on your behalf--
- Don't bother.
There must be something
that he would respond to.
If he were hit by a bus--
How about that? That would work.
That was totally inappropriate.
- No, no--
- No, I, uh...
I'm sorry that I wasted your time.
- Dr. Burke, please, you--
- No, I'm sorry.
Whatever you think I am, I'm not.
I'm not a leader, Mr. Alpert.
I'm a mess.
Well, hell.
Karl's gotta be in there.
What, you mean you ain't sure?
It's the only place I haven't looked.
You know the guard?
Yeah. His name's Aldo.
Okay, Lollipop,
you wanna tell me how we're gonna
get by him with one gun and no bullets?
I've got an idea.
Of course you do.
Open the door!
Alex? What the hell are you doing?
They must've gotten out of their cages.
I caught them in the jungle.
Now open up, Aldo!
Just stop!
You're not supposed to be here.
If your dad finds out,
he's gonna kill me.
My dad was the one who told me
to bring them here, to you.
Look, maybe you should call him.
I'm sure he's got nothing better to do.
Danny, I need Ben.
Why?!
Listen, I got Alex here.
She's got Austen and Ford with her--
Damn it, whatever she says,
don't believe it.
You hold 'em right there. I'm on my--
Don't get mad at me
just 'cause you were dumb enough
to fall for the old
"wookiee prisoner" gag.
Where's Karl?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Shoot him in the knee.
- What?
- Give me the rifle.
We don't have time for this. I'll do it.
Okay, all right!
He's at the end of the hall, room 23.
Keys are in my back pocket.
Damn good con, Freckles.
I almost believed
you were gonna shoot that boy.
It wasn't a con.
Here it is!
Sawyer!
Help!
- Is he okay?
- We got your boyfriend back.
Now where's your damn boat?
Idiot!
- Where are they?
- I don't know.
- Alex was with them.
- Danny!
We're letting them go.
- Letting them go?
- Ben gave the order.
- Ben's in surgery. I was just there.
- He woke up.
- Oh, he woke up, huh?
- Shephard won't finish the surgery
unless he knows his friends
are off the island.
Do you want Ben to die?
I know Ben would rather die
than let them go.
How was the interview?
It's not for me.
- What?
- It's fine.
They're too far away, anyway.
It's Portland.
Jules, you didn't say no
because of me?
Well, why would I wanna go
all the way to Portland
for research that doesn't even work?
Because it does work.
I'm pregnant.
I'm pre-- I'm pregnant.
What?
Look, look. I took a blood test, too.
I didn't want to tell you
until I was sure.
- It worked.
- Yeah.
All my life, all I've ever wanted
was to have a baby,
and now, because of you, I'm gonna...
God, now I just need to get healthy.
Now I just need--
I just need to get healthy
so I can see the little bugger
get into an ivy league school, you know?
You will. Of course you will.
Hey, now you can tell
that bastard ex-husband of yours
what he can do with his ethics.
Because you're insufferable,
and you're mean.
Well, you asked me for the truth, mom,
and that's--
Let me call you later, okay?
Hello, Jules. What's up?
She's pregnant.
Excuse me?
It worked. Rachel's pregnant.
Julie, that's...
I need, uh, I need to see your labs.
We'll have to verify the data before--
No.
I'm not interested in publishing, Ed.
It's my sister.
Fine, then if you're not interested,
why are you concerned if--
You okay?
Yeah.
I just don't like blood too much.
Well...
then you probably
won't wanna be looking at that.
So, uh,
if you really can get off the island,
why didn't you
just take him to a facility?
Why all this?
Because ever since
the sky turned purple, we--
What the hell happened?!
I just nicked an artery.
Isn't that what you already did?!
Yeah, well, that was on purpose.
Can you fix it?
Damn it.
- You got him?
- I got him.
Nice ride!
- Help me.
- We gotta go now, okay?
Can you stand?
All right, come on.
So... you're the boss' daughter, huh?
Never saw that coming.
Let's go, Cheech.
We're goin' for a little ride.
- Careful.
- All right, easy.
I'm gonna put you in the boat,
all right?
Wait, wait.
- You're gonna be okay.
- Danny...
No, Sawyer.
Danny!
- What happened? Is he--
- I can't see.
- What?
There's too much blood.
All right, get over here.
Tom, he's gonna die
if you don't get over here right now.
Go.
Get outta here.
You heard the lady.
Let's go.
Not you, Alex.
- You're staying.
- Why?
We both know your father,
and the only way he'll let Karl live
is if you're here when he wakes up.
I'm sorry, Alex.
Hey, Alex.
I missed you.
I know.
I missed you, too.
You have to go away now,
but I'll see you real soon, okay?
I love you.
I have to go to sleep now.
Wait.
Easy. Okay, easy.
- Wait, wait--
- Hold it steady, damn it.
Hold it steady.
Jack, are you there?
All right, hold that up to me.
- The walkie-- Hold it up to me.
- What about the surgery--
Just do it!
Yeah, I'm here, Kate. You okay?
Yeah, I... we've got a boat.
They're letting us go.
Who's letting you go?
The blonde woman.
So you're safe, you and Sawyer?
Yes, yeah.
Tell me.
Tell you?
The first day on the beach,
the day of the crash--
The story that I told you--
If you're safe, tell me.
- You think this is the best time--
- Shut up!
You... were doing surgery on a girl...
and you messed up.
You made a mistake.
You tore something on her back,
and all the nerves came loose...
and you said you were so afraid...
and you said the fear was so...
real, and you didn't know what to do...
so you counted to five...
and then you weren't afraid anymore...
and then it was just gone...
and you fixed her.
You saved her.
I need you to make me a promise, Kate.
Promise me that
you'll never come back here for me.
Don't come back, Kate.
Jack, where are you--
Turn it off.
Jack? Jack, please, where are--
Trades are comin' up.
We gotta go.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
We have some paperwork
that we need you to sign,
but take your time. There's no rush.
Thank you.
Were you able to remove the tumor?
Yeah.
You'll want to do a biopsy,
see if it's malignant.
So what now, I just go back to my cell?
Until they figure out
what to do with you.
"They"...
What did he say?
I'm sorry?
Ben-- What did he say
that made you want to save his life?
It doesn't really matter what he said.
It matters to me.
After everything
that I have been put through,
you owe me an answer.
And I wanna know what he said.
Tissue?
Thank you. Thanks.
Have we met?
Hello, Dr. Burke.
- Mr. Alpert?
- I'm, so sorry for your loss.
What are you doing here?
I saw what happened on the news,
end, uh, your office said
you were down here.
I just wanted to express my condolences
in person
before I went back up to Portland.
This is Ethan.
He's one of my colleagues.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
He was hit by a bus.
I know. They say
you were there when it happened.
- It must have been--
- No, no, in our interview,
I said-- I said that I wanted--
I wanted him to get hit by a bus.
Dr. Burke, I realize
you're a little shook up right now,
but this is just a tragic accident.
You can'blame yourself.
I don't even rember you saying that.
Why are you here, Mr. Alpert?
Look, uh...
I know the timing is horrible,
but we came because we're that serious
about getting you to come work with us.
Just give us six months.
If you need to, you'll be back
before your sister gives birth.
- How did you know that my--
- Well, we're very...
thorough in our recruitment process.
Can my sister come?
Won't work. We're pretty remote.
She wouldn't have access
to the treatment that she needs.
But it's Portland.
- There's plenty of clinics and--
- Well, actually,
we're not quite in Portland.
I wanna know what he said.
I've been on this island
for three years, Jack--
3 years, 2 months and 28 days.
He said that if I...
let him live...
and I helped you...
that he would finally let me go home.
swsub.com