[Clacking]
[Beeping]
[Young Jarod]
Hi, Mom. Hi, Dad.
I'm so happy to see you again.
Hello, Mother, Father.
It's very good
to see you again.
Sydney, I can't decide
what to say.
- And this tie isn't working.
- Jarod...
just try and relax.
Just please tell me
what to say.
Trust your feelings...
and you'll be fine.
[Beeping]
[Mr. Lyle]
So how much did the little thief get?
Sixty million,
give or take.
Considering what was sitting
in the account...
Jarod could have
hit us worse.
You know,
murder happens...
extortion
is sometimes necessary...
but theft-
simply taking for the taking-
has always escaped me as
an admirable criminal pursuit.
Little bitter about
your car being stolen?
Ten miles on the odometer.
Three hours filling out
police reports...
five pages of insurance
company fine print-
I know it's a little late to stop the happy
fellows at the chop shop this time...
but I saw this and I immediately
thought of you.
Consider it a little
preventative medicine.
Actually, with the $2,000
alarm system...
that the dealer
all but threw in...
I still hope to get
my car back in one piece.
[Jarod]
Now there's a good target.
Once you try
one of these puppies...
you'll never go back.
It takes a lot of jack to supply
the kind of order I'm talking about.
Who's funding you?
Some people
I used to work for.
I'm talking about 60 SAMs.
If they can afford 'em,
I can find 'em.
You get 'em to my place
in Venezuela, we're in business.
There's no business
like the arms business.
[Man Narrating]
There are Pretenders among us.
[Jarod]
I was taken from my family.
Thirty-six hours and he's already
demonstrating more talent than any of our others.
How many people died
because of what I thought up?
Since I broke out, I've spent
every moment searching for my past.
[Miss Parker]
He's a Pretender-
A genius who can become
anyone that he wants to be.
- The Centre wants him alive.
- Preferably.
[Miss Parker]
He defends the weak and abused.
Life's a gift.
- You a doctor?
- I am today.
Sixty million dollars-
What are you up to, Jarod?
Mmm. Actually,
it's 58,990,620.
It's not every day we get ripped off
to the exact penny.
Once again, Officer,
it's a black...
500 SL convertible...
license plate, LYLE-1.
Well, it didn't just vanish.
Found it. Thank you.
Mm. Have a nice day.
Jarod.
How goes the hunt,
Broots?
Well, Jarod's routed the money through
a maze of phony cover accounts-
nearly 100 of them so far-
but I'm still tracking it.
Look, I hate to bring the room down,
but we've been here before.
It'll take us three weeks
to run Jarod's little maze...
and by then
he'll be long gone.
Not this time.
Right, Broots?
I created a new
computer tracing program-
type of digital encryption.
I marked the Centre's funds
electronically-
like a bank marks cash-
and this program lets me
follow the money wherever it goes.
[Chuckles]
I, uh-
I call it "The Hound."
Too bad it doesn't work
for cars though.
Whoo-hoo!
Come on.
You're making me feel like McGwire.
[Grunts]
Whoo!
Three-bagger.
Come on. Put some heat on that ball.
[Groans]
I'm sorry, Mr. Blake.
It slipped.
Your turn.
- [Man Groans]
- [Bat Clatters]
[Man #2]
You all right?
I guess that one
got away from you.
Landed right where
I threw it.
Hmm.
Just stack 'em four high.
The missiles.
All 60 of them.
- I'll have my man cut you a check.
- Check?
What are you talking about?
That wasn't part of the deal.
I guess you should have
covered that...
before you brought
your weapons here.
You know something,
Mr. Blake?
In their current state
they couldn't take out a Tonka truck.
The guidance systems
are dead...
and I've got the only brain
that can program them.
I guess you should have covered that
before I brought them here.
Cash-
wired to my account.
Half now,
half when they can fly.
Ryan,
I'm in a meeting here.
- I'm sorry, sir.
- Ryan was just playing, Daddy.
Tuck in that shirt.
Oh. Yes, sir.
- Emma.
- Come on, kids. Your dad's working.
Let's get ready for lunch.
Your children
are very well behaved.
How long is it gonna take
to program my missiles?
I'll need to be here
for two weeks.
- You got 72 hours.
- We're talking about 60 missiles here.
It would take an entire team
of specialists...
to program those missiles
in 72 hours.
- I'll give you Logan and Dobbs.
- I don't think you understand-
No, I understand perfectly.
You got 72 hours.
You stay in the guest house. I want you
here until those missiles are programmed.
Seventy-two hours then.
Guidance telemetry...
needs to be downloaded
into each missile-
one at a time.
Which means we will
be working shifts around the clock...
if we're going to meet
the deadline.
[Man] Considering Mr. Blake
already has buyers lined up...
there's not much choice,
is there?
I'm going to get some air.
Get started, Mr. Dobbs.
[Man On Radio]
Inter-perimeter clear.
[Clink]
You know, if you center
the tail- like this-
it flies a lot further.
Thanks.
Who are you?
I'm working for your dad.
[Girl]
Do you know if"angel"is G-E-L or G-A-L?
- G-E-L.
- Thanks.
- Jarod.
- I'm Rebecca.
- Hi, Rebecca.
- Thanks, Jarod.
What are you writing?
A letter... to my mom.
I write lots of them.
- Your mom's not here?
- No.
She's...
right here, see?
- She's very pretty.
- Don't tell my dad about the picture.
- I'm not supposed to have it.
- I promise.
Our mom's in heaven.
She's an angel.
Thank you for your patience.
It's really been a madhouse here today.
- [Child] Mommy, Mommy!
- It's okay.
Oh! I am so sorry.
I swear, that's the fifth glass
I've dumped today.
Spilling a glass of water
isn't the end of the world.
Losing your children is.
What do you know
about my kids?
I know that you lost them...
and you won't be alive
until you get them back.
Wendy, my name is Jarod.
I heard about you...
and your story.
I know you don't have much reason
to trust people right now...
but I would like to help you
get your children back.
Why would you help me?
Let's just say
I know the feeling.
It's been three years
since-
I don't even know
where they are.
Not long after the court
granted me custody...
my ex-husband
stole Ryan and Rebecca.
I have spent every last penny,
every waking moment, searching...
and I'm still without them.
They could be anywhere
in the world by now.
Leave that to me.
Desmond is a monster.
When the judge granted me
full custody...
Desmond was furious.
I saw hatred in his eyes
like I have never seen.
You're talking about going
after his number one possession.
And that is exactly how
he sees our children, as a possession.
- He sounds like a real family man.
- He wasn't always like that.
Now... he would kill...
to keep me away
from our children.
Wendy. Let me help you.
Who are you?
I'm someone...
who believes that children
shouldn't be stolen...
from a mother who loves them.
[Rebecca]
We miss our mom.
She died three years ago...
in a car crash.
Jarod, there's been
an accident.
The plane
your parents were on-
it crashed.
There were no survivors.
[Emma]
Ryan, Rebecca, in the house.
Come on, in the house.
I don't know what your business
with Mr. Blake is...
but from now on,
you stay away from those kids.
Those children are lucky to have
someone like you watching out for them.
- [Whirring, Beeping]
- [Keys Clacking]
[Dobbs]
See you in 60.
[Woman Speaking Spanish On P.A.]
[Jarod]
Wendy.
Oh, Jarod.
I got here as quickly
as I could.
Just, uh-Just tell me
that my children are okay.
- They're fine.
- [Sighs] Thank goodness.
When I got your messages
saying to come as soon as possible...
I didn't know what to think.
I didn't expect to hear from you
for at least a week.
I had to push
the timetable up.
Desmond has only
given me 72 hours.
- Is that enough time?
- [Sighs] It'll have to be.
Just tell me that you are sure
that Ryan and Rebecca are okay.
See for yourself.
I took this yesterday.
- I never thought I'd see 'em again.
- You will.
- They ride horses.
- [Jarod] Lessons every day at 5.00.
Unfortunately, Desmond
is always with them-
- along with his armed guard.
- Well, how are we gonna save 'em?
This is a layout
of your ex-husband's compound.
Ryan and Rebecca's rooms
are in the main house.
I'm working on circumventing the
security cameras and the alarm system...
so that I have free access
inside the house.
Once I've accomplished that...
then we'll make our move.
You'll be waiting in a car
outside of this gate.
When?
Before my cover
with Desmond is blown.
- Soon. Very soon.
- [Sighs]
Oh, I hope we're doing
the right thing.
It's just, uh...
hard for me to even imagine
being with them again.
Trust your feelings.
You'll do just fine.
[Sighs]
There's something you have to know.
Desmond told your children...
that you died in a car crash.
I just-
I don't know if I'm gonna
make it through this.
Wendy, you can't
fall apart on me now.
It may be a shock for them
at first...
but your children need you.
They need a mother.
Trust me.
- I have to get back to the compound.
- Oh.
Jarod-
Oh, just thank you.
- [Chuckles]
- Thank you.
You can thank me
when you're back with your children.
The Hound did it.
Gee, Broots, come on in.
It found the money
thatJarod stole.
He routed it
through 506 bogus accounts...
and it ended up here.
"Raul Zenega-
real estate developer...
- Mexico City. "
- That may be what it says...
but Mr. Zenega's
an arms dealer.
And you know this because?
Let's just say he and I
have a history together-
back when I was still
building my résumé.
What would Jarod be doing
with 60 million dollars' worth of weapons?
Sounds like a question
for your pal Zenega.
So what happened
to your pitcher?
Disabled list.
You wanted to see me?
About a month ago,
someone tried to blow up my car.
Luckily I wasn't in it...
but lately...
I've been a little
mistrustful of strangers.
I went by your room
last night.
You weren't in it.
- I didn't realize I had a curfew.
- My house, my rules.
I went for a walk.
And I'm supposed
to believe that?
Look, Mr. Desmond, I'm not
here to blow up your car.
I'm here to program your missiles,
get my money...
and get the hell out of here.
- [Fence Rattles]
- [Mutters Angrily]
[Dobbs]
Twenty-three down.
Great.
Thirty-seven more to go.
[Beeping]
- [Jarod] Damn it.
- What was that?
- Must have blown a circuit.
- I'll go reset it.
No, I'll go.
Get that casing fitted.
[Man Over Radio]
Rear gate secure.
[Radio Chatter, Indistinct]
What do you think
you're doing?
I was hungry, so I thought
I would grab a sandwich.
Well, I'm afraid
that this area is off-limits.
Well, the old stomach was growling.
What can you do?
That's a very pretty
medallion you're wearing.
- What saint is it?
- I don't know.
It was a gift.
And now I have to insist
that you leave.
I don't allow Mr. Blake's associates
in this part of the house.
Tell me something, Emma.
If you have such a problem
with Mr. Blake's associates...
why do you work for him?
It's really none
of your concern.
It must be very difficult
to fill her shoes.
One doesn't replace a mother.
I'm sure...
wherever she is...
she's very grateful to you.
[Panting]
[Miss Parker]
Mmm. Work those quads.
You must be Raul Zenega.
Ay.
A beautiful young lady
has caught me at a disadvantage.
- Please don't get up.
- [Laughs]
[Mr. Lyle]
Hola, Raul.
- [Groans]
- Little out of shape, are we?
Please.
Whatever you want,
I'll give it to you. Anything.
- [Groans]
- You obviously made
quite an impression last time you met.
But to my credit...
very little scarring.
My legs, my legs.
I can't hold it.
[Groans]
Psst. This man gave you...
sixty million dollars
of our money.
I'd like to know
what he got in return.
Missile launchers-
laser-guided SAMs.
Sixty of them.
- [Squealing]
- [Groans]
Twenty-second time-out,
Raul.
Where'd he take them?
All I know
is the name ofhis buyer.
It's Desmond Blake.
Tell us where to find Blake...
and you keep your knees.
I would never lie to you.
I swear.
Not after last time.
[Groaning]
- [Groaning]
- Gravity's a bitch.
- [Knocking]
- Wendy?
Wendy?
Wendy!
Wendy.
Oh, no.
The riding school.
Good form, Ryan.
Keep working on it.
[Chattering, Indistinct]
That's not bad, Son. You're getting better.
You're getting better.
- [Ryan] Where's my plane?
- I think it's over there.
Hi, Daddy.
How am I doing?
Pull your horse in a bit.
Straighten your back, hands higher.
That's it.
Come on. Come on.
Don't give me that look. The only reason
I tell you what you're doing wrong...
is so you can do it better
next time.
- [Radio Playing]
- [Woman Speaking Spanish]
Ryan! Ryan! Ryan!
- Bring it!
- I think I saw a lady. I think it was Mom.
Let's go. Let's go. In the car.
In the car. Everyone.
Everybody, get in the car.
Son, get in the car!
Let's go. Let's go.
Beat it. Go!
- [Horn Honking]
- [Blake] Emma! Emma!
But it was Mom.
I saw her.
Ryan, you did not see your mother.
It's impossible.
- Inside, both of you!
- But what if he's right?
Maybe it was all a mistake. Maybe
she wasn't even in the car that crashed.
She could still be alive.
- What if my parents weren't even on that plane?
- Jarod...
denial is a very...
human response
to a devastating loss...
but this is a reality
that must be faced...
no matter how painful
that may be.
[Blake]
Did I tell you?
I said inside the house,
both of you, now.
But, Dad, if Mom's still alive,
she's gotta be looking for us.
It was her. She looks
just like she did in Rebecca's picture.
What picture?
Give me that picture,
young lady.
I said give me that book.
Why?
Why do you kids
do this to me?
Do you know how difficult
it was losing your mother?
How it tears me up inside...
to see her face?
- But, Dad, if it was Mom-
- Your mother is dead!
This does nothing
but cause me pain.
Ryan,
maybe the reason...
that you saw your mom
is because you miss her so much.
Your heart wants
to see her so badly...
that your eyes
went along with it.
Emma, get these two packed.
We're leaving first thing in the morning.
- Leaving for how long?
- I said get them packed!
Come on.
- Come on.
- The morning? Are you crazy?
There's no way I can have
the missiles done by the morning.
And I want to know what
you were doing out by the stables.
I was trying to tell you
that we're running behind.
Dobbs and Logan
aren't cutting it.
No, they're cutting it.
It's you who I'm concerned about.
I'm thinking it may be time
to just blow your brains out.
I'm the only one that knows
where the memory chips are.
You need me.
Unless, of course,
you don't want your missiles.
Jarod, I've got a brain too...
and it's telling me
not to trust you.
- [Jarod] What were you thinking?
- I wanted to see them.
I was just losing my mind knowing
that they were just a few blocks away.
Well, now Desmond is spooked.
He's taking the kids
and flying out first thing in the morning.
- What? Where are they going?
- He wouldn't tell me.
I have to get them
out tonight.
You park the car by the gate
at 11:00 p.m., like we had planned...
and you sit there
with the lights off and you wait.
- Can we trust Emma?
- Absolutely.
All right. I will create
some kind of diversion.
Then I will
get the children out.
In the meantime,
don't go out that door...
and don't so much
as peek out those windows.
Desmond's men
will be looking for you.
Ryan didn't even
recognize me.
[Sighs]
Of course he did.
It's all he could think about.
Rebecca too.
She carried this with her
all along.
11:00 p.m. Sharp.
Wendy, I'll get them out.
I promise.
[Broots] The name Raul Zenega
gave you? Desmond Blake?
- I think I found him.
- You think.
Remember the Centre account
thatJarod stole the 60 million from?
It just received
a very serious deposit-
- a wire for 40 million bucks.
- Where did it come from?
Jarod's buyer-
Desmond Blake-
from a small town in Venezuela.
I hope you brought
your sunscreen.
[Men Chattering]
Emma.
I need to speak to you.
- There's not much time.
- Time for what?
Time to get Rebecca and Ryan
out of here and into their mother's arms.
What are you talking about?
Do I have to remind you that
Wendy Dawson died three years ago?
That is what Desmond
always wanted you to believe...
but I am telling you,
she's very much alive...
and in a hotel
not ten minutes from here.
You know what?
I don't believe you.
[Sighs]
That medallion around your neck-
It's a St. Anne's medal.
Wendy gave it to you
the day her son was born...
to thank you for being
like a sister to her.
[Scoffs]
Desmond could have told you that one.
When you put it around your neck,
she made you promise...
that if anything ever happened
to her children...
you would devote your life
to raising them.
Desmond couldn't
have told me that.
He wasn't even there
that day his son was born.
Oh, my God, Wendy.
But I saw the casket
go into the grave.
You never saw
inside the casket, did you?
I was- I was in New York
when Desmond called me...
about the news
that Wendy had died.
And I'd been divorced
for a couple of months...
and he said that the kids needed me
desperately, so I flew here straightaway.
She was buried the next day.
Wendy had no other family,
so-
[Laughs]
Desmond said that he wanted
to bury her here...
so that the kids
could be close to her.
What lie have I been part of?
Be a part of the truth.
Help me.
Help those children.
Come on.
[Beeping]
Call the general now-
and get someone to put this out.
[Clamoring]
- [Beeping]
- [Whirring]
Ryan.
- [Beeping]
- [Whirring]
Rebecca. Rebecca!
- Where are they? Where are the children?
- I don't know.
[Phone Ringing]
- Jarod?
- The plan has changed, Wendy.
Get out of there. Go.
- Wh-Where are the children?
- They're gone.
Desmond took your children
to another part of the compound...
but they're okay.
Because he saw me at the riding stables.
[Groans]
- I can't risk anything happening to the children.
- Nothing will, I promise you.
You don't know Desmond.
He'll do anything
to keep them away from me.
- I mean, anything.
- Wendy, calm down. Now listen to me.
Go to the airport and park
at the south end of the hangar and wait.
- This is a mistake.
- I was stolen from my mother when I was a child.
I never wanted her
to stop looking for me...
even if it put me
in danger.
Wendy, never give up.
The children need you.
[Sighs]
I'll get them out.
[Electronic Whine]
[Beeping]
Here you go, Dawkins.
- The SAMs are loaded and ready to go.
- That's great.
It's been a rough
couple of days.
Keeping a family together
can be very difficult.
- Mr. Blake?
- Hmm?
There's been a problem.
Dawkins is feeling really ill.
- Who's Dawkins?
- He's my driver.
I could drive you.
Hey, it's the least I can do
for a paying customer.
What the hell.
An iron gate's not gonna
save you this time, Jarod.
[Blake]
What's the problem? Let's go.
Emma, aren't those two
parked over there the ones...
that were questioning you about
the children when you were in town?
- Uh, yeah, yeah. That's them.
- What questions?
I should have mentioned it
to you earlier...
but I, uh-
I didn't want to bother you.
They just seemed
really interested...
in Ryan and Rebecca,
that's all.
I told them nothing,
of course.
We've got a couple
of trespassers at the gate.
Make sure they don't
give us any trouble or follow us.
Then you can let them go.
- He's gotta come out sometime.
- I got a bad feeling.
Move it! Go! Go!
[Blake]
Okay, kids, let's go. Come on, let's shake.
[Beeps]
Unlock the door.
Hey.
What the hell are you doing?
Just making sure
I have a captive audience.
Oh, Desmond,
I hope you don't mind...
but I sent
one of those ahead.
- I thought I would do a little target practice.
- [Electronic Whine]
Wait till Logan and Dobbs
get here. You're a dead man.
The key word being "when."
[Chuckles]
[Groans]
Oh, man.
You have wonderful taste
in weapons, Desmond.
Who the hell are you?
Why are you doing this, Jarod?
So you would know
what it feels like...
to have everything
that you care about in the world...
ripped away from you-
Like you did to your ex-wife.
Like you did
to Ryan and Rebecca.
My kids? What do my kids
have to do with this?
Oh, they have everything
to do with this.
- I know what's best for them.
- Oh, really?
Like telling them that the one person
that they love in the world is dead?
That woman doesn't deserve them.
They're mine!
You make it sound like
having children is like owning-
well, a missile.
- [Panting]
- [Whirring]
No! No! No!
No! No!
You know, on second thought...
blowing you up is too easy.
I've got something...
that will get you
where you live.
Emma, bring the children.
[Blake] What the hell's
going on, Jarod? What are you doing?
- Ryan. Rebecca.
- I have someone here
who has missed you very much-
who loves you more
than everything in the whole world.
Don't be afraid.
Just trust your heart.
Oh, Wendy.
No! No!
No!
No, don't listen! No!
- Come on!
- [Ryan] Mommy!
- I can't believe it.
- [Rebecca] We missed you.
- You're actually here.
- [Blake] Wendy! Wendy, don't!
Mom, oh! Oh, my God.
[Wendy]
Oh, look at you.
Emma! Thank you so much.
Get on the plane.
[Blake]
Rebecca!
Ryan!
[Jarod]
Oh, Desmond.
You know...
the Venezuelan authorities
were very interested...
when I told them that arms dealing
was going on right under their very noses.
- You son of a bitch.
- They'll be here within the hour.
F.Y. I. -
All this time I haven't
been arming your missiles.
I've been disarming them.
Now they couldn't
take out a Tonka truck.
Rebecca!
Ryan!
Rebecca! You're my kids!
Come on. Let's go.
Jarod! You-
[Laughing]
You've given me
my life back.
Take good care of them.
- Let them take care of you.
- I will.
Oh. Here's a little something
to get your new life started-
from Desmond.
From Desmond?
Well, I helped out
a little bit.
Oh! Oh, my gosh.
- Good luck.
- Jarod.
I hope your parents
find you one day...
so that you can feel
what I'm feeling right now.
Thanks.
Thank you.
- [Whispering] Bye.
- Bye.
[Young Jarod]
Dear Mom. I miss you more than ever.
[Thinking]
Every day I think of you.
I make myself remember
your face...
and Dad's face.
I remember everything I can...
so I'll know you
when we see each other again.