[Cell Phone Beeping]
- [Rings, Beeps]
- This is Sydney.
[Jarod]
It's incredible how beautiful Yellowstone is.
- Even from 12,000 feet.
- I can barely hear you.
I'm going through
a little turbulence.
- Speaking of black clouds, is Miss Parker around?
- Hasn't arrived yet.
- Well, it's very important that I speak with her.
- Sounds mysterious.
I'm on my way to meet someone
that was very close to her mother.
- Someone who can answer a lot of questions.
- [Engine Pops, Sputters]
Jarod, is something wrong?
I'm fine, but my engine
doesn't appear to be.
Listen, Sydney.
I don't have much time.
- Did the package come that I sent for Miss Parker?
- It arrived early this morning.
- See that she gets it.
- Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
- If you don't talk to me in one hour-
- [Engine Sputters]
- [Beeps]
- [Whispers] Jarod.
[Beeps]
Come on, baby.
Don't fail on me now.
[Sputtering]
- [Applause On TV]
- Make with the hot stuff, stranger boy.
[Broots Laughing]
Hmm.
[Laughs]
[Broots Laughing]
- Home movies, Broots?
- [Clears Throat] Miss Parker.
- [Chuckles] Good morning.
- What's good about it, Cheetah?
Well, uh-
Are you okay?
Just peachy.
Thomas is out of town
for another week.
Last time I checked,
my father was still in Cabo with that troll.
And if that's not enough torment,
he left Raines in charge of this nuthouse.
Speaking of which,
just what the hell are you two doing?
Oh, uh- [Chuckles]
It's therapy.
Sydney's hoping that
a little cognitive stimulation...
might improve Angelo's
expressive abilities.
Well, it certainly seems
to be working for the monkeys.
Oh, Miss Parker.
- You wanted to see me, Dr. Dolittle?
- You okay?
I'm fine. Geez. You get a little gas,
and people think you're dying.
Seems like you've had
a great deal of indigestion lately.
Well, what do you expect?
I work with you three.
[Man On TV]
Right then and there.
And it sure made
a happy gal out of Fanny...
and made a big hero out of
the Lonesome Stranger.
Hi-ho, Plastic.
[Whinnies]
Oh, for God's sake.
What do you want, Sydney?
It's from Jarod to you.
Probably another
twisted attempt to...
rub my face in my twisted
dysfunctional family life.
[Broots]
A rosary?
Miss Parker has pain.
- Parker, are you okay?
- Sydney.
Hang on.
Oh, God.
Miss Parker!
Parker.
Parker, can you hear me?
Syd, she was just standing there,
and then- and then she just fell.
- Oh, my God. She's burning up.
- She's going into shock.
- We've got to get her to a hospital now.
- Okay.
Help! We need help.
Somebody call 911.
Miss Parker needs faith...
but faith is dead.
Miss Parker needs faith,
Mayday! Mayday! This is
2- niner Charlie Victor. Over.
- [Man] What's your problem, Charlie Victor?
- I've lost all power.
- And I'm descending rapidly.
- Charlie Victor, what's your location? Over.
Charlie Victor,
do you read me? Over.
[Man Narrating]
There are Pretenders among us.
[Jarod]
I was taken from my family.
Thirty-six hours and he's already demonstrating
more talent than any of our others.
How many people died
because of what I thought up?
Since I broke out, I've spent
every moment searching for my past.
[Miss Parker]
He's a Pretender-
A genius who can become
anyone that he wants to be.
- The Centre wants him alive.
- Preferably.
[Miss Parker]
He defends the weak and abused.
Life's a gift.
- You a doctor?
- I am today.
[Grunting]
[Woman's Voice] B.P. 's 70 over 40
and falling. Pulse 110 and thready.
Pupils dilated
and unresponsive.
O saturation, 78.
Respiration shallow at 40.
She needs plasma, O-neg-
lots of it.
I want a C.B.C., blood gases, the works.
You're a doctor, right?
- Psychiatrist.
- What the hell happened?
[Sighs] She was experiencing abdominal
pain. Then she just collapsed.
She has a history of ulcers.
And she's been under a lot of stress.
She appears to have massive internal bleeding.
Probably a perforated ulcer.
- Well, will she be okay?
- It's too early to tell.
Excuse me. Alert O.R.
To prepare for surgery.
[Sydney]
Broots, I've got to get back to the Centre.
- You're leaving now, Syd?
- Jarod's supposed to call.
- Jarod?
- I'll explain later.
Stay here
and monitor her condition.
I'll be back.
Okay.
I'm not goin' anywhere.
[Man] "Yea, though I walk through
the valley of the shadow of death...
I will fear no evil,
for thou art with me. "
[Speaking Spanish]
Amen.
The valley of
the shadow of death.
The shadow of death. The shadow of death.
[Echoes]
Jarod, can you keep
a secret?
I guess so, Miss Parker.
What is it?
There's a dead body
in the Centre.
A dead body?
Where is it?
I saw them deliver the coffin
this morning to Dr. Raines.
He told them to take it
to the containment area.
Yeah. I've heard Sydney
talk about that place.
They do a lot of special projects down there,
but they've never taken me there.
- I don't even know where it is.
- Me either.
I asked my daddy about the coffin
and the body, but...
he wouldn't talk about it.
For the last few weeks-
well, since Mommy died-
he's been too busy to talk to me
about anything.
I still can't believe
she's really gone.
I'm sorry about your mother.
I'm okay.
Anyway, if Dad won't tell me where the body is,
then I'll just find it on my own.
If you could follow Dr. Raines without him
knowing it, he'd lead you straight to it.
- Well, come on then. Let's go find him.
- I didn't say I would do it.
- You're not scared, are you?
- No.
It's just...
I've never seen anyone
who was dead before.
They can't hurt you- anymore.
I'm more afraid of Dr. Raines.
I hate doctors.
She's lost a lot of blood.
The pressure's almost undetectable.
- We don't have much time.
- [Woman] She's prepped for abdominal entry.
- Are you ready?
- She's out. Let's start.
- This one's gonna need a miracle to survive.
- [Machine Beeping]
[Groaning]
Ow.
[Grunts]
- [Crack]
- [Screams]
[Panting]
[Grunting]
[Groaning, Coughs]
[Young Jarod's Voice]
I wonder what it's like to die.
Ask Raines. Looks like he died
a long time ago.
Come on.
Let's go find the dead guy.
It's weird. Death is something
that everyone experiences...
but no one wants
to talk about it.
Yeah. When my mom died...
all the grown-ups would
come up and talk to me...
about anything except what
I wanted to talk about.
About what happened to her.
He went this way.
So when we find the coffin,
then what?
We open it.
I wonder what
it'll look like.
What if it was someone
who was mutilated in a wreck or-
or killed in a sim?
Or maybe it was someone the Centre
wanted to get rid of.
Maybe Dr. Raines created some kind of
monster, like Frankenstein.
- Who's Frankenstein?
- [Door Opens]
He's coming back.
Come on.
- There's nowhere to hide. What do we do?
- I don't know.
- [Doorknob Rattles]
- Who's in there?
- [Young Miss Parker] Thanks, Angelo.
- Faith is waiting.
That was too close.
Don't wet your pants, Jarod. You look like
you're gonna pass out or something.
[Soft Growl, Panting]
[Growls]
Perfect.
- Get out of here!
- [Rock Rattles]
Hello.
Can anybody read me?
This is an emergency. Hello. Over.
This is Montana Air Patrol.
Please respond.
This is 2-niner Charlie Victor.
My engine stalled,
and I've crashed...
into a- a river
or an inlet.
- I need some help.
- Are you hurt? Over.
I have multiple lacerations.
I dislocated my shoulder...
and I think I've broken
a couple of ribs.
- [Mouthing Words]
- I'm stable for now, but I
could use some medical help.
Roger that. Are there
any other survivors? Over.
- No. I'm alone.
- [Static]
Hello. Hello. Can you hear me, air patrol?
Over. Hello.
- Hello.
- This is air patrol. I'm losing your signal.
There's a cold front coming in.
We need your exact location.
- Respond.
- I'm not sure.
I was about two hours
outside of... Casper.
I was heading northwest.
I'm about 30 miles from-
Thirty miles from where?
Charlie Victor, I'm losing you.
Hello. Hello.
Please respond,
Charlie Victor.
- I lost him.
- Probably for good.
Nobody can survive
a night out there. No one.
[Jarod]
Hello. Can you hear me? Over.
[Grunts] Can anybody hear me?
[Echoes]
Hello!
Can anybody hear me?
[Echoes]
[Cell Phone Rings]
- Jarod?
- No, it's Broots.
- I'm here at the hospital. What's goin' on?
- Jarod never called.
- It's not like him. How's Miss Parker?
- I don't know.
They just brought her out of surgery.
They're getting her settled into I.C.U.
I want to go in there, but they're not
letting anyone see her yet.
She shouldn't be
alone in there, Syd.
Stay put, Broots.
I'm heading back there right away.
- Okay.
- [Beeps]
No one should be alone
at a time like this.
[Wolf Howls]
[Owl Hoots]
Come on.
Damn it.
[Grunts]
Come on. Come on.
Please light.
Come on.
Don't go out on me.
[Beeping]
[Chattering]
[Beeping Continues]
You look so cold.
It's so strange, what with you
givin' me a hard time all the time.
But I know you don't mean it.
I know it's just your way.
You've always
been there for me.
Whenever I needed someone,
it was you.
And you probably
can't even hear me.
But I just
want you to know...
that, other than Debbie...
I feel closer to you...
than to anyone.
Miss Parker...
you know, you-
you can't leave me.
Miss Parker.
[Moans Softly]
- Don't be afraid.
- [Moans Softly]
- [Moans]
- Don't be afraid, Miss Parker.
- [Young Jarod] Don't be afraid, Miss Parker.
- [Young Miss Parker] Afraid?
I'm not afraid. I just want to know
where the hell we're going.
M-M-Miss Parker needs faith.
We don't need faith, Angelo.
We have to find the body.
[Young Jarod]
Look.
That must be it.
What is it?
It's where
they're keeping the body.
Faith.
[Young Jarod]
It feels strange to be here.
[Young Miss Parker]
Maybe we shouldn't be.
Come on. Let's get out ofhere.
We've come this far.
What's wrong?
[Young Miss Parker]
Nothing. It reminds me of m- Never mind.
[Young Jarod]
But I thought you wanted to see it.
[Young Miss Parker]
I do. This just isn't the right time.
- Are you afraid?
- I don't know.
Come on.
[Wolf Whining]
You hungry?
Well, so am I. So, you'rejust gonna
have to wait a little longer for me.
- [Shouts]
- [Growls]
No.
[Machine Beeping]
Sydney.
- [Sydney] How is she?
- [Broots] Well, she lost a lot ofblood.
Her fever's over 102.
The doctor says she's developed peritonitis,
whatever the hell that is.
It's bad.
They said she-
that she might not make it.
I wish there was
something I could do.
[Whispers]
You're already doing it, Broots.
Sorry, guys.
Gotta ask you to leave now.
- It's real important she gets her rest.
- Okay.
Faith.
[Moans]
Shh. It's okay.
It's okay.
[Miss Parker Moans Softly]
Faith.
[Woman On P.A.]
Wheelchair, 412.
She keeps saying something
about faith.
That's what Angelo said-
in the sim lab when he saw
the rosary thatJarod sent her.
Right before she collapsed.
- What do you think it means?
- I'm not sure.
But I seem to remember
there was a project- long time ago-
which was code-named Faith.
- We need to get back to the Centre.
- Now?
I believeJarod was
in a plane crash.
- What?
- I need you to try and figure out
where he might have gone down.
- Nurse.
- Yes.
If her condition changes-
I have all your numbers.
I'll contact you immediately.
There isn't much
you can do here anyway.
- It's all up to her now.
- Thank you.
Faith.
I have to find...
faith.
It's-
It's a girl.
She's beautiful.
[Murmurs]
- You're not dead.
- Neither are you.
Yeah. It's just... we-
Never mind.
My name is Miss Parker.
Kind of formal, isn't it?
Hi. I'm Faith.
- Hi.
- I'm Jarod.
- And, uh, this is Angelo. He doesn't talk much.
- Hi.
- [Young Jarod] What are you doin'down here?
- Oh, I've been sick.
Really, really sick.
They brought me here
to get well.
I've never seen
other children in this place.
Yeah. They live here.
I'm here with my dad.
He works here.
But, as it turns out,
I'm usually alone.
I'm used to
being by myself too.
But I'm not alone now.
Maybe we could play together.
You know, be friends.
I'd like that.
- [Footsteps Approaching]
- Bad.
- We gotta get out of here.
- We're not supposed to be here.
We'll get in a lot of trouble.
- I won't tell anyone. I promise.
- Okay.
- We gotta go now. But we'll be back, okay?
- Come on.
- I'll be back. Bye.
I'm not going anywhere.
Close.
You know, I've never
had a friend before.
I mean, a girlfriend.
I can't wait for Faith to get well
so we can play together.
Faith, uh, isn't just sick.
She's very sick.
What do you mean?
I read her chart, and she's-
she's not gonna make it.
But...
I don't want her to die.
I don't want anyone to die.
[Echoes]
[Angelo] Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women,
and blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners,
now and at the hour of our death. Amen.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women,
and blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners,
now and at the hour of our death. Amen.
- Hail Mary, full of Grace, the Lord is with thee.
- [Steady Beep]
Blessed art thou among women,
and blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners,
now and at the hour of our death.
Amen.
[Girl Giggling]
[Giggling]
[Faith]
Hi, Jarod.
[Steady Beep]
[Woman]
All right. Bring it in this way.
- Got it.
- No pulse. No respiration.
We've got a full code here, people.
Ten c.c. 's of epinephrine now.
Prepare to defibrillate.
Starting at 100.
All clear.
- [Woman] Clear.
- [Man] Clear.
Hi.
You okay?
Yeah. I guess.
Come on.
Is she... asleep?
[Whispers]
Faith. Faith.
Oh. Hi.
Did you see her?
Who?
My mommy.
She was right here.
There's no one here.
I must have been dreaming.
But it was so real.
We were laughing and talking about
what we were gonna do.
And...
I didn't feel...
you know, sick anymore.
How do you feel?
Better since you got here.
Here. It was my mom's.
It's mine now.
She said...
that I should hold it...
and think about her
whenever...
I feel frightened or sad.
You know, it's like...
I feel her with me again.
[Sobs]
And...
before you know it...
I'm not frightened
or lonely anymore.
It always
makes me feel better.
Thank you.
And thank you
for being my friend.
I'll always be your friend.
I'll always be there for you
and watching over you.
Just like my mommy.
Mommy.
[Very Faint]
She's gone.
[Young Miss Parker]
No.
No, Faith.
Oh, please, no, Faith.
- Please, Faith. Don't leave, Faith. No. Please.
- [Alarm Ringing]
- They'll be here soon. Come on.
- M-Must... g-go.
No. Faith.
[Alarm Continues]
[Steady Beep]
I told you I'd always
be watching you.
You've got to fight.
You can't give up.
It's not your time yet.
All clear.
You mommy loves you
very much.
And she wants you
to fight too.
Up to 200.
One more time.
[Steady Beep]
[Faith] Your mommy loves you very much.
[Echoes]
[Young Miss Parker]
Mama, show me how to braid my hair.
All right.
- [Beeps]
- We got her.
This one's a fighter.
Jarod, you can't give up.
I don't understand.
Just hang on.
They'll be coming for you soon.
Don't give up.
[Giggling]
Not yet.
You can't... have me... yet.
Just hang on.
It'll be daylight s-soon.
Hang on.
- Any news on Miss Parker?
- Nothing.
But her father
should be there by now.
He was flying back in as soon as
he heard what happened.
- And I found something.
- What?
Buried deep
in the Centre Archive.
- Faith.
- Faith? Who is she?
Young girl who was here
a long time ago.
But the record's incomplete. Somebody
went to a lot of trouble to hide the truth.
- Any luck with Jarod?
- Oh, yeah. [Clears Throat]
Using a map of Yellowstone, flight charts
and satellite weather imaging...
from the last time
you spoke with Jarod...
I figure he went down
somewhere right in here.
[Sydney]
That would take days to search.
Well, maybe not. I contacted
the Montana Air Patrol...
and they received a distress call
from someone in this area...
but lost it before they could
establish an exact location.
- Jarod?
- Well, it has to be.
- Using an emergency radio.
- Mm-hmm.
I correlated my data along with the location
of the air patrol's receiving station.
See, I figure he's got to be
right here along this three-mile bank of river.
Contact the Montana
Air Patrol immediately.
Okay.
[Sydney]
I just hope we're not too late.
[Machine Beeping]
Her vitals are stable.
- All we can do now is wait.
- Th-Thank you, Nurse.
Faith, where are you?
Where are you?
[Crying]
Are you gonna be all right?
I think so.
Where did she go?
I don't know.
At least she didn't
die alone.
I wonder if we'll ever
see her again.
Have faith.
[Sobs]
She said she'd always
be watching over us.
I miss her...
and I don't even know
who she was.
[Sobbing]
[Machine Beeping]
[Exhales Deeply]
- Daddy.
- I'm so glad you're back.
- Yes, angel.
Who's Faith?
Faith...
was your sister.
[Young Mr. Parker]
What an awful way to die.
[Young Raines] Mr. Parker, the Cleaners
will be here soon to dispose of the body.
[Young Mr. Parker] God's sake, Raines.
Don't you have any compassion?
Find the priest that did
Catherine's funeral. Father Moore.
I want him to make
the arrangements.
[Young Raines]
Father Moore? I never trusted him.
We don't know what all
Catherine may have told him over the years.
[Mr. Parker]
I don't think you understand me.
Catherine's wishes
will be carried out.
The body is to go to Father Moore.
End of discussion!
[Young Mr. Parker]
Oh, Lord.
Nobody should ever die alone.
[Echoes]
- [Wolf Growls]
- [Gasps, Panting]
[Growls]
You can't have me yet.
[Grunts]
[Helicopter Whirring]
[Jarod Grunts, Pants]
Over here!
- He's alive.
- I'll be dammed.
[Miss Parker]
Daddy, why didn't you tell me about Faith?
I didn't tell you about Faith first because, uh,
I knew she was dying.
After your mother...
I couldn't tell you.
We'd both had enough.
She was my sister?
Her parents were killed.
She became a ward of the state.
Then she was diagnosed
with leukemia.
The doctor said there was, uh,
nothing could be done.
So the state, uh, put her
in a convalescent home...
to die.
How did she end up
at the Centre?
Well, your, uh-
your mother's priest, Father Moore,
told her about the girl.
They went to see her.
Your mother said that might have been
you in the nursing home.
She had to do something;
otherwise, she couldn't live with herself.
So the two of you
adopted her.
Ah. Well, with
Father Moore's help...
we brought her
to the Centre...
where Catherine
could be with her.
We doctored her with an experimental drug
the Centre was developing.
Future treatment proved successful
because of what we had learned from Faith.
She died
shortly after Catherine.
[Sobs]
Miss Parker.
There's some people
who would like to see you.
Miss Parker.
Hi.
- Mr. Parker.
- [Sydney] The nurse called to let us know...
that you'd regained
consciousness.
And I thought
you'd want this.
[Sobs, Giggles]
Thank you both.
Broots.
[Clears Throat]
Guess we'll see you later.
[Cell Phone Rings]
- [Beeps]
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- [Beeps]
What? Jarod?
They found him.
Alive.
[Man]
Jarod.
It's nice to finally
meet you in the flesh.
I'm Father Moore.
But how did you find me?
Well, I was concerned
when you didn't arrive at Butte.
You seemed so anxious to meet
the last time we spoke.
Our mutual friend at the Centre told me
what happened and where I could find you.
- The Centre?
- No. No, no. Relax.
The Centre has no idea where you are
or where we're going.
Thank you-
for helping me.
Catherine Parker would have
wanted it that way.
[Miss Parker]
I'd forgotten how beautiful it is.
- How did you get it?
- An old friend of your mother's.
- Father Moore.
- He found the rosary clutched in Faith's hand.
He knew how much
it meant to your mother...
so he wanted me
to give it to you.
Thank you, Jarod.
Do you ever
think about her?
I think about her
all the time.
- It's ironic too.
- What is?
All those years ago-
you and l-
we went searching for death...
and we found someone
who saved our lives.
I'm sure she was
in that room with me.
And I'm sure she was with me
up on that mountain.
She said she'd always
be watching over us.
She was.
- Are we crazy?
- I don't know exactly what happened.
- But I do know that I'm sure of one thing.
- What?
Love... transcends death.
That the people we love
touch our lives...
even after they're gone.
[Giggling]