- [Chattering, Laughter]
- [Hammering]
[Sydney] It was your grandfather's when
he was in the ranks of the Belgian Infantry.
- It's beautiful, Sydney.
- It said it kept him from losing his way.
- I'm glad to know you have it now.
- [Boy] Nicholas!
Come on!
You promised you'd read to me!
- I have to go. Thanks for the gift, Sydney.
- Oh, Nicholas?
- [Boy] Nicholas! This way!
- Don't call me Sydney. Call me-
- [Line Clicks, Beeps Off]
- Dad.
[Engine Cranking]
Come on. Read to me!
Green Eggs and Ham,
Sam-l-Am.
- What is that?
- It's a compass.
It helps you find your way
when you're lost.
Now, where were we?
Is that your mama?
- Yes.
- Where's your daddy?
[Indistinct Shouts]
[Gunshots]
- All right, back inside!
- [Scattered Shouts]
Stay with your mother.
Leave 'em alone.
They're teachers.
- [Groans]
- Rupert, get this one in the truck!
- Come on, boy!
- Get over there!
Get on in there!
Let's go! Come on!
[Thunder Rumbling]
- [Clicks On]
- [Male Newscaster, Indistinct]
She was known for her successful film career
during the '30s and '40s.
Services will be
held tomorrow at 4.00.
The family has requested that all donations
be made to the Cancer Society...
in the Galveston area
in lieu offlowers.
- Bill?
- In other breaking news, four volunteer teachers...
were kidnapped
in the hills of Appalachia.
The educators were abducted
by a group believed to be members...
- of a violent local militia.
- [Jarod] Nicholas.
The Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco and Firearms
are following all the leads they can.
At this point, they're gravely concerned
for the safety of these hostages.
A bird saturated in crude oil.
I guess afterJarod killed and basted it,
he forgot to put it on the grill.
- Jarod doesn't take life. He's making a statement.
- Save the swallow?
- Somebody call me when
you figure out what it means.
- [Phone Ringing]
- I think it's sad.
- Devastating.
Flush it.
- This is Sydney.
- [Woman] Sydney.
Michelle. Michelle?
- What's wrong?
- Oh, Sydney. They took Nicholas.
- They took him away.
- Who?
- Who took our son?
- They don't know for sure.
They don't-They don't even know
if he's alive, Sydney.
- What are we gonna do, Sydney?
- Michelle.
- We'll get him back.
- Yes.
[Man]
Put her down in the next clearing, Captain.
[Man #2]
Roger that.
[Faint Radio Chatter]
All right, gentlemen. Listen up.
We're gonna pick up the trail
right here where they were abducted...
and hope we all get lucky.
Now this country is
a real throwback in time.
We really don't know what to expect from
the locals, but I do not want another Ruby Ridge-
which is why we brought in
Special AgentJarod Miner.
Miner's a tracking expert in this region
and well-versed in the people.
- He's gonna help us find the teachers.
- And bring them back... alive.
All right, gentlemen. Pick up your equipment,
and let's move out.
[Agents Chattering]
[Man Narrating]
There are Pretenders among us.
[Jarod]
I was taken from my family.
Thirty-six hours and he's already demonstrating
more talent than any of our others.
How many people died
because of what I thought up?
Since I broke out,
I've spent every moment searching for my past.
[Miss Parker]
He's a Pretender-
A genius who can become
anyone that he wants to be.
- The Centre wants him alive.
- Preferably.
[Miss Parker]
He defends the weak and abused.
Life's a gift.
- You a doctor?
- I am today.
[Miss Parker]
What was Nicholas doing there?
He's a volunteer fighting illiteracy.
- Broots, will you cover for me while I'm gone?
- I'll do anything I can, Syd.
- Lyle. What about Lyle?
- Let me worry about Eddie Haskell.
Sydney, don't do anything crazy.
Parker, they took my son!
Hi, I'm Agent Cory with the A.T.F.
- Have you ladies seen anything?
- Mm-mmm.
- No.
- Just tell me what you saw.
- I didn't see nothin'.
Did you see anything?
[Sniffles]
I mean, you must have seen something, right?
Can you tell me anything? Could-
Was it something we said?
They're afraid to talk to us.
- Something has them spooked.
- So "unspook"them.
What the hell is this?
It's the trademark...
of the Appalachian Freedom Militia.
We raided their compound two months ago,
confiscated a stockpile of weapons.
The A.F.M. 's leader
is a man named Eldridge Hailey.
This abduction-
- It was a retaliatory gesture.
- Hailey's even more unstable than his followers.
We're talking about bombings,
church arson, attacking federal officers.
You'd think these locals would
bend over backwards to help us stop these guys.
A rattlesnake- It uses its rattle
to warn its victims when it's going to attack.
What, this is Hailey's threat
if they talk?
They won't put their families in danger-
not for us.
[Snake Rattles]
Green Eggs and Ham, Sam-l-Am.
Hi.
You don't have to be afraid.
My name is Jarod.
Nicholas gave it to me.
- Do you know who this is?
- Nicholas's mama.
Do you know where Nicholas is?
A man took him- took 'em all-
up in the hills.
It helps you find your way
when you get lost.
[Sydney]
There must be something we can do, Agent Swik.
The search party is already in the field.
But there are hundreds of square miles
of mountainous terrain...
where the A.F.M. Could be holding your son.
I want to help with the search, please.
I understand your concern. But until we can
pinpoint the hostages' exact location...
we have to be patient.
I'm sorry. I wish I could do more for you.
Sydney.
Don't worry, Michelle.
We will find our son.
[Sobs]
- Do you think they'll-you know.
- Don't even think that.
Hey, have you ever been to Flannery's?
The coffee shop near campus?
Hey, get back over there.
When we get back on campus,
I'll take you there, I promise.
- [Gun Cocks]
- Now everybody ain't gonna make it, son.
And the ones
that don't listen go first.
So you get over there,
you sit down, and you shut up.
Even though sometimes it feels
like my thumb is still attached...
there is something very streamlined
about a four-fingered hand-
the way the palm flows
seamlessly into the wrist.
It's sleek.
Of course, if you're not thinking,
holding a cup of coffee can be hell.
[Wheezing Chuckle]
Oh. I found Jarod.
He's working at a-
[Clearing Throat]
An oil refinery
near San Juan Capistrano.
That's where the swallows migrate.
Yeah, there was a foreman
who I.D.'d his photo.
And Miss Parker?
- Uh, she's out of the off-
- [Knocking]
Yes?
Excuse me, Mr. Lyle, but it's urgent.
She's out of the office.
- [Paper Rustling]
- Well...
I'm going to Capistrano.
And I want you near your phone
in case I need assistance. Clear?
Oh, yes, sir.
Talk to you soon.
What about Lyle?
He's, um, gone to California.
Dance, puppet, dance.
Please, Miss Parker, don't make me lie
like that again. I think I'm getting an ulcer.
- Try warm milk, shot of bourbon.
- Okay. Right.
What happens when Lyle realizes
that we sent him on a boondoggle?
It doesn't matter as long as Sydney
brings his son home alive.
[Phone Rings]
- Beth Swik.
- [Thunder Rumbling]
- I should be out there looking for him myself.
- Where would you start?
- I have his picture. Someone might have seen him.
- [Phone Rings]
Yeah?
Sydney, we have to be patient.
I have never been able
to help in his life, Michelle.
Now when he needs me,
I'm just sitting here-
patiently!
Come on.
Take a walk with me.
I'm sorry, Michelle.
It's just this helplessness-
I know the feeling...
all too well.
When Nicholas was born,
the doctors discovered a ventricular disorder.
They said that if it wasn't repaired immediately
that he was going to die.
He was only a few days old
when he had the operation.
It was a... five and a half-hour
open-heart surgery.
I sat in the waiting room, all alone...
trying to prepare myself
for the possibility...
that my baby-
of my baby-
[Sighs]
Leaving me.
And now it's all coming back, that feeling
of having to prepare myself all over again.
You shouldn't have
gone through it alone.
You should have called me.
Oh, Sydney.
I disappeared from your life because
the Centre threatened to kill you if I didn't.
It was hard enough
thinking of burying my child...
let alone the love of my life.
- I'm glad you called this time.
- So am I.
[Man]
Sir, pull over.
We're getting a satellite feed
on the remote from Eldridge Hailey.
Patch this through
to A.T.F. Headquarters immediately.
The feed is going through
to headquarters, sir.
There's a satellite feed
coming in from the kidnappers.
[Sydney]
Nicholas is alive, Michelle.
- He's alive.
- Yeah.
To whom it may concern:
If you want to see these
so-called educators again...
you will wire one million dollars
into an offshore bank account.
Hold up the access number.
Now these funds will be
considered as reparations...
for your violation
of our God-given rights...
under the Second, the First
and the Fourth Amendments.
And if I do not receive word
of this transaction by dawn...
further actions will be taken...
as demonstrated.
No.
- Oh, Sydney!
- [Gunshot]
- God Bless America.
- [Static]
[Whimpering]
I'm afraid it's not good, Sydney.
Uh, Eldridge Hailey started
the Appalachian Freedom Militia...
while serving 10 years
for voluntary manslaughter.
His first act after his release
was a bombing that killed 12 people.
He got off on a technicality.
Ever since, it's been extortion,
murder, kidnapping-
- Sydney, what's going on down there?
- We're not even sure if he's-
Listen to me, Sydney.
You have to believe he's alive.
You do whatever it takes
to bring your son home.
- Why are you doing this for me?
- Because you'd do the same.
[Receiver Clatters]
- [Beeping]
- We've got a partial triangulation...
on A.F.M.'s satellite signal.
It's about 12 miles southwest of here,
right in the heart of the national forest.
I suggest that we get within
a few miles on this fire road here...
and then we proceed on foot
to avoid being detected.
Well, we've got
three hours until dawn.
- Let's get it done.
- [Agent] All right.
[Man]
Yes, sir.
- [Thunder Rumbling]
- Okay, we're right on it.
Is that where they are?
Is that where they're holding my son?
I'm not at liberty to discuss those types of specifics.
There are contingency plans-
My son may have been shot,
and you're talking about contingency plans?
- Why don't you tell us where he is?
- I'm doing everything l-
- I got the governor's publicity aide on line two.
- Not now.
- Ma'am, the governor
wants to make a statement-
- Not now!
- [Ringing]
- Get the message?
No more games.
No more.
- Come, Michelle.
- Doctor?
Doctor, where are you going?
[Miss Parker] How will you know
where the kidnappers are, Sydney?
[Sydney] I took the coordinates
from the A. T.F. Office. It's a start.
Parker, I need you
to do something for me.
- What?
- Hailey is demanding a million-dollars' ransom.
Liquidate my assets and wire it
into a designated bank account.
It probably won't be enough,
but maybe he'll take it.
No. Syd, I got a better idea.
- Let the Centre pick up the tab on this one.
- The Centre?
Well, they're responsible
for you not knowing Nicholas.
The least they can do
is pay to get him back.
You think Hailey will keep up
his end of the deal?
I'm going to find him
and make sure he does.
Sydney, you don't want
to take this man on by yourself.
I have spent my whole life standing by
while other people did their jobs-
no matter who it hurt-
without protecting those who needed my help.
Not this time, Parker.
We need to go there.
Miss Parker, Sydney asked us
to stay out of it.
I understand a parent's need to do
whatever it takes to ensure their child's safety.
- But how does Sydney getting
himself killed accomplish that?
- Well, maybe he's not alone.
- Maybe Sydney has help.
- Jarod.
Why do you say that?
Well, before Sydney left,
he-he was at his keyboard.
E-mail toJarod?
Find out.
Kerosene lamps burning in that mine.
They could be anywhere around here.
Recon the area and surround the mine head.
If you see any militia, hold your fire.
We can't risk getting the hostages killed.
- [Van Door Opens]
- What the hell is this?
Hailey!
Hailey, the money's being wired
into your account!
- I've got a shooter by the mine.
- Hailey!
- I just want the hostages!
- Get down!
Hold your fire!
The hostages could be behind him!
All right, cease fire!
Martin, Jones! Get him!
- Nicholas!
- Stay down! Stay there.
- You were told to stay out of sight.
- I couldn't let him die.
Okay, go! Go!
Secure the area.
[Insects Buzzing]
Oh, my God.
We got bodies.
It doesn't make sense.
Three of Hailey's militia men.
Not one took less than
a half a dozen rounds.
And the... hostages?
Tracks indicate that they were
led out before the bloodbath.
Sydney, he's alive...
somewhere.
You called him Sydney.
How did you know his name?
I saw him on a news report.
He's the father of one of the hostages.
His namejust... stuck in my mind.
Lieutenant, we've got Hailey.
[Hailey]
No, don't. Don't! Don't let 'em get me!
Don't let 'em get me. Don't!
Don't let 'em get me! Don't let 'em get me, please!
You gotta protect me.
- From who?
- You gotta-
Hailey! Where is my son?
He's unconscious.
All right, get him stabilized.
Find out everything he knows.
Come on.
We'll find him.
Jarod, thanks for responding
so swiftly to my message.
What message?
[Broots]
Sydney did e-mail Jarod.
"Nicholas has been kidnapped in Appalachia.
Need your help. "
- I can't believe he'd send it from here.
- Meaning?
Meaning if someone put a tracer on it,
then they could easily intercept it.
- When's the last time we heard from Lyle?
- Oh, man.
- What?
- When I was at his office yesterday...
- Willie brought him an urgent memo.
- Did he say what it was?
- No.
- Huh.
Well, Lyle acted like it was nothing.
But he had that look in his eye, you know?
Like he'd just eaten a raw steak.
[Lieutenant]
Immediate medevac extraction.
Three dead, one wounded, all A.F.M.
My guess is that
some rival militia got them.
But the truth is, I have no idea where the hell
the other hostages went to.
We're tryin'to figure that out right now.
Yeah. Yeah, I know that.
I remember that look on your face
when you were young-
when you couldn't find an answer.
It doesn't make any sense.
There's four sets of tracks,
which means an outside group came in...
and ambushed the A.F.M.,
but took the hostages?
- And then they killed the militia.
- Executed them.
Except for Hailey.
He was shot three times...
but in a premeditated way.
As if someone wanted him to survive...
so he could talk.
So he could talk to me.
I've got him now.
Don't try to move.
A medevac unit will be here soon.
Now tell me about the men
who took the hostages.
[Sighs, Mutters]
I never seen 'em before.
I don't want- I don't want to see 'em again.
Speak to me about my son.
Did he get hurt?
Answer me, Hailey!
Did you hurt my son?
No. No, no, l-
I didn't hurt any hostage.
- But he will.
- Who?
The-The man who took 'em.
The one who made me watch
when he did the others and left me to die.
- He's crazy.
- Who is he?
Lyle.
- Oh!
- What?
- Lyle went to the Appalachians.
- Oh!
[Keypad Beeping]
This is Parker.
Get the jet ready.
Wait, what's gonna happen
to Sydney and his son?
For a shot at bringing Jarod back?
I wouldn't put anything past Lyle.
Yes, but... what do you intend to do?
Whatever it takes.
This man with the nine fingers-
Where did he take the hostages?
He took 'em west.
- Why would Lyle do this?
- He's using Nicholas as bait...
to capture me.
Jarod? Talk to me.
You were right.
Hailey said a rival militia group did this.
They're holed up
in a farmhouse in Pine Ridge.
It's about...
five miles due east of here.
- Martin?
- [Martin] We've got it, sir.
McWood, stay with the prisoner.
Jarod, you're with me.
Lieutenant, don't you think
I should stay with the prisoner?
I'm the only one here with medical training
in case... something happens.
All right, but see what else
you can get out of Hailey...
and stay in communication
with me through Base.
- We're out ofhere.
- Why did you lie to them
about where the hostages are?
I couldn't put their lives at risk.
- This is my fight.
- Lyle killed your brother, I know.
But now he's putting my son's life on the line,
which makes it my fight.
Nicholas is caught in the middle.
You stay out of this.
You'll have to shoot me
to keep me out of it.
[Vehicle Doors Closing,
Engines Starting]
[Vehicles Departing]
Hey! Where you goin'?
What about me?
Your wounds are stabilized.
The medevac chopper will be here shortly.
You can't leave me alone!
What kind of lawman are you?
Oh, I'm not really A.T.F.
I was just... pretending.
So what happened to Hailey and his men
after you got us out of the mine?
Oh, nothing too dramatic.
We just... tied 'em up, radioed the A.T.F.
An extraction team will meet us here.
- So what are you? F.B. I?
- Something like that.
Why don't you all go up in the attic...
in case there's more trouble, hmm?
Um, Nicholas?
Would you keep me company?
Why would Lyle want you
to track him this far out?
This trail dead-ends at
an abandoned mine shanty-
no other access-
which means he wants me walking in
without a way of walking out.
- Hmm.
- It's been a long time coming, him and me.
Jarod, do you think revenge...
will put an end
to the pain in your life?
He killed my brother.
[Groans]
That's all right.
Sit down here.
How did I get to this?
A lifetime working for a corporation
that takes my son away from me.
And when my son is back in my life...
they kidnap him.
What does that say about me, huh?
Who am I?
[Groans]
There was a little boy that...
Nicholas was working with.
He asked me to give this to your son.
- He looks just like you.
- [Laughs]
I could see in that little boy's eyes
that Nicholas meant the world to him.
Your son is a good man.
He also gave me this to give to him.
- Was it your father's?
- It was his grandfather's.
I thought Nicholas might
like a piece of his past.
It's important to know who your family is-
who you are.
Give it back to him.
I know, Jarod.
I know how much
you've missed in your life.
Let's go.
Sheriff!
Nothin'.
Hailey must have lied toJarod.
Did he?
Or did Jarod lie to us?
[Grunts Angrily]
We're goin' back.
[Jarod]
Three Sweepers.
- Only three.
- You saw what they were capable of.
The hostages must be
inside the structure.
Jarod, I really appreciate
everything you've done.
- [Grunts]
- I can't risk you getting killed for me.
Forgive me.
Shouldn't the extraction team
be here by now?
There's no accounting for punctuality.
But as the old cliché goes,
"All good things come to those who wait."
How'd you lose your thumb?
[Laughs]
I trusted the wrong people...
and I paid the price.
[Sydney] You haven't even made
a down payment on your debt.
Sydney?
- Are you okay?
- Thanks to Mr. Lyle.
- If it weren't for him, we'd be dead.
- Oh, Nicholas, you flatter me.
Do you two know each other?
[Moans]
Aah.
Base One, it's Jarod. Come in.
[Snapping]
[Grunts]
Sleep tight.
[Jet Engine Whining, Dying Down]
[Man]
Miss Parker. What are you doing here?
Hello, Roy. Take us to Lyle.
- Now!
- Yes, Miss Parker.
[Engine Revving]
Shh. It's okay.
You're safe now. Come on.
Up the creek bed.
Stay low and be quiet.
Move, move.
You seem angry, Sydney.
- You're using Nicholas as a bait to captureJarod.
- Hell, yes!
Two birds, one stone. Victory from
the jaws of defeat. Lemonade from lemons.
You've endangered my son's life.
Endangered? You're not listening.
I saved him from the bad people.
Sydney, Mr. Lyle is the reason I'm safe-
that we're all safe. He's a good man.
[Jarod]
Except for the fact that he's a murderer.
If you're looking
for Willie and the others...
they're a little tied up right now.
Revenge- It's a great equalizer.
Go ahead.
I won't give you another reason
to kill me, Jarod.
Oh, you think I need another reason?
Sydney, take Nicholas and go upstream.
Find the others.
They may need some help.
- I don't understand.
- Your father will explain everything to you.
Now go.
- He's right, Nicholas. Come.
- Who the hell is he?
Someone we need to listen to.
Jarod, you're sure
this is how it has to be?
I'm sure.
- [Phone Ringing]
- This is Martin. Yeah.
- Lieutenant, Base Camp's got
a message for you from Jarod.
- Yeah?
I'm a little curious. How did you know
where the militia was holding them?
The Centre has strange bedfellows...
even among our inbred brethren.
Needless to say, this-
this is not how I had things planned.
Oh, this is exactly how I planned it-
in my mind... every day...
since you killed my brother.
- I never meant to hurt Kyle.
- No.
You wanted to kill me.
Kyle just got in the way.
I told you once:
We can do great things together.
That offer's still on the table.
You think you can bribe me?
Jarod, it's not a bribe.
Mr. Lyle, do you want your last breath
on this planet to be a lie?
Now step to the center of the room.
Now turn around.
Turn... around.
- Drop to your knees.
- Please, Jarod-
On your knees!
So is this how it's gonna be?
An execution without a trial?
- You didn't give my brother a trial.
- I didn't-
- It was self-defense.
- So is this.
Jarod, I know things.
There are things I can tell you...
about your family...
about who you are-
things no one else knows.
If I die,
all those answers die with me.
Just let me walk out ofhere.
[Helicopter Propeller Whirring]
A Centre chopper.
How's that for karma?
- [Gun Clicks]
- Bad.
Ready...
aim-
No, Jarod.
Fire!
[Faint Radio Chatter]
[Man On Radio]
107 Bravo, we copy. Over.
Lyle?
Miss Parker.
- You've been talking toJarod?
- He's here! He went out that door!
What?
Well-
Well, he's not here now.
- Well, find him!
- Another day.
- What?
- Broots picked up a transmission
from an A.T.F. Unit flying in.
But he was right here!
What did he do to you?
Nothing. I had him,
and those idiots outside let him escape.
Whatever you say, Lyle.
But now it's time to go.
No, we can't just go.
Listen to me.
When the A.T.F. Walks in...
we don't have an explanation for anything
that's happened in the last two days.
If we don't go now, the trail leads back to
the Centre, and you know what that would mean.
- [Radio Chatter Continues]
- Could we- Could we go already?
Weird sense of justice, Jarod.
[Man]
I can't believe you found us!
[Chattering]
Get in!
Let's get out of here, Roy.
"I would eat them in a boat.
I would eat them with a"-
- Goat.
- Goat? That's silly.
[Both Laugh]
You made it.
Nicholas.
Michelle.
I've been meaning to return this.
- [Chuckles Softly]
- [Boy] Nicholas, Nicholas.
- Let's read.
- Not so fast.
There's someone I'd like you to meet, Seth.
- This is-
- I'm Sydney, Nicholas's friend.
No, Seth. He's not my friend.
He's my father.
Okay, here we go. "And I will-
- "And I will-
- "eat them in the rain.
- "And in the dark.
- "And on a train.
- "And in a car.
- "And in a tree.
- "They are so good...
so good, you see."
They are so good"- I see.
That's very good, Seth.
Sorry I couldn't stick around
to say good-bye.
[Sydney] Jarod, I don't know how
to thank you for everything you did...
and- [Chuckles]
I'm sorry I hit you.
It's okay.
Maybe it knocked a little sense into me.
- Where's Nicholas now?
- Back with his students.
- He's invited his mother and me
to come down to visit again.
- That's nice.
I mean, that will be really nice...
for your family.
We're hardly a family.
Boy barely knows me.
He knows-
He knows you love him.
You love...
him.