Previously on...
sounds to me as if someone's
let go of his rage.
Maybe i have.
Well, i haven't.
Felicia took matters
into her own hands.
You want me to call off
the weddin i'll do it.
I'll do whatever you want.
Karl put the ball
in susan's court...
with your d.u.i. Charge,
it could get ugly.
While andrew tried
to take bree to court...
(carlos) there's a father.
He's a kid!
Gabrielle and carlos
took the baby...
the papers aren't valid anymore.
Do y really wanna leave
this beautiful little girl
with that
white trash freak show?
And ran with it.
(mary alice) louispate
believed in the power of shame.
As a teacher,
she had found that the best way
to control unruly students
was to instill
a strong sense of shame...
in their parents.
I left trisha alone
with the school hamster
for only five minutes.
In this box
is all that's left of patches.
For show and tell, timmy decided
to bring in something
from your husband's collection
of nazi memorabilia.
Billy's been threatening
to beat up the other kids
for their milk money.
We found the proceeds
in his cubby.
Of course,
mrs. Pate also knew
when it came
to unruly children,
some parents had more reason
to be ashamed...
than others.
So, um... your message said
that parker had been involved
in some sort
of serious incident.
What... what kind
of incident?
Yesterday afternoon,
parker offered a cookie
to cindy lou peeples
if she would
show him her vagina.
What kind of cookie?
What does that matter?
Oh, it doesn't.
I'm just stalling because
i am completely mortified.
The kids were in a broom closet.
Our janitor walked in on them
just as cindy
was lifting up her pinafore.
Oh, my goodness.
I'm sure you've noticed
how obsessive parker can be.
A certain subject
will catch his interest,
and that's all he'll talk about
for weeks and weeks.
Oh, right.
That happened with dinosaurs.
Oh, yes, we all remember
his dinosaur phase.
More fondly now than ever.
Mm-hmm, so you think
that now he's obsessed with...
what's underneath
the pinafore. Yes.
Look, i think
he's just developed
a normal curiosity
about the human body.
You need to talk to him.
Remind him what's appropriate
and what isn't.
Of course.
I will talk to him.
I'll talk to him
till i'm blue in the face.
I promise. Take care.
Yes, louisa pate believed
in the power of shame.
She always believed,
when someone has that power...
so, mrs. Peeples,
you'll never guess
what your daughter is willing
to do for a gingersnap.
It's a shame not to use it.
Cync by xxy
www.1000fr.com
It had been six weeks
since andrew van de kamp
had declared war
on his mother bree.
The final battle
was about to be waged
at the fairview county
courthouse.
Bree knew
it was about to get bloody.
What she didn't know was...
the calvary
was on its way...
bree?
Whether she wanted them there
or not.
Eleanor!
Oh, thank god i found you.
This place is a maze.
What are you doing here?
Well, your father and i got
a call last night from danielle,
and she said that andrew
was taking you to court.
(scoffs) i mean,
to say that we were shocked
would be an understatement.
Hello, i'm eleanor mason,
bree's stepmother.
You're the lawyer?
We should talk.
Uh, no,
i'm not her lawyer.
Good.
The hair had me worried.
Peter is mom's sponsor
from a.a.
Oh, sweetie! (chuckles)
Since when are you
in a.a.?
It's a recent development.
Where's dad?
In chambers with the judge.
What?! Why?
Everything is fine.
The judge agreed
to a postponement.
Oh, thank god!
Luckily, he remembered me.
I spoke once at his law school.
Pardon me, sir,
i'm your daughter's lawyer.
Just so you know,
we've been waiting
for this hearing for weeks,
son, i've been an attorney
for 45 years.
You and i both know
how these cases can
turn into public spectacles.
Our family is perfectly capae
of handling this in house.
Dad, you don't understand.
This has gotten really ugly.
That's why we're here.
We're gonna put this family
back together.
Whatever it takes.
(beale) and that's
when mr. And mrs. Solis,
fearing for the welfare
of this helpless child,
fled the hospital.
You mean,
they kidnapped her.
Well,
technically, that's true,
but given the situation
that led up to the rescue...
kidnapping.
Your honor,
yes, in retrospect,
the plan was a little bit rash,
not entirely well thought out.
Idiotic.
(whispers)
Can we object to that?
Shh!
But the child is safe,
your honor.
And all we ask the court
is to allow baby lily
a lifetime
of the care and love
she has been receiving
from the solises.
As much as your story
tugs at my heart,
there is the issue
of parental rights.
What does the state
have to say about this?
We have located
the biological father...
mr. Dale helm.
Unfortunately, uh, circumstanceses
require that he be out of town.
He's in fort lauderdale today.
On business?
Spring break, actually.
Mr. Helm is
a high school student.
Charming. In between keg stands,
did the father happen to mention
if he plans
to waive parental rights?
I've left
a number of voice mails,
but the only response
i've gotten is a text message
that says this "blows his mind"
and he's extremely "bummed out."
All right...
mr. And mrs. Solis,
since you actually want lily,
it seems you're
the lesser of two evils.
I'm granting you
temporary custody
until we can get a straight
answer from the birth father.
Thank you,
uh, your honor.
In the meantime, try not
to steal any more babies.
Oh, we just needed the one.
(chuckles)
Sweetie?
Um, could you put
the crayons down for a second?
We need to talk.
So i spoke
to your teacher today,
and she told me
about the...
cookie deal
you made with cindy lou.
Oh. Are you mad?
(chuckles) no, not exactly.
I'm just...
i'm trying to understand
why you...
did that.
Tommy keenan told me
babies come from down there.
It doesn't
sound right to me.
Well...
actually, he's kinda right.
He's got the concept down.
That's weird.
How's a by get in there?
Daddy will be home from
his business trip in a few days.
Why don't you
wait for him?
Okay.
Or i can ask
tommy's brother.
He's 14,
and he knows everything.
And then
the mommy and the daddy,
because they love each other
so much,
they hug.
Real tight.
And, uh, a seed
is magically implanted.
(clucks)
And nine months later...
a baby is born. Here.
What kind of seed?
Oh, that's not important.
I don't believe you.
Parker, i'm your mother.
Mothers don't lie to their sons.
Now go wash your hands
or santa's not gonna bring you
anything for christmas.
I just saw edie drive off.
How long is she gonna be gone?
I don't know.
She just went to show a house.
Move.
What's the problem?
You mauled me
in edie's bed last night.
I think that deserves
a conversation.
Well, what's there to talk
about? I'm just a fool in love.
Oh, no!
You don't mean that.
Yes, i do. Look, i realize
my timing's a little off.
(scoffs) a little?
Ugh... the helium hasn't even
gone out of the balloons
from your engagement party.
(sighs) okay...
when are you gonna tell edie?
Tell her what?
That the wedding's off.
Is it?
Well, isn't it?
It's up to you.
Are... are you saying...
that you're gonna
go through with this wedding...
unless i tell you not to?
Just give me a commitment,
susie q.,
and i'll put a bullet
in edie.
This is insane!
Come on.
All this
can be yours again.
Ju say the word...
and i let go.
Oh, no!
No, don't you dare!
You know you want me to.
Just say it, susie q.
You're...
sick!
(chuckling)
Zach,
i'm going to the drugstore.
I'll be back in 20 minutes.
Oh!
Paul?!
I was making cookies, and i
heard the most sickening thud.
Are you okay?
There's...
shortening on my doorstep.
Shortening?
That's the last thing
you'd want on your front porch.
It's meant for baking.
it was
my grandmother's name.
So how you holding up?
You must be exhausted.
You know, i'm a little tired,
but it's not too bad.
Oh, wait a couple months.
She'll start
sleeping through the night.
Oh, honey, please.
Do i look like a masochist?
Firs thing tomorrow, i'm hiring
a nanny and a night nurse.
No, we're not.
(laughs)
My husband, the comedian.
I'm serious. I don't want
some stranger raising our baby.
Well, you guys are busy.
We should go.
Mm-hmm.
No, it's okay.
I'll win this battle later.
We are not gonna be
some yuppie couple
pawning off our kid on other
people. End of discussion.
Yeah, you should go.
Yeah.
Okay, bye.
Good luck.
Put down the burrito.
What is all this crap
about me not getting help?
Look, a brand-new baby
needs to bond with its mother.
The church knows it, science
knows it, nature knows it.
We have the money. What is wrong
with getting a little help?
Then i'll be able
to relax once in a while,
and i'll be able
to be a better mother.
You wanna be
a better mother?
Do what my mam* did...
make sacrifices.
My mam* worked her fingers
to the bone for me.
And that's what put her
in an early grave!
Well, that
and the hit-and-run thing.
Look, i don't know why
you want to be emancipated,
and i don't know what you've
been doing to drive him crazy.
Bottom line... it's over.
It's now time for you two
to kiss and make up.
And just how
are we supposed to do that?
Here's a thought...
just look each other
in the eye and say,
"i forgive you."
(laughs)
That's your solution?
It's actually
a technique invent
by this dutch therapist.
I saw him on tv.
He says,
if you verbalize forgiveness,
the brain can trick the heart
into letting go of resentment.
It really works.
I did it
with our cleaning lady.
Um, i'm sorry, dad, but i think
my relationship with andrew
is just a bit more complicated
than...
would it kill you
to at least try?
I'll do it...
for you, grandpa.
That's my boy. Bree?
Fine!
Yes, um...
so, um, who goes first?
Either or.
Doesn't matter.
Mom, i forgive you.
Andrew, i forgive you.
That wasn't so hard, was it?
Now don't expect
to feel differently right away.
It takes a while.
It took me a week
to forgive esperanza.
But now
she's like family again.
Family who stole from us.
So let's get back
to the waye were,
and forget all this nonsense
about emancipation.
Um...
well, grandpa, i'm... i'm still
gonna need my trust fund.
You see,
l-i can't live in a place
where i...
i don't feel safe.
What are you talking about?
Well, could you live
with a woman who hits you?
Bree!
I slapped him once,
and he deserved it.
Well, i just asked her
to stop drinking.
You were drinking?
She's in a.a.
Her sponsor has long hair.
Andrew,
i find your concern ironic,
given how tanked you were
when you ran or
our neighbor's mother
with your car.
Is she okay?
She's dead!
Well...
mom watched as her boyfriend
committed suicide.
And he was the same guy
who killed dad!
Andrew falsely accused me
of molestation...
in a mall!
You know,
the technique works best
if you don't talk right away.
Okay, let's go. I don't wanna
be late for the movie.
Oh, those are pretty.
Who sent those?
What?
"Say the word and i'm yours.
Love, karl."
Mom, i knew
this would happen
when you started
hanging around together,
all of your old feelings
resurfacing.
No, his feelings.
He's the one
with the feelings, not me.
Uh-huh.
Okay, don't "uh-huh" me. You're
not old enough to do that.
Oh, no?
Well, how do you like this...
i'm not gonna go
to the movies with you.
You're gonna make me
go by myself?
Well, you could always
ask dad to go.
In fact,
if you love him so much,
why don't you marry him?
Oh, wait, you already did.
Twice.
(sighs)
(indistinct conversations)
(woman) hey, carol,
come on. Sit with us.
Oh, you know what?
I think we're gonna need
some napkins with this.
Oh, okay, i'll go back.
Thanks.
My ex-boyfriend's here.
If he sees me alone, i'll die.
I'm begging you, please,
act like you know me.
Susan? Hey!
Mike, hi! (chuckles)
What a surprise.
How are ya?
Good.
Oh!
God, l... i'm being so rude.
Um, mike,
l-i want you to meet...
orson hodge.
Nice to meet you, mike.
Wow, i can't believe
i'm finally seeing
the man himself in the flesh.
So... how'd you two meet?
Oh, god, i've been
her dentist for years.
(susan chuckles)
But last week,
i was looking in her mouth
and decided
to stick my tongue in it.
I'll see ya, susan.
Thank you so much
for helping me out.
Hey,
i'm great in a crisis.
Well, i definitely picked
the right person to sit next to.
Actually,
is this seat taken?
No.
Okay, you can share
my popcorn.
Um, susan...
this is becky.
I'll probably be sharing
her popcorn.
I'll just wait
till the lights go out,
and then i'll...
while i get this going,
can you bring out the buns?
Uh, yeah.
(whoosh)
What the hell?
You all right?
This isn't lighter fluid.
It's gasoline.
What?
How'd that get in there?
How do you think?
Something smells good
over there.
Well, i don't understand.
Is she trying to kill you?
No, she's trying
to piss me off.
Why?
I'm not sure yet,
but i do know
i'm not gonna play along.
We got plenty of burgers
if you want to pop over.
And bring your appetite.
Gaby, the baby.
No, i got up twice already.
It's your turn.
Gaby, i have several
job interviews tomorrow.
I need my sleep.
What about my sleep?
You sleep
when the baby sleeps.
Every 40 minutes?
When am i supposed
to have a life?
What are you whining about?
You know, xiao-mel does
all the housework around here.
All you have to do
is take care of the baby.
Fine, fine, fine!
Psst!
(whispers) xiao-mei.
Psst, wake up.
Mrs. Solis?
Something wrong?
(normal voice)
The baby won't stop crying,
and i haven't slept
for two days.
Will you please
take lily for a while?
Uh...
oh, come on. I won't make you
do windows tomorrow.
Okay. What do i do?
Well, she's a baby.
You hold her.
You bounce her
and, i don't know,
maybe sing a little something.
Ahh.
Oh, and xiao-mei,
mr. Solis does not need
to know about this, okay?
Okay.
(singing in chinese)
Yeah, honey, can you
take that downstairs?
Thank you.
Eleanor,
i thought you'd gone to bed.
Oh, no, not yet.
I had to do my hair now.
There's never enough time
in the morning.
Uh, sit.
There's something
i have to discuss with you.
Your father and i
have decided to take andrew
back to rhode island
with us.
Really?
And whose idea was that?
Andrew's.
But henry and i feel
it's the right thing to do.
Absolutely not.
If we leave him here,
the two of you
will wind up in court,
and i'm not
going to all that.
Do you really think
that i am enjong airing
my dirty laundry in public?
This whole sittion
is mortifying.
But i can't back down
because he is my son,
and i need more timeto get th
you never give up.
I've always admired that
about you.
When you were a kid,
you used to make
these peanut butter cookies
that were god-awful.
But you kept baking them,
and you kept forcing everyone
to eat them.
(chuckles)
You were so determined
to get them right.
My mother didn't think
they were awful.
When i made those same cookies
for her, she loved them.
Well, some people
praise children
even when
they don't deserve it.
Oh, but not you.
With you, i had to work for
every kind word i ever got.
Well, you always resented me
because of my high standards.
No.
I resented you
because those were kick-ass
peanut butter cookies.
We're taking andrew.
Eleanor, please...
he hates you, bree.
Your own son.
You know,
part of being an adult
is admitting
that you've failed,
and then moving on...
with grace.
Do you really think that i am
a failure as a parent?
(sighs) well, i'd love to lie
and say something supportive,
but as you pointed out,
that was more
your mother's thing.
Xiao-mei?
So sorry.
I just take break.
Oh, no, xiao-mei,
that's okay. That's okay.
I know you were up all night
with the baby,
and i really
appreciate it.
You know,
i'm very grateful
for everything
you've been doing for lily.
So to thank you, i bought you
a gift certificate to my spa.
And you can take a whole day off
and just really pamper yourself.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Thank you!
Oh, thank you!
Oh, you're welcome.
All right, lily needs
to be bathed and put to bed.
I don't wanna miss
my yoga class. Hi.
Hi, pretty girl.
Oh, yes, mommy has to go.
Mommy has to go,
so she can stay pretty and thin
and you can be proud of her.
(chuckles)
Motherhood
is such a blessing.
I hopeou get
to experience it one day.
(front door opens, shuts)
(andrew) because
it's not a big deal!
(justin)
"It's not a big deal"? Okay!
It's not that far away.
Right. Oh, it's not
that far away?
Dude, it...
whatever, okay?
You didn't even care
to tell me before?
Bye.
(sighs)
Justin, what happened?
Andrew just told me he's
moving in with his grandparents.
They live so far away,
i'm never gonna
see him anymore.
I'm so sorry. I know
that you're good friends.
We're more than friends,
mrs. Van de kamp.
I love him.
Oh.
Why?
Yes.
I'd be curious to know
just what it is
you see in him.
Well, when my parents
first heard i was gay,
they kicked me out.
They said i had debased
the entire family
and that they couldn't
love me anymore
until i changed.
But andrew... he said that
i should be ashamed of them,
'cause they were too stupid
to know how great i was.
That's the thing
about andrew.
He doesn't take crap
from anyone.
How can you not
love someone like that?
You know,
it never ceases to amaze me
how people can turn their backs
on their own family.
I mean... but it happens
every day, doesn't it?
I guess.
You know, justin, if you
would be willing to help,
i'm pretty sure
that i could find a way
to keep andrew from moving.
What do you say?
I'm home.
Oh, hi.
Hey, mrs. Mccluskey.
So how did everything go?
Fine. Penny fussed a bit.
I think her molars
are coming in.
Oh.
And the twins
fought over the remote.
There's nothing new there.
No. (chuckles)
Here's the big news...
parker offered me a fudgsicle
if i would show him my vagina.
Oh, good god, lynette, relax.
I didn't do it.
I just got this
out of the freezer a second ago.
Uh, yeah. Of course.
No, sorry.
Apparently, parker wanted to put
a sunflower seed inside me
and see if a baby would grow.
Where do kids get this stuff?
Oh... that was me.
He was asking about
the birds and the bees,
and i fudged
a few of the details.
Well,
he's only 7 years old.
I don't think he needs
to know everything yet.
I don't wanna rob him
of his innocence.
Well, now,
that's where you're wrong.
You get 'em
when they're young.
Give them
all the gory details.
And then when they're good
and disgusted, you shame 'em.
Excuse me?
You tell them
sex is dirty and wrong
and he shouldn't
talk about it,
and if he does,
he's going straight to hell.
(laughing)
That is ridiculous.
Spoken like
a true liberal idiot.
No, i'm not
gonna shame my son.
Mm, i'm telling ya,
it works.
It keeps people
in their place,
it keeps parents
from being humiliated,
and it keeps me from
having to spend the afternoon
talking about my woo-woo.
In your haste to duck out before
the credits rolled, you...
oh, my god!
Oh, thank you so much.
I stuck a card in there,
just in case you ever wanted
to purposely sit next to me
at a movie, so...
orson, i'm flattered.
Uh, really.
(sighs) you...
you don't wanna date me.
L-i mean, my love life is just
so complicated right now.
Well... no, i won't bore you
with the details.
So the ex-boyfriend has no idea
you're secretly married
to the ex-husband,
who still loves you,
but unless you give him
a reason not to,
is gonna marry
the neighborhood slut?
Did i call edie a slut?
Mm-hmm.
Well, that's overstating it.
Edie's not a slut.
She's just... popular
with indiscriminate men.
Anyway... yes, those are
the relevant players.
Okay.
Now i'm absolutely
horrified
that i'm about to say
what i'm about to say,
but there's nobody else i can
talk to who won't judge me.
And since
you're a complete stranger,
i'll probably
never see you again
unless i randomly
run into you on the street,
in which case, you'll ignore me
'cau you know how crazy i am.
So here goes...
i'm having feelings
for karl again.
(sighs) does that make me
a terrible person?
You want
my unvarnished opinion?
Lay it on me.
It doesn't make you
a terrible person,
but it does make you a...
well... a sucker.
This karl's a coward.
He wants you to be the heavy
and take all the responsibility.
If you're having feelings
for a guy like that,
i say run...
far, far away.
He lives three houses down.
Hmm.
Well, good luck to you, then.
But like i said, if you're
interested in a tooth whitening,
my card's
still in your wallet.
Xiao-mei?
I'm late to meet
mrs. Van de kamp.
I'll be back
in a little while.
(indistinct conversations)
Bree...
i'm so sorry i'm late.
Oh, honey,
it's all right.
I mean,
with the new baby at home,
i'm surprised
you made it at all.
Ooh, i'll have a drink.
Anything with an umbrella.
So tell me,
how are you doing?
I mean, your entire world
must be turned upside down.
You must be exhausted.
You know, it's been challenging,
but l-i soldier on. (chuckles)
So what about you?
You look so rested.
I just got a massage
at misty spring.
Things have been
a little tense at home,
and i needed an hour
to relax.
Good for you.
I love that spa.
Mm. Um, oh, by the way,
while i was there,
i saw your, uh,
your housekeeper.
Xiao-mei?
Oh, no,
you must be mistaken.
I just left r.
She's at home working.
Are you sure? I was talking
to her in the steam room
for about 20 minutes.
What?
Yeah, apparently you gave her
a gift certificate.
Lily?
Lily, mommy's coming!
Oh, thank god!
Oh, honey, i'm so sorry.
I'm never gonna
leave you again. Oh!
Yes. Yes.
I'm home!
My interview got canceled.
(cooing)
Oh, that's my little girl.
Your chakra lining up nice
for mommy?
That's my girl.
(chuckles) hey,
let me take her off your chest
so you can do your yoga.
No! No, no, no.
We're doing just fine.
Aren't we, lily?
(playing rock version
of "hava nagila")
Bridezilla's got me
auditioning wedding bands,
and i'm clueless about
edie's taste in music.
What do you think
of these guys?
That's why
you brought me down here?
Mm-hmm.
Karl, you made it sound like
it was an emergency.
It is! I need to have somebody
to dance with so i can see
if these guys have the power
to help me get my groove on.
Karl...
uh-oh!
Oh, that's right.
You like it laid-back
and romantic, don't you?
Guys, can we play
something mellow?
No, don't bother,
'cause i'm going.
(drumstick clicks)
(man) two...
that was not
a coincidence.
This was playing
the night we first kissed.
I remember.
I also remember that
you are planning
on marrying someone else.
Not if you don't
want me to.
Come on, susie q.
I can see you still
have feelings for me,
and i know i have
never stopped loving you.
Okay, you want the truth?
I don't know
how i feel about you,
but i keep looking at you,
trying to see if you've changed,
if you've grown up.
You know what i see?
I see the same weak coward
that walked out on me
three years ago.
Of course i've changed.
I don't think so.
so i think you should
probably stay with edie.
and the band is good.
You should hire 'em.
What the hell?
For god's sakes...
what the hell
are you doing in there?!
This is my house.
What are you doing?
We're tenting for termites.
We got a work order.
Signed by who?
Paul...
i've never been so embarrassed
in my whole life.
They're supposed
to be tenting my house.
I must've written
the address down wrong.
(haltingly) muchachos,
mi casa est* aqu^.
You've taken it too far
this time.
These little mind games
are gonna stopop right now!
(lowers voice) and if
they don't, whatcha gonna do?
Blow out your brains
like your wife did?
(man) hey, hey!
Hey, you okay?
Did you hear that?
He assaulted me
for an honest mistake.
God knows what would've happened
if you hadn't been here.
Let go!
Dad, dad, dad.
Come on.
Come on, okay?
I talked to mrs. Mccluskey,
and for god's sakes, parker,
you can'task people
things like that.
Why?
Because...
it's rude.
I said "please."
Well, that doesn't matter!
You gotta quit talking
to people about their bodies,
and about where, you know,
babies come from.
Why?
Because it's not
an appropriate subject.
Why?
Because it's not.
Ugh!
Because it's dirty and wrong,
and i'll wash your mouth out
with soap! That's why.
In that moment,
lynette saw a look
on her son's face
she had never seen before...
and she thought of the look
he had on his face
when he had become obsessed
with dinosaurs...
obsessed with baseball
and obsessed with trains.
And it occurred to lynette
she didn't need
to shame her son.
All he needed was
a brand-new obsession.
But i thought you said
we couldn't have a puppy.
Well... it turns out
we really needed one.
You can go and play.
And though she didn't know it
at the time,
it would be another three years
before parker scavo would
ever ask about sex again.
Karl. What's going on?
Uh, i'm on my way
to a motel.
L-i just wanted to let you know
that the wedding is off.
It is?
I told edie
i wasn't in love with her...
at least, not in the way
that she deserves.
Wow.
Why did you change
your mind?
I mean, i hope it wasn't because
of me, because i told you...
it wasn't for you.
No?
You were right.
I have been a coward.
I was a coward three years ago
when i walked out
on the two most important people
in my life.
And i was being a coward
with edie.
(chuckles) i mean,
to even consider marrying her
when i know what real passion
and real love feels like.
Anyway, l-l-i just thought
i'd let you know.
Karl...
you look pretty beat up.
Why... why don't you...
why don't you come in and...
we'll crack open
a bottle of wine.
Come on.
All right, here we go.
This is the last
of andrew's things.
Once we tape up these boxes,
we can start loading the car.
I'm proud of you, bree.
You're being awfully big
about this.
Well, i have to admit,
i was a bit upset at first.
But then it hit me.
You're his grandparents.
You should bond,
get to know the real andrew.
(gasps)
Oh, dad,
l-i forgot to warn you.
These are some
of andrew's adult videos.
I don't approve,
but boys will be boys.
Oh, henry,
stop looking at that filth.
I don't get it.
Where are the women?
What are you talking about?
This is all just a bunch of...
naked men.
Sweet mother of god.
What the hell are they doing?
I don't know, and i don't
even know what i'm looking at.
Henry, this is pornography
for ho-homosexuals.
Oh, shoot! I wish you
hadn't gone through that.
Now we have to have
an unpleasant conversation,
and we were having
such a nice time.
Bree, is...
is andrew... gay?
Oh, dad, andrew hates labels.
I'm sure it's just a phase.
Excuse me,
but he has a magaze titled
"leather daddies in love."
That does not sound like
a phase to me.
Maybe not, but it's no longer
my concern
now that he'll be living
with you.
We have to have
a serious talk.
Let's don't freak out
about this.
The dutch therapist says...
forget the dutch therapist!
In the kitchen!
(eleanor) now!
Hey,
where's grandma and grandpa?
I need to start
loading up my stuff.
Oh, they, uh,
they already left.
Wait... they left?
Without me?
Uh, yeah,
they wrote you a letter.
It seems they came across
some personal items of yours
that, um, upset them.
They're taking away
my trust fund?
They can't do that!
Well, actually they can.
I mean, it's their money to
dispense with as they see fit.
I know
it doesn't seem fair, but...
no, it's really unfair.
In fact, it sucks.
What... what am i supposed
to do now?
Well, now that you can't afford
to become emancipated,
i guess you're gonna
have to stay here with me.
Andrew,
we can make this work.
We just have
to let go of our anger.
No.
Oh, i, um, had a chance
to have a nice chat
with justin the other day.
He really seems very sweet.
I've invited him over
for dinner tonight.
I hope you don't mind.
Now i wish i hadn't
torched our wedding photos.
(chuckles)
Who would've thought,
after everything
that's happened,
that we would've
ended up back here again?
It's been
one hell of a ride, huh?
Yeah.
(sighs)
So how do you feel now?
About us?
Mm.
I feel good. (giggles)
I feel happy.
You're not having
second thoughts?
I can't believe you actually
want to talk about feelings.
You really have changed.
Hey, this is the new karl,
baby.
He's not afraid to cry.
(chuckles)
(telephone rings)
Hello?
(sighs)
Oh, hi, edie.
Uh... yeah, he's here.
Hold on.
(whispering) how does
she know you're here?
(whispers) i don't know.
(normal voice) hi. Ahem.
Yeah, i just came by to help
julie with her civics homework.
Uh-huh.
Okay, i'll take care of it.
What kind of juice do you want?
Right. Bye, bye.
Are you getting juice
for her?
Yeah, just one carton.
You ripped
the woman's heart out.
Why would she want juice
from you?
Okay. (clears throat)
Now don't freak out,
but this breakup is
sort of a work in progress.
She doesn't know?
Will you calm down?
I can explain.
So if edie doesn't know,
then that means
that you just cheated
on her... with me!
You made me the other woman!
Please don't be angry.
I tried to break up with her,
but because i wasn't sure
you wanted me back,
the words just wouldn't
come out of my mouth.
Now that i kw that
you want me and love me again,
it's a done deal.
(susan) get out of my house,
you miserable son of a bitch!
(karl)
Can't we talk about this?
No, just get out!
Get out!
Susie, susie!
Our marriage was garbage!
Stupid, disgusting
pile of garbage!
No, no, don't say that.
And i regret everything
that came of it!
Don't do this right now.
Ugh! Except you, honey.
You're my rock.
Ooh, out! Get out!
I...
ugh!
I promise you i'm gonna break up
th edie and make this right.
I'll call you
when it's done.
Don't bother!
I won't pick up.
(door slams)
We've all done something
in our lives we're ashamed of.
Some of us have fallen
for the wrong man.
Some have let go
of the right woman.
There are those who have
humiliated their parents...
and those who have failed
their children.
Yes,
we've all made mistakes that
diminish us and those we love.
But there is redemption
if we try to learn from
those mistakes... and grow.
Cync by xxy
www.1000fr.com