previously on "desperate housewives"...
why on earth would you let
them finger paintbefore breakfast?
It's my job to clean
that up,so it's my call
Some households reversed roles
Let's give thisanother shot
Some old flames...
- you want me back?
- Yeah
Were put out
It has to be
somethingyou're ingesting
Who prepares your meals?
I understand you've
been havingsome marital problems
And while some learn to forgive...
deirdre got pregnantbefore
I went to jail
Zach is your son,isn't he?
Yep
Others could not bring
themselves to forget their past
The remarkable thing about danny farrell
was that he had only
been a paperboy for six months
and in that time,he had become the
enemy of every woman on wisteria lane
If there was a puddle
on someone's property...
he found it
If a new rosebush
had just been planted...
he destroyed it
If a cat was enjoying
a moment in the sun...
he ended it
People wondered if
danny would ever change
They should have talked to susan mayer
She could have told them...
obnoxious boys tend
to become obnoxious men
just like the one...
she had been married to
Hey!
Carl,I see you
Just stop right there
Hey,susie Q.
What are you doing?
I'm justgettin' the paper
That's edie's paper
and this is edie's house
Do we have to do this now?
I haven't had my coffee yet
Did you spend the nightwith edie?
Oh,my god
Susie,just calm down
You are forbiddenfrom ever seeing
her again.Do you hear me?Forbidden!
We're divorced
You can'ttell me who I can date
I live on this street
Yourdaughter lives on this street
I will not have you
flauntingyour sexcapades in front of us
- Sexcapades?
- Forbidden
I would love to continue this
but it's time for breakfast
and edie is making mea frittata
Oh! Well,I just bet she is
Mrs. Mayer,I gotta talk to you
Oh,now is not a good time,danny
You're a month behindin your payments
I'll take care of it,I promise
My dad says
if you readsomething and don't pay for it
that's the same as stealing
Hi,ida
Can we talkabout this later?
I just found out
my exis dating my neighbor
and I'm really ticked off
Save it!I provide you a service
and I deserve to be paidfor that service
Yes,the women of wisteria lane
believe danny farrell to be the enemy
Deadbeat!
they also believed the
enemy of my enemy is my friend
-=伊甸园论坛 http://www.ydy.com/bbs=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=COSL-YTET小组工作室=-
sync:YTET-ronald
Beautiful lawns...
spacious homes...
happy families...
these are the hallmarks of suburbia
but if you look beneath
the veneer of gracious living
you will see a battle raging...
a battle for control
You see the combatants everywhere...
engaged in their routine skirmishes...
Fighting fiercely to have
dominion over the world around them
all the while knowing...
it's a battle they will lose
Oh,hey,honey,just stick that anywhere
I'll take care of it
It's really pilin' up
Oh,don't worry
I have a system
Really?
Yeah,every two days,I clean
Two days
Yeah,I let the mess
accumulate for two days
and then I clean until it's sparkling
and then the cycle starts all over again
And why...
have I never seen the sparkling part?
Well,because by the time
you get home from work
the boys have
messed everything up again
See? That's what I would
call a flaw in the system
What are you doin'?
I think I'm asking
you to clean the house
Really?'Cause it sounds
to me like you're criticizing me
No
No,no,no,no. No
I'm not saying
it has to be sparkling
How many times did I come home to
a mess and I never said a word?
Please,don't take
this the wrong way
I think you are
doing a terrific job
but let's be clear
When you came home,it was to clutter
I mean,come on,this is...
more than that
Look at him,just chatting away
So inconsiderate
Phyllis,we've only been
waiting here for two minutes
I told you when we left
the house that I needed to eat
I have low blood sugar
Do you wanna see me keel over?
No... in theory
Here you are
Thank you
By the way
mrs.Van de kamp
I heard about
your husband's passing
I'm so sorry.Dr.Van de kamp was
one of my favorite customers,truly
That's very sweet of you
Thank you
I'm not just being polite
Mrs. Van de kamp
How are you feeling?
Well,mr. Pashmutti...
we're holding up as best
we can under the circumstances
I'm sorry
This is rex's mother,phyllis
I'm so sorry about your son
Thank you.You know
the hardest thing is to lose a child
I can't even imagine
Come on,phyllis
Let's get you something to eat
We had no warning
I was doing dishes when I got the call
Really?
Phyllis,there are
people waiting,so come on
Excuse me.I--I'm so sorry
but my son just passed away
Oh,I'm so sorry
Thank you.I mean I was telling
Mr.Pashmutti here my life is--is over
my life is over
This is ridiculous
you know that?
Pen
Don't you think I have better things
to do than to bring you checks every day
checks that I could
be signing at home?
This one's dry
You know,taking away my access
to our account,that's just vindictive
Thank you
Do you knowhow long it takes me
to schlep out hereto this hellhole?
Exactly. It's the only way
I can guarantee you'll come and visit me
That's ridiculous.You're my husband. I love you
Obviously,I would come visit
I thought it was obviousthat when
you love someone you wouldn't have an affair
I was wrong,wasn't I?
I'm getting really tiredof this song,carlos
Isn't it about timeyou forgave me?
You want my forgiveness,you got it. My trust...
that you're gonnahave to earn
Be careful,carlos
Up until now I've been really
lonelyin that big bed of ours
but when you're rude to me
itmakes me wanna be not so lonely
Comments like thatare exactly why
you'll never againhave access to my money
Why are all rich men jerks?
The same reasonall beautiful women are bitches
So same time tomorrow?
Sure,baby
What do you mean,you know?
I mean,I know
What are you saying
that your father actually told you
he was gonna be having a
onenight stand with edie britt?
Uh,mom,this wasn'ta one night stand
He's been going out with
Mrs. Britt for a few months now
What?
How could you not
tell me that?We share everything
That's what we're known for
That's our thing
Because I knew you'd wig out
Besides,haven't you always told
me to respect people's privacy?
Oh,I've neverapplied that concept
to your father's sex life and you know it
Are you done?
No! I have not even
begunripping into edie britt yet
Oh,that peroxide vulture
I just know as sureas I am standing here
that she went after your
fatherjust to tick me off
- Wrong again
- What?
He asked her out
You lie
It's true.He called her
for a datesix months ago
the day aftermy birthday party
The one at the piano bar?
Yeah
What is it?
Oh,your fatherjust came over
that day and told me some stuff
You know,some stuffthat
I haven'T...and can't tell you
Wait. Whatever happened
to"we share everything"?
Isn't that our thing
what we're known for?
Um,actually,I think what
we'reknown for is sharing clothes
Yeah.I thinkthat's our thing
why does he keep doin' that?
He knows it's annoying
He's just tryingto get to us
Yeah,well,it's working
Knock it off,down there
do you hear what I'm saying?
Matthew. Matthew!
Sit down
You knowwe don't talk to him
That's partof his punishment
How can you just sit herehour
after hour and listen to that?
Well,that's part of mine
carlos,what is thisbig emergency?
I had to cancel my
hairappointment with eduardo today
Baby,what is it?
I'm completelyfreaked out
Why?
There's this guy,his name's richie
and he's beensaying some stuff to me
and I'm gettin' worried
Honey,you and your macho pride
Just tell him you're flattered
but you don't swing that way
He's not hitting on me
you idiot,he's threatening me
Really? How?
He saidhe's gonna beat me up
unless I come upwith some money
Well,how much money?
$7,000
- $7,000?
- Keep your voice down
Why would he thinkyou
have that kind of money?
Because yesterday
in a visitingroom filled with criminals
my wife referred
to meas a rich man
Oh,right. Sorry
That's why I needed
you to bring the checkbook
He's actually willing
to take a check?
No
You're gonna take the
money to his girlfriend
and if she doesn't get
itby tomorrow,I'm screwed
Honey,I thinkthis is a mistake
If we give in to extortion
the guy's just gonna
keepcoming back for more money
What choice do I have?
You're a strong guy.You went to college
on an athletic scholarship,for god sakes
Yeah,it was for golf
Oh
You have all my pants
Yeah,I know.Come on in
I,uh,thought when I tookmy stuff back to my house
I got everything
Oh,it's fine.They're in the garage
So how have you been doing?
Good. Um...I'm,uh,good.
I got a question for ya
Sure,what is it?
- Where are we now?
- Where are we?
Yeah. We're notmoving in together
and we're not broken up,so where are we?
I don't know
Since the guywho held me hostage
turned out to be your son
I think logic dictatesthat I should move on.
The problem is...
I'm crazy about you
So...
so I'm thinking we shouldkeep it casual
Casual
What the hell does that mean,exactly,um,casual?
well,I-I don't--I don't think
there'sanything wrong with us
seeing a movieonce in awhile
A movie. Okay.Is that it?
Jogging?
There's no lawagainst jogging.
Anything else?
Shopping. That's casual.That's fun
Anything else we can do?
Anything at all?
brunch
Brunch would be nice
Sounds good to me
All I can do is
take itone day at a time.
yes
Oh,okay. Well...
thanks so muchfor calling.
Who was that?
Oh,someone namedalan hanley
My electrician?
Why were you on the phone
sobbing to my electrician?
Oh,he called to
offer youhis condolences
Then why didn't youput me on?
Oh,well,we got to talking
and then he had to go
He--he had some very
beautifulthings to say about rex
for god sakes,phyllis
don't you ever worryabout dehydration?
Are you sayingthat I am too emotional?
I'm saying that even
italianstake a break now and again
My son is dead.I'm grieving
So am I,but no onewould ever
know it with your incessantcaterwauling
Bree!
People want to knowhow
I'm doing,but the minute they ask you
you jumpinto the spotlight
and they forget all about me
I need consoling,too,phyllis
Have you ever thought of that?
I'm sorry
It won't happen again
Thank you
Of course,if you didn't
constantlysuppress your emotions
people wouldn't forgetto console you
Excuse me?
Well,it's true
You're stoicto the point of being cold
I am not cold. I just--well
I don't likepublic displays of emotion
Well,that's fine,but people
wonder why they haven'tseen you cry
I mean,some peopleactually
wonder if you truly mourn rex
People have said that?
A few,yes.
Excuse me
I'm looking for rita rivera.
Hi,are you rita?
Yeah,who are you?
I'm,uh,I'm gabrielle solis
Our--our husbands are
roommatesat the prison
Richie and I aren't married
Oh,I see. Well,uh,your boyfriend
asked my husband to give this to you
It's a sort of favor
It's all there. $7,000
Son of a bitch!
Oh,don't eventhink about it
hello...is there a problem?
- Let me ask you a question?
- Okay
This might seemkind of weird
but what do you thinkof my breasts?
Excuse me?
I mean,how do theylook to you?
they're--they're nice
Thank you.I like too
You're right.That was weird
You have no idea
what this money is for,do you?
No.No. You--you seem
to have everything you need
Richie wants meto get a boob job
He wants 'em bigger
He's obsessedwith huge breasts
So are you gonna do it?
I told him if he came upwith the cash,I would
I just never thought the
moronwould actually come up with it
Not that it's any ofmy business
but it's your body
I wouldn't change anythingunless
I really wanted to
But if I don't do it,he'll leave me
Honey,he's in jail.How far is he gonna go?
Maybe it's time you stood upfor yourself
Tell him you don't needthe surgery
It's worth a shot
There you go.I am so proud of you
when lynette went back to work,
she was aware her new job would be demanding
What she hadn't anticipated...
was the night shift
Hey,honey,I thought
I heardyou come in about an hour ago
I did. I had to loadthe dishwasher
You didn'thave to do that
Yeah,I sorta did
I'm sorry.I've justfallen
behind on my housework
I just had so many errandsto run today
But I'll make up for
ittomorrow,okay? I promise
That's the beautyof
my system--it's flexible
You know,for the sakeof our marriage
please don't mentionthe system again
I said I'm sorry
What in the world?
No,no,don't touch that
Don't touch that
Um,penny had a little
spitty-uppy on the sheets
And youdidn't change them?
The towelis very clean
Oh,that's disgusting
No,it's justa little spit
a little milky spit upon the sheets
Please,I made a judgment call
Please respect that
No,I can't respect that
and do you know why?
It's stupid
I'm gonna getnew sheets
We are not changingthe sheets
Why are youyelling at me?
I am not yelling at you
and this is not about spit up
Of course it is
No,it isn'T.It's about control
And as you and I both know
youhave some issues in this area
Why are you fighting
so hardto sleep on baby vomit?
I am fightingfor a principle.
Being too lazy to
changethe sheets is not a principle
You know what?
You're not gonna win this one
So you'd better
justcrawl back into bed
and let's go to sleep
No,tom!
Tom,no!
I'm gonnachange the sheets!
Oh,come on!No,you come on!
Just get up!Get up!
That's it!All right,fine!
Fine! Fine! Fine!
Normally lynette would
have spent a sleepless night
telling herself she
didn't have control issues
but she couldn'T
She was too busy figuring out
how to bend tom to her will
hello?
Hi
Welcome to the promised land
Go on.There
Good job!
betty?Betty?
Oh,betty
can I ask you a question?
Of course.It's susan,right?
Yes,hi.I was just wondering,
are you having some
remodelingdone on your house or something?
No. Why?
Well,I work at home
so I'm home a lot working
And I just keep
hearingthese noises lately
it's hard to concentrate
Well,I haven'tnoticed anything.
Really? It sounds likeit's coming from your house.
You know
it's likea clanging--clanging
there! There
that was it.Did you hear it?
Oh,yes
Matthew's very handy
He's always doingprojects around the house
I guess I just don't noticethe noise anymore
Even at 2:00 in the morning?
Cause that's kind ofhard to miss
I'm so sorry
Matthew is somethingof an insomniac,susan
But I will talk to him
and we'll put a stop to it
Afternoon,Mrs. Mayer
Hi,matthew
Well,it was nice chattingwith you,susan
This is my third
phone call,mr. Flannery
And if someonedoesn't call me back soon
I'm going to be irritated
Is everything all right?
That darn insurance
companyis dragging its heels
on paying rex's policy
and I don't understand why
Well,he died unexpectedly
And that brings
upa lot of questions
It's probably easier
when peopleare just diseased
Probably
Hi
- Hi
- Oh,hi,lynette
I'm sorry.Am I interrupting?
No,no,not at all
I saw you walk inand I've been
meaning to callsince the service
but work's been so crazy
so...how are you doing?
I'm all right
well,you look amazing
Do I?
Absolutely
well,I can't imaginewhat
you're going through
phyllis?
You're going to have to stop that
I can't help it
When people talk about rex
I-I...I just get emotional
Well,I'm very sorryfor
your loss,too,phyllis
He was my firstborn
I don't know what
I will do without him
Oh,I'm so sorry
is she gonna be okay?
yeah.Sure.Hold on a second
there we go.Feel better?
Lynette,you were saying?
I forgot
That's all right
It wasreally sweet of you to stop by
Okay
So,are we ready to order
or do you needa little more time?
I've been in the
insuranceindustry for 15 years
I've never receiveda
phone call like this
I'm having second
thoughtsabout rex's death
I've known rex and
breefor nearly 20 years
And I've never hadany reason to suspect
they were anythingbut
a happy,loving couple
which is whythis seems so strange
I found it in rex's roomafter he coded
"I forgive you"?
George,what are youdoing here?
I'm here to kidnap you
What?
Get your purse
I'm gonna take you bowling
I-I don't know how to bowl
Or to the moviesor for a frozen
yogurt Whatever you want
thank you,but I just couldn'T
bree,I'm sure you haven'
tgone anywhere in weeks
You gotta get out and
do things.It'll help. Trust me
I do.I'm just...
I'm just not ready yet
But it was very sweet
of youto think of me
Well,you know,I tried
And I appreciate that
It's all right
Let it out
You want me to
die in here,don't you?
Carlos,what happened?
What do you mean
"what happened?"
You talked rita out
of taking the money
Is that what richie said?
Yeah,the subject came
upin between kidney punches
Well,it's not my fault
She didn't want the money
Why wouldn't she want $7,000?
Because it's
for a boob job
- So?
- So her boobs are fine
And,honestly,what he's doing
to her self-esteemis just cruel
I feel sorry for her
Please,you don't care about
herself-esteem any more than I do
You just didn't want to
give upall that money
Well,I do think it's sillyto
give someone $7,000 if they don't want it
Listen to me
you're gonna go back there
you're gonna put
that moneyin rita's hands
and you're gonna convince
herthat life is not worth living
unless she has jugsthe size of texas
Do I make myself clear?
I just realized rita
and ihave a lot in common
Please don't tell me you have
low self-esteem cause if I laugh now
I'm gonna crack the
one good ribthat I have left
We are both controlledby our husbands
which is idiotic
becausethey're both behind bars
We should have all the power
I am not tryingto control you
I just don't wanna
end upin the morgue
This isn't about that
Gabrielle,the morphine's wearing off
I really don't have timefor these games
Me either,carlos
And if you expect me to go back and
sweet talk herinto getting the operation
I can't show up empty-handed
Fine,bring me the checkbook
I'll make out a checkfor some cash
See I was thinking
I'd be writing the checks
Gabrielle--
careful,carlos
you're notin a position to argue
Whoo-hoo!Susan!
Hey,edie
- So,How much do you hate me?
- What?
Oh,karl said that you know
allabout our dirty little secret
- Yes,yes,I do
- Well,I feel awful
I should have told youthat I was doing your ex
Well,it would've beenthe classy thing to do
Well,etiquette is a lost artfor a lot of people
You've gotta believe me,I never
ever thoughtanything would happenwith us
But on our first date
karl took meto a mexican restaurant
You know what I get
likewhen I drink tequila
A couple of shootersand
my bra unhooks itself
Circumstances beyondyour control
I get it.So if you'll excuse me
Hey. Hey,hey
I am offering youan opportunity here
I mean,go ahead--vent
Let me have it
Come on,tell mewhat a bitch I am
Yeah,for snacking onyour leftovers
I deserve it.Come on,bring it on
Honestly,edie,I don't mind
You can skate offinto
the sunset with karl Be my guest
Well,that's good to know.
I probably shouldn'ttell you this,but...
while we were in my jacuzzilast night...
karl said it was
the best sexhe's ever had
bar none
Actually,I'm gladthat you shared that
because here'sa tidbit for you
Karl said he's stillin love with me
Edie,what are you doing?
You are a lying liar
We're in the middleof the street
Would you get out of here?
Karl never said that
Okay,karl asked meto get back
together the day afterjulie's birthday
I said no
which I'm guessingis the reason
for the now legendary
tequilabra-popping incident
Please let go
Oh,no.We're not finished here
Well,yes,we are.I'm gonna go
You don'thave the guts
In five seconds,I'm gonna punch it
Yeah?I'll key your car!
Not if you're
suckingmy exhaust,you won'T
Take back what you said!
No,I won't!
Admit it,you'd do anything
to destroy my happiness!
Edie,for god's sake
Why would I care if you
end upwith a man I despise?
Cause you and mikeare finished
Yeah,word's out
And now that youcan't be happy
you don't wantanyone else to be,period
Edie,come back here!
We're not finished yet!
So you'd say the abuse starteda
few years into your marriage?
It started so slowly
I didn't realizewhat was happening
I mean,he'd slap
meover some little problem
But he'd always apologize
Then it got worse
And one day,eight years ago
my sonspilled soda on our new carpet
Before I could moveto protect him
virgil had knocked himon
the ground and began kicking him
I wanted to protect my baby
but I didn't get there in time
What happened to your son?
Well,he died
I came across one ofhis
baby pictures last weekend
That's when the
nightmaresstarted again
The last doctor I saw said
thatI needed to let go of my guilt
and then I wouldstart sleeping again
Of course
that's easier saidthan done
And I am getting so tired
I'm gonna start youon nitrazepam
That shoulddo the trick
Thank you
I certainly hope your
husbandwas punished for what he did
Oh,there was retribution
I made sure of that
Where are youoff to?
I'm,I'm going
to seerex's lawyer
We're going to go over
somedetails involving rex's will
Phyllis...
obviously,I'm just
mortifiedover slapping you
I've--I've just been ina weird
place since rex's death,but...
that's no excuse
I'm very,very sorry
No need to apologize
You're family
All's forgiven
Really?
It's been a difficult
timefor all of us
I totally understand
Now,go
You don't want to be late
foryour meeting about rex's will
Claims.This is joe flannery
Hello,could I speak to someone about the
death benefits for rex van de kamp,please?
This is his mother
Yes,we've already spokento
his wife several times
We are moving
as quicklyas we can
Are you aware that
mydaughter-in-law has a boyfriend?
I'm listening
Control--
it's extraordinary the
tactics people employ to obtain it
Some rely on deception
While others engage
in outright trickery
Then there are those
who resort to extortion
Why do we fight
so hard for control?
because we know to lose it
is to put our fate
in the hands of others
And what could be more dangerous?
-=伊甸园论坛 http://www.ydy.com/bbs=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=COSL-YTET小组工作室=-
sync:YTET-ronald