My name is jane vasco.
I could use
you on my team.
I work for a secret government
agency that hunts neuros.
People who can do dangerous
things with their minds.
On my first assignment..
Something a little
weird happened,
okay, something
really weird.
Until i get some answers
i'm getting on with my life,
doing my job.
Stocking up on aspirin,
because I gotta tell ya,
pain's a bitch!
suck it in, tammy, or
we'll never get
all of you zipped up...
Caitlin, you're supposed
to wear the outfit,
not wrestle it.
Relax...
Undo the top.
I want the audience to see
that some part of you
still looks
like a woman..
Lose the candy on
the runway, shannon.
It makes you look like
a chipmunk gathering nuts
for the winter.
Chipmunks are
adorable, geoffrey.
So are you, shannon..
Just ignore him.
Sweetie, it's good
to be nervous.
Use that energy
on the runway.
Turn it into something
hot, dangerous, sexy.
Make it yours.
Understand?
Arlene hasn't been
hot and dangerous,
since madonna
had a career.
You watch me work.
I'll show you hot
and dangerous...
And very sexy.
The beautiful katie heads
off fiddels's new collection
with this flowing outfit
representing flight
and freedom of spring
adding a nordic influence.
Next eve shows us a continuing
european theme here
as this lovely blouse
adding a bavarian flare
to a sexy summer look.
And joelle gives
us a modern update
that hips up evening ware
for a less traditional
urban look
that still remains classic.
The wonderful flowing design
here worn by rebecca
is equally at home in town
or out on the beach.
And yes, the stunning
wanda show us that
fairytales do come true.
With the classically
influencing gown and
the beautiful flowing satin.
And with a more modern
take on evening ware,
shannon shows off...
You okay?
Excuse me, excuse me,
where is she?
Right over here.
What happened?
Can you tell me
what happened.
She collapsed
on the runway,
she's only 19.
My god!!!
Transcript : swsub.com
Presync : IceFre@k
When I was a girl,
my grandmother gave me a book
of fairy tales.
What I learned from those
stories was that men had
to be brave, handsome
prince charmings.
And any woman who wanted
a prince charming to want her
had to be
kind and pure...
And beautiful,
mostly beautiful.
No prince worth his
kingdom would've kissed
sleeping beauty if she
hadn't been just... Perfect.
I'm grown up now.
Don't believe
in fairy tales.
Or princes.
And i'm a few light
years from perfect.
It's just a bruise.
'Normal' people get
them all the time.
But, since I'm 'abnormal',
when something doesn't heal,
it's not normal.
It's abnormal.
And just trying to wrap my
brain around this weirdness
gives me a headache.
You're having headaches?
A figure of speech, seth.
How have you been
feeling lately?
Physically?
Emotionally?
It's amazing what goes on
in my head sometimes.
You sleeping all right?
Rarely.
It's hard to go to sleep.
Hard to stay asleep.
Lots of dreams.
About?
Vampires.
Zombies.
Things that don't die.
It's sort of an
obsession of mine.
I know how hard
this is for you.
What's hard is not knowing
why i can take six bullets
and live...
And why a bruise
won't go away.
Right now, i'm wondering
how your state of mind
affects your body's
ability to heal itself.
You think there's
a connection?
I thought it was
something that...
Just happened.
We know what goes on in our
brains can affect our bodies.
But i've never done
anything to make it happen.
You haven't, but...
But perhaps your
mind has.
That makes me sound
more and more like a...
Don't jump
to conclusions, jane.
Maybe you should just
try and get some rest.
It started with one
isolated incident
that caught my attention.
The more i looked into it,
the stranger it got...
Look at this:
katherine cost,
amanda smart,
shannon conway
and carolyn merrit
were all fashion models.
All young, beautiful...
Carolyn merritt?
The babe who wore
the purple thong
in the 2005 swimsuit issue?
I was so wrong.
You do read.
That Carolyn Merritt.
They all knew each other.
They'd all worked
together...
Now they are all dead.
What happened to them?
They died of old age.
Margeaux, katie, amanda,
shannon and carolyn.
The oldest
girl was 23,
the youngest 19.
Shannon conway was
the most recent...
She died after the first
big show of the new season.
How do young women
die of old age?
The first medical diagnosis
was a segmental progeria
some sort of
accelerated aging disease.
NIH and CDC, they all checked out
all the usual suspects:
hutchinson-gilford, de barsy
syndrome, cockayne, gottron's.
They're genetic disorders,
but here's the thing.
None of the girls' DNA
presented any of the
expected genetic mutations.
And progerias kill
at a very young age.
Slowly.
These women were all healthy
one minute,
rapidly aged and dead
the next.
You see the progression
from left to right.
You said they
worked together.
What about exposure
to radioactive material,
Chemical toxines... ?
No.
I created lifestyle
and biographical
profiles on each girl,
I cross-referenced
everything I could.
and so far, no statistically
significant commonalities.
I am still working but...
If it walks like a neuro,
talks like a neuro...
Riley, you said.
This season's circuit
is just underway.
I think we'll have to investigate
this from the inside.
How inside is inside?
I'll have your bios and resumes
finished this afternoon.
Don't trip on the runway.
What's wrong?
I have to ask
you something.
Sure.
How do i look to you?
And not, not because
we like each other...
But objectively.
Would the average
man rather be with
some bony little twig
who wears a size zero
pink thong bikini?
Or this?
The truth.
I'm a grown woman.
I can take it.
So go on.
Hit me with
your best shot.
I'm sorry.
I put you on the spot.
You don't want
to hurt my feelings.
Now you think i'm a silly,
vain, insecure woman,
with low self-esteem.
Can i say something?
No, I think you've
said enough.
No, you have.
Can i get some
air time, here?
Fine.
The truth.
No lip service.
But it's the lips
that tell the truth.
You're, like, here.
This is where i,
like, live...
And you don't.
Don't you ever knock.
No.
Right.
I just came by to borrow
something to wear.
I met a new guy
and I plan to get lucky.
So, I want to look hot.
Help yourself.
I'm sure i've got
something that goes
with combat boots.
Cool...
Thanks!
My neighbor, amanda.
She has some issues
with boundaries.
And doors.
She just wants to
feel like someone's
taking care of her.
So do i.
No, no!!!
Ladies!!!
New guppies in the pond.
Win a contest or was
it "make a wish?"
i've got your
wish right here.
Save it.
Fear's like blood
in the water,
and we're surrounded
by sharks.
At least everyone's having
a really good time.
Now i know how hef felt
at the mansion.
Goldfish.
Barrel.
Riley...
You picking up a feed from
all the surveillance cams?
I'm hot, boss.
The only way i can
get into this dress
is if i paint it on.
Demarco designs his dress for girls
with single digit bmis.
You're just too healthy.
Good luck.
It's not your skin...
It's your skivvies.
Bra, panties.
History.
I don't think so.
Demarco will not
be pleased.
Go away, geoffrey.
I'll make demarco happy.
I always do.
I'm glad someone can.
He's a pain,
but he's right.
And the dress is discrete.
For a hooker
in times square.
It's just your
body, honey,
it's not who you are.
That's one of the two most
important things you need
to know in this business.
I like that.
What's the second?
Without a beautiful
body, you're worthless.
Enjoy it while you can.
Kirsten shows us the most
important aspect in spring ware.
Colour, colour, colour...
In this beautiful floral blowing dress.
Candy shows us
this beautiful summer style...
Even over
a simple black outfit.
Take it off your neckline and
you're ready to hit the club!
Jane, you're up
in three minutes.
Is It possible to stay
fashionable come rain or shine?
Wanda certainly does in this
simple yet stylish look
that has her
looking hot and dry.
Is on in 30 seconds,
has anybody seen her?
Nobody is there.
Go.
Maureen shows this tropical
colour in this gorgeous
expressionist influence.
And the lovely jane...
Jane is certainly
turning heads on the runway
and will turn surely
more on the finest restaurants
as well
as the most happening parties
in this stunning outfit.
I went into the dressing
room to put on the dress...
Came out and looked
in the mirror.
I'd put on 20 years
in five minutes.
You seem fine now.
All healed.
There's a shocker.
So what does this mean?
I live forever?
You can reverse whatever
dna damage the neuro
might have inflicted...
I don't know if you
can reverse
the 'normal' aging process.
The bruise has healed.
You look better.
We've got three dozen
possibles who were in that
room with you.
Did you get close to anyone?
Are you kidding?
It was like a tokyo
subway car at rush hour.
I got close to everyone.
Riley's looking over
surveillance footage.
I'm hoping he can isolate
something, or someone, unusual.
Backstage.
On the runway...
I'll tell you this though,
our neuro must have been damn
shocked to see you come out
on the runway.
Have to wonder what
the reaction will be to that.
The surveillance cams
picked up 86 people,
including the models,
at the fashion show.
But only three of them
were present for the other...
Incidents.
Geoffrey graham.
It's not your skin,
it's your skivvies.
Bra, panties, history.
I don't think so.
Thanks for the replay,
riley.
It's one of my
favorite memories.
It'll be in my
top ten, too...
Wanda norton.
Demarco designs for girls
with single digit bmis.
You're just too healthy.
Good luck.
Arlene watson.
The show coordinator.
Without a beautiful body,
you're worthless.
Enjoy it while you can.
It's show time.
We need dna from
all three of them.
I'll takes dibs on wanda.
Jane,
you take wanda.
You can handle arlene.
You'll get geoffrey.
To date, all the victims
are women.
We don't know if our neuro
requires physical contact
or merely proximity.
You're telling us
to be careful.
What else is new!
We know jane can recover.
Bring a chip gun with
you just in case.
Connor, as to how you
want to handle geoffrey,
i'll leave that up
to you.
Jane, are you home?
It's me amanda.
The dress was totally hot,
which means i didn't
have it on for very long.
You have anything i could wear
to a soiree tomorrow night?
Whatever.
You want to know what kind
of a career modeling is.
That's not
the right question.
Not even close.
What is.
Modeling isn't a career,
sweetie, it's life.
Every day 24/7.
There's nothing else.
It's consuming, addictive
and very seductive.
It's also degrading
and humiliating.
You're just a beautiful
means to an end,
a lovely commodity
like the fabrics
that make
the clothes you wear.
And you are expected
to be perfect every day 24/7.
That's impossible.
It's insane.
The models cry on my
shoulder every day.
I hear all
the horror stories.
Models sacrifice real
lives for 15 minutes
of fantasy and illusion.
But, when they
can't sell schmata,
they're useless and invisible.
And for a model, being
invisible is a death
a lot worse than dying.
I have an appointment
with a designer.
I still sell beauty.
Only now...
Not mine.
Hey, you were
at demarco's show?
That depends.
What are you?
I was doing security.
Security?
No,
you didn't see me.
Let me ask you something.
Those models, they get
paid pretty good, huh?
Those models, yes.
Why do you ask?
Just seems like an easy
way to earn a buck.
Just strut your stuff
and they pay you.
And you're wondering if your
"stuff" is worth strutting.
You're the pro here.
So this is a consultation.
I guess so.
I charge for that.
Let's say one margarita?
I can do that.
I'm going to buy
some cigarettes.
I'll be right back.
May i help you?
Hi..
This may seem
a little presumptuous but,
I met you
at demarco's show.
- My name's...
- I know...
Jane vasco.
I'm in the penthouse.
After the other night...
I'm just not sure if
i'm cut out for this.
Thank you.
You have all the credentials,
you'll get over it.
Opening night jitters.
Hell,
i'm still jittering.
It doesn't seem to
affect you at all.
It did.
Like anything else,
you do something
long enough,
you get used to it.
I guess i'm still wondering
if i want to.
I felt like i was
in a shark tank.
Is it always like that?
Goes with the territory.
These particular type of
"shark" has a short life span.
The "fins" only
hold up so long.
In all that
feeding frenzy,
how do you find
your friends?
Often in the most unlikely,
unexpected places.
As long as they don't
let them smell blood.
Exactly.
That is a lot to think about.
Just out of curiosity,
how'd you know my name?
How'd you know my address?
People have a way of
finding each other...
When they need to.
Cheers.
Dna results on geoffrey
and arlene were negative.
And guys i think you'd better
take a look at this.
Wanda norton's real
name is phyllis carson.
Born in erie, pennsylvania.
Got a lot of mileage
out of being pretty.
Junior and senior
prom queen.
Won the miss 'battle of lake
erie' beauty contest, twice.
Other than that did some local
modeling et cetera, et cetera.
Ts is phyllis on
the hood of a 1978 trans am.
What's your point,
she models classic cars.
Today, it would
be classic.
When this photo was taken
the car was brand new.
This photo was
taken september 1977.
Wanda... Phyllis...
was born in 1955.
Puts her in her 50's.
Has jane checked in yet?
No.
Can't get her on
the comm, either.
You try wanda's place?
It just rang.
Keep trying jane's comm.
You and i'll check
her apartment.
I want to know if
you hear something.
Anything.
I don't think the insecurity
ever really goes away.
How can it?
As models we spend
our entire careers
watching the hourglas
slowly empty,
pretending it isn't,
but, it is...
It's getting late..
I should... Go.
No.
You belong here...
With me.
You see.
Models are like roses:
first we're delicate buds,
then we're beautiful flowers.
Then our petals slowly
fall and we die.
But you're different...
Somehow you're special too.
You...
...are a beautiful flower
that doesn't die.
jane, open up!!!!
Clear!!!!
There's no way
that's vasco.
You found me so easily.
Where are we?
Where have you taken me?
That makes me uncomfortable.
I thought it best to relocate
to someplace we might
have more privacy.
I've been watching you,
studying your face
for hours.
You have
a timeless beauty.
Raphael would have loved
painting you.
What do you
want from me?
Youth.
You have it.
I need it.
Those girls...
The ones that died...
Beauty comes with a price.
Those girls didn't suffer.
A small kiss is
all it takes.
And then there's you.
Someone who can give me
what i need without...
Apparently paying
the price.
An endless drink from
my fountain of youth.
Alright people,
i need some answers!!!
Bowers and i went over
every inch of wanda's condo.
We found jane's prints on
a glass, but that's about it.
No clue where they went.
What about the girl
in jane's place?
Amanda worth.
She was jane's neighbour.
She must've been in the wrong
place at the wrong time
when wanda came in,
looking for jane.
Riley, anything?
Ask me to track down
a serial killing neuro, a pyro,
a minor and i'm good, but
damn, these frickin models
live out
of their purses.
Harder to track than a...
Find her!
A celebration's in order.
You've taken ten years
off my face
and you've saved
someone's life.
Think i'll get nominated
for a nobel?
To you, jane...
You can't appreciate how amazing
it feels to be young
because you've
never been old.
You know what they say
"skin deep" and all.
What's beneath your skin
is already old and dead.
Young and quick to judge.
Do you know how you'd react
if you were in my shoes?
The first time
it happened...
When i realized what
i was capable of..
It was an accident.
I didn't understand it.
It terrified me.
It made me sick.
But you got over it.
I swore it would be the last
time, never happen again. But..
I suppose vanity
triumphed over...
Self-control.
So, i did it again, for
the last time, i told myself.
And every time
after that...
It was always going
to be the last.
I suppose it's the same
as anyone's addiction.
One last time at a time..
Every "addiction"
has its price.
As just mine.
It seems that, along
with youth and beauty,
the girls also leave a little bit
of themselves inside of me.
Sometimes it's
little quirks.
Shannon loved
these candies.
Lose the candy on
the runway, shannon.
Amanda?
You killed amanda?
...She smoked.
I've never smoked
in my life.
Now i dream about it.
But why?
Why amanda?
I was looking for you.
I found her.
You're not an addict.
You're a monster.
No, darling.
I'm a model.
You've cut yourself.
It'll heal.
You're scared.
Suspicious.
But, i can make this
arrangement very nice for you.
Clothes, money, jewelry...
Anything you want...
Like i said,
in time you can get used
to the things you want,
excuse the ways
in which you get them.
Alright.
Uncuff me
and let me show you
what i can give you.
I'd like that...
But, not yet.
Anticipation
heightens sensation..
I'm pulling data on every
designer and agency
wanda's worked for, every
model she's worked with,
family, friends,
lovers, everyone.
It's going to take awhile.
A while is too
long, riley.
I know.
Boss.
Get back on it.
Tracing all those contacts
could takes days.
I'm open to ideas.
Arlene, the woman who
coordinates the shows,
she said the models
spill their guts to her
the good,
the bad, the ugly.
Maybe wanda did, too.
Good.
Go.
I know how hard
this is for you.
What's hard, is i can take six
bullets and live,
and why a bruise
won't go away.
We know what goes on in our
brains can affect our bodies.
But i've never done anything
to make it happen.
You haven't but perhaps
your mind has.
You don't know me, Jane
but this really
is for the best...
For me, for girls who would
otherwise have to die...
When you think about it,
we have so much in common.
Both of us alone, putting
on a front to show
the rest of the world that
it doesn't touch us.
Despite the pain inside,
we're just fine.
But we both know
better, don't we?
It does touch us.
Deeply.
And profoundly.
And maybe true peace of
mind can only come
when we can touch
each other.
Wanda is different than
the other girls
She doesn't come to
me as much as they do.
Most of these kids
are scared, lonely.
They need someone
to talk to.
Not wanda.
Close friends?
Lovers?
I don't think she
has close friends.
And i know she doesn't
hook up with any of
the boy toy models.
She has dated one man,
some high tech mucky muck.
Keeps a penthouse in town.
When he'd fly in
on business,
they'd be inseparable.
Got a name?
Jim blenheim.
I met him once.
Good looking but thirty
years older than wanda.
Never understood
the attraction.
For her?
For him.
I can think of at
least thirty reasons.
You know where
blenheim's place is?
No.
Blenheim was very private.
I like to know where
my models are 24/7,
but when wanda
was with him,
it was like she'd
dropped off
the face of the earth.
I just got off the phone
with liz logan,
the new head of the taa.
She's building
a new dynasty
and she's dying to work
with me!
If it hadn't been for you,
this couldn't have happened...
What have you
got on blenheim?
The guy's got
a lot of money.
And that buys
good privacy.
I did get a hit.
Architectural digest did
a spread on blenheim's 'palace'
the place
he has downtown.
No mention of
where it is,
but i grabbed some background
detail through a window...
That's the cronkite
building in the background.
That window's just
south of the building.
Given the angle we're
looking down from,
i calculate we're
460 feet in the air.
The ceilings in that
room are ten feet.
Assuming two feet
for structural...
Riley, just give me a damn
address !
231 west 71st.
Penthouse.
You asked me how it
feels to get old,
to see everything that makes
life worth living slipping away.
Now you know.
I should've known it was
too good to be true.
There's always a price
that has to be paid.
Always..
I wish i didn't
have to pay it.
I wish i didn't need it...
...And, sadly, you
can no longer help me.
I like you, jane,
i really do.
I'm sorry things have
to end this way,
but i know you understand why
i have to do what i'm doing...
You're useless to me now,
like a dress that's gone
terribly out of style.
I'm going to have
to replace you...
I don't go out of style.
I'm timeless... Remember?
You all right?
Feeling my age.
Chip her.
It'd be fascinating
to understand
the neurological mechanism
at work here...
Some kind of seizure.
Andre here.
I got her.
Hurry!!
Grab the legs!!
Seth, what's happening?
I don't know.
I do...
She's experiencing
my life...
Every bullet, every cut...
Everything
i could heal from.
I know how it feels,
i know.
It's okay.
She's gone.
You let yourself get old.
I didn't 'let'
myself get old.
I made it happen.
How?
Let's cut
the cat-and-mouse, seth.
I know what you're
looking for.
And i know you know
more than i know.
So i'm kind of
curious here.
Am i a neuro?
The whole science of
neurological aberration
is new field, jane...
Remember the bruise i
had that wouldn't heal?
Of course.
You wondered if
i wasn't healing
because of how
i was feeling.
Mentally.
Emotionally.
Before that, i'd always assumed
the healing just happened,
that i was like
a salamander that regrows
his tail after
it's cut off.
He doesn't make it happen.
It just... Does.
Yes...
Every neuro we've encountered
has had mental control
over what they did.
Exactly my point.
If my brain
controls my healing,
then i should be able
to turn the healing off.
Theoretically.
I decided to check the theory
and take my brain
for a test drive.
Meaning?
When i was with
wanda, i cut my hand.
It started to heal,
but i made the healing stop...
I let the pain of what
had happened to amanda...
Take hold of my emotions.
The same thing happened
with wanda.
I made the healing stop.
We don't know that's
what happened, jane.
Not for sure.
It's my brain and my body.
I know what's going
on inside of me.
So do i, and neither
of us should jump
to any conclusions.
Not yet.
You jump whenever
it feels right.
I already have.
A part of me felt sad
for phyllis carson,
of erie, pennsylvania.
An innocent little girl
learned that being 'pretty'
made the world
go around.
It made life worth living
for her, and for wanda..
At any cost.
Maybe wanda has been
released from an evil curse
and is finally free.
Maybe somewhere phyllis
carson is still a pretty
little girl...
And that's enough.
And maybe amanda has
finally found the home
she never had..
I want to believe she has.
Then again, i'm the girl
who once believed
in fairy tales.
And maybe that's
not so bad.
In the end, the slipper
fit cinderella's foot,
didn't it?
www.seriessub.com