Who are these people...
I cannot wait to get the hell out
of this Podunk town.
Make sure you do,
and before it's too late,
- Believe me, I know.
- How'd she know what I was thinking?
Oh my God!
I think Merlotte's just got
its first vampire.
I think you're right.
And what can I get for you tonight?
Do you have any
of that synthetic bottled blood?
No, I'm so sorry.
You're our first... vampire.
What the fuck is this?
You had sex with a vampire?
Once. I videotaped it.
You like this?
You know how many people
are having sex with vampires these days?
- Can I get y'all anything else?
- He's got 11 or 12 pints in him.
Holy shit, that's almost $10,000.
- We have to stop them.
- Who?
The Rattrays. They're gonna drain him
and sell his blood.
This ain't over.
What are you?
I'm a waitress.
Guess who was found strangled
to death in her apartment?
- You know Maudette Pickens?
- We've already seen the videotape.
- You didn't know she was taping it?
- You need to come with us.
- May I call on you sometime?
- Sure.
Would you mind meeting me around
the back of the bar when I get off?
- I have a favor to ask you.
- I'd be delighted.
Where's your fuckin' chain now?
God!
Dumb-ass ponytail.
Here we go.
- I love you.
- I love you too, baby.
Fuck you, Fido.
What the fuck...?
Show your fuckin' face, freak!
Synchro: mpm, SilverArrow
¤~ True Blood ~¤
Season 1 Episode 02
www.sub-way.fr
www.seriessub.com
- It's too bad I don't have fangs.
- Oh, yeah!
Rip your fuckin' throat out.
Fuck, yeah!
Here it comes.
Are you ready?
Fuck.
Fuck, yeah!
That was intense, huh?
Shit.
Fuck
Fuck!
Oh, Jesus.
A moron.
I didn't kill her.
I didn't kill her!
Somebody sure as hell did.
A vampire?
You're sure?
I saw his fangs.
Maudette had fang marks
on her inner thigh.
We know. We examined the body.
This be the same vampire
your sister's messin' around with?
First,
my sister ain't messin' around
with nobody. She don't mess around.
And second,
I don't know.
I never met the other vampire.
I never met any vampire,
I hope to hell I never do.
What did this vampire
on the videotape look like?
Bald-headed.
Weird skeleton tattoo.
And he looked crazy.
Crazy out of his motherfuckin' mind.
It's interesting, because...
this the only videotape we found
in Maudette's apartment.
I guess that means
somebody took them all, right?
Somebody didn't
want you to see them?
Or somebody only wanted us
to find this one?
Because it supposedly
clears him of a crime
that maybe
he came back later to commit?
Come on, Andy.
I'm not that smart.
I can't feel my legs.
Quick, drink before
the wound closes.
- Would I be a vampire?
- You won't be. Goddamn it,
do you want to live or not?
Go back to the green room.
Turns out I'm first
in the walk and talk challenge.
Walking and talking
can't be too hard, right?
B.J., your category
is Names of U.S. States.
Oh, Mother, damn.
Memphis.
New Jersey. New York. Connecticut.
- Hello, Hooker. What's the T?
- Where are you?
I'm on my way to a party in Monroe.
And hell, no, I ain't swingin' by
to pick your needy ass up.
Lafayette, please.
My momma's passed out
on the coach, and...
I can't face cleaning her up
and putting her to bed.
It's just too goddamn depressing.
What's depressing is how often
I get this phone call from you,
that's depressing.
Why come you won't call
Jason Stackhouse?
You're a mean, nasty bitch.
And you need to move your sorry
ass out your momma's house,
- that's what you need to do.
- Yeah, whatever.
Alright.
Alright, I is on my way.
But you might got to find
your own ride home.
Just in case I get lucky.
What you mean if you get lucky?
Your standards are so low
you always get lucky.
Damn straight.
Hallelujahs, hallelujahs.
Good Lord, I'm comin'!
Jesus.
What the fuck?
Did I say you could come in?
Look, it's 3:00 in the morning.
You have no idea
what I've been through since last night.
I spent the whole day thinkin'
I'd really killed Maudette Pickens.
Oh, my God.
I thought I'd accidentally
strangled her during sex.
And Bud and fucking Andy waited
12 whole hours to show me a videotape
that proved I didn't do it!
I thought I'd ruined my whole life.
Do I taste different
from other people?
Yes.
What are you?
Apparently I'm not dead.
What I am is telepathic.
I can hear people's thoughts.
Even mine?
That's why I like you so much.
I can't hear you at all.
You have no idea how peaceful it is
after a lifetime of...
May I ask you a personal question?
Bill, you were just
licking blood out of my head.
I don't think it gets
much more personal than that.
How do you manage a social life
with men your own age?
- Their only thought must be...
- I don't date.
Ever?
Oh, I've...
I've been on a few dates.
Man, I can't wait to see her naked.
I wonder if she's a natural blond.
Nothing worse than a blond
with a big, black bush.
What the heck?
Not every guy was a pig.
The kind of girl I could marry
and spend my life loving.
And never have those thoughts of Matt
Damon, Jake Gyllenhaal in Jarhead
with that little Santa hat on.
Where you goin'? What's wrong?
But
it always ends up the same.
There must be some people
who know about your talent.
The people closest to me.
But... we never talk about it.
And I do my best
to stay out of their heads.
Over the years I've learned how.
I figure it's kind of unethical
to listen in to my family
and my friends, my boss.
But... they know.
Other people suspect
or... they think I'm psychic.
Most people just think I'm crazy.
What does it sound like?
It's sort of like
a stream of consciousness.
Gets weirder
when people are mad, or...
upset and...
sometimes...
Sometimes it's just images.
I should be gettin' home.
Bill, I feel completely healed.
You are.
Do doctors know
that V-juice can do this?
And we wanna keep it that way.
I should show you to your car.
- How you doin', motherfucker?
- What's up, Joe?
Sexy ass over there.
Hey, baby.
Big boy, what's up, you?
What's up, baby?
I'm Terrell.
Tara. All right.
So what's
a fine girl like you
doing sitting here all by herself?
I'm watching my fool cousin trying
to hit on the straightest man here.
All right.
Baby, I am the straightest man here.
Really?
You can just ask
any one of these honeys.
Look,
I should tell you. I am married.
- That's not a problem for me.
- Well,
my husband is a mercenary.
Black oil.
He just got back from assassinating
some guys in Iraq.
- You makin' this shit up.
- I wish I was.
'Cause he ain't worth me, I can tell you
that, if he caught me with another man,
he'd kill us both.
I'm not sure who he'd kill first.
Probably me.
I hope so.
Bitch, you crazy.
He already shot one guy in the nuts,
just for buying me a CD.
Hell, no.
Fuck!
Oh, my God!
This how you wanna play?
How old are you?
- Am I allowed to ask that?
- I was made a vampire in 1865.
- When I was 30 human years old.
- You look older than that.
Life was harder then.
Were you in the Civil War?
I was.
Would you be willing to come,
talk to my grandmother's club?
It's... mostly a bunch of old people
who had family in the war.
They call themselves
the Descendants of the Glorious Dead.
The Glorious Dead?
There is nothing glorious
about dying in a war.
Bunch of starvin', freezin' boys,
killin' each other so
the rich people can stay rich.
Madness.
I'm sure it was awful.
Would it make you happy
if I did this?
It would make
my grandmother ecstatic.
Would it make you... happy?
Yes.
I'll do it then.
And look forward
to meeting your grandmother.
When may I call on you?
I'm off work tomorrow.
Just after dark then.
Sam's still up.
That's creepy.
We never should have
given them the vote
and legitimized their
unholy existence.
The American people need to know
these are creatures of Satan.
Demons, literally.
They have no soul.
But Reverend Newlin,
you must be aware of polls
that show consistently
growing support
- for vampire rights.
- Those polls are fixed.
Do you know how much money
these monsters have givent o politicians
of both parties?
As well as the corporate media?
That's nonsense. Vampires don't seek
to control human policy
It's of very little interest to us.
We simply want the...
You can't trace any of it.
It's all been laundered.
Are you accusing my organization
of criminal activity, sir?
I will not speak
to her directly, Sharon.
- Why is that, Reverend Newlin?
- My commitment to Christ Jesus,
praise his name, compels me
not to recognize her kind.
That's gonna make it
difficult to have a dialogue.
I will not speak to her directly.
Thank you, Sharon. Now, TBBN...
I don't think Jesus would mind
if somebody was a vampire.
I don't either, honey.
Is this sausage different
from what you usually make?
It tastes so much more complex
than it usually does.
Oh, dear, you think it's gone bad.
No, it's delicious.
It's like I can close my eyes
and I can see the farm
the pig lived on,
and feel the sun and the rain
on my face,
and even taste the earth
that the herbs grew out of.
Good morning, Tara.
No, you sit down.
- I'll make a new pot.
- All right.
- You look awful.
- Yeah.
Well, I feel even worse.
Yes, you can take a shower here.
And you can borrow
some of my clothes.
Thanks.
Any news about Jason?
Yeah, we heard already.
They let him go last night.
- I knew they would.
- I didn't.
Well, I'm glad to see
you're still alive.
You obviously did not hook up
with that vampire last night.
- Sometimes you are just plain dumb.
- Shut up!
Lucky Gran was already in bed
when I got in last night.
Did he bite you?
Are you sure? 'Cause you know
they can hypnotize you.
Yeah, and black people are lazy,
and Jews have horns.
You must be glad they let
Jason go home Miss Stackhouse.
I can't even believe
that they arrested him to begin with.
I have a good mind to call
Bud Dearborne and chew him out.
Jason's a good boy.
Everybody knows that.
I'm sorry I was such a bitch
to you last night.
Well, I'm sorry I been acting
like I'm your mother.
I just worry about you.
- You're basically my only friend.
- Am I too late for breakfast?
I'm so glad they didn't lock you up.
Me too.
I don't even know
why they suspected me.
I think somebody heard
I'd been with Maudette.
Had you?
- No.
- Are you sure?
She was a woman.
That's funny.
At least she was human.
You will never believe
what happened.
- Hey, Gran.
- Sit down.
- I'll fix you breakfast.
- What happened?
Apparently,
a tornado touched down
over at Four Tracks Corners.
It turned over that rent trailer
in the clearing.
You know the one?
And it killed that couple
- That's been staying in there.
- Mack and Denise Rattray?
They were trapped under the trailer.
Mike Spencer said
they were crushed to a pulp.
What are you doing here?
You know Mike Spencer.
Of course. You buried my parents.
Yep. My new job. Parish coroner.
But I still run the funeral home.
That's gotta be convenient.
This is still
a restricted crime scene.
Why are you here?
When I heard what happened,
I just had to come look.
What an awful thing.
You know, I did hear you weren't
too fond of the Rattrays.
Where'd you hear that?
My niece is the emergency room nurse
in Monroe.
Says somebody busted up
old Mack pretty bad last night.
- And everybody says that it was you.
- They were hurting a friend of mine.
This be that vampire
I been hearing about?
The one who was living
at the old Compton house?
The old Compton house?
- Just across from where I live?
- That's the one.
Your grandmother lets you
associate with a vampire?
You can take that up with her.
I'm sure she'd just love to know
that somebody thinks
she's not taking proper care of me.
The Rattrays were draining him.
Draining vampires
is against the law, isn't it?
I was simply doing my civic duty
by stopping them.
And now they're dead.
Killed by a tornado.
Tornados hop.
This one didn't land anywhere else.
And nobody around here heard or saw
anything like a tornado last night.
Are you telling me you seriously
think one man could do all this?
He's not a man.
They're really not that
different from you and me
if you bothered to try
to get to know one.
You're a good girl.
I have to see you go down this path.
Lucky for you, Sheriff Dearborne,
nobody's forcing you to watch.
Now, if y'all two rednecks
will excuse me, I've gotta go.
You know, he sleeps
in the ground all day.
I don't think he's gonna even
look at the rug.
I'm not doing this for him.
I'm doing this for me,
so I can be proud of my home.
And how do you know where he sleeps?
I don't, actually.
What's that smell?
What smell?
It smells like rotten food,
or something. You can't smell that?
Well, find it.
You can't smell this?
I better throw this out.
Jason and Tara are coming over
this evening as well.
- Gran.
- Well, they invited themselves.
Jason said that he wants to meet
the vampire for himself,
and Tara said she thought
she ought to be here as well.
Why everyone's getting their panties
in a wad about some stupid vampire?
Did you want to be alone with him?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Aren't you gonna tell me
to be careful?
You're always careful, Sookie,
about what counts.
And I can depend on that.
Isn't that right?
Look, I'm just saying.
Do you want a vampire
sucking blood out of you?
I'm just trying to get to know
the man, that's all.
'Cause that's where it's gonna end up.
Always does.
What do you know
about vampires, anyway?
Yeah, I know a lot more
than I care to.
Oh, please, you ain't even got
enough sense to pour piss out of a boot.
That's my beer.
You asked if I wanted anything
to drink,
and I said I'd have a beer.
And that's when you went
to the fridge.
Oh, my god, I'm so sorry.
- Here.
- It's okay.
I don't like it when you do that.
I've upset you.
Since you're here.
What's wrong?
You have to invite me in.
Otherwise it's physically impossible
for me to enter a mortal's home.
Seriously?
Come on, try.
I can't.
I can't even try.
That is so weird.
Oh, Bill, won't you please come in?
- Thank you.
- So
if I were to withdraw my invitation,
would you have to leave?
Well, I'll have to remember that.
Oh, my stars.
Of course.
You don't...
I... I'm sorry.
Your people, Mr. Compton,
they were from this area I believe.
Yeah, my father's people
were Comptons,
and my mother's people
were Loudermilks.
Oh, there are a lot
of Loudermilks left.
But I'm afraid old Mr. Jesse Compton
died last year.
Yes, ma'am.
That's why I came back to Benton.
There were no living Comptons so
I've set up home
in the old Compton place.
And as I expect the VRA to pass...
I wouldn't be too sure
about that if I were you.
A lot of Americans don't think
you people deserve special rights.
They have the same rights you have.
No, I'm just saying there's a reason
things are the way they are.
It's called injustice.
Listen, it's called,
"This is how we do it."
This is my house.
I will not tolerate rudeness.
Did you know the Stackhouses,
Mr. Compton?
I remember Jonas Stackhouse.
He and his wife moved here
when Benton was just a hole in the road.
I was a young man of 16.
Isn't this the house he built?
I mean, at least in part?
Yes, it was.
Did you own slaves?
I did not, but my father did.
A house slave, a middle-aged woman
whose name I cannot recall,
and... And a yard slave.
A young, strong man named Minus.
This is just the sort of thing my club
will be so interested in hearing about.
About slaves?
Well, about anything having
to do with that time.
I look forward to speaking
to your club, Mrs. Stackhouse.
Now,
if it's all right with you,
I thought that Sookie and I
might take a walk.
It's such a lovely night.
It's all right with me
if it's all right with Sookie.
- I don't think that's a good idea.
- I don't think it's your business.
She's right, Jason.
Look, Gran,
I am the man in this family.
You are a man in this family,
but I am the oldest person here
and this is my house.
You better respect me, boy.
Actually,
I'm the oldest person here.
Shall we?
We shall.
Well, thanks for making me
look like a fool in front of him, Gran.
You don't need any help
looking like a fool.
I went to the Rattrays' trailer.
I told you I was strong.
I don't believe I fully gauged
the extent of your strength.
Over the years, we become stronger,
and more skillful of hiding
what we've done.
You might want to remember
for next time: Tornados hop,
they don't just land in one place.
So I guess you've killed
a lot of people.
I killed a few by accident at first.
I was never sure
when I was gonna get my next feed.
But it's all different now.
There's Tru Blood.
I can get donor blood
from a clinic in Monroe.
Or I can glamour someone
into letting me feed on them for love,
and then they'll forget all about it.
Did you feed on the Rattrays?
After I'd given you my blood,
while you were healing.
You drank a lot of my blood.
What will that do to me?
Well, you'll have keener senses.
What else?
Your libido will be more active.
Is--? Is that it?
I'll always be able to feel you.
I'll be able to find you fast.
If you're ever in trouble,
that could come in quite handy.
You're gonna have to give me
a minute here, Bill.
I'm feeling a little overwhelmed.
Of course.
I don't know why your grandmother
was so short with you.
You're just trying to protect Sookie.
I hate it when people treat me
like I ain't got a lick of sense.
Like I'm still just a kid,
I don't know, in the way.
I know what that's like.
It sucks, that's what it's like.
You feel alone in the world,
like nobody understands you,
or even sees you.
Sucks.
That ain't right,
because everybody is, you know,
somebody.
What?
We're all just trying to be...
Trying to be seen to...
To matter.
You're right.
How'd you get to be so smart.
I'm not smart at all. I'm not.
I am constantly doing things
I shouldn't
and end up getting me in trouble.
I'm a fucking idiot sometimes.
Well, can I tell you a secret?
I am too.
It's not that much of a secret.
What? What?
"Not that much of a secret."
Shit.
I was supposed to pick up Dawn
from work.
Goddamn it.
She gonna be all pissed.
- Good night, Gran.
- Night, Jason. Drive careful.
You said you could glamour somebody
into letting you bite them?
What is that, hypnosis?
Kind of.
It's similar.
All humans are susceptible to it.
Have you done it to me?
- And I never will.
- Really?
Try.
- I don't feel comfortable with that.
- You chicken?
Can you feel my influence?
No, not a bit. Sorry.
Well, Sookie, this is very strange.
You don't like not being able
to control people, do you?
It's not a very attractive trait.
Humans are usually more squeamish
about vampires than you are.
Who am I to be squeamish about
something out of the ordinary?
Sookie, Jason, y'all get out
of the water now.
How can our car insurance go up
so much after just one ticket?
Damn it all to hell, Iate
having to ask Mama for money.
Damn what all to hell?
I can break open my piggy bank
if you need some money.
- Who told you we need money?
- Mama.
Corbett, I swear,
I haven't spoken a word.
Do you know why you're here?
Your parents, they're concerned
about something
that can't possibly exist.
But you and I are gonna put all
this silliness to rest today.
Now, can you tell me
what I'm thinking?
I'm thinking about
the color red and the number 9.
The color red
and the number 9.
The psychologist thinks
that Sookie just reads
our body language
and is highly observant. That's all.
That's a relief. That's bullshit.
Isn't it?
What's body language?
Why was that doctor so scared?
Because she was lying to me,
that's why.
Because there is something
to be scared of inside my little girl.
Oh, my God. She knows
everything I'm thinking.
Oh, sweet Jesus. What do I do?
Poor child. She can't.
I was diagnosed with ADD.
They tried to put me on drugs
but my mama wouldn't let them.
She knew that wasn't it.
She tried to protect me
even though I scared her.
When did you lose her?
Just before I turned 8.
Both my parents.
Flash flood.
I lost my wife and my children.
Everyone I knew from human life.
Most of them are buried here
in this cemetary.
You really don't consider
yourself human at all?
I'm not human.
Can you turn into a bat?
There are those who can change form,
but I'm not one of them.
Can you levitate?
Turn invisible?
Sorry.
You don't seem like
a very good vampire.
What can you do?
I can bring you back to life.
This is where you live?
Since old Compton had no living
heirs when he died,
ownership reverts back to me.
I thought that wasn't for sure
unless the VRA passes.
I haven't been getting in any trouble
with the renovations I've been doing.
Although of course
I've been doing it myself in the night.
I need an electrician, but I can't get
anyone to return my calls.
Maybe if I made a few calls tomorrow,
I could come by after work
and tell you who to contact.
Thank you.
Take your clip out.
May I?
I can smell the sunlight
on your skin.
I should see you home.
All right.
What's the matter, baby?
Don't you like me?
Oh, sure, I like you, Jason.
I wouldn't tie any old man
up to my bed.
So call in sick.
Sam won't mind.
One, Sam would mind.
And two, we've had sex,
like, three times today.
At this rate, we're gonna burn out
by the end of the week.
And then you're gonna
get all weird and closed-off,
and I've already been down
that road with you, baby.
But I'm horny.
Well, I'll be back by midnight.
You're not...
You're not leaving me here like this.
You just better be happy that's
all I'm doing to you, baby.
What?
You can just think of it as foreplay.
Foreplay my...
Don't!
Okay, this ain't funny, goddamn it.
Goddamn it!
Don't!
Fuck!
Bitch.
Hey, sugar.
Make Mom another stinger, would you?
You listen to me, Jane Bodenhouse.
You're already drunk as a skunk.
Ain't no man in here
gonna wanna take you home.
Sam will have to call your son
to come and get you
just like he always does,
even though everybody knows
it humiliates him to death.
Ain't you ashamed of yourself?
- What'd you just say to me?
- I said any particular brand of cognac?
No. Whatever you have
that's nice and cheap.
I told you to buy your uniform.
How come you don't wear a uniform?
Because I own this place
and wear what I want.
How come Terry Bellefleur
don't wear a uniform?
Because I spend enough time in them.
No. Because you're a man.
And Sam don't feel the need
to sexualize the men
in his employment the same way
he do the women.
- You don't have to wear the uniform.
- Thank you.
- Remind me why I hired you again.
- Affirmative action.
Loaded skins and a pitcher of Bud.
Is that it for y'all?
If you serve them nachos
off them titties,
we'd all be mighty obliged.
Ain't nothing I like more
than lickin' food off...
That's a fine ass too.
You wanna let go of the lady, you?
Or you want me to knock you
into next week?
Damn it, you're about
to break my arm.
Apologize.
Sorry.
Maybe you and your friends
should find someplace else to eat.
Let's go.
Don't look at me, you.
Rene, you should have let me
handle that myself.
Merlotte's is a nice place.
And we all want to keep it that way.
And besides, you remind me
of my baby sister, you.
I hope to God that somebody
will stick up for her
if some asshole
ever does her that way.
Would you tell Rene thank you for
helping me out with that jerk tonight?
I was so flustered I think
I might have seemed ungrateful.
Please let me get my period tonight.
Even though Rene wants one of his own,
but I sure don't want him to
feel like he's being forced...
Did you just read my mind?
Sorry. I'm not very focused tonight.
My private thoughts
are none of your business.
Wanna step into my office?
I swear I try not to listen,
but I can't always keep my guard up.
Is it true you can't hear
the vampire's thoughts at all?
God, that's...
I mean, that must be
very relaxing for you.
You know, not having
to work so hard not to hear.
Can you hear me?
- I don't want to hear you.
- Why not?
I'd have to quit if I read
your mind and I like it here.
- You don't have to quit.
- I've had to leave
every job I've ever had because
I could hear my boss' thoughts.
You might be surprised
by what you find.
- Not all surprises are good.
- Try sometime.
Now listen,
don't you worry.
You got a job here
as long as you want one.
I should get back to work.
Come on.
Baby girl,
don't even let that get you down.
Don't let what get me down?
Don't let nothing get you down.
It's the only way to live.
- Ain't that right, Big John?
- Right.
Hey, how's Jason?
He's probably pretty
pissed off at me right about now,
- but, hell, he probably deserves it.
- You know, I have to say I...
I'm surprised you and him
got back together.
No more than I am, baby. Believe me.
Think it's gonna last?
Is there a reason you want to know?
Ever since I've been friends
with Sookie,
I've just gotten a kick out
of watching Jason's escapades
with women, you know.
Sort of.
God only knows what happened
to my tables.
In other news,
a tragic car crash in town has
claimed three lives today...
Hey, turn it up.
... Theodore Newlin, his wife, Yvette,
and their 18-month-old daughter,
Bethany.
All pronounced dead on arrival
at Baylor University Medical Center.
There were a total
of seven other casualties as well
in the freak accident,
apparently caused when a freeway...
Well, hey, there, little human chick.
Hi, I'm here to drop off
some information
about an electrician for Bill Compton.
Is he here?
Maybe.
She smells fresh.