It's me. Sookie, it's me.
You all right?
Come here.
- Get your fuckin' hands off me!
- What are you doing here?
I was making sure Sookie got home safe.
The door was open.
- What are you doing here?
- It's okay. Let him go.
What happened?
Synchro: Arrow, mpm
Episode 6 Season 1
www.sub-way.fr / www.seriessub.com
- You get any prints off that drawer?
- Nothing plain.
Think we got a partial
on the sink, though.
Why don't you go upstairs
and lie down.
They're gonna be in there a while.
As soon as we find anything,
I'll let you know.
- Oh, shit. I got blood on my boots.
- So more blood, don't be sick.
Pull it together,
you pull it the fuck together.
Do your job.
No wonder they don't respect you.
Cut her up real good.
Must be 30 stabs.
Throat's wide open. Holy hell,
we've got ourselves a serial killer.
Lynn and the grandkids to
the lake for the weekend.
Poor woman stuck raising
these bat-shit crazy
Stackhouse kids
didn't deserve this....
Maybe I could
use a little air.
So I should never have left you alone,
and I lost my temper. I shouldn't have.
Do you think you could
apologize to me some other time?
I just...
Whatever you need, anything I can do,
you know I'm right here.
I know.
- Thank you.
- Hold you, make it better
I'm the one. So sorry.
Sorrowful. Soft skin.
I said another time, Sam.
What happened to Bill?
I'll go get him.
Thank you.
She's asking for you.
There something you wanna say to me?
- I want you to stay away from her.
- Sookie doesn't take kindly
to people making decisions for her.
You don't need to tell me
who Sookie is.
I know who she is.
I've known a long time.
Then you also know that
this is neither the time
nor the place for you to...
- mark your territory.
- There's a woman lying dead downstairs.
She wouldn't be there
if it weren't for you.
Anything happens to Sookie,
I promise...
I'll be sharpening a stake
with your name on it.
Looks like she put up
a hell of a fight.
See those defensive cuts
on her hands?
Straight to the bone?
Hardcore.
Psycho son of a bitch.
Going after her all the way that way.
It's the sickest thing I ever seen.
I've seen worse.
There was a murder
about six years ago.
Lady snapped.
Blew her husband's head off
while he was watching the game.
Big chunks of brain all over the TV.
Why'd she do it?
I guess she wanted to
watch something else.
How the hell would I know?
People don't murder
'cause they're right in the head.
I told you we never should
have released Jason.
Now, come on.
This is his grandma we're talking about.
You think
that little pervert ain't capable?
Adele did bring the fang
into a church.
Sure that ruffled more
than a few feathers.
If he didn't do it himself.
- But vampire Bill said...
- Vampire Bill?
You on a first-name basis
with that bloodsucker now?
These things are crafty.
They've killing long enough
- to know how to cover...
- Am I interrupting?
Mr. Compton, this...
Official crime scene.
You can't be in here.
It's all right.
I suspect vampire Bill's
been around a dead body
or two before.
Isn't that right, sir?
Friend of yours, wasn't she?
I suppose she was.
We got couple more questions for you.
You mind?
Not at all.
Sookie tells us you were here
when she found the body. Is that right?
I arrived a few moments after.
Kind of late
to be making house calls.
All right.
I guess you don't sleep.
They sleep.
Just not at night.
So you make a habit of visiting Miss
Stackhouse in the middle of the night?
We had certain personal
matters to discuss.
After you left my home, I was waiting
for her to return from her engagement.
When I heard her car in the drive,
I came across the cemetery.
You're saying you heard a car coming
from clean across the cemetery?
Heightened senses
are a common side effect
- of our condition.
- But you didn't see or hear
any other vehicles
coming from the house?
- Something like a truck maybe?
- No.
Lot of folks wouldn't be too keen on
a vampire moving in next door,
but Adele Stackhouse,
she welcomed you
with open arms, didn't she?
- She was very gracious, yes.
- So...
They were all very gracious
to your... people.
That's just about the one
thing they had in common.
Now, is that one hell
of a plus-size coincidence or what?
I don't believe so.
- Excuse me?
- I suspect whoever did this
is targeting women
who associate with vampires.
You can't be serious.
Adele Stackhouse? And a vamp?
I don't think Sookie's grandmother
was the intended victim.
I should probably call Jason.
I could do it if you like.
Thank you.
This is Stackhouse.
Know what to do.
To leave a voice message...
What's going on?
They are about to move
your grandmother.
You might wanna go sleep
at a friend's. Someplace less isolated.
I'm not going anywhere.
- Sookie, perhaps...
- No. This is my house.
- I'm staying right here.
- Turn her there. All right.
Coming through.
Please, God. Hope she didn't
recognize meat that vampire bar.
I look different, it was dark,
and she was...
Dumb luck you're not
in that bag right now,
screwing that vampire.
You could be next.
- Truly sorry about your grandmother.
- Are y'all done in there? 'Cause...
I'd like to clean up.
If that's all right.
All right, then.
You call us
at the first sign of anything.
- Keep an eye on her.
- I will.
They are right.
You should not stay here.
I agree.
You can have my trailer.
I'll sleep at the bar.
I'm as safe here as anywhere.
Besides, I got both of you
to protect me, haven't I?
I have to go.
Of course.
It's almost dawn.
And I will come back. Later.
I can take it from here.
Don't worry about me.
Go.
There's an extra mop round back.
Would you mind getting it for me?
Gran took a lot of pride
in her home.
She wouldn't want anyone
to see it like this.
Oh. That looks great.
- Why don't you put it in the kitchen?
- It was so sad.
That Stackhouse girl hasn't
come out of the kitchen.
I heard she hasn't cried
a single tear.
You know she's been going around
with that vampire.
Mrs. Fortenberry,
- you shouldn't have.
- You poor child.
I am so sorry for your loss.
That's very kind of you.
Gran often talked about you, so...
thank you.
Yeah, 'cause nothing says
I'm sorry like a tuna cheese casserole.
Another one?
I ain't seen Jason.
Is he here yet?
How the hell should I know.
I ain't his keeper.
Bitch.
Adele was just an angel
sent from heaven.
Too good for this world.
We're all gonna miss her so much.
Heard they almost cut off her head.
I don't see any blood.
I should have gotten here sooner.
Maybe I should have brought
my red velvet cake
- instead.
- Excuse me.
I just can't believe it.
Are you all right?
- I'm fine. Thanks for coming.
- Of course.
It's the least I could do.
You poor thing.
I can't imagine
what you're going through.
Now, if you need help with moving
or anything at all...
Am I moving?
I'm not moving.
But, honey.
With it happening...
- right here.
- I have far more good memories
of this kitchen than bad ones.
What a good way to look at it.
You know, you really are smarter
than anyone gives you credit for.
Oh, sweetie.
I didn't mean it like that.
Maxine Fortenberry,
you put that pie down
right now!
Come here. She's losing it.
This is Gran's pie!
Well, I'm sorry.
I was just making some room.
Poor girl is crazy as a bedbug.
- We know you killed your grandmother.
- After I spent all morning
- making this casserole.
- Dead because of you.
- ... your face in front of everybody...
- If y'all excuse us.
I need Sookie upstairs.
Just give us a little girl time.
Come on!
- I shouldn't have lost it like that.
- Don't you feel sorry for yelling
at that snoopy old bitch.
She's been sticking her nose
- where it don't belong for years.
- Say it.
I mean, if she talked any more shit,
she'd be shaped like a toilet.
I'm sorry.
Gran's gone.
She's really gone.
Yeah, she is.
I don't know
what I'm supposed to do.
- Can't even think straight.
- Of course you can't.
How can you,
with all these circling buzzards.
You know you're not
their entertainment.
You don't have to dance for 'em.
You gotta feel whatever you're feeling.
I'm not sure I'm...
feeling anything.
I'm just numb.
- Numb is good.
- Yeah.
Numb is probably exactly
what you need right now.
Stop worrying about being
so damn appropriate.
This is not an appropriate event.
Thank you for getting me
out of there.
I haven't had
a single minute of silence.
Can't seem to...
block anything out right now.
You want me to tell 'em all
to shut the hell up?
- I wish it were that easy.
- It is.
Your wish...
is my command.
I don't do drugs.
Relax.
This is not drugs.
This... is just a Valium.
I'll tell you what.
Put it in your night stand,
just in case you change your mind.
I'm gonna go
and check on the circling buzzards.
- Lafayette?
- Yes ma'am.
Would you mind...
taking this downstairs for me?
I will guard it with my life.
Holy shit.
This ain't no good.
Yeah, I know. I know.
I'm late.
My alarm broke
and I couldn't find my phone.
What you doing here?
My job.
Fuck.
He don't know, him?
Man, I am so sorry.
About what?
You want me to call anyone?
Your cousin Hadley?
No one's heard
from her in over a year.
Since she ran away
from that rehab Gran paid for.
I don't even know
how to get hold of her.
What about Bill?
Gonna invite him?
Tara, he can't go.
- You're right.
- It's not like you've...
known a lot of vampires.
Kind of takes getting used to.
I'm not sure
I'll ever get used to it.
What?
'Cause not everyone is as open-minded
as you. Shoot me.
- Hear the things people are saying.
- I do.
- Bill did not kill my grandmother.
- Don't you get all mad at me.
Nobody's blaming Bill...
exactly.
But didn't you tell me
he had scary-ass friends?
Not all vampires are like that.
I'd fuckin' lose it if anything happened
to you. You know that, right?
Tara, last night was so horrible...
I don't know how I would've gotten
through it if it weren't for Bill.
When I'm around him...
I don't know
how to explain it exactly, but...
it's like I almost feel normal.
- What the fuck?
- It's your fault!
Gran is dead 'cause of you.
It should have been you!
Don't you lay a hand on her!
She's screwing a vampire.
A fucking vampire!
That vampire was there for her
when you weren't.
You ought to be ashamed of yourself!
Is that how your grandma raised you?
To beat on your own sister?
Look at you!
I don't even recognize you anymore!
Get the hell out of here.
Get out!
You okay?
- I need to ask you a few questions.
- Not now.
- Where were you last night?
- I don't know.
I was with a girl.
Tara Thornton?
What? No.
Yeah, I didn't think so.
What's this one's name?
I don't remember her name. Okay?
I got a number.
- I don't know what I did with it.
- Why ain't that convenient?
What the hell is
that supposed to mean?
It's Detective Bellefleur.
And what the fuck
do you think it means?
Are you saying
I killed my grandmother?
You's a stupid bitch,
Jason Stackhouse.
Jason Stackhouse tossed Andy Bellefleur
like he was nothing but a rag doll.
Rene makes me watch
that Friday Night Smackdown with him.
Those men are built
thicker than walls,
but I ain't never seen
one of 'em do that.
Well, you know, Jason?
He work out a lot.
He real strong.
All right, everybody!
Sookie needs her rest.
It's time for y'all to go now.
What the hell are y'all staring at?
You heard me. The sideshow's over. Get.
Let's go! Let's go.
We appreciate y'all coming out.
Love you all. Come on, let's go.
Let's go. Thank you.
That means you too.
Look, I get it.
But right now she needs to be alone.
If there's anything I can do,
you call me.
You're a good friend.
Now get the fuck out of here.
Please.
All right.
Don't make me throw you all out myself,
'cause you know I will.
I heard you.
What the fuck is it
with white people and Jell-O?
I don't understand.
What the hell are we gonna do
with all this?
Toss it.
Sookie don't need
no bad juju cooking.
Bad juju?
Way to a man's heart is through
his stomach. That shit true as gold.
You put some love in your food,
and the folk can taste it. Smell this.
You can smell the... fear and nastiness
coming off that corn bread.
Taste just fine to me.
See, bitch, you gonna wish
you ain't did that. Watch.
Maybe I should go
check on Sookie.
Trust me. That child is dead
to the world right now.
What the fuck?
What the hell are you doing?
Bill, what's wrong?
I thought...
I had a dream. That's all.
You go back to sleep. But I...
You don't worry.
I'm not going anywhere.
Go on.
Do you think they're capable
of loving a person?
Who knows what they're capable of?
Lord,
we gather here today to remember
the life of Adele Stackhouse.
To celebrate the time that
she enjoyed here on Earth.
And to thank you
for each precious moment...
Sookie, my hand.
Sorry. Sorry.
But even as we grieve,
we shall be comforted...
knowing that she is at peace
in the Lord's kingdom.
And there shall be
no more death.
Uncle Bartlett,
what are you doing here?
She was my sister.
You haven't been part
of this family in a long time.
Come on.
Give the guy a break.
Sookie Stackhouse
has prepared a few words.
Honey?
You wanted to say a few words?
Sookie, you okay?
"Adele Stackhouse was
"everything to me.
"She wasn't just my grandmother.
"She was
"my parent, my teacher
and my best friend."
Oh, please. If it weren't for you,
she'd still be alive.
Vampire giving a eulogy.
Thought she was a good girl.
Guess you never know.
You oughta be in that grave.
And you will be one...
Shame on you, we all know
To say she'll be missed...
just doesn't cut it 'cause...
I can even imagine a world
without her in it.
She was always there,
with a kind word
and a hot meal...
and a shoulder to cry on.
Not just for me, but...
Forgive me.
... everyone who knew her.
I never meant to hurt no one.
I couldn't...
Poor pathetic thing.
Just as nuts as nuts can be.
You're sleeping with her killer.
She's dead because of you.
Shut up!
All of you,
just shut the fuck up!
Look at her, cursing...
This whole world's
just plain crazy...
Oh my God, Sookie, oh my God.
That's a shame.
Is there anyone else who'd care
to share a few words?
I got something to say.
What is she doing?
No, Mama.
Oh, my fuckin' God, girl.
This is about to get ugly.
I didn't know Ms. Stackhouse
like a lot of you did.
But the few times I did meet her...
she was nothing but kind to me.
She was a good
God-fearing woman.
And when I was going
through some bad things...
my daughter would go stay with her.
And I always knew
she'd be just fine.
Adele Stackhouse took care
of my baby when I couldn't...
and I'll always be
grateful for that.
Just hold on for a sec.
Why? So you can hit me again?
Go ahead, tell me it's my fault.
Tell me how you wish
it were me in that coffin.
- I deserve it.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
- Don't touch me.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
- You gotta know that.
- You invited Uncle Bartlett!
- How could you do that?
- He has a right to be here!
Look, I know he and Gran
had their problems.
But wherever they were,
it don't matter no more.
'Cause that's what family does.
Always forgive each other.
You have no idea what
you're talking about.
Please.
I mean, we're all we've got.
We've got nothing.
I was moved.
Very moved.
You should come to our next Descendants
of the Glorious Dead meeting.
That some kind of
support group thing?
I went to one of those
AA meetings once.
It was nothing but a cult.
Hi, baby.
This is my precious daughter, Tara.
We've met like a hundred
times too many. Excuse us.
- The hell are you doing?
- Just talking to that nice lady.
Let go my arm.
You're hurting me!
Oh, I'm hurting you?
That's funny.
'Cause the last time I saw you, you
were beating my head in with a bottle.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
You poor child.
I am so sorry.
You have no right
to speak for that woman.
She was more of a mother
to me than you ever were.
She took care of me.
She fed me,
she put clothes on me.
She called Social Services
on you twice.
- You hated her guts.
- No.
- I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
You used to call her
a white devil bitch.
That wasn't me.
That wasn't me
that said those things.
'Cause you were
too drunk to remember
- don't mean it never happened.
- Please, baby.
Just listen.
All those terrible things
I did to you.
It wasn't me who did them.
I have a demon inside of me.
What?
A demon.
Living and breathing inside me.
Eating me up.
Don't you laugh
at the devil, Tara Mae.
'Cause he's as serious as cancer.
I'm sorry.
You have a demon inside you?
- Fuck me. That's too good.
- It ain't funny.
You have no idea
what I go through,
wrestling with this demon.
I try and do right.
I try so hard...
but it breaks me down.
It poisons everything.
I wanna be the mama
you deserve.
I can make up for everything.
I can. It's not to late.
But I can't do this alone.
Do what?
I got to get it out of me...
and it's very expensive.
And that's why you came
to this woman's funeral?
'Cause you want money?
I had nowhere else to go.
Tara, please.
Don't walk away
from me.
I am still your mama.
I need you!
You're all I've got.
I'm so sorry.
Sorry for you loss.
We're not done, Stackhouse.
What?
Oh, Lord.
Fuck!
Shit!
I was looking for you.
Well...
you found me.
I liked your speech.
What I heard of it, anyway.
Especially liked the part where you told
the whole town to shut the fuck up.
Yeah, I'm a real crowd pleaser.
I'll walk you home.
So how about you take a bath?
I'll find us some stupid movie on TV.
Something with aliens.
- Romantic comedy then?
- Sam, not now.
I just...
I need to be alone.
Thanks.
She said she wants to be alone.
Well, I don't.
Me either.
Won't ever give you enough
of this goddamn chicken.
Lady, I want the legs.
You piece of shit!
I'll fucking
kill you.
Don't worry.
She says that all the time.
Come on, you gotta admit,
it has a certain charm.
You live here?
You want a beer?
- They're warm.
- Yeah. Sure.
This is really where you live?
Yes, Sam.
This is really where I live.
You trying to make me feel bad?
No. It's just...
- Thought you lived with Lafayette.
- I was.
Do you know he has
a webcam in his bathroom?
No way I'm letting a bunch
of perverts watch me pee.
You should've told me
you needed somewhere to stay.
Why?
So you can ride up on
your white horse and save me?
- Why do you do that?
- Do what?
Try and turn everything
into a fight.
Why is it so hard to just let
someone be nice to you?
I don't know.
You think maybe I have
bad self-esteem.
Maybe it's the only way I know
how to express my real feelings.
- I should go.
- Would you relax?
- I was only teasing.
- Maybe I'm sick of being teased.
Stay!
- Please.
- What for?
'Cause I want you to.
I don't wanna play games.
I don't want no strings.
I just...
I want something real in my life.
And you think I don't?
If we do this...
we really did this.
- Holy shit.
- I'll take that as a compliment.
I guess I really
needed that.
Me too. Let's do it again.
- Come back.
- I had to baby. I'm sorry. I love you.
I love you too.
I need you. I need you
so fuckin' much...
I guess they made up.
Listen...
I gotta go.
What?
It's the middle of the night.
What just happened?
Did I do something?
It's not about you.
I'm sorry.
I'll see you at work, okay?
This feels so good!
Oh, God!
I love you.
Is...
Is something wrong?
Hi, Mama.
I knew you'd come.
Do it.
I want you to.