Don't take it personally.
The Were you were fighting
had vampire blood in him.
Bill's, in fact,
so I know it's strong.
Werewolves doing V?
Goes against everything
we stand for.
- The rest of the pack into that shit?
- The ones who took Bill, at least.
Like I need more reasons
to hate them.
Is Debbie your ex-girlfriend?
She's my fiancée.
She moved out a month ago.
A month?
And you still haven't got
new furniture?
I don't have time for it.
You ever hear from her?
My sister, Janice, does.
She runs a beauty parlor.
Debbie still goes in
to get her hair done up.
Almost done.
Are you hurt?
I know the werewolves have you.
Nobody has me.
I have left my life in Bon Temps.
And I am leaving you.
Shut the fuck up.
The last time I saw you,
you asked me to marry you.
You did us both a favor
by not saying yes.
You have to say that.
Someone's listening.
Lorena, actually,
to whom I have just made love.
Ça va, Sookie?
We fucked
like only two vampires can.
I didn't hold back
for fear of hurting her
like I do with you.
Look at your life
since I entered it.
I've only caused you pain.
That's not true.
I am death.
I will bring you only suffering.
Our worlds are too different.
Our natures too.
We were doomed from the start.
I don't believe you.
Believe what you want.
You are no longer of concern to me.
Do not try to find me.
I do not wish to be found.
What does he mean,
he doesn't wanna be found?
I'm pretty sure it means
he doesn't wanna see you anymore.
That isn't what he said.
- What do you think he said?
- I don't know what he said.
I just know that isn't
the man I love.
Maybe the man you love
never existed except in your head.
Is that supposed
to be making me feel better?
No matter how well
you think you know somebody,
they can still turn around
and kick you right in the nut sac.
I don't have a nut sac, and Bill...
he's risked everything for me.
Our love is way bigger
than him breaking up with me
over the phone.
How many relationships you been in?
What does that matter?
All I'm saying is there's no nice way
of getting out of these things.
Come here.
Oh, my God, you're so warm.
It's okay, I'm just not used to it.
It's a Were thing.
We run hot.
I thought maybe
you were coming down with the flu.
You probably want some privacy.
That's the last thing I want.
At least let me go put on a shirt.
Get back here, you little shit!
Were you sleeping in my parking lot?
We hadn't left yet because...
well...
we got nowhere to go.
We're a little behind in rent.
Plus, our landlord
got foreclosed on.
That's why you came here.
To eat my food and steal from me.
Tommy tried to break into my safe.
Shit.
Sometimes I think that boy's cheese
done slid right off his cracker.
He does desperate things
when we fall on hard times.
When you fall?
How often does this happen?
I don't wanna know.
This is not my problem.
I know it ain't.
Just please
don't take it out on Tommy.
- What happened now?
- No one's hurt.
Sam caught Tommy stealing.
Oh, that boy makes my ass itch.
I ain't asking for your sympathy.
I can't have you living
in my parking lot.
No, we'll be gone
the second he gets back.
He's just off somewhere
being himself up.
Won't be long.
It better not be.
Tell me everything you know
about Bill and Sookie.
She says it was love at first sight.
- You don't believe that?
- In love?
Hell, no.
People just get what they want
and leave.
And what does Sookie want?
Quiet.
Being a telepath gets real noisy,
and she can't hear Bill.
Her brother, is he a telepath too?
Jason barely knows
what he's thinking,
let alone anyone else.
If you keep smiling like that,
I'm gonna get jealous.
I thought I loved him
for a long time
but he never loved me back.
Then he is an idiot.
- Where is Sookie now?
- Jackson, Mississippi.
- Where in Jackson?
- I don't know.
Find out.
You sound awful.
Bill...
broke up with me.
Oh, my God.
What an asshole.
Tell me where you are.
I'm coming to get you.
No, I just need to cry my eyes out
for about a week.
What you need
is your best friend, right now.
Give me your address.
After all you've been through?
I don't want you
getting mixed up in my mess.
You'd do it for me. I'm getting
in the car right now.
Address.
I'm exhausted.
I'll call you tomorrow, I promise.
What do you want from Sookie?
You should be more concerned
with what I want from you.
Let me go.
Not gonna happen.
That was the best sex
I've had in decades.
At least somebody enjoyed it.
There was true passion
between you and I tonight.
Any passion you felt was me
killing my love for Sookie.
It had nothing to do with you.
It's been a long night,
and I need to sleep.
Now get the fuck out.
I'm happy.
You're with me.
And you're not going anywhere.
Even if it takes 40 years,
I know you will love me again.
You can't help but love.
Cheese and rice.
You scared me half to death.
- What the hell are you doing out there?
- Waiting for you to invite me in.
Can all vampires fly?
Can all humans sing?
Are you kidding?
Couldn't carry a tune
in a bucket with a lid on it.
Come on in.
How goes the search?
Turns out,
he's not who I was looking for.
You smell like the ocean in winter.
How is that possible?
Bill doesn't smell like anything.
That's not possible.
You played by the North Sea
as a child.
How did you know?
I'm smelling your memories.
Not even you can do that.
I got skills you can't even dream of,
cowboy.
You want more?
Or I boring you?
That'll be all.
... The Vampire Rights
Amendment's impending passing
has left many up in arms,
but perhaps none so much...
What time you wanna head back
to Bon Temps?
Since you're not looking
for that asshole anymore.
I still plan on finding him.
Okay, doormat.
I'm not a doormat.
I just want him to say it
to my face.
- What, he didn't hurt you enough?
- I think he's in trouble.
Maybe I'm wrong, but if he can
look me and tell me it's over,
then I'll leave him.
You looking for closure?
Just let it go, move on.
Says the man cooking in a wok
because he's too sad
to buy a new frying pan.
I need more information.
Take me to that engagement party.
No fucking way.
I paid my debt.
I know you're still
hurting over Debbie.
Seeing her with those creeps
might help you get over her.
Are you insane?
Either one of us showing up
after last night
is just asking to get
our asses kicked.
You go if you gotta.
Don't put your shit on me.
Ring, ring, hooker.
Ring, ring.
Now, I know
you holing up at Sookie's,
but long story short,
I gots me a six-figure bucket seat
cradling my black ass
right the fuck now.
And you got yourself my old ride.
That's right, Buddha done did us
a 180, he did.
Now, why don't you calls
a motherfucker back, please?
Shit.
You must be Janice.
And you're Sookie Stackhouse?
Thank you, Jesus.
I'd have settled
for a two-bit hooker
to get my brother's mind off
that bitch Debbie Pelt,
but you are cute
and sweet.
You're just what he needs.
Thanks for coming over.
When you called,
I was checking my horoscope.
Do you know what it said?
"Things are looking up
for somebody close to you."
Nailed it.
Don't get too excited.
Alcide and I are just working together.
You don't look like
you work construction to me.
Someone I care about's gone missing,
and Alcide...
has inside information
about the folks I think have him.
I called you because I need to get
into Lou Pine's without standing out.
You need to look the part.
Well, that is my specialty.
How deep do you wanna go?
I wanna look like
I could kick some serious ass.
Which I can.
All right, let's pick out
some temporary tattoos.
No chance of anything more
between you and my baby brother?
I'm not really looking,
and he's still hung up on his ex.
Finding out about her engagement party
did not help matters.
Yeah, right, engagement party.
Excuse me?
No, right. That's right,
engagement party.
That bitch Debbie's getting herself
initiated into
that nasty pack of freaks.
- How did Al find out about it?
- Hollis told him last night.
Fucking Hollis and his big mouth.
I'm glad he didn't say nothing
about her being hooked on V.
But if Alcide still loves Debbie
don't you think he should go
and try to...
- talk her out of it?
- No, he should not.
My psychic told him if he stayed
with her, he would get himself killed.
Did he listen? No.
She ended up dumping his ass.
Why'd he stay with her so long?
She was his first love,
he never met anybody so alive,
all that shit.
But how many bullets
are you gonna take for somebody?
How many bad things gotta happen
to you and the ones you love
before you realize
feeling alive ain't enough?
I am just glad he made it out alive.
Arlene, what's happening, baby?
I'm trying to buy my crew here a round
after a long day.
A long day?
It's lunch, okay?
And I'm the only waitress working,
as usual.
You'll get your beer
when you get it.
Where's she takin' it?
Right here.
QB 1 gets the first beer.
Who's that cocky little shit?
You're mad
because he's about to break
your passing record.
He's close.
Say he's got the best arm
of any kid in Bon Temps since...
Well, since you.
What's his name?
Kitch Maynard.
Don't even think
about finishing that pitcher.
Fucking winning name.
Get on up here, Bud.
Get up here, young man.
I'm gonna keep it short.
Everything I learned
about being a good cop,
I learned from you.
You always been a hell
of a sheriff, Bud,
and I'm gonna miss you.
Kevin.
We figured, since you hung up
your hat for good,
it's time
you put on your new dancing shoes.
Thank you.
They're beautiful.
It's been a great honor
serving this community.
And it's an even greater honor
having served with such fine men.
And woman.
And it is in that spirit
that I announce to you
your new acting sheriff...
That's how you drink a beer.
That's a surprise.
And a hell of an honor.
It's Kitch, right?
Around here they call me QB 1.
But you probably can't remember that
far back, can you?
- What's your name?
- Tammy.
You are smoking.
You got all them dimples.
I'd have made out with you,
but unfortunately for you,
you're with a disrespectful
fucktard...
... who's causing a ruckus
when a fine, upstanding citizen
is getting all commemorated.
You think you're a rock star,
don't you?
World at your feet,
folks serving you beer underage.
Girls sucking your cock whenever
you say go. No offense, Tammy.
You ain't nothing, boy.
You'll find that out soon enough.
Yeah, well, come end of season,
they'll be shouting my name,
and they'll forget you ever existed.
But 10 years from now,
there's gonna be a version of you,
10 years younger,
doing the same thing to you.
And then who you gonna be?
What?
Yeah, that's right.
You heard me.
Touchdown.
Well, I guess the only way
to get a promotion in this town
is to drink like a fish,
hallucinate farm animals,
and kill a black man.
Promotion.
Pig!
- Here, let me help you.
- God, you wanna help me?
How about doing your job, boss?
Right now I'm a hostess,
waitress, bartender,
busboy,
because everybody you hire
comes to work whenever they fucking feel
like it or ends up dead.
And I've got enough
on my plate without...
I'll get someone else in here
soon enough, okay?
You have got to start looking
out for your own, Sam.
In here.
I guess my sister took to you.
Debbie's getting initiated into
Coot's pack, and she's addicted to V.
Shut the fucking door.
Debbie's a bloodhead?
How'd you find out?
I was poking around
in Janice's brain.
She didn't tell you
because she's trying to protect you.
- Why don't you let her?
- Because I know you care about Debbie.
No matter what she did to you.
You'd wanna know if she were in danger.
She's gonna let
those fucking mongrels brand her.
- V's the only reason. It's gotta be.
- Of course it is.
Maybe it's not too late
for you to get through to her.
Stop her from ruining her life.
Fuck!
That mean you're coming with me?
I probably won't get in otherwise.
Fine.
We're gonna have to go
in separate, though.
You might be able to fool some
with that getup.
They're just gonna
beat the shit out of me, again.
How long did you work
for Sophie Anne?
- Thirty-five years.
- As?
I was a procurer.
Were you any good?
I received no complaints.
And then you started sampling
the local flavor in Bon Temps.
I was on sabbatical.
Well, now you're
playing coy, William.
So which is it you doubt,
my intentions
or my power?
Can you assure me that you will be able
to usurp her territory?
That depends
on the quality of your information,
now, doesn't it?
I insist.
"A woman
"is only a woman,
"but a good cigar
"is a smoke."
Rudyard Kipling.
No Shakespeare, but less impetuous.
And he never stole spoons.
Your Majesty,
if I am going to sign
my own death warrant
I will need something in return.
When I have fulfilled my duties,
I want Lorena gone.
Gone?
It is a punishable offense
to kill another vampire.
Not if no one reports it.
Eric Northman,
the queen's sheriff of Area 5,
has been selling vampire blood,
and I believe it is at her behest.
If the Magister finds out,
he'll put her on trial.
He's been itching
for another inquisition for centuries.
Why on earth would she be so stupid?
The Great Revelation.
She's close to losing her fortune
now that we're being taxed by the IRS.
Tug on the purse strings,
you'll find a lady's heart.
That's very nice, Bill.
Very nice.
I feel like celebrating.
Missed you.
You miss me?
Did you miss me?
I can't stop thinking about you.
Something about you is just so...
What's the word?
Motherfucker.
Magical.
We have so much ahead of us.
When people come in, first thing,
count how many of them there are.
More than two always gets a table,
never the bar.
So say there's three.
Pull out one, two, three menus
and walk them to their table.
What about the waitressing part?
You gotta be 18 to serve alcohol.
That is so not fair.
I'm never gonna be 18.
I used to be the best server
at our church pancake night.
- Think you can handle it?
- I'm a vampire, not a fucking idiot.
Hi, welcome to Merlotte's.
Table 5's available.
If you'll just follow me
right this way.
A hostess ain't gonna help me
with my workload.
And she sure as heck ain't
helping herself to my tips.
Calm down.
I put an ad for another waitress.
No one said anything
about Jessica getting tips.
People love giving redheads tips.
And I've always been
the only redhead at Merlotte's, Sam.
You know that.
Sorry.
I get a little emotional when I'm...
When I see people
taking advantage of you.
What are you talking about?
You let in every stray, Sam.
First that old dog,
and then your folks,
and now Jessica.
I mean, it's your business.
It's not a charity.
I can take care of myself.
My folks won't be
coming around anymore.
You sure they know that?
They're grilling in the parking lot.
One thing's for sure:
we'll never be as bad
of parents as they are.
Your server will
be right with you, all right?
- Excuse me.
- Sorry.
- No, you've got me confused, I think.
- Jessica, it's Chip from Bible study.
Hi. Oh, my God.
I can't believe you're alive.
Your folks are gonna be so happy.
- My God, it's a miracle.
- Yeah, I guess so.
Praise Jesus. Praise him.
You shitting me?
My little brother
just got busted dealing dope.
You won't find a better product.
- You a cop?
- No, sir.
I know your boy's a lean,
mean selling machine.
I'm just here to up your game.
Help you step up in the world,
clean some shit up.
I'll go grab the Dirt Devil
from Felton.
- See if he's hungry too.
- I ain't his mama.
What do you say?
You feel me?
Nothing this hot
will cost you this little
and earn you so much.
We're not getting in business
with people like you.
People like me?
- Look...
- No, you look, son.
Polite's in short supply around here.
It's time you get your ass home.
Ain't you pretty, princess?
- Get the fuck up out my ride.
- How about no?
- How about I whup your fucking ass?
- Faggot.
I told you we ain't
so polite around here.
How'd you end up
in Bon Temps tonight?
I was just on my way home
back from picketing
the baby-killer factory
up in Birmingham.
Stopped for a bite.
You wanted to stop for a bite
but you decided it was too late,
so you drove straight home.
It is late.
Then you got a little lost
on the 165,
and that's why you got home
a little late
and a little hungry.
And you never even saw me.
I hate being hungry before bed.
Take that.
Get your fucking hands off me,
dead man.
- Take the deal.
- You'll have to kill me first.
I think I'll kill
all your brother-cousins first.
- How does that sound, Lafayette?
- That sounds good.
- Excellent.
- We'll sell.
Just let me fucking go.
And that's called closing the deal.
Let's go, RuPaul.
Get the fuck up out of here.
What do you want
with Sookie and Bill?
Nothing.
My employer's interested in them.
Him, mostly.
That where we're going?
To your employer?
"Slappy's Snack Shack, five miles.
Persimmons and cherries."
If there is one thing
that I miss more than sunshine,
it is good fruit.
Where are you taking me?
Here I am trying to make
pleasant conversation,
and you wanna ruin all my surprises.
There ain't nothing pleasant
about being bitten and tied up.
You're tough.
I could taste it in your blood.
I'm not a bad guy, Tara.
I just wanna make sure
that we have a chance.
Untie my hands.
I'll give you whatever chance you want.
Are you like this
with your other boyfriends?
This is kidnapping.
This is opportunity.
My job supports my financial needs.
My emotional ones.
It's just there's so much
I wanna tell you.
Then tell me where we're going.
I've been so lonely.
But now you're mine...
all that's changed.
I figured the sooner you left Bon Temps,
the happier you'd be.
Unless you plan
on stealing from me more.
You don't know shit about me.
I know you got
a pretty raw deal with your folks.
I know you think I got off easy.
Why'd you even look us up, anyway?
When I was your age...
I had no example.
And everything I did...
Shit that was worse
than stealing, by the way.
... I did blind.
And I survived,
but it caught up with me so bad,
sometimes I wished I hadn't.
Guess I wanted to see
how different it could have been.
And now that you have?
I see that I can't get back
what I lost.
But you're still young,
and you don't have to make
the same mistakes.
And you could stay with me.
- I could set you up at the bar.
- You don't get it.
My folks are fucked up,
but they can't get by without me.
Now, I know it feels like that,
but they're not your problem.
That's all they are.
I ditch them tomorrow,
they end up in the gutter
by the end of next week.
You think I can live with that?
I won't be free of these people
until the day they die.
I have to say
I'm a little disappointed, Lafayette.
I pegged you as a professional,
but clearly, you lack
the necessary artistry.
Bossman, have you seen this face?
It ain't nothing but art.
You walk into every situation
all flash and fire.
You expect them to adapt to you.
That's not salesmanship.
It's ego.
- What?
- We're being raided.
That is the Magister.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
Magister.
What a pleasant surprise.
There's nothing pleasant about this.
This...
is blasphemy.
Take her.
I know I ain't got no fangs,
and I know I can't talk
whatever language
that is you talk in,
but I can move your shit.
Oh, hell.
How am I supposed to deal
with this fucked-up-ness?
I wanna be a cop.
A real one.
- That's good, Stackhouse.
- I've been old Jason long enough.
Apply yourself like I told you.
Someday you might make a good one.
No, I don't think you're hearing me.
You see, I'm not doing
them fake ride-alongs
and filling out forms.
I'm thinking
there's gotta be an easier way.
You've been thinking
that way your whole life, Stackhouse.
Where's it gotten you?
You're gonna make me a cop,
and you're gonna make me one now.
Even if I wanted to, I couldn't.
There's rules.
There any rules
about taking
TV interviews and promotions
for not shooting a killer dead
when I'm the one who's gotta
live with doing it?
Any rules about that?
I push this, it'll blow up
for the both of us.
You know, I read something
in all that cop homework
about when you make up stories
about murderers and crimes.
What do they call that again?
Falsifying evidence.
Falsifying the evidence.
Last few days,
shooting a known killer,
tackling a drug dealer in Hotshot.
I'm already the best cop you got,
Sheriff Andy Bellefleur.
Shit.
These dogs plumping up real good.
There you are.
Boy, I'll whup you.
Now, here's what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna give you a place to stay
for now
till you get back on your feet.
No more stealing,
no more drinking,
- or the deal's off.
- I think we can manage that.
Don't see why not.
Think you can fly
straight from now on?
Supposed to be a joke.
Maybe I can.
- Not you.
- Russell's expecting me.
He's out.
He'll be a while.
We'll wait.
Is this for me?
It's skinny.
It's a private party.
Hollis ain't here.
We're on our own.
- Shoot it.
- No, thanks.
She looks familiar.
Did I bang her?
Fuck, yeah!
- Again.
One more.
Third time's the charm.
Who the fuck are you?
She's with me, Debbie.
In the mood for anything
in particular?
Someone smoky.
Not too fatty.
See, I was thinking...
ethnic.
You said you were a procurer?
Procure.
As you wish.
Let her go!
I am who you want.
But I have been framed.
"You've got the wrong man."
"My dog ate my homework."
"I saw Goody Osburn with the devil."
Excuses are one thing I can assure you
do not get better with age.
Do you deny the blood was being sold
in your area?
Not on my orders.
Then on whose?
Your queen's?
What shall it be, sheriff?
Desecration of the blood
or treason against your regent?
Both among the most dire of crimes.
It was Bill Compton!
It's true. He's gone missing.
You've seen yourself how easily
he betrays our kind for personal gain.
I believe he is behind this,
and I am gathering evidence
to bring him to you.
Now let me finish my work.
They say the loss of a child
is the deepest of despair.
Two days, Mr. Northman,
or she dies.
A true death.
You thought this
knight-on-a-white-horse shit would work?
- With me?
- What have you done to yourself?
I finally got free of you.
And I never been happier in my life.
I still care about you.
- The pack will never let you back in.
- I don't need your pussy pack.
And I was fucking Coot
when I was still with you.
- This isn't about us.
- Like hell.
You came here and brought this skank
just to make me jealous.
Skank?
Well, coming from you,
that's just funny.
You did not just say that to me
at my own fucking party.
Alcide came here despite
every good reason in the world not to
because he believes
the woman he fell in love with
still lives inside you somewhere.
He's willing to risk his life
to make sure you hold on to her,
even if he doesn't get to.
It isn't too late.
We can get out of here right now.
What the fuck is this?
- It's just a conversation, Coot.
- She's all done with you, Herveaux.
She went and found herself
a real wolf.
Come on.
Let's do this shit!
Leave him alone, Coot.
- Let him stay.
- No way in hell.
He needs to see this.
He ain't never gonna let us b baby,
till he understands
I'm with you for good.
He's one of the ones who took Bill.
I have...
an errand to attend to.
If I'm not back before Mr. Compton
returns with our dinner,
you feel free to start without me.
Who's that?
Russell Edgington.
He's a rich antiques dealer here.
What's a vampire doing
in a wolf den?
Why are they submitting
to this fanger?
He supplies them.
Holy shit.
Not tonight, pumpkin.
Otherwise
your brand don't last.
Tonight...
you continue the grand tradition
of expanding our pack.
My contribution
is but a small token of gratitude
for our collaboration
throughout the ages.
The ages?
Drink.
I leave you amongst your own
to celebrate.
All yours.
- Shy?
- Perhaps.
I'll take good care of you.
- What's your name?
- Destiny.
What is your real name?
Camilla.
What is your name?
Ann.
What does your husband think
about your profession?
- No husband.
- Children?
Never wanted any.
World's too fucked up.
- And your family?
- Told me I wasn't worth nothing.
- I figured they ain't worth knowing.
- Perhaps you're right about that.
No point anyway.
What?
Loving anyone,
anything.
Feels good at first,
but it always turns to crap.
I know the truth about life.
It's a hell I'll never
get out of alive.
No one does.
Debbie, you dumb bitch.
This is so fucking wrong.
What's happening?
Are they all shifting?
You need to get out of here.
Sookie, run. Run!
What have we got here?
So, what kind of party we having?
- Ladies first.
- Why, thank you, Russell.
Please join us.