Hey,who doesn't love a guy who lives in danger?
"Then again,the dangers we perceive
aren't often the real ones."
Take our local fireman,tony vera.
The guy on the boardwalk.
"Last time he burned himself
it was taking a chicken out of the oven."
"But when he coats his mouth
with that lighter fluid?"
"Every slug that he ingests,every accidental nip
eats away a little more of his liver."
Or take my job.
"Jealous husbands with switchblades,
crackheads with semi-automatics."
Does that sound perilous?
"In the entire lapd,we had one cop killed
in the line of duty last year."
And only one the year before.
Well,we did have 13 suicides,though.
Shame they don't make kevlar for the things we see.
are you thinking about killing yourself?
Detective?
Yeah.
I asked you a question.
You mentioned suicide,I've gotta ask.
Are you thinking about killing yourself?
Every time I walk in this office.
I'm not thinking of killing myself.
All right.
You also mentioned kevlar for the things you see.
Were you referring to the vests?
Well,I didn't mean the canoes.
"These things you experience,that you see,
you think that they're harmful?"
Maybe. I don't know.
Why don't you tell me about the case?
I thought you knew about the case.
You said you saw it on the news.
Then why don't you tell me?
We found the body of a ten-year-old girl.
She'd been stuffed into a duffel bag.
Kt? What do we got?
Petechial hemorrhaging,for one.
Strangulation?
No facial congestion,or neck contusions.
Broken neck?
That's my guess.
she's missing two buttons.
and a third is unbuttoned.
"You think her mother let her
leave the house that way?"
- Boyer.
- Yeah?
We need to throw up a tent.
You worried about the gulls?
"No,we need to remove the victim's clothes,
and run a rape kit."
She can't be more than ten years old.
I'm gonna need the keys to your patrol car.
- Boyer?
- Yeah?
The keys to your patrol car!
have you figured out who did it yet?
No,not yet.
How about now?
You're not very good with kids,are you?
Raines.
"Adam 9 just called in a missing person's report
on a ten-year-old south of rose."
We're uploading it to the cws database now.
Give me the highlights.
Emily strong,4'2",red hair,light brown eyes.
What was she wearing?
Pink ruffled top and denim capris.
Yeah,that's her.
Uh,you got an address?
1892 indiana court.
It should be up on the cws by now.
Thanks.
so I have a name.
emily.
Your name is emily.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-jarfar
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Raines
Season 01 Episode 06
Yeah,he's with him now.
I gotta call you back.
Detective.
Bruce.
What do you know?
"Girl went to westley,had an early dismissal today,
mother had no idea."
She walk to school?
"Westley let out at 1:00,
mom didn't realize she was missing till 3:00."
I wanna know why you are not looking for my daughter.
We told you everything we know.
That's the father,he just came home.
You need backup in there?
You wanna tell him his daughter's dead,be my guest.
I... I have to... oh,my god.
I--I can'T...
I can't believe...
mr.Strong... henry.
Why--why wouldn't she have told us she had a half day?
Henry,I know this is difficult,
but we need to focus on finding out who did this,
and on bringing that person to justice.
- Any--anything you need.
- Thank you.
I'm gonna need to ask you a few que--
detective?
Yeah,just a few questions.
Hasn't he been through enough?
It's standard procedure.
Go ahead.
When was the last time you saw emily?
- This... this morning,before I went to work.
- And you were at work all day?
- Yes,until judy called.
- You didn't go out for lunch?
- No,I ate at my--
- why are you asking him these questions?
Could emily play the piano?
What?
The piano,can she play?
She was just starting to learn.
"Excuse me,were you just suggesting
that I might have killed--?"
A young victim in these circumstances,
chances are she knew her attacker,which is why--
I'm sorry. Under what circumstances?
We think your that daughter might
have been sexually assaulted before she was killed.
- Henry
- I told you,I was at work all day.
Do you mind if I,ah,look around?
That wasn't very nice.
I had to gauge his reaction.
"His reaction to the fact that
I might have been assaulted before I was killed?"
Hey,why don't you go play with your dolls?
Want to do that?
I'm tired of my dolls.
What's assault?
None of your beeswax.
Fine.
You like nancy drew?
Never read any.
Really? She's a schoolgirl detective.
I bet she could solve my murder.
I was just starting to learn that song.
My dad was gonna play it with me.
Lucky him.
Hey,maybe you could play it with me.
Ugh,maybe not.
Why are you so cranky?
Why are you so annoying?
I don't know.
Maybe it's easier if I'm annoying.
Easier?
You know,to deal with the fact that I was murdered.
That I'm dead for no good reason.
Okay,isn't there--?
There's got to be something in here to keep you busy.
I could play with my computer.
There you go.
"I mean,there's so much to do,
so many people to talk to."
I just love im,don't you?
Who were you chatting with,emily?
Something wrong?
No.
Don't you want to know who I'm iming?
Wait a minute. You can'T...
im without an e-mail account.
she had an e-mail account.
Henry was so protective.
He didn't want her to have it.
I tried to read everything.
She only e-mailed with a few other girls.
Can you show me her account?
judy!
Judy!
Henry?
The tobmans called. Grace,she told them...
"she told them she and emily
lied about the early dismissal."
Grace,that's one of emily's school friends?
Grace tobman.
They snuck down to the beach.
Henry,where are you going?
You don't want to go outside.
- I need to talk to her.
- No,that's not such a good idea.
I have to do this!
I have to do something.
No,please--  He's taking no questions.
Don't answer any questions. No questions.
Uh,henry,listen to me,
the best thing you can do right now
is to sit down and start working
on a list of adults who knew emily.
- You don't understand.
- I do understand,henry.
But you gotta let me do my job.
Uh,could you give me the tobmans' number? Please.
"And if you could jot down emily's,
uh,e-mail address and password."
- You don't think that--?
- No,no,I'm just being thorough.
you don't want to tell her that 65% of
sexual solicitations occur through im and chat?
What exactly is a sexual solicitation anyway?
- Lance.
- It's raines.
"Yeah,the media's all over this,
so I'm gonna call the family of the little girl
who last saw emily,send her in."
"Make sure there's somebody there
to roll out the welcome wagon."
Yeah,no problem.
Great. While I've got you,
I'm gonna need a background check
on emily strong's buddy list and e-mail address book.
You got a login and a password?
Estrong@friendpost.Net
Password is lion tamer.
As in siegfried?
Uh,I'm guessing that's not who she had in mind,but yeah.
Is that raines?
Boyer wants to talk to you.
Boyer? Really? What,is it my birthday?
Hey,detective.
"Listen,I'm making a list of suspects
from the N.E.C.S.Database."
"Now,I figured I'd target sex offenders
that live in the strongs' neighborhood."
You're taking initiative? Really?
Is this remi boyer?
Should I be targeting them by crime?
I don't want you to strain anything.
Rape? Sodomy?
Yeah,sure. Anything with a child victim.
And make sure to include guys convicted of se--
hold on,one second.
Shouldn't you be in the back seat?
It's my car. And my head.
Fine.
Uh,yeah. Make sure to include guys convicted of...
"of,um,Sexual abuse or lewd and
lascivious acts with a child."
What?
Sexual abuse or lewd and lascivious acts with a child.
Why were you whispering?
Because it's easier if I think that you can't hear.
Which I guess sounds pretty stupid,doesn't it?
No stupider than making me sit in the back seat.
That's correct.
"If I'm so innocent,
what was I doing sneaking down to the beach?"
mr.Tobman,this is michael raines.
He's the detective working the case.
- Is grace here?
- In my office.
- Mr.Tobman,please
- uh,detective?
"Before we called the strongs,we were pretty angry
with grace,there was a lot of yelling..."
you haven't told grace yet.
- We didn't want,on the heels of all that
- of course.
grace,this is detective raines.
***
Uh,grace?
Try a little less big and scary.
Yeah.
grace,um,just need to talk to you a little bit.
I need to know what happened.
Yeah?
It's okay,baby.
We wanted to go to the ballet store.
ballet store?
Oh,the one next to the paddle tennis courts?
And walk on the boardwalk.
she loves the boardwalk.
I like the boardwalk too.
Um,so you were on the boardwalk with emily?
We were watching one of the performers.
"But then,emily wasn't there
and I thought she'd gone home so..."
so I did too.
did something bad happen to emily?
Detective?
"Uh,grace,what were you watching when,
uh,emily disappeared?"
Thank you,thank you.Thank you
Hey,don't forget,man,do not try this at home.
I used to be a white dude.
Wow,$20,man,thanks.
So what can I do for you,detective?
Uh,does she look familiar?
"Is that the little girl
they found in the kids' playground?"
Yeah,her friend said she was here at your show today.
Might have been 2:00,2:30?
We think she might have been assaulted.
In my show?
You mean someone was messing with her at my show?
Well,that sicko's been back again,you know?
Oh,that guy that you,uh,ided last year?
Yeah,that scrawny little bastard.
"The one who was messing with kids at my show,
feeling them up."
He's been hanging around again?
Yeah. I saw him last week.
"I mean,I would've chased after him,
but I was juggling four torches and a bowling ball,you know?"
Been there.
What was his name? Do you remember?
I don't know,but I'm pretty sure you guys got it down.
Yeah,I'll bet.
- Tony,thank you,baby.
- Well,thank you,man.
Just try to go easy on the sauce.
Oh,I will. Thanks for the $20,detective.
I'll pay you back,man.
- You will not.
- I'm serious,man. I'll pay you back,man.
- I love you,tony vera.
- I love you more.
I'll pay you back every dime. Every dime,man.
what's this?
"It's the coroner's report,
and the original tony vera complaint."
The cops couldn't substantiate tony's claim at the time,
but charlie newman,the guy he ided?
"He had a prior for solicitation of a minor,
so we're bringing him in."
- We got a rap sheet on mr.Newman?
- Yeah.
"You know,I can head over to the strongs,
finish up the interview,if you're stuck here."
Really,what did you put on your wheaties this morning?
Nothing. Just doing my job.
Yeah,that's what's so surprising.
This vaginal bruising pretty much confirms sexual assault.
"And they think they may get a dna sample off the pubic hair,"
but,I mean,she didn't have any,
- so they figure the guy
- listen,I can read.
Sexual assault,that's like rape?
Why would someone do that?
I'm ten years old.
Why would god let someone do that?
" we got the guy from
the vera complaint in interrogation."
Charlie newman.
You need a minute?
Yeah,thanks.Yeah.
detective? You didn't answer my question.
Are we ever gonna talk about what happened to me?
Sure.
No,we're not.
You're a ten-year-old figment of my imagination.
So it's difficult?
Difficult,very difficult.
Detective,I don't exist.
You just said so yourself.
That's right.
So it's not me you're avoiding.
Why can't you face this?
Because!
"When you asked me two minutes ago why somebody would
rape and murder a ten-year-old girl,that was me asking."
Don't you get that?
"And because I don't know
why somebody would do that to you."
I don't know why god would let somebody do that to you.
And because...
because you don't know if you can do this anymore.
"Did you wonder about that
when you had the other victims in your head?"
Absolutely,sure.
You know you didn'T.
Okay,little miss wisey pants,no,I didn'T.
I didn't,'cause they were older.
You know my partner,charlie?
"Yeah,it sad and it's tragic that he's dead,
that his son jack is gonna grow up without a father."
But at least he lived long enough to have a son.
And you? All you had was an american girl doll.
- That's sad.
- Well sure,sweetie,isn't it?
The other victims.
They helped you solve their cases.
Detective,how can I help you?
"Unless you read a nancy drew mystery where she
solves a child rape murder,I don't think you can."
Here,here's how you can help me.
"I'm about to go in and interrogate a possible suspect,
a convicted pedophile."
What's a pedophile?
Like that. Don't-- don't--
that's what I can't have you do.
"When I go in there,I can't have you be asking questions
and interfering with my interrogation."
I gotta focus.
So could you stay out here while I'm there?
That's how you can help.
It's your head,detective.
Just stop thinking about me.
"If you haven't noticed,I don't exactly
have complete control over my delightful imagination."
You should talk to someone about that.
Yeah,thank you.
Could you do that,please? I'm asking nicely.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- On one condition.
Ultimatums?
"When we're done with my case,
we'll play the song I was learning."
You know how I feel about that song.
I'll teach you one note samba.
- detective!
- Yeah?
- You ready?
- Here I come.
well hello,mr.Charlie newman.
Mr.Charles newman,I'm detective raines.
Thank you very,very much for coming in.
Are you nervous about something?
No.
'Cause really,charlie-- can I call you charlie?
Man,there's nothing to be nervous about.
Everybody's got a thing,you know?
I can sympathize.
Hey,I like...
I like younger women.
Maybe not quite as young as you,but,you know,19,18.
French.
You know,a one piece.
Preferably a nice riviera tan.
And sure,there are people,charlie,
I don't know them personally,
but I'm told there are people who think that...
I'm too old?
That it's disgusting.
Can you imagine?
Are you with me? But you know what I say?
I say screw 'em.
Screw them and their,frankly,uh,bourgeois sensibility.
Their protestant moral code.
That's what I say.
How about you,charlie? What do you say?
"I say I'm tired of getting hauled in here
every time a little girl is molested."
Did I mention that a little girl was molested?
"No,but every time one is,you pull my name up
on the database and you bring me in."
Charlie,that's what you get for molesting little girls.
She was standing on a street corner.
She looked like she was 22.
I make one mistake,and I'm marked for life.
"And thanks to that damn megan's law,
it's out there for all the world to see."
"Do you know how many times I've had to move
because of uptight landlords and crazy vigilantes?"
Welcome to los angeles.
over here.
Thank you very much for staying out here.
I was just trying to help.
I lied before.
"When I was your age,the hardy boys,
I was really into it."
"I read every single one,then one day I got kind of curious
about the girl detective,so I read nancy drew."
And I liked it very much.
I know.
Do you think he did it?
Charlie newman?
"Well we're checking out his alibi,
but no history of violence,no prior contact with you..."
detective,we don't have any other leads.
No,we don'T.
What if we don't find him?
What if we don't find the guy who did this to me?
- Hey.
How's the investigation?
Oh,the investigation is swell.
"no witnesses,nothing from the scene,
no prints on the duffel."
It was canvas?
Mm-hmm,and the tobman lead,dead end.
How about the emails?
"One of the addresses in her address book was
bounced off another site,raised a red flag with the isp."
- Which means?
- I have no idea.
Lance is tracking that down?
Okay.
All right.
" Tomorrow morning,I want to go public
with the fact that she was assaulted."
Oh.
"Hang on,we haven't canvassed the neighbors,
talked to her teachers--"
yeah,but you know what?
I've have half the city breathing down my neck.
"We're working off a database of what,
500 recent offenders?"
If there's a nervous witness out there...
yay,collect calls from half the nuts in venice.
"It's gonna be like our very own red carpet
show for the megalomaniacally insane."
- Michael.
- Its gonna traumatize the family.
Which is why you'll run it by them first.
I'd be happy to send lance.
Or boyer.
CA Sex Offemder Database
how do you protect them?
How do you...?
God.I mean,we could have moved.
Where?
She loved the beach.We all did.
I mean,what was I supposed to do?
You alarm the house.
Check on her at night. You hold her hand.
"And one day,she decides
she's old enough to walk to school alone."
"I mean,it's only five blocks,
and so you think about it,you say no."
And then after six months of crying,
and carrying on and drama,you say yes.
You say yes.
"All the time,you have no idea
that this is living all around you."
You've confirmed it,haven't you?
She was molested.
henry...
"we think it would be best
for the investigation if we told the public."
Excuse me?
"Yeah,often,um,if the public hears
that a young child has been,uh,"
harmed in this way,they react strongly.Helpfully.
Reluctant witnesses become less reluctant.
I haven't told judy yet.
Let me tell judy.
We have to find him.
Maybe you should take a break.
Why?
We could play the song.
Ugh,we haven't solved the case yet.
"And,uh,I don't think my neighbors
would appreciate being serenaded at this hour."
Can I play?
- They won't hear me.
- I will.
These are cool.
Thank you.
You have a lot of toys.
"Do you think it's
because you didn't have any as a kid?"
isn't it past your bedtime?
Isn't it past your bedtime?
Why don't you have any kids?
'Cause they irritate me.
'Cause I didn't have time.
"Cause I didn't wanna,uh,
lose another argument with my ex-wife."
Seeing me makes you regret not having kids,doesn't it?
There were 800,000 kids kidnapped in the U.S.Last year.
"Sure,only 50 were killed,
but that's still one a week."
"And all those parents' lives,
they're ruined and destroyed"
"because the thing they love most
in the world is gone forever."
Or so I imagine.
You know,even my wonderful imagination has limits.
What your parents are going through now...
I-- I--I don't know.
I don't know.
"It's a dark gray ocean
whose depths I'm never gonna know."
Don't really wanna know. So...
seeing you?
"Frankly,kinda--kinda makes me glad
that I've never had kids."
Okay then.
Lapd homicide hotline,detective boyer speaking.
No,she didn't have a nose ring. She's ten.
Remember,service with a smile.
Homicide hotline.
- Good morning.
- Is it?
"You know some people like to start the day
with some breakfast,some coffee,sleep..."
"we've got two convicted sex offenders
living a block away from the strongs?"
" yeah,one's back in jail,the other has an alibi,
but you know,it's shaky,I'm looking into it."
What about the bounced email address?
Belongs to gary marsh,emily's teacher.
A 4th grade teacher emailing a student?
Boyer said they were general assignments,
apparently he cced the entire class.
I can go grab them...
of course,mrs.Strong,but I wouldn't jump to any...
I'm sorry,could you hang on a second?
"It's judy strong,she's been up all night
poring over the megan's law site."
"There's a handyman who worked at
their house a few months ago."
What's his name?
I'm sorry,mrs.Strong,what'S...
she says his name is charlie newman.
Mr.Newman? Charlie?
damn megan's law.
There's nothing at the back exit.
"You want me to cordon off the floor
and set up a security log?"
hi there,little girl.
I never did catch your name.
Detective? You--you want...?
I just got a new puppy back at my house.
You wanna go see him?
Detective?
I'm scared.
It's right this way.
Leave me alone! Leave me alone!
come on. It's right down the hall.
- No.
- Come on,sweetheart. Come on.
- You sure I shouldn't
- I want everyone out until S.I.D
- leave me alone!
- no,no,no.
Come on,sweetheart. Come on,sweetheart.
- Come on.
- Leave me alone.
- Detective?
- Come on!
I don't want to.
It's a little puppy.
Little yellow puppy.
- Detective?
- You're gonna like him.
I'm not gonna hurt you!
Listen to me.I need you and
everybody else to get out of the buil---
Thanks,detective.
detective?
Wait for S.I.D.
you're just gonna let her do that to me.
Yeah.
Well,I guess that figures.
"You know,between the megan's law website
and the newsflash that poor,"
"sweet emily was molested,you might as well
just stuck a bull's-eye on my back."
You're not talking to me? Well,fine. Fine.
You know what?Just another innocent man,
"condemned to die at the hands
of an overzealous constabulary."
"You know what,next time,
why don't you just hand out pitchforks"
and torches to every idiot with a batman complex and
nice shot.
Daddy never let me play with guns.
Don't listen to newman.
He so got what he deserved.
you know he did it.
"What he knows is that recidivism rates
for sex offenders is dramatically overstated,"
"that only 13% repeat,and that all the evidence
that he has is circumstantial."
Not to mention the fact that you lived down
the block from a convicted sex offender,
who,from what I hear,has a rather shaky alibi.
they'll run a dna test,prove it was you.
They'll run a dna test to prove it was you.
Where are we going?
come on now,you're a bright girl.
Who do you think did this to me?
You have anything for me,detective?
Sorry,betty,you know I try not to feed the animals.
he didn't do it!
Just because he was upset,doesn't mean that he...
please. Please.
Where is he,judy?
and she had no idea where he was?
no,sir.
all right.
- Let's put out a warrant and want on mr.Strong.
- okay.
Carolyn,keep it away from the press.
And see if you can get the deputy chief on the line.
Are you okay?
Dandy.
My daddy didn't do anything wrong!
Really? Because you don't look so hot.
Why can't you leave him alone?
Don't listen to her. She's just a child.
You want some aspirin?
Think that'll do the trick?
Michael,you did your job,you found her killer.
Well,still we don't know that.
No,we do know that.
"We just got a dna match off
the hair at the crime scene."
Like that proves anything.
I could have an identical brother. Or sister.
My point is,I can put somebody else on the case.
You don't have to finish this.
No,I do.
I have to. It's my job.
didn't my daddy do your job for you?
What...
henry did was wrong.
"Sometimes justice,what we think of as justice,
it has to take a backseseat to law and order."
what's up?
"Hey,we've got a 5150 matching
henry strong's description."
He's at the hollywood zoo.
At the zoo? Why would he be at the zoo?
one of her teacher's online assignments.
Her winter break essay?
My birthday was over break so...
my daddy and I did what we always do on my birthday...
we went to the zoo to visit the lions.
Isn't it strange?
"Even though I'm almost all grown up,
I still love the lions."
All right. Get over there.
we're gonna go lock him up and throw away the key.
Please. Tell everyone to turn around.
Sometimes justice has to take a back seat
to law and order.Right,detective?
Please. Just turn around.
Don't worry,nobody's gonna hurt your dad.
Hey,hey,hey! Hands off.
- Hey,she's the one that keeps shooting me.
- Stay away from her.
- If I have to stop this car
- he deserves it!
- Raines.
- Detective raines,this is dr.Kohl.
Oh,no--not a good time.
See? You should turn around and go to therapy.
I'm a dealing with a double homicide here.
We had an appointment at noon.
- He doesn't need therapy,he needs to arrest your father.
- If you're going to miss an appointment you need to
shut up! Shut--
detective?
Sorry,that was-- I'm working two phones here.
"Look,I've got to go arrest somebody for
killing the guy who murdered his daughter."
"I don't have time to be
scheduling therapy appointments,doctor."
Look,I've got some time this evening.
Maybe you,uh...maybe you wanna stop by.
Uh...yeah-- yeah,I gotta go.
What's going on?
They made a positive id on the guy. It's mr.Strong.
Is he okay?
He's got a gun.
He's threatening to kill himself.
Stay back.
Just wanna-- just wanna see you.
Do you have a gun?
What am I gonna do,shoot you?
No.
Oh,henry.
I wish you hadn't,uh,killed him.
You don't think he deserved to die?
Well...sure.
"Hey,if I were you,
I probably would've killed him myself."
But look where it's brought you.
she used to be afraid of them,you know.
When she was little.
She wouldn't go near the fence.
She'd make me stand a good ten feet away.
A jury is gonna have a lot of sympathy for your story.
I don't want sympathy,I want my daughter back.
Henry...
are you thinking of killing yourself?
It's better that way.
- It's easier.
- Oh!For who?
Judy?
And how about emily?
What about her?
Can you see her?
What?
Imagine.
Right here.Right now.Right next to you.
You can even close your eyes.
Do you see her?
I can.
She's such a beautiful girl.
So full of life.
You can kinda-- kinda see her,can't you?
That beautiful girl lives in you,henry.
And if you're not here to talk about her,
and remember her,and share her stories...
Henry,if you kill yourself,she'll die all over again.
Take it easy,take it easy.
Yeah,henry,I'll put it in your pocket.
" I know everybody's wondering
why I've been busting my ass."
You saw the girl in that duffel.
"First thing,all I could think about
was how much I hate this job."
And then I realized,no...
that's why you took the job.
yeah,he's right,you know.Boyer.
"A case like this one,
it's the reason I hate being a cop."
It's also the reason I am one.
well,that's the hour.
I thought we just got started.
Yeah.How would next thursday at 3:30 be?
Oh. No,I'm serious.
What do we have,eight more hours?
You know,I've got stuff to do tonight,
but I'm just down the block,
if you don't mind watching me exfoliate...
3:30 next thursday.
Yeah. Okay. Got me gabbing there.
- Detective?
- Yeah.
When we talked earlier today,you said
you couldn't get the little girl out of your head.
Did you see her?
I'm sorry,what?
Emily.
Did you actually see her?
You said that you talk to the victims.
Do you see them as well?
No. I don'T.
Okay.
Bourbon on a tuesday night?
Better than tuesday morning.
Why are you still here?
- I want you to play the song.
- No.
Please?
Maybe you should have that drink.
Look,I'm sorry about your dad.
It's okay. Really.
I know you had to do it.
That it was the right thing.
Then why haven't you left yet?
It isn't just the song...
"because I think you should talk to
that doctor lady some more and tell her the truth."
You do,huh?
I could lose my job.
So?
It's all I've got,honey.
"I think if you don't talk to her,
you're gonna lose it anyway."
- I think you should mind
- I'm ten.I don't say beeswax anymore.
If I play it,will you go?
You know,I hate this song.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-jarfar
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Raines
Season 01 Episode 06