- [Man] Already checked Corridor 2.
Nothing there.
- [Man #2] Anything at all?
- Where is he?
- Find him!
- [Buzzer Blaring]
- Come on, go! Let's go!
[Buzzer Sounding,
Helicopter Whirring]
[Ship's Horn Sounding]
[Man Vocalizing "Jingle Bells'"]
[Man] Well, I guess Mama won't be
kissing Santa Claus this year.
Just tell me what you saw.
Hey, I'm just an elf.
I do what I'm told. You know?
"Be jolly"? Besides, I haven't seen
the big guy since the party last night.
- Oh, yeah?
- When are you gonna shovel him out?
Soon enough.
The meat wagon just got here.
- Don't you mean the "meat sleigh"?
- Ho, ho, ho.
- Hey.
- [Cop] Evenin'.
Okay. Got a live one.
- A live one?
- It's a joke.
Snowblowers must
have buried him.
[Jarod]
Is that... Santa Claus?
Yeah. The red hat's
a dead giveaway.
- Anybody got a shovel?
- No.
But I've got the gift wrap.
[Man Narrating]
Thanks, Gus.
Dr. Drake? Thesejust came
in from the mayor's office.
- Same gift as last year?
- Smells like it.
Oh, well.
'Tis the season, Fugimora.
Pass 'em out.
We'll see who survives this year.
Yes, ma'am.
- Uh, so, how's the new guy doin'?
- A lot better than Santa.
- Drinking on the job?
- Actually, this was from the scene.
Dr. Jarod Marley?
Meet Dr. Lisabeth Drake, our chief coroner.
- Hello.
- Hi. You finished with St. Nick?
- Yes, I am.
- [Man Clearing Throat]
Detective Guerra.
Gee, right on time.
- Now, can we do this?
- Victim is not Kriss Kringle...
as we first suspected,
but a Theodore Hargrove...
58, stockbroker, played Santa at
one hell of a Christmas party downtown.
- Go ahead, Doctor.
- He died of a combination of factors,
mainly a heart attack.
Kim, I thought we were
going with exposure.
Well, that was my first instinct, but
further examination revealed the truth.
Heart attack makes sense. Folks at
the office party said St. Nick was doin'...
- one hell of a lambada that night.
- I don't know who "Lambada" is...
but, yes, lividity was
affected by the cold.
But the blood distribution in the leg muscles
would suggest he was doing strenuous acts.
- What about time of death?
- [Dr. Drake] No way.
We can't pull that off
in this weather.
Actually, that's
where this came in.
The eggnog was hard when we found it,
but it wasn't completely frozen through.
Mainly because Mr. Hargrove
had quite a bit of brandy in it.
- Oh, there's a shocker.
- The milk had time to curdle.
So I compared the bacteria
levels in the cup...
with that of the sample
that fell on the snow...
and I deduced that Mr. Hargrove
succumbed to his heart attack...
somewhere between
1:45 and 2:00 a.m.
My guess would be 1:48-ish.
- [Whistles]
- I ask for an autopsy, he gives me an eggnog.
[Phone Ringing]
Yep? Okay.
Dr. Drake? The delegation
from the mayor's office is here.
Damn! They're early.
We're done here.
- Career anxiety?
- Oh, you haven't met the mayor.
But, hey, he gives
killer Christmas presents...
And I mean... killer.
[Groaning] No, not again!
- Is this for me?
- Geez, Jarod, don't tell me...
you never got a Christmas present before.
Not in a very long time. Thank you.
A pastry with candied cherries.
It's fruitcake.
A cake with fruit baked right in.
Thank you.
This has to be delicious.
[Woman On P.A.] Records Department,
please call the third floor.
- Should we tell him?
- Let him discover it.
Yeah.
Mmm!
[Christmas Carol]
Jarod has been moved to his room.
As always, I begin my
Christmas hiatus tomorrow.
I'll be in Mount Pleasant
at the usual number.
It is the Christmas season.
But the Tower deems it best
to insulateJarod...
from the trappings of popular culture.
[Young Sydney]
Jarod, I'll be gone for the week...
and I wanted to say good-bye.
Why do you go away every year
when it turns cold outside?
Business, Jarod. That's all.
If you can keep a secret,
I brought you a little something.
A gift.
A gift?
- This is snow.
- Yes. Remember.
- Tell no one I gave this to you.
- Take me outside, Sydney.
- To see the real snow.
- I can't, Jarod.
- But I want to see it for myself.
- Enjoy this snow.
And I will see you again soon.
Okay?
- I got you!
- Aah!
[Laughing]
[Gasps, Screams]
Let's get out of here!
[Both Screaming]
Two kids found her buried in the snow
a couple hours ago.
[Guerra]
Now, that's criminal.
Vagrant. After you thaw her,
check for needle marks.
My prelim is overdose.
- I wonder who she is.
- We'll never know.
L.G.L.
Bag her and tag her.
And next time, please...
don't make me wait.
- "L.G.L."?
- Little girl lost.
No witness, no I.D.
Her family must be worried sick,
wondering where she is.
That's the tragic part.
She's probably a runaway.
We get them all the time.
Nothin'to go on, so
she becomes a case number.
Like all the rest.
- Are you okay?
- No.
[Electrical Crackling]
Fascinating, hmm? Only one twin is wired,
but they both feel the shock.
I don't even wanna know.
- Cleanup crew just came in from Cleveland.
- Any luck?
- Jarod's last life in a box.
- [Chuckles]
You're the shrink. Maybe you
can figure out their meaning.
Jarod's trying
to tell me something.
Makes a great greeting card.
But face facts, Syd.
At this rate, your boy won't
be home for the holidays.
Maybe not, but he'll contact me.
He has to.
- Well, it is Christmas.
- I worry about him.
- Out there this time of year.
- Relax.
He's probably holed up in Whoville,
experiencing the Grinch for the first time.
[Bell Ringing]
Would you like some?
It's called fruitcake.
Fruitcake?
I'm not that homeless.
What, are you
writing a book?
Um, no, not exactly.
- [Sighs]
- You miss him, don't you?
- Who?
- George. Christmas George.
- You knew George?
- I feel like I did.
George was
all the family I had.
Well, he was all the family
a lot of people had.
- The children at the shelter miss him.
- Yeah. Foster kids, runaways...
They knew the real George.
Oh, everybody thought he was a bum...
because he didn't have a home,
and panhandled to get by.
But he took all that money,
and one day a year...
he made sure they had
presents and a special meal.
Every Christmas Eve
he'd dress as Santa...
and read to those kids all night long.
That's why they called him
Christmas George.
Yeah.
When George was alive...
they all had family
for at least one day.
Christmas doesn't count
for squat without family, son.
No.
I'm beginning
to realize that.
[Woman]
Oh, there you are, Jarod.
I just wanted to thank you
for all the work you've done this season.
Without Christmas George,
it hasn't been the same.
Oh, I'm happy to help.
For a happy man,
you look perplexed.
Well, the truth is, I am.
- Have you read this?
- [Chuckles] "The Night Before Christmas'"?
- It's a classic!
- It's very good, but I'm a little
confused about something.
Now, if Santa Claus were to deliver
a present to every child on Earth...
he'd have to visit
830 homes a second.
Which would mean his reindeer would have
to travel about 700 miles per second...
and he'd have 1/1000th
of a second to park the sleigh...
to crawl down the chimney, to pass out
the presents and to eat cookies and milk.
And for a middle-aged, overweight man,
that's quite a feat.
[Chuckles]
Santa works in mysterious ways.
But it's so fantastical.
Why would anybody believe it?
It's Christmas, Jarod.
Anything's possible.
- Oh.
- [Laughs]
Angel, they're getting ready
to string some popcorn.
Don't you want to help?
Don't you want
to talk to Santa?
- He's not Santa.
- Is something wrong?
Is Christmas George
coming back?
No. No, he isn't.
Why not?
Christmas George died.
Do you know what that means?
We won't ever see him again.
Well, that's true,
and then again, it isn't.
Could I ask you something?
Why did you
like Christmas George?
Well, he was nice. And he made
sure the kids always had...
something under the tree
on Christmas.
So what you're saying is that he had
a spirit, a feeling, that made you feel good.
Well, as long as you have that feeling,
Christmas George is gonna be right here.
So every time it's Christmas, I can think
about George, and he'll be here?
Every time.
[Chuckles]
- Can I help?
- [Boy] Sure. Come on.
[Violin: "O Holy Night'"]
[Continues]
[Dr. Fugimora]
Geez, Jarod. You've run 137 tests.
Any luck on the L.G.L.?
- That's not her name.
- I didn't mean anything.
She should have a real name.
Her family should know.
Especially at
this time of the year.
You're not gonna
give up, are you?
[Male Deejay] And we've got
more Christmas hits coming your way, so...
snuggle up by the fire
with that special someone...
and enjoy the holiday season.
[Ringing]
- What?
- [Man] It's me.
I'm having a holiday
gathering at the club.
It wouldn't be the same
without my favorite girl.
- I'll be there.
- Very well. Christmas Eve at 7:00.
- European associates will attend. Be prompt.
- Of course, Daddy.
- Merry Christ...
- [Line Disconnects]
[Beeps]
[Woman On P.A., Indistinct]
- Gunshot wound to the gill?
- [Laughs] Not a patient.
- Lunch.
- Aren't you a little young for poison fish?
- Puffer fish is only poison before it's prepared.
- Kim.
- Fugu toxin is 500 times stronger than cyanide.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But when it's done right, all you get
are tingly toes and a great buzz.
Christmas dinner around here.
My fugu's a tradition.
The boys in the morgue love it.
And it goes great with cranberries.
I'll stick with fruitcake.
And relax. My uncle was
a master fugu chef in Tokyo.
- Was?
- He's retired.
[Laughs] Oh, good.
Well, I'm glad to hear that.
- Uh, would you help me with this?
- Man, did you spill a whole mug?
Well, actually, I spilled a whole pot.
- I'll get you a duplicate.
- Oh, no, no, no. That's okay.
Just show me where
the old files are.
- [Chattering, Phones Ringing]
- [Woman] It should take a few seconds...
to start working.
Yes, I've already
dispatched the ambulance.
Ma'am... Ma'am.! No.
An overflowing toilet
is not a 911 call.
Ma'am. Would you please
hang up and call a plumber?
[Speaking With Mouth Full]
Okay. You need to... induce vomiting.
Yes.
Uh, no, your finger will be fine.
- Yes.
- [Man] It's not working. It's not working.
Your son is going to be fine, Mr. Hodges,
if you just listen carefully.
- Okay.
- [Jarod] Now, remember, clear the airway...
- and tilt his head back.
- Right. Tilt his head back.
- Now back to the breathing.
- Okay.
[Beeping]
- [Hodges] Okay.
- Now, continue the up and down
motion on his chest.
- Okay. Five-count?
- Yes.
- [Beeping]
- [Hodges] Oh, my God. He's breathing.!
- My son is breathing.!
- That's fantastic, Mr. Hodges.
They're here!
The ambulance just got here.
You see? That wasn't so difficult.
- Merry Christmas.
- Thank you so much. Thank you.
- [Woman On Tape] 911 Operator.
- Hello. My name's Harry.
I'm calling from the corner
of Lawson and Hill.
My friend... Oh, God,
my friend George is...
- [Woman] Tell me what the problem is, sir.
- They ran George down.
You gotta get somebody down here.
Lawson and Hill.
Right in front
of the children's shelter.
- Hurry. You gotta hurry.
- [Operator] I'm calling it in, sir.
- Is anyone else hurt?
- No, they just hit him, and they left.
I didn't see no car.
- This is where it happened?
- Where I found him.
They just left George
there to die.
- "They"?
- I don't know. Crash woke me up.
I didn't see it.
I'm sorry.
I never left his side. Never.
Not until the coroner showed up.
- The coroner?
- [Sniffles]
Not the police?
Better directions, I guess.
[Sighs]
You know, he held my hand, and...
And we got to say good-bye.
You mean, he didn't
die instantly?
Ah, hell no.
He was a fighter.
Coroner tried to save him.
Gave George a shot
and everything, but...
Didn't help.
I never knew coroners
carried doctor bags.
Neither did I.
She did what she could, I guess.
But by the time the cops got here...
- she told them George had passed.
- She?
- Was she alone?
- Yep.
- And she had red hair.
- Uh, yeah.
How'd you know?
[Woman On P.A.]
Any available assistance to the I. V. Unit.
Why haven't you shipped the L.G.L.?
We need slab space for the holidays.
- I found stress fractures in her legs.
- Forget about it.
We've done our due diligence.
- Finish up the paperwork and send her along.
- I understand.
By the way, new guy
works Christmas Eve.
Don't worry about it. Last year was so slow,
we broke out a bottle of Christmas cheer.
Too bad I won't be here
with you to share a toast.
Well, you never know, Doctor. Christmas
has its way of bringing people together.
[Jarod]
OurJane Doe's real name is Gabrielle.
Gabrielle Ryan.
She's from Nashton.
She would have been 18 next month.
How'd you do this?
Lower tibial fractures
to the medial malleoli.
- Media who?
- Bad ankles.
From compression impacts.
That, and she had callous patterns
on her hands like this.
Parallel bars were
her specialty.
Will you tell her family right away?
Count on it.
Hey. Good work, Jarod.
See you around.
[Women's Choir: "Coventry Carol'"]
Face it, Sydney.
It's almost Christmas.
He's not going to call.
[Sighs] I see you're clearing out
for your usual holiday hiatus...
so, here.
A Christmas present?
From you?
Don't go hanging mistletoe.
See you after the first.
And a merry Christmas
to you too, Miss Parker.
- Kim.
- Hey.
Hi. I was going over
last year's duty roster...
and I see that you were
working on Christmas Eve.
I was the rookie last year. That means that
this year, you get to wait up for Santa.
[Laughs] I don't mind
working the holiday.
The truth is, I've never
really had Christmas Eve off.
I wanted to ask you about the autopsies
that were performed that night.
- Shoot.
- According to the files, there were only two.
A homeless hit-and-run victim
named Christmas George...
and an 80-year-old woman
named Edwina Morris.
- Do you remember them?
- I remember the Morris woman.
Dead ringer for
Grandma Walton. Only fat.
But I really wasn't involved
in the hit-and-run.
I thought you were the only one
on duty that night.
I was, until Drake
came in with the hit-and-run.
She did that autopsy.
The chief coroner came in
on Christmas Eve...
to perform an autopsy
on a homeless man?
With karma like hers, she's probably
not that popular on the party circuit...
if you know what I'm sayin'.
The other body.
Edwina Morris.
- Was she a psych patient?
- No.
Just a very large
grandmother of six...
who died of natural causes.
- Why?
- According to the toxicology report...
there were traces of
phenotripticol in her blood.
- Phenotripticol?
- Yes.
Isn't that used to subdue patients
during psychotic episodes?
And in stronger doses,
it induces a state of paralysis...
where the patient is conscious,
but rendered immobile.
- Dead. But not dead.
- Oh, my God.
Please don't tell me that I performed
an autopsy on someone who was alive...
- and conscious!
- No. No.
- You didn't.
- Well, this couldn't have happened.
Someone must have messed up
the toxicology reports.
Or switched them.
On purpose.
[Women's Choir:
"What Child Is This? '"]
[Ends]
- You're Miss Parker, aren't you?
- I didn't know anyone was here.
- Please don't tell anyone I was here.
- No, wait.
Why did you come?
My mom lets me see the rabbits
when no one's here.
I want one, but my father
won't let me have pets at home.
[Young Jarod]
We've been studying them.
There are three sets of twins.
Now watch. They've never
been together before.
But somehow, the ones that are genetically
identical just seem to find each other.
Like something inside them
draws them together. See?
They're soft.
[Door Latch Rattling]
[Car Alarm Beeping]
- Excuse me. Can you sp...
- Not my neighborhood.
[Starting Engine]
[Engaging Gears]
- [Screams]
- [Grunts]
Oh, my God. Didn't you see me?
Jarod!
[Grunting] I'm okay. I'm okay.
It was just a... a little scratch.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine. Come on.
l-I can help you out
with that.
- [Panting]
- You certainly come prepared.
Our patients may be dead,
but we're still doctors, right?
- I suppose.
- I always keep it on hand.
You never know when
somebody might need one of us.
You never know.
- [Beeps]
- [Whirring]
Why, Jarod. I thought they'd
taken you back to your room.
- What are those, Sydney?
- They're another project I'm working on.
- [Buzzing]
- [Woman] Your car is ready to take you...
- to the Mount Pleasant Home.
- Yes. Thank you. Tell them to wait.
[Young Jarod]
You will come back, won't you, Sydney?
[Young Sydney]
I always come back, Jarod. Don't I?
[Whirring]
[Woman] Your car is ready to take you
to the Mount Pleasant Home.
Yes, thank you.
...take you to the Mount Pleasant Home.
[Beeps]
[Woman] Your car is ready to take you
to the Mount Pleasant Home.
I'll be right there.
[Big Band: "God Rest
You Merry, Gentlemen'"]
[Line Ringing]
Last Minute Gifts?
I need a last minute gift.
Dr. Fugimora?
Well, I hate to be
the bearer ofbad tidings...
but you're going to need
to come to work today.
Something terrible has happened.
I'll explain everything when you get there.
Don't you love Christmas?
- It's so Christmasy.
- Jarod, I thought you were working today.
I am.
But I wanted to give you
a little something.
- For me?
- Mm-hmm.
Open it.
[Sighs, Scoffs]
Fruitcake.
[Sniffs]
This actually smells good.
I was so impressed with the mayor's gift,
I tried baking one myself...
and I want you to be
the first to taste it.
[Sighs]
- Mmm?
- Oh, no thank you.
Mmm. Mmm!
It's actually good.
So, um, are you gonna see your family
for the holidays?
I don't think that's
going to be possible this year.
Are you okay?
I... feel a little...
My God!
[Retching]
Dr. Drake?
Let me help you.
[Gasping, Groaning]
My stomach! My God!
[Gasping]
- What was in that cake?
- I went to great pains making that cake.
- It couldn't have possibly been the...
- What?
- Uh-oh.
Well, Fugimora has been teaching me
how to prepare puffer fish.
And I was practicing when
I was making the fruitcake.
And some of it might have
accidentally slipped into the batter.
- Puffer fish?
- I'm afraid so.
You idiot!
You poisoned me!
- [Grunting In Pain]
- I'm sorry.
- Call 911.
- Okay.
- [Cell Phone Beeping]
- Uh...
- I can't.
- Jarod, what are you doing?
- I can't call 911.
- Are you crazy?
No, but I am thorough.
If I call 911, they'd be able to help you.
But they could hurt me.
- What?
- They would come out,
they would see that you were sick...
and they would realize that
I accidentally poisoned you.
And that could
cost me my career.
[Moaning, Gasping]
You can't do this.
- You can't do this.
- [Recorder Clicking]
- [Operator] Tell me what the problem is, sir.
- [Harry] They ran George down.
You gotta get somebody down here.
Lawson and Hill.
Right in front of the children's shelter.
Hurry. You gotta hurry.
- I'm calling it in, sir. Is anyone else hurt?
- No. They just hit him and left.
- [Clicks Off]
- You're a coroner.
Your business is dead people. Even when
you're the one who kills them. Right, Doctor?
Did you have a little too much to drink
at last year's Christmas party?
Can you imagine how Christmas George must
have felt when you hit him with your car...
and left him in the snow?
He went into the alley to recover,
and you heard over your police scanner...
that he was still alive.
You couldn't have that,
could you?
That could hurt
your precious career.
So you went back to the scene,
before the police got there.
Now, you didn't have anything in your bag
that would actually kill him...
but you did have something
that would paralyze him.
He was conscious of everything
that was happening to him...
but he looked dead
to the police.
He was just a homeless man.
You figured, no one
would miss him, right?
But like you always say,
bag 'em and tag 'em.
[Mumbling]
No. Don't do that. I'm not really dead.
Well, if it makes you feel any better,
I'm not really a coroner.
[Voice Echoing]
But everybody thinks I am.
So I'm just going
to declare you dead.
And they can finish you off.
On the slab.
Just like
you finished off George.
Merry Christmas.
["Jingle Bells, '"Off-tempo]
[Voice Distant] Wow.
I never got to work on a boss before.
We'll start cutting on her after lunch.
Who wants puffer fish?
The effects of the phenotripticol
should wear off in a few hours.
She's gonna wake up with a wicked case
of diarrhea from the fruitcake.
- Merry Christmas, Jarod.
- Merry Christmas.
- [Chuckles]
- [Knocking]
Merry Christmas.
He said to give you this.
He who?
Excuse me.
Dr. Marley?
- Yes?
- I'm Timothy. Timothy Ryan.
Gabrielle's brother.
I just wanted to say... Well, this
detective said you identified her.
- Went the extra mile, he said.
- I'm sorry that it took so long.
And I'm sorry that
you had to find out at this time.
I'm not. Imagine wondering a lifetime if
someone you love is out there or not.
Thank you for saving
my family that hell.
Thank you.
[Children's Choir:
"Silent Night'"]
- [Ends]
- [Phone Ringing]
- [Ringing]
- [Clears Throat]
Hello. Daddy, hello.
I was just getting ready...
[Piano: "Silent Night'"]
I understand. No.
We'll do it next year.
- [Beeps]
- [Exhales]
Merry Christmas.
- [Continues]
- [Footsteps]
[Woman]
He's ready now.
You know, I admire you, Sydney.
For 30 years, he just lies there,
and yet you've never missed a Christmas.
It's all I can do.
He's the only family I have.
- What about your son?
- My son?
Yes. Jarod.
Jarod was here?
He stayed just long enough
to leave the gift.
I don't know what
he said to him...
but when he placed that in his hand,
I swear I thought I saw your brother smile.
[Chuckles]
[Jarod]
"'Twas the night before Christmas...
"and all through the house,
not a creature was stirring...
- "not even a mouse.
- [Chuckles]
"The stockings were hung
by the chimney with care...
"in hopes that St. Nicholas
soon would be there.
"The children were nestled
all snug in their beds...
"while visions of sugarplums
danced in their heads.
"And Mama in her kerchief,
and I in my cap...
"hadjust settled down
for a long winter's nap.
"When out on the lawn
there arose such a clatter...
"I sprang from my bed
to see what was the matter.
"Away to the window
I flew like a flash...
"tore open the shutters
and threw up the sash.
"When what to my wondering eye
should appear...
"but a miniature sleigh
and eight tiny reindeer.
"With a little old driver,
so lively and quick...
"I knew in a moment
it must be St. Nick.
"And he whistled, and shouted,
and called them by name:
""Now, Dasher.! Now, Dancer.!
Now, Prancer and Vixen.!
"On, Comet.! On, Cupid.!
On, Donder and Blitzen.! '
"He sprang to his sleigh,
to his team gave a whistle...
"and away they all flew
like the down of a thistle.
"But I heard him exclaim,
ere he drove out of sight...
"Happy Christmas to all,
and to all a good night."'
[Giggling]
- [Sleigh Bells Jingling]
- Did you hear that?
- [Girl, Gasping] What?
- From the other room.
- Could it be...
- [Children] Santa!
[Girl]
Let's go in the other room.! Under the tree.!
[Chattering]
A present for me?
- I wonder who it's from?
- Let's see what you got.
What's it say?
"Friends make Christmas special.
To Angel, Merry Christmas,
From Christmas George."
[Mews]