The deceased is not to be picked up
until this coming Saturday?
Yes, just after dawn. Um, details
for the arrangements are all there.
And a choice of casket
and cemetery.
I would prefer a quiet service.
Of course, Miss Will.
The deceased was your father?
Is my father.
If your father
is still alive, then why...
Just have a casket ready
Saturday morning.
Please.
[Engine Starts]
[Young Jarod]
I don't wanna die.
But I know it's too late
to change any of that.
[Young Sydney]
There's nothing you wanna confess?
[Young Jarod]
You keep asking me for the truth...
when that's all
I've ever given you.
[Young Sydney] Even in the face
of death, you maintain your innocence.
Yes.
He's innocent, Sydney.
An innocent man is going to die.
[Man] Off the bus.!
Move it.! Move it.! Move it.!
You heard the man, side by side.!
Line up and shut up.!
Let's go.! Move it.!
Welcome to Oakfield
Penitentiary, gentlemen.
Sound off.
[Man Narrating]
[Sydney] There's been a breakthrough
concerning Jarod's next destination.
"Top Hat Café pay phone.
January, weekend of the 15th...
meeting with cowboy
regarding Parker brothers."
I don't have a brother,
do I, Sydney?
That I don't know.
What we do know is the 15th
is this coming weekend...
and that note is distinctly
written in Jarod's hand.
- Cleanup team find this?
- In Jarod's last lair...
stuck in the toilet pipe
after having been flushed.
Okay, the arrangements
are all set, Sydney.
Uh, oh, uh...
Go on, Broots.
What arrangements?
Mr. Broots
will be joining us.
Uh, the director thinks
a little technical support might help.
Technical support?
Well, she thinks that some details
are getting overlooked...
that you and Sydney are maybe a little
too emotionally involved with Jarod.
And you're the fix?
Well...
[Snickers]
An...An objective eye, maybe.
Uh, I'll get the car.
[Whistling]
Duller than hockey
in September.
[Man] Never forget,
Mr. Bradley, that in this place...
we are dealing strictly with
a mentality of desperation.
A desperation born from being
locked down in a 10-by-10 cell...
for 20, 30 years,
sometimes longer.
I would say that desperation
was a good word for that, sir.
A man's fiber, if he had any
to begin with, quickly frays.
It's yourjob to keep
those frayed ends knotted.
You're here because
of your experience under duress.
With the Carl Will execution on Saturday,
there promises to be plenty of that.
Sounds like he's got all the classic
symptoms of a career criminal.
Carl Will has a criminal record
dating back 30 years.
Car theft, armed robbery...
a dozen other felony violations leading to
the brutal murder of a fellow inmate.
You worked Folsom
during the '91 inmate riot.
I'm proud to say that we squelched
that one with extreme prejudice.
We don't wipe noses.
We don't lend shoulders to cry on.
We manage, Mr. Bradley, with,
as you say, extreme prejudice.
I'm sure the execution will send
a message to the entire population.
That's the idea.
He's not in there, and none
of the locals have seen him.
- Mm-hmm.
- [Clears Throat]
Maybe we should stake him out.
They didn't let you
have a weapon, did they?
No.
And where do you propose
we do our stakeout?
Right there.
[Man] So, Jarod, how many men
did they run on a shift at Folsom?
Oh, we had a crew of 35 during the week,
slightly less on the weekends.
I hear Warden Harper's
a tough man.
His name is Hopkins.
- Right, Hopkins.
- Morris.
Ah, Jarod Bradley,
Tommy Larson.
Bradley.
The guy from Folsom?
- And all points west.
- Tommy can show you around.
Uh, keep both eyes open.
The animals are getting restless.
Let me take you out,
show you the main yard.
Most of the population
spends four or five hours a day here.
Different zoo, same routine.
Gotta make sure they don't kill each other
and herd 'em in at the bell.
Seems tense.
Yeah, well, it'll ease up
after the, uh, the event.
- The event?
- Execution.
You get it up close and personal.
New guy gets death watch.
- Why me?
- I don't know how it was at Folsom...
but around here, it's considered bad luck
to get too close to a condemned man.
They make the new guy do it.
[Man]
Walkin'through.
Is that him?
[Buzzer Buzzes]
- Larson.
- What?
Is that the man
they're going to kill?
Yeah, that's him.
[Miss Parker]
What do you mean you're booked up?
Who the hell would purposely stay...
at the Park Place Motel?
Well, we got a convention. The electric
company booked the entire facility.
- Do you know this man?
- Jarod.
Yeah, he comes through here
every now and then.
Matter of fact, he said something
about passing through this weekend.
Got a meeting or something.
I'll tell you what.
You being friends of his and all,
you and your brother and... and your dad...
you can stay in the celebrity room
that I keep open for special guests.
Celebrity room.
Burl Ives stayed here once.
We even had Mama Cass.
Not to mention
that Osmond boy.
You know, the goofy-looking one
with the... the big ears.
You know, I bet it wasn't Donny.
Mail call for inmate Cockran.
Thanks.
Oh, I'm sorry. I wasn't watching
where I was going.
You okay, boss?
I'm fine.
And the name is Jarod, Mr...
Cockran, Henry.
Well, it's nice
to meet you, Henry.
[Buzzer Buzzes]
- You're new around here.
- Yes, I am.
- And you?
- Oh, I've been walking these halls for 27 years.
That's a long time.
There isn't a cockroach
I'm not on a first name basis with.
- Is that mail from home?
- Uh, my wife.
She writes me every week
like clockwork.
Sends me seeds for my garden.
These should be marigolds.
Cockran.
You got somewhere
to be, old-timer?
Kitchen, boss.
That what they call
extreme prejudice at Folsom?
You have to know your enemy.
[Male Reporter]
Tonight we bring you a story of love, law...
and its connection between
a man on death row...
and a daughter whose life
has been a fight to free him.
Ten years ago, Carl Will,
a career criminal...
was sentenced to five years
for car theft.
Only weeks away from parole,
he was involved in a bloody altercation...
inside Oakfield Penitentiary, in which inmate
Anthony Lewis was stabbed to death.
After a speedy trial conducted
by then state attorney...
and present governor
Charles Edwards...
Will was convicted
of first-degree murder...
and sentenced to die
in the gas chamber...
which is where the story
takes a most unusual turn.
At the time of Will's initial arrest,
his daughterJessica was a senior in high school.
Jessica's belief in her father fueled her
to spend the next seven years...
in college and law school, and every day
since, fighting to free her father.
But with the governor's denying
final appeal...
and the execution scheduled
for midnight Friday...
her odyssey oflaw and love
appears to be at an end.
[Jessica's Voice]
I love my father, I believe in him...
and I will never stop fighting.
How do you respond toJessica Will's
call for clemency from the governor?
The governor's refusal
is the only answer I need.
Miss Will calls the quick processing
of her father...
a political act by Governor Edwards based on
his reelection law and order platform.
- How do you answer that?
- No one doubts Miss Will's love
or devotion to her father...
but she is working from emotion,
and we're working from fact.
[Man]
Warden, what facts are those?
Officers Clancy and Larson found Carl Will
next to the body of Anthony Lewis...
holding the murder weapon.
Unfortunate as it is, when you concentrate
transgressors in the system...
these things happen, but they won't be
tolerated by me or the governor.
The time has come for us to do our job,
and we're going to do it at dawn Saturday.
- Thank you.
- [Reporters Clamoring]
[Buzzer Buzzing]
Didn't you hear it's bad luck
being around a dead man?
Well, I'm the new guy.
I have no choice.
- Bon appétit.
- I'm not hungry.
It's grilled porterhouse steak,
medium rare.
Poached snap beans.
That's what I ordered
for my last meal.
I know.
That wasn't supposed to be
for, uh, two days.
Well, it's your favorite.
I figured why wait.
They move in on you, don't they?
The walls.
You stare at them long enough, and you
swear they start creeping in on you.
You sound like a man that's
been on this side of the bars.
It's tough...
when you don't belong there.
You're innocent...
at least that's what
you keep saying.
Nobody's listening.
I am.
You're telling me a man wearing
that uniform hasn't heard this story?
I've heard the story.
I'm interested in the truth.
I was headed back to Block "C"
from laundry detail.
I heard voices.
Some people struggling
down the gantry.
Turned around to see
what the commotion was.
Got knocked out.
Woke up in this nightmare.
Corn bread or fritters?
Fritters.
Just like you asked.
Just the wayJessica asked.
She arranged all this.
She loves you very much.
Bradley.
The prisoner's meal is delivered.
[Over Listening Device]
Oh, darlin', I miss you so damn bad.
I ache all over thinking how pretty
you looked laying in that bathtub.
That Mr. Bubble dancing
on your skin like a love potion.
And you stood up and I drank
in the vision of your peryectly shaped...
[Turns Off Device]
[Clears Throat]
Phone tap seems to be working.
I guess I'll poke around
the room for signs ofJarod.
I'm going to go
out of my mind.
You're welcome to borrow
one of my books if you want.
"Relative Thinking. '"
"The Inner Mind. '"
My God! Sydney, is Jarod
all you think about?
Because you don't?
- There is a lot more to life than Jarod.
- Such as?
Such as fun.
Such as sex.
Interesting that in a conversation
aboutJarod, you mention sex.
Well, nothing in the toilet.
How long has it been since
you've been with a woman, Sydney?
Sydney's private life
is not a subject for public discussion.
Well, it's not healthy, you know, keeping
all of that animal emotion bottled up.
Next thing you know, you'll be
on the roof with a rifle in your hands.
You know, I've been
seeing a woman.
Really. Broots.
Tell us about her.
There's not much to tell really.
We... We met online.
You pick up women
on the computer?
How romantic. Details.
Well, uh, she's an accountant.
She has three dogs and a bird.
And, uh, oh!
And she's a hugeJohn Tesh fan.
Sounds like a real wildcat.
What's she look like?
You know, I think, uh,
I should start dusting for prints.
We haven't actually met... yet.
You are pathetic.
God, can they make it
any hotter in here?
[Miss Parker Groaning]
- [Sydney] You all right, Miss Parker?
- I'm okay.
It's this, uh, swill
from that greasy spoon.
How much more exciting
can this get?
Look, Monopoly.
[Country]
Psst. Psst.
Yeah, it's amazing
what they let sit down in this place.
Mm, you smell something?
[Sniffing]
Smells like somebody's
about to fry.
Would you just
leave me alone? Please.
- What you gonna do if I don't? Huh?
- [Door Bells Ring]
Pull out one of them knives
like your daddy did?
Stick me with it?
Jessica. Hi, honey.
Sorry I'm late.
Traffic was a bear.
You will excuse us,
won't you, gentlemen?
- Thank you.
- Bet that's happening a lot these days.
You have no idea.
You're a guard from the prison.
- I'm off duty.
- It's nothing personal...
but it's just guards aren't high
on my list of dinner companions.
I just shared a meal
with your father.
He misses you very much.
Why are you here?
Fate.
And I don't think
your father deserves his.
My mother left when I was little,
but he never left me.
We lived in this rusted-out Airstream
for most of my life.
You know, we didn't have much...
but he always made sure
I had what I needed.
Look, I'm not saying that my father
is the epitome of virtue.
I mean, he was... he was pretty wild
when he was younger.
But stealing cars
and committing murder...
are worlds apart.
He spent five years
in that lockup.
He was a week away
from parole.
He had a job on the outside...
and I was on the outside.
He wouldn't have done that to me.
Did you know Monopoly
was developed by Charles Darrow...
an unemployed heating engineer
from Germantown, Pennsylvania in 1935?
Yeah, that's fascinating.
The game was originally rejected
for containing 52 fundamental errors...
but there still have been
over 100 million sets sold worldwide.
You sound like quite an expert
on the subject.
Monopoly club, high school.
What a surprise.
[Groans]
Miss Parker, you all right?
It's just so damn hot in here.
You know...[Clears Throat]
there's something wrong with this game.
[Grunts] There's something wrong
with this whole damn thing.
No, there's, uh...[Clears Throat]
there's something missing here.
[Grunts]
The only thing missing is Jarod.
- [Groans]
- Miss Parker!
Get a doctor now.!
[Computer Beeps]
[Beeps]
[Inmates Chattering]
Narcissus.
I call them daffodils.
They're my wife's favorite.
Well, I can see why.
They're beautiful.
Talk like that, and no one
will believe you're really a bull.
Only thing the other guards
know how to grow is resentment.
[Man]
Walkin'through.
Is it always this tense around here
before an execution?
Always.
Did you know Anthony Lewis?
No. He'd only been here
a couple of days.
Couple of days?
Hardly seems long enough...
for Carl Will to grow to hate him
enough to wanna kill him.
Strange things happen in stir.
Like the other inmates
who have died in here?
Seven in the last five years.
All accidents?
It's a lot more
than the national average.
I wouldn't know anything
about that.
Oh, come on, Henry, you're on
a first name basis with the roaches around here.
What happened
with Anthony Lewis...
and the other dead inmates?
Prison's a place to keep your head down
and your mouth shut.
Especially this place.
And this warden.
[Whistle Blows]
Let's move it in.
[Young Jarod]
I have two minutes left to live.
My mouth is dry.
I'm calm, but I'm scared.
I feel my heart
pounding in my ears.
[Young Sydney]
It's time to tell the truth.
- I did.
- This is your last chance.
I did tell the truth.
You're about to die.
Clear your conscience.
It is clear.
I'm at peace.
Rosenberg was telling the truth, Sydney.
He didn't give the secrets away.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Aren't you?
[Young Sydney]
Yes.
[Young Jarod]
But if they knew he was innocent...
why did they execute him?
[Young Sydney]
What do you think?
Because someone
had to be guilty.
[Cell Door Clattering]
Tighten it.
I don't want the prisoner to go
into spasm and break those straps.
Initiate the sequence.
[Breathing Heavily]
Larson, drop the pellets.
[Beeps]
- Why the hesitation?
- Mistake in communications, sir.
It won't happen at showtime.
[Warden]
Yeah, well, see that it doesn't.
'Cause we're gonna have a roomful
of press back there for the real execution...
and I don't wanna
have to kill Carl Will twice.
- Get him out of there.
- [Larson] Yes, sir.
Thanks, Bradley.
Do you know what's wrong
with me or not?
I think you have an ulcer.
And from the way you were folded up
when I got here, it's a doozy.
- What can be done?
- For now, I'm going to prescribe...
a mild acid inhibitor.
I'm not sure
that it will be helpful...
given the fact that she smokes...
and has an unusually
stressful demeanor.
You can say that again.
I don't know what it is
you do, Miss Parker...
but it's eating you away
from the inside out.
You're going to have
to change your lifestyle...
- or else.
- Or else what?
You could die.
I suggest that you learn
to control your emotions.
Like your father here.
Have a pleasant evening.
- [Sydney] Thank you, Doctor.
- [Broots] Thanks, Doc.
He's right, you know.
If you don't keep those feelings
aboutJarod in check...
it could be your ruin.
It's a little late
to be worried about my ruin.
[Clamoring]
My flowers.!
Break it up!
- No, boss!
- [Warden] Clancy.!
Clean up this mess.
Get 'em back
in their cages now.
[Man]
All right, clear the yard.! Move it.!
You ever make a move like that
on me again, I'll put you in this plot.
I just didn't want
my flowers trampled.
Well, that won't be
a problem now, will it?
- You okay?
- Sure. Fine.
You're sure?
I don't understand.
If these letters aren't real, wh...
Where's my wife?
She died three years ago.
Cancer.
- I'm sorry.
- Pretty pathetic, huh?
No.
You lock a man away
long enough...
it bends him...
sometimes till he breaks.
Rita and me
were married 43 years.
You didn't know that, did you?
No, I didn't.
I broke the law, and I've paid every day
for the last 27 years.
But there's certain things
that a man...
can't allow
to be taken from him.
His pride, his dignity.
I understand rules.
But what Warden Michaels
did to me was wrong.
All I wanted
was to be there when...
my Rita was laid down.
I put her through a lot of pain.
And I just wanted to be able
to put flowers on her grave...
and feel her in my heart...
one more time.
He wouldn't give me a furlough.
Hell, they...
they let cons out
for that kind of thing every day.
All I wanted to do
was say good-bye.
Is that why you planted
your garden?
Crazy, huh?
I keep praying maybe...
one day I'll actually get the chance
to show how much I loved her.
But Michaels,
he's set on making...
a statement with this place.
I guess maybe
they were my statement.
I just didn't want them
to think they broke me.
[Slinky Clanging]
- Hey, buddy.
- [Boy] Hey, wait up.!
I hope you don't mind.
I brought your kids some toys.
Hi, cutie.
Give this to your mother.
Tell her I'll be there
in a second, okay?
You have
a beautiful family.
- You're a lucky man.
- Thanks.
Something on your mind?
Carl Will.
- What about him?
- Well, I'm a little bit embarrassed to admit this...
but I'm not sure
I can handle this execution.
I know it's what we do,
but I've never seen a man die before.
I was hoping you could help me.
- Well, you're talking to the wrong man.
- Yeah.
I saw your face as we were
doing the walk-through.
It's pretty difficult for you
to imagine Carl Will strapped to that chair...
gas rising up,
choking the life out of him.
Why is that?
It just is, okay?
Hmm.
Did you ever notice
that these things are just like guilt?
You can move it
from one place to another...
but it always comes back.
Who are you?
Someone who doesn't want
to see an innocent man die.
Someone who thinks thatJessica Will
deserves to have her father...
just as much as those kids
deserve to have theirs.
I've been walking
the yard for 20 years.
It's all I know.
It's too late
to start over, and...
I can't afford to cross
a guy like Clancy.
- You're afraid for your life.
- Yeah, well, you should be too.
You know how it is on the inside.
Things happen.
And I'm damn sure not gonna end up
like Anthony Lewis and the others.
Lewis was transferred in
from Joliet.
Just like all the other men
who died here.
I pulled the inmates' files
and I tracked them.
It's really interesting.
Each one of them belonged to
the same Chicago crime family.
My guess would be that somebody
paid to have them silenced.
Is that the way
the operation worked?
Yeah. Clancy's
brother-in-law...
is a pencil pusher atJoliet.
He made a deal
with a rival family.
They transferred targets
into Oakfield.
Clancy does the job.
They split the money.
Are you a part of it?
No, I wasn't.
I didn't find out until
after Anthony Lewis was killed.
And by then,
I was in too deep to say anything.
What about Carl Will?
Clancy was finishing up
on Lewis, and Will walked in.
I was supposed to make sure
the area was clear.
Hell, I thought he was just hitting
the guy up for cash.
- Is that when you knocked him out?
- Yeah, well, I had to.
Clancy would have killed
the guy right there.
Clancy planted
the shiv on him.
By the time Will came to...
it was over.
And now he's going to die...
for something he didn't do.
[Broots] There's definitely
something wrong with this game.
Maybe not all the pieces are there.
They're not, they're not,
but it's more than that.
I have a feeling we're not seeing something
important with this whole thing.
[Pills Rattle]
Speak for yourself.
Got us a Stetson.
- [Gun Cocks]
- Well, I hear that.
Twitch and your next stop
is Boot Hill.
Hey, relax, little lady.
I'm just the pony express.
Put the phone down
and turn around... slowly.
That's an awfully big gun
for such a pretty little lady.
Save it for the hoedown.
What are you doing here?
Well, I told you.
I was paid to make a delivery.
Yes. What kind of delivery?
Hey, I'm unarmed. I swear.
Left hand only.
I knew there was
something missing.
What are you talking about?
The game. Chance.
Get out ofjail free.
[Sydney] What do you think
it means, Miss Parker?
Damn it.
I need to see
your registration book.
[Clerk]
Okay.
[Muttering]
[Pages Turning]
"Jarod Short. Jarod St. James.
Jarod Ventnor.
Jarod Chance. Marvin Gardens.
Room 5." The room...
The room right next to ours.
[Sydney]
"Go directly tojail. Do not pass Go.
Do not collect $200. '"
I am sick of being a token
on his game board.
Miss Parker.
[Miss Parker]
Go directly tojail.
Damn you, Jarod.
[Chanting]
Free Carl Will. Free Carl Will.
Hey, Clancy.
The warden just called.
He wants you to make another check
of the gas chamber.
- Make sure there's no malfunctions.
- It's fine.
I loaded the cyanide myself
not an hour ago.
Hey, don't shoot the messenger.
Guess there's some kind
of electrical problem.
Have Larson check it.
His wifejust called.
He's sick.
My butt. He's yellow.
You check it.
I can't. I'm the new guy.
I have to bring Will his last supper.
All right, damn it.
You need something
done right...
Do it yourself.
Well, good thing
we're not frying this guy.
[Door Opens]
- Warden Michaels?
- [Door Closes]
[Clancy] Hey, what's going on here?
Who shut the door?
Who's there?
Scary, isn't it?
Being locked up
like a wild animal...
waiting to die.
Funny, Bradley.
Now let me out.
Mm.
I don't think I'll do that.
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
Same thing you've been doing.
[Clancy On Intercom]
I don't know what you're talking about.
[Jarod On Intercom]
Oh, come on, Clancy.
I know you killed Anthony Lewis.
You set up Carl Will
to take the fall for it.
You were going to let
an innocent man die...
for something you did.
[Clucking Tongue]
Who the hell are you?
I'm you... judge...
- jury...
- [Switch Clicks]
- and executioner.
How many men?
How many men
did you kill, Clancy?
Five? Six?
They were animals.
I did the public a favor.
[Jarod]
And you almost got away with it.
Except Carl Will was
at the wrong place at the wrong time.
[Clancy]
Name your price.
[Jarod]
My price?
Money.
How much is a human life
worth anyway?
How much did you make?
5,000?
10,000 a head?
Nah, I think it's time
for justice to win this one.
I'd ask if you had
a last request...
but the truth is...
you don't really deserve it.
It's showtime.
[Beeps]
- No!
- [Sizzles]
[Clancy Yelling, Indistinct]
Don't you think
not telling that man...
those cyanide capsules were fake
is cruel and unusual punishment?
- [Clancy] Bradley.! Aah.!
- Nah.
[Clancy Screaming]
I, uh, would be happy
to answer any questions you have...
but right now,
I'd like to hug my dad...
and tell him
how much I love him.
[Miss Parker]
Get out of my way.
[Reporters Clamoring]
[Miss Parker]
Hey, you, open up. We're expected.
[Buzzer Buzzes]
No civilized person could sit here
in front of you people...
and tell you that
he enjoys giving the order...
to have cyanide pellets...
dropped into acid
to kill someone.
But we do that to deter people
from committing crimes.
Unfortunately, there are events that would
prove we have corruption on our staff.
And inspired by these events,
changes will be made here...
that hopefully benefit
all the inmates.
My resignation
will become final in 24 hours...
after my last official act
as warden.
[Man] So, we understand
you like to play games, Mr....
Parker. Yes.
And I've invented one.
I call it
Get Out ofJail Free.
[Mews]