- [Young Sydney] What are you seeing, Jarod?
- [Young Jarod] I'm not sure.
Come on, think.
Think, Jarod.
What does it mean?
These people...
some are angry...
some are sad.
- But all for the same reason.
- And that is?
Their trust has been
violated, Sydney...
by someone they look up to.
And now,
they can't trust him.
[Sirens Wailing]
[Shouting, Indistinct]
- Captain Harrigan.
- Are we clear?
O'Leary's still in there.
O'Leary, get the hell out.
That place is gone.
[Crying]
O'Leary, report.
- What the hell are you doing in there?
- Mommy, where are you?
Somebody help me.
It's okay.
You're gonna be all right.
Damn it, O'Leary.
Get the hell out of there, now.
Sir.
That's my baby!
That's my baby.!
Gail. Oh, Gail.
Thank you.
Just doing my job, ma'am.
[Man Narrating]
[Miss Parker]
So Mr. Raines loaned him to us?
[Sydney]
Yes, Miss Parker.
You wanna tell me why?
Bear in mind thatJarod's
modus operandi thus far...
has been to collect
newspaper stories.
So if we can establish
a correlation...
between his selection
process and his movements...
we may be able to predict his next move
by scanning the local and national press...
for stories
which may interest him.
And Cousin It
is your man for the job?
Please don't trivialize this,
Miss Parker.
His name is Angelo.
He's very special.
Oh, I can see that.
[Chattering, Indistinct]
Man, Jarod. You barely get your boots
unpacked, you're already king of the hill.
- [Chuckles]
- You know, I thought that place was a goner.
I can't believe you just walked
right through that inferno.
Well, I wouldn't recommend
trying it at home.
- Actually, it's safer on the job.
- Safer?
68.6% of your serious
injuries occur at home.
You run the numbers, it's a bigger risk
taking a bath than it is fighting a fire.
- The truth is, I was just following the exit signs.
- [Chuckles]
Hey, can you show me
where I can stow this gear?
Yeah, follow me.
You take any locker you want. Just
make sure it doesn't have a name on it.
- Any one but this one.
- I'm sorry. I didn't know...
Lieutenant Gleason?
Sorry, man.
I should have warned you.
That's Tamara Copeland's locker.
- The firefighter that was killed.
- Mm-hmm.
She and Gleason were tight.
I guess you coming here kind of,
you know, closes the door on all that.
- Or opens a wound.
- Jarod, there you are.
One day on the job with us...
and you're kicking ass
like a 20-year veteran.
I want you to take a good look at this guy,
Roy. Guts, brains and a touch of the crazies.
That's what the Fighting 16th
is all about.
Listen, Jarod. The reporters are ready
to get up close and personal with you.
Uh, sir, I don't want
any publicity.
Jarod, you are now a member of the best
damn fire-fighting unit in this city.
You should be proud of that.
Besides, it's good for the team.
Yes, sir.
Smile pretty.
[Cocktail]
And how long are we going to have to wait
until your savant zeroes in on Jarod's location?
Angelo is not a savant,
Miss Parker.
Actually, we don't have
a classification for what he is.
But think of him like
a sponge, if you will.
He has no personality
ofhis own...
but he can absorb the personality
data that we give him.
And he has read every
scrap we have on Jarod.
- So now he's another Pretender?
- No.
He could never make
a moral judgment of his own.
Also, he would never run away.
Where have I heard that before?
- Parker?
- Michael.
Come here.
- I can't believe this. How long has it been?
- Too long.
- What are you doing here?
- Short business trip.
I'm a sales rep for
a pharmaceutical company now.
This is part of my territory.
What about you?
I, uh, have a mid-level
position with a local firm...
nothing very exciting,
I'm afraid.
I cannot get over
how terrific you look.
Despite the lack of good sex.
[Clears Throat]
Michael Patrick,
this is Sydney...
my assistant.
- Michael.
- Sydney.
Anyway, I would ask you to join me
for a drink at the bar...
- but I can see that you're both, uh...
- Oh, Sydney was just leaving.
Yes, apparently, Sydney
was just about to leave.
Oh, great.
I'll be at the bar.
See you at the office, Syd.
Let's see.
I'm doing my nails...
washing my hair,
smoking a cigarette.
[Jarod]
And you're talking to yourself.
Yeah, so what?
That's what arson investigators do.
Jarod O'Leary.
I'm with the 16th.
Yeah, I heard all about you. You're the guy
who saved the little girl in this building.
Harrigan must be
doing backflips over you.
- John Zimmerman.
- Oh, I know who you are.
You caught the North Hills arsonist,
pretty impressive work.
Yeah, well,
it didn't get me any dates.
It's glory boys like you
that get all the play.
I bet you could
tell me some tales, huh?
Well, I do know this one about this little
monkey and this man in the yellow hat.
[Chuckles]
Yeah, I can take a hint.
Nobody wants to talk to guys like me,
unless there's a fire.
Then there's questions,
nothing but questions.
If you're so unhappy,
why did you pick this line of work?
I didn't have
any choice, really.
Most guys who wanna be
this close to a fire...
they either set 'em
or fight 'em.
I fall in the latter category.
[Groans]
- Are you okay?
- Oh, bum knee.
Sports injury?
Is that some kind of a joke?
I didn't mean anything.
- Do you mind if I take a stab at this?
- Feel free.
Well, we know that
the occupant was a smoker.
She was smoking a cigarette,
doing her nails.
So my guess would be that she fell
asleep, dropped the cigarette and...
- [Imitates Blast] ignited the fluids.
- That's good.
Real good. Also wrong.
- Electrical fire.
- Really? What makes you so sure?
Well, see, the outlet
was overloaded.
The burns are mostly
concentrated on the walls.
The fingernail polish fluid
ignited much later.
Oh, another needless
catastrophe solved.
- Impressive.
- Eh.
- You know, the saddest thing is...
- Hmm?
this singed mattress.
This is the closest
I get to sex.
Long lunch, Miss Parker.
Not boring for once.
- Any progress?
- Well, slow but steady.
Although I can say
with 90% certainty...
thatJarod is due to land
somewhere east of the Mississippi.
Angelo has eliminated
everything west of that.
We are definitely closing in.
You don't get out much,
do you, Broots?
Page me if you have
a breakthrough.
- Where will you be?
- Out.
What was that all about?
It appears Miss Parker
has taken a sudden interest...
in the pharmaceutical industry.
[Growling]
[Roy] Don't worry.
Ember growls at all strangers.
- How long do I gotta keep stirring this mess?
- Just until it coagulates.
That's a good word for it.
- He thinks you're a dog.
- He does?
Yeah, you're a stranger in this place.
He's just trying to establish dominance.
- Really?
- What, you never had a dog before?
No. I did drive a chimp
through the Amazon once.
[Chuckles]
- Here you go.
- [Whining]
He'll love you in no time.
Dogs are amazingly loyal creatures.
You keep their bellies full,
they'll do anything you ask.
Quit screwin' around with that stupid
mutt. We're waiting for lunch.
Coming right up, sir.
Now we know why you had to transfer
from your last assignment.
- [Jarod] Bon appétit.
- What is this slop?
It's optimized
nutritional supplement.
Hearts of palm, wheat grass and
asparagus stewed with tomato.
[Disapproving Chatter]
- I grew up on this stuff.
- Threw up is more like it.
- [Clicking Tongue]
- [Whining]
People, there's only one thing
that can save this disaster.
Insta-Cheez!
Haven't had a decent meal
around here since Copeland died.
[No Audible Dialogue]
[Miss Parker]
So he's on the floor. I'm on top of him.
We're both spent,
covered in sweat.
And you're still doing this?
At least three times a week.
Isn't it hard to maintain
that level of intensity?
Not if you're doing it right.
Hmm, you're not doing it
at all, are you?
No, truth is...
I gave up fencing after college.
Besides, I never found
an opponent as formidable as you.
Never will.
[Chuckles]
You still have
that look in your eye...
half invitation,
half intimidation.
So which do you want?
[Chuckles]
Don't tempt me, Parker.
Too late.
Uh, check, please.
"Aerosol cheese-like
imitation food product."
Official food
of the Fighting 16th.
According to these ingredients,
there's absolutely no nutritional value.
Hey, tastes great,
and it makes me sleep like a baby.
Well, I doubt I'm going to be
getting much sleep around here.
Oh, the beds are pathetic,
I know. You'll get used to it.
No, I mean, I've been going over
some of these old records.
- Boy, you guys are good.
- 92% knockdown rate.
That makes us the most
efficient company in the city.
- I just hope I can live up to your standards.
- Well.
You follow Harrigan,
you'll be fine.
I watched him lead
a response with one pumper.
He put out a six-alarm fire
before the other five even got there.
Sounds like he takes
a pretty aggressive approach.
Except for these
warehouse fires.
The company arrived before
the structures were completely engulfed.
Yet each time, Harrigan
pulled the team back.
- Yeah, they were N.W.S.'s.
- N.W.S.?
Not worth saving. Harrigan decided
they were too volatile to risk his men.
Live to fight another day.
Right. Look, Jarod,
you're gonna fit in fine here.
It's like I said... you trust Harrigan's lead,
he'll take care of us.
[Michael]
Nice place you got here, Parker.
[Miss Parker] How do you know?
You haven't even seen the bedroom yet.
And at this rate,
I never will.
- How about a drink?
- Don't tell me you're tired.
I'm just getting warm.
I'll definitely
be wanting that drink.
I can't believe you let all this energy
go to waste on a sales job.
Don't forget...
if it weren't for that job,
I wouldn't be here.
When do you leave?
I thought you weren't
done with me.
I'll be here for...
two days.
Then let's not
waste any time.
Here we are, gentlemen.
Eat in good health.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Hey, handsome.
Nancy, what are you doing here?
I was in the neighborhood.
Thought I'd drop off your work shirts.
- You don't have to do this.
- I know. I want to.
Business looks good.
Oh, since breakfast this morning,
on top of which, Manny calls in sick.
Manny is sick?
Well, who's cooking?
Hey, Herb.
What should I do
with these balls of meat?
I think you two know each other.
I'll take care of the meatballs...
- if you'll finish cleaning up, okay, Jarod?
- Sure.
- Careful, it's hot.
- Okay, thanks.
Great guy.
- You have no right to be here.
- I came by to pay my respects...
and the cook called in sick,
so I offered to help.
- You would have done the same thing.
- What do you want?
A truce would be nice.
Look, Lieutenant, I know we haven't
gotten off to a very good start.
I just want you to know that I
understand how you must be feeling.
- Really?
- Tamara Copeland was your best friend.
I'm not trying to take her place.
I just wanna do my job.
Grab those plates, would you?
- You're not gonna make this easy, are you?
- What?
Me hating you.
- Thanks, Nancy.
- See you later.
I worry about that girl.
- What do you mean?
- It seems like she can't let go of what happened.
It feels like she blames
herself for Tamara's death.
It was an accident, wasn't it?
My daughter was
a great firefighter.
And I loved her more than
anything in this life.
But she knew this was
dangerous work...
and people die.
I gotta go check on
the meatballs.
Broots, another
possibility from Angelo.
Sydney, Broots.
I'm confident it's a landlocked state,
either Pennsylvania or West Virginia.
This isn't an exact science.
It's an experimental technique
with a huge human element involved.
- Been up all night, haven't you?
- Uh-huh.
Let me get you some coffee.
Maybe that might help.
- Oh, man. Who brought that damn mutt?
- Guilty, sir.
Well, keep him out
of the house, will you?
Hey, Hank.
Off with the shoes. House rules.
That Italian slate cost me
$20 a square foot to put in.
You heard about a king
in his castle?
Between that mutt and these slobs,
I'm gonna have to build a moat.
Cap's a regular Bob Vila.
He built the bar.
I'm gonna build
a garage this summer.
A remodel this beautiful
has to be expensive.
- Well, there's a lot of sweat equity.
- [Roy] Yeah.
- Our sweat, his equity.
- Check the hamburgers, Roy.
And don't let 'em burn.
Good kid. Can't handle a belt sander
to save his life, but he's a good kid.
You know, this railing...
1934 ladder truck.
The very first one
the Fighting 16th ever had.
Harrigan's used that railing a lot,
and I don't mean in the line of duty.
- [Chuckling]
- You know...
you landed yourself
in a very special unit, Jarod.
Historical is more like it.
This is the first unit in the city
with two female firefighters.
Yeah, with Gleason and Copeland there,
it felt like a real family.
- Nancy misses Copeland very much.
- We all do, son.
Must've taken a lot of guts for Copeland
to run into that burning warehouse.
Yeah, electrical fire like that.
That place must've been
hotter than Satan's armpit.
Copeland was good, but she had
an overzealous sense of the heroic.
I told everybody to hang back.
She thought she heard screams
and went inside half-cocked.
Really? That wasn't
in the papers.
Copeland did outstanding
work on this team.
I wasn't about to let her
be disgraced over one mistake.
I called the hose crew in to bring in
a line and went in after her.
By the time I got inside, she was
sucked into the smoke and flames.
- I never found her.
- That was very brave.
Truth is, bravery had
nothing to do with it.
As long as I'm in charge, this team
will never leave one of its own hanging.
You're not going to accept this
as a passing good mood, are you?
- I know you too well.
- Don't be so sure.
But I'm concerned.
Mr. Patrick seems
awfully transient.
What I do for recreation
is my business.
Besides, I like him.
Ask yourself this then.
Are there enough
healthy relationships in your life...
to compensate for what
you're doing for recreation?
These entanglements?
They're not free from emotional
repercussions, you know.
Let me give you a nickel's worth
of free advice, Syd.
You only know as much about me
as I want you to know.
And your concern,
though touching...
- [Cups Clink]
- is wasted on me.
I'll tell you what, Jarod.
- This is the best meal
we've had around here in months.
- Oh, thanks.
So how did you become
Martha Stewart overnight?
- Insta-Cheez.
- [Chuckles]
Actually, it was an old recipe
ofTamara Copeland's.
- Excuse me.
- Nancy, l...
Oh, man. I was trying
to do something good.
I think you did.
I think cooking one of Copeland's meals
helps to keep her here among us.
- We don't wanna ever forget her.
- No, we sure don't.
- [Young Sydney] What are you seeing, Jarod?
- I'm not sure.
Think, Jarod.
What does it mean?
Focus on the faces.
These people,
some are angry, some are sad.
- But all for the same reason.
- And that is?
They were betrayed by Amin.
He killed his own people.
Yes, and?
They could no longer
trust their own leader.
[Young Sydney]
What are you seeing, Jarod?
What does it mean?
Think, Jarod.
- [Aerosol Spraying]
- [Whining]
[Jarod]
Nothing like a Grinder at Herb's.
- Now that will get you talking to yourself.
- They are good.
So, you buying me
a turkey sandwich.
If you're hoping
to get lucky, you're not.
Lucky?
- It's a joke.
- Oh.
Well, I was hoping I might
ask you a few questions.
- Figures.
- You see...
I'm trying to get a grasp
on this burn pattern thing.
And I have a bet with Roy that
this was an accidental electrical fire.
- Yeah, well, you better pay him.
- Really?
Why is that?
See the char trail lead from the middle
of the room, travels out in a web pattern?
All the flames are below
the electrical fixtures.
It's a planned torching.
Arson.
You gonna eat that pickle?
So if it was ruled
an electrical fire...
Whoever did it was a moron.
Hmm.
Well, I guess that moron
would have to be you.
Because it was your ruling from
the Tri-River warehouse fire.
You remember the one.
She died in it
trying to save your life.
You don't know
what you're saying.
I know you checked into
St. Joe's Hospital the night she died...
with a third-degree burn
on your back.
And I also know that Harrigan let three
other warehouse fires burn to the ground...
fires that you ruled accidental.
Insurance payoffs.
Is that why she's dead?
[Herb]
Gentlemen.
- How do you like those sandwiches?
- They were terrific.
- How much do we owe you?
- Hey, your money's no good here.
You guys are family.
[Zimmerman]
An empty warehouse goes up...
a mini-mall gets built.
[Jarod] Insurance pays for it all.
Nobody gets hurt.
That's the way it worked
until that night.
[Sighs]
All I had to do was...
spread an alcohol-based
propellant around the floor...
and bust a couple of pipes,
make it look electrical.
Once the fire was burning steady,
I started to beat it out of here...
but my knee gave out,
and I couldn't hardly move.
Is that how you got burned?
Yeah.
Flames were everywhere.
They caught my shirt. The damn pain
was so bad, I must've let out a shriek.
- Tamara Copeland heard you.
- Yeah.
I tried to crawl over to an exhaust vent
I'd rigged up to get past the fire crews.
But the smoke was searing
my lungs, and I collapsed...
and I thought I was
a goner for sure.
Then I looked up and saw her
emerging through the fire.
- She must've recognized you.
- Yeah.
She knew I'd done this,
but it didn't stop her.
She just went about her job.
Instead of saving her own life...
she started to save mine.
And then Harrigan came in.
He hit her with a crowbar.
Told me to get away.
Said he wasn't
going down for the fire.
He took her oxygen and handed
it over like it was nothing.
All she wanted to do
was save your life.
Instead she died
in that fiery hell.
Jarod.
[Miss Parker Chuckles]
- Parker.
- What?
Are we ever gonna make it
to your bedroom?
[Both Laughing]
Getting there is half the fun.
- [Phone Rings]
- Don't.
I have to.
- What?
- We have a confirmed hit, Miss Parker.
- Angelo?
- Oh, the guy's amazing.
He narrowed it down
to five clippings.
The winner's a place called
the Borodin Smoke House in Pittsburgh.
They confirmed thatJarod
was there until recently...
and his trail is
probably still hot.
Borodin Smoke House, Pittsburgh.
Get Sydney on the horn and get
transportation ready. I'll be right over.
Yes, ma'am.
Pretty family.
Time to go see them.
Your business tripjust ended.
- [Knocking On Door]
- Yeah?
- Lieutenant.
- Yeah.
- Can I show you something?
- Sure, come on in.
This is a duty roster.
From the night
that Tamara Copeland died.
If that's some sick joke,
it's not funny.
And if it's a reminder,
I do not need one.
You were supposed to work
the shift the night she died.
But she filled in
for you, didn't she?
It should have been me.
I know that you feel that way.
But maybe you could allow yourself
to see the other side of the coin.
They're more duty rosters.
From shifts you filled in
for her over the years.
Nancy.
We all know the risks.
You can't blame yourself.
I wasn't there for her.
Maybe you feel you weren't there
for her that night.
But you can be there
for her now.
ThatJarod Vronsky
was a godsend.
I didn't think we were going
to survive after my father died.
Did Jarod leave
anything behind?
Oh, he increased productivity...
restructured our investment strategy
and organized a dental plan.
All he asked in return
was to sit in there.
Now why would Stepford Boy
want to sit in a smokehouse?
Jarod thinks in metaphors.
He could be anything from smoke jumper
to sideshow fire-eater.
Oh, he loved smoke.
- Said he wanted it in his pores.
- Mr. Borodin.
Did Jarod leave anything behind,
like a red notebook?
Same as before.
I don't have it.
- "Same as before"?
- I have hams to stow.
[Speaking Russian]
I gave it to the other man.
- Who?
- A man came here less than an hour ago.
He knew many things
aboutJarod.
He said that the others would come.
The others that would want to hurtJarod.
Broots is the only
other one who knows.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- What?
- [Broots] Uh, Miss Parker.
I got him.
I know exactly whereJarod is.
Okay, Ember.
It's showtime.
Come on.
You can do it.
- It's easy.
- [Whines]
Come on,
you can do it.
It's easy.
Watch.
Like this.
Come on,
you can do it. Come on.
- [Whines]
- Come on.
Ember, come on.
Come on.
Come on, boy.
[Whines]
[Barks]
[Chatter, Indistinct]
Anybody seen Zimmerman?
He's been paging me all afternoon.
Yeah, he just
pulled out of here.
He looked kind of
strange, excited.
- He say where he was going?
- No. Oh, he left you this.
- Anything wrong, Cap?
- No.
[Harrigan]
Zimmerman? You here, Zimmerman?
Why, you little bastard.
Harrigan.
Is this any way to treat a dog?
- What the hell are you doing?
- I wanna show you this neat trick I taught Ember.
- I don't care about that stupid mutt. Uncuff me.
- Hey.
He's not stupid.
He's man's best friend, you know.
And I've learned that
if you just keep him well fed...
he'll do just about
anything for you.
His food of choice,
as is yours, is Insta-Cheez.
It's not very good for you,
but, what the hey, it does taste good.
O'Leary, if I get out of here,
I'm gonna break your neck.
Then I better not let you out.
Now, about that trick.
[Aerosol Spraying]
Ember, light this place up.
Come on, boy.
Come on.
Good boy.
Neat little trick, huh, Harrigan?
But watch, there's more.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Oops, electrical fire.
Started by a dog.
Terrible accident.
- Put it out!
- I'd like to, but I don't know how.
You see, I'm not really a fireman.
Oops, there goes another one.
- Take the damn cuffs off me now!
- Can't. Gotta make a phone call.
[Touchtones Beeping]
- [Phone Ringing]
- Company 16.
[Jarod]
I'd like to report a fire, please.
16309 Ellsworth Terrace.
Thank you.
- [Ringing]
- [Beeping]
Well, I sure hope that
the Fighting 16th gets here on time.
The flames are spreading
pretty fast in these walls.
But that's not
really a surprise.
You see, I've treated the wiring
throughout the house with this accelerant.
That way the flames
and the fire spread completely.
And it looks like an accident.
No one will ever know.
- What about me?
- Well, even the best arsonists make mistakes...
- [Flames Building]
- don't they, Chief?
Oh, no!
- Give me the key!
- He looks pretty scared...
doesn't he, Ember?
I bet Tamara Copeland looked pretty scared
too the night of the Tri-River fire.
But she had you there
to back her up.
Someone she trusted
to protect her.
Go wait outside, Ember.
- I'd hate to see you get burned.
- [Sirens Approaching]
- Lieutenant!
- Hold it, guys.
There's something
you need to know first.
[Jarod] I've got to go now.
It's getting pretty stuffy in here.
O'Leary, you can't
leave me here to burn!
Why not? You left
Tamara Copeland, didn't you?
- Yes, I left her!
- You left her to burn.
So you could collect
the payoff money.
So you could buy
this Italian slate tile.
Or that 1934 ladder truck railing around
your wet bar that you're so proud of.
Yes, I left her.
Now, give me the key, please.
- This key?
- Yeah.
Sure.
Hope you don't burn.
O'Leary.! O'Leary.!
[Screaming]
My house!
That son of a bitch
burned my house!
Put it out.
Put it out!
Hang back.
This place is definitely N.W.S.
Come on, guys. I built that house.
Don't let it burn like that.
I'm your captain.
I'm your damn captain!
To hell with you.
[Glass Shattering]
- You must beJarod.
- [Gun Cocks]
- Who are you?
- [Chuckles]
Uh, you're really not
in a position to ask.
Now put your hands up
and turn around.
[Barking]
Good-bye. Good-bye.
Thank you very much.
I have to go.
It was very nice to meet you.
[Miss Parker] You cover the back.
Everyone else with me.
Who're you working for?
I told you, Parker.
I'm a sales rep for a...
Oh, you bitch!
You don't know the half of it.
Who're you working for?
All right. All right.
The Centre.
Mr. Raines.
Don't, Parker. Don't.
There might be repercussions.
[Groaning]
By the way,
I was faking it.
Hey, I can't eat this.
- I wouldn't give that crap to my dog.
- Oh, no problem.
I can fix that.
Bon appétit.
[Mews]