- [Bell Ringing]
- Sorry about the principal not
being able to give you the tour.
He's real busy.
Working up the school lunch schedule
is trying work, I'm sure.
This was Mr. Jarod's classroom.
He was, like, the best substitute.
Kids would sit in on the class
even though they weren't enrolled.
And he did
the coolest experiments.
- I can see that.
- Oh, yeah.
We even did a virology unit on bugs
to learn their resiliency.
He told us that roaches would be the only
living thing after a biological holocaust...
them and some woman
named Parker.
Hardly sounds like
high school biology.
Mr. Jarod, like,
marched to his own drummer.
He's a one-man band, all right.
The best part is he wouldn't grade us.
It was like he was
conducting his own experiment...
and we were collecting
the data for him.
You run along to homeroom now.
Aah!
Carlos?
Wait! Come back here!
Hold it right there!
Come on, now! Stop!
- Carlos, come on! That's it!
- Aah!
- Where's your dad?
- Down the hall, last room.
My name is Jarod.
You're going to be just fine.
[Man Narrating]
Okay, the father's symptoms
include weight loss, fever...
night sweats, violent cough,
swollen lymph nodes...
- Mycobacterium tuberculosis.
- Looks like it.
- You don't see that much anymore.
- No.
- But he'll be fine once we get him admitted.
- How's the boy?
Too early to tell.
But much better off than you're gonna be...
once Garber finds out
what you did with the kid.
Violating quarantine procedures
with these people was damn foolish.
I realize it was
a bit unorthodox, sir...
but T.B. is
a Level 2 classification.
It doesn't require
an on-site quarantine.
Friendly advice, Dr. Reilly. If you don't wanna
end up dead, you'll remember that...
every one of these situations should be
treated as a Level 4 situation.
Walter, whether or not the boy was already
exposed, or... What difference does it make?
- He's protected either way.
- [Jarod] And the boy gets
to be with his father now.
I felt like he needed that.
Great. Our new guy's
Florence Nightingale.
[Man Coughing]
Yeah, you're gonna love this place.
Stove and oven in the kitchen,
hot and cold running.
170 a month plus utilities.
- 170?
- Okay, 150.
I'll pay the water.
Come on down to the office.
- We'll sign the papers.
- Does it have roaches?
Of course not. This place is
a bohemian's dream, not some slum.
- Come on to the office.
- No roaches?
[Violin]
- Damn it!
- What is that?
It's a never-endin'
cat-gut nightmare is what it is...
not to mention
the worst rental decision...
of my life.!
[Baby Crying]
There's another building
two blocks west of here.
Might be able to find
somethin' quieter there.
No. I'll take this place.
It's a lot nicer
than where I used to live.
[Sneezes]
Bless you.
Sounds like the flu.
It's cold and rainy in Portland
this time of year.
Here, keep it.
It's clean.
So I took a trip without you.
Don't tell me you're jealous.
Confused.
I thought we were working together.
So did I, until I discovered
your personal ads...
all over the country
trying to contactJarod.
I don't like secrets.
Well, he wasn't answering my e-mail
messages, so I tried another tack.
But I would have let you know
if he had contacted me.
- I have a fever, Syd...
- [Door Opens]
but it's not bad enough
to believe that.
- What?
- Um...
[Clears Throat]
He's in the lab.
Who?
Mr. Raines.
Mr. Raines hasn't been
in the lab in 10 years.
Well, uh, he's in there now...
and he's looking for you two.
So, good luck.
[Labored Breathing]
- Mr. Raines?
- The Empire State Building.
Who would've thought something
so beautiful could be replicated...
by a four-year-old boy
in only two hours?
Jarod was brilliant
the day he got here.
He was brilliant the day he escaped.
And the question is...
where is he?
Mr. Raines, Jarod has been
harder to catch than we thought.
Sydney, we need him.
- I know.
- [Sneezes]
[Coughs]
May I?
Mr. Raines, I have the flu.
I'm dying.
Mmm.
[Coughing]
Keep it.
Bring Jarod back where he belongs...
or I'll get someone who will.
Are we clear?
My father wants me to do it.
Unlike everyone else around here...
I'm not afraid of your father.
I don't have to be.
[Garber] Ourjob here at RIDA
is to contain viral outbreaks...
before they spread.
I've seen the worst that a virus can do,
and because of it...
by the numbers is usually best.
In retrospect, you did the right thing
with Briggs and his son, Jarod.
Listen, I was out of line.
It's all right.
Well, your credentials
are impressive.
A stint in BAMRI D in London...
M.D. /Ph. D in virology.
Where did you do your doctorate,
by the way?
- Horace Greeley High School, Portland.
- [Chuckling]
The door's under negative air pressure
to contain leaks.
Yeah, we pioneered
the technique here.
I noticed in your file that you were vaccinated
for anthrax and the W.E.E. series.
I was working in the Gulf
with NATO's Q. R. T...
and the W.E.E. was for the
Pekowsky Syndrome in Johannesburg.
- A frightening scenario.
- Yes, very.
Watching somebody suffer
can have an effect on you.
I hope I can make a difference here.
[Beeping]
[Female Electronic Voice]
Code accepted.
Jarod, Jeff Baytos...
decontamination
and facilities specialist.
- Nice to meet you.
- Uh, ix-nay on the andshake-hay, Doc.
[Chuckling]
Mr. Baytos tends to be overcautious.
No such thing in a place like this.
One wrong move
like pressing the flesh...
and, uh, it's off to
the submarine for 10,000 years.
You call your morgue the "submarine"?
What did you call it at BAMRI D?
Chernobyl.
Well, we're working
a Level 3 today.
An offshoot strain
of Rift Valley fever.
You ready to battle the unseen enemy?
Absolutely.
Will you be joining us,
Mr. Baytos?
Level 2 is my limit now, man.
Live long and prosper.
[Garber Chuckles]
Baytos witnessed a man die of Ebola.
He's been reluctant
to go past Level 2 ever since.
Fortunately, he's the best there is...
when it comes to decon.
[Woman]
It's nice to have visitors.
Our friends don't know what to think
or say, so theyjust stay away.
Did you meetJon in South Africa?
No, but I heard a lot about him.
We were both working on separate
strike teams in the Mutaba village.
Oh. You know, he loved that job.
He was the first to arrive
and the last to leave.
He'd stay in places where there was
no hope, no chance to make a difference.
Holding the hand of a dying man
to let him know he's not alone...
that's making a difference.
I'm working with Walter Garber now. I'm
trying to finish the work your husband started.
Well, you're lucky
to be working under Walter.
Jon thought the world ofhim.
That's them at the W.H.O. banquet.
[Door Opens]
Hey, you're supposed to be napping.
I thought I heard Daddy.
No, it's not Daddy.
It's just a friend.
- Oh.
- Hi. My name's Jarod.
- Hi.
- Go lie down, honey.
This has been especially hard on her.
He vanished right before her birthday.
How do I explain that to Cindy?
I mean,
how do I explain any of it?
You know, l-I know
he's not coming back.
You know, l-I've accepted that.
I have.
I just, uh, wish I knew
where to go from here.
I mean, how to go from here.
I mean, is he dead?
Is he alive?
That's a very beautiful ring.
Jon designed our wedding bands.
You know, I know it's corny, but he wanted
them to be the only two alike in the world.
Here. Jon wore this when
he went into the field to work.
- He never got sick wearing it.
I'd like you to have it.
- l...
I couldn't possibly accept that.
No, he'd have wanted somebody
who cared as much as he did to have it.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Fits like a glove.
[Chatter, Indistinct]
- Excuse me. I was wondering if you might help me.
- Uh, sure. What's the problem?
It says here that
this is a-a motel for roaches?
Yeah. It's like, uh,
the Hotel California...
for our little
six-legged friends, you know?
Hotel California?
Yeah, they can check out anytime
they like, but they can never leave.
Oh.
Oh! Like a trap.
- Yeah. Somethin' like that.
- Well, that's peryect.
I'll take 100.
Right on.
- [Trumpet]
- [Pounding On Wall]
[Woman] I'm gonna
wrap that thing around your neck...
if you don't shut up.!
Come and get it.
- [Pounding]
- You're a dead man, Hansel.!
Come and get it.
[Trumpet]
[Man]
I've paid my rent. You can't evict me.
Sir, my name is Jarod.
I'm your neighbor.
l-I just wanted to tell you that
I'm very intrigued by your music.
I'm not falling for that.!
I would very much like to meet you,
and I would like to ask you a question.
[Chain Rattling]
Are you here to give me the boot?
I wasn't planning on it, sir,
but you're more than welcome to mine.
Come in.
It's nice to have
a friendly audience for a change.
Ben Hansel's the name.
- Ben, I need your help.
- And I yours. Do you play?
I've conducted a symphony
here and there.
Ah! Well, then what
do you think of this?
[Loud, Harsh]
[Woman]
Shut up.! You're driving me crazy.!
- Cultural dwarves, all of them.
- [Man] You suck.!
That's very interesting.
Haydn's "Cello Concerto in "C' Major,"
I believe.
I rewrote it for trumpet. I'm working
on an arrangement for glockenspiel.
- An artist must stretch, you know.
- Yes.
- How long have you been a musician?
- Fifteen-odd years.
That's a long time.
But it'll all be worth it
when the philharmonic calls.
I sent them a tape about a week ago.
- You... You had a question.
- Yes.
I'm trying to attract roaches, and this
doesn't seem to work. Do you have any?
Roaches?
I can't get rid of them.
I spilled a box of Crunchy Crawlers
cereal behind the fridge once.
Now every night,
they come out hunting.
- Crunchy Crawlers?
- "They're grotesquely delicious."
You know, I was wondering about
my interpretation of the first movement.
It was a tad subtle.
Subtlety is a virtue in any form.
A neighbor who's a scholar of
the arts and letters. Thank you, Jarod.
Um, you can yell at me
through the wall anytime.
And thank you for the tip.
You will do very nicely here.
[Jarod] In seconds,
the virus invades the host cell.
- With a Level 4 virus, the results are devastating.
- [Chattering, Laughing]
The Mutaba village outbreak.
Subjects begin coughing
only four hours after exposure.
Internal bleeding
commences at hour 12...
and by hour 36...
the subject completely bleeds out.
- [Chattering]
- Gentlemen, you can ignore
the flight attendant...
as she tries to teach you
how to fasten the seat belt...
but with the Mutaba virus
and other level fours...
the kill rate is 90%.
And, may I add,
an airborne virus...
coupled with a pinprick
in your glove or a faulty seal...
sends you into the slammer,
and from there...
it's an express
straight to the submarine.
Lights.
Thank you for
the safety review, Dr. Reilly.
You misled them back there.
You and Jon Florence did develop
a vaccine for the Cahuenga virus.
We got lucky on that.
But with Ebola or Mutaba...
Well, I have to keep 'em honest.
I'm sorry about Dr. Florence.
You must miss him.
- Very much.
- From what I understand,
Dr. Florence was a family man.
- Hardly the type tojust up and leave.
- He was a good man.
Of all people,
you two should know that...
awful things swirl beneath
the healthiest of exteriors.
Jon confided in me that
things at home weren't optimal.
He never went into specifics, but he certainly
enjoyed working the extra hours here...
rather than being at home.
This is an airborne Level 4 virus.
Let's be on our toes.
Commencing phase two dissection.
We are 72 hours after expiration
by Mutaba strain "B,"
subject 247.
- Walter.
- Good God.
- Decon!
- Come on. Let's move it. Go!
- [Alarm Blaring]
- Okay, let's remain calm.
Proceed with decon shower.
- Coming through.
- [Garber] Stay calm. You'll be fine.
- Code denied.
- Damn it! The code isn't working!
Here, let me.
[Electronic Voice]
Code accepted.
- Get the glove off.
- Inoculate.
Hurry up.
No skin breaks.
The blood must've been from the sample.
Well done, everybody.
Everything by the numbers.
We'll review
the security tape tomorrow.
Well, you handled that simulation
as if it were completely real, Jarod.
Well, I've had a lot of practice, sir.
Who changed the slammer access code?
Lisa, the fewer people that have the code,
the fewer people that are at risk.
I don't want anybody near the slammer
unless they have to be.
- It's your funeral.
- No, it's his.
Garber's the only person that has
the access code to the slammer?
And the submarine.
Oh, Jon.
How's my goddaughter?
About to turn six, but she thinks she's 16.
I hope you can make it to her party.
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
I've proceeded with the autopsy
on the monkey. Look at the liver.
Mush.
This virus has mutated.
We'll finish this first thing Monday.
Forgive me, Father, for I have sinned.
It's been...
Oh, my God...
33 years since my last confession.
I have betrayed a friend.
Then you must seek his forgiveness.
Mm-mmm.
He has shut me out.
You're troubled by something else.
Have you prayed to the Lord
for forgiveness?
Not even he can forgive me
for what I've done.
Look at the liver.
- [Jon] Mush. This virus has mutated.
- Mm-hmm.
It's like the Cahuenga virus,
but worse.
This is a Level 5 virus.
What the hell have you done?
You made Ebola look like the flu.
- I've been working on it, genetically.
- No, you've been playing God.
We gotta shut down this project now.
- I'm destroying it.
- You can't.
- Yes, I can.
- I won't let you.
Let go of my air hose!
- Let go of my air hose!
- I won't let you.
- Let go of my air hose! Let go of my air hose!
My God, Walter, you've killed me!
Quick, into the decon shower.
- [Alarm Blaring]
- The lab is full of the virus.
Stay calm. Don't panic.
Pressure failure! Get into the slammer.
I'll meet you there.
Hello, Jon.
I was afraid I'd find you here.
[Cello]
[Woman]
Hansel, you are driving me nuts.!
Shut up.!
Interesting interpretation.
- [Pounding On Wall]
- [Man] You suck.!
You're a polite neighbor, Jarod...
but I fear the cultural dwarves
are right.
I'm terrible.
It takes a long time
to master music, Ben.
A lifetime would not be
long enough for me.
My music kills plant life.
I'm Salieri to Mozart, Jarod.
I curse God for bestowing me
with mediocre ability.
[Music Box]
What are these?
Trifles, larks.
Pointless exercises.
Did you make these?
Yes.
Ben, these are exquisite.
Your compliment
is appreciated, Jarod.
But, art it is not.
Art is many things.
Some choose a brush,
some a bow...
some a pen,
and some... choose glass.
What do you mean?
Maybe the way you create is
through these pieces rather than that.
You said it yourself, Ben.
Sometimes an artist
needs to stretch.
[Beeping]
[Young Jarod]
Sydney, I'm scared. I can't do this.
[Young Sydney]
You have to, Jarod.
There's smoke.
People are screaming.
Sydney, they're burning!
They're burning!
Make it stop!
Make the burning stop!
- Jarod!
- Make it stop!
No, go away!
Leave me alone!
It's all right, Jarod.
It's all right.
Aah!
It's all over, Jarod.
It's all right.
- I want my daddy.
- The code word makes it stop, Jarod.
- You didn't use the code word we came up with.
- I said, I want my dad.
Let me.
Jarod, remember.
When you're doing the simulation
and you become frightened...
and wanna stop, say, "Refuge."
All right?
Mm-hmm?
Refuge.
[Beeping]
[Miss Parker Sneezing]
[Coughing]
He contacted me.
No secrets.
Why the sudden change of heart?
Lately, I've been seeing things
from another angle...
and maybe it's best if you get him.
Dr. Hoffman,
do you have a minute?
What's up?
- What do you make of this?
- Hmm?
Well, let's see.
Liquefication of organs, blood secretion
through skin pores, loss of hair.
Looks like an advanced
version of Mutaba.
That's what I thought
until I found this.
I've never seen this before.
Did you cross-check it?
Against every sample on record.
There's over 3,000 on record.
It did get a little tedious
after the first 800.
- [Chattering]
- [Hoffman] My God.
Jarod, this is worse than
any Level 4 I've ever seen.
- It's a Level 5.
- What?
There's a Level 5 here?
It's a sample off a body
in the submarine.
Wait. H-How did you get
in the submarine? Only Gar...
Go. Go.
Garber has the code.
Is all research here sanctioned
by a governing body?
Which project isn't?
It's only hearsay,
but I trust the source.
Garber was working on some research.
l-I don't know what.
What else did Jon Florence tell you?
How'd you know Jon was the source?
Besides Garber,
he was the only person...
that knew everything
that was going on here.
What else did he tell you?
That Garber was working on
some radical mutations of a Level 5.
He said it started out good,
but it got corrupted.
Jon said God
would never forgive him...
if he let this project continue.
Well, unfortunately
forJon Florence...
he never had the chance to stop it.
Oh, my God.
[Jon]
Mush. This virus has mutated.
Mm-hmm.
We'll finish this first thing Monday.
[Tape Rewinding]
I'm guessing between the knob,
the mouthpiece and the city water
you're drinking...
there's enough germs
to kill a cockroach.
Dr. Reilly. Hi.
Yeah, you're probably right.
I deal with the germs I can,
but something tells me...
I wouldn't last long
living in a plastic bubble.
Even one equipped
with a decon shower?
It was an excellent
performance, Jeff.
Look, l-I don't know
what you mean.
Are you gonna make me enhance
the image so I can see your face?
Do you know what it's like
not being able to sleep?
You'd be surprised.
I watched a man beg for his life.
He begged to see
his wife and kid again, and l...
l... I didn't help him.
I know Jon Florence got infected,
I know his body's in the submarine...
and I know that you helped
Garber doctor this tape.
But what I can't figure out is why.
Because it was my fault,
that's why.
l-I was working late
likeJon and Dr. Garber...
and l-I saw Jon
come into the slammer...
and he-he...
he looked so frightened.
The decon shower lost pressure...
and that is my job
to make sure that it doesn't.
That-That is my job, Dr. Reilly.
And then Garber went ballistic,
and he blamed me forJon's contamination.
You know, l-I have never seen a virus
do what it did to him, or so quickly.
And that's why you won't
go past Level 2 anymore.
It's just thatJon...
he begged me to get
his wife and kid...
and-and Garber...
Garber told me to keep it quiet.
He said that... that the authorities
would have to be called...
and that they would
shut down the facility...
and that more lives
would be lost because of my error.
Jon Florence did not die
because of you or the decon shower.
He died because
Walter Garber murdered him.
Hello, Butcher Bob's?
I'd like to order a dozen pig livers,
please. Yes, a dozen.
Say "cheese."
Good morning, class.
Today's lesson takes us into
the fascinating world of cockroaches.
- Walter?
- Yes?
It's Jarod.
I've made a very interesting discovery
that I think you should check out.
- What have you got?
- Well, it's still too early to be sure...
but I think I found
a vaccine for Mutaba.
- I'll-I'll meet you in the lab in an hour, Jarod.
- Perfect.
What have you got?
Where'd you get the sample?
From this liver.
My God, man!
It's an airborne virus!
Walter, your air hose.
- Hit the alarm.! Help me.!
- [Alarm Blaring]
Help me!
God!
Oh! There's pressure failure
in the decon line!
Well, you'd better
get into the slammer, sir.
[Electronic Voice]
Code accepted.
Where is everybody?
Where are the doctors?
Baytos!
There's nobody here, sir.
- I sent them all home.
- Jarod, you've killed me!
Relax, Walter. I told you.
I made a little discovery.
It's a derivative cross between your
Cahuenga virus and the Rift Valley strain.
An anti-virus.
It shuts your strain down.
Give it to me, please.
- I can't.
- Jarod, please, help me!
Like you helped Jon Florence...
by exposing him to
a Level 5 without any cure?
Who the hell are you?
Well, I sure as hell
am not Florence Nightingale.
But, then again, neither are you.
How long, Walter?
How long beforeJon Florence
started to show symptoms?
How long before
the internal bleeding started?
How long before his brain tissues
started to leak into his ears?
How long before his internal organs
started to liquefy? How long, Walter?
- Give me that syringe.
- Why?
Jon Florence never had this option.
Why should you?
- Jarod, it was an accident.
- He knew he was going to die.
And I'll bet the last thing he wanted to do
was just to see his family one more time...
to say good-bye to his wife
and to his child.
But you couldn't give him that peace,
could you, Walter?
Because then the truth would come out
about how you were trying to play God...
with all these viral experiments.
You tookJon Florence's life...
and you ruined his family's as well.
- That is no accident.
- All right, I did it. I admit it. I killed him!
The-The research
was very valuable.
- Please, give me the vaccine!
- All right, Walter.
But I will warn you.
It's only sugar water.
Sugar water?
I don't know how to make a vaccine.
You see, I'm not really a virologist.
- The truth is, this place gives me the creeps.
- What?
You can check out anytime you like,
but you can never leave.
No! No!
Don't leave me! Jarod!
[Over Monitor]
Jarod.! Come back here.!
Jarod.! Wait, don't.!
Please, don't leave me here.!
Please, don't.!
Help! Help!
- Aren't you gonna tell him
you didn't really infect him?
- [Shouting Continues]
Nah. Why don't you do it?
In 48 hours.
Help.! Please.!
Somebody, help.!
- After the police get this.
- Help me.!
Oh, no.! God.!
Oh, God, help me.!
Come back.!
Jarod.! Jarod.!
- What is that smell?
- I can't smell.
Go left.
You take that room.
Good morning, class.
Today's lesson takes us into
the fascinating world of cockroaches.
- Nothing. He's gone.
- Yes, but not forgotten.
- [Groans]
- This is a bug motel.
When the hormones
off a roach's body...
which is the wet stuff
you just walked through...
combines with the sticky stuff inside
of the box, which you are standing in...
it forms a bond...
which is stronger than epoxy.
Welcome to the world's
largest bug motel.
You son of a bitch.
Enjoy your stay.
Class dismissed.
I'm stuck.
[Trumpet]
- [Pounding On Wall]
- [Dog Barking]
Chivas on the rocks.
One ice cube.
Clever way of contacting me, Sydney.
No one at the Centre
would've ever known what this meant.
I had to see you face-to-face.
Did Miss Parker take the bait?
Presumably.
I have to ask you for something.
You're in no position
to ask me for anything.
Not even your forgiveness?
- What?
- For keeping you in the Centre.
For the lies all these years.
Did you send me this?
No, I did not.
Parker did with your name on it.
- What is it?
- Reminders.
Issues I must take up
with myself...
God...
and with you.
- It's too late.
- I come to you with an olive branch.
All right.
You want my forgiveness?
Then tell me what happened
to my mom and dad.
I can't.
I don't know the truth.
Then you and the Centre
will never get me back.
And I can't forgive you, Sydney.
I can't forgive myself.
[Ringing]
- Ben Hansel.
- [Woman] Mr. Hansel,
this is the Chicago Philharmonic.
We received the extraordinary
glass sculpture you made...
and we'd like to set up a time for you
to meet with our merchandise coordinator.
We have next Wednesday available...
Thank you... for everything.
Where will you go now?
I'm starting a new job.
You've got roaches?
[Mews]