Previously on Weeds
People seem to like what we're selling !
MILF Weed.
It's the brand ... the date, made by lo
If you'll notice above me,
our very first camera !
DRUGS ARE WROOOOOOONG !!
I think you're turning Agrestic into a police state.
Yeah !!!
I totally kick ass !
You want be to be your girlfriend ?
They think he's cool ever since he took up your cause.
What cause?
GO DRUGS RA-RA-RA !
Can I come in ?
Bad timing.
Its dad's birthday for fuck's sake !
We're married.
It's a business arangement.
What was that ?
I don't know !
Your boys at the DEA do they know about me ?
Probably not you're a small type
I thought we were under your radar ?
YOU are under my radar.
And since I'm keeping you there,
I gotta show my boss some results.
Don't Move ! NOBODY FUCKING MOVE !
This is a house of worship.
Did you tell Heylia yourself or
did you have your boy Conrad do it ?
You just wouldn't listen.
You went all, with one of my customers
and created a new game behind my back.
She's not gonna stay mad !
You do not know Heylia.
www.seriessub.com
presents
Weeds saison 2 épisode 10
" Mile Deep and A Foot Wide "
All starts here.
Under beautiful blue sky.
Yes Ma'am. No it ain't. Yes it is
This is where you find out who you are.
You gotta push.
Or you're gonna get pushed.
So which one do you think
gonna win ?
The fat one.
He got more leverage.
Unless the other one bites him,
or (this ain't anyone's game?)
I got here as soon as I could, this is not off the freeway.
You make a left...
We don't know you.
As you...
Sit your pretty ass on over there
and stare off somewhere else.
You wouldn't want the good men parked over in the chabby
thinking you something other thant what you look like
Bitchin' way over her head.
Yeah ! That's what happens when you get raided.
You get two white boys, in an Impala
following you everywhere you go.
(laughs)
But she don't have to worry about that.
Do she Levin ?
No she don't !
Cause she went off and
married herself a DEA agent !
Yes she did shipped off some Armenians
and started farming. Can you believe that ?
Can you believe that ?
I had no choice.
And I warned you about the bust.
Am I supposed to say thank you ?
You shut me down.
I ain't nothing comin' in now.
We can help you to get bio
or you get yourself up and running again.
Oh she did not just said that.
You took away my livelihood.
You think your help will make that right?
No. That's just the Bitchin' way over her head talkin'.
What do you want me to do Heylia ?
You start by talking to you husband.
Look you're gonna have to do whatever it takes.
And if that means you got to sit on his face
with roses up your snatch 5 nights a week,
you're gonna do that.
Help me ! Who the fuck are you ?
Hey Vanita, what happened to that child? umm...
Nancy something like that ?
.... Ain't that that white Bitch that thought that she was somethin' ?
Yeah, where she head now ?
She gone now. Vanished.
- What ?
- Nobody seen her since.
Oh man ! Those poor little boys !
Losin' both their parents !
Ain't that somethin' ! Can you imagine ?
Okay stop it !
I will stop everything.
I am Heylia Turner James.
And I know where you grow.
And I know where you live.
And both you, and Conrad on the clock.
To make this thing right.
Tick fucking tock.
Come on lil' girl.
Captain Too
Scottson.
Sit down.
I'm re-reading your report.
I gotta tell you Pete. First time through it
gave me the shits and giggle so good.
I had elamonade it. (?)
All nine pages. I'm gonna put them
up on my wall over there.
And everytime I might have a crap day,
I'm gonna read about you.
and your muslim prayor meeting.
Suspects were tipped off.
Oh you think ?
Tell me agent,
Where is the next big bust ?
Our lady at the crack pipe or temple Beth meth ?
Surveillance is continuing.
Mike and Robin are in the Impala.
And we still have wire tapes.
And we're gonna wait around
for the woman's food stamps to run out.
She's an open door to U-Turn,
I need some slack here.
Shuman needs Mike and Robin.
- Captain.
- You got hosed Pete.
Wrap it up.
Yes sir.
It's my anniversary today.
He forgot.
He forgets a lot of things.
17 years.
How long have you and ... ?
20.
18.
22.
I'm not cool with numbers.
You're an accountant.
Different. Those are guy numbers.
Years married, that's girl maths.
I'm ceased with guilt,
are you ceased with guilt ?
Ceased.
Good girl, good girl, good girl !
Oh we shouldn't be doing this.
You're right.
We have families.
Children.
Beautiful children.
This would destroy them.
(Legendaryyyyyy)
She thinks I can make Peter disappear.
Peter wants her in jail,
me out of the business.
Silas wants to skip college and be like me.
I think Shane knows what I do.
I can't even look at him in the face.
- I've never been to China.
- Sit down.
She threatened to kill me !
(?) motherfucker (?)
Give me your hand.
Breathe.
Look at me.
What are you doing ?
A Korean girl taught me this.
Keep breathing, and look at me.
I don't know what to do.
I'm out of moves.
Baby.
You never had any.
Moves mean you think things through,
you have been reacting.
That feels good.
You ready to get in the back seat ?
You ready for Conrad's plan now ?
You out.
I'm out.
You don't dug yourself a better mile
deep in the foot while and you ain't look to back up on your ... home. (?)
You out.
You go to him.
You tell him you love him.
Tell him you out after this office.
You get your money back.
Heylia James gets wiped off his board.
I take the equipment and disappear.
I'm sorry.
No I don't ... really wanna hear this.
No listen ! You've been a good friend.
This ain't no drive at miss Daisy.
I ain't about to feed you no Thanksgiving pie.
If thinks work out with Peter,
you get your money.
We're done.
You love him ?
Who ?
Agent wonder bread.
I'm not sure.
You think you could ?
You're out ?
The hour suck.
There's no health insurance.
It's a bad job for a danger junkie.
And that's you.
I admit I have a problem,
I'm going cold turkey.
I'm sceptical.
Let me convince you.
Come to dinner tomorrow night.
You with my family.
Your sons ?
I don't know how thrilled they'll be.
They are good kids.
I know that.
And you're amazing.
Eat with us !
Heylia walks, Conrad leaves.
We make a go of it.
Dinner ?
My place. Bring your tooth brush !
I'm staying the night ?
Peter is my boyfriend.
He makes me happy.
Just your boyfriend ?
And he's in some sort of law inforcement I hear ?
So we can all feel safe.
I've invited him over for dinner tomorrow night.
It needs to go well.
Can I invite Gretchen ?
Absolutely !
What is this we're having ?
It's paella.
Great ! It's pretty !
I want you to make this again tomorrow night.
We don't have to eat the same thing I can make ...
No no no, I want you to make this.
(You got it?) !
Kat !
Did you lost your cat ?
I'm Kat, you're Nancy, right ?
I am.
There's a ... smell.
Grip jelly ? (?)
No ! It's... fish.
Oh that's me ! That's me !
It's sockeye salmon.
If you want (?)
No, I'm good. Who are you ?
What do you want ?
Is ... Andy here ?
Mom, uncle Andy's choking !
Come on in !
I've been eating nothing but sockeye salmon
for the past 47 hours
the map (?) said it took 33 which is bullshit !
I mean who's that boy ? You must be Shane.
Hi. Hug hug.
(?) your car or
You're the crazy chick from Alaska
who tried to kill my uncle ?
That is a great story !
Hi Silas !
You drove here all the way from Alaska ?
Yeah I borrowed some salmon
from the fishery.
That means she stole it.
The man at the 7-Eleven
gave me a case of Red Bull
And that mean she stole it.
And that's all I've been eating and drinking
for the past 47 hours, I feel great !
I drove and I drove and I drove,
till I get the innerstate 5.
and that's a straight line for 1211 miles
But I knew a shortcut,
hi !
Hi !
How did you find me ?
I read about your toe accident
online, Google.
I missed you so much.
I'm tired.
XXX is not beautiful.
I wrote a book.
And she is ...
Gone by tomorrow.
Promised.
Thank you.
How was your day?
How was my day ?
It was well.
How was your day ?
Isabelle had a call-back for voice over (?).
I didn't like the material.
AH !
I stopped by Doug's office but he wasn't there.
I'm still trying to patch things up.
Good luck with that !
Dean, we have to talk !
Just a second !
No, I mean we have to talk !
What is this ?
Happy anniversary !
You thought I forgot, didn't you ?
I thought you forgot.
It's lovely.
Thank you.
Anything for me ?
"Permafuck"
" A journal of spirit rape ".
Yes, it's about us.
And our time in Alaska.
You're not gonna like everything you read,
but I wrote the truth.
And Bump Chuck was very upset with you.
Who is Bump Chuck ?
He's my boyfriend.
He read my memoir and he wants to kill you Andy.
But don't worry I ditched him in Bakers field.
I don't think he followed me.
Big Eskimo guy ?
The correct term is inuit
Is that him ?
No !
He is much bigger than that.
Your orange juice.
Can I .... please ?
Sure !
Alright let's stay focused here.
So you wrote a book about us ?
Yeah and I just need you
to sign a letter that says that
everything in the memoir
happened in the real life.
Okay so I just have to sign something
and then you.. then you go away ?
And you can read that in the van.
In the van ?
After I fuck you !
Yeah.. No no no no no.
Bump Chuck is an old XXX he beats people  ..
but he's a premature ejaculator.
I can't have sex with you.
You (?) man that made me come.
No no no, I can't.
April 28th, 2005, 5:26 PM, Ketchikan, Alaska
Women's bathroom, Deer Mountain Hatchery
We'll take the check.
Yeah I don't know when I stopped really loving Dean.
The only reason we're still together
is 'cause of the kids.
You know once Isabel graduates...
Turn the TV.
It'll take your mind off your troubles.
God that feels good !
...
I have tapes in my bag.
Porno ?
Better !
We'll have Gretchen home by nine.
She's a great kid.
So enters ...
... the eldest son !
Where have you been ?
It's 5:30 I thought dinner was at 5:30
Dinner was supposed to be at 5:30,
but you're uncle didn't show up to make it, so...
...we're making it ourselves.
Hey Silas !
Hi !
What's with the outfit ?
Just an outfit !
You wanna help out ?
I'm not exactly a gourmet here.
Call me when it's ready.
So this guy is your mom's boyfriend or something ?
I guess so.
My mom has got a boyfriend.
Your two parents are divorced ?
Separated.
My dad's got an appartment.
I see him on the week ends.
What's that like ?
I don't know.
We go to the movies, when they ... off.
Mostly says he's sorry, stuff like that.
Sounds awesome.
Back
Punishment ?
The Alphabet backwards.
z, y, x, w, v, u, t, s, r, q, p
Just ... not as good as last night.
Yeah, the thing about paella is
you have to watch it pretty close
or it turns into a ...
Sticky ... of crap ?
The thing with paellas,
You have to be here in order to cook it,
and some people weren't here.
So, Peter, I think your paella is great !
I tried my best.
In fact, I'm gonna have me some more.
Anybody else ? Gretchen ?
Oh, no.
Thank you.
Silas, get your elbows off the table.
Hum, I don't wanna make this awkward,
but I wanted to apologize for coming by last week.
Your mother told be that you were
having a party, in honor of your father.
Yeah that pretty much sucked.
Silas, don't be a brat and
get your elbows off the table.
I wanted you two to know that,
I respect the memory of your father.
We've heard the speech :
I'm not hear to replace him, I just want to sleep with your mom.
Your mother asked you several times, Silas.
You're gonna let him do that ?
Show some respect.
Gretchen, this isn't how we usually act,
I apologize.
She's right, we usually have dinner
at the dining room table,
we usually don't eat the same thing
two nights in a row,
we don't use cloth napkins,
we put our elbows wherever the fuck we want !
Pull ...
We don't dress up like
we're going to some movie premiere,
What are you, on your 8th glass of wine ?
You could use some boundaries, son.
Okay, dinner's over.
Silas go up to your room.
Andy, would you drive Gretchen home ?
I would like to, I'm a little hum...
He's too stoned to drive !
I'll take her.
Silas, you're not going anywhere !
I'll drive her home.
Er, I don't know you.
He's a police man.
I don't know him.
You don't know Silas either !
He's Shane's brother.
Alright, I'll drive her.
You've had too much to drink.
Sorry mom.
No.
You're right honey.
No need to apologize.
Gretchen, Silas will drive you home.
Silas, there and back, this is your last drive.
- Peter.
- Yeah ?
I'm sorry about what I said about the food.
I'm gonna go feed the cat.
Dinner with the family.
I can't believe they let you have this stuff.
This is awesome !
You think the Agrestic police force
has the budget for someone to monitor these things ?
No, no one sees these except me.
There !
Oh, that's Kate Valenski.
Martin's wife ?
- Yeah.
- Jesus !
I know, can't be anymore than 75 pounds now,
Monday to Sunday, vanishing away
Wait, I think something good is coming up.
Better than the guy shiting
in the mail home ?
Better ! Wait for it. Wait for it !
There !
Is that Litman ? Naked ?
Around at 10 o'clock, every evening !
I haven't had any complains yet.
That's cause everyone's inside molesting their kids.
Dark !
Well 3 hours of Agrestic going wild
will do that to you.
Has it been 3 hours already ?
Oh shit. Oh shit !
This is better than porn.
Yeah well, better enjoy it while you can,
some fucking low life stole two of them already.
The cameras ?
And the free-drug zone signs,
and the sasquash costume.
You're pissin' of a lot of people Celia.
Yeah that must mean that's working.
Hey !
Thanks for the dick.
Sure thing
Promise you'll change my name.
I promise.
Good, here you go.
Unite victims everywhere, make millions.
You're not gonna read it ?
No, no, I'm gonna go to bed.
Sleep in the van,
You gotta be up the morning.
Okay? Give my best to Abumb Chuck.
I drove half a continent to see you Andy.
Well you've got your signature,
so god speed.
Have you ever been fishing in Baha ?
In Baha ?
No, I...
You don't understand, I have a thing here.
I'm helping my sister-in-law.
I'm taking care of these kids.
I'm getting my shit together.
That would be lovely,
if you truly believed it.
What are you doing ?
Do you realize how many felonies we've commited ?
I'm publishing the book as fiction.
Then why are you here ?
I'm going to save you Andy !
Hey!
You look good.
Are you okay ?
Yeah !
No.
Not on this side.
I thought you sleep on the left side.
I do, just not in this bed.
Okay.
I see.
Thanks.
Candles are nice.
it's calming
You're incredibly sexy.
We have to be quiet.
Of course.
Why did you do that thing ?
To his elbow ?
This didn't work out so good.
No ! It's just...
the first time I invite somebody over.
And we rushed things a little ?
Oh, maybe just the
sleep over part.
But I'll call you.
Thanks for trying.
It's me.
Everything's right ?
Everything is not alright,
Conrad's plan did not work out.
Then we got some problems.
We sure do !
Talk to me.
He has walked out of my front door 5 minutes ago,
and I don't want him
ever coming back.
Did he do something to you ?
No no it's nothing like that, it's just ...
I forgot myself.
Agent Wonderbread is not my husband.
He isn't ?
Not in this lifetime, I do not love him.
And I'm never gonna love him.
He don't know that right ?
No, I left it okay, I think.
You're going to have to play like that for a little while long.
Are you cool with that ?
Oh yeah, I think I can do that.
Meet me at the house tomorrow, alright?
Okay.
Transcript/Synchro : Greendies
Relecture : Le_Chuck