Wormhole’s established.
M.A.L.P. is on the way.
- What kind of facility is this ?
- Some sort of research outpost.
The database has little information
other than whatever was being done...
... was completed.
The place is abandoned.
- Well, sounds promising.
- We have M.A.L.P. telemetry.
Environmental sensors
indicate viable life support.
- Visuals coming in now.
- Put it on-screen.
Or maybe it never was abandoned.
Ancients ?
- He got one of their scanners.
- So do we.
Just because they know how to use
Ancient technology--
I am speaking to whoever
sent this machine to our home.
If you intend us harm,
proceed no further.
But if you come in friendship...
... please know
you are most welcome here.
Put that thing away.
We told them we were friendly.
l’m friendly.
Is that thing set to » stun« ou » ??
- Friendlier.
- You coming too ?
Well, Ancients or not,
they’re obviously an advanced society.
l would like to establish diplomatic
relations with them immediately.
Well, you’re the boss. Let’s go.
What happened ?
We make a U-turn ?
No. This is the place. We’re here.
Look.
So not exactly like our gateroom.
Hello. We’re the people
who sent the machine through earlier.
We come in friendship.
l am Niam. Welcome to Asuras.
Still waiting to meet an ancient
race that’s invented the car.
Our destination is not much further.
The High Council is eager to meet you.
How long have your people lived here ?
We built this city
thousands of years ago.
You actually built it ?
You didn’t find it ?
- No.
- You’ve had no trouble with the Wraith ?
- Any particular reason ?
The Wraith do not concern us.
See ? He didn’t answer my question.
l’m sorry, you didn’t actually
answer my question.
- Oh, my--
- No kidding.
How many people live here ?
Millions.
The power requirements
for a city this size must be enormous.
Plus shielding from the Wraith...
... we’re talking, what, three
Zero-Point Modules, maybe four.
Sorry. ZPMs. A device that taps vast
amounts of power from vacuum energy.
Oh, yes. We have many of those.
Exactly how many is » many« ou » ??
Exactly doesn’t matter.
Many is plenty.
Truthfully, l do not know
the exact number.
More than enough to suit our needs.
l assume
that you built them yourselves ?
- Yes.
- Rodney, you’re slobbering.
- Please.
The Council is waiting.
- Well, we have our answer.
- To what question ?
Whether or not they’re Ancients.
In which case,
l got a bone to pick with him.
Where did you come from ?
We are explorers. We come
from a world very far from here.
Really far.
In fact, you can’t get there from here.
How did you happen to discover us ?
We came across an Ancient outpost...
- ... that listed this gate in its database.
- But no other information, l might add.
The database neglected
to include information...
... on a society of millions of Ancients,
such as yourselves.
- Why is that ?
- We are the last of those...
... you refer to as » Ancients. »
We were a race united in our pursuit
of knowledge and enlightenment...
... but our paths diverged...
... after a disagreement
tore the fabric of that unity.
What kind of a disagreement ?
Suffice it to say they chose to disregard
our counsel during a time of conflict...
... and they suffered the consequences
at the hands of a relentless enemy.
The Wraith.
We parted ways with our brothers
and sisters, and came here...
... where we have thrived
for many thousands of years.
Yeah, you’ve been doing
a lot of thriving.
May l ask what counsel...
... did you offer
that the others chose to disregard ?
Our Ancient brothers were arrogant...
... which led them to greatly
underestimate the Wraith...
... an enemy
inferior in intelligence, yes...
... but vastly superior
in numbers and ruthlessness.
Wouldn’t have been outnumbered
if you helped.
- There’s that bone l wanted to pick.
- You said they were your brothers.
Where we come from
we take care of our family.
What my friend is trying to say is...
... there’s still a lot of Wraith,
and we could use your help.
Eradication of them
is among our goals.
You mean you have a plan ?
We do.
Great. Let’s hear it.
Your plan, l mean.
l doubt that you would be able
to grasp its complexity and scope.
- l’m very good with complexity.
- And scope.
All you need to know...
... is that one day soon
the Wraith will exist no more.
All we need to know ?
There are matters of importance
for me to attend to.
In the meantime, you are explorers,
and in need of rest and sustenance.
We have made arrangements for you
to spend a short time among us.
He says the other Ancients
are arrogant ?
l apologize if you felt Oberoth
was condescending in any way.
How about in every way.
It is difficult for him to see you
as capable of understanding.
Yeah, well,
how many Ph. D. s does he have ?
l was wondering, your people have
been here for thousands of years ?
- Yes.
- In that time...
... most Ancients
we know have Ascended.
You know of Ascension ?
Well, yes. In fact, we always thought
that Ancients were no longer around.
That most of them evolved
to the point of transforming...
- ... into beings of pure energy.
- This is true.
But l take it your people
aren’t interested ?
Oh, Ascension is the goal
of many of us...
... but Oberoth feels
there is still much to do.
We must become all that we can.
You don’t agree with him, do you ?
Your guest quarters are this way.
Must have been quite a serious
falling-out for the Ancients...
... to eliminate any reference
to them in the entire database.
Unless they’re lying.
Might it not be possible that these
people merely discovered this city...
... as you discovered Atlantis ?
Wouldn’t be surprised.
They don’t seem very Ancienty to me.
Ancienty ?
Yes, that’s the word l was looking for.
You think they could be deceiving us ?
Teyla’s right. They could’ve found
the city and moved in years ago.
l feel they are hiding something.
Other than their plan to defeat
the Wraith, you mean ?
There’s no plan.
No. l don’t think so either.
Why would they say that
if they don’t ?
They figured a way to hide
from the galaxy, including the Wraith...
... and are happy to go on with their lives
just minding their own business.
Whoever they are.
l think that
is what we need to find out.
Thank you for taking
the time to see me.
l felt we might achieve more...
... in a one-on-one meeting,
leader to leader.
What is it you wish to achieve ?
The establishment of diplomatic
and trade relations between our people.
Trading ?
Do you really believe that you have
anything of value to offer us ?
It’s possible, Oberoth.
And there is only one way
to find that out.
But l do know that there is something
you could offer us.
That is assistance
with our fight against the Wraith.
As l’ve said before, we will commence
our plan at a time of our choosing.
Would you consider sharing tools so
that we could better protect ourselves...
- ... until that time comes ?
- Tools ? Such as ?
What we call Zero-Point Modules.
They’re our power source.
We are in urgent need
of as many as you could spare.
Then am l to assume that this
settlement of yours is of Lantian design ?
Yes. We discovered it on our travels.
It was uninhabited, so we decided
to establish a base there...
... but as l’m sure you know...
... sufficient shield generation requires
tremendous amounts of power.
Where is this settlement
of yours located ?
It’s on the outer edges of this galaxy, in
an area teeming with Wraith hive ships...
... which is why
we need the power modules--
We are unable to part
with any power modules.
Our needs require all of them.
Would you consider offering your city
as a place of refuge to my people--
Many of our citizens are amused
by the occasional visitor...
... such as yourselves, for a short time.
- But not you.
- No.
And the very idea
of greater numbers...
... over a protracted period of time
is out of the question.
Now, we have had some success...
... fighting off the Wraith
with limited supplies and personnel.
l believe that
with your assistance we might--
l am unaccustomed
to repeating myself.
However, leader to leader,
l will say this once again.
We will eliminate the Wraith
at a time of our choosing.
And you don’t care how many
of my people or anyone else...
... dies while you make up
your mind to act ?
You said earlier
that your brothers’greatest weakness...
... was their arrogance.
May l suggest it runs in the family ?
- l am sorry you feel you must leave.
- Yes, so am l.
Oberoth can be intractable.
Not exactly the word
l was looking for.
- Un-Ancienty ?
- Not that word either.
We will send you a message
through the stargate soon.
Hopefully this is just
a stumbled beginning of a--
Lower your weapons.
How low would you like them ?
Do you really wish to challenge us ?
Maybe the floor ?
l thought you didn’t want us here,
Oberoth.
l don’t, but you possess information
that l simply must have.
These trade negotiations
can be real murder.
We need to find a way out of here.
Rodney ?
This cell is similar to ours.
Is there something in the design
that could offer a possible escape ?
- Are you serious ? It’s a jail cell.
- Yes, l know.
The only way out would be
to disable the force field...
... which is only accessible from the--
Outside ?
- l brought you food.
- Oh, thank God. l’m starving.
Ronon, l can’t think
on an empty stomach.
- Why are we being held here ?
- Oberoth wishes to speak to you further.
He can no longer trust
that you’Il remain in your quarters.
He’s right.
- If he wants to talk, why doesn’t he ?
- He will. Very soon.
That’s nice. Isn’t that nice ?
Here’s a question :
- Who the hell are you people ?
- And don’t tell us you’re Ancients.
We know enough about them to know
they’d never treat people this way.
l am sorry about this.
But once Oberoth has finished
his discussions with you...
... you will all be released unharmed.
l’m sorry, but all your credibility
was removed when you locked us up.
You left us no choice.
Neither did you.
You’re the one we liked,
so don’t take this personally.
What are you doing ?
Preventing the Jumper
from communicating.
- Element of surprise.
- Nice.
Go ahead, dial the gate.
Any sign of our new friends ?
Nothing. No unscheduled gate activity,
nothing on the long-range sensors.
l think it’s safe to say
we made a clean getaway.
That or they’re biding their time,
waiting for the right moment to attack.
We’Il keep the security
teams on alert, just in case.
But if they were able to come after us,
l think they would have done so already.
How is Rodney coming
with the database ?
l’Il go check on him.
l wonder how many
rogue Ancients are out there.
If they’re anything like the Asurans,
we’re better off leaving them alone.
How’s it going ?
l’ve searched the database
for any indication of the Asurans, but...
- Still nothing ?
- ... still nothing.
Maybe the Ancients didn’t want
to be reminded of them.
Even if they deleted every reference,
there’d be some hint--
-Colonel ?
- Go ahead.
I need you and Rodney
in the control room immediately.
- Hive ships.
- How’d they get so close ?
Why are we picking them up now ?
- Everything is working.
- Engage the cloak.
l’m already on it. Cloak engaged now.
They’re right over the city.
- How far away is the Daedalus ?
- Not due for weeks.
Doesn’t matter. l’m counting seven
ships. There’s nothing they could do.
They’re scanning for us.
- Hopefully the cloak is--
- They’re firing.
Switch to shields.
l can’t.
The shield generators were hit.
- They knew right where to hit us.
- The cloak has failed.
We need more firepower.
Headed to the Chair room.
- More ships arriving in the system.
- How many more ?
Fifteen.
We can’t fight off that many.
Not without shields.
Attention, this is Weir.
All personnel to the gateroom
for immediate evacuation.
Dial Earth.
John, we need to set the self-destruct.
We just lost automated systems.
We’Il lose the gate.
Go. l’Il detonate it manually.
Maybe the Wraith will take care
of destroying the city.
If they wanted to,
they’d have done it already.
- If any part is left intact, they can find--
- They’Il know how to find Earth.
- l know.
- Okay. Enter your number.
When you are ready, hit this button.
You’Il only have a few seconds.
- Go.
- No, no, no.
l can’t let you do this
without tossing a coin. It’s not right.
l appreciate the offer, Rodney.
Now, get out of here.
Go, all of you !
The way up is blocked.
- How many are trapped ?
- We can’t tell.
We’re losing power.
Get through the gate.
What the hell just happened ?
Who the hell are you people ?
They’re not people.
They’re machines.
Replicators.
What’s happening ?
What’s to become of them ?
We have mined everything we need
from their consciousness.
They are no longer of any use to us.
Ending their lives
seems to be the most prudent course.
l disagree. l believe we still have
a lot to learn from them.
- Learn from them ?
- Yes.
Is it that you fear that ending their lives
would end your hope of Ascension ?
l do object to killing them,
but it is more than that.
l don’t believe we uncovered how much
they’ve learned about Lantian society...
... nor how much
they’ve passed on to others.
They’re of no threat to us, Oberoth.
We see no reason not to continue
our study of them.
Very well. Keep them alive if you wish,
but l shall hold you accountable.
My head is killing me.
How’d we get back here ?
What do you mean » back here« ou » ??
We broke out, got to the Jumper,
gated back to Atlantis.
At least l thought we did.
That is not what l remember.
The only thing l remember
is being in a dark room...
... fighting hand-to-hand for hours.
They created different scenarios
for us during the mind probe...
... looking to gather
information from our responses.
- l thought our escape seemed too easy.
- At least you escaped.
What’d they do to you ?
Torture, in ways too hideous
and intimate to recount.
- Like what ?
- l said too hideous to recount.
l just had a horrible thought.
What if it is still happening ?
Yes.
There’s got to be a way
to know for sure.
- Doesn’t really prove anything.
- It’s real, Dr. McKay.
Your minds are no longer
being probed.
Good to know it was just our minds.
Oh, please don’t make me sick.
Please, come with me.
We’re in space.
The star drive. Of course,
the rumbling sound we heard.
With all the ZPMs
you’re able to fly the city.
Yes, Dr. McKay.
Watch now. We’re about
to open a hyperspace window.
Where are we going ?
Atlantis.
The probes of your minds
uncovered the truth.
Atlantis had not been destroyed
by the Wraith...
... 10,000 years ago
as we had believed.
You came to live there from home,
a planet called Earth.
Why didn’t you dial the gate
and send us through ?
We’re not taking you to Atlantis.
Our intention is to destroy it.
Why ?
- Retribution.
- For what ?
The disagreement you once had ?
The Ancients no longer live there.
We are the only inhabitants of that city.
There was no disagreement, Dr. Weir.
Only betrayal.
If you wish to know the truth
of who we are, l will show you.
Élizabeth...
It’s okay, Rodney.
The Ancients, as you call them...
... were desperate in their search
for a way to fight the Wraith.
Though greatly outnumbered, they relied
on their technological superiority...
... to give them a needed advantage.
Soon, they succeeded in creating one.
Instead of building bigger, more powerful
weapons, they built smaller ones.
Microscopic machines designed
to infiltrate and destroy from within.
Nanites.
In these tiny killing machines,
the Ancients imbued an aggression...
... that surpassed
even that of their enemy.
The technology allowed
for organic assimilation...
... and self-replication
to increase their effectiveness.
And replicate they did.
They grew in numbers, evolving at a
rate that took the Ancients by surprise.
The molecular machines
began interlocking...
... assembling themselves to form
even more complex organisms...
... eventually evolving
into the most effective...
... and efficient form they knew of.
This is how we were born.
We took the image of our creators,
yet we were far different from them.
The aggression programmed
into our core remained...
... fueling a rage we could not contain.
We implored them to have this removed
from our programming...
... but the Ancients wanted a weapon.
Since their scientists
included a directive...
... prohibiting us
from ever harming them...
... they continued the experiment.
When the Ancients concluded that
the experiment had gone too far...
... that we would never become
the weapon they desired to create...
... they decided to end it.
And so they chose to destroy us,
to leave no trace of us behind.
Thank you.
Obviously, the Ancients didn’t do
a thorough enough job wiping them out.
No, a few of the nanites
managed to survive.
All they needed to begin replicating.
- Replicating ?
- This is bad.
They’re similar to an artificial intelligence
SG-1 encountered years ago...
... that evolved from a tiny block
Replicator into human form.
- They may even be related.
- l read those reports.
Stargate Command could barely
defeat the human form Replicators.
Which is why l said this is bad.
The difference here
is they’re emulating the Ancients.
They’ve even built themselves
a version of Atlantis.
- And then some.
- Why would they do this ?
l think they look at the Ancients
like parents who betrayed them...
... and now they see humans
as the favored siblings...
... who receive all the parents’love.
They’ve been seeking revenge
ever since.
Just what we need. More bad guys.
Which means
we just identified the race...
... that created the nanovirus
that nearly killed me.
It almost killed a lot of people.
Weren’t you able to defeat that virus
with an electromagnetic pulse ?
That was different.
Those were individual nanites...
... easy to disrupt
with a simple EM pulse.
These things have evolved
way beyond that...
... with the interdependent organic
constituents of a far greater complexity.
Are you feeling better ?
Yes.
Follow me.
l have an offer to make you. Something
that could greatly benefit us both.
Well, if the offer involves
saving Atlantis...
... we’re willing to listen.
It does.
We have achieved much
since our second birth.
We have evolved
to take the form of our creators...
... built a city far grander
than they ever achieved.
Yet, we are still restricted from reaching
a pivotal point in our evolution.
You want to Ascend.
Yes.
Many among us, like Oberoth,
have no desire to experience this.
They are content
with our present state.
But there are a few of us who recognize
that as a civilization, we are stagnant.
We seek to continue
our own evolution.
Truly emulate the Ancients
and their ultimate achievement.
Even though they betrayed you.
They are our creators...
... and Ascension is the final step
to equaling them...
... to becoming one with them.
No offense, but how are a bunch
of machines gonna do that ?
Are you so different ?
- We’re living, breathing people.
- Constructed from cells...
... consuming and burning energy,
governed by electrical impulses--
l didn’t say l could Ascend.
Metaphysical debates aside,
what do you want ?
We’re not exactly Acension experts.
We do know killing people
isn’t the best way.
We realize this, and we have done
much to repress our violent nature...
... but yet it still remains within us.
We believe this, above all,
is what prevents us from Ascending.
You looking for therapy ?
We want to rewrite our base code
to remove the directives for aggression.
What’s stopping you ?
Ancients put in place measures
to prevent us...
... from altering the code ourselves...
- ... but you can do it.
- Me ?
During our probe we learned
that you are capable of doing this.
Funny, all l remember is the torture.
What’s in it for us ?
We’Il stop the others
from attacking Atlantis.
We’Il help in your fight
against the Wraith.
And Oberoth will agree to this ?
l believe Oberoth is attacking Atlantis
as a result of that programming.
If we can prove to him
it can be altered--
- You think he’Il see the light ?
- Hallelujah.
l will do everything in my power
to persuade him.
- Why should we trust you ?
- Because we are willing to trust you.
By extending this offer,
we are jeopardizing our very existence.
l saw in you compassion, Dr. Weir.
Someone who could
come to understand our plight.
Help us, and we will help you.
When it comes right down to it,
we don’t have much of a choice.
We’re drawing closer to Atlantis.
Soon we will drop out of hyperspace.
How’s it coming, Rodney ?
-Slowly.
- What’s the holdup ?
The holdup ? Do you have any idea
what l’m trying to do ?
Niam gave you access to the
program code, you’re screwing around.
Oh, that is so relatively accurate.
Thank you.
We’re not dealing
with Rock’Em Sock’Em Robots.
We’re dealing with a complex code of
over 3 billion chemical-based sequences.
It’s like trying to reconfigure
the DNA double helix.
Okay, so, what, five minutes ?
It will be done when it is done, and you
applying pressure is not gonna--
- What ?
-Gotta go. mcKay out.
Rodney, what’s going on ? Rodney ?
- Did you do it ?
- Yes, yes.
l have removed
the aggression directive.
It is uploading to Niam as we speak,
but l discovered something else...
- ... nothing short of brilliant.
- What ?
Okay. Even though these Replicators
are each separate functioning beings...
... their command code is interconnected
over a powerful subspace frequency.
They have these
periodic collective-program updates...
... or merges,
where they exchange new information.
That’s how Niam
hopes to distribute the new code.
Exactly. While l was working on it,
l figured out a way to create a glitch...
... that, on my command,
should momentarily freeze them.
- Should ?
- Okay, will. Dead in their tracks...
... temporarily,
until they figure out how to override it.
How long ?
l don’t know.
That’s why l said momentarily.
- Days ? Hours ? Minutes ?
- It’s minutes, but l don’t know.
- That’s what l was saying.
- Ten, 20 ?
You want a number ?
Seven minutes and 31 seconds.
- You happy ?
- No. That’s not enough time.
- You wanted a number.
- Bigger.
- Might be longer.
- Or shorter.
l don’t know.
You’re missing the point--
Gentlemen, focus, please.
Will that be enough time
for us to escape ?
It will have to be.
Not much point in leaving
without blowing this place up first.
How do we do that ?
Oh, that’s me.
Right. Surprise, surprise.
Look, why don’t l just go
on these missions by myself ?
l’Il rig a ZPM overload.
What about Niam ?
Are we not exploiting his trust ?
Even if he’s able to honor
his end of the deal...
... there’s no guarantee he can stop
Oberoth from attacking Atlantis.
We will offer him the chance
to come with us...
... but we cannot leave this city intact.
- Are you sure this will work ?
- Please. Of course it will work.
- Why’s it taking so long ?
- Why do you always have to-- ?
l need to calibrate the frequencies.
- l wanna make sure l freeze them all.
- Oh, yeah, all would be good.
Okay, just let me finish ?
Thank you.
Okay.
Here we go in five, four, three, two...
- Hey, it worked.
- Interesting.
Okay. We should move
to the ZPM room.
- Why isn’t he frozen ?
- His code’s changed.
Until he’s distributed it to the others,
he’Il be different than the rest.
What happened ?
What was that ?
- We just dropped out of hyperspace.
- We need to move.
Come with us. l’Il explain on the way.
Now, Ronon, l could use...
Thanks.
You want me to go with you ?
You must understand our situation.
If you can’t stop Oberoth--
l said l would do everything
in my power.
But can you promise
that you will succeed ?
Our lives and the lives
of all of our people are at stake here.
You merge through a subspace
connection. Even with us...
... you should be able
to spread the new code amongst others.
Come with us, Niam.
Ascension is within your grasp.
You can’t turn back.
- Damn.
- What is it ?
l need to utilize all three ZPMs.
- l was hoping to bring one with us.
- Do what you can. Three minutes.
Look, l already told you-- Never mind.
l need an access code
to remove the fail-safes.
Now, how about our weapons ?
We can recover them on the way.
Not so arrogant now, are you ?
McKay !
Come on.
- So much for seven-and-a-half minutes.
- Hey, it was an arbitrary number.
Colonel Sheppard...
Go !
Ronon, set your gun to » kill. »
- It is.
- Okay, start the overload.
We need to be in a Jumper,
or clear of the city--
The Jumper’s not far. Almost there.
No, l didn’t want them to stop it.
As soon as l trigger the overload...
- ... there’Il be practically zero lag time.
- Practically ?
- A few seconds for it to build up power--
- How many ?
- l don’t know.
- Five ? Ten ?
- Again with the arbitrary numbers.
- We need to move.
Okay, start the overload. Now.
- This way.
- What is that ?
The sound of the city
about to blow. Move !
Get the roof open
or this is gonna be a short trip.
Don’t wait for me.
l’m saying
if we can’t get out of the bay--
No matter,
the overload’s happening now.
- We’re about to explode.
- Is the roof open ?
Yes, go.
Nice work, all of you.
Thank you.
What’s wrong ?
Something is happening.
What is it ?
The others on my planet.
They know what l’ve done.
l’m being reset.
Rodney, do something.
It’s too late. They’re--
That’s not going to hold him.
l’m so sorry. l had-- l didn’t--
You okay ?
Yeah.
- How’s it going ?
- Still nothing.
Either the Ancients chose
to conceal every record extremely well...
... or they simply deleted them.
l’m leaning towards the latter.
Perhaps they think
they’re all destroyed.
Or they didn’t want
anyone to know they failed.
Again,
there is nothing more annoying...
... than people that won’t admit
their own mistakes.
True.
McKay and Zelenka are scouring
the database for any information.
So far, not much, as in nothing.
These Replicators,
they’re probably already at work...
... building themselves another Atlantis.
Now they know all about us.
Well, we beat them this time.
Maybe we scared them off.
Yeah. Maybe.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]