NARRATOR :
Previously on Stargate Atlantis :
l know definitely that the Jumper
is somewhere in this area.
Friendly ? Or are you hungry ?
Must be broadcasting
at a frequency you can hear.
SHEPPARD :
Sending through 1 000.
ZELENKA :
Your sea monster.
It’s still swimming around in circles
in the same area which means--
l have the Jumper.
The animal is circling around it.
SHEPPARD : All you have to do is open
your door, walk to my Jumper.
McKAY : Hey, pal. You won’t get
to eat me today.
- He’s the reason we found you.
McKAY : Really ?
SHEPPARD : How did the camping go ?
ZELENKA : Oh, splendid.
l was able to run
ground-penetrating radar tests...
... to test the dielectric permittivity
of the region’s subsurface.
Sweet.
What about you ?
How was the hunting ?
If there was any game...
... it was scared off
by the noises the machines made.
l said l was sorry.
It was necessary for the tests.
You volunteered to go.
Well, if l do something like that
again, shoot me.
He was like this all night, you know,
very agitated. Had me scared.
He’Il be all right. Get him home,
get him a nice warm bath, hot meal--
Oh, no.
- What ?
- Where’s Atlantis ?
- It should be right in front of us.
- Why isn’t it ?
l don’t know.
Is it cloaked ?
No. They would have radioed us.
- What are you saying, we’re lost ?
- Wait.
Adjust your heading
40 degrees south.
The navigation system is off.
- Why ?
ZELENKA : l don’t know.
It could be any
of a number of reasons...
... clock drift, the fluctuations in the
magnetosphere from the sunspots.
There it is.
[ZELENKA SPEAKING IN CZECH]
See ? No harm, no foul.
You might want to take Teyla up
on her offer for meditation lessons.
- You could use a little unwinding.
- Just land this thing.
TEYLA :
And then slowly exhale...
... allowing each breath
to cleanse you...
... restoring your body and spirit.
Feel your mind clearing...
... open to all that surrounds you.
Embrace the silence.
[DEX SNORING ]
Ronon ?
[WOMAN SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
l’m sorry, l do not understand.
McKAY :
Élizabeth. Did you get my e-mail ?
Which e-mail ?
One of the seven today ?
Or one of the 18 yesterday ?
l know
l’m being unusually persistent...
... but that should underscore
its importance.
We cannot keep all three ZPMs from
the Replicator takeover, Rodney.
We get one. l don’t know
how to make it clearer for you.
l felt if l could just outline
the reasons for keeping them.
- You know, bullet point, very brief.
- It was 26 pages.
But if we hope to persuade
Stargate Command--
Okay, so tell me. Who would you
deprive of the other ZPMs ?
The Antarctic outpost ?
No, they need it to protect Earth.
How about the Odyssey ?
They’re getting the ZPM to help
in their fight against the Ori.
Already we have enough power now
to raise the shield...
... and cloak the city and dial home.
Can you start seeing
the glass as half-full ?
You mean one-third full.
- No more e-mails.
- Right.
[DEX GRUNTING ]
l’m sorry.
You weren’t expecting that ?
[TEYLA LAUGHING ]
l was tired. It was a long day.
- And to be honest, l--
- You don’t care much for meditation.
Never could sit still
long enough for it.
All the more reason for you
to consider--
What is it ?
[WOMAN SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
That woman.
What woman ?
[WOMAN SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[GROANING ]
[GASPING ]
Hey, hey. What’s wrong ?
What ?
McKAY :
Hm.
Hey. How long have you been
standing there ?
- Hour or so.
- What ? Why didn’t you say anything ?
l feel like a-- Oh, it’s the kidding.
- What did you wanna show me ?
- Right there.
- Wow, all that water.
- Just wait for it.
That’s my friend. He’s back.
The scan’s clean.
No sign of any physical abnormality.
We’ve seen devices that mess
with people’s minds...
... cause them to hallucinate.
They’ve had corresponding
neural activity to indicate a problem.
No, l’m afraid for the moment
there doesn’t appear to be...
... any physiological reasons
for her hallucinations.
Then why did she see what she saw ?
l don’t quite know.
Many ancestors died here recently.
During the Replicator invasion, the
crew of the Tria were all murdered.
Perhaps they attempted to ascend
but were prevented from doing so.
Trapped between this plane
of existence and the next.
You mean ghosts ?
If you ask me,
it’s too much meditation.
- Is she gonna be okay ?
- l don’t know.
She just needs rest.
We’ve been through a lot--
- There you are.
- l told you--
- No, not you. Sheppard.
- Thank you.
Not that l don’t wanna talk to you,
in fact, you’Il find it interesting as--
What are you saying ?
Check it out.
l found it in the Ancient database.
They’ve a subsection
on indigenous Lantian animal life.
Did you know there was a lobster-like
crustacean the size of a Buick ?
- Hm. And what is that ?
- That’s Rodney’s whale friend.
But not actually a whale.
Whale-like, but not a mammal.
- It’s a fish. A big fish.
SHEPPARD : Ancients have a name for it ?
Yeah. Flagisallus.
They were terrible at naming things.
- l’ve just called it whale, for now.
- And why are you studying this ?
McKAY : Because he’s there now,
circling the city.
Probably the whale that saved me
last year...
... when l was trapped in that Jumper.
l thought Zelenka and l saved you.
You did, technically,
only after Sam led you to me.
Sam ?
It’s the whale. l named him
after Samantha Carter.
It’s for personal reasons.
You named him after
Samantha Carter.
Well, Sam’s a boy’s name too.
And how do you know he’s a he ?
Because l cross-referenced
the renderings in the database...
... with the whale outside and you’Il
see, the males have a prominent--
It’s okay. Never mind.
l’Il take your word for it.
l trust this little diversion
isn’t cutting into your work time ?
Oh, no, of course not. No, l’m just
dabbling in my free time.
All right then, boys, dabble away.
So these whales, did the Ancients
say they’re good eating ?
- Oh, you wouldn’t.
- l would.
[WOMAN SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Hello ?
Wait.
[GROANING ]
[WOMAN SPEAKING
IN SCREECHY FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
KATE : You don’t understand
what the woman is saying ?
No. l believe she’s speaking
in the ancestral tongue.
You said she’s afraid
of the burned man ?
No. It is my sense
that she’s trying to help him.
Whatever it is she fears,
l do not know.
- Did you try to talk to her ?
- Yes.
But she seems unaware of me.
It is as if l’m not even there.
If these are apparitions, why do you
think they’re appearing to you ?
Too much meditation.
Something Ronon said to me.
Well, there are those who believe
that meditation...
... is a way of opening a door
to the spiritual world.
If these are ancestors trapped
between planes of existence...
... perhaps they’re trying
to communicate something to me.
Maybe they believe
l can help them to move on.
KATE : l don’t know why
she’s experiencing these visions.
She’s always been one to shoulder
a lot of emotional responsibility.
She may be carrying guilt...
... over what happened
to the Ancients here recently.
- Why ? It wasn’t her fault.
- No, of course not.
But somewhere deep inside her
she may feel complicit...
... in the actions
that led up to their murders.
l’Il continue working with her,
see if l can sort things out.
l’Il make sure she gets rest
even if it means...
... taking her off the next mission.
Oh, she does seem tired.
She hasn’t been sleeping well...
... and she’s been complaining
of headaches.
Dr. Beckett gave her
a clean bill of health.
Well, we’Il just keep an eye on her.
Hopefully it’Il all pass.
Let’s hope so. Thank you.
[GROANING ]
KATE : Now both of you are seeing them ?
Why do you suppose that is ?
Well, that’s why we’ve come to you.
Perhaps they believe
that appearing to two people...
... will increase the chance
their message will be heard.
If, in fact, they are trying
to communicate something to us.
Or maybe it’s just
the power of suggestion.
It’s been documented that
when one person sees a ghost...
... it won’t be long before others
around them see it too.
You said it yourself. You’ve all
been through a lot recently.
When’s the last time
you took a day off ?
Exactly. Have you seen
any more apparitions ?
- Not recently.
- How are the headaches ?
Still have them.
Have you been able to sleep ?
Perhaps Dr. Beckett can prescribe
something for you.
For both of you.
Here you are.
You are not going to believe this.
l’ve been monitoring Sam
on the scanners--
Stop calling him that.
- Why ?
- It’s creepy.
No, it’s not. Here he is, circling
the city. He won’t leave.
- You didn’t feed him, did you ?
- No. Look, now, if l widen the scan...
SHEPPARD : Another whale.
- Yeah, probably the mother.
That guy’s the size
of a football field.
A Canadian football field.
- So the first one was a baby ?
- Yeah.
Hey, want to take a closer look ?
McKAY :
Uh...
Radek. Didn’t know anyone
was here.
- Do you need to use the Jumper ?
- Yeah.
Gonna check out some whales.
Rodney’s on his way.
He’s taking some Dramamine, but,
yeah, we can take another Jumper.
Just be careful. l’m not sure
if l fixed the navigational glitch.
The other Jumpers
might be affected as well.
We won’t go far.
We’Il stay within sight.
Plus, you’Il be tracking us
from the control room.
l will ? Oh, yes, l will.
Did you say whales ?
These should help.
But don’t take them
until you can have...
... at least eight hours
of uninterrupted rest.
Around here ?
When does that ever happen ?
Both Dr. Heightmeyer and l think...
... you should take the time
to make it happen.
- All right. Thank you, Carson.
- Thank you.
[PEOPLE SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[GROANING ]
- You all right ?
- Yeah, l’m fine.
l just-- l never feel safe
in these things underwater.
But in space you’re okay ?
Yeah, of course l am.
Why wouldn’t l be ?
- Zelenka, are you there ?
ZELENKA [ON RADIO] : I’m here. Hello.
The whales are deeper, less than
a kilometer, in your 2:00 position.
Oh, there they are.
Should have a visual on them
any moment now.
McKAY :
There’s Sam.
And there’s Mama.
We need to get a closer look.
[PEOPLE SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Ronon ?
You saw them too.
McKAY :
All right, not too close, okay ?
We still have no idea
what these things eat.
What ? What is it ?
Nothing. Just got a headache
all of a sudden.
- Where’d they go ?
- l don’t know.
[WHALE MURMURING ]
Oh.
- They’re right in front of you.
- Yeah, well, we’re aware of that.
[WHALE MURMURING ]
- What’s wrong ?
- Now my head’s hurting too.
- That’s not a coincidence.
- l don’t think so.
- l’m pulling back.
- Good idea.
Perhaps it’s the whales’
echolocation mechanism.
It’s creating uncomfortable
vibrations--
Yes, Radek, we are moving away.
Try to keep up, okay ?
Oh, my.
SHEPPARD :
my what ?
l’m detecting
several more whales.
How many more ?
Dozens more.
They’re still several kilometers
away from you...
... but they’re heading towards you.
[WHALE MURMURING ]
- Rodney.
- What ?
Your nose is bleeding.
Oh.
Now you’re all seeing them ?
l just got word
that other people in the city...
... are starting to see them too.
Some see the burned man,
others the Ancient woman...
... and a few, such as Ronon,
see what appear to be scientists.
Something’s going on here.
Two things remain constant.
All of the apparitions are Ancients,
and they seem pretty worried.
It is as if they are trying
to warn us about something.
ZELENKA [ON RADIO] : Dr. Weir.
- Yes, Radek ?
You’d better come
to the control room, right away.
Be right there.
WEIR :
What’s their status ?
They’re moving away
from the whales.
Hopefully that will alleviate
their pain.
John, this is Élizabeth.
How are you holding up ?
Other than feeling like my head’s
about to explode, l’m fine.
[WHALE MURMURING ]
l thought we were moving away
from them.
l’m trying to,
but they’re cutting us off.
WEIR :
What happened ?
These whales are getting
way too close.
Oh, crap.
John, what’s going on there ?
Rodney’s passed out.
His ears are bleeding.
We gotta get out of the water.
Medical team to Jumper bay.
John, are you all right ?
John.
SHEPPARD : We’re out of the water.
Rodney’s in trouble.
-Have a medical team ready.
- Already done.
[BLEEPING ]
Their eardrums have been perforated.
How ?
The whales are emitting an intense,
low-frequency pulse, like a sonar...
... as well as an EM field.
The combination is dangerous
to humans.
Particularly in close proximity.
[YELLING ]
It’s the whales.
Hearing’s been impaired. It’Il heal.
It’s their echolocation. It’s
creating very powerful vibrations.
The closer we got,
the worse it became--
Yes, yes, Rodney, we know.
Oh.
- What ?
- They should rest.
Agreed. l’Il come back.
ZELENKA : The whales are approaching
from every direction.
It appears that they’re converging
on Atlantis.
- We’re their destination ?
- Yes, it appears so.
The signals they emit are their way
of communicating with each other.
The closer they get to the city...
... the more it may affect
the people living here.
- Even above the waterline ?
TEYLA : We are already being affected.
Several are experiencing headaches...
... not as severe as Dr. McKay’s
or Col. Sheppard’s.
- If these whales get any closer--
- Turn on the shield.
Aye.
These apparitions
we’ve been seeing...
... if they are indeed trying to warn us
of something, perhaps this is it.
l first saw the Ancient woman...
... at the same time Rodney saw
the first whale.
[SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
The pain’s going away.
l think my hearing’s getting
better too.
What about you ?
Rodney.
Canadian Football League’s a joke.
Celine Dion is overrated.
Zelenka is smarter than you are.
Hey.
l found mention of a biolab
in the database.
Ancient scientists used it to study
animal life. We should check it out.
Okay.
Meredith.
How’s it going ?
More people are falling ill.
Headaches, nosebleeds.
l’m giving everyone painkillers
until we figure out how to stop this.
How are you feeling ?
My head’s throbbing a bit,
but l’Il manage. You ?
l’m fine.
Here. Painkillers.
- Just in case.
- Thank you. l hope it doesn’t get--
Hey, hey. What’s this ?
That’s a damn good question.
Who said you could get out of bed ?
We’re feeling a lot better.
l beg to differ. Back to bed.
- We need to check out a lab.
- What lab ?
It’s a biolab.
It turned up in my whale research.
It’s in one of the flooded areas
of the city.
Formerly flooded.
With the area repaired,
we’re able to access it.
The Ancient biologists used it
to study animal life on the planet.
There may be more
information stored.
Such as, how to tell these whales
how to get out of here.
But we won’t know that for sure
until l can have a look at it.
All right.
MAN [ON RADIO] :
Dr. Weir ?
- Go ahead.
- Daedalus just arrived in orbit.
They’re requesting permission
to beam people down.
What do you mean, no ?
WEIR : I’m afraid things down here
might get a lot worse...
... before they get any better.
It’s safer for you to stay up there
until we can sort this problem out.
[WOMAN SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
TEYLA :
l’m sorry, l do not understand.
[HIGH-PITCHED NOISE]
[PEOPLE SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[HIGH-PITCHED NOISE]
[GROANING ]
Come on. Gotta get you
to the infirmary.
This is it.
All right. Let’s see.
[GARBLED NOISE]
- Did you put up the shield ?
WEIR : Yes, but it only extends so far.
And the whales’signals seem
to be able to penetrate it.
We might manage it
if there were only a few whales...
... but we’re talking hundreds now.
They’re swimming closer as we speak.
WEIR : Dr. mcKay is checking out
an Ancient biolab.
Hopefully there’Il be information
there that could lead to a solution.
And if there isn’t ?
We’Il consider evacuating
Atlantis until the whales leave.
Supposing they don’t leave ?
What are you suggesting ?
You’ve got plenty of drones
in your arsenal.
- You’re saying we should kill them ?
- Before they kill you.
McKAY :
They’re not trying to kill us.
It’s quite the opposite.
l think they’re trying to help us.
WEIR : Help us ?
- Come on. You should see this.
- l see your hearing is improved.
- What ?
What is he-- ?
It’s like a receiver calibrated
to the specific frequencies...
... on which the whales communicate.
Ancients designed it to study whales
so they could learn their songs.
They were studying the language...
... trying to assign frequencies
to emotions and identify moods.
All sorts of tree-huggy stuff.
Tell them about the ghosts.
Not ghosts. Image projections. There
appears to be a causal relationship.
They may be what’s been
projecting the images...
... and this receiver should
be able to interpret them.
Seems we’ve been going backwards.
The ghosts aren’t warning us.
- They’re not ?
McKAY : No.
No, the whales may be
using the images to warn us.
About what ?
Yeah, well, that--
That l don’t know yet.
Judging from the way this machine
is freaking out, it can’t be good.
BECKETT :
All right.
How are you faring ?
[GROANING ]
l keep seeing them.
Aye.
[GROANING ]
Me too.
l just spoke with Colonel Caldwell.
The Daedalus infirmary is ready to
beam up the sickest of the patients.
Good. Teyla should be amongst
the first to go.
- No. l’m staying.
BECKETT : You’re far too sick, dear.
He’s a pilot.
The burned man.
l just noticed his uniform.
He is an Ancient pilot.
- Carson.
- Aye.
Your nose.
Oh, bloody hell. Excuse me.
How’s he doing ?
l don’t know. He’s taking a while,
a lot longer than he usually takes.
He can hear you, you know.
Yeah, we know.
Okay, let’s have a listen.
[BEEP]
[GARBLED SPEECH]
- Who’s that ?
- The woman, the Ancient woman.
- That’s her voice, l’m sure.
SHEPPARD : She’s speaking Ancient ?
No. l mean, it doesn’t sound
like the language.
The phonetic rhythm is similar but
l don’t recognize any of the words.
That’s because it’s gibberish.
To be more accurate,
it’s an attempt at mimicry.
Look, it turns out
the receiver is also a transmitter.
They weren’t just trying to learn,
they were attempting to teach theirs...
... by sending auditory
and visual signals.
While doing that, they experienced
a traumatic moment...
... which the whales stored
in their genetic memory.
- The images we’ve been seeing ?
- Exactly. Reruns.
Now, unfortunately, these whales
are several generations...
... removed from the incident, they’re
finding the language a tough go.
It’s like trying to sing
the lyrics to » Macarena. »
You sound out words, but you have
no idea what you’re singing.
Okay, so this traumatic event...
l’m assuming it’s the war
against the Wraith.
That would be my assumption, yes.
The whales are trying to
warn us it might happen again ?
- l don’t know. Possibly.
- So what ? The Wraith might attack.
- Tell us something we don’t know.
- Interesting thing is...
... Ancients seemed aware of
the whales’deficient mimicry skills.
So they incorporated an acoustic
language filter into the receiver.
That’s what’s been taking me
so long to figure out.
Well, did you figure it out ?
Let’s have a listen, shall we ?
[GARBLED SPEECH]
- l guess the answer’s no.
- Well, just hang on, hang on.
If l-- Right.
[WOMAN SPEAKING IN ANCIENT]
Hey, wait a minute.
Play that back again.
[WOMAN SPEAKING IN ANCIENT]
This is Ancient. At least l can
make out a few of the words now.
Incursus ? Something was
attacked or overtaken.
- Meaning Atlantis.
- No. l don’t think so.
- Adarus ?
- What’s Adarus ?
l don’t know.
ZELENKA :
They’ve arrived.
Hundreds of them.
CALDWELL [ON RADIO] : Dr. Weir.
- Go ahead, colonel.
The sick patients have been
beamed up. Infirmary’s filled.
Thank you. Unfortunately, more
people are falling ill down here.
So it’s not making much of a dent.
Whether these creatures are
communicating or not...
... you have to deal with them.
If they don’t--
l’m sure there are options
besides killing them.
- What’s wrong ?
- We figured it out.
l did most of the figuring--
Adarus is a ship.
We found it in the Ancient database.
It’s an Ancient science vessel. About
15,000 years ago, it ran into trouble.
The entire crew was killed
except for the pilot.
The burned man. Teyla noticed
the uniform. He was an Ancient pilot.
- Which would explain the burns.
- What does ?
Ship got hit by a blast of radiation
from the sun.
It’s a coronal mass ejection...
... on a scale that dwarfs
anything our sun has ever emitted.
Apparently, the sun in this system
goes through...
... an unusually turbulent sunspot
cycle every 15,000 years or so.
Ancients have records of this
class of CME occurring twice.
The ship was very close to the sun.
It was a massive prominence.
It arced up, and collapsed...
... when the magnetic field weakened.
An intense proton stream traveling
at over 4 000 kilometers per second.
Most of the crew was killed...
... the pilot opened up a hyperspace
window as they were hit.
He flew the ship here, jumping
ahead of the radiation...
... to warn everyone.
They raised the shield, extended it to
protect a large portion of the planet.
What ?
This is going to happen soon ?
Not soon. It’s happening right now.
How are you doing ?
l have felt better.
- You need any more pain medicine ?
- No.
It does not seem to help anymore.
Well, just hang on.
You’re gonna be fine.
Teyla, look at me.
Look at me.
You gotta hold on.
You gotta teach me
those meditation lessons.
You are hopeless.
Yeah, l know.
Teyla.
Nurse.
McKAY : The magnetic field
is already beginning to weaken.
When that prominence collapses,
the coronal mass ejection will occur.
It’Il erupt from a very small area,
a mere pinprick in comparison...
... to the total sun surface, but
it’Il immediately begin to fan out.
Within a few million miles,
the blast will cut a swath...
... wide enough to take out
this planet.
How much time ?
It will collapse any moment. Less
than an hour before radiation hits.
- Why didn’t we notice this ?
McKAY : These things happen quickly.
This kind of sunspot cycle is chaotic,
impossible to predict.
That caused the glitch
in the Jumper’s navigational system.
Not to mention our focus was on
attack from the Wraith, not the sun.
The whales were aware
this was happening ?
- A lot of animals : whales, dolphins--
- Pigeons.
- -are affected by anomalies
in the magnetosphere.
It’s as if their internal compasses
are somehow--
Pigeons ?
Yeah, homing pigeons. Yes, l used
to raise them before coming here.
We’d consult solar charts
before our pigeon races.
- Pigeon races.
- Rodney.
It’s still a mystery
how they sense this trouble...
... but they do well before we do.
What are our options ?
Raise the shield,
stretch it wide enough...
... to protect a portion of the planet.
Attenuated, more of a thin bubble,
it was able to block enough radiation.
We have found evidence
of mass extinction...
- ... on other parts of the planet.
- Wow. Now we know what caused it.
Okay, so our shield is already
activated. What else ?
Small problem. The Ancients
had three ZPMs at their disposal.
We, as you know, only have one.
Maybe l was insistent on keeping
them because...
... l, too, am able to sense
trouble on the horizon.
Just like a pigeon.
So we just need to get the other
two ZPMs back here temporarily.
The Odyssey’s away. In the time
it would take them to return...
... the blast wave would hit us.
How far can we extend
the shield with one ZPM ?
Enough to cover the city and perhaps
a bit of the ocean surrounding it.
- We should evacuate.
McKAY : We can’t gate to Earth.
We need the ZPM’s power
for the shield.
- The intergalactic bridge ?
- Midway isn’t completed.
We’d need to ferry people
by Jumper. Again, no time.
We’Il send everyone to the Alpha
site, pick them up when it’s over.
l don’t think you understand.
Look, the shield will protect the
city from the initial blast, yes.
The entire ecosystem of this planet
will be damaged beyond recovery...
... for hundreds of years.
We’re talking no plant life,
which means no breathable air.
SHEPPARD :
Beckett.
Élizabeth.
Damn it.
Sergeant Bale. Developed an aneurysm
from the pressure. First fatality.
- How is she ?
- Out of time.
l guess we all are.
Sheppard.
You got a plan ?
Sure.
ZELENKA : Look at them seeking shelter
underneath the umbrella of the city.
No. We don’t have nearly
enough power.
We can extend the shield 20
kilometers beyond the city, maybe.
There’s no way of knowing
whether we can sustain it...
... under a radiation blast
of 50,000 rem.
Colonel Caldwell, this is Sheppard.
- Go ahead, Colonel.
-I think we have a plan.
We do ?
McKAY : This is not a good plan.
SHEPPARD : Sure it is.
You realize how close
we’Il get to the sun ?
Pretty damn close.
- Suicidally close. We’Il be toast.
- We’re taking the ZPM...
... to give the Daedalus’ shield
an extra boost.
Okay, you want to deflect the coronal
mass ejection away from the planet.
- Like an umbrella.
- Okay, listen to me.
This, this is the sun.
And this, this is us.
A bolt of energy unlike anything
you can possibly comprehend...
... is gonna shoot out of the
photosphere at a tremendous velocity.
Okay ? It is going to immediately
start fanning out, like so.
- l know.
- Which means we’Il have to be...
... really close to the sun if we wanna
intercept that stream and deflect it...
- ... before it can start spreading out.
- l know.
l don’t think you do. l don’t think
you grasp the reality...
... of just how damn hot it gets
that close the sun.
We’re taking the ZPM,
to strengthen the shields.
From the blast wave, yes, even
with the shields at that strength...
... the buildup of residual heat
could cause...
... problems for the Daedalus...
- ... and everyone inside it.
- Could. Could cause.
Okay, tell me.
If this is such a great plan,
why didn’t the Ancients do it ?
They were in a war.
They probably didn’t have
a ship at the time...
... and like you said,
they had three ZPMs.
ZELENKA [ON RADIO] : Rodney.
- What ?
The prominence
has begun collapsing.
Colonel Caldwell, we’re ready.
SHEPPARD : How’s it going, Rodney ?
- You know, this might look easy...
... but it’s actually more complicated
than just flipping a switch.
Hurry up, please. We’re there.
What ? We are ? Already ?
CALDWELL :
Didn’t have far to go.
In position, doctor. Shields are up.
We need that extra power
from the ZPM now.
Yes, yes, l just need to--
Oh, no.
What ?
The prominence is collapsing into
the photosphere. Brace yourselves.
SHEPPARD :
Rodney.
The ZPM is online.
How long will this last, doctor ?
Anywhere from a few seconds
to several hours.
Hours ? You never said
anything about hours.
We’re building up heat
behind the shield.
l told you this wasn’t a good plan.
DEX :
How are they doing ?
According to my calculations,
the blast should have hit by now...
... but l’m reading no discernible
increase in radiation.
So they’re doing good.
Yes. So far, anyway.
McKAY :
Temperature is rising too fast.
l’m already detecting several
failed sensors on the bow.
If this keeps going,
the heat could damage the hull.
Not could. It’s already damaging it.
We have a breach at the 302 bay.
Seal it off.
Another breach, deck four.
We’re venting atmosphere.
Rodney ?
It’s over.
And we’re not toast.
We’re not toast.
Good plan, huh ?
ZELENKA :
Most of them are gone now.
They began dispersing
almost immediately.
Without so much as a thank you.
[YELLING ]
No, thank you.
- How are you feeling ?
- Much better.
Walked the whole way over here,
didn’t see one ghost.
Nor did l.
- Mind if join you ?
- If you fall asleep one more time...
Hit me with that.
- They’re gone, Rodney.
- Not all of them. Look.
- Let me guess. Your buddy Sam.
- l’d like to think so.
l like to think he’s saying goodbye.
Makes sense. He saved your life.
Now you saved his.
You’re even.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH SDH]