???
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
Are you all right?
You need to get out
of the street, honey.
You need to get out of
the street. Watch out!
Watch where
you're going!
Keep moving!
Go on.
Hey!
Excuse me!
???
Champagne, please.
I'll have the same.
Yes, ma'am.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You do know it's free.
Nobody tell you
this is a charity concert?
Well, it can't be
that charitable
if they force you to sit
through the damn thing.
Cheers to that.
Cheers.
I'm Jacob.
Hi. Elizabeth.
Pleasure to meet you.
So what do you do?
I'm special science advisor to the FBI.
How intriguing.
Job description would be...?
Well, scientific advancements
have greatly benefited
humanity, but...
if those advancements
are abused, could be very dangerous.
My job...
is to make sure
that never happens.
And what kind of science crimes
do you like to handle, Jacob?
Kind of classified.
What about your phone number?
That classified, too?
Hood.
We have some place to be.
Let me give you my card.
Duty calls.
I always wanted
to say that.
Sorry to interrupt.
The FBI is holding
two seats on a flight that leaves
in half an hour.
So what's this about,
Rachel?
Okay. Teresa Kimsey.
She's 16.
Went missing July 7.
Suddenly showed up
August 9.
Unharmed?
Physically.
Benjamin Gonzales, 15.
Disappeared August 11.
Reappeared September 8.
And Reggie Leinhart, 17.
Missing September 10,
back October 15.
When the National
Center for Missing and Exploited
Children detected the pattern,
they contacted the FBI.
Well, the approximate age
is the same.
Duration of abduction is roughly a month...
That's not what
they're focusing on.
Or why they want you involved.
All of the children
are severely autistic.
At least, they were
when they were abducted.
Were? Now they're exhibiting symptoms of savant syndrome.
From mentally challenged to mentally gifted
in the space of a month?
That's extraordinary.
-==http://Www.Ragbear.Com==-
第十一小时 第一季 第4集
-==破烂熊字幕组==-
时间轴：卢 斌
When they found
Reggie Leinhart,
he'd carved
657 squares
in the side of an 18-wheeler
with a screwdriver.
Perfect quadrilaterals.
Benjamin Gonzales's
mother
found her recently
abducted son
frantically
building that.
Which means these must
be Teresa Kimsey's.
I find it hard to believe that
these children were diagnosed
with Heller's syndrome.
It's a relatively
rare form of ASD.
Autism spectrum disorder.
I have a cousin who's autistic.
But he has a mild form.
So, what were you saying
about Heller's syndrome?
Well, it's one
of the most severe.
A child can
be developing normally
and then sometime between
the ages of two and four,
they start to regress.
They lose skills that
they've already developed
like, uh, language,
motor skills.
Some of them even stop
communicating altogether.
Savantism
is an even more
uncommon condition
where a developmental
disability coexists
with an extreme ability
in other areas
like mathematics
or art.
Yeah, I never understood
how that works.
Well...
Okay.
Um, wait.
Look.
Wait. That's mine.
This is an ordinary
person's brain.
By ordinary you mean incredibly charming
and full of personality.
Ordinary people organize.
They sort things.
They make connections.
It's called logic.
Now, this...
Um, what are you doing?!
Is the brain...
Hood!
...of an autistic person.
You see, although types
and degrees of autism
vary widely
across the spectrum,
most of them have trouble
with connections.
The ability to organize that
I was talking about. Now...
Hood!
This...
...is the brain
of a savant.
It's the ability
to focus on one thing
to the exclusion
of everything else.
Now, if you have nothing
but toothpaste in your suitcase,
what would happen?
You'd know a hell of a lot
about toothpaste.
Exactly.
You know everything there is
to know about toothpaste.
You'd be a toothpaste expert.
The question is:
how does a severely
autistic
otherwise ordinary person
become a savant
inside of a month?
What happened
to these children?
And why?
Well,
we'll start with Teresa Kimsey.
She's our first victim,
with the thickest case file.
And next time,
use your own luggage.
I didn't know the FBI
had a science division.
They don't. They have a
Science and Technology branch-
deals with all manner
of intelligence-gathering
and criminal investigation.
And then there's me.
Is this Teresa?
Yes.
She was two
when that picture
was taken.
She was such a
funny baby,
always smiling.
About six months later,
she just stopped.
No more smiling,
no more hugs.
Sometimes
she'd look at me
like she didn't
know who I was.
Before we go in,
I should warn you.
Usually Teresa doesn't
like visitors.
She can get
anxious and upset.
But then...
she hasn't exactly been
herself lately.
Wouldn't even go
near a coloring book
before she went
missing.
Hi, Teresa.
Now I
can't get her to stop drawing. Mmm.
And not that
I want to.
Mrs. Kimsey,
would you mind if we spoke
to Teresa for a few minutes?
Well, actually,
you see,
Teresa doesn't
really talk.
Oh, it's okay.
She doesn't need to.
There was a 13-year-old
girl with autism
at Syracuse a
few years ago.
She never spoke.
Certainly didn't think
she could read or write,
and when they gave her
a computer keyboard
she typed out the words
"I love Mom. "
So Teresa's preferred
method...
Would appear
to be drawing.
Hiya.
This...
...is me.
Sort of.
I like science.
That's an atom.
this is...
Rachel.
She likes to beat up bad people.
Hey!
And this
is you.
Can you show me
what happened to you
when you went away?
You were sleeping?
Were you sleeping?
You're being very
helpful,
Teresa.
Thank you.
What is that?
Some kind of tube.
Is that a tunnel?
Were you in a tunnel?
Where'd they take you,
honey?
Is that a...
Was she in
an MRI machine?
Were you in a machine?
You see, these
are, uh,
these are surface coils.
They increase
the magnetic sensitivity.
And... these...
Rachel, can I have
the sidewalk picture, please?
These are DTIs-
Diffusion Tensor Imaging.
DTI is a specific
type of MRI
that tracks the movement
of water through the brain.
Teresa,
you're drawing
what's inside your head?
But...
the last time
she had an MRI
was when she was
but five years old.
Where?
Well, the Autism Institute
of Chicago.
We're meeting
with the chief administrator,
Catherine Bonatelli.
Both kidnap victims
Benjamin Gonzales
and Reggie Leinhart
had MRIs taken here.
They were also five
years old at the time.
That's got to mean
something, right?
Means we're getting closer.
I don't understand.
Why are these children
being taken?
That's what we're trying
to find out.
Well, I want you to know
that the Institute will do
whatever we can to help.
Thank you.
Rachel.
Do you have the picture
of Benjamin's sculpture?
These were taken
of Teresa
over ten years ago.
I hope they still pertain
to your investigation.
Miss Bonatelli,
we'll also need to see the scans
for Benjamin Gonzales
and Reggie Leinhart.
Excuse me. Do you mind
if I take over for a second?
Oh, sure.
These scans are almost exactly
the same.
Even if these patients
have the same type of autism,
it doesn't mean their scans
would be this close.
Brain patterns
are as unique as fingerprints.
You have so many kids with the
same distinct brain pattern.
I'm going to need to see all
the DTIs you've taken here.
Oh, I'm sorry, but we've
confidentiality issues.
Without express permission
from every patient involved...
Or a court order.
Our facility's
been taking DTIs since '94.
We're talking
thousands of patients.
And if any one
of those
matches the three
we just found,
they're in real danger
of being abducted.
So the sooner we get started,
the better.
Hood...
Yep.
I think I've got one.
Scott Butler.
He doesn't have
Heller's syndrome
like the other three victims.
But his scans were also
taken when he was five.
He's 18 now.
And they're almost identical
to the others.
Yeah, that's a match.
If these MRIs were taken
over ten years ago,
then it's
not these MRIs
that the kids are
remembering, is it?
No, I don't think it is.
I'm going to try
Scott's contact number.
Yeah.
Voice mail full.
We'll need to go
check on him.
Hold on.
I found another one.
Cameron Stewart.
Five years old
when he had the scan done.
Now he's 16.
Let's give it a try.
Hello?
Hello. Is this... Mrs. Stewart?
Yes.
Who's this?
Hi. I'm Jacob Hood.
I'm-I'm with the FBI.
Is your son home, please?
Hello?
Did the police call you?
No. Is he all right?
Then, how did you know?
Cameron went missing from school
this morning.
All right now. We have to be
real quiet. Okay?
Don't want to upset
our new friend Cameron.
Hello, Cameron.
You're going to be very
comfortable here.
I promise.
Missing Persons Unit is
at Cameron Stewart's residence,
getting a full report.
Dr. Hood and I found
four more potential victims.
Are they accounted for?
Yeah, they're all accounted for.
Placing undercover units
at each one of their houses,
24-hour protection.
Mr. Butler?
Scott Butler?
Scott?
Hood, look at all of his mail.
There's at least
a month's worth.
He's already been taken, Rachel.
Taken and returned.
Clear.
Looks like
he lives alone.
Well, that explains why no one
reported you missing, Scott.
Scott...
we're with the FBI.
Do you mind if I, if I just make
a recording of that?
Scott, would you mind stopping
playing for a moment.
I'd like to ask you
some questions.
Scott, are you all right?
He's bleeding.
Get an ambulance!
Code Eight. Ambulance needed
at 146841st Street,
You hear that?
What?
Music.
The same notes.
Same as what?
Full sentences, Hood.
*
Hear that?
Now listen.
Same notes.
Scott's phrase used
the same notes
as a common
anesthesia machine.
You don't need one of those
to get an MRI.
I don't think
someone
was taking pictures
of his brain.
I think
they opened it up.
I don't think he was
the only one either.
Look at the back wall.
It's a clean room filter.
You don't need one of those
to get an MRI either.
You only need them
for operations.
Time of death
is 3:47 p. m.
'Cause of death:
rapid blood loss
due to a trauma
to the carotid artery.
Cause of trauma:
yet to be determined.
Perhaps I can help with that.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
FBI.
I'm Dr. Jacob Hood.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to take a look
at the body.
What is this about?
What are you looking for?
A scar.
Would you mind if I, uh...
What kind of scar?
Can I borrow a nasal probe?
Right here.
Thank you.
This should just take a second.
Okay. I got it.
There's the scar.
Have you taken X-rays yet?
Cameron?
Cameron!
The operation was done through
an incision in the gum,
and then you walk the bone
up to the pituitary gland.
It's a new kind
of brain surgery
that doesn't leave
any visible scars.
Wait. You're saying someone
secretly performed
brain surgery on this boy
without consent?
That's exactly what I'm saying,
Dr. Fisher.
Someone tried to alter
Scott's brain neurons
by surgically implanting
some kind of microfilament.
That sounds risky.
The brain is
highly prone to infection.
Or you can nip the carotid
artery during the procedure
and the clot wouldn't hold.
One sneeze would
dislodge the clot,
and you'd bleed to death.
Which is exactly what happened
to Scott.
Hood, Teresa and the other two
boys could be walking around
with these wires
inside their head.
Cameron Stewart could be
undergoing
the same procedure
as we speak.
We need to go.
Can you check the wires
for serial numbers
when you do the autopsy, please?
No problem.
Don't send me
somewhere else, please.
This is the third place
that I've been to
in this hospital.
Now where is he?
Where's Scotty?
I want to see him.
I just...
I want to see my son.
You're Mr. Butler?
Do you know something
about what's happened to Scotty?
What's happened to my son?
It was a month.
A month.
The most he'd ever gone
without calling me back
was two weeks.
I should've flown out
to check on him.
Why didn't I fly out?
It's not your fault.
Yeah...
Yeah, it is.
I never should have let him
move away.
He had no business
living by himself.
How long was he
on his own?
I lived with him
the first six months
to make the transition.
He was high-functioning
in terms of his autism.
He had been on his own
about a year now.
He only wanted to be normal.
What did I do?
I promise you, Mr. Butler,
it was nothing you did.
Whoever took Scott
would have done it
whether he was
with you or not.
Still no answer at Teresa's.
I hope she's all right.
What is up
with this damn traffic?
You okay?
I'm fine. I just...
I just keep thinking
about Cameron Stewart,
out there somewhere.
Who would do this, Hood?
Put kids through this?
What would their motive be?
Well, some people believe that
autism, specifically savantism,
is like some sort
of clumsy step forward
on the evolutionary path
to the ultimate potential
of the human mind.
And if someone
could figure out
how to recreate what gives them
certain advanced abilities while
preventing the disabilities...
then you can significantly
advance human intelligence.
How does sticking wires
in somebody's brain do that?
By forcing the neurons
to find
alternate paths
to their destination.
Those alternate paths
could be better paths.
I'll try her cell.
No!
Miss Young.
Hi.
Dr. Hood, hi.
Teresa, look
who's here.
She spoke yesterday.
She said,
"Thanks, Mom.
Do we have any ice cream?"
And "Where's Bob?"
Who's Bob?
Our dog.
Oh.
Mrs. Kimsey...
um, we'd like to take
Teresa to the hospital.
Why?
What is it?
She needs an X-ray.
No.
No, she's not going anywhere.
Mrs. Kimsey.
Teresa might have been, um,
subjected to an experimental
neural implant.
Her health could be at risk.
But Teresa's never
been better.
Look at her.
I mean, she's
talking.
Not a lot, but
she is talking.
She called me Mom
for the first time
in 16 years.
Do you know
what that's like?
No, I don't.
And that horrible month.
No, uh-uh.
No, I don't want
to lose her again.
Of course you don't,
Mrs. Kimsey,
but this is happening
to other teenagers, too,
just like Teresa.
One died yesterday.
Another was taken
from his home.
Kidnapped.
His name's Cameron,
and he's 16 also.
You see,
the more we know
about what happened
to Teresa...
the better chance
we have to find him.
I'm sorry.
She's not going with you.
Yes, I am.
???
Cameron's gone.
He must be hiding.
I searched his room.
He's scared.
It's not unusual
for them
to find refuge
in extremely confined spaces.
I looked everywhere.
He's gone.
You okay back
there, Hood?
You're awfully quiet.
It's nice, but I'm
starting to worry.
There's probably
only 50 or 60 doctors
in the Midwest capable of this
kind of surgery-
maybe we should just visit
them all and see if Teresa
recognizes anybody.
You can't just go
around confronting
upstanding members of
the medical community
without probable cause.
Why not?
I have to go
to the bathroom.
Cameron?
Teresa?
You okay?
Come on, Teresa.
You're scaring me.
What's going on?
Teresa?
You okay?
Hood.
You're drawing again?
Well...
I suppose it is still
her dominant form
of communication.
Teresa,
what is this?
Looks like a pattern.
It's definitely some
kind of sequence.
I wonder...
What?
Synesthesia.
Or, actually,
a specific kind
of synesthesia
called grapheme.
Okay, back up
and start
with the first word
I don't understand.
Um, many people
with savant syndrome
experience something
called synesthesia
where one sensory
experience
triggers an overpowering
response in another.
Like, um,
every time you
hear a door slam,
you get a taste of
mint in your mouth
or vice versa.
Okay... and grapheme?
Well, it's the most
common type, where letters
or numbers are perceived
as inherently,
uh, colored
or textured.
So, like, an A
could be red?
That's right.
Okay, so she could
be writing a name.
Yeah, or a place.
Teresa, do you mind if
I borrow one of these?
Seven letters or...
or numbers.
Could be a phone number.
It's hard to see
what you're doing
with all the graffiti, Teresa.
Graffiti.
No, that's it.
She's not writing
around the graffiti.
She's using it.
If she's intentionally
incorporating it,
we can use it as a key.
That's brilliant.
Okay, okay, Teresa,
so the first color
in your sequence is...
yellow-
what's yellow?
I got a four here
that's yellow.
There's yellow scribbling
over a four over there, too.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Red's next.
These two Os are red.
It's not a phone number.
It's a license plate.
I have to be honest with you.
The very idea
that you're considering me
some kind of suspect is...
well, incredibly insulting,
not to mention absurd.
This is your
license plate number, isn't it, Miss Bonatelli?
And you got it from a girl
who has a severe case of Heller's syndrome.
It may be
a simple coincidence,
or she may actually
remember it
from her earlier visits
to the facility.
When she was five?
Do you have any idea how long
we've been doing research
on autism here?
Do you?
Over two decades,
and we still don't know
what causes it.
Right now, one
out of every 150 children
has autism.
That means one and a half
million in America alone,
and it's growing.
Which means we'll
have four million
in one decade.
The research has to continue.
What happened to Scott Butler
isn't research.
It's murder.
If that's the case...
I certainly hope
you capture whoever
is responsible for all this.
I can't believe
we just let her go.
We don't have
any proof.
Proof?
It's obvious.
Law is like biology, Hood.
You can't just decide
something's true.
You got to dig up
some dirt,
find a few nasty
little microorganisms
to prove your point.
Good use of a scientific
analogy, Rachel.
Hey, speaking of
digging up dirt...
I just got a text.
My friend at the Bureau
who's running
a background
check for me.
It seems Miss Bonatelli
did some consulting work
for a company
that was a cover.
A cover for who?
The CIA.
You weren't easy to
find, Mr. Whittier.
Means I'm
fairly good at my job,
Agent Young.
Means you are, too,
I may say.
Must have friends
in high places.
What we have
is a dead
19-year-old boy
and a 16-year-old
who is missing as we speak.
Somebody's operating
on autistic children
without their consent.
Catherine Bonatelli
did some consulting work
for you in '05.
I'm assuming it
involved her work
at the Autism Institute
of Chicago.
If this person in question did
do some contract work for us,
those records
would be
part of our HCS.
Human Control System.
But HCS info is accessible
on a need-to-know basis only.
Well, unless
the health and well-being
of innocent teenagers
means nothing to you,
we need to know right now.
If the person in question,
this Catherine Bonatelli,
did contract work
in '05,
it would have involved
an interest
in a common trait of autism:
superior memory.
We would have used her
as an easy access route
for information, statistics.
Possible test subjects?
Never got that far.
People realized
that it would be decades
before we got
anywhere useful on this,
not to mention
the potential
for a public relations
disaster of epic proportions.
So, if this...
theoretical pilot study
ever did exist...
it was shut down.
So, basically,
you're telling us nothing.
If someone is doing what you say
to these children,
I'd like to help.
The Agency
would like to help.
So, prove it.
When it comes to passing
sensitive information,
the trick is to make sure
that you didn't leave behind
physical evidence of any kind:
notes on paper,
phone records,
voice recordings,
that kind of thing.
The best way to leak...
is simply lean forward and
whisper in another person's ear.
What?
What did he say? Catherine Bonatelli's
coded cell phone number-
we can use it
to trace her movements.
Stay here.
I'm gonna go check this out.
Rachel?!
Rachel.
Are you okay?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
But Miss Bonatelli isn't.
Building was rented
in Miss Bonatelli's name.
Do you think
she's our mad scientist?
No. No, she didn't
even go to med school.
Brain surgery's
not the kind of thing
you learn on the internet,
no matter what they say.
Probably wasn't her idea
to blow herself up, either.
It's pretty clear
there was someone else.
Bonatelli provided
the test subjects based
on the DTIs from the Institute,
but I don't think
she knew the medical details
of what was going on.
Or how far they'd go
to cover their tracks.
No.
We've gone over
the whole site.
She's definitely
the only casualty.
Cameron?
What did you find?
He's nearby.
They weren't just doing the
surgeries in this building.
They were holding them
in here, too.
So, where's Cameron?
If he's
still alive,
they've moved
him somewhere.
Hey, Hood.
Or maybe he escaped.
I need an immediate
door-to-door search
for a special needs 16-year-old
named Cameron Stewart.
Yes, ma'am.
Have you seen this boy?
In this place?
No.
You're welcome to look
around if you want.
We won't be long.
Take your time.
Rachel...
he was here.
Are you sure?
We have no other choice.
Are you really going
to do this at the hospital?
There's nowhere else left.
I can't believe
we did that at the lab to Catherine.
We have to stop.
It's too risky.
Don't think about the risk.
Think about the reward.
Now what?
We've got one clue left.
It's not here.
What do you mean,
it's not here?
How do you lose
a brain?
Well, the brain is here,
but the wires-
they were in a specimen cup.
Okay, who has access
to this area?
Hospital staff, cleaning crew.
I'm sorry. Somebody must have
made a mistake.
It wasn't a mistake.
The wires are gone
for the same reason
they blew up the building.
Whoever's behind this
is getting rid of the evidence.
I need to find out what
the wires were made of.
The compound could tell
us where it was made,
and right now,
we have nothing.
No. No, we do
have something.
Or more specifically, someone.
You're doing
great, Teresa.
Just remain still.
And thank you for helping us.
You're very brave.
The composite of the wires
in Teresa's brain is
primarily platinum.
As in wedding bands?
As in nerve stimulators.
They're like small
defibrillators
that are surgically implanted
in the chest
to shock the vagus nerve
and prevent epileptic seizures.
If somebody's dismantling them
to make neuroconductors,
they're gonna need
more than a few.
We need to find out
what local hospital is ordering
an abundance of these things.
Hold on. Those
missing wires.
It's not easy to
swipe something
from a hospital morgue
without clearance.
You're right.
Our doctor must have privileges
at this hospital.
???
@@@
I have eight doctors
who requisitioned nerve
stimulators in the last year.
No. Hang on. Seven.
Hmm. That's strange.
Why?
It's okay. It's just,
the stimulators usually go
through the thoracic department,
but I've got 25 of them assigned
to a surgeon in neurology.
What? Why would a brain surgeon
be implanting nerve stimulators?
What's the
surgeon's name?
Dr. Edward Fisher.
The doctor who tried
to save Scott Butler?
I'll have Chicago PD
pick him up.
Do you have his address?
Don't need one.
He's upstairs.
Scheduled for surgery
about 15 minutes ago.
Nobody move.
Put that down slowly,
Dr. Fisher,
and step back
from the table.
You don't understand.
You don't know
what I'm doing.
Then tell us.
What are you doing?
Trying to save my son.
Your son?
Noah.
He's four.
Diagnosed with Heller's syndrome
a year ago.
He's autistic.
So you're trying to fix him?
Find some kind
of cure?
Who are you to say
he needs fixing?
Just 'cause
someone's mind works
atypically doesn't mean
they can't experience happiness?
Or thrive on their own terms?
In fact,
one of those atypical people
helped us find you, Dr. Fisher.
You remember your patient
Teresa Kimsey?
I'm so close to a breakthrough,
I can't stop now.
You don't understand.
I understand
you can't conduct
deadly experiments
on other peoples' kids
to save your own.
Noah deserves...
a normal life.
I have to finish now.
Get any closer to
that boy's head,
and I'll put a bullet in yours.
Why was Fisher
working on teenagers
when Noah's only four?
Our brain stops maturing
around 15 or 16.
If you operated any younger, there'd
be no way of telling
if the changes were
due to
the operation,or simple maturation
of the brain.
Poor kid.
Let's hope he
has more family.
If they're anything like
Mom and Dad, maybe not.
Any news on Noah?
I wonder if he has
an aunt, an uncle.
Actually, I've filed
for a friend-of-the-court
brief for adoption.
Not for me.
I love kids.
I'm a big fan, but all
that traveling we do,
along with all the
scientific crimes and crises.
Then who?
Mr. Butler,
Scott's dad.
He has the
experience,
and, uh, I
don't know.
It seemed like a good idea.
What?
That's very
thoughtful, Hood.
Sensitive.
What, scientists
can't be sensitive?
She hasn't spoken
in a week now.
I understand why they had
to remove the wires,
but I miss her.
She's still in there.
We're going
to start therapy at the
Son Rise Institute
in Massachusetts next week.
Teresa?
We wanted to thank you
for your help.
Now, we wouldn't have found
the bad doctor
if it hadn't been for you.
You're an amazing girl.
破烂熊字幕组作品
-==http://Www.Ragbear.Com==-
欢 迎 加 入
www.tvsubtitles.net