Mea culpa, mea maxima culpa.
This is unit 25.
In pursuit of tan pickup,
refuses to stop.
WOMAN
25, copy.
Mea culpa, mea maxima culpa.
Forgive them, Father,
for what they've done.
My God.
That makes 19 of them, sir.
19 containers...
19 fetuses.
Is this the last one?
Yeah.
Hey, there's a guy
from Washington, DC
in the evidence tent.
Sorry. Who did you say
you work for?
I didn't.
What the hell's
going on here?
Do you have a badge?
I'm Detective McNeil.
I'm in charge of this case.
Sorry.
But you came up on him
too quick.
Good morning.
I'm Dr. Jacob Hood.
Special science advisor
to the FBI.
And that's Special
Agent Rachel Young.
Science advisor?
Yeah, I was appointed
to investigate
crimes and crises
of a scientific nature.
What you found here
certainly falls
under that category,
wouldn't you say?
You.
Out.
You mean the 19 dead babies
and 19 graves
that didn't dig themselves.
That's not accurate;
what you've got here
is 19 terminated fetuses.
You drink milk from a carton?
Why?
The barcode on the carton
is the same principle
as a DNA profile.
DNA is a personal
barcode.
Each one is different,
therefore unique.
Now, this... is the profile
of the 12-week-old fetus
that was thrown from
the truck last night.
And this is a profile
of the first one
you dug up.
Spot the difference.
I dare you.
I can't.
Of course you can't.
Because they're identical.
All 19 of them.
Do you know anything
about cloning?
Remember Dolly the sheep?
Yeah.
Well, this abomination
is what happens when you try it
with human beings.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
Eleventh.Hour 第1季第1集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
时间轴：ＲＡＹＥＳ&菜猪猪
????
What's he need you for?
Dr. Hood is
a high-priority asset.
He's a brilliant
biophysicist,
but he spends most of
his time in his head,
so I have to
watch his back.
About a year ago,
some radical group
had his car bombed.
You want to
see him blush,
ask him where
the shrapnel is.
You see,
he's got this annoying habit
of telling the truth,
and the truth hurts
a lot of people's pockets.
And no, I'm not free for dinner.
It's in the eyes,
Detective McNeil.
David?
Has anyone seen my son?
The judge told you
to leave us alone.
It's a free
country, Kelly.
I can move to any
city I want to,
just like you did.
Kid's got a right to
see his dad, you know?
Not after what you did to me.
Let go of my son.
Wait for Mommy
over there, okay?
Well...
I notice you've
been keeping busy.
I'm taking care of us,
which is more than you ever did.
Don't say that,
and then walk
away from me!
Hey, you leave her alone!
Should I call the police?
This guy you arrested
is not a microbiologist,
by any chance, is he?
He's an unemployed
security guard.
No priors.
He said that someone
was paying him
to incinerate the containers;
then once he found out
what was in them, he couldn't
bring himself to do it.
How come you
don't know
who's behind all
this cloning stuff?
You seem to know
everything else.
There's someone
we've been chasing
for a long time,
and his first attempts
at human cloning
were in Eastern Europe,
then South America.
Both failed.
Now I believe he's come here.
The question is, why?
So, what's next?
Can you recommend a good hotel?
Kelly?
It's Mrs. Muller.
I've come
to get you.
Kelly, can I come in?
I trusted you people.
That's why I'm here.
Your own personal nurse.
Let me help you.
Please.
Hi.
So, I'm gonna charge Sanders
with accessory to murder.
That will get him talking.
A judge will ask why.
Technically, a fetus
is medical waste.
It's not murder.
What, so I've got nothing?
Breathe, McNeil.
You got a crime here,
a big crime.
I wouldn't be here
if you didn't.
Implanting a woman
with an embryo
created by any means
other than fertilization
is illegal.
Yeah, but it's not murder,
which means I've wasted
too much time already.
Tell me you didn't
just say wasted.
Anything that helps us,
Detective,
call me.
He's just doing his job.
19 fetuses.
You know
what that means?
19 mothers.
How do you keep them all quiet?
Is the baby okay?
Please tell me.
Kelly, in a minute.
I just keep thinking
about that childless couple,
and it would break their hearts
if I lost this baby.
That's a nice
thought, Kelly.
Keep that thought.
What is it?
What's wrong?
It's the placenta.
It's lying a little low
and blocking the entrance
to the womb.
Is that bad?
You just relax.
Nature has a way
of making things right.
If something
did go wrong,
I would still get
the money,
wouldn't I?
That childless couple
you're so concerned about
are not a charity, Kelly.
I need that money, Doctor.
I need to get away from here.
From people.
We should send her home.
She's got
grade three previa.
She's also got the most
viable fetus we've ever seen.
More reason to have
her in a hospital
under constant
supervision.
For a doctor, you can
be amazingly stupid.
She should be delivered.
It's too early.
Besides, the baby
might not survive.
At least the girl would.
She's a time bomb.
You want to risk that?
With great risks
come great rewards.
I don't want
another dead mother
on my conscience.
If she goes into labor,
she will die.
Hello, Will.
Do I know you?
We need to have a talk.
Cops never charged me.
Who the hell are you?
By nature, a deeply
sensitive person.
But she's not.
Get lost.
Sugar rush.
Wait. Wait.
You can't do this to me.
It's time to clear
your conscience, Will.
I know you're
a man of faith,
and we both know, at
the heart of faith...
lies the truth.
Jesus knows my heart,
and he forgives me.
Does he?
Okay, let's ask him.
Look at him, Will.
Look at the nails
in his hands,
in his feet,
the wound in his side.
You telling me you'd let
that suffering continue?
Answer me!
Please let me go.
Ask his forgiveness,
and he will forgive you
if you truly repent.
Now, tell the truth.
Who paid you to get rid
of the containers?
Can you please stop this? He knows
the secrets of
your heart, Will.
Cleanse yourself, Will.
Tell him.
It was a woman.
I didn't know her name.
You lie to me,
you're lying to him.
I burned the first one 'cause
she said it was medical waste.
It was easy money.
I didn't think.
Easy money
means restless nights.
You must have a name.
I don't know her name.
Liar!
I looked inside the second one
and I wished I hadn't.
But it was too late.
My soul was dark.
God must forgive me, though.
Yoknow what I think, Will?
I think you're a waste
of God's time.
Let's go.
Geppetto.
She talked to somebody
on the phone called Geppetto.
There's where they treated
the girls.
I worked here as a night guard till
they shut the place down.
You don't see divine
intervention at hand, man?
The woman asked me to
drive the girls here.
Then she gives me something,
says I should burn it.
I look anyway.
I praise God for choosing me
to give them a decent burial.
It's a shame he didn't choose
you to tell the cops instead.
How did they
keep this quiet?
Cash.
Lots of cash.
A traveling clinic.
Is this where the woman
treated the girls?
Her and a man.
Sharp guy-
a... doctor.
Geppetto?
No, that's who they call
after they were finished
with the girl.
Well, this is stage two.
This is where they implanted
the embryos, but this isn't
where the actual cloning
would take place.
That would require
a real lab.
Liquid nitrogen.
Westec Veterinary Services-
for the transporting
of bovine semen.
They're hardly going
to label it
"Frozen clone embryos:
handle with love. "
This was just a cover.
You got your panic button?
I think so.
Freeze! FBI!
Hey!
Hood!
What was that?
What?
That, with the arms?
I got the license plate.
Why do I bother?
I guess they won't be coming
back here for a while.
Ow.
This place was
set up just to...
monitor the pregnancies
and terminate the failures.
Any obstetrician, along
with a half decent nurse,
could do that, but
stage three, the birth-
that's when you need
the scientist.
Geppetto.
What?
Wood, where are we going now?
To see a vet.
What if I told you
that someone not far from here
is close
to cloning a
human being?
Is that supposed
to shock me?
What was your
title again?
Dr. Hood is fine.
Well, Dr. Hood, some people
think it's already been done.
Not by you, right?
We found this
in a... makeshift delivery room.
And so you presumed
we're cloning people?
I'm flattered.
We're the largest biological
distribution company
on the West Coast.
We ship hundreds of samples
from around the world
every day.
And you're asking me
to trace a label?
That was a waste of time.
In science,
a negative result
is just as important
as a positive one.
"And when the king
returned to his castle,
"he found that his trusted
servant had made him
a beautiful... "
..."a beautiful coat
filled with all kinds of... "
Oh!
Oh, David, honey.
Oh, give Mommy a second while...
while this pain goes away.
Okay?
Yes.
Dr. Hayward?
Kelly.
Can I meet you at the warehouse?
No.
Y- Y-You can't do that.
Oh!
Then I have to go
to the hospital.
No, uh, Kelly, um,
if you go to the hospital,
Social Services
will take David away from you.
Do you want that?
But I'm bleeding really badly.
No hospitals.
Understand?
Can I buy you a drink?
Before you disturb me,
you should know I'm
filling out this paperwork
because I shot at a man today.
Why?
Because he disturbed me.
Okay.
Thanks.
Why does the name Geppetto
sound so familiar?
You mean apart
from being Pinocchio's dad?
Right.
You know, I never
understood that story.
An old wood-carver
wants a son so badly
that he makes
one of his own?
Get a wife,
why don't you?
Weird.
Rachel.
Hmm?
You are brilliant.
I know.
Why?
Why am I brilliant?
I kept asking myself,
"Why choose to do
the embryo implanting
here?"
But he didn't choose,
you see.
That decision was made
for him, for Geppetto.
He who pays the piper
calls the tune.
Somebody right here in Seattle
wants their son
back from the dead.
Excuse me.
Local publications,
2005, please.
Why 2005?
The first fetus
was found 18 months ago.
Whatever we're looking for
must have happened
before then.
Give Mommy her phone, please.
I'm calling 911.
Look for families
who have lost a son.
What makes you think
we'll find it here?
Whoever fronts Geppetto
has got to be wealthy.
Cloning is
a very expensive business.
The poor die in silence,
the rich die public.
That's the way it's always been,
so keep looking.
For what?
The small ads
under "Human Cloning"?
What's your name?
Can you hear me?
Laura.
Laura's my name. Laura, how
long have you been bleeding?
Not long.
Mom!
David!
Just relax. Social Service
is taking care of him.
No!
Mom!
I think I've found him.
A needle in a haystack.
How many needles try
to commit suicide three times
after they've
lost a loved one?
Why can't we go
visit this man,
Mr. Gifford?
Because it's late.
Keep your panic button
handy, please,
and use your cover name if... If I want
to order in myroom.
Good night.
What is your
cover name?
Mr. Smith.
Jones.
Mr. Jones.
I'll be right down.
What do you got?
The car that tried
to run over your guy
was rented
by a Dr. Sidney Hayward,
an obstetrician.
Can you trace him?
Already did; he's gone.
What do you mean "gone"?
Struck off the medical registrar
two years ago.
Drink?
No.
His house was put
into foreclosure
and the IRS froze
his bank accounts.
Ah.
I owe you one, okay?
So how long you been
with the doctor?
Uh, it was supposed
to be two months and...
You know,
I looked you up.
FBI Executive
Protection Detail.
That's, uh,
pretty cool.
Sure you don't want a nightcap?
I said I owe you one.
I never said I'd give you one.
Sidney Hayward- erratic driver
and baby doctor.
What did he do,
run off with a patient?
Does it matter?
Give me a doctor
with a steady hand
over one with a
steady home anytime.
But you don't think
he's our Geppetto, do you?
No.
To clone anything
requires skill
and knowledge way beyond
this guy's capabilities.
Well, how do you know
he doesn't have
those capabilities?
Because
to clone anything...
takes science
stroked gently
with artistic hands.
You got a pair of tweezers?
Yeah.
Not to keep.
Now, imagine
this is a woman's egg.
Well, the seed
inside it is her nucleus
that contains her unique DNA.
Now, if you want
to make a clone,
the first thing you do
is get rid of the nucleus.
Believe it or not, I use those.
Then, you replace it
with the nucleus of any cell
of the person you want to clone.
Original egg, new DNA
in the nucleus.
So, next, you shock it
with a little jolt
of electricity.
Don't say Frankenstein.
The electricity
fools the egg
into thinking
it's been fertilized.
Within a week,
it's making
stem cells,
which then grow
into the person of your choice.
You place these
inside the womb
of your carrier.
Next, you hire
a disgraced and
penniless gynecologist,
like Hayward,
to bring in the harvest.
Cannibal.
McNEIL: We've been monitoring
city hospital maternity wards
for any suspicious activity.
We got a call on the radio
about a girl who was admitted
to intensive care
with her four-year-old son.
Hospital child care
was looking after the boy
when she just goes in
and grabbed him
and then just vanished.
Apparently,
she's in bad shape.
And pregnant, right?
Right.
The bleeding's not
her biggest problem.
Her placenta is covering
the exit of her womb.
Placenta previa.
If this girl's
contractions start
with this condition,
she could die.
Can we go home, Mommy?
Not just yet, sweetie.
We're wasting precious time.
We should go
and see this man.
Let the cops find
the girl first.
See if she leads us
back to Gifford.
Right now you need
to get some rest.
We'll go first thing
in the morning.
But this is the only lead
we've got.
He's a name in a newspaper,
not a lead.
You don't know if this girl's
involved with Geppetto,
and you want to go bang on some
billionaire's door in the middle
of the night with no
real justification?
Don't push me, Hood.
I won't let you
wear me down
like you did the
others before me.
I have never failed
at any assignment,
and I don't intend to start now.
Settled.
If you need me,
I'll be right
down the hall.
WOMAN It can literally turn
back the clock on aging skin.
Its special
deep-penetration formula
acts to reduce lines...
Lies.
Do you suffer
from male-patterned baldness?
Not anymore.
Renewgent 12 is guaranteed
to grow new hair...
More lies.
You got a nice, uh, 18-year-old
single malt?
Okay.
No ice.
Hood? Hood?!
Oh, crap.
I must have sat on it.
Drink?
We shouldn't be doing this.
It's a blind risk
factor for you.
Based on what, a hunch?
Once upon a time,
gravity was just a hunch.
Mr. Gifford,
I'm Dr. Jacob Hood.
This is Rachel Young.
What can I do for you?
We're here
about your late son, Gabriel.
Meningitis
is a terrible disease.
Maybe it wouldn't be
if they did some more research.
Is Mrs. Gifford at home?
Losing a child
has repercussions.
My wife left.
Would you say life is precious?
Where did that come from?
It's just a question.
Can you answer?
Hood.
See, there's a pregnant girl
out there, Kelly,
and she's going
to lose her life
because she's too scared
to get medical help,
so... is life precious,
Mr. Gifford?
I think you should leave now.
I suppose you don't know
who Dr. Sidney Hayward is?
Do you?
Where is she?
Where's Kelly?
That girl is
somebody's mother,
and if she dies,
she'll be missed
by her own son.
Don't you dare try
to teach me about grief.
And if you don't leave,
I'm calling the police.
We'll save you the call.
Guys like him can lie
all day day long
and never get
tired of it.
Let's try... this.
You stole his telephone?
It was just lying there.
Now this'll
work as long
as we stay 100 feet
from the phone base.
There was a brochure
for Westec Veterinarian
services on the table,
and in about 30 seconds,
he's gonna make a panic call.
Why are you calling us?
Someone named Jacob Hood
just left my house.
He knows.
I'm telling Geppetto
to cut this girl loose.
You can't do that.
Why not?
Because she'll die.
And her baby has the best chance
of a live birth yet.
Now, calm down while we go
check on the girl.
Kelly?
Kelly, it's me.
I brought Dr. Hayward for you.
The contractions have started.
He'll take care of you.
No. I want a hospital now!
McNEIL:
Kelly Frost, 20 years old.
She has a criminal record?
Yeah, assault.
Her ex used to treat her
like a punching bag.
When she got sick of it,
she fought back.
And what do you know.
He pressed charges.
We've got a problem.
A big problem.
Girl needs
an emergency C-section.
Oh, my God.
Wait. Geppetto wants
to be present at the birth.
I've made that call already.
If we don't do this right now,
they're both going to die.
Whatever it takes.
There's a clinic
on Bainbridge Island.
It's been closed
only a few months,
but it's still fully equipped.
I can use it, but we're
gonna need cash up front.
Consider it done.
And Gifford,
you know we're only talking
viable here.
Nobody's promising perfect.
Who are you?
You must have
the wrong apartment.
Where's Kelly?
I don't know any Kelly.
All right.
Kelly?! Kelly?!
David, can you tell Daddy
where Mommy went?
The man took her.
What man?
Do you know?
Uh-uh?
All right,
can somebody please tell me
what the hell's going on here?!
Can you talk?
Who are you?
...you!
Right.
Abusive ex-boyfriend.
Who did this?
Some woman did this.
Can you get me an ambulance?
Please?
Where's Kelly?
I don't know. Agh!
Okay, okay.
Just pull this out of my neck.
It's not a good idea.
That's your external
jugular vein.
Scissors are actually
slowing the blood flow.
Pull those out,
you'll be dead in minutes.
Best if you
stay calm.
Where's my mommy?
It's okay.
I need you
to help me save a life.
But it could mean your job.
Would I be doing this
in the name of science
or the law?
How about in the name of good?
Geppetto will
be here soon.
Hayward?
We could save ourselves.
Give them Geppetto.
I agree.
Make the call.
Mr. Gifford?
You know what today is,
Yes.
It's my son's new birthday.
No.
Today is the first day
of you accepting
Gabriel is dead.
Do you have any idea
how long I've waited for this?
How many false hopes?
You won't stop this.
In an hour,
I'm gonna have my reborn son
in my hands again.
You can't believe that.
You ever lost a child?
How could you possibly know
what I'm going through?
Two years ago my wife died.
I nursed her
till her last breath.
Every day,
I'd look for some...
little sign.
Helped me to believe
she might get better.
There isn't a day
that passes...
when I don't wish she was back.
It's not the same.
One of you dies first.
That's sad.
But that's the deal.
When my son died,
my life was over!
It's called grief.
It's natural.
I want him back.
What you're doing is only making
your pain intolerable.
What could be worse
than my son dying?
Your son dying
over and over again.
That's not possible.
You want to see Gabriel again?
Do you?
Behold...
your son.
Now, even if he'd survived
the genetic mutation,
even if he'd been perfect
in every sense,
this would never have
been the boy you knew.
This would have been
some other...
different child.
Gabriel is not the
product of his DNA.
He's the sum of every day
you spent with him.
Every meal his mother
cooked for him.
Every story you read him.
Every ball you threw
for him to catch.
I'm sorry you had
to find out this way,
that Gabriel's soul...
is so much more than just
its constituent chemical parts.
I don't know
what's going to happen
to the baby
the girl is carrying,
and she is that.
She's just a girl.
And she will die
unless you help me.
So where is Kelly?
What happened?
Somebody asked me
to come in here and help.
Do you know this girl?
Kelly.
Her name is Kelly.
Do you know CPR?
Of course.
Get the air bag.
She's lost a lot of blood.
Find a refrigerator,
O negative.
Do it.
You a doctor?
I was.
More oxygen.
Squeeze until you see
the chest inflate.
What about the baby?
She lost him a long time ago.
"Him"?
How'd you know that?
You're Geppetto.
You'll have
to take over now,
if you want to save her.
So you just walk away?
Every scientific experiment
requires sacrifice.
She's not an experiment.
She's a human being.
You should care.
Playing God
has its disadvantages.
Nice to finally meet you,
Dr. Hood.
Come on, Kelly!
Hood!
Rachel, I need your help.
Cops are on their way.
Oh, God...
Come on, Kelly!
Come back for David!
Come back for David,
Kelly. Come on.
Hood.
So thank you, again,
for everything.
You're gonna be okay.
The doctor said I can't
have kids anymore.
All the more love
for the one you have.
You take care.
You, too.
No sign of Geppetto.
But, uh, Lea's in custody
and talking.
Yes?
Hello?
Okay.
Gotta go.
There's a situation.
What kind of situation?
A delicate one.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入