Come on,Sacha.
Come on.
That was almost twice
as fast as the last time.
That little guy is gonna
save a lot of lives.
Here's your reward,dude.
Get to chill with your buddies.
Get in there.
Dr. Miller,
has he been getting the
required amount of sleep?
Mm..hmm.
This is nice work,Bruce.
You've exceeded our most
optimistic projections.
- By a large margin.
- Well,how fast
- can you be ready for clinical trials?
- To collate
and quantify the data,we're
talking months now,not years.
Now,if this thing
ramps up as it should,
Belton Pharmaceuticals is gonna
let you write your own ticket.
Everything okay?
Yeah,just a question down at the lab.
I better go.
Don't want to fall behind schedule.
Sacha,what have you done?
Where did he say to meet him?
Right here.
Dr. Hood,
Special Agent Young,I'm Henry Brooks.
I appreciate you taking
the time to see me.
- Colonel Brooks,isn't it?
- That's right.
With the Defense Advanced
Research Projects Agency.
DARPA,the folks who really
invented the Internet.
Tell me,Dr. Hood,what do you know
about the Warfighter
Enhancement Program?
Well,I gather there's
a great emphasis on miniaturizing
some of the 80-plus pounds
of gear carried
by the average soldier,
enhancing the strength and
flexibility of battle armor.
That's only part of it.
We're also working on how to improve
raw human physical
and mental performance
in battlefield situations.
Hardware,software.
Now wetware,too?
Working on the soldiers themselves.
Could be,um,controversial.
Well,we think we mostly do
a good job in balancing
the scientific ethics with the need
to find new ways to protect
our troops in wartime.
Mostly.
Not always?
We've had an incident in
one of our primate studies.
The contractor is a biotech start-up
called Belton Pharmaceuticals.
The head researcher
is a neuroscientist
named Bruce Nesic.
The results were off the charts...
until this.
The chimp attack left traces
of hair and blood everywhere,
including on the victim.
Now,local animal control
authorities want him destroyed,
but we have millions
of dollars invested
in this particular
animal,and we need somebody
on the ground in Nevada... yesterday.
I don't get it,Colonel.
Why not use your own people?
I don't have that
kind of infrastructure.
Besides,anybody I could send
is already too close
to this research.
Their objectivity
could be compromised.
It's very simple,Dr. Hood.
Finding out what happened in Nevada
is essential for
the national security
of the United States.
Okay,I'll look into it.
Thank you.
Hood,watch this.
The guy's got as much
security as the President.
Hey,where are you going?
That man's agency was responsible
for the world's first breakthroughs
in artificial intelligence,
GPS,unmanned aircraft,
other things you've never heard of
but you'll be using every
day in ten years' time.
Odds are,the science
that that man makes happen
will have more impact on the
future than the President.
How is the veterinarian doing?
Dr. Miller is still unconscious.
She's stable,but just barely.
There were no signs of a break-in,
so that means Sacha would have had
to open his own cage and
all of the others,too?
Well,like us,chimps
are very ingenious,
even devious.
Back when I was doing my grad work,
I heard of a young male who
picked his handler's pocket,
hid the key for hours,
and then freed himself.
This is Sacha.
Looks docile enough now.
Too docile.
He's been sedated.
Well,yes,we thought it
best,given what has happened.
What exactly is the nature
of the research you're
doing with Sacha?
he's been given a drug cocktail
of neurotransmitters
and endocrine compounds
to enhance the mind/body performance
by speeding up the chemical
reactions in the brain.
It is our hope that
by using this regimen,
along with others like
it,that we can improve
the fighting abilities
of the soldiers.
That's where Enhanced
Warfighter funding comes in.
You are right.
Now,we know that
Russia and the Chinese
have similar active programs,
but we believe that we can leapfrog
what they're doing by years.
Any theories on what
provoked the attack?
Well,at first I thought
maybe Sacha had contracted
an infection of some sort,so
I began running a series
of tests,the results of which
we'll know in a few days.
But to be frank,Dr. Hood,
I think it was sabotage.
Really?
Why?
Some of the surveillance files
from the time of the
occurrence are missing.
Who was the last person to
have access to the files?
Rudy Callistro.
He's a veterinary technician.
He was Sacha's hands-on keeper.
Now,when all this happened,
everyone who works here in
the lab was greatly affected,
but Rudy just disappeared.
It adds up.
Deep background checks
on the personnel here
turned up blog comments hit
me on animal rights Web sites.
I had him flagged for
priority questioning.
We'll need to see everything
else you have on him.
And I'd like to see
your lab records,please.
Uh,going how far back?
Um,start of the project.
You realize that's
been about five years?
I mean,it's going
to take quite a while
just to print out the stuff.
No need to kill any trees.
I'm all about the bandwidth.
Come on,man... over here!
Put it up,put it up,put it up.
Good shot,good shot.
Watch out,watch out.
Pass it out,pass it out.
Sorry,man,you okay?
Yo,Pierce,relax,man.
Nobody's trying to
foul you on purpose.
Hey,Kevin.
Dr. Nesic.
I came looking for
you the other night,
but you weren't in your bunk.
I was probably out taking
a walk,trying to relax.
What's up,Doc?
It is time for your next treatment.
Can I just shower first?
Of course,I can wait.
Hey.
- Hi.
- I just got a hit
on a property held in the name
of Rudy Callistro's sister.
Get this. She was arrested
for throwing red paint
at a celebrity's fur
coat at a fashion show.
- So,runs in the family.
- Property's less than an hour
from here... we should check it out.
Maybe that's where he's holed up.
What I don't understand...
why he would harm the chimps
if he loves animals so much?
Well,I say it's all
about the missing video.
Maybe that was his idea alone
admistering some kind
of drug or... or goading the chimp.
I mean,can't you
just see this footage
all over the Internet
in the next few days?
It would be a huge
public relations victory
for the animal rights movement.
Sometimes,Rachel,
you have a very dark
view of human nature.
You know,some cultures,even
ones that eat meat,
treat their animals with
much more respect than we do.
In Japan,there's Wagyu cattle.
Feed them beer,sake,massage
them every day.
Forget the cattle.
I need someone to do that for me.
Mmm.
We're in the right place.
All of these species are...
commonly used in animal testing.
- Rudy Callistro?
- Who wants to know?
We're from the FBI... we need
to talk to you about Sacha.
Whoa.
Get back here!
Hey!
If I have to shoot you
to get you to stop,I'm
gonna be really pissed.
Ow. What the hell did
you throw at me,anyway?
Ground beef heart... it's cheap,
and if the animals don't eat it,
it goes to waste.
That's just great.
Give me your other hand.
I don't know,Doc.
Last time,I couldn't
sleep for a week afterward.
A common side effect.
It will diminish over time.
That's not all.
I'm tense all the time.
I get these headaches,
and the meds you give me
aren't really helping,either.
If it's all the same to you,
I'd rather just skip this treatment.
I understand,
but we're at a crucial
stage of the sequence.
In fact,
this may be the last one.
I really just want to go home.
I thought the whole point of this
posttraumatic stress disorder therapy
was to make it easier
for me to spend time
with my family
in-between deployments.
This is... it's just
taking me away from them.
Kevin,you know the stats.
The whole point of all the treatments
is to reduce conflict
on the home front.
Tell me that doesn't interest you.
Yeah,but I didn't sign up
to be a damn guinea pig.
Why did you
volunteer for this study?
- For my wife.
- Then,why do you
want to quit at this point in
the game when we're so close?
Okay,Doc.
I'll take my medicine like a big boy.
So you went to work for Belton
in order to sabotage the lab?
No.
I was only there to
gather information.
Laying the groundwork for
a new Equal Rights Amendment
that includes all species.
The way science is
treating animals...
it... it's criminal.
Sometimes.
But you're diabetic,
right?
How'd you know that?
Your fingertips.
From,uh,testing for
blood sugar with a,
what,portable glucose meter?
The discovery of
insulin,which makes it possible
for diabetics like yourself
to live with the
disease,was made possible
by animal testing.
Without the sacrifice of
those animals,you'd be dead.
Rudy,
what do you think
happened at the lab?
It's obvious,isn't it?
Nesic is the Dr. Frankenstein
of the animal kingdom.
He takes peaceful primates
and turns them into killers.
- Why did you run?
- 'Cause when it
all went to hell,I knew
that Nicicould find some way
to blame me for what happened.
Did you steal the surveillance video?
- No. No.
- Download any files?
I never accessed the system
and I never took anything.
Okay.
Let's say we buy your story.
Is there anything you can remember
that might help us to figure
out what's going on with Sacha?
Yeah.
I did notice something.
You know chimps exhibit handedness
just like people do,right?
For picking up items
like seeds or raisins.
Some prefer the
left-hand,and some the right.
Well,Sacha was a righty.
But in the last few days,he switched.
He went totally ambidextrous
for,for feeding himself,
and he even began to
favor his left hand.
Three...
two... one.
Did your screening for
pathogens turn up anything?
Not yet.
Did you also test for T. gondii?
Toxoplasmosis?
No.
Yeah,it's a parasite
that infects the mind of its hosts
and can alter behavior
and things like handedness.
But there are no felines
or rodents at this facility.
And they're your most common
carries of toxoplasmosis.
Well,it could have come in contact
with any number of species
during transshipment.
You may be right.
That could help
explain Sacha's actions.
We'll test for it.
Whoa.
Sacha's gone.
Let's go,lock them down.
All right,
come on,now.
All right,put that up,put that up.
Oh,yeah,yeah.
All right,come on,come on.
You all right,man?
No,I'm out.
Hey,Kev,Nick's hurt.
Come on.
Hey,Kev,
get your stuff on,man.
Hey,Kevin,let's play some ball,man.
Come on.
You'll never get away with this...
Kevin?
Daddy!
Hey,hey,buddy.
What are you doing here?
Honey,I thought you only
came home on weekends?
Why aren't you at the base?
What's wrong,Kevin?
- Are you okay?
- I got
a killer headache,babe. We
got an aspirin or something?
Stronger the better.
Are you hung over?
No.
Just my head hurts,that's all.
Jackson,honey,you just
keep watching TV,okay?
Mommy and Daddy
need to have a talk.
I haven't been drinking.
- I just had to see you.
- Kevin,
the therapy you're
getting is supposed
to help you be with
us. You need to get
- back before they think you're AWOL.
- Just wanted
to see my wife and kid.
And my head hurts.
From those treatments.
The ones that are
supposed to be helping me.
Damn it!
Kevin,your hand.
It's fine. Did you
see what I just did?
Yeah,you punched a
hole in the cabinet...
Not that. I...
I just,I... I threw a left.
I should have thrown a right.
I'm a righty.
You shouldn't have
thrown a punch at all.
It's these stupid treatments.
Abby,
I'm sorry.
It's just... I know.
I'm sorry,too.
I can't pretend to
know what it was like
to be in combat.
I don't know what you saw out there.
But I'm glad to have you here.
At home.
Thanks. We'll be in touch.
Animal Control has
every available officer
doing a grid search for Sacha.
Let's hope they turn something up.
Does the data check out?
I've only really seen
the tip of the iceberg.
It's going to take a
while to sift through.
You know,the Bureau is
not without its resources.
We have a entire department devoted
to data analysis.
As talented the,uh,
government's programmers
may be,Rachel,
not many criminals are found
by running linear regression
on their credit card
purchases and porn downloads.
Analysis softwares
are written to spot common
denominators of falsehood.
If you're looking for anything
specific,you can't really
use generic data sifting code.
I get it.
Instead of relying
on electronic intel
you need to put your
own eyes on the target.
Do your own legwork. Exactly.
Only in this case
I get do it sitting on my ass.
Check left,I'll check right.
Gary,you go down the embankment,
check the drainage pipe.
Remember the missing
chimp can hide high or low.
Copy that.
Special Agent Young,FBI.
What've we got?
Single victim,took a bad beating.
His tranquilizer gun's been fired,
so he probably put
up some kind of fight.
We've got compound
fracture to the ulna,
defensive wound,most likely.
Got broken collarbones.
Both elbows hyperextended.
- Extensive facial contusions.
- Okay.
Same injuries as the
chimps at the lab,
and Dr. Miller,the veterinarian.
You think Sacha could be responsible?
Well,it's possible.
Fully-grown chimpanzees are
up to five times stronger
than a human being.
Hood.
Over here.
The Animal Control
Officer's tranq dart
did hit Sacha.
But the chimp must have attacked
before the drugs could take effect.
It looks like the officer
inflicted Sacha's fatal injury
- while defending himself.
- Where's Sacha?
Well,Dr. Nesic,I believe
Animal Control and
County Coroner are having
an interesting jurisdictional
debate about the body.
Seeing as how a chimp shares
98% DNA with a human.
Who should get the corpse?
I'll take Sacha
back to the lab with me.
He's the property of
Belton Pharmaceuticals.
And we have not
completed our research.
I'm sorry,Dr. Nesic.
This is a criminal matter now.
It's out of your hands.
Faster! Faster!
Faster,Mommy!
More! More!
Contents of the bowel
was very interesting.
I was afraid you'd say that.
Sacha's large bowel was empty.
Just what you'd expect
after a sudden death.
His bowel should have
evacuated immediately
upon dying.
But there was no signs
of defecation where
the body was found.
Anything in his system
would have left at least
a trace where he died.
More likely a big trace.
Which means Sacha was
killed somewhere else.
His body
must have been planted
there after his death.
Also means Sacha
couldn't have attacked
The Animal Control Officer.
Then who did?
Dr. Hood,we're about
to cut into his skull.
Just one moment.
I have to see what
was inside his skull.
Kevin,baby,you've been
in there a long time.
Are you coming to bed?
Congratulations,Hood,
you've got me staring
at monkey brains.
Well,they're worth staring at.
Well,no paramecia...
rules out toxoplasmosis.
Most of the brain
structures look normal.
See the,uh,amygdala here.
It's pretty much
the same in chimps
as it is in humans.
It's the center of the fear response.
The fight-or-flight
reflex.
When the senses tell it of a threat,
it responds by sending alarm signals
to the,uh,other organs...
the pituitary,adrenal glands...
they flood the system with adrenaline
so you either run away or
you fight your attacker.
Or an enemy soldier.
That's not all.
The amygdala helps
regulate handedness.
All of Sacha's new behaviors...
his aggressive reactions,
his change from right
to left handedness...
all would tend to indicate
changes of that part
- of the brain.
- So Nesic was
messing with the amygdala?
Yeah,somehow,Nesic
managed to make Sacha's two amygdalae
twice their normal size.
Which speeds up reactions.
It's like when you sneeze.
When you sneeze every
muscle in your body
involuntarily convulses.
By giving the amygdala
the size and heft to take over
the entire system,I mean
dealing with total force,
you're kind of turning the urge to...
to violence into the
equivalent of a sneeze.
Something you can't control.
The result? The subjects...
the-the chimps would respond
to any perceived threat,
no matter how small,with
overwhelming force.
That's one hell of an
unintended consequence.
I'm not so sure it's unintended.
Come on.
All right. Bring it up. Bring it up.
Hey,check it out.
Gentlemen!
Anyone know of the
whereabouts of Kevin Pierce?
It is very important
that I speak with him.
Nobody?
For a three-day leave
at the Hard Rock Casino,
all expenses paid?
If he has gone AWOL,
you could save him a lot of trouble.
You would be helping him.
We're not stupid,Doc.
Sergeant Pierce does need help.
And whatever you've
been doing to him,
it ain't working.
That's right. Mm-hmm.
So you here to play?
Or just hog the ball?
I know that you think that
you are watching his back,
but you are screwing him.
You are screwing yourselves.
Nesic's data is perfect.
Too perfect.
What do you mean?
Let me show you.
Hood?
Minibar... expensive.
Oh,don't worry,Rachel.
Live a little.
Now this... is what data looks like.
It's a group of far-flung points
on a graph.
Can I use your phone charger,please?
Thank you.
If we were to draw
a curve on this data,
it would look something like this.
See,the phone charger represents
a line that encompasses
a general rule.
We call that an average
of all the data points.
But Nesic's data
doesn't look like that.
Nesic's data never leaves the curve.
That... is statistically impossible.
You're saying he fit
the data to the curve,
rigged it to say what
he wants it to say.
Well,he's definitely
hiding something.
The question is what?
We need to get back in his lab,now.
This is Special Agent Young.
I need the Megahut to send
Entry and Exit people for T-3s.
- I'll give you the
address.  - T-3s?
I absolutely love,that for once,
you have no idea what
I'm talking about.
The Entry and Exit specialist
should be here any minute.
So,Hood,I've been
meaning to ask you...
How exactly did you get this gig?
1986 World Series.
Excuse me?
Mets versus Red Sox.
I'm a Mets fan.
And,uh,one of my classmates
at Princeton was this,uh,
annoyingly button-down
history major from Boston.
So he had tickets for the games,
but he had no way of getting there.
I had a 1979 VW Passat
that I'd modified to
run on vegetable oil.
So,we,um,inevitably,declared
a truce,and,um,
we ended up driving up to,uh,Fenway.
We watched game five.
Then we drove down to the city,
and we saw game six at Shea Stadium.
By the time we got home to Princeton,
he and I were pretty much friends.
He went on to become an
officer in the Marines,
and earn his law degree.
And become director of the FBI.
That's exactly right.
One day,he gives me a
call,asking for a favor,
and before I know it,I'm
spending most of my time
- with people like you,
- Hey!
in places like this...
Don't worry. You ever get
into trouble with the Bureau,
I got plenty of dirt on the director
you can use to get out of it.
Here we go.
Agent Reed,sorry
for the short notice.
No problem.
- Thanks.
- Any time.
Rachel,tell me this is legal.
Please,we've got the
FBI and DARPA behind us.
I'm pretty sure we can get
the breaking-and-entering
charges thrown out.
- Six?
- So?
There are only six primate cages.
Nesic had extensive histories
on seven experimental subjects.
What are you looking for,exactly?
Well,we've seen how
numbers can be manipulated.
I'm looking for
hard,scientific evidence.
He must keep the blood and
tissues samples somewhere.
Hood,I think I've got it.
The samples are in here.
Rachel...
subject seven's blood chemistry is...
all wrong.
He's got type AB...
and only one primate has type AB.
Subject seven is a human being.
Hey.
There you are.
Hi,Abby.
Dr. Nesic?
Is something wrong with Kevin?
I don't know.
I was hoping you could tell me.
Oh,God.
Kevin may be having
extended combat flashbacks.
I've seen it before
with soldiers suffering from PTSD.
I told him he should
go back to the base.
You've seen him then?
Is he here? I need
to get a hold of him.
No,Kevin's not here.
But I can tell him to
call you when I see him.
Good-bye.
I apologize.
This wasn't on my radar.
It turns out the company
Nesic's working for
is running another
defense-related study
20 minutes up the
road from your location
at Nellis Air Force Base.
They're testing therapies
on a sequestered group
of return combat troops
who suffer from PTSD.
Any indication which one
might be subject seven?
One of them,a Sergeant Kevin Pierce,
left the facility without permission
after exhibiting strange behavior.
It sounds like our guy.
Dr. Hood,Agent Young,
if you need anything
else,you just ask.
We will. Thank you,sir.
Thank you.
We need to get to this
air force base,now.
I think it was Pierce that attacked
the animal control officer.
He probably approached
him in what seemed
like a threatening manner.
Pierce would've responded
autonomically,as if programmed,
his nervous system taking over
to deal with any perceived threat.
So maybe Nesic staged Sacha's escape
to hamper our investigation.
When the animal control officer was
attacked,Nesic saw an opportunity
to end the scrutiny.
He killed Sacha and planted the body
and then went
off the grid.
That's true
and appears out there
is a danger to himself
and anyone who crosses his path.
Nesic's out there,too.
I'm gonna order a 24-hour guard
for our injured veterinarian.
She's the only witness we've got.
We come from all different units,
different areas around the country,
but we all got the same story.
When I came back from over there,
it was like,like the world
was moving in slow motion,
and I was still in combat speed.
So when they offered
this study,I jumped on it.
You know,anything to
help me fit back in.
- Has it helped?
- Maybe.
We mostly just sit
around watching videos,
filling out psych tests.
But your friend,Pierce,got
special treatment.
Yeah,they hit him hard,man.
I mean,drugs,
endurance tests.
I mean,he was hurting.
Always seeking for painkillers.
He even started shifting the hand
he dribbled with playing ball.
You know,he went from right to left.
It was weird.
This is very
important,Private Vasquez.
Sergeant Pierce is not in trouble,
but we need to find
him for his own good.
That's the same thing Nesic said
when he came looking for him.
Nesic was here? When?
Last night.
Looking for Kev,same as you.
We didn't tell him,jack,though.
What makes you think
we're gonna tell you?
Before being assigned to Dr. Hood,
I spent six months
as an FBI component
of Task Force Eagle
in Kabul,Afghanistan.
I worked with guys like you,everyday,
doing sensitive site exploitations,
looking for intel and what
the bad guys might be up to.
I'm not one of
them,and neither is he.
I believe that you've all been
victims of a scientific fraud.
Dr. Nesic has already
aborted one failed experiment,
and I believe he's trying to
do the same with Kevin Pierce,
and any one of you could be next.
That's why I think
you should tell me.
There's a park near here.
You know,a couple times
when things got rough,
he'd go there,decompress,chill out.
Thank you.
Yo,Joey,we've got your stuff.
Hell,man,that ain't Joey.
Look at what we got here.
This is a place of business homes.
We don't need any
suspicious looking characters
bringing the cops around.
Did you hear a word he just said?
You need to leave,buddy.
My phone died.
Do either one of you guys have
a spare cell phone battery?
Are you kidding me?
Hello? Hello?
Hey... hey,baby,it's me.
I didn't recognize the number.
It scared me.
I had to borrow a phone.
I just called to tell you that...
it's almost over.
What? What's almost over?
What's happening?
Where are you? Why did you leave?
I had to leave,babe.
I didn't want you to get hurt.
Who's going to hurt us?
I am.
What?
Nothing.
Kevin,Dr. Nesic stopped by today.
He wants to talk to you.
Yeah,I got something
to say to him,too.
You're not in some
kind of trouble,are you?
When are you coming home?
I can't come home yet,babe.
Not until I stop it.
Stop what?
The war?
You're home now,Kevin.
I know where I am.
I'm not crazy.
It's okay,Jackson.
Come to Mommy.
Hey...
is he still awake? Put him on,okay?
Daddy.
Hey,Dad.
Hey,buddy.
You remember when I
used to sing you to sleep
when you were little?
Huh?
I'd sing,Twinkle,twinkle,little star
How I wonder what you are
Up above the earth so far
Like a rocket powered car.
Good night,pal.
Now remember,if we find Pierce,
we need to approach him
in a nonthreatening manner.
Try not to... you know.
Hood.
A nine millimeter casing.
Oh,God.
They're alive.
Barely.
This is Special Agent Young.
I need an ambulance
at Desert View Park,
415 Ryder Street.
Hey,Hood,blood and tire tracks.
I think Pierce took their car.
He could be anywhere.
Not anywhere.
He was hurt.
Private Vasquez said
he was seeking painkillers.
He'll be looking for a pharmacy.
Freeze!
Put your hands up!
Hands where I can see them!
Unit five-David,requesting backup.
Subject in sight.
Turn around!
- Pierce,stop! Hood...
- Don't.
The slightest move could set him off.
Let me do my job.
Rachel...
Put the gun down. Trust me.
Listen to me,Kevin.
We're not here to hurt you.
We know what they've
been doing to you.
We're going to make it stop.
Who the hell are you?
My name's Jacob Hood.
I'm a scientist.
Oh,like Nesic?
No,not like Nesic.
Nothing like Nesic.
Sergeant,Can I ask you a question?
I want you to answer very carefully.
What do you want to happen here?
How do you want this to play out?
I need...
... to make it stop.
I have to keep them from
doing this to anybody else.
Well,in order for that to happen,
you've got to focus.
First you have to let these men go.
If you kill them,it's all over.
There won't be anything
I can do for you.
I think I understand what's
going on in your head.
Every nerve must be screaming
for you to go into action.
The urge must be uncontrollable,
but you're gonna have to
damp it down somehow.
Use the part of your
thoughts you can control
and think it through.
Think about where you are.
Think about what your options are.
Make a choice.
FBI. This man is now
in federal custody.
Stand down.
I repeat,stand down.
It's okay.
It's over.
No.
It's not.
Not until you see this.
Hello?
Kevin?
Sergeant Pierce isn't
coming,Dr. Nesic.
But he was,um...
kind enough to let me
have the missing video.
What are you doing here?
When he broke in,he just
wanted to destroy the lab
and free the chimps,but
they attacked him.
So he fought back.
Dr. Miller was working
late,em,heard the commotion.
What are you doing?! Stop!
Well,you know results.
Congratulations.
You found a way of
turning off the conscience.
Soldiers with no moral
or ethical compunction
about killing,
able to act,react...
lightning efficiency.
Say that without the...
smug,self-righteous sneer,
and it sounds like a
heroic advance to me.
An advance?
Really?
Don't think you've given
much thought to the long-term
implications of this?
You think someone like Pierce
will ever be able to
reintegrated into society?
Do you even care
that you may have destroyed
a young man's life?
I'm trying to save his life.
Save all of their lives.
Do I have to remind you...
every day soldiers die in the field.
My work will help them to survive.
Oh,he'll survive.
No thanks to you.
He's in federal custody.
Dr. Nesic.
You can tell the caliber of a man
by the way he faces
up to his mistakes.
The bad ones always
make it worse by trying
to cover up their tracks,
and it's the cover up
that brings them down.
Get him out of here.
Hands behind your back.
I love you.
I love you,too.
Love you.
Thanks for talking me down.
I just gave you a
little encouragement.
You talked yourself down.
Nice work,Dr. Hood.
Nesic is going to jail
and Sergeant Pierce is going
to get the therapy he needs
to undo what was done to him.
Whatever it takes.
But the program's
going to go on,isn't it?
Of course.
If it didn't,it would
mean I wasn't doing my job.
Super-soldiers are coming.
Nesic just bent the rules too far,
even for us.
You know,some people refer to DARPA
as a hundred geniuses
connected by a travel agent.
Truth is,we're always on
the lookout for number 101.
Oh.
Thank you,Colonel,but,uh,I got a job.
Anyway,I prefer to tackle problems
created by the world at large
rather than problems
created by my employers.
Well,suit yourself.
But if you change your mind,don't
hesitate to get in touch.
Let's leave it this way
Next time you get
yourself in trouble...
you have my number.