******
Where are we going, Dad?
Higher ground, Nicky.
This flash flood could kill us both.
I don't feel so good.
The doctor said to keep
taking your chemo pills.
Here. Take one of these.
Hang on, Nicky.
If we get up over the
ridge, we'll be safe.
Come on...
Dad! Dad!
Can't hardly see anything.
Come on! Come on, baby. Come on!
We're gonna make it!
We did it, Nicky.
No way the floodwater
will reach this high.
Dad?
If I'm gonna die...
who's gonna take care of you?
Come here, buddy. Come here.
You're okay.
****
Stealing second. Stealing
second. Bring it in, nice!
Listen to that crowd go crazy! Yeah!
Hey, hold on, Nicky.
Why don't you head inside, son?
Okay.
Dr. Reeves.
Nicky was scheduled
for surgery a week ago.
Why haven't you returned our calls?
'Cause Nicky doesn't
need surgery. He's fine.
Daniel, he has a tumor on his kidney.
Without surgery, he is going to die.
Where's your faith, Dr. Reeves?
You know I'm not going
to let you take him.
Officer?
Mr. Harris, we have a court
order appeal by Child Services.
They're forcing us to act in the
best interest of Nicholas Harris.
Lave my son alone!
Let go of my son!
He'll die if we don't
get him to a hospital.
Does it look like he's gonna die to you?
Dad, it's okay.
- Nicky!
- It's okay.
Dr. Reeves?
Do you believe in miracles?
You will.
******
What's the problem, Dennis?
Veronica, where exactly was
this tumor supposed to be?
On the right kidney.
It's on the MRI scan and the ultrasound.
Taken when?
Three weeks ago.
Well, look at the ultrasound now.
I checked the other one,
too, just to be safe.
This boy's kidneys are
immaculate. Perfectly normal.
That's not possible. I
performed the exam myself.
The tumor was right there.
Well, it's not there now.
People are flocking to what is
being called a miracle spring,
which suddenly appeared during the heavy storms that
hit Lewiston, Montana a little over three weeks ago.
Now, this is eight-year-old
Nicholas Harris,
who was diagnosed with a
cancerous tumor on his kidney,
but after he started drinking from the
mysterious spring, the tumor just disappeared.
The boy's father
believes it was a miracle.
What the...
- Hood?
- Hey, Rachel, you seen this?
Hood, what are you doing here?
- Nice place.
- Hood, it's Sunday.
Rachel, you have to see this.
I have to see this?
Miracle boy.
Miracle cure for cancer found.
Miracle spring.
Okay, I saw them. Are you happy?
Hood, it's Sunday and it's 6:00 A.M.
Rachel... we have to
go to Montana right now.
No. No, no, no, no. Please,
please don't. I'm begging you.
If this is my weekend free of all
things "Hood," unless this is a dream.
Is this a dream?
Actually, you know what,
uh, I just realized...
I think I could be able
to do this on my own, huh?
Wait.
I need an airtight, seamless, indestructible reason
to leave my apartment before 7:00 A.M.Monday morning.
Let's hear it.
Okay.
If this causes very sick people to walk away from
their medical treatment to drink from this spring,
they're going to die.
That'll do. Turn around.
Turn around.
How'd you find my place, anyway?
Oh, the FBI has its resources, Rachel.
Anyway, what about Mr. Shoes?
Don't worry.
He'll wait.
So, Hood,
what if we get to Montana and
realize it really is a miracle?
Oh, take it from me, Rachel.
There's no... such... thing.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Eleventh
Hour Season01 Episode11
***********
$40 a jar.
There you go, sir. Good luck to you.
And you can keep the jar. That's on me.
Come on. Who's next?
And you've been using
the walker for how long?
About ten years.
There he is, over there!
Nicky, how much water did
it take to cure your cancer?
When did you start
drinking from the spring?
No more questions. Please, come on.
Hey, Daniel, are you a religious man?
FBI. Clear a path! Or you'll
be charged with trespassing.
- Can you do that?
- Sort of.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Mr. Harris, we need to talk.
Those didn't look like weekend bags
you were loading onto your truck.
Planning a trip?
I'm sorry I ever told
anyone about that spring.
I just want to get
Nicky away from all this.
You think what happened here
is just going to go away?
If you leave here now, you're
going to be running forever.
This needs to be explained.
I can help you do that.
Now, I want to know
about the spring. Tell me.
Well, what's to tell? I mean, three
weeks ago the storm hit real bad.
So, we took off until it was safe.
Then we found water
gushing out the hillside.
Who owns this property?
Travis Dobbs and the guy
that owns this trailer.
So, what, you just filled a bottle with this mysterious
untested liquid and gave it to Nicky to drink?
- No.
- My dad didn't do anything. I did.
The spring-- it looked so clean
and fresh, I wanted to taste it.
I had to.
Buddy, give us a few minutes.
Okay.
Look, my son was going to die.
And he drank some of that water,
and something happened, I...
I don't know what, but
he got better quick.
I took it as a sign and I threw
away all those pills he was taking.
- The chemotherapy pills.
- Yeah.
Do you mind if I, uh, just do a little
investigating into Nicky's recovery?
What's there to investigate? I mean,
he's perfectly healthy. You've seen him.
Even the doctor said so.
Yeah, and that's an incredible thing.
But my concern is how Nicky got better
will lead to other
people getting sicker.
Do you know why they call it a miracle?
Because there is no explanation.
I owe you, tough stuff. Thank you.
That's okay, Lily. No sweat.
Nicky? Come here, son.
Come on. One at a time, folks.
There's plenty of miracle
water for everybody.
$40 a jar.
Please have your money ready.
Exact change is always appreciated.
- There you go, ma'am.
- Oh, bless you.
You take care of yourself now.
I'm just curious.
Has anyone been down here
to prove this empirically?
I mean, like a researcher or
scientist-type person to see what,
if anything, is actually in this water?
It cures cancer. That's all I know.
That's all any of these
folks need to know.
Look, buddy, you're holding up the line.
You want to buy a jar or don't you?
Oh, yes, please. How much?
$40, please.
40,00 Okay.
Thank you. You take care now.
So, uh... this is going to
fix all these sick people, huh?
Yeah.
Going to cure over 200 types of cancer--
leukemia, brain tumors, breast cancer?
How about insomnia? I have trouble
sleeping. Is it any good for insomnia?
We'll see, huh?
As far as I know, only one person
actually seems to have gotten any better.
One person.
I'll tell you what. How about I take this
back with me, I test it scientifically,
and if I can prove it's not what you say it is,
you can give all these people their money back.
Well, let me ask you this.
How are you going to
test a miracle? Huh?
Besides, it don't matter.
I own this land and everything
on it, so go ahead and test.
You're Travis Dobbs, correct?
Yeah.
The same Travis Dobbs who's on
probation for selling alcohol to a minor
at the Gas and Sip off of Route 28?
The hell is this?
FBI.
With your criminal record, fraud can
get you up to ten years in prison,
whether this is your property or not.
So arrest me.
You're okay. What's your name, honey?
Lily.
Lily, can you tell me
what's wrong with you?
I have lymphoma.
Let's get her to the hospital.
We have got a serious problem here.
Most of these people are patients from
across the country who should be in bed,
not standing in a
field for hours on end.
Where do you want me to put them?
First the storm flood shut down
half the hospital, now this.
Okay, put 'em on gurneys,
keep them in the hallways.
I'm going to check out maintenance, see if
we can get "B" ward up again and running.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, careful
where you step, Ms. Cole.
You know, we still got a few live cables
down here. Those puddles could be damn hot.
Hurdle, what the hell is taking so long?
Well, the storm really did a
number on this place, you know,
so, uh, we're about halfway through
replacing the fried circuitry.
I need power back up on "B"
ward. I need it yesterday.
How about a week from yesterday?
How about I fire you and hire someone who will charge
half of what you do and get it done twice as fast?
Ma'am, we've been working all kinds
of hours to get thelace fixed up.
I don't want to lose my job.
How about two more days?
You know, we'll just
work around the clock.
All right. Without overtime.
Sure, no problem.
Come on. Let's get back to work.
All staff, please stand
by to test power...
Okay.
Lily, what happened?
She overdosed on spring water.
And you are?
Dr. Jacob Hood.
He's the special science
advisor to the FBI.
I'm Agent Rachel Young.
Lily, you've stopped your
chemo treatment, haven't you?
Not you, too.
Oh, come on, Dr. Reeves.
We both saw what that
water did for Nicky.
You can't deny that it cured him.
There is no scientific proof of that, which means
there is no reason for you to stop your treatment.
When did you go off the chemo?
Just over a week ago. I...
I got to know Nicky while we
were both being treated here.
I trust him; he wouldn't
lie to me about the water.
Nina.
Yes, Dr. Reeves.
Make sure she has zero water and
start her on a hypertonic saline drip.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Doesn't really make sense.
Coming off the chemo, she should be
feeling better, at least temporarily.
Any other patients exhibiting symptoms
not really typical of their illness?
Yes, several.
Um, there's a woman with rheumatoid
arthritis who can't stop vomiting.
There's a Down syndrome patient
who's got chronic insomnia.
I mean, these are symptoms that are
completely unlated to their illnesses.
But they're all drinking from
the same spring. Am I right?
I have tested that water countless times,
and I can tell you there's no mystery to it.
Good or bad, it is just water.
Okay. Can I see your results?
Can you wait for me to get off my shift?
Cute dog.
I rescued her from the pound.
You're a sweetheart,
aren't you, Bonnie? Come on.
You know, understandably, Helen Cole
and the rest of the hospital hierarchy
want nothing to do with this miracle,
so I brought my research home.
Any idea of the source of the water?
We can't get any access
to it because of Dobbs.
Property owner?
Yeah
Is there any way that you could have the FBI step
in and shut him down so we can trace the source?
Well, first we have to get proof of some
dangerous element in the water, then we can...
shut him down.
Could I see your results, please?
Thank you. You mind if I...
Nicky's tumor was
diagnosed six weeks ago.
The storm that caused the spring to
emerge was three weeks after that.
Nicky started drinking
the water immediately.
Three weeks later,
Nicky's tumor is gone.
Now, still, I tested that water
and I can't find anything in it.
I see that you tested for infrared
spectroscopy, crystallization...
You're right.
This is normal water.
Veronica, can I ask you a question?
Do you think it's possible this spring
water contains some magic property
that could wither away a tumor?
I don't know.
That's not really an answer. Either you
believe in miracle water or you don't.
The fact is: an eight-year-old
boy had cancer and now he doesn't.
It's not because of any
medical treatment I gave him,
so whether you like to believe
it or not, that is miraculous.
Yeah, well, there's just this
one fact going through my head,
and that's that every year, half a million men,
women, children in this country die of cancer,
and they all ask for miracles,
every last one of them.
So what makes this...
little boy special?
No, I believe there's
something... in this water.
I'm gonna find out what it is.
Thank you very much for
your time. Excuse me. Rachel.
He wasn't speaking as
a scientist, was he?
He always speaks as a scientist, but he did
lose someone to cancer a couple years ago.
Thanks again.
Who the hell are you?
You need to close the spring down.
You need to get the hell
out of my truck, pal.
Wrong answer.
Yes.
Well, I respectfully disagree.
I feel that it is in
our jurisdiction t...
Yes, sir.
It's the director. He's really pissed.
Your face has been all over the TV.
Hey, Frank.
Well, 'cause I'm worried about the media spreading
the kind of superstition that could cost lives.
No, I know it's not an official case, but
there's definitely something going on here.
Well, 'cause I'm looking at a
body right now. That's how I know.
Um, you're breaking up. I
can't... you're breaking up.
What do we have here, Detective?
Somebody snapped his neck.
Death was instantaneous, but we
found some blood in his pickup truck.
Looks like they wanted his cash.
Maybe.
So why make the statement?
Why drag his body all the way up
here and dump it in the spring?
Thk you, Detective.
Well, if you wanted to shut
the miracle spring down.
But it's just a crime scene.
In 72 hours, it goes back to
being open to the hopeful masses.
72 hours would be enough.
For what?
Well, if someone is dumping
contaminants in this spring,
then all this miraculous attention has
got to be the last thing they'd want.
72 hours could be enough
time to flush the water clean.
We need to find the underground
source of this spring right away.
I'll get the Department of the
Interior to send out a hydrologist.
Good, but even if we can't get results from
the water, maybe we can get it from the cancer.
We need to talk.
What about?
One of the miracle seekers just died-- a
26-year-old man-- and the others are getting sicker.
Was he an oncology patient?
No, it wasn't cancer. It was sepsis.
Blood poisoning?
Hold on.
Was he sick before he took the water?
How much spring water did he drink?
A gallon a day for the past week.
A gallon a day?
Okay, well, that settles
it. It's definitely a cause.
Jacob!
Couldn't have done this by phone
or computer or satellite link?
Well, then, you wouldn't get
to meet Dr. Veronica Reeves.
Oh, see, he thinks I'm buying
this crap, but I know his MO.
Firsthand observation,
hypothesis, experiment, result.
It's all about the
cheeseburger and the beer.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Matthew Kaplan, genius.
Matthew is one of the country's
leading cancer researchers.
One of. He jests. Big-time.
- Is that the specimen?
- Yes.
I call him Quasimodo. Nefroblastoma.
Stage 3 kidney tumor. It's
the same tumor that Nicky had.
It's just what we're looking for.
Well, let's hope the
little guy is thirsty.
Miracle water for the
rat coming right up.
You're not gonna see results
for at least 24 hours.
I'm gonna get back to my patients.
Very nice to meet you, Dr. Kaplan.
That's what they all say.
Now, if this soil had a
higher salt concentration,
I'd be using a resistivity array to
chart the flow of subterranean water
by measuring changes in electrical conductivity
at progressively deeper subsurface levels.
Oh, you would, would you?
Have you tracked the
source of the spring?
Ironically, the, uh, rocky soil here
actually helps our ground-penetrating
radar map subterranean terrain.
Soft, silty soil, on the
other hand, would, uh,
deaden our signals and make
undergrnd mapping far more difficult.
Oh, my God.
What is it?
Hood, you're not gonna believe
what this water runs under.
This place was a storage depot
until just after the first Gulf War.
Storage for what?
Depleted uranium, mostly.
What did you say?
Depleted uranium.
Uh, the base was decommissioned
by the army in 1995.
Post-Cold War downsizing.
Yep.
Dr. Hood, it's Veronica Reeves.
I just spoke with the coroner who worked
on the patient that I lost to sepsis.
And?
And there was significant cellular damage
to the stomach lining and the intestines,
none of which would have
shown up on X-rays or MRIs.
- It's classic symptoms of...
- Radiation poisoning.
You know what? I think
I just found the source.
Will you excuse me a second?
Rachel... think we're gonna need a full
radiological analysis of this facility now.
Yeah. Sergeant.
Hello again.
Where are you?
I'm at an armory on Pennington Hill...
where they used it to store
depleted uranium routes.
I know where that is.
I'm coming right now.
Still nothing above
background radiation.
Have you checked the storm drains,
the, uh, ventilation shafts?
All done, and we found nothing.
Okay, thank you.
Can you check the calibration
on your Geiger counter?
You're operating at maximum sensitivity?
Dr. Hood, we've checked and rechecked.
I'm sorry, sir. There's no radiation.
If depleted uranium was ever stored
here, it was removed a long time ago.
Can I see your hydrological map, please?
This doesn't make any sense at all.
She drank the water, but it
made her worse. Not better.
Hey, it's not your fault,
Nicky. It's not your fault.
This was your miracle, okay? Come on.
No, no, this isn't fair!
Lily deserves a miracle, too!
I know. I know. It's okay.
Some unknown substance is
contaminating the groundwater.
Groundwater that's...
sprung up since that storm.
The armory is testing
negative for radioactive waste.
And there's no natural radiation.
No radioactive ore within 100 miles.
But, uh, well, there's...
there's something.
Something's here, and I can't see it.
And I'm not wrong.
Everybody's wrong sometimes, Hood.
Yeah, yeah, maybe, Rachel. Not today.
Okay, well, we'll start from
the periphery of the water table,
and we'll work our way down the slope.
Hood.
There's a possibility that it could be
something else causing the contamination,
something that mimics the
effects of radioactive poisoning.
We know that it's not a miracle.
It's not a miracle 'cause
there's no such thing.
Hood...
don't make this about your wife.
It's not about my wife, Rachel.
This is about all the people who
will die if I don't help them.
Really?
You said, "What makes
this boy so special?
"How come he gets a miracle
and no one else does?"
Agent Young.
We'll be right there.
Dr. Reeves is dead.
Clean swipe of the femoral artery.
She knew what she was doing.
Must have bled out in a second.
And this was in her hand?
Yeah.
One clean cut. Suicides...
even with doctors, you
usually have hesitation marks.
You check her system for drugs?
Already in the wor.
Should have results by tomorrow.
- Thank you.
- Detective, coroner needs you.
- Rachel.
- Yeah?
I have a really horrible feeling...
Veronica died because she gave a damn.
Me, too. Come on.
Where?
I want to confirm this really
was suicide and not murder.
Hey, Quasi.
Drinking like a camel, aren't you?
You like this stuff.
I'll be damned.
Hello.
Jacob! I've never seen anything like it.
Quasimodo... his tumor,
it's gone. It's disappeared.
Look, you got to find
out what did this, Jacob.
Yeah. This is unbelievable.
Okay, thanks.
Tell me.
That spring water we gave Quasimodo
seems to have shrunk his tumor.
So, it did cure Nicky.
- Look out!
- Geez.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay. That raccoon isn't.
I didn't hit it, did I?
No, raccoons are nocturnal animals.
They don't come out in the day.
So, maybe it has rabies.
Maybe it has somethinglse.
Hey, Bonnie. Hi, girl. How you doing?
How you doing? You miss your mommy?
No water, no food.
If she were gonna kill herself, she would have made
arrangements for someone to take care of her dog.
It wasn't a suicide.
She was murdered,
just like Travis Dobbs.
Should I ask?
I'm making ice cubes.
Okay, Bonnie.
Pee-pee time.
Hey, tough stuff.
How you feeling?
Fabulous.
You know what I'm going to
do when I get out of here?
No.
Teach you guitar.
We could get our own band going.
What do you say?
Okay.
It's my fault you're in here.
No, it's not. Come on.
But you could do me a favor.
Anything.
I need a drink.
Can you get me a lemonade?
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Okay, Rachel.
What do we know about ice?
It goes great with Scotch.
Yeah, well, off of
that, you know it's cold.
It's hard. It's crystalline.
And...
With normal water,
It floats.
Now, this ice is from the spring.
Our so-called "miracle water."
What kind of water makes
ice cubes that sink?
Very rare, very special kind
of water called heavy water.
The molecules in heavy water have
extra neutrons that make it, um...
heavier.
and in humans it has been
known to shrink cancer cells,
but this never occurred to me
because it's so incredibly rare.
But if it shrank Nicky's tumor, that
would make heavy water a good thing, right?
No. Heavy water is not a good thing.
It's really toxic.
It's like radiation except it's not
radioactive and it's practically undetectable.
However, it is the only substance
that can actually effect a change
in sleeping patterns in mammals.
The raccoon.
So, it's just a fluke that this
spring pops up full of heavy water?
No, no, it's not a fluke.
Only one in 5,000 water
molecules is heavy water.
Only human technology can
produce it in large quantities.
Even I know one use for heavy water.
Nuclear weapons.
So, this is the kind of
water worth killing for.
So, you're telling me that Dr. Reeves was
murdered by some nuclear terrorist here in Montana?
She was killed because she was
getting too close to the truth.
And Travis Dobbs was killed because he
wouldn't stop promoting s miracle stream.
Your radiology department's the only place
in the area actively producing nuclear waste
of any kind on a daily basis.
Now, I know it's small amounts
but it's real nonetheless, so...
where do you store it?
We've been doing electrical
repairs ever since the storm.
Look, is this really necessary?
Only if you want to find out
if you've been irradied or not.
It's normal levels of
background radiation.
Still use this?
No, it's one of the original water heaters
from when the hospital was built in the '50s.
- It hasn't been used in years.
- By you.
That is a centrifuge tube.
And it's used to make
heavy water by electrolysis.
See, with the right
amount of, uh, current,
you can split regular water molecules
leaving nothing behind but heavy water.
Yeah. There's some radiation.
Nothing dangerous, but
more than there should be.
Well, whoever was here probably used
the thalium 201 from your hospital's, uh,
stress tests, add the neutrons,
to change it to thalium 202,
thereby increasing the gamma ray count.
- Gamma rays?
- Yeah.
Puts the "dirty" in dirty bomb.
The heavy water must've been
stored in here in this tank.
Yep.
When the basement flooded, the water
pressure must've cracked the fittings.
The heavy water would've flowed out.
Into the hospital drains, down in the
water table that runs below ground.
The amount of pressure changed,
and found its way into the spring.
And gave Nicky his miracle.
Yeah, I think they must've
built a dirty bomb here.
Explains residual radiation.
Then took it with them.
Who did you hire to do
the electrical repairs?
Just our regular people.
Our chief maintenance
man and his assistant.
What are their names?
Brandon Hurdle and Ben Adams.
I think the symptoms all your patients have been
suffering from are caused by heavy water poisoning.
You need to flush it out
of their systems right away.
Brandon Hurdle has a degree in physical
chemistry from Emory University,
as well as a record of
weapons and explosives charges.
A little bit overqualified to be a
hospital maintenance man, don't you think?
What about Adams?
He was separated from the service
during basic training two years ago
for refusing to take orders from
a non-white recruit squad leader.
This is all very hard to believe.
Timothy McVay's neighbor
said the same thing.
Hold on, guys.
Agent Young speaking.
Got it. Stay on the line, please.
Local cops hit both
their homes. Nothing.
Do you have any idea
where they might be?
Hurdle has a house up at Kramer Lake.
He uses it during hunting season.
Really think these guys
have a dirty bomb in there?
Positive.
And now we're going to get a look at it using
my Bluetooth and the camera on their computer.
We got barely 50 milligrams.
More than enough to turn
Billings into ground zero.
A few dozen milligrams of that, a stick
of dynamite: a hell of a lot of damage.
All rit, when the
suspects exit the cabin,
I will order them to lay
down what's in their hands.
If they comply immediately,
we will take them into custody.
If they do not, we will
put them down. Understood?
- Copy that.
- Keep your head down.
This is the FBI!
Drop what you're carrying or we'll sot.
You bastards!
Hood!
The dirty bomb has
got to be in the case.
Don't touch that! Don't touch that.
Don't touch that.
Central, we're going to need
an ambulance dispatched...
Hi, Lily.
How are you feeling?
Better. At least for now.
Now's good. Nicky?
I think Special Agent
Young has something for you.
She likes you.
What do you say, Nicky?
You think you can give her a good home?
- Can I, Dad?
- Yeah.
Here you go.
Hey, little one.
I spoke with the director.
He said to tell you "good call."
So, the big question is, do
you believe in miracles now?
Define "miracle."
Well, if that storm hadn't hit,
Nicky Harris would still have cancer and half
of Billings, Montana could have been irradiated.
Sounds like a miracle to me.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚