SeriesSub presents...
The world
will have to deal with us.
Previously on The 4400...
I took the shot.
I'm fine.
Mom, what's wrong?
Someone help, please!
Mom!
Isabelle's in Promise City.
As soon as she gets close
to Collier, she'll move.
She knows
not to damage him, right?
For a while there,
I believed you'd changed.
- So did I.
- We're not gonna make you
a martyr to your cause, Jordan,
we're going to make you
a traitor to it.
Once you're marked,
you'll single-handedly
destroy the movement
you created.
I don't know what lessons you
took in bodysnatching school, but...
you make
a terrible Tom Baldwin.
If we really want to kill
that thing inside him,
we're gonna have
to kill Tom, too.
- Don't make me shoot you.
- You going to fix me, Diana?
- Going to get your old Tom back?
- Goddamn it, Tom, stop!
Oh, my god, Tom?
He pulled a gun.
I had to fire.
- Where's Shawn?
- He's waiting in the car. I'll get him.
We can't do it here.
He's in bad shape.
We have to move him.
Uncle Tommy?
I need to heal him now.
He's losing blood too fast.
Not yet.
That's not Tom.
We need to get rid of that thing
inside of him first.
- Everybody out.
- Here's the polonium...
We need to inject it
directly into his spine.
I can't lie to you, Tom,
this is going to hurt.
But it's going to kill
that thing inside you.
We lost pulse.
Mom?
Is she dead?
Is my mom dead?
We don't know yet.
Sir, you need to let us work.
You can wait inside.
You did everything
you could.
I think you need to prepare yourself
for some bad news.
- Your mom's a textbook case.
- A textbook case of what?
- Promicin death.
- No...
She landed
on the wrong side of 50-50.
My mom didn't take the shot!
Are you okay?
Sir?
Are you okay? Help!
Wait... Sir!
Come on, uncle Tom.
Dammit!
I can't.
It's too late.
I think I killed people.
I think I killed people, Diana.
We can talk about that later.
Right now,
you need to rest.
Don't know what happened.
I was talking to the guy
and he collapsed.
Kind of like what
happened with my mom.
Mr. Farrell...
I need some information.
Do you know who your mother's
insurance carrier is?
No.
Ma'am?
Oh, my god, ma'am!
Somebody!
Are you okay?
Season 4 - Episode 13
The Great Leap Forward
[ Transcript ]
www.ragbear.com
[ Synchro ]
Benj!
aSpro5oo
[ www.seriessub.com ]
What happened?
I can barely
remember anything.
And the few things I do,
they're all...
They're all bad.
How am I supposed to live
with what I did?
How can I even be positive
that thing is gone?
Well, we're going to
watch over you until we're sure.
You're going to
recover yourself,
and when you do,
you'll tell us who the Marked are.
All of them.
And after that,
whatever you did...
We'll deal with it, okay?
Nobody's getting into
or out of St. Ambrose.
Seattle police have it
under strict quarantine
and we have tactical agents
reinforcing them.
No one knows exactly
what happened in there yet, but...
I did manage to get on the phone
with a doctor who's trapped inside,
and he has personally seen
dozens of deaths.
How is that possible? There's no way
all those people took the shot.
Maybe someone's going around
injecting patients, like...
an orderly or a doctor.
No, it'd take time to force the shot
on all those people.
- This is spreading way too fast.
- What if it's a virus?
You know,
someone took the shot,
and the ability they developed
is to spread promicin like...
I don't know, the flu.
- God...
- Well, if that's true,
we have more than just a bunch
of victims on our hands.
50-50. For everyone who died
in that hospital,
someone else survived, Someone
who'll develop a brand new ability.
How many people do you think
are trapped inside that hospital?
500?
1000?
Whatever the number,
we'll deal with it,
but at least there haven't been
any reports of deaths
outside the hospital.
Your brother danny's outside.
Tell him to come in.
I can't.
He's out in the gardens,
and he won't come inside.
It's a little strange,
to be honest.
He's not letting anybody
near him.
What's going on?
You're making everybody nervous.
Everyone's dying, Shawn.
- Everyone around me is dying.
- What are you talking about?
That hospital?
I killed all those people.
Danny, what do you mean?
How? What?
It's the shot.
My ability.
I think I'm infecting people
with promicin.
And I don't know
what to do.
I've been hiding out
all night in a park,
and I can't even turn myself in
without making more people sick.
Okay, you can't infect anyone
who's already promicin positive, right?
I don't think so.
So you're going to come inside.
I'm going to clear everyone else
out of the building.
Dr. Burkhoff can probably get his hands
on some of the inhibitor.
Come inside.
We're going to suppress your ability.
We'll figure this out together.
Okay?
Come on...
Mom's dead, Shawn.
What?
It happened last night.
It was my fault.
I killed her.
I'm sorry, Shawn.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt her.
I didn't mean to hurt anyone.
I wanted you to hear something
while you're still you.
When Kyle brought me to you,
I wasn't lying.
I really did want to change.
I tried,
but I'm not meant to lead
a normal life,
and it was stupid
to think I could.
Isabelle, everyone is in charge
of their own destiny.
You may not have liked
the choices you had.
Still, you made one.
I was created to do a job.
I fought it for a while, but...
now I know
I have to do what they want.
Kill me.
Kill me right now.
Don't let them use me
to end this movement.
You were told
not to speak to Collier.
Don't worry.
It won't happen again.
Because I'm ready
to get out of here.
You've got collier.
I did what you asked me to do.
Now you can let
my father go.
No.
Not yet.
Your father will be released
when everything's arranged
exactly as we want it.
That is not what we agreed to.
I don't really feel
like arguing about it.
I like having
my abilities back.
I'll go get
my father myself.
I don't think so, Isabelle.
I think you're forgetting.
We took out a little
insurance policy on you
while you were in prison.
You remember that kill switch
that Tom told you about?
You're feeling it right now.
If you insist on disobeying us,
I won't hesitate to use it...
Fully.
I wanna make a statement on behalf
of everyone who lives in Promise City.
We had nothing to do
with the deaths
at St. Ambrose hospital.
Forcing people to take promicin
goes against everything...
Jordan Collier stands for.
If Jordan were here,
he would tell you himself.
But, unfortunately,
he is missing.
He was abducted
by enemies of the movement.
We are working to find him,
but while we do,
we'd like to extend
a gesture of goodwill
to the city of Seattle.
The residents of Promise City...
are already promicin positive.
We're not vulnerable
to what's happening in the hospital.
We'd like to offer our services
to the authorities.
We will not move out into the city
without an invitation,
but we do stand ready
to help.
All the government
has to do is ask.
So, ready to hand over
control of the city to Collier's army?
We might need them
before this is over.
I'm not sure, Meghan.
I didn't even know Collier was missing
until just now.
Has Tom been able
to tell you anything?
Let me know if he starts to remember.
I'll call you if anything changes here.
Everything's gone silent
within St. Ambrose
and we just had word
that authorities
are considering sending in
the first relief team.
How would you like to have
that job, huh?
- How are things at the hospital?
- It's quiet.
Whatever happened in there,
I think it's over.
At least, the screaming has stopped.
Guys...
Look at this.
Authorities tell us that...
- What just happened there?
- I'm not sure.
We need to talk
to the agents on site, right now.
They told us
it was contained.
Everybody,
get away from her!
Get away from her.
We need to
seal this place off, now!
It's not fair.
I didn't even take the shot.
Ok! Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
I was five feet from him...
and I lived.
It doesn't seem right.
What's going to
happen to us now?
I mean, everyone
who survived...
are we going to
develop abilities?
You two okay?
What's going on out there?
We're picking up the pieces.
The worst is over,
for us, anyway.
Someone must have gotten out
of that hospital
and infected everyone
on the perimeter.
The sickness is spreading
through the neighborhood
near St. Ambrose.
And the police,
emergency services,
their people must have
brought the virus back
from the barricade, too.
They've been devastated.
So who's watching over the city?
Right now, no one.
The army has Seattle surrounded.
The entire district
is under quarantine.
How far is this thing
going to spread?
We don't know.
But right now,
I want to keep focused on this building.
Marco, we gave everyone promicin tests.
- Have the results come in yet?
- Yeah, um...
They're preliminary, but...
It looks like everyone
who survived is positive.
Except for one person.
You.
Me?
Why?
It's just a guess, but...
you know, last year, Dr. Burkhoff forced
an early version of promicin on you.
You didn't get an ability, but...
it looks like your body developed
a resistance to promicin exposure.
There's no chance
that I could infect anybody?
No.
I mean, I don't think so.
How do you feel?
Tired.
What did you give me?
I included a sedative in the sample of
the inhibitor I mixed up.
We won't know
if your ability's suppressed for...
a few hours.
I don't want to sleep.
I want to help.
There's nothing
you can do right now.
Just close your eyes, buddy.
Have you given any thought
to what you want to do?
I'm gonna give Danny to NTAC.
I think I have to.
I think so, too.
They have to study your brother.
He may be the only way
to find an antidote.
Once the government has him,
who knows
if they'll ever let him go.
I don't want to lose my brother
and my mom on the same day.
Jesus, my mom is gone...
The virus got into city hall.
The mayor's down,
half the city council,
police, paramedics.
People are abandoning
their posts in droves.
I think we need to take
Kyle Baldwin up on his offer,
see if his positives
can't restore some order.
Are you ready
to cross that line?
We don't have a choice.
The federal government
is focused on containment.
They're basically
writing Seattle off.
We can't let that happen.
I'm going to Promise City.
Well, you can't just
drive across town. Let me go.
I'm the one who's supposed to be
resistant to this thing.
That's why you're going
to the 4400 center.
You could be the key
to ending this.
If someone could figure out
why you're not vulnerable,
maybe they could replicate the effect
and create a vaccine.
Okay, well,
we're not doing it,
Because NTAC medical's
shut down.
Shawn farrell is not developing
that compatibility test on his own.
Someone is doing the research,
someone with a scientific background.
Someone like Kevin Burkhoff.
My sister's dead.
That was shawn.
Susan was in that hospital. She's dead.
Oh, my god, Tom.
I'm so sorry.
You should lie down.
I can't imagine
what you're feeling now.
No, no, I'll mourn later.
Where'd you put my gun?
I remember it all now.
Everything.
The marked have Jordan Collier.
I know where they're keeping him.
OK, tell us where he is,
and I'll put together a task force.
It has to be me. Isabelle's there.
She has her abilities back.
They think I'm one of them.
I'll walk in, I'll get Collier,
I can find out what they're planning
next. Let me do this, please.
I have to.
I've been authorized to accept
your offer of assistance.
What did you have in mind?
We need to restore order
to the streets.
I would like to use your people
as a temporary security force.
The first thing we need to do
is write a list of all the abilities
at your disposal.
Then we can figure out
how to deploy them.
Look, there's no reason to make a plan.
Jordan already has one in place.
I know exactly what we have
at our disposal,
and I know where to send them
to take control of the city.
I'm glad you're so prepared
to take over Seattle,
but when this is over,
I want my city back.
The whole world is terrified
of what's happening here.
That's an opportunity.
Once this is over,
we use all our influence,
here and abroad,
and push for all-out
war against the positives.
This time, we will be heard.
Yes.
Great.
Funny how things happen.
You've got Collier,
but you're losing Seattle.
You're wrong.
I'm not going to stand by
and watch a militia
of positives
take command of this city.
We thought the movement would
fall apart. Once we had Collier,
but that didn't happen.
Someone stepped in and took his place.
- You're talking about Kyle?
- That's right.
He has to be stopped.
You have to stop him.
You're going back
into Promise City
and you're going
to kill Kyle Baldwin.
Kyle's your only real connection
to your past, this idea of yourself
that you've been hanging onto.
Once he's gone, you'll let it go.
You want him dead.
I'm your weapon.
I get it.
You've been out of contact
for a long time.
- Where have you been?
- I was doing damage control.
Skouris has been telling people
I'm marked.
Do they believe her?
My boss doesn't.
Meghan Doyle cares about Tom Baldwin.
I brought her around.
Anyway, their hands are full.
The virus got into NTAC.
It killed Baldwin's sister, too.
I had to shed a few tears
just for appearance's sake.
This thing has gotten out of control.
Half of NTAC is developing
new abilities.
How are we responding?
Collier's been marked.
We're waiting for him to turn.
In the meantime,
I sent Isabelle to Promise City,
to deal with the new
leader of the movement,
Kyle Baldwin.
Good.
Your body produces
abnormal amounts
of an enzyme
called Ubiquinone.
It's a compound that
boosts the immune system,
and overproduction of it
made you resistant to promicin.
If we replicate that effect,
can we make a vaccine?
People are dying right now.
We don't have time
to mass-produce some enzyme
and get it to people.
We don't have to
mass-produce anything.
Ubiquinone is already
available as a supplement.
They sell it in pills in health
food stores, pharmacies.
If you take enough of them,
can you develop a resistance quickly?
I just checked in on your brother.
He doesn't look good.
We have to get word
out about these pills.
You go.
I'll start making phone calls.
The inhibitor is working.
You're no longer contagious,
but your body is still
producing promicin, and...
since it can no longer disperse it
into the air via your ability,
it's building up in your system.
I'm choking on the stuff.
It's all right, Danny,
we're going to figure it out.
So, what can we do to help him?
We could take him off the inhibitor.
Physically, he'd be fine.
But I'd be contagious again.
- Exactly.
- No way.
- That's not an option.
- Danny!
No, Shawn.
What happens
if I stay on the inhibitor?
You saying I'll die?
I'm getting you out of here.
That thing inside you.
There's a way to get rid of it.
How?
You can worry about that
once you're out of here.
No matter what happens to me,
don't stop
until you're through the front door.
My car's right outside.
If anything happens to me,
you need to call Kyle right away.
Parrish sent Isabelle after him.
If you're an NTAC agent again,
what happens once we're outta here?
You mean, am I going to arrest you?
I'd love to,
but that's not the plan.
As much as it hurts me to admit it,
this city needs you right now.
Are you ready?
You flinched when I told you
Isabelle was going after your son.
No one's ever managed
to get rid of a mark before.
You're going to have
to tell me how you did it.
Later.
All our teams are in place.
We already have Ravenna under control.
Beacon Hill's quiet, too.
Good, let's move some of
your people into Northgate.
See if we can stop the looting.
We can't start distributing
these Ubiquinone supplements
until the city is calm.
Hi, Kyle.
Close your eyes.
No.
If you're going to do
what I think you are,
you have to look me in the eye.
You couldn't kill me.
You're human.
There's so much of
the world that I never saw.
So much that's beautiful.
You have time.
You can see whatever you want.
We can.
You have a good heart, Kyle.
Goodbye.
These pills are the way that
we can stop anyone else from dying.
I'm proud to say
that the 4400 center
is working in conjunction
with the government
and residents of Promise City
to distribute this
over-the-counter product
to every neighborhood in Seattle.
If you haven't already been infected,
these will either save your life,
or they will keep you
from getting an ability.
The goverment is also working
with relief agencies
to air-lift supplies
of Ubiquinone into the city,
so there'll be enough for everyone.
People are wondering what
seattle is going to look like
when this is all over,
how many people...
will have lost their lives,
how a city with so many unwanted
new abilities Is going to function.
The truth is,
we don't have any answers,
but this city has survived a lot,
and it will survive this.
Thank you all for coming.
You risked a lot to get this message out
and do not forget
to take your pills.
Shawn... Thank you.
None of this is going to mean anything
unless that air-lift happens right away.
We're working on it.
I'm coordinating distribution
between the CDC, FEMA
and the Red Cross.
Look, I know that you're
dealing with a lot,
but you helped keep this contained,
and you were the right face
to put in front of the public.
Yeah, buddy, I'm right here.
It really hurts.
It hurts to breathe.
I'm going to fix that.
- Make you feel better for a little bit.
- No...
Don't.
You did that an hour ago.
Look at me.
Danny...
we're going to take
you off the inhibitor,
and we're going to put you
in isolation...
- It's too dangerous.
- Not anymore.
We know about those pills now.
What if they don't work around me?
Or what if in a week from now,
my ability gets stronger?
The whole thing could start again.
Too many people are
dead because of me, Shawn.
It's not your fault.
I know, but I have to live with it.
I'm not going to make
it through this, Shawn.
I know it.
You're not going to die, Danny.
- I'm not going to let you.
- It's okay.
But I need you
to do something for me.
Just make it stop hurting.
Just make the pain go away
for good, okay?
Oh, Danny, no,
I'm not going to do that.
You're my little brother.
Then I'm begging you, brother.
- Don't.
- Please, Shawn.
Let me be the last victim.
Please do it.
Please...
Please, Shawn, I beg you.
Please, shawn, do it.
I love you.
Please! I can't breathe.
You made your choice.
You were our only hope
for the future!
Your future's dead now.
You're free now.
Make this world
better than it is.
You understand what you have to do
to get rid of that thing inside you?
You'll have to mend fences
with Shawn.
Well, I'm more than willing.
I hope he will be, too.
Jordan...
there's one more thing.
There's seven names there.
The rest of the marked.
They're going to need
the same treatment you get.
These are powerful people.
That's why NTAC can't handle it.
We'd never be able to get
them through official channels.
I can't help but wonder
when we walk back into the city,
who's going to be in charge,
my side or yours?
I think, soon...
that distinction
won't mean a thing.
Be well, Tom.
We are gathered here
today to pay our respects
to Susan and Danny Farrell,
a wonderful mother
and a loving son.
They will be missed,
as will so many others.
The entire city is
grief-stricken today.
We're all asking ourselves
the same question...
Are we going to deal with
all this lost, all this pain?
But I believe that in that question,
relies our answer to salvation.
Because it is a shared lost,
it is a shared pain,
that only together,
with your sympathy,
with your understanding,
with your love,
we could realize all this tragedy.
Shawn, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, man.
Thank you.
- Hey, dad.
- Hey.
Jordan told me everything
that happened.
You okay?
Yeah, I'll get there...
And I know you cared about Isabelle.
I'm sorry she's gone.
I know how you're feeling
right now, Shawn.
You're thinking that everyone's gone,
that you're alone.
But you're not.
I'm here.
So's Kyle,
And we're going to help
each other get through this.
We're going to figure out
how to be a family, okay?
I just got a revised
estimate of the tally so far.
We know the city's
lost 9,000 people.
That's just confirmed dead.
It's not a final count.
So we're looking at 9,000
new abilities at the very least.
A lot of those abilities are gonna
belong to people we know.
NTAC, police, paramedics.
I mean, we were the first
ones exposed to this thing.
What are we gonna do,
arrest ourselves?
No one's arresting anybody right now.
Every city agency's
operating on a skeleton crew,
and we won't have federal
help until they lift the quarantine.
That'll be a week, maybe more.
So we're still on our own.
The loudest voice
of authority in Seattle
right now is Jordan Collier's.
Well, his p-positives are the most
effective law and order we've got.
And when quarantine's lifted,
what happens?
Are Collier's people gonna stand down?
Will they give the city back to us?
Would you?
The time has come...
for this city to begin healing.
I never intended...
promicin to spread this way,
but the sacrifices
of the past few days
have not been in vain!
This tragedy,
terrible as it may have been,
had meaning,
and those who died...
are the heralds of a new age!
Thousands upon thousands
of you have new abilities,
and in time, you will all
contribute to this movement,
a movement...
that now claims all Seattle
as its home!
Who are you?
I'm Jed Garrity.
Who the hell are you?
We stood by the city...
in its hour of need,
and we will now guide
this city into the future.
We're all miracles.
Every one of us,
and together,
we will do wondrous things.
See?
I told you he was a good guy.
Maia, can't you see
what's happening?
Jordan Collier is naming himself
dictator of Seattle.
There's nothing good about that.
You're wrong, mom.
We're in charge now.
It's better that way.
I've spoken to the world before...
of heaven on Earth.
Many of you thought it impossible,
But now,
I'm convinced...
we will see it in our lifetimes!
There's a way to live with it.
You killed people.
Even though it wasn't really you,
you still feel responsible.
Believe me, I have been there.
2 people are dead. They're not Collier.
They're not coming back.
But you're still here.
You have to figure out
how to move on.
How?
Dad, it's time.
[ www.seriessub.com ]
v1.01