SeriesSub presents...
The world will have to
deal with us.
Previously on The 4400...
Jordan, you've done
great things for the 4400,
but you are on
the wrong path here.
And you've always
been rebellious.
But I think
you're afraid of change, Shawn.
Or is it just me?
I'm shrinking.
What did you do to me?
I met Cora.
She has an amazing ability.
She can actually
make people younger.
- Isabelle?
- Daddy!
If your mother were here,
she'd want us to do this.
She'd want us to be
a family again.
When your wife fainted
this morning,
she was a young woman.
When she woke up
less than a minute later,
she was 50 years older?
Richard, I'm dying.
There's a faction of elites
who want the future
to stay exactly as it is.
I call them "The Marked."
When we need him...
he'll be there for us.
Mr. Tyler,
can you hear my voice?
He's been under
for almost 20 minutes.
We should have begun
the procedure already.
Where have you been?
Who are you?
We have to work fast.
This is our only chance.
I've practiced enough...
with plenty of time.
Tonight, Richard Tyler
becomes a father.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just had a... weird dream.
You wanna talk about it?
No, I'm okay.
You should go back to bed.
I'll be right there.
Ready, you're ready ?
Daddy loves you.
It's nice to see you happy,
sweetheart.
Daddy's been wanting that
for long time.
Who are you?
Who am I?
I'm Lily... your wife.
Who else would I be?
Season 4 - Episode 10
One Of Us
[ Transcript ]
www.ragbear.com
[ Synchro ]
Benj!
aSpro5oo
[ www.seriessub.com ]
You're not lily.
Lily is dead.
- Dead?
- You got old. You passed on.
No, you're wrong.
I'm...
I'm right here.
I didn't die.
Where have you been?
How did you get here?
Well, I woke up
about an hour ago. I...
I wasn't sure where I was.
Not exactly, but...
Somehow knew
you'd be home soon,
and you'd have Isabelle.
That's the last thing I remember.
I was...
I was looking for her at the Center,
and she wasn't in her crib.
You look different, Richard.
You look sad.
- You are not real.
- You keep saying that, but I feel real.
I mean I remember
everything about my life,
about us.
I can pick things up.
I can touch things.
You.
You can feel that, right?
I can't explain
where I've been, Richard,
or how I got here, but...
I'm not questioning it, either.
I'm here.
Isn't that enough?
Can I ask you
a question?
Sure.
You're left-handed.
Of course.
- Is there a question coming?
- You already answered it.
I've been studying the reports
on who survives the promicin shot,
and who doesn't.
Did you know
nine out of ten
left-handed people
who take the shot,
survive?
- No, I didn't.
- Well, it's true.
I learned that a couple weeks ago,
but I didn't know...
what it meant...
until now.
There.
There's a small part of the brain
called the corpus callosum.
It's like a bundle of wires
that connects the two hemispheres.
It's usually slightly larger
in lefties than it is in righties.
That's why the lefties survive.
The size of that part of the brain
helps determine whether or not
you'll be able to integrate
a new neurotransmitter.
Well, how big
does it have to be?
I don't know... yet.
But I think I can figure it out.
And if I do...
A simple cat scan will tell me
how anyone's body
will react to the shot.
And you'd know in advance
whether or not you'd live or die.
The shot wouldn't have to
kill anyone anymore.
How long do you need?
A couple of months,
maybe less.
This is huge.
Keep working.
I'll get you anything you need, okay?
- Where are you going?
- I gotta get in contact with Collier.
If this test is really
only a few months away,
all he has to do
is make an announcement,
telling people that are
thinking about taking the shot
to simply wait.
This is great.
Hey, Tom.
What are you doing standing
in the middle of the hallway?
Is everything all right?
Yeah, I'm... fine.
I've just...
had a strange morning.
Well, join the club.
We've just had a surprise visit
from Rebecca Parrish.
Some might say an ambush.
The director of national
intelligence is here?
She's been in Meghan's office
the past 20 minutes, and that's not all.
She's asked to see us.
I don't think she likes to wait.
Morning, agent Baldwin,
agent Skouris.
I'm Rebecca Parrish,
and it is a pleasure to meet you.
The pleasure's all ours.
I know that you have difficult jobs
here at NTAC.
But lately,
it seems that we've had
nothing but bad news
coming out of Seattle.
Promicin use is growing.
The founding of Promise City
was a major defeat for this agency,
and in the administration.
It's temporary.
We'll arrest...
Collier,
and we'll shut that place down.
I like your attitude,
but you'll forgive me
if I'm not reassured.
Because recently,
it seems like we're...
even botching the little things.
We had Richard Tyler and his daughter
surrounded, outnumbered.
The situation was in hand,
and we lost him anyway.
Well, with all
due respect,
I was there, and that situation
was anything but "in hand."
Richard Tyler has become
an extremely powerful man.
I understand,
but we can't simply just
throw our hands up,
now, can we?
In two weeks,
I'm being asked to testify
before a congressional subcommittee
on the progress of the war
against promicin.
I'll be here for the entire week
to prepare,
and I would like to go back
with a victory.
So, you want us
to bring in Richard.
Ms. Parrish asked to meet
my two best agents.
That's why you're here.
That's also why you're heading up
a task force to find the Tylers.
I will be checking in
on your progress.
I trust this won't be a problem.
Agent Baldwin?
Did you have something
you needed to say?
I'm...
sure Tom just wants
to get to work.
We'll find the Tylers for you.
I don't know
what's happening, Diana.
It's like I'm seeing myself
in the future, only it's not me.
I'm doing things
I would never do.
What if
they're not just dreams?
they're someone else's memories?
What if they really did put something
inside me when I was in that hospital?
What if it's starting
to affect me?
I'm becoming
one of the marked.
Listen,
Even if you're right,
it hasn't happened yet.
You're still you.
- Okay, so we can fight it.
- How?
Well, have you been to see a doctor
since these dreams began?
- No.
- Okay, well, why don't you start there?
Go find yourself a private physician,
get yourself checked out.
We're supposed to be
looking for Richard.
Just go.
Go.
I'll cover for you.
Okay.
She looks so much older.
How long
have I been gone?
A little while.
More than a year.
Tell me what happened.
I want to hear it all.
Why do you look so sad?
I buried you, Lily.
I mourned you.
I never imagined
I'd be sitting beside you again,
and I don't wanna waste
the time we have with explanations.
We have all the time
in the world, though.
Why wouldn't we?
You still don't believe
I'm real, do you?
I don't know.
If I let myself believe it,
and I turn out to be wrong...
I'm not sure
I could live with that.
Let's just see, okay?
We'll just lay here
for a while...
and if I'm still beside you
when we wake up...
I guess we're real.
- You saved these pictures of us.
- Of course I did.
Who's this?
She's a friend of mine.
She lived at the 4400 Center
after you were gone.
She's pretty.
She looks nice, too.
I can see why
you saved the picture.
I don't know.
There's nothing different
about me, Diana.
I had every test
they could give me.
They all say
I'm in perfect health.
I'll call you back.
- What's going on?
- Sorry for the intrusion.
My security detail
is nothing if not thorough.
They have to be.
The administration has enemies
- everywhere these days.
- What are you doing here, Ms. Parrish?
I wanted to have
a word with you in private.
Gentlemen...
Gentlemen, agent Baldwin and I
need the room.
Thank you.
Damn it, this is my house...
I'm going to pay you
the respect of being frank.
I was a little concerned
with your...
outburst in Ms. Doyle's office
this morning.
Are you quite sure you're up to the job
of tracking down Richard Tyler?
- I'm fine.
- That's good to hear.
This might surprise you,
but I think I have an idea
of what you're going through.
Right after I took this job,
I felt like I was on the verge
of a breakdown myself.
I was overwhelmed at work,
and I was...
having these strange moments
where I was seeing things.
It was almost like
I wasn't myself.
Like... someone else
was in my head.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
I think I do.
Let me ask you something,
Ms. Parrish.
If I look behind your left ear,
would I find a mark there?
A mark?
You mean like a mole?
That's hard to say.
Once you turn 40,
your skin changes all the time.
I remember how nervous I was
in those days.
I thought I was going to
lose myself forever.
I fought it.
My God, how I fought it.
And then one day,
I just couldn't fight it
anymore.
I gave in.
I accepted my situation.
And you know what?
Things have been
much better for me since then.
I'm happier.
My friends tell me
that I'm like a new person.
You should relax, Tom.
Whatever you're going through,
just...
let it happen.
You'll feel better.
I promise.
You're saying Rebecca Parrish
is one of these people?
- She's marked?
- Yeah, I think so.
She never came out
and said it.
But you haven't had
any more hallucinations,
so, maybe she was talking
about something else.
What do you think?
I think it's crazy,
and I doubt we'll be able
to prove any of this, but...
I have to go with Tom.
I think that there's a very good chance
the director of national
intelligence is marked.
We're going to have to be very careful
with how we proceed.
NTAC would be looking for
Richard Tyler no matter what,
so we'll keep doing that.
I'm passing the case over
to Garrity and Ashmore.
Tom, you're taking
a personal day tomorrow.
Diana and I
will keep an eye on you.
We'll watch over you
in shifts.
I'm sorry, Shawn,
are you really asking me
to tell people
not to take promicin?
Only for a few months.
Jordan, I know that
we have had our differences in the past,
but this is good for both of us.
All we have to do is be patient.
It's not the need for patience
that concerns me.
It's the worldwide implications
of this test.
Shawn, there would be millions of people
with abilities
and millions without any chance
of having them.
Yes, but they would be alive.
And living in a world
with two classes of human being.
Positives and negatives
cannot live side by side.
Those without abilities
will tear down the ones who have them.
Or, the positives will simply
use their powers
to rid themselves
of the negatives.
Inquisition, or holocaust.
Either way, it's a recipe
for hell on earth.
What's your alternative?
Do you really want
- the entire world to take promicin?
- Yes.
Yes, I do. It's what I've always said
has to happen.
Half of the planet will die!
- You're talking about mass suicide!
- I am talking...
about a single generation
of sacrifice.
And at the end of it,
a more fully-evolved species.
All of our failings
as human beings
will be addressed
when we are all gifted.
I am not making
any announcement.
And no one who cares about
what's right for the world would.
Somebody got so big!
Oh, she got heavy, too.
Yeah.
- Just one, just one.
- I'm going to go play.
All right, go play.
She seems so happy.
Aren't toddlers
supposed to be moody?
Oh, Isabelle's had her moments,
believe me.
Oh, I'm sure she has.
Ever since I got back,
I've been...
thinking about what it must
have been like for you,
raising her on your own.
You know, neither of
us asked to be parents,
not that it makes it any less
wonderful, but still...
It just kind of happened.
But you've always been
there for her,
even while I was gone.
You're a great father, Richard.
You can tell
just by looking at her.
I'm definitely using my ability
on Richard Tyler.
He's seeing his dead wife,
but I have no idea
if they're talking about
what he did to his daughter.
I just make him see her.
Everything they talk
about comes from him.
Allright, keep at it.
We don't have any other
options at this point.
I don't know how much
longer I can do this.
Look, I know you're tired,
but this is very important.
I won't forget
what you did for me.
- Can I get a coffee or something?
- Absolutely.
Absolutely.
It's working.
We just need more time.
If you know where Isabelle is,
just tell me. I can help her myself.
Didn't really work out so well
the last time you tried it, did it?
It's too soon for that.
Richard's not ready to give her up yet.
This is just the first
part of a plan to get her back.
When we're ready for the next part,
I'll let you know.
Or you can tell me now.
Did you know he was involved
with her grandmother?
Why do you think
we picked these two?
After we send them back
to their time,
they'll find each other.
They'll form a bond.
It's done.
She's pregnant.
Honey...
Honey, Meghan.
Honey, wake up.
I had the dream again.
Of course you did, Tom.
You're becoming your new self.
You're one of us now.
Welcome aboard.
Did you have another dream?
No, I slept like a baby, actually.
I feel great.
Forgot how much I hate it here.
There's so much noise
in this time period.
So many people.
Look at them.
They have no idea what's coming.
They just move from pointless
errand to pointless errand.
It's disgusting.
I'd think you'd be
glad just to be alive.
You were given a chance
to continue your work.
The work that failed so badly?
The work that got
my previous host killed?
Don't blame your shortcomings
on Matthew Ross.
We are our hosts.
Your inability to harness
Isabelle Tyler was your failure.
I'll do better this time.
You need to get back to work.
Convince them to return
you to active duty.
I'll pull some strings if I have to,
but it's better if you
got it done on your own.
- And after I'm  there?
- That's the easy part.
Do what Tom Baldwin would do.
Find Isabelle Tyler.
I'll be in touch.
Richard, come play.
I can't.
Lily, I have to tell you something.
What is it, sweetheart?
I lied to you.
That picture you saw.
The pretty girl.
That was Isabelle.
My god, Richard. I had no idea
things had gotten so bad.
I don't expect you to forgive me,
but I need you to understand.
I did it for our daughter.
Why didn't you tell
me the truth right away?
I've been happy,
being with you the last few days.
You don't know how long it's been
since I've felt that way.
A good father will
do anything for his child,
and you're a good father.
But, Richard,
you took away her life.
The good and the bad.
You erased everything she was,
everything she could have been.
I knew I was wrong
after I did it to her, but...
Other people told me as much,
but I didn't listen.
I guess the only person
I could listen to was you.
Daddy...
I feel real.
We're talking.
- I've held Isabelle.
- No, you haven't.
My ability makes it seem
like you have.
I don't know if I'm  seeing you
because I want to,
or if someone conjured you up for me.
I don't know, Richard.
I don't know how I got here,
but maybe it doesn't matter.
I don't think I'm going
to be here much longer.
But if I have to go,
will you just hold me?
I love you, Richard.
I'm not saying we don't have to worry,
but nothing happened last night,
and this morning, Tom said he felt fine.
He said he didn't
want me to come over,
but where is he?
Because Tom is always
here at the crack of dawn.
Hey, what's up with Tom?
He just dragged Marco
out of his office.
I think Baldwin's
gone nuts or something.
Your mind is no match
for the power of my mind.
You are now under my control.
My mind is no match
for the power of your mind.
I am now under your control.
Total control.
You should see their faces.
Sorry, Di, we were just trying
to ease the tension a little bit,
- that's all.
- You idiots!
Marco, you're fired.
You too, Garrity.
- Come on, that was classic!
- You can't fire this.
Go back to your office
and solve something.
- Hey, come on...
- Quick.
I'm sorry.
Good work.
No humor.
No humor in this room.
What?
Ah, you know what?
Seriously, look,
I'd like to thank you both
for helping me get through
these past few days,
but I had a great night's sleep.
I feel...
better, and, look
I really hope this is all over.
If I have any more flashes,
I'll tell you right away,
but in the meantime,
I'd really like to get back to work.
What about Rebecca Parrish?
I think we need to keep an eye on her.
Her visit to my place was...
definitely weird.
but maybe you were right.
Maybe the whole thing
was her bizarre version
of a pep talk.
Look, whatever it is,
I don't have to trust her
to do my job.
And I really want to do my job.
All right,
but I'll be watching you, okay?
Any more attempts at mind control
Baldwin, and you're out.
That wasn't funny.
I have a very simple message
for anyone who's thinking
about taking the shot.
Wait.
In a few months, the research
that I'm funding will be complete
and 50-50 will be a thing of the past.
We will have a very simple test
that can tell you whether
or not you'll survive the shot,
and no one ever has to risk dying again.
What about Jordan Collier?
Is he in favor of this?
You'd have to ask him that, Paul,
but we're talking about preventing
thousands of needless deaths here.
I don't see how anyone
could think that's a bad thing.
You did this to your own child.
I'm disappointed in you, Richard.
You told me you wanted
to use that water I gave you
to help an old army buddy.
I know it was wrong.
But you never would
have gave me what I needed
- if you knew what I had in mind.
- Oh, you're right about that.
These abilities we have,
they are a gift from god,
and we need to treat them
with respect.
I know that,
and that's why I'm here.
I'm hoping you can set things right.
Cora, please.
I need your help.
I'll see what I can do.
Byron, you gotta wake up.
Byron...
Isabelle needs you.
- Come on...
- Let him sleep.
He did what he needed to do.
Does that mean Isabelle's okay?
Not exactly,
but we're getting close.
I need you to call your father.
Call my father? Why?
You're going to have
to tell him where Isabelle is.
You want me to betray
her to the government?
If you know where she is, tell me.
- I'll go there myself.
- This is how it has to be.
I promise you, Kyle,
if you do exactly what I say,
Isabelle will not wind up in jail.
Think of everything we've done, Kyle.
All that we've accomplished together.
Are you really going
to start doubting me now?
Did it work?
Daddy...
Are you going out?
We had a tip on the Tyler case.
Someone called in from Promise City,
gave us the name
and address of a 4400
that Richard claimed
he'd been in contact with.
It was anonymous,
probably nothing.
You had the appointment
at Maia's school.
I figured I'd run it
down while you were out.
I'm back, so I'll go with you.
I'll just get my jacket.
Okay, great.
Did you see that?
The curtain just moved.
Well, so someone knows we're here.
That tip of yours said this lady's
just an associate of Tyler's, right?
Yeah, but we'd better play it safe.
Knock on the door.
I'm gonna head around back,
make sure no one
tries to flee the scene.
Richard, a car just pulled up outside.
Some people are coming.
Isabelle,
get down to the basement.
If you hear any kind of struggle,
run out the back, understand?
Answer the door if they knock.
See if you can get rid of them.
Cora Tomkins?
Hi. I'm Diana Skouris.
I'm from NTAC.
I'd like to ask you a few questions
about Richard Tyler.
Richard Tyler?
I haven't seen him since quarantine.
Do you mind if I come in?
So Richard hasn't tried
to get in touch with you at all?
No phone calls? No emails?
No, but I keep
pretty much to myself.
Right.
Oh, I'm  sorry. I didn't realize
I was interrupting something.
- You have company.
- No, no.
Pardon my mess.
I'm not too good about
cleaning up after myself.
Like I say,
I knew the man in quarantine,
but I don't really keep in touch
with many of the 4400s.
- You people just don't quit.
- Don't move.
Are you okay?
What have you done to them?
Honey...
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
I'm sorry. I went around back,
and Isabelle was already
halfway down the alley
when I got out there.
I was going to chase her,
but I came back when
I heard the gunshot.
Where is she now?
I don't know, Diana,
she got away.
Good job, guys.
Today, agent Baldwin
and agent Skouris
provided a textbook example
of what we need to win this fight.
Initiative, savvy,
and exceptional teamwork.
The apprehension of Richard Tyler
is a huge win for us,
a reminder to everyone
that the rule of law still prevails
in this country.
Make no mistake,
there's lots more to be done,
but today....
Today we won.
Nice speech.
Yeah, exactly what Parrish
would say if she were marked.
Then again, it's exactly what Parrish
would say if she wasn't marked.
I know, either way,
she won today.
Nice work, you guys.
I gotta go make nice.
Hey, you...
- You gonna be okay?
- Yeah.
Sure?
We really got lucky today,
just finding Richard in that house.
It's a good thing you got that tip.
Yeah, well, it has to work
out for us sometimes, doesn't it?
This is not how this
was supposed to end!
Richard is in prison!
It's all over the news!
Isabelle's on the run.
Government's looking for her.
You said that she'd be okay.
You lied to me!
I promised you she
wouldn't end up in jail.
- She's not in jail.
- Yeah, and she's not safe, either.
- This is not what I wanted...
- This isn't about what you want, Kyle!
It's about what has to happen!
I'm not your sidekick.
I'm not here to run errands for you.
I'm here to tell you
what the movement needs,
and right now,
it needs for you to be strong,
because the next thing you have to do,
trust me,
it's not gonna be easy for you.
- What are you talking about?
- Your cousin Shawn?
The work he's doing
with that scientist
is threatening the entire movement.
Collier knows about it,
but he's too afraid
to get his hands dirty.
He shouldn't have
That's what he has people like you for.
People like me?
What do you want me to do?
Shawn Farrell has to be stopped.
Don't worry. You're safe.
- Where am I?
- You're at my house.
I gave you a tranquilizer,
then I brought you here.
- Where's my father?
- We put him on the inhibitor.
He's in prison.
He's gonna be there
for a very long time.
He didn't do anything wrong.
He was just trying to help me.
Isabelle, it's okay. It's okay.
There's a way to get him out.
I know people
who could make it happen.
It would be easy.
There's just one thing.
You...
have to take your abilities back.
Then, you can bring
Jordan Collier to me.
[ www.seriessub.com ]
v1.00