so every time i asked you "how's
work?" and you said "fine,"
you were having your own
private little joke on me?
what's going on?
i went to blockbuster today
to rent "cinderella man"
- and guess what?
- is it still a classic?
i found out
that our son-- the liar--
had been fired
three weeks ago.
from blockbuster?
how the fuck do you do that?
they got rhesus monkeys
working as managers over there.
he was taking promotional items and
selling them-- posters, standups.
standees! this whole thing's bullshit.
most of that stuff gets
thrown out anyway.
the store's policy
was very clear.
well maybe i care
about the environment.
did that ever occur to you?
"wallace and gromit,"
i mean that weighed like 50 lbs. how
many trees gave their lives for that?
- it just goes to the dump.
- can i come home to a peaceful house one goddamn night?
you tell me to think like a businessman,
yet every time i do there's something wrong.
i made money promoting parties
in high school, that was no good.
- now this.
- you know what i think? all those days you go in late,
you call in sick,
you deserve to get canned.
the worst part is you
don't even give a shit.
what, i should care about blockbuster?
fucking religious fanatics!
- i can't live on what they pay me anyway.
- why not?!
you live at home!
we feed you!
you have a social life
but i can't?
you have any idea what it costs
at a decent club in new york?
it's $500 for a bottle of cristal,
and it's a two-bottle minimum.
you spend $1,000 a night on champagne?
no, not every night.
all right, barely ever.
and hernan, everybody--
we take turns
picking up the tab.
hernan. or the girl he crippled
when he flipped over the car?
is she there, drinking champagne
with you... in her wheelchair?
it wasn't his fault.
her parents are going for a big payday
because his dad was in "forbes" magazine.
oh god almighty!
if it makes you feel any better i've been
looking for a new job-- every day online!
oh jesus!
you can't even talk to her.
are you fucking kidding me?
you should be kissing her feet.
because when you were growing
up, if it wasn't for her,
i would have knocked all your
baby teeth out with one shot.
i can't sleep.
- a.j.
- somebody call?
it's not only that he's a
complete stranger to the truth,
he's got this dead streak in
him. it chills me to the bone.
he's fuckin' spoiled, that's
all. we gave him too much.
come on, he went to school
with lots of privileged kids.
most of them are off in ivy league
universities now, doing very well.
no, this is something in him. deep down
it's like this big "fuck you" to everything.
i don't know
what that's about.
remember that whole god-is-dead
business on the day of his confirmation?
- maybe he'll surprise us.
- aren't you the sunny optimist when you want to go to sleep?
- i saw the light was on. can i come in?
- sure, hon.
i'm going to california.
i don't know for how long.
- california? what are you talking about?
- finn took that year off.
and it was great when dad
was hurt-- he was here for me.
but now he's going back to dental
school, i want to be with him.
i thought you two
were having problems.
i never said that.
i don't know if i want to go
to law school or med school.
those are nice
options to have.
that's what we call
a high-class problem.
his dad said
that he can get me
a lab job at ucla where
he teaches oral surgery.
i mean if i decide
on med school
that will look really great
on my application.
what you're really saying is you're
following this man to california.
meadow, you drop this bomb
on us at 1:30 in the morning--
forgive us if we need
some time to adjust.
- i have to make plane reservations--
- you'll be back for christmas?
i don't know.
no pressure please, okay?
tidelands project--
your slice of no-shows--
i spoke to the union and we
can't make five work no more.
rollbacks, not to mention
my end's way down.
now more than ever i got
captains looking to me
to deliver them
those no-show jobs
- on account of the medical insurance.
- health care costs these days.
bitch all you want
about john, he understood
that ours is a
mutually-beneficial arrangement.
john's folding laundry
in fucking danbury.
it's on my shoulders
to take care of the family,
even if he's boss just in name.
now i made a decision,
and, with all due respect,
it's final.
you see, this is what i get. i never
should have let you slide on the vitamins.
again with the vitamins.
you told me there were 1500
cases of centrum on that truck.
when your nephew delivered it, there were
cartons ripped open, pills all over the floor.
anybody got shorted, it was
yours truly, but you know what--
all right, all right, all right,
put it back in your pocket.
but i gotta get some relief
on this other situation.
for the supreme commander's
control over the sworn enemy's
capital city is the epitome
of their power in europe.
i need to talk to you. remember i
told you about that trip to paris?
i won it at the silent
auction at the feast.
well, the date is here and
i think i would like to go.
you don't remember the first
goddamn thing about this, do you?
we stood right here talking
about it for 15 mites.
- i know, you won a trip to paris.
- why do you have to lie?
i'm not! you're always saying i'm lying.
- why paris?
- it is one of the great cities of the world.
but the frogs hate us.
- go to italy.
- they weren't auctioning a trip to italy.
it's actually a good deal.
it's a week for two for $5,000.
how's the euro doing?
i don't know, tony.
i had three years
of high-school french.
- i can't get away for a week, carm.
- i could go with ro.
we've been talking about taking
a trip together for years--
ever since our rome thing
went belly up.
oh yeah... when anthony walked
through the plate-glass door.
i could really use a
vacation now-- meadow leaving,
my spec house-- the thought of
tearing it down and starting over,
- it makes me nauseous.
- yeah.
plus him. i just don't
know what to do anymore.
you know what?
you should go.
you deserve it.
it'd be good for you too.
do whatever it is
that boys do when
they're on their own.
whatever.
i said go.
i'll be fine.
i'm so excited.
i'm gonna call ro.
oh, hey hey!
look.
tony. hey.
what the fuck?
my brother's over there.
- what's that supposed to mean?
- nothing. he's just there, that's all.
you sandbag me, i cut
your fucking throat open.
i'm sorry. i didn't
know what else to do.
i want back in.
- can i sit?
- no, you can't sit.
it was complicated.
i was working things out.
i'm sure it gets complicated when
you're taking it up your fag ass.
i'm not a fag.
i never was.
- excuse me?
- it was the medication i was on.
for my blood pressure.
it fucked with my head,
but i'm over that now.
i can probably get
a letter from my doctor.
a note from your doctor saying
you don't like to suck cock?
first off,
i pay my way back in.
i got 200k that goes
directly to you personally.
no one else
needs to know.
long term, i know
construction's out.
those guys--
but meth, running girls,
a lot more
tolerant atmosphere.
i got contacts in a.c.
with your support
i could set myself up there.
i'd be close
but not too close.
ton'!
please, don't turn
your back on me.
he was fucking
stalking you, t.
that's the thing
with the gays.
it's the living in the
closet, makes them devious.
speaking of crystal meth,
look at this walyo.
say what you will about
richie aprile,
but when he found out
his son was gay,
he did the right thing.
he disowned him.
i got an a.a. meeting.
alcoholics-fucking-anonymous
now too...
salvatore lucania must be
looking down on all of us
- with great pride.
- there's gonna be a lot of popular sentiment
to get rid of vito.
phil alone--
fuck phil!
you know what that's about? he's
gotta polish his rep as a tough prick
so he can make boss.
vito in atlantic city...
he's out there.
he's not part of us.
and we get, you know, a trickle
of cash coming in each month.
- you ready?
- oh, there's so much going on here,
just the thought of flying,
the heightened security...
come on.
i got something for you,
for your trip.
now this is the real
louis "vitoon."
you had a rough year--
me in the hospital,
you there
around the clock--
i want you
to enjoy yourself.
hmm?
when you were in that coma,
i told you i loved you.
- do you remember?
- no.
- i should tell you more often.
- well...
nobody's stopping ya.
okay, listen up, kids.
francesca, look at me.
you can't tell anyone,
even your friends at school,
that daddy's home
- for a little while.
- are you gonna have to go back to afghanistan?
the cia doesn't tell you
where they'll send you next.
is it dangerous
to be a spy?
not as long as nobody
knows who you are.
i'm what they call
"working deep cover."
that's why,
like i said,
- you gotta keep the secret.
- i won't tell.
- you better not!
- i won't!
i love you guys.
how long till you can
move back in with us?
just until i straighten
this shit out with tony.
it's looking good.
in a few days i'll know.
what about counseling
for your problem?
- have you talked to father macken?
- marie,
i thought i made it clear--
i don't have a problem.
that's over with.
in fact,
i'm seriously thinking
we should have another kid.
yo, dad, check it!
attaboy, v!
hello?
hi.
fuck you.
- i know, look--
- not a word, not a note.
- what kind of person are you?
- i'm sorry.
you ed help.
you're seriously fucked up.
i got kids.
i couldn't live without 'em.
bullshit.
it was the fucking life
you couldn't live without--
the gambling, the money,
who knows what else.
you're right. i didn't want to
drag you down into this pit i'm in.
hey, fuck that! everybody else
is stupid to you, aren't they?
- no.
- you can throw your weight around down there
in fucking jersey.
everybody kisses your ass.
- i miss you.
- i don't want to know you.
i don't want to hear your
voice. don't ever call me again.
do your bowels just
jam up when you fly?
hey-yyy!
hopalong che-se-dic'.
what do you know?
what do you say?
- how you been?
- word is you reached out to tony.
i appreciate you coming out
to see me. how you doin'?
nicole is choking my balls
with this child support.
i could be looking at
six months in county.
- oof!
- i was wondering if you could float me 20k at two points,
but maybe now is not
a good time for you.
no. no,
i could do that.
but i'm gonna have to say
two and a half.
okay. you know
i'm good for it.
would you stop?
heard on 1010-wins
the tunnel's a parking lot.
i hope you didn't
get caught in that.
you said you were gonna take
care of that fucking finook.
oh, for christ's sake. fucking vito
again? what the fuck is wrong with you?
he's in town, isn't he? i was
at marie's the other night.
she played the innocent, but
i could tell she'd seen him.
you're fucking carnac
the great now too, huh?
i gotta tell you, anthony,
if vito was here
- and you knew about it...
- fuck this.
i love they let you
smoke here.
i think i should have slept in a
while before hitting the stores.
i told you.
- is your stomach still upset?
- i put in the fucking memory stick.
i love that sound--
french.
it's so elegant.
isn't it?
nobody fucking knows us here,
ro. can you believe that?
all the guidebooks say you should
try and get on the local schedule.
- did you reset your watch?
- yes, napoleon. jesus.
eloise and abelard,
my god!
what?
i would say today the first
cultural stop should be the louvre.
again, remy!
- how do you say "please"?
- s'il vous plait.
- and the check please.
i don't know
what the fuck he said.
you keep talking english. why
don't you try and use your french?
i don't know.
i feel strange.
me and tony went to miami. he
knows like six words in spanish,
but he was right out there with them like he
was fucking ricardo montalban or something.
mmm.
i told you we should
have gone towards rue dauphine.
god damn it, where's my other glove?
i had it when we went in there.
- i'm all turned around.
- you had to hurry me out of that restaurant.
- we're miles from the louvre.
- fuck, damn it. i already lost a glove.
oh my god.
holy shit.
look at those clouds.
paris skies...
who could have built this?
look!
just like "charade"!
make sure you clean
that shit off her tit!
vito-- atlantic city,
forget it.
why the changeup?
i can't keep
fighting phil on this.
our businesses are
all entwined.
you gotta pick your battles. you want
your no-show jobs, vito's gotta go.
it's the right move, t.
all those weeks
in the hospital,
surgeries, constant pain, for what?
come out here and get shot
over something like this?
i'm sorry.
if vito wanted to pursue
that lifestyle,
he should have
done so quietly.
he was, wasn't he?
anyone in particular
you want to give this to?
carlo had the biggest problem
with it, let him handle it.
it's vito's own fault.
why couldn't he stay
wherever
the fuck he was?
don't beat yourself
up about this.
i'll tell carlo
to be at the mall.
hi, it's me.
i just wanted to let you know
that we got in safe and sound.
call me back. remember,
it's six hours ahead.
miss you.
i notice all these little plaques
all over-- what do they say?
"august 20, 1944.
this man francois martine
fought in the resistance
and the germans shot him
right here on this spot."
phil?
what the fuck did that
tailor do to my zanella's?
- what?
- my slacks, what!
he's losing his eyesight,
poveret'. diabetes.
i'll take them to the korean
on my way to church tomorrow.
i've got a meeting
of concerned catholic mothers.
tell you the truth,
i almost want to not go
to the meeting.
- here we go.
- a gay in our own family?
this protestant minister from denver
is coming to speak to us tomorrow.
an expert.
i'm so embarrassed
in front of father.
father told me vito doesn't
renounce that lifestyle
- he's damned.
- i know.
- what?
father put it so well
last week.
- "there's nothing gay about hell," he said.
- that's good.
i'm sure he didn't
come up with that himself.
one thing i do know,
vito has to be made to face
his problem squarely.
thanks for the ride.
new york's only
classic rock station:
- q104.3
- here.
you don't need to do that,
but you're sweet.
okay.
- yeah?
- i was just wondering if you thought about my offer.
yeah, i thought, and i need to know
who these atlantic city contacts are.
meet me in the mall, 11:00.
don't be late.
- get him up.
- no!
- come here, come here.
- shut up.
don't be moving.
stop.
you're a fucking disgrace.
...husband comes home with
a duck under his arm, he says,
"this is the pig
i've been fucking."
the wife says, "it's
not a pig, it's a duck."
- he says, "i wasn't
talking to you."
vito... he was found beat
to death this morning
in a motel in fort lee.
- my cop up there told me.
- minchia.
plus the homicide detectives
told him
vito had a pool cue
rammed up his ass.
- lover's quarrel maybe?
- look, we all know who did it.
phil! the fucking balls on that prick!
what did i always
say about him?
i see you
heard the news.
- that must have been phil, right?
- jimmy olsen over here.
i know he's out of line, but still,
you kind of have to admire the guy.
it's not all talk
with him.
i'm just saying he saved us
all a lot of trouble, right?
can't have been an easy
decision, killing a made guy, huh?
naturally phil won't brag
about it 'cause he can't.
phil was in a tough situation,
his family honor was stained.
if i got to vito first, net
result would have been the same.
fucking-a.
i wish i'd have
borrowed money from vito.
you know what
this is, right?
it's not about vito,
it's about me.
phil's saying he can do
whatever the fuck he wants,
including kill a
captain in my own family
and i can't do a fucking thing about it.
it's always been
partly about that.
believe me, the vitamins
are just the beginning.
it's carmela.
- is paris burning?
- hi, you busy?
no no, just bullshitting
with sil.
how's it goin'?
actually it's cold,
raining.
- when it drizzles, huh?
- you're worse than ro.
i'm going out of my mind
with these pop references.
i am seeing some
incredible things, tony.
talk about the history channel,
you would love it here.
- how's the toast?
- the what?
the french toast?
actually they call it
something else.
- how's the french fries?
- pommes allumettes.
- fuck it.
- have you heard from meadow?
more than i thought.
you realize this kid knows
how to do absolutely nothing?
she was asking if she needed to
get the car serviced regularly
'cause there's no snow
out there.
- how's prince albert?
- he'd fit right in over in france.
none of those dipshits
want to work either.
i did get him to hose down
the trash cans though.
that's something.
you're probably busy.
i'll let you go.
i just wanted to say hello.
i miss you.
i miss you too.
be careful, eh?
people are gonna
expect a response.
see, this is what the fuck
i was talking about.
- we hit one of phil's guys?
- joe bananas went after carlo gambino.
made guys got killed,
the war went seven years.
how many times
do i gotta say this?
when guys are on the mattresses,
they're not out earning.
so? what?
all phil cares about
is fucking money.
he's got that wire room
in sheepshead bay, right?
- our guys have seen it.
- yeah.
i live in las vegas
six months.
my friend has a restaurant.
i work there.
- i like u.s.a.
- and i like france.
ro, are you coming
or what?
- okay, you call me, yeah?
- d'accord.
he lives in belleville.
they've got a belleville
in france.
you're not really gonna
go out with him, are you?
- i mean he's like 26 years old.
- duh!
god, isn't this pretty?
"1350 a.d."
you realize some woman
just like us wore this?
she was probably married,
had children.
"gallo roman baths,
third century."
i wonder what they
got up to there, huh?
this city is so old.
you think about all the
people who have lived here,
generation
after generation,
hundreds and hundreds of
years, all those lives.
god, it's so sad.
i mean, it isn't sad, i don't
know. it just makes you think,
- just makes you look at yourself differently.
- mmm.
there was this one night in the hospital
when it was very touch-and-go with tony.
- mm-hmm. - he came out
of the coma for a minute
and he said, "who am i?
where am i going?"
at the time i didn't know
what he meant.
but coming here,
i feel the same way.
isn't that odd?
let me get a picture.
oh honey, what?
we worry so much.
sometimes it feels
like that's all we do,
but in the end it just
gets washed away.
all of it just--
just gets washed away.
come here. oh.
i know what
the papers are saying,
but the police think it might've
not have been a gay thing.
marie, honey,
they pick up strangers
in bars and truck stops.
the way they beat him--
oh god, his face.
he didn't even look like
a person anymore.
- you can't let
your mind dwell on--
turn that off!
aunt cel' hasn't called.
not even to talk to the kids.
how could people
be so cruel?
it is a sin
after all, marie.
the church is
very clear on that.
but you're here.
you came.
father always says
hate the sin,
love the sinner.
i wish i was dead.
i mean it,
i wish i was dead!
you know what? i'll make
the funeral arrangements.
you're in no condition.
given the circumstances,
a small private service,
just the immediate family.
he was a good man,
wasn't he, phil?
he was. i loved him
like a brother-in-law.
- but god moves
in strange ways.
our tailor, he's going
blind, 47 years old.
walk in those shoes.
and i gotta think, marie,
vito on some level--
maybe it's better for the kids
not to have that role model.
so...
all the women
in your house are gone.
how do you feel about carmela
taking a trip without you?
do we really have
to fucking talk about this?
of course not.
before we end, is there
anything you'd like to discuss?
okay.
how about the fact
that i hate my son?
i come home and he's
sitting on the computer
in his fucking
underwear.
wasting his time
in some chitchat room,
going back and forth
with some other fucking jerkoff,
giggling like
a little schoolgirl.
i want to fucking smash
his fucking face in.
my son.
what do you think
about that?
anthony, i think
your anger towards a.j.
has been building
for some time.
we have to deal
with this.
all i know is it's a good
thing my father's not alive,
- because he'd find this fucking hilarious.
- find what hilarious?
the kind of...
son i produced.
you mean because anthony
doesn't conform
to your father's idea
of what a man should be?
his, mine or anybody's.
let me tell you--
if carmela let me kick a.j.'s
ass like my father kicked my ass,
- he might have grown up with some balls.
- like you.
yeah, like me.
he might have
also grown up
taking out his anger
at his father's brutality
towards him on others.
he might have grown up
with a desperate need
to dominate and control.
anthony, we've been dancing
around this for years--
how you live.
what is it you want
fr your life?
i couldn't even hit him
if i wanted to,
he's so fucking little. it's
carmela's side of the family,
they're small people.
her father-- you could
knock him over
with a fucking feather.
okay.
but i have to point out
what you resent carmela
doing for a.j.,
protecting him
from his father,
is the very thing
you had often wished
your mother
had done for you.
i love this fois gras.
i can't get enough.
the presentation alone gives
you calories, but who cares?
we should feel guilty?
we walked our asses off.
man, you know
what's strange, ro?
when you go to a place you've
never been before, it's like...
all the people were
imaginary till you got there.
it's like until you saw
them, they never existed,
and you never
existed to them.
i don't know, maybe you're more
a philosophical person than i am.
no no, it just made
me think, that's all.
you know, it's the
same as when you die--
life goes on
without you.
like it does in paris
when we're not here.
tomorrow we hit
the stores.
- chloe, dior.
- a kelly bag pour moi.
bordeaux
is so delicious.
when we were
in st. eustache's
i noticed that
you lit two candles,
for jackie
and jackie jr., right?
you know we never really
talked about that.
- about what?
- about jackie jr.
what's there
to talk about?
madame.
oof, madonn'.
- merci.
- oh boy!
i didn't mean
to invade, ro.
it's just--
i mean, we're friends.
if there was anything
you wanted to share...
i mean, i-i cannot
begin to imagine
losing a son.
jesus, carm.
we're on vacation.
we're having a beautiful dinner.
why would you
bring this up?
i didn't mean
to upset you, ro.
i thought because we had
this time together--
- it's fucking morbid, that's what it is.
- i'm sorry, ro.
he's dead.
he's gone.
what can i do about it?
light a candle.
i picture him
with his dad,
and with his grandma
who he loved
and with jesus.
what's the matter
with you?
why would you bring
new jersey here?
- why can't we just have a good time?
- you're right, i apologize.
i'm going out
with michel tonight.
okay.
you know, you're welcome
to come, carm.
- i mean that.
- thank you, but no. you go.
i want to walk along
the seine one more time.
we gotta call the exterminator.
these are rat turds.
what time did patsy
and them say?
there they are!
the pirates of prosciutt',
- the brigands of bracioll'.
- hey, dom.
game out in canarsie. i
appreciate the rollers you sent.
linguini fra diav',
you want to stay?
naw, i gotta stop by
my daughter's in metuchen.
hey... sorry to hear
about your boy.
uh-huh.
terrible thing.
son 13,
daughter nine years old.
syracuse--
tanked again.
that pool cue--
i wonder if it was chalked.
very funny, dom.
very cute.
i don't quite get it,
but cute.
hey, you know the autopsy found
a three ball in his side pocket?
- you're on a run.
- they found a hankie with carlo's lipstick
in his other pocket.
i'm just breaking balls.
you're right though--
shouldn't laugh about a tragedy.
that old homo actor--
raymond navarro?
he had an ivory dildo stuck
up his ass when they found him.
pretty up on all this shit, huh, dom?
come to think of it,
he was from jersey too.
- what'd they find up your mother's cunt?
- time to hit the trail
- for metuchen, huh, what do you say?
- my mistake.
carlo's lipstick
was on vito's cock.
hit him!
hit that prick!
no, carlo!
carlo!
get him off me!
how's that, you fuck?
fuck!
call patsy and them,
say we had to leave...
a pipe broke.
we wait till the store closes,
we get him out.
cut him up
in the work area?
no more of that.
uh, dna.
ditch his car,
get some biangaleen.
sil!
come on, open the door!
- shit.
- hello, anybody in there?
ton', you don't want
to come in here.
- get back in your car, go for a ride.
- what?
fat dom gamiello
came over,
you know, just to break balls re vito,
carlo...
sil hit him
first.
tony,
let me just--
that's right, ton', u go.
you don't know nothin'.
you were right. they kill a
made guy, this is what happens.
say hello to gab. tell her
i hope she's over the flu.
goddamn vito!
what's the hardest thing
about skateboarding?
i give up. what's the hardest
thing about skateboarding?
- telling your parents
you're gay.
- signore.
- i thought you were going out for dinner.
see you in the garage
a minute?
- what now?
- tomorrow morning, 7:00 a.m. you go to this address.
you ask for
a mr. caravalho.
- i just got off the phone with him.
- at 7:00 in the morning?!
- for what?
- you're gonna be working construction.
- what?
- ferrying cement in a wheelbarrow.
- so, it's outdoors?
- yeah.
- well, it's wintertime. - you've got
a lot of those hooded sweatshirts--
like the mulignans wear
that you watch on mtv.
- you can double up.
- come on, this is bullshit.
every penny you make, you keep.
we won't charge you any rent.
and believe me, the pay
is good. it's a union job.
i just want to see
you do good.
you're my son
and i love you.
look, i 'm just gonna
have to leave your friend
in the lurch
when i go back to school.
that's okay, he deals
with that all the time.
i'd just as soon
keep searching online.
i'm sure you would,
but if you're not
at that site tomorrow morning,
i'm gonna
take away your car.
and then i'm gonna
take away your clothes.
and then i'm gonna take away your room and
then i'm gonna take away your mother's cooking.
and pretty soon you're gonna
be out in the fucking street.
- what the hell are you doing?
- it might get a little drafty driving down there tomorrow.
but i will have this fucking
thing towed out of here
and ground up
into fucking brillo pads.
i mean look at it.
you don't take care of it.
don't put me
to the test.
look, i found cosette.
your friend-- someone needs
to tell her she's dead.
your taxi
is coming.
bonsoir, madame.
shit! the toulouse-lautrec placemats.
i got the other one.
there she is!
the world traveler.
- mmm.
- hey!
- how was your trip?
- oh my god, tony.
welcome home.
how was the trip?
oh my god, ma, paris!
"police are withholding
specific details of the murder.
a brooklyn relative
of spatafore
who spoke on conditions
of anonymity--"
what does that mean?
it means...
when you don't know
who the person is.
"--told reporters that
spatafore and his wife
had recently separated.
relatives say
that the victim
had surprised
his friends and family
by declaring
himself a homosexual
and saying he wished to lead
an openly gay lifestyle."
i don't understand.
dad wasn't a spy?
no.
with this jetlag,
i can't sleep.
i'm doing darks
if you have any.
have a great day at work.
- hey, i knew this guy.
- what?
he was in the mob?
i shot him
for the thin club. here.
synch: frm
www.1000fr.com