You holding up okay?
Dying of boredom yet?
BRIDGETTE:
Nuh-uh.
Just 15 more minutes.
Then we'll meet Mom
and the girls by the shoe department,
and then we'll go
to the movie, okay?
Okay, but what are
you buying socks for?
Don't you have plenty
of socks at home?
It's not
like you're still growing.
Well, you know,over time, they wear out.
And sometimes
the dryer eats them.
You mean we have a dryer
that eats things?
Huh?
Uh, no, no, it's just sometimes
things get lost in there.Socks mostly.
It's not like
it actually eats anything.
Stay here for just one second, baby.
I just want to ask
this salesman something.
Excuse me, uh,
I'm looking for
these in the crew.
I'll be right over, sir.
Thank you.
Bridgette?
Bridgette?!
Bridgette.
Bridge?
Bridge!
Bridge!Bridgette Dubois?!
ALLISON:
Hey. It's 4:00 in the morning.
What are you doing up?
What are you doing out?
LISON:
What can I tell you.
People are terrified.
Every time
a red-headed woman who lives alone
hears the wind jangling
a loose screen,
she thinks she's got
a close encounter with the Phoenix Phantom.
And...?
Not tonight.
Not the three women
that I sat with,thankfully,
although I did have the distinct honor
of watching
the coroner pull the body
of the first victim
out of a Dumpster behind
a gentleman's club.
Ah...
well...
Okay, can you reset the alarm
after you get up at 6:30
for me at noon?
Absolutely. Wouldn't want to be
late making the kids breakfast,
getting them dressed,
taking them to school,
making them dinner or helping them out
with their homework.
I'm sorry.
I'm... I know you are.
I-I'm sorry.
People are dying.You're trying to help.
I get it. I do.
It's just...
It's... it's unfair.
I can fix this.I swear.
Oh... now let's just hope
that between now and noon,
I don't have any scary dreams
that wake me up.
Well, I don't think
you need to worry
about that.
I already did that
for you, too.
I'm sorry.
Mommy always puts her hand
on the top of my head so the hair doesn't pull.
Yeah, I'm sure she does.
...was discovered
yesterday evening
in a Dumpster outside
the Fantasy Lounge.
Bridge... hey, hey.Bridge,
Bridge...turn that off, will you?
...apparent abduction three
nights ago of Darlene Denise.
Another redhead...
She's eating cookies.
Nuh-uh!
You know what? I don't care.
Everybody get their stuff
together.
Let's get this show
on the road.
Mommy's not taking us
again today?
Ariel, look around.Do you see Mommy?
Come on.
This isn't new.Mommy worked late,
so Mommy's sleeping in.
Good night.
WOMAN:
Must be the night shift.
He's waiting for you.
Have a nice evening.
Are you kidding?
I'm going home
and rinsing out
the little bit of red
I have left in my hair.
Knock, knock.
Tell me you had a dream.
I had a dream.
I was having dinner
with my family.
Keep dreaming.
We had 11 calls last night
from women convinced
the Phantom
was trying to break
into their homes
or apartments
from virtually every precinct
in the city.
We've still got guys out
in the field running them down.
Allison and I interviewed
three of them ourselves.
And...?
And two of them were genuinely frightened
although without cause.
The other one, she just wanted
some attention
from her boyfriend.
Uh-huh.
All together, since
the second disappearance,
we've had over 1,400 calls,
tips, supposed sightings,
even six confessions.
What's the "want"?
What's the "goal"?
I mean, it can't
just be about red hair.
Whoever did it,they know how
to break and enter.
Places are clean as a whistle.
These abductions are planned
and extremely well-thought-out.
They're not random.
Excuse me.
It's home.
Hello?
Hi, baby.
Just a second.
It's my oldest.
Scanlon.
Ariel, everything okay?
Yeah. I was just wondering
if you knew yet.
Knew what?
About tomorrow.
Horseback riding.
It would just be a lot more fun
if you could go, too.
You know what?
Let me talk to my boss.
See what I can do, okay?
I'll call you back, baby.
Bye.
I have a problem.
I mean, I don't
mind working
as a human lie detector,
but it's been four nights
in a row now,
and, frankly, my family
is starting to lose it.
Is there any way I could take
a pass tonight?
We just got a call.
Apparently he's struck again.
SCANLON:
You're awfully
quiet tonight.
Hmm. Count your blessings.
Sounds like a dare.
Don't mind me.
I'm just frustrated,
that's all.
What are you frustrated about?
That I'm here,
that everyone's frustrated
with me.
There's nothing I can do
about it.
I'm guessing we're talking
about the home front, 'cause...
no around here
is frustrated with you.
Look, I'll make
you a deal.
Let's just check out
this crime scene.
It'll take all of half an hour.
If nothing happens for you,then we'll call it a night.
No home visits, no interviews.
You'll be back at your car
by 10:00.Home by 11:00.
How does
that sound?
That sounds fantastic.
God, I'm nice.
MAN:
'Evening.
That it is.
Who have we got here?
The mother had been calling
for two days,
saying she was trying
to reach her child.
We finally got over here.
Landlord let us in.
Seems to fit
the pattern.
The victim appears
to have been roused from sleep.
Haven't found
any blood or DNA just yet.
No signs of a struggle.
Redhead?
Of course.
Can I see
the bedroom?
SCANLON:
This is Allison Dubois.
She's with the D.A.
Find anything?
Uh...
Well, then, it's unanimous.
The crime scene techs found
some nothing in the kitchen.
That led them in here
where they found
a little more nothing.
Now they're checking
the perimeter which,
if everything goes
according to pattern,
will yield absolutely nothing.
Hey, honey.
Hang on a sec.
We'll be out of here in 15.
I'll be back.
Hey, eldest child, good news.
Mommy's leaving work shortly,
which means...
I'll be going horseback riding
with you!
Yes. Tell Daddy
I should be home by 11:00.
Sure, put him on.
MAN:
We're looking
for Isaiah, men.
Find me Isaiah.
Hello.
I think
I might've
found it.
I think it's on this mirror.
I'm sorry, sir
but I just don't see it.
JOE ( over phone ):
Allison?
He did it with his
finger. Come here.
JOE:
Allison?
Joe, I gotta call you back.
You still don't
see it, do you?
Let me show you
something.
There we go.
There it is.
Isaiah 14:21.
Damn it!
I see him.
All right.
SCANLON:
You still on the phone?
Allison... you ready
to get out of here?
I think he left us a message.
Who are you talking about?
I didn't get anything
in the bedroom
because it didn't happen
in the bedroom.
It happened in here.
Whoa,
whoa,
whoa.
There may be evidence in there.You probably
shouldn't...
Look at the mirror.
What is that?
It's a message.It's a piece of scripture.
Isaiah 14:21.
I am not a toy.
I'm not a thing.
You're hung up on me.
You can't just
start kissing me
and expect everything
to be all right.
Boy, you give up easily.
Wow. Actually home
before midnight.
You talking to me, toy?
You talking to me, thing?
Someone is very cocky.
Well, I cracked the case.
Caught the guy?
Well, I nicked the case.
Turns out the killer
left a message
and nobody saw it but me.
I'm proud of you, baby.
Are you?
Yeah.
I'm always proud of you.
Whatever else, I am
always proud of you.
Want to hear something funny?
You going to start, start
calling me "toy" again, huh?
You know who showed
me the clue?
Who?
Captain Kenneth Push
of the Texas Rangers.
I don't get it?
What was he doing there?
Well, that's the thing--
he wasn't there,
It was a vision I had.
That's right.
You've haven't met
Trust me, you have
nothing to worry about.
Oh, really?
Are you prepared to prove that?
Maybe.
On your mark.
Get set...
Go!
Hey.
Mom?
Can you still ride
horses in a hurricane?
Aren't there supposed
to be two dice?
What's the difference?
We'll just play with one dice.
I don't think that's gonna
work 'cause you have to move
at least seven paces
for the game to work.
Well, just double
whatever you roll.
Well, then you're never
gonna roll an odd number.
I'll just get a dice
from another game.
ARIEL:
You can't be
everything.
BRIDGETTE:
Can, too. Mommy said that
I can be anything
I want to be.
She wasn't talking
about the game, stupid.
She was talking
about life.
Games is a
part of life.
Hey, admit it. Isn't this
so much more fun
than horseback riding?
Not if I can't
be orange.
Okay. Girls, enough. Stop.
For the rest of today,
everyone's
going to be something
they've never been before.
What do you mean?
I mean... Daddy
is going to be green.
Mommy is going
to be orange,
and you girls can be
something new. Ariel.
You're going
to be yellow.
Bridgette,
you're blue.
Blue? Blue is
a boy's color.
Here we go...
Hold on a second.
ALLISON:
Hello?
Captain Push,
you got my message.
One second.
Since I saw you,
I've been doing a lot of work
for the local
district attorney's office.
Some pretty
interesting stuff, really,
which is what
I'm calling you about.
This is gonna sound
kind of strange,
but if I say to you,
"Isaiah 14:21,"
does that ring any bells?
Good news.
What's the good news?
Hey, I thought
we were gonna play a game?
Yeah, that was an hour
and 20 minutes ago.
I-I'm sorry.
I just, I...
It turns out there is
a connection.
A killer with
the same M.O.
made his way
across South Texas
a couple of years ago,
so I called Devalos.
The three of us conferenced.
He's flying out
to meet us tomorrow.
Sunday?
Miss Dubois.
In April of 2002, the state
comptroller called me up.
His sister's 19-year-old
daughter was going to school
in Austin and she hadn't
called home in over a week.
So I went down there
to take a look.
I was about half certain
she was in Corpus or Cabo
or Daytona, one of these
spring break towns where they stop
serving you beer
if they find out you been calling your folks.
Three days later,
we found her body behind
a massage parlor off the I-10.
Over the next 11 days,
there were two more kids
reported missing--
a 20-year-old Galveston woman
and an 18-year-old
fellow from Houston.
Sorry. Did you
say one of your
victims was male?
Yes, sir.
Was he by any chance a redhead?
None of them had red hair.
Huh. Well, now
I'm starting to wonder
if we're all talking
about the same perpetrator.
Our profilers
seem fairly sure that what we're
dealing with here in Arizona is some kind
of sex killer
who is only interested
in redheaded women.
You just have the one
girl so far, right?
One body?
Either of you see her?
Detective Scanlon
and I did.
We watched the coroner fish the body out
of a Dumpster the other night.
And?
And it looked like she'd
been stabbed, or worse.
She was covered with blood.
Any autopsy results yet?
Due in first thing tomorrow.
PUSH:
Well, let me tell you
what they're going to say.
The girl's going
to be clean as a whistle.
No signs of
sexual violation whatsoever.
She will, however,
be missing her heart.
SCANLON:
Excuse me?
He takes their hearts.
Carves it right
out of their chest.
Doesn't have anything
to do with sex.
It's Biblical.
Isaiah. Chapter 14, verse 21.
"Prepare slaughter
for their children
"for the iniquity "of their fathers;
that they do not "rise, nor
possess the land,
nor fill the face
of the world."
Every time we'd find a body,
there it'd be.
Every time we'd
go to a residence
or someone was reported missing.
SCANLON:
Wait a second.
Let's not jump
the gun here.
This Isaiah thing
was on a mirror
the other night.
That's the only time.
Excuse me.
When you found that body,
did you look in the Dumpster?
Well, look
in the Dumpster again.
Look all around the Dumpster.
Look under
the Dumpster.
I'm betting you,it's there. It's the guy's M.O.
It's like writing
in the mist on a mirror
where you might
not see it.
This guy wants you
to have to
look for it. He wants you to
have to work for it.
You're a philistine.
We're all philistines.
I still think it's possible
we're talking about another guy,
a copycat.
It's possible... but I doubt it.
We never went public
with the quotes.
Didn't want to
encourage him.
Okay, so where does
this leave us?
A quotation
from the Bible about children
being killed
for the sins of their fathers.
I'm not sure I get it.
Well, don't feel bad.
I didn't get it either.
11 days, three kids,
and then...
it stopped.
Like a... storm.
Just-- pff!-- gone.
I figured
he's dead.
Apparently I figured wrong.
This is completely
unnecessary, you know.
Takeout rotisserie
chicken and sides
served on dinner plates
with three kids fighting
over the wishbone?
This is something you're willing
to pass up?
All right. This one time.
So how's your heart?
It's happy
to be here.
JOE:
Well, I finally met the amazing
Captain Push.
And?
I thought he'd be taller.
Ooh. Someone's
in a mood.
What are you
talking about?It's 6:30 on Sunday night.
I've spent all day
entertaining the kids
and w I'm spending all night
entertaining a surprise guest.
Why would I be in a mood?
BRIDGETTE:
And I rode Whisper.
And I rode Lightning,
and Daddy and Marie rode...
Old Glue.
Old Glue?
He was very...
very gentle.
Mommy, it was
so much fun.
I know. Daddy said
it was the most fun ever.
The only thing that would
make it funner
was if we had
our own ponies.
ALLISON:
Excuse me?
Who gave you that idea?
Danielle Moynihan
She has her own pony.
We saw her riding it
when we left the stable.
Ladies, we
have a guest.
Now's not the time
to be discussing...
I had a pony growing up.
You did?
What was his name?
Jacinto.
He was named after a great battle.
Why? Was he mean?
No.
He sure did make a mess, though.
ARIEL:
A mess?
How?
Well, you know how
when you have a cat,
you have to clean up
his litter box?
Well, you imagine
doing that for
something so big,
he leaves behind
six or seven shoe boxes
full of manure every day.
Only it's not
in shoe boxes
You got to
shovel it.
Every morning, every night.
Every morning and every night?!
Plus you got to feed
him twice a day.
12 gallons of water,
half a bale of hay.
You gotta pick up
his hooves, check them
for thrush. You gotta stay
with him when he's sick.
Do horses get sick a lot?
Well, my horse got very sick at the end.
He had colic.
Bad.
I had colic.
We had to take tube
and run it down his nose
and pump oil
through it
to try to get his
belly to loosen up.
Unfortunately...it didn't do the trick.
He died.
Does anyone feel like dessert?
Oh, yeah.
Okay, girls, come help
me with dessert.
Thanks.
All right, he did get
taller as the night went on.
You like him. I know you do.
All right, I liked him.
I'm gonna tell him
tomorrow when I take him
to the airport.* I'm gonna
tell him. *
Okay, you do that.
And now that's
out of the way,
what do you say we
call a moratorium
on all things, topics
and people work-related,
just for the next
nine hours or so, huh?
Would that make
you happy, toy?
Would that make you
happy, thing?
Shut up.
PUSH:
Ms. Dubois?
Ms. Dubois, wake up.
Ms. Dubois.
As soon as it happened
I had to tell you.
I had to let you know.
You were right.
You were right all along.
What are you talking about?
Oh, my God,
what are you doing here?
First thing that hits you is
everything you know.
Everything.
Your whole dang life.
It hits you like a wave.
Takes a second,
but you see it all,
feel it all, too-- the...
sadness, the exultation.
It's all in there,
and it's not even a second.
And then, the second wave is
everything you don't know.
Everything you ever
wondered about.
Everything.
(whispering):
Captain Push...
my husband, it-it's 3:30
in the morning.
You're just...
annihilated with
extraordinary clarity.
I mean, I see it all from here.
I see everything.
Allison...
they're related.
What's related?
The murders, the victims,
the ones he chooses.
It's not random.
Okay...
And there's
another girl.
She's next on his list.
Her name is...
I'll get the baby.
You wake the girls.
Good morning, ma'am.
Morning.
I was wondering if you could
ring up Kenneth Push's room
and let him know that
his ride's in the lobby?
Certainly.
You haven't by chance
spoken with Mr. Push
or any members
of his family this
morning, have you?
What?
I don't really have
all the details.
All I know is that
they called an ambulance
for Mr. Push sometime
after 3:00 this morning.
They took him over to
St. Christopher's Hospital.
Now, look, Captain
Push, I appreciate
you're far from home
but these temporary
pacemakers are
only designed
to work three or
four days at a time
before a permanent
unit can be placed
inside the body.
It's a pretty straightforward
procedure.
I wish you would reconsider
and let me do it.
Doctor...
this is the first time
you and I have met, right?
No offense, but...
I'm not in the habit
of letting a perfect stranger
slice me up the middle
and install miniature
electronics in my chest.
Now, I have a wonderful doctor
back home
who knows me inside and out,
and in a day and a half,
when you let me out of this bed,
I'm flying back to Texas,
and I'll have him do
whatever is necessary.
ALLISON:
You causing trouble?
Uh-huh.
You Mrs. Dubois?
Yup. I'm the woman
who fed him
whatever it is that
put him in here.
DOCTOR:
Well, maybe you can convince him
to let me operate,
put in that pacemaker
so he can go back home.
I'm fine.
I got this outboard model
right here.
Tells my heart when to beat,
holds all my addresses
and phone numbers.
I even get AM/FM radio.
DOCTOR:
Yeah.
Well, I'm gonna go ahead
and call your doctor in Houston,
see if he can't convince you.Mrs. Dubois.
(muttering):
He's gonna phone my doctor in Houston...
Oh, boy.
I let you out of my
sight for 20 minutes.
I don't know
what to tell you.
Woke up in the middle
of the night.
Recognized the feeling.
Knew exactly
what was happening.
Called downstairs
to the desk
and must have...
blacked out right after that.
Next thing I know,
they're working on an ambulance.
I'm guessing this
was around 3:30
in the morning.
Yeah. I don't know.
You were wearing
blue boxers
and a white T-shirt.
You gonna guess
my weight now?
I think you came to see me
last night.
Come again?
You came to visit me,
in my bedroom.
It was around 3:30
in the morning.
I thought that I was dreaming.
I didn't know
what was happening.
But now I realize...
it was you.
You must have died
for a minute or two.
I know you have a
difficult time with
this kind of thing.
( quietly ):
I don't know what to say.
Showed up in my boxers, huh?
Hope I didn't offend
the other guests.
( laughs )
You said that where you were,
you could see everything,
that you had
this enormous clarity.
Allison...
You were very excited--
you told me that
all the murders were related.
That the victims
weren't random.
Not random, huh?
That hardly seems
like a revelation
worthy of a near-death
experience.
And then you said you knew
who the next victim would be.
And...?
And...
I guess that's when
they brought you back to life.
You never said
their name.
You just disappeared.
Or I fell asleep, or...
I know you well enough to know
that you wouldn't be
telling me these things
if you didn't believe them
with all your heart.
Captain Push...
I have
no recollection
of seeing anyone last night
except a very frightened
hotel manager
and a couple very able EMS guys
whose names I don't remember
and who probably saved my life.
Allison...
I'm a lawman.
This maniac
killed three Texans.
Don't you think
I'd tell you if I knew
what tied all these people
together?
Don't you think I'd tell you
if I knew who he was fixin'
to kill next?
Of course.
Related? How?
You're not giving me
much to work with.
I don't know,
they're just related.
And you came upon this
startling revelation how?
It's not important.
It's Detective
Scanlon. Damn.
It's 2:40. You'll
wake the baby.
Just click it
and hang up.
( over phone ):
Allison...
All right, talk to him.
I'll get the baby.
Hello?
No, it's okay, he understands.
What's going on?
We found the bodies
of Darlene Denise
and, uh, Katie Fisher.
Okay, where did he leave them?
A church. Downtown.
Right in the middle
of Metro district.
Wait a second,
does that fit the pattern?
Well, it's not a nudie bar
and it's not an abortion clinic,
but it's kind of
a nontraditional church.
Female priest.
Gay choir. I mean,
if you're the kind of killer
who likes fire
with his brimstone,
it's probably the kind of place
that would tick you off.
What about Isaiah?
He's here--
every prayerbook in every pew,
there's a bookmark
so you open right to it.
So, you want to come down?
( Marie crying )
I can send a car for you.
It's up to you.
I just thought y you might want
to come down here and,
uh...commune.
You know what?
Let's talk tomorrow.
I'll give you a call.
All right. Absolutely.
'Kay, thanks.
Is it anything
important?
Nah.
Shh... sweetheart.
You're making
the right decision.
Don't gloat.
I'm not making any decision.
You brain-washed
my doctor back home.
Captain Push here.
Allison Dubois here.
Well, you're in
an awfully good mood.
I'll bet that's 'cause
you're not surrounded
by people hell-bent on playing with your innards.
No. But I am staring
at my little baby
who has a bit of a fever--
which is why I'm calling.
I really wanted to stop by and
see you today before you left,
but I just don't know
how I'm gonna do it.
Well, then I have some good news
and I have some bad news.
The good news is,
I'm not leaving quite so fast.
The bad news is,
they're opening up my chest tomorrow morning,
and I may not feel too much
like entertaining after that.
Oh, no.
Well, maybe I could swing by
and see you after
my husband gets home.
Hell, I'll have them dress me
in some fresh gauze
if I know you're coming.
( laughs softly ):
It's a deal.
Captain Push, forgive me,
I'm getting another call.
Give me a second,
I'll get rid of 'em.
Hello?
DEVALOS:
Allison.
Good afternoon, sir.
I have somebody
on the other line.
Let me just...
That's all right,
this'll just take a moment.
Now that we have two bodies,
and based
on our conversation yesterday,
I took a flier and ordered up
some comparative DNA.
Now, I just received
the first report
about 20 minutes ago, and...
( sighs ):
Allison, these two women
are related.
Excuse me?
I haven't figured out how
quite yet,
but according
to their DNA markers,
both women have the same father.
Allison?
( sighs )
I-I'm sorry, I just, uh...
Just thought you'd want to know.
Bye.
Thank you.
Hello? Are you still there?
That is not the kind of thing
you want to be asking
a man in my condition.
Okay, I hear no laughter.
You all right?
Yeah. N-No. I just...
That was the office--
they ran some comparative DNA
on our first two victims.
They don't understand how,
but according to the lab,
both of these women
are actually related.
From a genetic standpoint,
they have the same father.
Captain Push?
Hey, everybody.
Hi., Daddy.
Wow, Daddy, who's that for?
The balloon is for Marie,
the wine's for Mommy and me.
Where's everyone?
Marie's sleeping
and Mom's getting dressed.
Hey.
Thank God. I was hoping you'd
show up about 15 minutes ago.
I stopped to pick up
a couple of things.
Are you going somewhere?
Don't be mad.
The Phoenix Phantom snatched
another girl.
Devalos called. He asked me
to stop by the crime scene.
I've been waiting
for you to get home.
I have to stick my head in
at the hospital.
Say hi to Captain Push.
Turns out they're
operating on
him tomorrow
I feel badly--
he's in a strange city.
He doesn't know anybody.
Marie's fever broke hours ago.
She's out like a light.
There's meat loaf in the oven.
It'll be ready in 15 minutes.
There's coleslaw
in the fridge.
So, if I leave
right now
I have a chance
of getting back by 9:30.
You still proud of me?
BRIDGETTE:
Look what
Daddy brought.
Isn't Marie a little young
for this?
Get out of here.
We'll have this fight at 9:30.
You promise?
I'm uncorking that at 9:15.
Shall we synchronize
our watches?
Just go.
PUSH:
Hey.
How long you been sitting there?
A bit.
They told me they gave you
a little something
to help take the edge off.
Is that what they call it,
an edge?
For what it's worth,
apparently this is a fairly
run-of-the-mill operation.
It's not about my heart.
I could have stopped this thing.
You don't know that.
Yeah, I do.
Called Texas right after
you and I got off the phone.
Had them pull out
the old lab work.
It was there all along.
Just never
looked for it.
You told me.
You said, they're related--
and they were.
No, Captain Push.
You told me.
I can't remember
the person's name.
I've been thinking...
I've been trying all day.
The next victim.
You told me I...
I tried to tell you.
What time is it?
I lost all track of time.
It's 10:15.
He got her today.
I just came
from the crime scene.
Her name was Sarah Duffy.
I'm sorry.
That... God...
He is one perverse entity.
First you die...
then you see everything.
WOMAN:
I'm sorry,visiting hours are over.
And you need your rest.
You have a big
day tomorrow.
We're coming
for you at 5:30.
Duly noted.
Oh, by the way...
could you bring me a comb
and a pair of nail clippers?
I want you
to do something for me.
I want you to forget
about all this.
I want you
to concentrate on getting better.
I want to come by,
check on you tomorrow.
( whispering ):
Hey, it's me.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I would have called,
but they don't allow cell phones
in the cardio unit.
So... how'd it go
with the kids?
Joe...
Are you really asleep?
i'm sorry
Hello.
Allison...
Captain Push.
I just called
to make sure you made it home.
That you're safe.
That you're in your bed.
I'm home.
I'm safe... in my bed.
Good.
Okay, then.
Let's get some rest.
And I'll see you soon, okay?
Not if I don't see you first.
Okay?
( chuckles ):
Okay.
Bye.
sjz:duanyz