WOMAN: Tim, listen to me.
A certain amount of
selfishness is good.
A marriage without selfishness
is a marriage
without pleasure.
And a marriage
without pleasure is doomed.
Yes, we love. Yes, we give.
Yes, we want to
make our partner happy.
But it's like
that announcement
they make on the airplane.
If the cabin should
suddenly lose pressure,
first you must attend
to your own oxygen mask,
then put on your child's,
your partner's.
Do you follow me?
Okay, then.
The rest is simple.
You want to do
something with Donna.
To Donna.
You've wanted to
do it for a long time,
but you thought it was wrong.
You thought Donna
wouldn't understand.
You thought society
Well, today
you're going to do it.
Right here. Right now.
Okay. Stand up.
Tim.
Nothing can happen unless you
stand up and face your wife.
Now come on.
Are you embarrassed?
Are you embarrassed
to do it in front of me?
Don't be embarrassed.
I've seen it all.
Now come on.
Stand up and face your wif
( gunshot )
Excellent, Tim.
Excellent job.
( gasps )
( groans )
What's going on?
We fell asleep
watching the news.
It's almost
2:00 in the morning.
Yep.
Oh, I just had
the weirdest dream.
Of course you did.
It's a day that ends in "Y".
( birds chirping )
Joe?
Girls?
( indistinct chattering )
But I feel funny
not telling Mommy.
But if you tell Mommy,
it won't be a surprise.
Right.
Hello, my sneaky family.
You don't give
a dentist candy,
you don't buy a
kitten for a veterinarian,
and you don't plan a
surprise party
for someone like me.
Who said anyone was
planning a
surprise party for you?
All right, fine.
You tell the kids.
They're the ones who wanted
to have the
early morning meeting.
They're the
ones that are really
fired up about your birthday.
Really? So it was
their idea, not yours?
Hey, do I look
like a fool to you?
You are a
deeply disturbed man.
Thank you, darling.
Now, listen, as long as
you know about everything,
there's a list of things
they say they
need for the party.
I can't get
them until Saturday.
( chuckles ):
You want me to buy
supplies for my
own surprise party?
Well, it's not like it's going
to ruin it for you.
Well, okay, fine.
You're the one that's going
to be disappointed when all
the good pi~atas are gone.
So what do you
make of that dream?
Some guy kills his wife?
I don't mean to
make you nervous,
but that happens every day.
At the marriage counselor?
Every other day.
With the
therapist urging him on?
I take your point.
I know it's not
a realistic dream.
If that had really happened,
it would have
made the headlines.
I just can't figure out
whether or not to
mention it at work.
What do you mean? To the D.A.?
Why would you do that?
I don't know, I must
have dreamt it for a reason.
Yeah, and the reason is,
the TV was on,
and subconsciously
you were listening
to a bunch of
lunatics who are married
talk about how they
want to kill each other.
That's true.
Which is why the next time
we fall asleep
with the television on,
I'm going to make
sure we got a little
soft-core something going on.
You get my meaning, woman?
Go to work.
Oh, yeah. She heard me.
Call Maury Povich.
Tell him I'm
ready for my close-up.
( sighing ): Ha-ha.
( cell phone ringing )
Detective Scanlon.
WOMAN: Scanlon?
This is Dispatch.
What's your 20?
I'm at a crime
scene in Scottsdale.
Scottsdale? That's
not in your jurisdiction.
I'm having a
difficult time copying you.
Why don't you call
me back in 15 minutes?
( cell phone ringing )
Detective Scanlon.
Detective Scanlon? I
guess we were disconnected.
The Lieutenant
was looking for you.
May I connect?
Absolutely. Put him through.
( cell phone ringing )
( ringing stops )
Manny.
Thanks for coming.
You're the best.
Yeah, well, I'm
starting to think
that I'm the most naive.
Every one of these men wants
to know what I'm doing here.
to know what
you're doing here.
Tell 'em to take a
'lude. It's a crime scene.
Lee, I'm not going to
tell anyone to take anything.
And as a matter of
fact, no, it's not.
It's not a crime scene.
Not the way you mean.
This is a murder-suicide.
This man killed his wife,
then he killed
himself, and that's how
the Coroner's going to find
and that's how the
City's going to record it.
There's no need
for a prosecutor,
there's no need
for a detective.
Particularly one who's
outside his
jurisdiction
and is on the verge
of being suspended.
Manny, you ever seen this?
What?
Bowling for Columbine.
I think so. ! Belongs to them.
They owned it.
It's like the
Gone With the Wind
of gun control
movies. Yeah? So?
So you're telling me
a young, married couple
whose idea of a
hot Friday night
is watching an
anti- NRA documentary
keep an
unregistered, loaded .32
in their
apartment-- I don't think so.
Someone did this.
This is like the
other ones, Manny.
They're connected.
Yeah.
But why are you the
only one who sees it?
You know, I've never
really shared with anyone
who you are or what you do.
Okay.
But I have a friend,
he's a police detective.
He called me this morning,
wants me to go to the mayor,
get funding for a
special task force.
What kind of task force?
For the past two years
or so he's been obsessed
with a string of
deaths here in Phoenix.
And?
And it's
destroying his career.
He's ignoring
all his other work.
I don't think
his personal life
is anything to
write home about either.
I don't understand...
He sees a crime where
others just see
personal turmoil.
He sees a pattern where
others see
only random tragedy.
He'll tell you all about it.
He's waiting for you
up at the crime scene.
I've asked them
to leave the bodies
and everything else they found
exactly the way they found it.
I was pretty vague with him.
I told him that
you were someone
who worked for
me, someone I trust.
Listen to what he has to say.
Look at the things
he wants to show you.
Tell me what you think.
Okay.
Thanks.
Hello?
SCANLON: Up here.
Put some booties
and gloves on first, though.
District Attorney
Devalos asked me to stop by.
Are you his friend?
Guilty as charged.
Detective Scanlon.
Allison. Allison Dubois.
So what do we have here?
Young married
couple found shot to death.
Guy was 29. Girl 27.
Coroner thinks the
husband put a bullet
in his wife's head, then
turned the gun on himself.
So what do you think happened?
I don't know. Not that.
"Not that"?
That's your
basis for a task force?
"Not that"?
Look, I don't know what it is
exactly you do with the D.A.
I don't know what
your specialty is.
Forensics?
Linguistics? Criminology?
Maybe you were
with the FBI or the CSI
or the CIA or the kiss my ass.
Don't misunderstand me.
I don't mean any
disrespect, but
me, I'm just a cop.
Not a specialist.
Started in Traffic control.
Glorified crossing guard.
And I'm here to
tell you that I could
look into a
windshield 30 feet away
and tell you if the driver
was going to see the stop sign
I was holding up or if he was
going to run the intersection.
And I was always right.
Instinct.
It got me this
far, so I listen to it.
Is there anything else?
Yeah.
In the past 27 months,
there have been three cases
in the Greater Phoenix area
of supposed murder-suicides
among couples married
little more than a year.
Well, they do say the
first year's the hardest.
I wouldn't know.
But what I do know is, in the
90-some years prior to that,
in fact for as long
as they kept records,
there wasn't one other case
thought to be murder-suicide
among couples married more
than one year
but less than two.
Not one.
Well, these are
complicated times.
Phoenix is a bigger
than it's ever been before.
People get married,
there are bound to
be disappointments,
temptations...
( sighs )
The first couple...
was my sister and her husband.
I'm sorry.
He would've killed for her.
She would've killed for him.
There's nothing
complicated about it.
They didn't do
it to each other.
Someone did it to them.
Same thing here.
So, how do you
want to do this?
Do you want to wait outside,
or-or should I call you or...?
What do you mean?
I need to be alone,
so I can concentrate.
Oh.
All right.
( eerie breathing sound )
Nice to see you again.
They did a wonderful
job, don't you think?
Really rose to the occasion.
Actually, I don't
know what to think.
Who are you?
Are you dead, too?
Me? No. I'm... no one.
I'm not even a real person.
I'm just energy left
behind by the two of them.
A way for them to
communicate with you.
Through your
dreams last night.
Here, now.
They'd speak
to you themselves,
but their souls
are still in shock.
Both their souls.
You see, this happened
not because onwas
angry with the other.
This happened
because each loved the other
more than life itself.
It's important to
them you understand this.
( gasps )
( groans )
A third person?
And you're cerin of this?
Can I tell you who it is? No.
Can I tell you what
they were doing there? Uh-uh.
Can I tell you why
all this happened? No.
Not yet. But I do
agree with Detective Scanlon.
This is not something
that these two
people did to each other.
This is something
that was done to them.
( slapping desk )
I knew it, I
knew it, I knew it!
Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
So what'd you pick up? A
third set of fingerprints?
A hair sample?
Maybe there was
something about the wounds?
Lee...
Allison
specializes in a more...
unconventional
branch of criminology.
Okay. So what is
it convinced you?
Some kind of evidence, right?
Something Manny here can
take into a court of law?
Something he can use
to... persuade the mayor
to fund a task force,
get some manpower and
some resources on this case?
( clears throat )
I had a dream the other night.
Oh, crap.
Shoot me now.
She's not a
criminologist at all, is she?
Allison is an extraordinarily
sensitive and intuitive person
who I've worked with to great
effect on a number of cases.
Do I have the word "jackass"
stenciled across my forehead?!
All right, you
need to lower you voice.
Oh, my God!
Did you hear what I said?
What do I look
like to you, Manny?
She's one of those
sob-sister fortunetellers
that crawls out
from under a rock
when you can't
find the missing kid
and it's been over a year
and the parents
are getting desperate
and they'll listen
to just about
anyone, isn't she?
Point in fact,
up until recently,
Mrs. Dubois was a very
accomplished law student...
What were you thinking?
How the hell is she
going to get me a task force?!
What are you going to do?
Walk up to the mayor
and tell him she had a dream?
No, seriously. Answer me that.
How is putting me
together with Milli Vanilli
the Psychic here
gonna get me a task force?
You're right. That
was never gonna happen.
Would you mind telling
me just what was the point?
The point--
assuming she agreed with you
that there was
something
worth investigating--
was that Mrs.
Dubois is your task force.
That's it. She's
all the resources
anyone is ever
gonna give you, period.
Oh, boy, you really
know how to make
a girl feel special.
You're insane.
And you're insaner.
And you do have the word "ass"
tattooed on your
fehead except it doesn't have
a "jack" in front of it!
Don't you want to know
about the other three cases?
Seeing as how I seem
to be the only person
on the planet who agrees
with you even a little bit?
Wouldn't you want to know
if I see any similarities?
I don't know what's
she talking about, Manny.
I don't have three other
crime scenes to take her to.
Give her a set of
the crime scene photos.
Will that do it?
Well, it's a start.
She's here!
Daddy, she's here!
I'll watch the baby.
Whew!
( rapping on glass )
You just aged me by ten years.
And that would
make you a whopping 38.
Very nice. Good recovery.
I think I'll keep ya.
So, listen, so when
you walk through that door,
the kids are going
to be all over you.
I told them I
needed them to distract you
so I could sneak
all the party stuff
out of my car
and into the house.
Out of your car.
Yeah.
Of course,
because you bought it
because you are
superdaddy and a superhusband
trying to pull off a
supersurpise party for...
For my 28-year-old wife.
You're really
pushing your luck.
Wow,
the things you won't do
to try and spice
up our love life.
I don't know about you,
but this does nothing for me.
It's not funny. These
people are really dead.
Boy, as you get older,
approaching your
30s and everything,
you're really starting to
lose your sense of humor.
You know, you've
gotten every bit of mileage
you can out of that joke.
Someone's in a good mood.
The more I look
at these pictures,
the less sense
everything makes.
( yawning )
So, why don't you tell Devalos
to take you off
whatever this is?
Tell him you're
not getting anything.
Well, that's just it. I am.
It's just what I'm
getting doesn't add up.
And it's not just Devalos.
There's this
cop. This detective.
You should have heard him
talking about his instincts.
Suddenly when it
became about my instincts,
about him working with me?
Well, that would be insane.
I must be insane.
Well, then, this
is perfect, isn't it?
You don't like him.
Sounds like he
doesn't like you.
The things you're
sensing about this case
aren't clarifying anything.
All great reasons to
respectfully remove yourself.
Hmm. Well, I
might just do that.
I might just do that.
Good. I'm glad I
could be of help.
( alarm clock beeping )
( groans )
That makes no sense.
I'm just
telling you what I saw.
What you dreamt.
What I saw in my dreams.
Help me out
here, will you, Manny?
All right, let me see
if I can understand this.
You would see their faces...
They came to me in
flashes, like
crime scene photos.
Right. But always
the husband first.
Yes.
And always having
already been shot.
And that makes you think
that the husbands died first?
Allison, the
husband was always found
at the crime scene
with the gun in his hand
covered with
blowback and powder residue.
You can't kill yourself first
and then kill your wife.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Could you remind the detective
that I am on his side?
It's all right. Tell
her I appreciate the help.
But I would really prefer it
if her theories
made a little more sense.
Excuse me?
But with all
due respect, ma'am,
all you do is come up
with things that
contradict the
physical evidence.
That kind of
help I don't need.
At least I have a
theory. What's yours?
You've been on this two years
and what have
you come up with?
"My sister's
husband wouldn't do that."
Frankly, I'm not
impressed. Allison...
Golly, ma'am. Not
impressing you?
I can't tell you
how upsetting that is.
I'll probably
be awake all night.
Lee, would you
give it a rest, please?
( intercom ringing )
I told you not now!
( sighing )
Well, I guess
this was a bad idea.
You two are clearly not
meant to work with each other.
Allison, I appreciate
your time and effort,
and I
apologize for my friend's
extraordinary
lack of gratitude.
Lee, I hope I can count on you
not to say anything to anyone
about who Allison is
and how we u her talents
here in the D.A.'s office.
You're kidding, right?
Is there anything else
you would like to share
before I put this
investigation to
bed once and for all?
No.
We're done.
Yes, there's one thing.
Like I suspected,
when I looked at
the crime photos,
I always saw three people
at every one of the killings.
Except for...
this one.
This one had four people.
Oh, four now? Well, the
killer bring a
friend with him?
Damn it, Lee!
Hey, Task Force,
you got any idea
what any of these people
actually might look like?
I mean, that would
give us a real leg up.
Are they male?
Are they female?
It doesn't work like that.
I don't see them. I feel them.
Oh, well, okay, so does
it feel like an Anglo guy
or a Latin guy? Is he black?
Or maybe he's got
kind of an Asian feel?
Wow, she's right.
You are an ass.
Thanks for that
vote of confidence.
Yeah, and as far
as this not being
what it appears to be?
Well, there's
an old expression:
If it walks like a
duck and talks like a duck,
then it is a duck.
Personally, I think
you're up to your knees
in a duck pond, Detective.
rdon me, um, Mr.
District Attorney,
The Third
Precinct keeps calling,
and they were wondering if
you could run down there.
Apparently, they have
some kind of situation.
All right. Tell
them I'm on my way.
Allison, Detective Scanlon.
Idiot.
Sorry to make
you come across town,
but the chief
wanted to cut you in early.
Cut me in early on what?
Our guys were called
to a homicide last night
and they brought this guy in,
but nobody can
quite get a fix on whether
he's the
victim or perpetrator.
And he's like, "I'm
doing an experiment.
A social experiment."
And he's standing
there in my house;
ski mask, you know?
He's about my height,
I think. I don't know.
And he's pointing a
gun at me and my wife.
And I'm like...
"experiment"? What
kind of experiment?"
And I'm talking, you know?
'Cause I'm
thinking. Talking is good.
Talking is better
than dying, you know?
And he's like, "You love her?"
He's pointing at my wife.
I'm like, "Of course I
love her. She's my wife!"
He goes, "Okay,
here's the deal.
You shoot her and
we'll let you live."
And I'm like, "What?!
Are you... are you insane?"
He's like, "No,
I'm a social scientist,
you bourgeois A-hole!"
And he takes his
gun and he puts it
right under my chin, right
here, and he
goes, "Okay, lab rat,
"you shoot her or
I'll shoot you both.
Make a choice. You
wanna live? You wanna live?"
And I'm like, "Yeah,
of course! Of course!
And he goes, "Okay, so do it.
Choose life! Shoot her!"
And she's wailing,
you know? She's screaming,
and you can't even make
out what she's saying, even.
And for a
second, like, I almost
thought she
was saying, "Do it.
And I'm thinking,
"Do it? Shoot my wife?"
I can't! I can't do
that. I can't do that!
And then, and then the gun
was... the gun was so light...
the gun was so...
And then I'm
thinking, "Oh, I see,
"I get it. It's a joke.
It's a freakin'
joke," you know?
And he's got
his gun right here
and she's
wailing, so I did it.
I pulled the trigger.
Mr. Conrad,
so am I to understand
that you're now
admitting to what happened?
Admitting that you
did kill your wife?
No. No.
It's like I said before.
I did pull the trigger,
but nothing happened.
It went "chik". Nothing.
It's an empty gun.
And that guy laughed.
And he goes, "You're
the first one to ever do it.
"You're the first
one I've ever met.
Congratulations."
And then he just
stood behind me, holding me
and sudden I
felt his gun leave
my chin and (
mimics gunshot ).
He shot her.
( mimics gunshot )
And I could
feel... I could feel her...
her blood, I guess.
Skin and stuff hit me in
the face... in the chest.
And then he just... handed
me the gun, the real gun...
and he left.
So what do you make of that?
Yeah, track down Lee Scanlon.
Ask him to come down to
the Third Precct right away.
Ask Allison to
come along, too.
Okay.
DEVALOS: And do you have any
idea how this mysterious man
in a ski mask gained entry
to your home, Mr. Conrad?
No. I have no idea.
I came home from
work, I walked in the door,
and there he was, a
gun to my wife's head,
talking about how he's
this social scientist guy
and how we've
been specially chosen
to be part of his experiment.
So let me ask
you this question.
Why do you think a killer
would go
through all the trouble
to find a way to
discreetly enter your home,
confront you and your wife,
kill your wife
in cold blood
right in front of you
and then let you live?
Don't you
think he'd worry that
you'd do the very
thing you're doing now?
Describe what happened,
describe him to the police?
Why would he do that?
I... I don't know.
You think I did it, don't you?
I didn't say that, sir.
Well, you don't have to be a
mind reader to figure it out!
I guess because I did it.
He told me he'd let
me live if I did it,
and then I did it.
( sniffling ): I
mean not really, but...
I showed him that I could...
that I would.
I mean, think about it.
I know it sounds crazy.
I mean, it is crazy!
But maybe it's not that crazy.
I mean, here I am,
telling you
about what happened,
and you're thinking
I'm crazy or I'm lying.
Which is what he
wants you to think, right?
So, actually if you think
about it, it's not that crazy.
In fact, that's pretty smart.
Right?
He's heading over
to the crime scene.
He asked me to ask you
if you'd like to go along.
So I hear you
wanted some company.
Did someone have
a change of heart?
Nah. Same old heart.
Remember
yesterday when you said
you thought there
were four people there
when my sister
and her husband...
Didn't make
sense to me at first...
then I remembered.
My sister was three-and-a-half
months pregnant when she died.
Hey, Joe, this is Bill.
Gosh, I hope I'm
calling the right number.
Uh, listen,
Jenny and I would love to
come to the surprise party.
We both remember meeting
Allison at the
company Christmas party
and we've been meaning to
call and get
together ever since,
so this is, uh,
this is perfect.
Anyway, count us in.
Uh... Friday night.
Your house. 8:00.
See ya.
That was great.
It's incredible.
Thanks. And, uh,
I can count on you?
Mm-hmm.
Two tickets. "Our Town".
At the Church. Starring you.
Break a leg.
How does this work?
I don't know.
Whoever made
me this way forgot
to give me an
instruction book.
I like those.
Could you stop doing that?
Stop what?
I think I need some fresh air.
You feeling any better?
You seen many dead
people in your life?
The reason I ask is, I've
actually seen quite a few.
It's funny you
come to a crime scene,
you see them laying there,
the first place
you look is their eyes.
You know better, but
it's just... natural.
You want to believe there's
some kind of answer there,
but there's nothing.
For me anyway,
but... not for you, huh?
There were
flashes, like from a camera.
And you know
what else is strange?
The other night, I... I
dreamt in
pictures... photographs.
I mean, have to
keep reminding myself
that we're looking for a
killer, not a photographer
Excuse me. I'll be right back.
Planning a wedding?
Shopping for a photographer?
I don't know.
SCANLON: Just an instinct.
( Bridgette screaming )
Bridgette! If you don't
let me brush those knots
out of your hair, we're
going to have
to chop it all off!
Don't let her
chop my head off!
JOE: Chop your head off?
Aw, you bringing your
work home with you again?
Let me at her!
Um, can I make a suggestion?
Why don't we
call in an expert.
Somebody with
beautifully maintained hair,
who also knows a thing or
two about dealing with kids.
Hmm...
Ariel!
Oh, no!
( chuckling )
Or you can do it yourself.
Foiled again!
Ow!
Wow. You one of those people
who can talk out their ass?
It's not funny.
Kind of funny.
Great. We have a message.
( phone beeps )
( sharp exhale )
Hey, it's Bill...
Hmm, nice. It's someone
named Bill from your office.
Hmm. He's calling to
RSVP for my surprise party!
Cool.
You're actually
very good at this.
You're quite the
little the party planner
and quite the surpriser.
Hey, you don't buy
candy for a dentist,
you don't give
a kitten to a vet,
and you don't waste time
trying to surprise someone
who's always one
step ahead of you
8:00. Hmm.
Tomorrow.
Friday night at your house...
Here?
( phone beeps )
You invited everyone here?
Well, yeah. Why not?
Well, for one thing, who
are you gonna get to clean
all day tomorrow so you'll
be ready to have this party?
You're joking.
Well, I mean as long
as you're not working.
It's... it's my party!
It's supposed to be
for me! It's my birthday!
That's all the
more incentive to...
( phone ringing )
Aren't you going to get that?
Why? It's one of the
wicked stepsisters calling
to say she's
coming to the ball,
but she wants me to
stop and clean her fireplace.
Hello?
Yes.
For you.
Hello.
Yes, Detective Scanlon?
Sorry to be
calling your house so late,
but you want to hear an
interesting coincidence?
The man who
photographed Conrad's wedding
also
photographed Tim and Donna's.
Wow.
And my sister's.
SCANLON: Feeling like
paying him a visit tomorrow?
Work.
Tomorrow.
Hmm.
Absolutely.
As long as I'm
home before 8:00.
Okay. Thank you.
( phone beeps )
( pounding on door )
SCANLON: Mr. Rondell?
This is the Phoenix
Police. I have
a search warrant.
You want to open
up and let us in?
( thudding )
( yells )
Go, go, go, go!
It's clear, it's all clear!
( voices over
police dispatch )
Any idea how your
sister found this guy?
She really doesn't want
you to see her like this.
OFFICER: Detective?
Mr. District Attorney?
Look at the files he
kept on these people.
My God.
What? First he'd
photograph their weddings,
then it's...
like he owned them.
He studied them. They
were his test subjects.
There's gotta be
hundreds of contact sheets
of this couple's
comings and goings.
They didn't even know
th were being watched.
Going to work,
getting the mail,
birthday parties...
Death.
He'd give them a year
of marriage, and then...
just after their
first anniversaries...
I think you need
to look at these.
These must be
works in progress.
We've got wedding photos,
some surveillance, but no...
I wonder who's next.
This couple. Tonight.
How in the hell
do you know that?
Your sister told me.
( sniffling )
( sobbing )
Welcome home.
We've been waiting for you.
Close the door,
please, and step
into the room,
where we can see you?
Thank you.
We're conducting an
experiment, a
social experiment.
And your lovely
bride and I would both
very much like you to
participate, if
you would just...
Who are you?
I'm Detective Lee Scanlon
with the Phoenix Police,
and you're
under arrest for the
murder of my sister, Lorraine.
Now drop that gun, and
I'll read you your rights.
( distant siren wailing )
Or you can try
something stupid
and we'll get a priest in here
to read you a
different set of rights.
( siren continues )
( car pulling to a stop )
Please, give me an excuse.
( sobbing )
( distant siren wailing )
Put your hands
behind your head.
You have the right to
remain silent. Fascinating.
It's an absolutely
fascinating display.
Anything you say
can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
You have the
right to counsel. You
so obviously
wanted to kill me...
If you are unable to retain
counsel... and
easily could have.
...counsel will be
appointed for you....
And yet, convention
and society and a host
of other outside
forces convinced you
that your own survival...
...you will
still have the right...
...depended upon
your ability to suppress
your desire for
revenge and let me live,
and that's fascinating. ...are
you willing to
answer questions
without an attorney present?
I'm so glad I
was here to see it.
That was
extraordinarily
courageous, Lee.
I'm genuinely proud
to call you my friend.
Ah, there was
nothing courageous about it.
I knew he wasn't going to
shoot. Not her.
Not me. Not anybody.
Oh, and how did you know
that? Oh, Allison told me.
I did not! I did
not say... You didn't?
...a word to you
before you went in there.
Damn. I must need a drink.
Anyone interested?
Wait a second.
What time is it?
Uh, 7:35. I do
believe I'm buying
Oh, my gosh. I
completely forgot.
I have to rush
home and get surprised.
But I'll take a
rain check on that drink.
DEVALOS: Oh,
right, right, right...
Hey, guys!
Sorry I'm late for dinner!
Things got crazy at work...
and...
Hello?
Anybody home?
Okay.
I'll play.
Hello?
( sighs )
JOE: Happy Birthday, baby.
I don't get it.
Where is everybody?
Well, let's see...
Ariel is sleeping over at
her friend Megan's house.
Bridgette's sleeping
over at Hannah's house.
And Marie is at my
sister's in Prescott.
What?
Surprised?
Confused.
Oh. Did I leave out the part
where you and I go to Mexico
for the weekend
for your birthday?
( car horn honks )
That would be the
limo to take us...
to the airport.
What about all
the party supplies...
( chuckling ):
and the phone calls?
It's not easy
surprising someone
who's always one
step ahead of you.
You bastard.
Thank you.
Now hurry up and
put together a bag.
I'm going to go
out and make sure
the driver has
the champagne chilling
and gloat to
myself over the fact
that I finally
put one over on you.
( chuckles )
I don't know if I
can get ready that fast.
Well, put your
track shoes on, baby,
'cause our plane
leaves in exactly one hour.
Hey, Hot Lips, hurry up.
Driver says there's traffic.
I'm packing as fast as I can!
Okay, I'm ready.
I can't believe
you did this to me.
I hope I didn't
forget anything.
Just wait till
your birthday comes.