Season 3 - Episode 3
The Gangs of Camden County
Subtitles by Loky, Ricana and Jarick
Transcript by swsub.com
When you're in prison,
nobody trusts you to do the simplest
things you used to take for granted.
I don't understand why they're so touchy
about us having our own nail clippers.
Yeah, seems kind of silly.
But last year an inmate used a pair
to cut off another guy's arm.
Took a week and a half.
Big lawsuit.
Oh, I forgot. I'm supposed
to take you to the warden.
- The warden?
- Yeah.
I got so caught up watching you
cut your nails, I lost track of time.
Do you mind if I tell him we're late
cause you resisted a little?
I guess not.
Great, thank you so much.
Got make it believable.
No, don't rub it.
It only makes it worse.
It hurt to get maced in the eyes,
but Randy miss me so much,
he felt like
he'd been maced in the heart.
So hoping to join me in prison,
he stole a car.
Oh, my God, I'm stealing a car!
I'm stealing a car!
Come and get me!
Then he waited to get arrested.
And waited...
and waited.
And after three days, he gave up.
Then Randy had another not so good idea.
Excuse me, Officer.
What's the name of that killer that's
killing all the people at truck stops?
The Truck Stop Killer.
That's me.
We already caught that guy.
See that graffiti over there?
- I did that.
- Really?
That's nice work.
My wife's been looking for somebody
to do a mural in the baby's room.
Would you do it for 50 bucks?
They're not going to send you
to prison for slapping a cop.
And even if they did, you know the odds
you'd be sent to the same place as Earl?
Seven.
Seven what?
Seven going to prisons?
That don't even make sense.
Twelve?
I'm going to bail you out because
I promised Earl I'd take care of you,
and I'm a woman of integrity.
Just be thankful your brother's
in prison for a felony I committed.
My uncle once slapped a cop.
He got 12 years in the penitentiary.
Guess what color he was.
Lucky.
Oh, wait, that's not color.
As warden,
Jerry Hazelwood was responsible
for oversee in the prisoners.
Thing was,
he didn't like seeing prisoners.
You wanted to see me... Warden?
Sir?
Sir Warden?
Nice work on helping that Camden Scout
make his parole a couple days ago.
As a reward,
I would like to give you a certificate
for one week off your prison sentence.
And a coupon for 20% discount
at the prison store.
A week off my sentence.
Plus, I like those coffee mugs they sell.
And I always thought
they were about 20% too much.
Well, you were a big help.
Lord knows,
I need all the help I can get.
Don't tell anyone, but this being
a prison warden... it's hard.
The warden used to have
a pretty sweet life,
but then his wife became governor
and ruined all his fun.
Jerry and I are honored to be living
in the Governor's Mansion,
and to be a part of
its distinguished history...
What? I have underwear on.
And so the governor decided
to get Jerry a job.
Unfortunately,
the first job didn't work out.
Training?
These guys don't need training.
We're the National Guard,
we're ever going to fight in a war.
So his wife made him a warden.
But he just kept making mistakes.
Like letting a company hire
prison labor to make something
that probably
shouldn't be made inside a prison.
And there was his mandatory:
"Bring Your Daughter to Work Day".
And I bet with that ladder incident,
nobody talks about
the 740 inmates that didn't escape.
I like that.
You're a prison-half-full kind of guy.
Anyway...
I've got this problem
with these two gangs.
It's kind of an ebony-ivory
sort of thing.
Only the ivory is a spanish gang,
so it's...
ebony and spanish.
The gangs the warden was talking about,
had one thing in common:
they hated each other.
So, the warden tried keep the peace
by taking the leader
of the latin gang, Hector
and the leader
of the black gang, Jamal,
and locking them in solitary
together for a month.
The warden was a big fan
of that TV show The Odd Couple,
and thought if it didn't work out,
then at least there'd be some laughs.
All right, open it up.
Sure enough, after a month together,
they hated each other more than ever,
and the gang violence continued.
You get these two gangs
to stop fighting,
I'm going to give you
another certificate.
This time,
for one month off your sentence.
A month?
I'm in.
All right, just a little
reward of advice.
These fellas can smell fear.
You got to let them know
who's boss from Jump Street.
You got to stand taller than they do,
you got to speak louder than they do,
you got to be tougher
than they are, you got...
The warden was going to give me
a certificate for time off my sentence
if I could stop the gangs from fighting.
First thing I had to do
was figure out what started it.
Balls.
And so I convinced the warden
to get another ball.
That way both gangs could play
and everyone would be happy.
More balls.
Too many balls.
Your ex-wife and current brother
are here to see you.
They, uh, they look mad.
Why can't people just be nice
to each other, Ron?
People need guarding, Earl.
That's all I know about them.
I had to go bail out this dummy
and miss my Brazilian wax.
If I go into labor now, I'm gonna be
all stubbly on my home video.
I didn't ask you to bail me out.
You could have gone
to Brazil if you wanted.
It's so humiliating.
The police tought Randy was my husband.
Although they thought Darnell was
my driver, that was flattering.
I miss you, Earl.
It's all he ever talks about.
He's making me crazy.
Randy, I miss you, too,
but you got to get used to the fact
that we can't be together right now.
I brought us a Snowball.
We can unscrew it, and I'll eat the top
and you can eat the inside.
Kind of like we used to do
when we were kids.
Oh, God, somebody turned
the sprinkler on again.
- Shut up!
- You shut up.
Unfortunately, living in
the trailer together
wasn't any easier for Joy and Randy
then living in solitary was
for Hector and Jamal.
Knock it off.
Both of you.
I want you to look Joy and
find one nice thing to say about her.
Go on.
I suppose she does have a nice rack.
Was that so hard?
Now, Joy, you say
something nice about Randy.
He has been remembering more
to flush the toilet,
especially after a big job.
I'm trying.
And I appreciate that.
It was working.
And suddenly I had an idea.
Ron, I have to see the warden.
What? You're leaving?
What about our snack?
Sorry, Randy,
I'll have to take it with me.
Is that a Snowball, Earl?
- Sure is, Ron.
- I love Snowballs. Especially the top.
Really?
Cause I only like the insides.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Stupid bad-guy zookeeper
is eating my Snowball.
The warden was happy to let me use
his office to try my experiment.
Mostly cause it meant
he could leave and go see a movie.
Thanks for agreeing not to kill
each other while we try work this out.
I want you to say
one nice thing about Jamal.`
You don't want to be photographed saying
something nice about him, is that it?
Fine.
I'm not giving up on you guys.
We're going to stay here
as long as it takes for...
So...
you're kissing.
What's with that?
I'm not going to lie anymore.
Jamal is my everthing.
I can't hear that enough.
Then they explained what really
happened insolitary that month.
But after a few days,
they were worn out.
At the beginning, it was awkward.
Eventually, they started talking.
And it turned out
they had lot in common.
Both of them didn't like spiders
or negative people
or being startled while taking drugs.
- It sucks.
- It does suck.
And a few days later, well...
it was a relationship.
You have incredible eyes.
Fierce like an eagle,
but soft like a water bed.
When their time in solitary was up,
they knew they'd have
to keep their feelings secret
so as to not undermine their authority
as vicious gang leaders.
Well, I guess this is it then.
I'm sad.
This time together
has been so special for me.
I'm sad.
All right, open it up.
- I'll see you in my dreams.
- I'm sad.
And so they pretended
to still hate each other.
They couldn't be together,
but they couldn't stand to be apart.
When their longing
for one another got too great...
well, they got together
the only way they could.
- I missed you.
- Squeeze my buttocks.
So you make your gangs fight just so
you can have a few seconds together?
In fairness, they also enjoy fighting.
You guys should just be honest
about how you feel.
You could be prison role models.
We could use more of those.
Or one.
You know what, I think he's right.
I want to be honest.
I'm sick of living in the shadows.
Puss, we've talked about this.
My gang will never accept you.
So what? I'm not good enough for them?
You're just not the right color, Jamal.
Plus the gay thing.
They'll think it's icky.
Well, I need more from you than
just an occasional punch in the throat.
If I can't have that,
I don't want anything.
Don't.
But you guys aren't going
to fight anymore, right?
Unfortunately, Jamal felt scorned,
and that meant all-out war.
I got the spoon last time.
Hopefully,
the guy you're fighting has soup.
Now just so we're clear.
You'll only get a month-off certificate
if you increase the peace,
not decrease it.
That I could have done on my own.
Sir, I'm doing my best.
Your best has gotten me an infirmary
full of stab wound victims,
not to mention a guy
with a bucket stuck on his head.
They're not sure that thing's
ever going to come off.
Yeah, they're already calling him
"Bucket Head."
I'll level with you.
I have a fraternity reunion coming up,
and if I'm not employed,
Slime Cracker and Man Boobs
are gonna tease the crap out of me.
I'll fix it.
While things were getting
worse in prison,
they were finally getting better
for Joy and Randy.
Joy, I have a question
and Darnell won't help me.
- It's a book, Randy.
- I know.
I figure the only way I can be with Earl
is to try to become a prison guard.
I think it's a dangerous job for him.
I mean, look at his reaction time.
Randy, I'm going to slap you.
He's like a snake in winter.
Is this a full-time job
that'll get you out of the house
so I don't stare at you sitting
on my couch like a uncooked biscuit?
And part of what you just said
hurt my feelings.
I'm sorry, Randy.
Let me make up for it,
by helping you study.
We'll start slow.
"True or false?"
"If I was held hostage,
I would sue the city."
False?
That's right.
If I was going to fix the gang problem,
I needed to fix the romance problem.
I started by stealing
Jamal's sweaty shirt.
Since Jamal was
the one feeling scorned,
I had to get Hector
to make the first move.
Lights out.
Next I talked to Homer,
who works in the prison laundry.
Other than once killing
nine people on a party boat,
he's a real nice guy.
Thanks, man.
While Hector was watching
Jamal lick his ice cream,
Randy was hoping
he could lick his prison guard test.
Then he waited for the results.
Are you Randy Hickey?
Tell me I didn't get that one wrong.
Mr. Hickey, you scored 55%.
I think I'd like
to play the race card.
How do I do that?
Randy might not have gotten
the results he wanted, but
it looked like I was starting
to get the results I wanted.
I miss Jamal.
Go talk to him.
Tell him you want him back.
And then your gangs can stop fighting.
I can't go over there.
His people will kill me.
You tell him.
I'll write down
what I want you to say.
All right, but...
since I have to read this,
nothing too embarrassing.
"You're my pouty-lipped he-slut."
"My chocolate-covered man Candy."
You know what,
I'm going to just cut to the chase.
Hector's sorry,
and he wants you back.
He broke my heart, Earl.
I can never trust him again.
Tell him it's over.
Then kiss him hard for me
and squeeze his nipples.
He likes that.
That's all he said? "It's over"?
But that's no reason to keep fighting.
These things happen.
Sometimes people
just can't be together.
I can't live without him.
There's times we all have to live
without the people we love.
That's what sadness is all about.
Would you want to live
in a world without sadness?
Without sadness,
we wouldn't know joy...
or love.
And love is what makes life worth.
Tell Jamal...
I'll always love him.
Hector, where you going?
We're all lining up for lunch.
Come on, fish sticks.
It turned out Hector would rather die
then live without Jamal.
And seeing that made Jamal realize that
he couldn't live without Hector either.
So he tried to get him off the fence.
Jamal's gang assumed
he was just beating their sworn enemy
as he was being electrocuted,
which they thought was cool.
- Hector, you crazy fool.
- I can't go on without you, Jamal.
Then be with me. Always.
We'll find a way.
I love you.
You're the first thing I've ever
said that to that I haven't killed.
Get him!
Get him! Stomp him! Get him!
With Hector and Jamal back together,
I convinced the warden
to let them use his office once a month
to work out the gang's differences,
alone and in private.
That sounds like it's gonna be
a tough negotiation.
I would not want to be
in the middle of those two.
Cause they're
definitely fighting in there.
That's what's happening.
Two straight guys fighting.
And with Hector and Jamal
able to be together every month,
the gang violence stopped and
I earned another month off my sentence.
Congratulations, Earl.
So what are you going to do
with your five weeks off?
- It's almost two years away, so...
- Fine, don't tell me.
We'll just be work friends.
I get it.
It felt good to see everyone
on the yard finally getting along.
It also felt good to realize that,
no matter how difficult it may be,
if two people want to be together,
well, they'll somehow find a way.
I took the guard test and got 55%.
That's the highest score
they've had this year.
And my cholesterol tests
were off the charts.
Keep walking, Ron.
First, they did fight.
But after a few days,
they were worn out.
At the beginning, it was awkward.
Eventually, they started talking.
And it turned out
they had lot in common.
Both of them didn't like spiders
or negative people
or being startled while taking drugs.
- It sucks.
- It does suck.
And a few days later, well...
it was a relationship.
You have incredible eyes.
Fierce like an eagle,
but soft like a water bed.
When their time in solitary was up,
they knew they'd have
to keep their feelings secret
so as to not undermine their authority
as vicious gang leaders.
Well, I guess this is it then.
I'm sad.
This time together
has been so special for me.
I'm sad.
All right, open it up.
- I'll see you in my dreams.
- I'm sad.
And so they pretended
to still hate each other.
They couldn't be together,
but they couldn't stand to be apart.
When their longing
for one another got too great...
well, they got together
the only way they could.
- I missed you.
- Squeeze my buttocks.
So you make your gangs fight just so
you can have a few seconds together?
In fairness, they also enjoy fighting.
You guys should just be honest
about how you feel.
You could be prison role models.
We could use more of those.
Or one.
You know what, I think he's right.
I want to be honest.
I'm sick of living in the shadows.
Puss, we've talked about this.
My gang will never accept you.
So what? I'm not good enough for them?
You're just not the right color, Jamal.
Plus the gay thing.
They'll think it's icky.
Well, I need more from you than
just an occasional punch in the throat.
If I can't have that,
I don't want anything.
Don't.
But you guys aren't going
to fight anymore, right?
Unfortunately, Jamal felt scorned,
and that meant all-out war.
I got the spoon last time.
Hopefully,
the guy you're fighting has soup.
Now just so we're clear.
You'll only get a month-off certificate
if you increase the peace,
not decrease it.
That I could have done on my own.
Sir, I'm doing my best.
Your best has gotten me an infirmary
full of stab wound victims,
not to mention a guy
with a bucket stuck on his head.
They're not sure that thing's
ever going to come off.
Yeah, they're already calling him
"Bucket Head."
I'll level with you.
I have a fraternity reunion coming up,
and if I'm not employed,
Slime Cracker and Man Boobs
are gonna tease the crap out of me.
I'll fix it.
While things were getting
worse in prison,
they were finally getting better
for Joy and Randy.
Joy, I have a question
and Darnell won't help me.
- It's a book, Randy.
- I know.
I figure the only way I can be with Earl
is to try to become a prison guard.
I think it's a dangerous job for him.
I mean, look at his reaction time.
Randy, I'm going to slap you.
He's like a snake in winter.
Is this a full-time job
that'll get you out of the house
so I don't stare at you sitting
on my couch like a uncooked biscuit?
And part of what you just said
hurt my feelings.
I'm sorry, Randy.
Let me make up for it,
by helping you study.
We'll start slow.
"True or false?"
"If I was held hostage,
I would sue the city."
False?
That's right.
If I was going to fix the gang problem,
I needed to fix the romance problem.
I started by stealing
Jamal's sweaty shirt.
Since Jamal was
the one feeling scorned,
I had to get Hector
to make the first move.
Lights out.
Next I talked to Homer,
who works in the prison laundry.
Other than once killing
nine people on a party boat,
he's a real nice guy.
Thanks, man.
While Hector was watching
Jamal lick his ice cream,
Randy was hoping
he could lick his prison guard test.
Then he waited for the results.
Are you Randy Hickey?
Tell me I didn't get that one wrong.
Mr. Hickey, you scored 55%.
I think I'd like
to play the race card.
How do I do that?
Randy might not have gotten
the results he wanted, but
it looked like I was starting
to get the results I wanted.
I miss Jamal.
Go talk to him.
Tell him you want him back.
And then your gangs can stop fighting.
I can't go over there.
His people will kill me.
You tell him.
I'll write down
what I want you to say.
All right, but...
since I have to read this,
nothing too embarrassing.
"You're my pouty-lipped he-slut."
"My chocolate-covered man Candy."
You know what,
I'm going to just cut to the chase.
Hector's sorry,
and he wants you back.
He broke my heart, Earl.
I can never trust him again.
Tell him it's over.
Then kiss him hard for me
and squeeze his nipples.
He likes that.
That's all he said? "It's over"?
But that's no reason to keep fighting.
These things happen.
Sometimes people
just can't be together.
I can't live without him.
There's times we all have to live
without the people we love.
That's what sadness is all about.
Would you want to live
in a world without sadness?
Without sadness,
we wouldn't know joy...
or love.
And love is what makes life worth.
Tell Jamal...
I'll always love him.
Hector, where you going?
We're all lining up for lunch.
Come on, fish sticks.
It turned out Hector would rather die
then live without Jamal.
And seeing that made Jamal realize that
he couldn't live without Hector either.
So he tried to get him off the fence.
Jamal's gang assumed
he was just beating their sworn enemy
as he was being electrocuted,
which they thought was cool.
- Hector, you crazy fool.
- I can't go on without you, Jamal.
Then be with me. Always.
We'll find a way.
I love you.
You're the first thing I've ever
said that to that I haven't killed.
Get him!
Get him! Stomp him! Get him!
With Hector and Jamal back together,
I convinced the warden
to let them use his office once a month
to work out the gang's differences,
alone and in private.
That sounds like it's gonna be
a tough negotiation.
I would not want to be
in the middle of those two.
Cause they're
definitely fighting in there.
That's what's happening.
Two straight guys fighting.
And with Hector and Jamal
able to be together every month,
the gang violence stopped and
I earned another month off my sentence.
Congratulations, Earl.
So what are you going to do
with your five weeks off?
- It's almost two years away, so...
- Fine, don't tell me.
We'll just be work friends.
I get it.
It felt good to see everyone
on the yard finally getting along.
It also felt good to realize that,
no matter how difficult it may be,
if two people want to be together,
well, they'll somehow find a way.
I took the guard test and got 55%.
That's the highest score
they've had this year.
And my cholesterol tests
were off the charts.
Keep walking, Ron.