THE MAGIC HOUR
Recently Randy had become
curious about hair dryers
so we borrowed one from Joy.
I really like the look, Earl,
but come on,
who has 30 minutes every morning
to spend on their hair?
You keep practicing,
little buddy.
I gave up the xylophone
and always regretted it.
Lucky kid.
Still got a shot
at being somebody.
What's going on?
It's the grand re-opening
of Mystery Funland.
These Make-A-Wish T- shirts'll keep us
from having to wait in long lines.
- I'm dying.
- I'm dying, too.
I'm not going to the funeral, Earl.
Tiny coffins creep me out.
And you still owe me 45 cents
from when I used to live here.
- We need to settle up, pronto.
- They're not sick, Randy.
Joy's just taking advantage
of Make-A-Wish.
The kid two trailers down
got to go to Space Camp
once his sickle cell kicked in.
Why should my kids suffer
just 'cause they're healthy?
I couldn't be too judgmental.
A few years back, I did a bad thing
to the Make-A-Wish people myself.
It was late New Year's Eve
and Randy drove home without me
on account of me accidentally
giving him a midnight kiss.
Which we still don't talk about.
Walking wasn't working well,
but I found
another means of transportation.
That's a giant dog!
You're going the wrong way.
Next morning, I felt like
I'd been kicked in the head by a horse,
which might have happened.
Make-A-Wish child
Buddy Zaks lost his wish today
when the pony he was to ride
in the New Year's Day parade
was tragically stolen.
So, well-wishers tried bravely
to salvage little Buddy's dream.
This sucks.
This was Buddy's last chance
to ride in the parade,
because while not
all Make-A-Wish kids are dying,
this one is.
Now here's Chick Dabney
with the weather.
It was almost ten years
since Buddy died,
so there wasn't much
I'd be able to do for him.
But I figured I'd try
to do something for his parents.
This is so cool!
I wonder if getting tattoos
hurts trees
as much as it does humans.
Hello... Mrs. Zaks?
A few years ago, I stole
your son's Make-A-Wish pony
and I'm here
to make it up him.
I mean, not to him,
'cause he's, you know...
an angel.
What's up, bro?
You stole my pony?
I thought you were dead.
I saw you on the news.
I know what happened.
He made a wish to still be alive.
Why don't they all do that?
After I told him about my list,
Buddy invited us in
and he explained how he had defied
all the doctor's expectations
about him dying.
It may surprise you,
but Camden doesn't have
the best doctors.
I've had three watches
dropped in my body during surgery,
and one of them's still in there.
So you're a movie buff?
Hell, yeah!
You spend 95%
of your teen years in bed,
- you're gonna watch some flicks.
- What's your favorite?
Without a doubt,
2 The Max.
It's all action
with Max Patrick...
CIA agent,
Navy SEAL, gigolo,
and devoted family man.
Watch as Max stops
the terrorists
from using a giant robot squid
to kill the president!
Me and Randy love squid movies.
- How'd we miss it?
- Wait.
Is that the one that started out boring
with the Renée Zellweger girl?
'Cause we walked out of that thing.
You didn't miss it
because it hasn't been made yet.
It's all up here.
And... in here.
And some of it's over here.
Stop it!
Do it again.
Wait.
Let me lick it.
I like your brother.
He likes you, too.
Wait a minute.
I like him.
He likes me.
We all like squids,
and you owe me.
You know
what we're gonna do?
We're gonna make this movie!
And it is going to be...
awesome!
Stop it!
Do it again.
Hold on.
- We're going to make a movie?
- Don't worry.
I've got plenty of books
on how to do it.
And if you want to cross me
off your list, you'll help me, man.
- You can be the producer.
- Producer?
- Look at me, Randy. I'm a producer.
- I know. I saw.
Besides sounding cool,
what exactly does that mean?
Being a producer is awesome.
You get to pay for everything
and hire everybody.
You get to make sure
that everything happens exactly
like it looks up here.
Yeah,
we can absolutely make your movie.
Or...
Nah. I want the movie.
Buddy wanted each person he cast
to fit his artistic vision.
For Max's wife,
he wanted someone who was hot,
but edgy.
Teresa!
Get your fat ass out here
and bring your noisy little brat inside.
And he seems
to have misplaced his xylophone.
- What are you looking at?
- You're perfect.
I know.
And who was I
to judge his artistic vision?
Oh, God!
Soda water, please!
It's setting!
Does anyone have a Tide stick?
This is my best irregular
Tommy Bahama.
There's our panicky scientist.
That's right, cucaracha.
Drink the poison
and bring it back to your filthy home
to feed to your babies.
Ruthless terrorist.
Nice!
Check out this great suit
I found behind the motel.
I had to kick a litter
of fresh cat babies off it,
but I left them my T-shirt.
That's a sweet suit.
We have our president.
And here's my Secretary of Cute.
Once we had our cast,
we started shooting our movie.
Okay, so...
This is the scene
where the president first hears
about the giant squid.
Everybody know what to do?
All right.
Lightning in a bottle, people!
And...
action!
Mr. President,
as per your request,
we are unfreezing
Benedict Arnold
so you can punch him
in the stomach.
While he thaws,
the vice president
has an announcement.
Mr. President,
this fax just came in.
New York City is under attack
by a giant squid.
The joint chief of staff
has declared
a state of emergency.
He is requesting permission
to go to death con six.
I didn't take this job
to let our free land
be swallowed by some squid.
Get me Max Patrick.
And then you hear a big thud
from outside and react.
What in the tarnation was that?
And then we'll cut to a shot
of the squid. Randy, you say...
I said get me Max Patrick! Now!
And then I enter.
Did somebody say my name?
Ad-lib excitement!
Cut!
You don't say "ad-lib excitement."
You just act excited like...
We have a major problem here.
Earl.
Listen...
Thanks.
Thank you.
Listen, other than Randy,
who is awesome,
everybody else stinks.
These other actors...
Patty sounds like a transvestite.
And Joy, she just keeps
looking right in the camera,
so you got to fix this.
I'll be in my trailer!
Don't worry, I'll figure it out.
Look...
Buddy isn't happy
with some of the performances.
And Joy, you got to stop
looking at the camera.
If I don't, how would
the audience know I'm talking?
He says Randy's
the only one who gets it.
Acting's easy.
You just pretend to be different people
and then talk like that.
Joy should say,
"Mr. President,
"per your request,
"we're unfreezing Benedict Arnold
so you can punch him in the stomach."
And then Patty goes,
"Mr. President, this fax just arrived.
"New York City's under attack
by a giant squid!"
See?
You can do anybody.
Are you talking to me?
Nobody else is here,
so you must be talking to me.
E... T...
phone... home.
We didn't land on Plymouth Rock!
Plymouth Rock landed on us!
I want a hard target search
of every farmhouse,
doghouse, henhouse,
in-house and outhouse.
Your fugitive's name
is Dr. Richard Kimble.
I'm not an animal.
I'm a human being.
It puts the lotion on its skin.
It does as it's told.
Put the lotion in the basket!
Choosy moms choose Jif.
Randy showing off
just made people more upset.
And it wasn't just the performances
that caused problems.
I eat terrorists for lunch
with my caviar.
I'm Max Patrick.
I am afraid of no one.
It's time for me to declare...
a jihad!
Cut! Did we get it?
I need to take a five.
Another thing I learned about movies
is special effects can be tricky.
Everybody remember, the last thing
that's gonna happen in the scene
is that my flamethrower watch goes off.
Is safety ready?
And...
action.
Mr. President, this...
The president's on fire!
Keep filming!
But the hardest part of all was
dealing with Buddy's perfectionalism.
Cut!
Earl, I need real limousines
for the motorcade.
The president needs
a kick-ass limo.
It has got to be...
awesome!
I'll be in my trailer!
Maybe you didn't see.
This is a '98 Civic,
and it's got a spoiler.
What with the screaming
and people catching on fire and all,
by the end of the week,
morale was pretty low.
So the president and Max's wife
are trapped by squids on the roof
of the White House, and it's like...
And they're all...
And then,
Max Patrick appears out of nowhere,
he saves the president
and blows up the squid
with his laser watch.
It's gonna be awesome.
- Any questions?
- How is this not gonna look like crap?
You got to trust me.
It's all gonna be done
with special effects and camera tricks,
but we only got one shot at this
while the sun is rocking
that awesome gold color.
In the business,
we call that "the magic hour".
Well, my magic hour is
when this thing is done
and we're all drinking
at the Crab Shack. Huh?
Let's go!
All right, Earl...
Call it.
And... action.
Wherever you are,
please save us.
Sorry I was late.
DC traffic is a bitch.
The fate of the free world is
in your strong, handsome hands.
Now... helicopter!
Mr. President,
I've got to get you both out of here.
Come with me.
- We have to go.
- I'm not going without you.
Don't you realize what these suction
cup bastards will do to you?
Okay, I'll go,
but not without a kiss first.
- Can I do it on the hand?
- Lips.
Cheek.
Let me check my watch
and see what time it is.
It's time for fish stew.
Explosion!
Awesome take, everybody.
Let's do a couple more.
Oh, hell, no. I quit.
I only do tongue kisses
if it's Brad Pitt or Eric Roberts.
What the heck is that smoke?
My eyes hurt,
and I have an unproductive cough.
Don't worry,
I got it from a crop duster,
it's even safe for plants.
Oh, God.
Now my nose is bleeding.
I quit.
Come on, don't quit.
I'll get you a Wet-Nap.
Your people love those.
Magic hour.
Sorry, Earl, but I quit, too.
And so will William,
if he ever wakes up again.
What's going on?
Crew call's at 10:00. It's 10:02.
What do you mean?
You were there. Everybody quit.
So what? In Hollywood,
people say they quit all the time.
Nobody actually does it.
I'm sorry, but this is Camden.
People quit everything here.
That's why
the freeway ends in a field.
But, look...
I can play the president.
And I got a blonde wig
to play your wife.
We just tape down
the button on the camera,
I can hold the boom mic
down low out of frame,
or hide it on my head under a hat.
We can do this.
Yeah, but it'll suck donkey.
You know what?
It's fine.
Things happen in this business.
Production gets cut short,
you gotta roll with the punches.
And I already got
all my dream shots.
Better to make a short,
awesome movie
than a long, mediocre one.
So, is that it?
You don't need me anymore?
One more thing.
Give me two weeks to edit the footage,
and then throw me a movie premiere.
But everybody quit.
Who's even gonna show up?
If you throw it...
they will come.
What?
If you throw it...
they will come.
Have you ever seen a movie
without Burt Reynolds in it?
Not all the way through.
A couple weeks later,
2 The Max was set to premiere.
It was the first film
shot in Camden
since the documentary
about the chemical spill,
so we got a good crowd.
As if turning down
the part of Indiana Jones
to play a bank teller
on Laverne & Shirley
wasn't bad enough.
I also made the mistake
of not nailing Penny Marshall
when I had the chance.
So what part do you play
in this movie?
What movie?
And despite the bad taste everyone had
in their mouths from the filming,
they came out to enjoy the glamour
of a Camden movie premiere.
Here come two of the film's stars,
Joy
and Darnell "The Crab Man" Turner.
So, Joy, tell the viewers
whose clothes you're wearing.
What are you talking about?
These are mine.
I meant, which designer?
I got it at Rite Aid.
Supposed to be worn the other way,
but what would you rather see,
shoulder blades or cleavage?
Sometimes I think
clothing designers are gay men.
I did all my own stunts.
I even caught on fire.
That wasn't in the script.
Turns out I've been doing
my own stunts my whole life.
I've just been calling them
accidents until now.
In my younger days,
I did some commercial acting.
See if this rings a bell.
"Pretty sneaky, sis."
I didn't say that,
but I was the sneaky sis.
I finally got everybody seated,
then realized not everybody was seated.
The man of the hour
still hadn't shown up.
Hey, Mrs. Zaks.
Where's Buddy?
The projectionist has to get
the equipment back tonight
before the janitor
locks up the school.
Earl, Buddy's not coming tonight.
Buddy's mom had
some really bad news.
There was a reason Buddy kept
storming off to his trailer.
He wasn't just
a bitchy little Hollywood wannabe.
He was a bitchy little Hollywood wannabe
who need hourly treatments.
I put a Fonzie sticker
on the IV bag today.
I thought it would make it more fun.
Turns out the doctors were right
about Buddy's health.
They were just about ten years off
on the expiration date.
I can't believe he's gone.
His one dream was
to make a movie,
and he didn't even get
to see the premiere.
Making the movie
wasn't his only dream.
Buddy had tons of crazy dreams,
and you helped him with all of them.
You'll understand
when you see this.
I decided not to tell anyone about
what happened to Buddy
until after the premiere.
I kind of figured he wouldn't want
people feeling sorry for him.
He'd rather
they just enjoy the movie.
I didn't take this job
to let our free land
be swallowed by some squid.
Get me Max Patrick.
What in the tarnation was that?
I said get me Max Patrick, now!
Did somebody say my name?
And everyone did enjoy it,
including me and his mom.
Watching Buddy's film,
I realized
what his mom was talking about.
Making that movie let him live out
every crazy dream a boy could have.
He got to meet a president.
He got to be a spy in the CIA.
He got to save someone's life.
The president's on fire!
And thanks to special effects,
Buddy finally got to ride a horse
in the 1999 New Year's Day parade.
And the best part was,
Buddy somehow
pulled off his magic hour shot.
Sorry, I'm late.
DC traffic is a bitch.
Stand back, honey.
The fate of the free world is
in your strong, handsome hands.
Here comes the chopper.
Mr. President,
I've got to get you both out of here.
Let me just check my watch
and see what time it is.
It's time for fish stew.
Lasers are awesome,
but not as awesome
as your lips, baby.
Why not put them
2 the Max?
Rocket shoes, engage.
Hey, baby, you ever been to Paris?
Buddy knew
his own sun was setting.
That's why he was
so particular about the movie,
and even though we didn't finish,
he got all his dream shots.
And everybody in the audience could see
he'd really made something special.
After that, you couldn't help
but think of your life as a movie,
knowing eventually
your own sun was gonna set,
making every hour
into a magic hour.
Buddy made us all realize
we shouldn't waste our shots
screwing around.
We should do the things we always wanted
to do while we had the chance.
Darnell tried his hand
at creating great art.
Catalina used
one of her shifts at Club Chubby
to try something
she always dreamed of.
Instead of stripping,
I'll be doing improv.
I need a location
and a kind of food.
Joy started her own clothing line.
I did it!
You made that shirt?
No, I stole the shirt.
I designed a way to make
the security tag look like jewelry.
And Randy decided to explore
things he was curious about.
And I took up the xylophone again.
And I wasn't very good,
but that didn't mean I wasn't gonna
give it my best and try to make it...
awesome.
Subtitles:
Jarick & loky