WITCH LADY
On a slow day at the Crab Shack,
me and Randy liked to bet on who
was gonna come through the door next.
I think it's gonna be
a Chinese guy named Townsend.
Randy, no Chinese guy
named Townsend's ever come in here.
I'm feeling pretty confident.
I already called a black chick
named Henrietta.
Chinese Townsend.
Crazy Witch Lady!
I heard that
if her shadow falls on you,
your blood freezes
and your heart falls out your butt.
I've heard that, too,
but I got to go talk to her.
She was #186 on my list:
"Was mean to the Crazy Witch Lady."
Every town has a spooky old lady
who lives in an even spookier old house.
In Camden, ours happened to be
on my way to school.
But every time
I tried to cut across her lawn,
- she would chase me away.
- Get away!
My birds are buried there!
So I came up
with a plan to get even.
A plan that involved
superglue and food coloring.
A plan that I'm ashamed to say
I still think is pretty awesome.
When everything was ready,
I sprang my trap.
911.
There's a Crazy Witch Lady
trying to eat a kid
at the corner of Fourth and Pine.
Come quick.
I have no respect for your property!
I'll get you.
You're trampling my hemlock!
Help! Crazy Witch Lady's
trying to kill me.
Sweet mother of God,
drop the broom, Witch Lady.
- I can't!
- Do it now, kid eater!
So, I just want to say
how sorry I am.
Mrs...
Sorry. I don't know your real name.
Young man, you are the first person
who has bothered
to ask me my name in years.
Griselda Weezmer.
I know.
It doesn't help things much.
There's got to be something I can do
to make is up to you.
I do get lonely.
Maybe you could come over for tea
tomorrow afternoon.
I'd like that.
I hear good things about tea.
Look at that cross-eyed old goofball.
God broke the weirdoes stick on her.
- That's not very...
- Hold on. I got more.
She's creepier than babies with glasses.
She smells so bad,
when she sits in the sand,
the cats try to bury her.
Listen. I've been waiting
for a time to bring this up
that wasn't premenstrual,
menstrual or postmenstrual,
but I think I'm gonna jump in.
Why do you always have
to say those kind of things?
Here we go. Always sticking up
for nearsighted babies.
It's not just nearsighted babies.
You say mean things about everybody.
It's not mean if people laugh.
What about when they cry at it,
like Eugenia did yesterday?
She set me up.
She said she thought
she could be a plus-size model.
I had to say,
"Yeah, plus-size model home."
One person cried, six people laughed.
That's all I'm saying.
The next day,
me and Randy drove over
to Mrs. Weezmer's house
so I could have tea with her.
Come on. I need you in there
to keep the conversation popping.
You like talking
about the same things old ladies do,
- like socks and joint pain.
- Say, that reminds me.
Last week, my sleeping socks
came out of the dryer so damn fluffy,
my knees didn't hurt all day.
See? This is great stuff.
She'll eat it up.
No, she won't,
'cause I'm not going in there,
it's suicide.
She'll lop off your head,
make pudding out of your blood
and trick people like me into eating it,
and I'll do it, because I love pudding.
Even if she doesn't give me a spoon,
I'll find a way.
Fine. I'll go by myself.
I'll see you in an hour,
'cause my head will still be on.
When I was kid, there was no way
I'd have been caught dead
having tea with Griselda Weezmer,
but as a grown man,
I saw that I misjudged her.
Sure, she was a little odd.
These are my mother's teeth.
Okay, a lot odd,
but she was harmless.
Your mom's teeth?
That's quite a...
Rise and shine.
What's going on, Griselda?
This is a little weird.
Last week,
I would have agreed with you.
Truth is, I haven't thought about
what you did in years,
but your big apology
brought it all back.
In a good way?
And then I got thinking about the things
that people have done to me.
That angry mob that tried to drown me
in the lake to see if I'd float.
I didn't have anything
to do with that.
I was just drinking beers
and watching from a house boat.
And then, yesterday,
when you went blabbing on,
I thought, "Griselda,
you know what you should do?
"Lure him to your house,
"drug him,
"and then stick him
in the basement."
So that's just what did.
Well, it worked.
I'm totally freaked out.
This is a...
real pants-crapper.
I guess we're even, huh?
You little scamp.
You'll never see daylight again.
When I didn't come back out
to the car,
Randy worked up his nerve to go
knock on the Crazy Witch Lady's door.
I'm looking for my brother
or any parts of him you
haven't made into pudding.
Goodness.
I didn't turn him into pudding.
We just had some tea.
He's in the video game room
playing with my wrestling action figures
and watching naughty movies.
And what other things
do boys like you enjoy?
I think you've hit everything
except for peanuts.
And there's a big bowl of peanuts.
I'm coming in.
Come on, lady.
Just please let me and my brother go,
and we'll forget
all this ever happened.
Let you go?
Don't be silly.
I couldn't possibly.
I'm having such fun.
You know what you could have
even more fun with? Money.
Thank you, but no amount of money
can beat the look of terror
in a fresh victim's eyes
as he takes a header
into the coffee table.
The feeling is exquisite!
It's what I always imagined
an orgasm might be like.
Where am I?
Locked up
in Mrs. Weezmer's basement.
We're gonna die!
And it's gonna hurt!
I guess this is good-bye, head.
Thanks for all your hard work.
Apparently, Mrs. Weezmer
had a reason to be mad at Randy, too.
A few years ago,
he'd come up with a plan
to get rid of the Crazy Witch Lady
once and for all.
Why aren't you melting?
Come on, melt, bitch!
Okay, so she's mad at both of us.
Let's just stay calm
and think of a way out of this.
Sorry.
Stopped breathing
for a second there.
Meanwhile, above ground,
Joy was still ticked off
that Darnell didn't think
she was nice.
Hey, loser...
If you had to describe me
in one word...
Mean.
Let me finish.
... and it couldn't be "hot,"
- what word...
- Mean.
Not "hilarious"?
Here's one.
If you had to describe Darnell
in one word,
and it couldn't be "black,"
what word would you use?
Can't use "black"?
It's a toughie.
How about "nice"?
I'm gonna go with "great."
Or "marvelous."
I'm really going back and forth
between great, marvelous and nice.
All right, fine.
You can use "black."
After an hour of trying
to come up with an escape plan,
Randy thought he had something
Step 1: we catch a mouse.
Step 2: we teach him sign language.
Step 3:
we throw him as hard
as we can up that chimney.
Someone's up there.
- We should yell for help.
- Okay, let's yell on three.
Damn it.
Since when does everybody like tea?
So you're telling me her MO is to kidnap
people she want revenge on?
Yeah,
but she's not just going after Mos.
She's taking straight guys, too.
I've never seen this woman before,
let alone done anything to her.
And I'm sure you haven't, either.
Kenny shouldn't have been so sure.
My fault?! How could this
possibly be my fault?
Look, ma'am,
I don't want to offend you, but, uh,
you fit a certain profile that we,
in law enforcement, call a whackjob.
But I'm not hurting anybody.
Yes, but you're different,
and that's bad.
We all have parts of ourselves
that are wrong and weird and shameful,
but it's our responsibility
to bury those parts very deeply
and go bowling
with our straight friends.
Good day, madam.
Don't give me that look.
You are turning into your mother.
Guys, blaming each other
isn't going to help us.
You were a cop. How do people
get out of this kind of thing?
They don't.
We used to find mutilated skeletons
chained up in basements all the time.
We never saved a single person.
No tears.
We've got to be strong, Bear Cub.
Back at the Crab Shack,
Joy was getting desperate to prove
she was as good a person as Darnell.
See, what people don't realize
is I got tons of, like,
secret inner niceness.
Well, niceness really is best
when no one ever gets to see it.
You're just trying to get me
to snap at you, but I won't,
because I am full of super niceness.
How can I help...
Witch!
Sorry.
- Hello.
- Pardon me.
I wondered if you could come
to my house and do me a favor.
Of course, I will do you a favor,
ghoulish old lady.
Because I am a nice person,
and favors are what nice people do.
Oh, my God, it's Joy.
This one's nasty.
She took a swipe at me
on her way to the floor.
I wasn't surprised to see Joy.
A few years ago, somebody told her
it was good luck to push over a witch.
Idiots, idiots.
If just one of you butt-nuts had been
man enough to stop the biddy,
she wouldn't have gotten to me.
Are you just down here
waiting to starve to death?
No, Joy.
We tried screaming.
And Randy's got a great mouse plan
we can pull out if we ever see one.
If you have a better idea,
we'd love to hear it.
Nope. Seems like you guys
covered every reasonable base.
All that's left for me
is to be an idiot and call 911.
She's got a cell phone!
Can I check my e-mail?
This is what I was talking about.
You have a media disease.
What the hell?
They put me through to voice mail.
It's 3:30 on a Friday.
Sharon's probably knocked off.
Her boyfriend got a house on the lake.
I'm calling Darnell.
He was a government assassin,
and he takes vitamins.
You might want to watch and see how
a real man handles this kind of thing.
Crap.
That sack has the same
ring tone as Darnell.
I wouldn't drink the tea,
so she whacked me in the head
with a giant ceramic rooster.
If you're here, then you must have done
something nasty to the old biddy, too.
See, y'all, Mr. Perfect can be
just as mean as anybody.
Who's the black calling
the kettle pot now?
Tell what you did.
Actually...
Hey, Darnell.
You see that lady over there?
- Which lady?
- That crazy lady over there.
- That lady.
- Which lady?
- That lady!
Which lady?!
Son of a bitch, Darnell.
It's like I married Jesus nicer brother.
Makes me want to kill somebody.
Let's start with the woman
that locked us up.
That's a good idea.
I learned on the force
that if you punch an old person's head
from the correct angle,
their skull pretty much
turns to powder.
Let's do this!
She's coming.
Tell me the angle!
Hi, everybody.
How did you find us?
What are you doing?
Mrs. Weezmer lured me over here
and tried to drug me,
but I've had so many roofies
slipped in my drinks,
I've developed quite a tolerance.
She was trying so hard,
and she looks a little like my aunt.
Anyway, here I am.
Like Joy, Catalina had grown up with
a lot of superstitions about witches.
And just when the little blind boy
turned to the tree and said:
"Mommy, why is the floor so cold?"
The frozen lake cracked under him...
and he drowned.
That is so sad.
I did it!
I captured the tear of a witch.
I shall live forever!
Seriously, what the hell is
with sticking people in burlap sacks
- before you kick them down the stairs?
- It's more dramatic.
She's right. It is dramatic.
No, I never did anything bad to her.
The old bitch is just crazy.
I can't tell you the number of times
I've been out working
and she's been standing there
and staring at me.
It's creepy is what it is.
And she wonders why I took
Dad's side in the divorce.
She's my mom.
Hookers have moms?
Patricia!
As long as you are under my roof...
and my kitchen floor,
there will be no smoking
in this house.
What are you going to do, ground me?
If grounding worked, you wouldn't be
sleeping with men for money
and food and gasoline.
Now, what was I here for?
Oh, yes.
- I'm going to kill one of you.
- What?
I have a lot more people to kidnap,
and we're running out of space.
Now,
I'm not a monster.
I'm going to let you folks decide
which one of you I stab and stab
and stab until you're dead.
Not it!
Good luck, suckers.
It's bad enough being kidnapped
and chained in a basement,
but when the kidnapper tells you
to pick somebody to get stabbed,
relationships show the strain
pretty fast.
Everybody, calm down.
- We got to figure out what to do here.
- We know what to do.
We decide who we'll miss the least,
and the others get on with our lives.
Good idea.
I say we give her the bitch.
You better be talking
about your boyfriend.
That's the kind
of mindless hate speech
that proves the world would
be better off without you.
But if I don't get the votes for that,
I say we snuff the whore.
- Why?
- Hookers are killed every day.
Face it, you're living
on borrowed time.
Darnell, you're a nice guy.
Why don't you just volunteer
to be killed?
I'll give you a ride to the airport,
but I'm not dying for you.
Nobody's going to die.
She's just going to stab
and stab and stab one of us until...
Oh, my God.
New front-runner: the dumb guy.
Of course. The dumb guy.
Why didn't we think of it before?
If we lie to him, he won't realize
what's happening until it's too late.
I heard that.
You burn in hell, stripper!
Look what we're doing to each other.
It's exactly what we did
to Mrs. Weezmer.
Again, never did anything to her.
Totally innocent and still might die.
- Welcome to being gay.
- Don't you see?
We labeled her as the Crazy Witch Lady,
and now we're labeling each other.
The bitch, the nice guy,
the gay guys, the stripper.
- Freaking Karma zombie.
- Okay, that, too.
But maybe this is what
Karma wants us to learn.
Look, guys.
When you label somebody,
you stop seeing them as a real person,
and suddenly, you can do
all kinds of terrible things to them.
And pretty soon, they stop seeing
themselves as a real person, too.
They just turn into that label.
Yeah, so Mrs. Weezmer acted crazy,
but after 20 years of people
treating her the way we did,
can you blame her?
Mrs. Weezmer,
we're all real sorry for what we did.
Do you mean that?
If you're going
to kill someone, kill me.
But I know you won't, 'cause...
you're not really crazy.
We drove you
to act like this because...
of what we did.
It's okay.
It's all okay now.
Crazy Witch Lady stabbed me!
It hurts so much!
Sorry, Mom.
Collect her tears!
We can all live forever!
Turns out, Mrs. Weezmer was crazy,
and so the courts placed her
in a home for the mentally frazzled,
where they could give her the help
and care she needed to get well.
And we all found ourselves
making a little extra effort
not to let other people's labels
define who we were.
Joy did what she could to show Darnell
she really could be nice.
Here's some sugar peas
for my sugar pea.
Hope you enjoy it.
And Darnell knew
Joy would be happier
if she didn't feel like
she was married to a saint.
Bitch, I hate peas!
Thanks, baby. That's all I need.
Just act like a mean bastard
every once in a while.
And I decided
to spend a day relaxing
and show that I wasn't always just
"that guy with the Karma list."
And Randy got himself
a "word of the day" calendar,
so he could show people
he wasn't always dumb.
This beer obviates the need
to go to the Crab Shack.
Obviate.
And Patty?
Patty was called a lot of things,
but the one label she never
really lived up to was daughter.
She decided to fix that.
And after Mrs. Weezmer
spent some time
being seen as a mom
instead of a crazy witch lady,
she was well enough to come home.
And that gave us a chance to treat her
like a person with no labels at all,
which meant that I could finally
cross her off my list.
I'll do it later.
Subtitles:
Jarick & loky