Sorry, I didn't mean to wake you.
It's all right.
I'm just glad you're still here.
You didn't think I would be?
Well, you're a woman
of mystery, Paige.
The Celtic Wheel of Being.
Four elements, all balanced,
all connected to each other.
How did you know that?
Nobody knows that.
I just...
...read a lot about different things,
sometimes magic things.
Do you ever read
about magic things?
No, I just got it because
I thought it would look cool.
I'm joking. I'm kidding.
Come on. Let the voice mail get it.
Oh, it's my sister. Hello?
I found a way to vanquish
the leader of the Creepers.
Okay, not a good time.
Sorry, but the potion's
already been made.
Strike while the iron's hot.
No can do.
Look, we take him out,
we take out his entire clan,
which means there's
no demons left out there
- to threaten the Wiccanning.
- Timing bad.
What part of that
don't you understand?
Okay, fine.
If you don't want your nephew
to be blessed by his ancestors
and you don't mind him
falling prey to evil...
- All right, all right.
- Is there a problem?
Always.
- What, are you leaving?
- No, I'm just going to the bathroom.
I'll be right back. Promise.
- All right, let's get it over with.
- Oh. Sorry.
Yeah, me too. What do you got?
You summon, I will vanquish.
Demons who dwell
In slivers oF night
Uncloak your shadows
To witches' sight
Creepers, check.
- We done here?
- Yes. Sleaze away.
- Yeah, well, at least I get some.
- Yeah, yeah.
Paige?
I'm sorry, I didn't hear you.
You didn't hear me?
You don't have to hide in here.
I know what you're doing.
- You do?
- Yeah.
You smoke.
Okay, so we have Wood Mist,
which is kind of natural and earthy,
or Rouge Sensation,
which definitely has that...
More of that, you know,
"va-va-va-voom" feel.
You're a guy. What do you think
Jason will like more, huh?
We got this one or this one.
Okay, Rouge Sensation it is.
Very good.
You are so cute. Yes, you are.
Your grandmother is just gonna
eat you up when she meets you.
But no spitting up
and none of that toxic poop
that you like to do,
because she hasn't been around
babies since she was alive, okay?
Piper is gonna freak if Wyatt's not
down in his Sunday best in, like, five.
- Hi.
- I know, I got a little sidetracked.
Hey, what's with
the come-hither makeup?
Jason called from his corporate jet,
and I'm gonna meet him at the airport.
- Oh, he's back from Hong Kong.
- Yeah, just for the day.
International booty call.
Most impressive.
Hey, there's a minor
in the room, Paige.
Sorry. But you know
what will be good?
Piper and I don't have to see you
moping around the house anymore.
I was not mopey.
You are too mopey.
Okay, that's just because
I missed him,
and I didn't expect to miss him
as much as I did.
I'm just curious. Has anyone ever
tried the truth spell that's in the Book?
Yes, and don't.
- Don't what?
- Don't try it, especially not on Nate.
I wasn't going to.
Be good.
Okay, fine, so maybe I was.
But how else am I supposed to find out
if he can handle the big, dark secret?
Don't you think it's a little early in
the relationship to start thinking that?
No, I don't think so. He's the first guy
I've really liked since Glen
and I actually think he might be able
to handle my being a witch.
Really? How do you know?
I know this sounds insane,
but he's got this kind of cool, mystical
Celtic tattoo, and he actually knows
what it means.
You could be on the cover of GQ,
you're so handsome.
I don't think it would really hurt
anything if I did the spell,
because, you know,
it does wear off after 24 hours,
and he'd forget everything anyway.
What's the harm?
It could hurt a lot. You never know
what you'll get when you cast that.
I know what I'll get if I don't.
I'm gonna have to dump him.
It's not gonna work otherwise.
- Come on, hurry up!
- Okay, we're coming!
So you think the green outfit is cute?
Because I can have them put him
in the one with the clouds on it.
It's her great-grandson. I don't think
she's gonna care what he's wearing.
She's not coming
as a great-grandmother.
She's coming in an official capacity
as the matriarch of our family.
Well, she's not gonna come at all
unless we summon her.
Okay.
Hear these words, hear my cry
Spirit From the other side
Come to me, I summon thee
Cross now the great divide
Well, it's about time, Piper.
What took you so long?
Hello to you too, Grams.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm just so excited.
- How are you, my dear?
- Excited too.
- Hi, Grams.
- Leo.
So where's the little one?
Right behind you.
Grams, meet the next generation
of Halliwells.
- Baby Wyatt.
- Wyatt?
That's a silly name for a girl, isn't it?
Grams, it's a boy.
- Look at the outfit.
- What?
You didn't know?
Well, no. I mean,
I just assumed it was a...
- What went wrong?
- Wrong?
Well, I don't mean "wrong" wrong,
it's just that we've always had girls.
Well, now we have a boy.
Right, well...
Okay, well, we've got a lot of work to
do before I perform the Wiccanning.
- Work? What work?
- Are you kidding?
I'm gonna be calling every matriarch
in our family since the witch trials.
We've got to make sure
the manor is safe.
Oh, we've got that covered.
Every demon that could attack
their spirits has been taken out.
- The zombies, the rigors...
- Creepers.
- We're all set.
- What about the Necromancer?
- Who?
- Okay, you guys discuss this,
I have to pop by the airport
and pick up my friend Jason.
- Who's Jason?
- A guy, Grams.
Don't start the Wiccanning without me.
Be right back.
Actually, I have to check
on my man too.
You know, they'd be better off
with a dog.
More loyal and they die sooner.
- Excuse me?
- Oh, don't mind me.
I never had very
much luck with men.
You've been married four times.
Exactly.
So can we get back
to this Necromancer?
Yes, we should, and fast.
The last time he attacked
was during your mother's Wiccanning,
and we can't take any chance on that
happening again. So chop, chop.
Now you know why we don't
summon her more often.
Yeah.
You've got to be kidding.
Don't judge it by its size, sir.
She's not just any fairy,
she's a queen.
I don't know.
Hardly seems worth the trouble.
You forgot to put holes in the lid.
No, actually, I didn't.
Go for it, sir.
Well, that won't sustain me for long.
Okay, well, what,
maybe I should get you an ogre?
Or maybe I should just devour you.
But, sir, you need me, remember?
A century ago I didn't need anyone.
I was a powerful demon.
A ruler.
Alive!
I grow weary of it all.
Scrounging around for magical spirits
just to get a taste of life.
Actually, I do all the scrounging.
I wanna live again,
do you understand?
I wanna be resurrected.
I will be resurrected.
I am so glad you're home.
Well, if leaving means more reunions
like this, I'll go away more often.
No, don't go away ever.
I'm afraid I have to.
What do you mean, baby?
We just bought an Asian media
conglomerate, I gotta go to set it up.
Well, for how long?
Six months, maybe longer.
I got you something.
Open it.
It's a dictionary.
Chinese-American.
- Thank you.
- You don't like it?
No, I do.
It's just... I found out that I'm not
gonna see you for the next six months,
I was kind of hoping
for jewellery or something.
Well, jewellery won't help you
get around Hong Kong.
The dictionary will.
What?
Come back with me, Phoebe.
That's why I flew out,
to see if you'd fly back with me.
It leaves tomorrow morning.
Are you serious?
I can't just pick up and leave and move
to Hong Kong for the next six months.
- Why not?
- Well, for starters, I have a job.
Well, I'm your boss, I'll transfer you.
Okay, and how about my family?
My sisters
and my new little nephew?
You can use the jet
whenever you want.
It'll be at your disposal.
I missed you, Phoebe.
- I missed you too.
- Well, I don't wanna miss you again.
Come back with me.
Yeah, what's this gonna cost?
For a new thermostat?
Come on, you can do better than that.
All right.
Hey, let me call you back, all right?
- Hey.
- Hi.
Nice to see you.
What are you doing way out here?
I just... I kind of wanted
to talk to you.
- Do you have a minute?
- Yes, we don't open for another hour.
You wanna have a seat,
you want a drink?
No. It's okay.
What's the matter? You all right?
Maybe nothing, but there's
only one way to find out.
For those who want
The truth revealed
Open hearts and secrets unsealed
From now until it's now again
After which the memory ends
Did you see that?
Okay, here goes nothing.
Nate...
...I'm a witch. A real witch,
with real magical powers,
and I just kind of wanted to see
if maybe you'd be open to that.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about this.
Behind you.
- How did you do that?
- I told you, I'm a witch.
I just kind of wanted to see
how you'd feel about it
before I went any further
into the relationship.
I can see that you don't feel
so very good about it.
Let me just get my head around this.
You don't see stuff like this every day.
Maybe you would be okay with it?
Yeah. Hell, yeah.
I mean, but I always sort of thought
this stuff was real, you know,
I just didn't really know
it was really real, you know?
My God, my wife is gonna love this.
- Excuse me?
- Did I just say "wife"?
You're married?
You never told me you were married.
Yeah, and I didn't tell you
I had children either, but...
Did I just say kids too?
See, I was right. You vanquished
this demon 60 years ago.
The Necromancer is not a demon,
he's the ghost of a demon.
And it wasn't a vanquish,
I banished him back
into the spirit realm.
Well, then you should be
a little more specific in your wording.
The point is, he's had about 70 years
to find a way out of the spirit realm.
And that man, that...
That demon is nothing
if not confident.
I guess I'll take your word for it,
considering you seem to know
so much about him.
"Enjoys Clark Gable movies"?
"Favourite dinner,
lamb chops with mint jelly."
Well, I mean, you never know
what will be useful.
So, what do you suggest, that I go to
the video store and you get cooking?
Don't be so literal.
I was just trying to show
how much he craves life,
the sensuousness of it.
Food, drink, sex...
Don't! I don't wanna hear
about a dead demon doing the dirty.
He wants to be resurrected.
It says that he has dominion
over the dead.
You would think
that would be enough.
Not for him it isn't.
He only uses his power over the dead
to absorb their spirit
and get a temporary fix of life.
But he was always searching
for magical spirits
with enough power
to resurrect himself for good.
Like all the spirits
of the Halliwell matriarchs.
That's why he attacked
at your mother's Wiccanning.
Now you see why I'm so worried.
Okay, so if he's out, we'll send him
packing back to the spirit realm,
because nothing is gonna get
in the way of Wyatt's Wiccanning.
Good. And I know just the potion
to use on him too.
Let's see,
we'll need some dragonroot,
eelskin, blood wort...
You know, Piper,
I'm still surprised that you had a boy.
- Well, fifty-fifty chance.
- Not in our family.
Three hundred years
and not a male in the bunch.
I guess our family's changing.
Well, I mean, it just begs
a few questions, don't you think?
I mean, we've never had a male witch.
And, you know, men are just so...
They're just evil,
that's what they are.
They are just plain evil.
Oh, I take it Nate wasn't too happy
about you being a witch.
Nate was fine with it. It's maybe
his wife that would've had a problem.
- He's married?
- Yeah, with two kids.
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry.
I told you she should've
gotten a dog.
What did you do
when you found out?
Plenty. I mean, I'm sure plenty will
happen to him, karmically speaking.
The cheat.
Well...
...there's no wrath like a witch scorned,
I always say.
Care to take it out on him?
What measly crumbs
have you brought me this time?
Nothing you're gonna like.
- Penny!
- Penny?
What are you waiting for?
Throw the damn potion.
What?
Wait, so he called her by her name?
Penny. Yeah. Kind of weird, huh?
Yeah, and he acted like he liked her.
- That's Chinese for "excuse me."
- Fascinating.
- Did you guys vanquish him?
- He's dead, he can't be vanquished.
But we did send his sorry male ass
back to the spirit realm.
Okay, let's not jump on Grams'
male-bashing bandwagon, please.
Grams is a wise woman.
I'll be sure to let Wyatt know.
Don't worry, we're not gonna let him
grow up to be a slime bag.
Great, so let's focus on blessing him
in light and goodness.
Okay, we don't got a lot of time.
Now, white or patent leather?
That's "white."
Okay, what is with
the Chinese thing?
It's a little souvenir that Jason
brought me back from China
when he was there
on his business trip.
Business trip. Yeah, business trip.
A likely story.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- I'm just saying.
He could be leading a double life.
He could be married, he could have
a mistress, he could be gay.
You don't know.
There are many variables.
- Or he could just be perfect for me.
- Don't be so sure.
Men are full of surprises, that's all.
Funny you should mention surprises,
because he had a little surprise for me.
Paige?
Darryl's on the phone. He's pissed.
Something about your boyfriend?
He's not my boyfriend,
he's my ex-boyfriend.
What are you doing with Wyatt?
Grams was gonna spend time with him.
- Well, she didn't want to.
- What? That's ridiculous.
Really? Then why didn't she want to
touch him, change him or feed him?
Well, she's probably just resting
before the ceremony.
She said she would do it as soon
as we get rid of the Necromancer.
This has nothing to do with
the Necromancer, and you know it.
Grams doesn't like that Wyatt's a boy,
and she makes no bones about it.
- Am I really back?
- Yes.
And I summoned you
in record time too.
Bet Penny didn't count on that.
She can't fool me.
She's a spirit too. I can tell.
- Who's Penny?
- Penny Halliwell.
The witch who stole my heart.
You should have seen her.
The glint in her eye.
The way she held up her hand
and sent me hurtling into that wall.
Didn't hurt as much
as the potion did, though.
I could tell she made it herself.
The flames were excruciating.
She was furious with me.
Which can only mean one thing.
She still feels the passion, the heat.
You sure that wasn't the fire?
If only I knew why
she came back here.
Why leave a cosy eternity up there?
It could have to do
with the new baby.
Baby? What baby?
It's the talk of the underworld.
One of the Charmed Ones had a kid.
It's a powerful one too,
one we're not to mess with.
That's it!
She's here for the Wiccanning.
I'll need you to get me a troll.
No, better yet, an elf.
I'm gonna need all my energy
if I'm gonna take on Penny Halliwell.
- Grams?
- Oh, Piper, you scared me.
I didn't know you could
scare a ghost.
- We need to talk.
- About?
I think you know what about.
Leo seems to think you don't wanna
be around Wyatt for some reason,
and I'm beginning to wonder myself.
This is all my fault.
I mean, maybe if I'd lived longer,
had been around longer,
maybe things would've worked out
the way they were supposed to.
What are you talking about?
This. Wyatt.
Oh, you mean because
he's not a girl?
Piper, you know as well as I do
that the Charmed line
is supposed to be led by women,
- not men.
- Who says?
Tradition says. Destiny says.
Tell me that you didn't hope
to have a little girl,
expect to have a little girl,
just like you foresaw.
Well, of course, but so what?
"So what" is something went wrong,
terribly wrong.
This is not the baby
you were meant to have.
Grams.
You saw it when you went
to the future.
The future where Prue was still alive
and witches were burned at the stake.
- Things change.
- Not this.
It's just that I'm worried
about the family, you know.
We don't know what to expect.
I know. That's why we shouldn't treat
him any differently because he's a boy.
That's why we're going
to do the ceremony.
At the very least, he deserves that.
I'm sorry, Piper.
I can't.
Come on, this is outrageous.
I'll sue you for false imprisonment.
When I get out, I'm gonna tell
everybody about you, you witch.
For your information, spells can do
more than just make you tell the truth.
Something you might
wanna think about.
Are you out of your mind? You can't
orb in here and think that's gonna fly.
- Because it's not.
- Why not?
- Do you know what he did?
- I don't care what he did.
Get him out of here, now.
Listen to the doughnut hog.
What?
Men.
Do you know how much trouble I'm in?
The man's got constitutional rights.
Oh, constitution,
shmonstitution, Darryl.
Look, he's a jerk, fine.
But cheating is immoral,
it's not illegal.
All right, I understand that.
And I can't deny
that I'm taking some sort
of personal pleasure from this,
because I am.
But that's not the main thing
that's happening here.
I cast a truth spell.
- Oh, no.
- It's just a little one.
But it's a good thing I did. Otherwise
I wouldn't know what a jerk he is.
- This is so not my problem.
- Actually, it is.
Because if he goes out, he's gonna
be telling people that I'm a witch,
and also about my special friend,
the cop who helps the witch.
What am I supposed to do,
keep him in here indefinitely?
No, not indefinitely.
Just, like, the next 20 hours or so.
What am I supposed to tell
the other cops if they hear him?
Just tell them he's insane.
You are crazy.
This isn't about him or our legacy.
- This is about you.
- Piper, you don't understand.
That you don't want to perform
a blessing on my son?
You are damn right
I do not understand.
You see him as an innocent little boy.
But he won't be like that, not for long.
So you can't even hold him
because someday,
some very far-away day,
he will become a man?
Men cannot be trusted with magic.
They can't handle it. They're weak.
- And evil will eventually win out.
- That is silly. Look at Leo!
Oh, well, Leo. I mean, he's an angel.
You can't count Leo.
Hey, what's going on here?
Your grandmother hates her grandson,
that's what's going on.
That is not true.
Oh, I'm sorry, you just hate men,
is that correct?
No, I don't trust men.
There's a difference.
And there is a reason that
they don't last long in this family.
They're always trying to
take advantage of what we have.
- That's not true.
- Isn't it?
Look what Cole put you through. Look
what your father did to your mother.
We're supposed to give up on trying to
find love because we might get hurt?
Oh, no, you will get hurt.
- That's our legacy too, unfortunately.
- You know what, forget it.
You couldn't bless my son
with any kind of goodness
because you are too consumed
by your bitterness.
- Piper.
- And since his father is an angel,
we will take our chances
without a Wiccanning!
Leave them alone.
- Surprise.
- Piper!
Well, let's face it.
Grams would not be in this position
if she hadn't sent us after the guy
in the first place.
Not helpful. We have to
summon her back here, fast.
We can't. The Necromancer will follow,
and you don't have a way to stop him.
How did he get a clean shot at her?
Weren't you guys with her?
- We were fighting with her.
- Fighting? About what?
Later. Let's just focus
on the vanquishing and the saving.
Yeah, but I don't know how to.
It's not like we could even
vanquish him, he's a ghost.
Well, ghosts can still feel pain. Maybe I
could just orb his testicles somewhere.
Paige, there will be no talk of
testicle-orbing in front of the child.
And not around his daddy either.
Oh, criminy, I'm just trying to help.
Okay, there's got to be a weakness
in here somewhere.
I mean, he must have
a weakness, right?
Well, do mint jelly
and Clark Gable movies count?
She wrote it.
Oh, my God.
That's why she's so obsessed
with him.
Grams was
the Necromancer's lover.
- That's disgusting.
- Oh, no, I think you're right.
That would explain everything.
Grams was alive when she banished
the Necromancer, right?
- Right.
- Okay, so now she's dead.
- You sound so happy about that.
- No, that's not what she means.
The ghost-vanquishing spell.
- You gotta be dead to use it, right?
- It's worth a shot.
Your spirit is strong, Penny.
Almost strong enough
to sustain us both.
Almost.
Awaken.
No need to worry, Penny.
You're safe here.
You're well aware
of my powers, Penny.
I covet your spirit,
and any spirit I covet, I control.
You son of a...
Of course you know,
the more you fight me,
the more I know
that you still love me.
Are you crazy? I hate you.
Yes. But you only hate me
because you once loved me.
After all, we only hate those
who have gotten close to us, don't we?
Those who've gotten close enough
to touch our hearts.
You used me.
You preyed on my affections
just to get to my family.
And for that I am truly, truly sorry.
I was just trying to survive.
I never intended to
fall in love with you either.
What do you want, Armand?
What I wanted then. Life, with you!
Think about it. Think about it, Penny.
There's enough magic in
the Halliwell line to resurrect us both!
To give us
a second chance together.
All you have to do is to call up
the spirits of the matriarchs.
I'll do the rest.
No, no.
You will never make me do that.
I can if I have to.
I'll tell my granddaughters,
they will destroy you...
Oh, you haven't changed one bit.
Isn't that why you loved me?
Because I was dangerous?
Exciting?
Why your heart beats a little faster
when I'm near you?
Or when I do this?
You still love me, Penny.
You know it and I know it.
And you're going to help us both
to live again...
...forever.
As soon as we summon her,
we gotta get her straight to the Book,
because the Necromancer
is gonna be right behind her.
All over it.
All right, let's do this.
- Who is that?
- It's Jason.
Guys really do have bad timing,
don't they?
- Yeah, I kind of owe him an answer.
- Answer to what?
He asked me to go back
to Hong Kong with him.
To live.
I'll be right back.
- Now is not really a good time.
- I need to talk to her.
- I don't have much time.
- It's okay, Leo.
- What about...?
- Don't worry about it.
Come in. Come in.
- Hi.
- Listen, Phoebe, I've been thinking.
- Yeah, me too.
I shouldn't have asked you
to come with me like that.
- You shouldn't have?
- It's not that I don't want you to, I do.
I just... I think I sort of blind-sided you
with it and I feel bad about it.
- Jason...
- And it was unfair of me
to spring it on you like that, knowing
how close you are to your family.
That's really sweet...
I don't wanna pressure you
into deciding.
And I wanted you to know that if
- you need more time to think about it...
- I don't.
- You don't?
- No, I don't.
I do love my family,
and I don't wanna leave them.
But I think if I don't,
at least for a little while,
then I'm gonna wind up like my
grandmother, and I don't want that.
- I don't think I understand.
- You don't have to understand.
What time does the plane leave?
- Ten. In the morning.
- I'll be there.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Okay.
- All right, so...
- All right.
Go on, go on.
Well?
How do you guys feel
about intercontinental orbing?
We'll talk about that later.
Read.
Hear these words, hear my cry
Spirit From the other side
Come to me, I summon thee,
Cross now the great divide
They're calling you, my love.
Don't. Don't try to fight it.
You have no choice
but to do as I wish.
Welcome back, Grams.
- Girls...
- No time for apologies.
Come on, come on.
This way, this way, this way.
That is a spell to vanquish a ghost.
But only a ghost can read it.
- And that's you.
- You shouldn't have done this.
Oh, come on, Grams,
we're not that mad.
You will be.
Grams, he's gonna
be here any second.
I know, I know.
It's just that I don't think that...
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
I never meant to hurt you.
Or Wyatt.
Right. Okay, we kind of need to focus
on the demon at hand here, okay?
Incoming!
- Now, Grams!
- Grams, read the spell.
Don't bother. She's with me now.
It's time, dear.
Piper, blow him up or something.
The ghost? You want me to blow
up the ghost? He's already dead.
I call Forth From space and time
Matriarchs From the Halliwell line
Paige, the truth spell.
Use it on Grams.
For those who want
The truth revealed
Open hearts and secrets unsealed
From now until it's now again
After which the memory ends.
Penny, finish the spell.
Grams? Tell him how you really feel
about him. Tell him the truth.
I love you.
Any other bright ideas?
And now I know that
you didn't just use me,
that you really did love me too.
I still do.
I know. But the truth is
that our love isn't nearly as powerful
as the love I have for my family.
Ashes to ashes, spirit to spirit
Take his soul
Penny, what are you doing?
Banish this evil
Penny.
I am so sorry.
I never realized how much my anger,
my bitterness, affected my life.
Or yours.
But I'm most sorry for what I did
to my great-grandson and you.
And if ever I wanted a second chance,
it would be with him...
...and you.
Don't make the same mistake I did.
Don't ever give up on love.
Paige, you gotta
let me out of here sometime.
You can't keep me in here forever.
Don't worry. When the spell wears off
you won't remember a single thing.
Although I've got a couple of things
I'd like to say to you before it does.
Say it fast, will you?
You know, Paige, I've been thinking.
I've been in here a long time,
and I realize what I did to you
was really wrong.
I hope you're buying this.
You know, I thought you would
have a problem with magic,
I didn't think you would be a problem
on a basic human level.
I was gonna tell you about Morgan
and the kids at some point.
No, I wasn't.
For what it's worth, Nate, I don't
hate you. You're just too pathetic.
It doesn't matter anyway, it's gonna
be over in, like, a second.
What happened? Why am I in jail?
I don't know,
why don't you ask your wife?
- What's so funny?
- You'll never know.
A little friendly advice:
Don't ask any questions,
don't call Paige,
and walk away as fast as you can.
Is that a threat?
Actually, Nate, it is.
I'm sorry, Mr. Dean,
if we don't leave very soon,
you'll miss your meeting.
I know, I know.
- Jason!
- Phoebe!
Wow, you're cutting it pretty close,
aren't you?
Where are your bags?
- Jason...
- You're not coming, are you?
No, I'm not.
I want to. More than you know.
Well, then why don't you?
It's hard to explain.
I just feel like, for now at least,
that my place is here, you know?
That this is where I need to be.
Not forever.
I mean, God, I hope not forever.
Just for now.
I guess I should've gotten you
jewellery after all.
Hurry back.
I think he looks a little like
your grandfather.
Oh, trust me, that's a good thing.
- He was a good man.
- Nice to know.
Shall we?
I call Forth From space and time
Matriarchs From the Halliwell line
Mothers, daughters, sisters, Friends
Our Family spirit without end
To gather now in this sacred place
And help us bring this child to grace
The next generation has been born
into our family.
Our legacy.
We pledge to be with this child,
this beautiful boy, always.
Apart but never separate,
free but never alone.
He is one of us,
and because of that,
we will bless him with
all the goodness that we are.
Welcome to the family,
Wyatt Matthew Halliwell.
- Blessed be.
Take good care
of my great-grandson.