I guess my invitation must've
gotten lost in the mail.
- I told you I'd find you again, satyr.
- There's nothing for you here.
- Leave this place or I'Il...
- Or you'll what?
You gonna play your flute?
Who are you? What do you want?
I want you to show me
the Eternal Spring, that's what.
Unless, of course, you want to end up
like your poor satyr here.
Only he can tell us
when to reveal the spring.
Now I'm telling you.
Where is it?
I will find you!
Congratulations again, Phoebe.
- Thanks, sweetie. Good night.
- See you.
Where are you?
Where are you, where are you?
- Did you lose something?
- Just my brain and my keys.
Well, I got some cabs waiting
to take us home downstairs.
I need to find my keys so nobody
has to wake up to let me in.
Piper will kill me
if I wake up the baby.
Well, why don't you stay here?
I mean it. I got the place for the
whole night, somebody ought to use it.
Oh, that's sweet.
- Thanks, but I can't.
- Sure you can.
I insist.
Columnist of the year?
Come on, you deserve it.
Sleep in, have breakfast,
get a massage. It's on me.
What?
You're just a really nice guy,
you know that?
- That's just the champagne talking.
- No, it's not.
Okay, maybe it is a little.
But, no, you are.
Renting this suite
and making sure everyone
gets home okay,
the speech you made...
Well, you guys deserve all the awards,
not me.
All I did was buy the paper.
I'm glad you did.
Me too.
Good night, boss.
Good night.
- Well, I better get going.
- Yeah.
- Good night.
- I'm not sure we should be doing this.
- Yeah, me neither.
Gosh, what's that smell?
I hope it's not breakfast.
I'm making an herbal sleep remedy.
Remind me never to get insomnia.
- Cute.
- Cute is a sleeping baby.
That baby woke up
every 15 minutes last night.
If I don't make something
to help him sleep,
you're gonna have one cranky mom
on your hands.
"Going to have"?
Now, where is the dried dill?
I can't find anything around here.
It's in the middle cupboard,
bottom right.
See, I switched things around.
I wanted to separate the herbs
for potions
from the ones we use for cooking.
But we use dill for both.
Well, that's why I put it there
with the herbs and spices that we use
for cooking and magic.
It's a whole new system, see.
Voilà, you have your dill.
Okay, but what was wrong
with the old system?
I mean, it worked perfectly well
for about five years.
Nothing was wrong with it, honey,
it just didn't work for me.
You know, your mind is just
a little more linear, that's all.
Well, you know, I know with Wyatt
and everything lately
that you've had to, you know,
take on more responsibility
for all things Wiccan lately.
But, you know, you don't need
to shoulder the burden
all by yourself anymore.
Sweetheart, it's no burden.
That's why I quit my job, after all.
Yeah, but still, I mean,
it's not fair to you.
Now that I have Leo being Mr. Mom,
I got a little bit more time on my hands.
Well, I don't mind taking the lead.
Morning. Never mind, don't ask.
Hey, somebody's doing
the walk of shame.
Details, details.
I knew I wasn't gonna
get away with this one.
Not a chance.
- Spill it, sister.
- Okay.
I think I did something really bad.
I slept with my boss.
- Jason?
- No, Elise.
Yes, of course, Jason!
Wow, that is bad.
For future employment's sake.
Unless, of course... Maybe it'll
work out, and you guys will get married
and have kids, and you could own
half the newspaper.
- Paige.
- Sorry.
- How did this happen?
- It was very fast.
- Downer.
- No, that part wasn't fast.
That part was...
- So that's good, right?
- Yes.
No.
I don't know. See, I'm very conflicted
about this whole thing,
because it's not just the fact
that he's my boss,
it's just I didn't plan on this all
happening right now in my life.
Well, honey, unfortunately, that's
when these things usually happen.
Yeah, can we get back to the whole,
like... part?
Talk about "orbis interruptus."
Sorry, I just got an alert
from the Elders.
- Do you know about wood nymphs?
- Wood nymphs?
Yeah, frolicking little tree sprites,
protectors of the forest,
always in the company of a satyr.
Yeah, I know what they are.
It was a rhetorical question.
What about them?
Well, I guess a couple have been
spotted in the city by mortals.
The Elders are worried
about exposure.
Well, that doesn't make any sense,
because they don't abandon
their forest unless...
- They're flushed out.
- By a demon.
- I'll get right on it.
You're tired, honey.
I am. I'll also be in the attic.
Paige, will you orb to the office
and grab my laptop?
I have to finish this article,
and I don't want to see Jason.
I'm sorry, I really can't.
Ask Piper.
Hey, that's cheating.
Why is he still playing this melody?
Maybe he doesn't recognize us.
- Hi.
- He must be our new satyr.
Look how many people
have gathered to adore him.
He's not playing the melody.
Excuse me. Pardon me.
All right, girls, you had your fun.
Let's go.
I know, I know.
- What should we do?
- Flee.
What are you doing?
I'm practicing.
In case you can't find the nymphs,
I thought maybe I could try
and lure them to us.
How many times
have I told you, Tull,
only a satyr can master that thing.
I don't know why you keep trying.
- Well, because Father...
- Father's dead!
Don't you understand?
And we're never gonna
get our revenge
unless we find that damn spring
and become unstoppable.
I'm just trying
to help you find them, Xavier.
I already did.
They've escaped to the city,
just like I thought they would.
But they're out of their element.
Lost without nature, confused.
So how do you know
where they are?
They found an oasis
in the middle of it all, a fountain.
One which they'll return to tonight
when the moon is full.
To rejoice in it.
Xavier, can I come?
Please, can I join you?
No.
You aren't strong enough to help.
But don't worry, you will be.
Once you drink from the spring.
Until then...
...keep practicing.
- Phoebe.
- Shoot.
Hey.
I didn't even see you come in.
I just came by to get my laptop.
I'm gonna work from home.
- Okay, bye.
- Wait, there's a staff meeting.
You have to stay for that.
Oh, that's right, I totally forgot.
Listen, about last night...
It was a huge mistake. I agree,
it should've never happened.
Actually, that's not what
I was gonna say.
- No?
- I thought it was amazing.
I think you're amazing.
Really?
See, but that's not the point.
The point is, you're my boss.
And I don't want my professional
and personal life to collide.
Isn't it a little late for that?
No. We can stop this right here
and now, before it gets any worse.
Before what gets any worse?
Phoebe, we have nothing
to be ashamed of.
We're two intelligent adults who
happen to be attracted to each other.
What's so wrong with that?
Sorry to interrupt, Mr. Dean,
but looks like those Godiva girls
popped up again.
Oh, no.
- Anybody know who they are?
- Not yet,
- but everybody wants to know.
- Then let's be the first to find out.
Pull Bill and Jean from Metro,
get Francesca online.
I don't want to trail this story,
I want to lead it.
- Understood.
- Phoebe?
What exactly are you doing over there,
writing a dissertation?
No. Actually, since wood nymphs
are considered
the personification of nature,
I am devising a spell using the four
elements to try to locate their home.
Well, what good will that do?
The Elders said the nymphs
were loose in the city.
But I'm thinking that
if we can find out where they lived,
you know, we can find out what
flushed them out
- and see what demon's after them.
- Talk about your roundabout methods.
No, actually, it's like that cliché,
"thinking outside the box."
It kind of applies here.
Well, me, I'm just gonna stick to good,
old-fashioned scrying to find him.
How's that working out for you?
Let's just say it's been a busy day
for evil in the city.
I wonder if nymphs have
any natural enemies.
What are all these?
I indexed the Book oF Shadows
to make our searches more efficient.
You colour-coded
the Book oF Shadows?
- When?
- Yesterday.
Now, you see, demons and warlocks
will be under red,
angels and beings of light
under white,
and wood nymphs, because they're
spirits of nature, will be under green
- because green represents...
- I know what green represents.
Great. Then you'll just love it.
I don't think so.
- Isn't that Wyatt calling you?
- Nice try. Leo's got him.
You're not getting rid of me
that easy.
I am not trying to get rid of you,
all right.
I'm just trying to take point
because your life is so busy now
that I thought I would just try to help
a little bit.
I got your busy right here, lady.
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
I'm stuck at work.
I forgot there was a staff meeting.
- Have you seen the news yet?
- No.
We're too busy fighting over
the best way to find nymphs.
Okay, well, stop arguing
and turn on the TV,
because they're all over it.
- What? What do you mean?
- What's she saying?
Nobody knows who they are yet,
but believe me,
the demon is not the only one
looking for them now.
- Where were they last spotted?
- Downtown, City Plaza.
Maybe they'll go back there.
Well, if they do, there's gonna be
a demon waiting for them.
Okay, how much longer before you
realize this is not working?
Hey, Phoebe was the one who said
they were here, not me.
No, excuse me. You were the one
that said a demon was here waiting.
I was the one that said
they'd be stupid to come back.
And you think they're not? Half of
San Francisco has spotted them.
Well, at least it looks like
they're having fun.
Hold it. Shouldn't we see
if the demon attacks?
Ladies.
Wait's over.
Last chance.
- Where's the spring?
- Oh, please. Please.
Please, help us.
Why didn't he blow up?
- Let's get out of here.
- First thing we've agreed on all day.
No, no, no.
But we need to be outside
to find our new satyr.
No. No, you don't. Not when there's
a demon out there, you don't.
Paige, a little help, please.
Sorry, Miss Nymph, you're stuck here.
But... But you're suffocating us.
But we're meant to be outdoors.
We were born to be wild.
I hear what you're saying.
Nature is a part of us.
We're meant to preserve it,
to nurture it.
Well, that's really great, honey,
but our job is to preserve you, okay?
All right, inside, inside, inside.
What's going on down here?
- Who are they?
- Nymphs, Leo. Clearly nymphs.
Hi there. No wonder the Elders
were worried about exposure.
Who's the sexy beast?
The beast is married, to me.
Now, I don't mean to rain
on anybody's parade,
but didn't you two just lose a sister?
Shouldn't you be,
I don't know, grieving?
Oh, we don't mourn death,
we celebrate it.
It's the way of nature.
The Eternal Spring we protect
ensures that life is always renewed
in the forest.
So she'll be reborn or something?
If not in the plants and trees,
then in the wind and rain
that brings them sustenance.
Isn't that awesome?
Still, without her,
we may not find our new satyr.
We need three to perform the dance,
or we may not hear his call.
I'm a little confused.
See, if you guys protect this spring,
what do you need a satyr for?
Because that's the way
it's always been.
- Oh, okay.
- So do you know who the demon is?
No, only that he wanted us
to bring him to the Eternal Spring
to drink from it, we assume.
Which would make him immortal.
Indestructible.
We need Phoebe.
- Hello? Anybody home?
- Ask and you shall receive.
Try and keep an eye on them.
Hiya. Where you been?
Avoiding Jason.
Apparently, it didn't work.
Yeah. Well, we found something.
Enough, stop.
- I thought there was three of them.
- Yeah, the demon got one.
Yeah, but on the plus side,
you got some really pretty flowers.
Yeah, see, I don't want
to talk about that.
Tell me about the demon.
Well, Piper let him get away.
Come on, I blew off his hand,
didn't I?
Yes, but the rest of him got away.
Yeah, well, okay,
demons don't always go poof
when you want them to, you know.
What the hell is going on
with you two?
It seems that Paige thinks
she's the lead witch all of the sudden.
That's what's going on.
I don't think I'm lead witch, I've just
had to be for the last few months.
It's all I do.
Maybe while I was
on maternity leave.
But it's like sports, you can't lose
your starting job due to injury.
Vanquishing demons
is not a sport, Piper.
It is if you're good at it.
All right, come on.
- Where are you going?
- Wyatt's crying.
They are all yours.
We need to frolic.
We need to find our satyr.
Okay, I would like to frolic too,
but I actually have work to do.
Are you always this tense?
Look, we need to find this demon
before this demon finds them.
All right,
I'm gonna go check the Book.
- I'll go.
- No, wait.
- Let your sister go.
- Thanks.
Why?
You'll see.
Something wrong?
Not anymore.
I will have your revenge, Xavier,
I swear it.
They will not get away with this.
It's not the nymphs you have
to worry about, it's the witches.
You're not strong enough
to stand up to them.
But I will be
once I drink from the spring.
And then I'll use the immortal waters
to heal you.
Always the dreamer.
You'll never trick them into thinking
you're their new satyr.
No?
Watch me, brother.
Watch me.
Demons and warlocks are red,
beings of light are white.
Oh, yeah? Well, what's a bunyip?
Because it's not good or evil.
So, what the hell colour is that?
Well, that's confusing.
- Everything all right?
- Yeah, sure, fine,
if you call Paige defacing
the Book oF Shadows "all right."
She defaced the Book?
For all intents and purposes.
Look at this.
This is a sacred book.
It looks ridiculous.
Well, look, these things
just come right off. See?
That is so not the point.
- It's not?
- No.
She's done this a lot lately,
and it's not just this. The kitchen.
The least she could do
is discuss it with us beforehand.
You're right, she should've
discussed it with you.
But that's not
what's making you angry.
What are you really feeling?
Okay, you know,
just because we've gone to counselling
doesn't mean
that you're a shrink now.
I'm just saying that this whole
competitive thing you guys...
I'm not competitive, she is.
You both are,
and you both need to stop.
Otherwise, you'll never help
the nymphs reclaim their forest.
I know, I know.
I just can't help but feel like
I'm being pushed aside.
She's not pushing you aside.
She's just picking up the slack.
Okay, just so you know
for future reference,
you're supposed to be on my side
in these situations.
It keeps us out of counselling.
I am on your side, honey. Always.
I'm just saying that maybe
you should look at this
like an opportunity.
Now, this is me talking,
this isn't a shrink.
You're always complaining
about how you're not able to have
a normal life because of witchcraft,
and maybe letting Paige take the lead
once in a while,
it'll allow you to have that.
That's some good
reverse psychology there.
- I'll think about it.
- Okay.
So how do you know this potion
is gonna work?
Shouldn't we wait for Piper
to find the demon first?
She won't. That's why I went ahead
and made this garden-variety,
kick-ass vanquishing potion.
You guys have to stop butting heads.
We work best
when we work together.
Well, tell her that. Don't tell me that.
Are you sure she's the one?
She needs us as much
as we need her.
That looks beautiful.
You guys should be florists.
We are. That's what we do.
- In the woods, I mean.
- Right, of course. Sorry.
That's all right.
Most people don't even know we exist.
They take us for granted.
They take the forest for granted,
as if it'll always be there.
- That's why we have to help you.
- Helping us helps you.
After all, all of nature is intertwined:
Forests, flowers,
- love.
- Love.
It's in the air.
Not where I'm standing, it isn't.
- I'll get it.
- Good.
You know, Paige,
we think that you need
- to get back to your wild side.
- Wild side.
- Girls, you might just have a point.
- You're right, she is the one.
The one for what?
The one to help us
find our new satyr.
Hi.
Jason.
- Hey, what are you doing here?
- Well, we never got to finish our talk.
Yeah. Now's not really a good time,
though. I'll call you.
- Did you get the flowers I sent you?
- I did. They were beautiful.
That was very sweet.
Look, I know this is awkward for you
because of work and all,
but I think we can
work this thing out.
It's a lot more complicated than that,
believe me.
Phoebe, we have to talk.
I know, and we will soon, I promise.
Phoebe, what's wrong?
Is there something going on here
that you're not telling me about?
No, of course not.
- What was that?
- What was what?
- Oh, that?
Oh, my God, Paige.
So handsome.
You found them.
Isn't that your sister?
Yeah. Paige.
She's one of the Godiva girls?
No, she is not.
Paige, you get back here right now.
What's going on here?
I don't suppose you can just forget
about everything you just saw, right?
Personally or professionally?
- Both?
- Phoebe.
Okay, look, just promise me
you won't do anything
- until we talk, okay? For me.
- Talk?
- Talk when?
- We're gonna talk later.
Okay, thanks for the flowers.
I like your jacket. Okay, bye.
Piper! Leo!
We really need to be out looking
for our new satyr, Paige.
I thought all we had to do
was dance to hear his call.
It's her first night as a nymph,
Miranda.
Let's see what she can do.
All right, why not?
Follow me, girls.
I can't sense her. Probably because
she's not a witch anymore.
No, of course not.
Because, thanks to me,
she is now a nymph.
Thanks to you? What did you do?
I had to be the one in control.
I had to be the one to find
the stupid demon,
which, by the way,
I have not done yet.
Well, thanks to me, my paper's gonna
get an exclusive on her,
because I slept with Jason.
Oh, good, so this is all
your fault then? Perfect.
Let's forget about
whose fault this is, okay?
Either way, we need a way
to find Paige before the demon does.
That's not gonna do any good unless
we come up with a vanquishing potion.
- Paige already did that.
- She did?
Yeah.
Hello.
I think we found Paige.
I don't see her.
You don't want to.
That cat's out of the bag.
Come on.
Paige, what are you doing?
I'm dancing, Leo.
Do you want to come dance with me?
No, Paige. Come down here
before somebody recognizes you.
- All right, Paige, looking good!
- So much for that.
Come on, Paige,
we're getting out of here.
I can't.
I can't leave till I find my satyr.
Her satyr? Get...
- Talk to her.
- Paige, honey, listen, we need you.
We can't save your fellow nymphs
without you.
- You don't need me, Piper.
- The hell I don't. Paige, listen to me.
You are not a nymph. You are a witch,
and a damn good one at that.
That is your true nature.
Hey, Piper, you've gotta get
those groupies off the stage.
- They're distracting my band.
- I know, I know. I'm working on it.
Piper.
Paige! Wait.
- Where are we going?
- To our new satyr.
Do you hear his call?
Welcome, my little nymphs.
Welcome.
I don't know how the hell to find her.
Well, maybe if we knew
why they decided to turn her
into a nymph in the first place,
that would help.
That's because they needed
a third sister, right?
Yeah, well, the Book also says that
only certain types of magical creatures
can be turned into a nymph.
So, what type was she?
The type that needed
a change, maybe.
From being a witch? That's ridiculous.
Paige loves being a witch.
Until I came roaring back.
And I didn't just push her aside,
I actually pushed Paige
right out the door.
Are we back to blaming you again?
- Yeah.
- Just checking.
Maybe they sensed that
she was overdue for some fun.
She has been working
around the clock lately.
Well, she had plenty of fun
at P3 last night.
Film at 11.
I'll take care of it.
You guys stay on it.
Okay, what haven't we tried?
I think we've pretty much
tried everything.
All right. Well, then it's time to start
thinking outside the box.
Come again?
That was Paige's theory.
It worked pretty damn well for her.
Paige was working on a spell
to locate the nymphs
using the four elements of nature.
- Wow, that's a novel concept.
- Yeah, well, I mocked it.
But if she's right, it should lead us
to where the nymphs live,
and therefore, Paige.
Here's water and fire.
A little bit of wind.
Okay, so all we're missing is earth.
I'll go get some dirt
from the back yard.
Hi. Hello.
- Hey, it's Jason.
- Hey.
- I can't really talk right now.
- It's not about us, Phoebe.
- It's about your sister.
- What about her?
I'm not the only one who saw her.
There was a photographer
at your sister's club last night
because oF the band.
I've got pictures.
And what are you gonna do
with the pictures?
Well, iF I don't print them,
I'll be the only paper in town
that doesn't.
- You know what, just print them.
- Phoebe...
Look, if we hadn't slept together,
Jason,
you'd have never known
that she was one of them.
If we hadn't slept together,
I wouldn't have hesitated to print them.
Phoebe, will you please tell me
what's going on here?
No comment.
No. No, I don't want any wreaths.
No, no berries.
I just want the Spring.
What's the matter?
Why aren't you dancing?
Something doesn't feel right.
- Is this much farther?
- No.
- We're almost there.
- Good.
How did you know
we needed a new satyr?
You called me with your little dance,
didn't you?
Forgive her, she's new.
Then she should be silent,
shouldn't she?
Shouldn't we be worried about
the demon that killed the last satyr?
- I'll take care of him.
- How?
Enough with your questions, nymph!
It's not our place to question him.
We only wish to please.
But you don't know him.
We protect and nourish the forest
while caring for our satyr.
- That's all we need to know.
- It's in our nature.
It's in your nature.
It's in our nature.
You're one of us now.
- We're here.
- Where? Where is it? Show it to me.
So beautiful.
You.
Hi. No offence, but we were looking
for some wood nymphs.
Wait, you two know each other?
Yeah, I was the one
that blew off his arm.
- Wow, that looks like it hurts.
- It does.
You sure we even need this?
Well, that depends on
how many parts I blow off
before he tells us
where the nymphs are.
You're too late.
My brother's found them already.
Oh, your brother. Where is he?
You know, we can just keep doing this,
but he's never gonna talk.
And then he's just gonna try
and fry us.
We'll have to dive out of the way,
get all dirty,
and we're just gonna end up
vanquishing him anyway.
- So should we just cut to the chase?
- I don't see why not.
No, wait. I'll tell you.
- Told you.
- Oh, man.
Now how are we gonna find Paige?
Well, we can just sit and wait
for his brother to come back.
I thought no one was supposed
to drink from the spring.
They're not.
At last.
Satyr, we should leave now.
Your satyr is dead, nymph.
My name is Tull,
brother of Xavier,
son of Nades.
And I will have our revenge.
That's right, nymph, be afraid.
There are no witches here now
to protect you.
Oh, no?
- Hurry, close the spring.
- No!
No. No!
Xavier. Xavier, where are you?
You're stepping on him.
What?
- No. No.
- Now, you should tell us
where our sister is, unless, of course,
you want to join your brother.
Throw it!
Paige calls that a potion?
If we kill him,
then how are we gonna find Paige?
What have you seen
in the last few minutes
that leads you to believe
we'll kill him?
- Just try it.
- Hang on.
Your powers have no effect on me.
I'm immortal now.
Arrogant.
Okay, run.
Paige!
- Oh, God, what if she's...
- Don't go there.
Paige!
You know, maybe we shouldn't be
calling for her. Maybe we should be...
- Yes.
- Daisy?
- Miranda?
- Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid. You don't need a satyr
to tell you what to do anymore.
- Come on.
- We need you.
And helping us helps you,
remember?
- Come with us.
- Here we go.
Paige.
- She's bleeding.
- We have to call for Leo.
Here, I think this will help.
- What is that?
- Water from the Eternal Spring.
Wood nymphs wear a drop
to remind us of what we protect.
You all right?
Yeah, I'll be all right
if you tell me you got that bastard.
No!
Oh, I guess you didn't.
- He drank from the Spring.
- Yeah, we noticed.
You think you can
orb us out of here?
No, but maybe we don't have to.
If we can't vanquish him, maybe we
can turn him into something else
that's also immortal, like a tree.
Yes, even when they die, they're
reborn into new life and new growth.
Vengeance will be mine!
Piper, do you have any idea
what they're talking about?
- I think so.
- Good.
I will avenge my brother, Xavier!
Changing seasons changes
All liFe renews as creation calls
Nothing is immune
Everything transmutes
So take this demon
And give him roots
- That had to hurt.
- Nice job, sis.
You're not so bad yourself.
You know, you two make
a great one-two punch.
- Yeah, well, who's number one?
- We'll talk about that later.
Thank you for your help.
Told you you didn't need a satyr.
We don't know. We can't imagine
protecting the forest without him.
It's never been any other way.
Well, changes are good
for all of us.
He's so...
...innocent.
If he only had any idea what
Mommy and Auntie Paige did today.
They turned a very bad man
into a very big tree.
He's gonna have enough problems
growing up around me as it is.
Are you kidding me?
He is lucky to have you.
Yeah, well, lucky or not, he's got me.
I so missed
not being around him today.
Hello?
Sorry. You guys, I just wanted
to let you know
that I'm going out.
Trolling for satyrs, are we?
No, I'm not trolling.
I'm just gonna go out
with one of the guys in the band.
Oh, really?
Don't you think he's gonna be
expecting the wild child?
Never know, I might just have to give
him a little somethin'-somethin'.
Paige and I have decided to share
the responsibilities of head witch
so that I can spend more time
with Wyatt,
- and she can...
- Rock on.
Good night, you guys.
- Right, rock on.
- Don't do that.
- Rock on.
- Give it up, man.
- What?
- Give it up.
I'll show you give it up.
You give it up is what I'm saying.
Right now!
Your plant could use some water.
I'll get right on that.
I saw tomorrow's advance copy.
I noticed that you're running
the article.
Yes, I am.
And I also noticed
that Paige's name wasn't in it.
No, it isn't.
Thank you.
You know, it's ironic.
You were the one who was worried
about sleeping with the boss,
how it might affect your job.
Turns out it affected mine.
- How so?
- Well, I didn't buy this paper
to bury stories like this one,
Phoebe.
But that's basically what I just did.
I don't know what your sister's
involved in,
but the truth is, I...
I care about you too much
to cause you any hurt.
- That's not very professional of you.
- I know.
- Maybe you should fire you.
- Maybe.
I am still a little curious about what you
know of these Godiva girls, though.
Where they come from.
What happened to them.
You're not gonna tell me, are you?
I didn't think so.