Dad wants us to pick up
where he left off --
Saving people, hunting things,
the family business.
There's a really good cure
for a hangover.
It's a greasy pork sandwich
served up in a dirty ashtray.
Oh, I hate you.
I know you do.
We're not gonna start
that crap again.
Start what up?
That prank stuff.
It's stupid,
and it always escalates.
What's the matter, sammy?
Afraid you're gonna get nair
in your shampoo again?
Just remember,
you started it.
What the --
One, me.
That's all you got?
It's weak.
You're a friggin' jerk!
You smell like a toilet.
Chicken.
Jerk.
Bitch.
Shut up.
You wuss.
Tch.
Jerk.
Bring it on, baldy.
Excuse me.
Are you lost?
No.
I've been waiting for you,
professor.
Huh.
Oh, you're in one
of my classes?
Don't you recognize me?
Well...
They're big classes.
Anyway, my office hours are
tuesday and thursday mornings.
Really? I was...hoping
I could see you now.
Um...
Well, since you asked
so nicely, come on.
Such a handsome photo.
[ Chuckles ]
that old thing.
So, what can I do for you?
How's the anscombe paper coming?
Uh, professor,
I [chuckles]
Uh...
I have a confession to make.
Oh? What's that?
I'm not really
one of your students.
Really.
Then, why are you here?
Maybe I should just go.
Wait.
I get it.
I understand how you're feeling,
and it's only natural.
You are young and wide-Eyed.
And I'm somewhat of a celebrity
around here.
Don't get me wrong,
you're a very beautiful girl.
But it would be wrong of me
to take advantage of you.
I just, uh...
I just respect you
too much.
Oh, my god.
What?
Don't you like me anymore?
Don't you want me?
Supernatural
Dude, you mind not eating
those on my bed?
No, I don't mind.
How's the research going?
You know how it's going?
Slow.
You know how it would go
a heck of a lot faster?
If I had my computer.
Can you turn that down,
please?
Yeah, absolutely.
You know what?
Maybe you should just
go somewhere for a while, huh?
[ Music stops ]
hey, i'd love to.
Unfortunately,
my car's all screwed to hell.
I told you,
I have nothing to do --
[ Knock on door ]
Hey, bobby.
Hey, boys.
It's good to see you again
so soon.
Yeah, uh,
thanks for coming.
Come on in.
Thank god you're here.
So, um...
What didn't you want to talk
to me on the phone about?
Sam: it's this job
we're working.
We weren't sure
you'd believe us.
Well, I can believe a lot.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
It's just we've never seen
anything like it.
Not even close.
We thought we could use
some fresh eyes.
Why don't you begin
at the beginning?
Yeah.
Um, all right, please.
So...
It all started when we caught
wind of an obit.
See, a professor took a nose dive
from a fourth-Story window,
Only there's a campus legend
that the building's haunted.
So we pretexted as reporters
from the local paper.
Yeah, we both had the professor
for "ethics and morality."
So, why do you think
he did it?
Who knows?
He was tenured, wife and kids.
His book is a really
big deal.
Then again, who's to say
it was suicide?
Jen, come on.
Well, what else
could it be?
Well, you know
about crawford hall.
No, I don't, actually.
It's a bunch of crap.
It's a total urban legend.
Well, heather's mom
went to school here,
And she knew the girl.
Wait, what girl?
Like, 30 years ago,
This girl was having an affair
with some professor.
He broke it off.
She jumped out the window
and killed herself.
You know her name?
No.
But they say she jumped
from room 669.
Get it?
You turn the 9 upside down...
So now she haunts
the building,
And anyone who sees her...
They don't live
to tell the tale.
Well, if no one
lives to tell the tale,
Then how does the tale
get told?
Curtis, shut up!
You know what?
Uh, thanks a lot, guys.
Excuse me.
Dean.
What are you --
What are you drinking?
[ Burps ]
I don't know, man.
I think they're called
purple nurples.
I think we should check out
the professor's office.
Oh, no, no, no.
I can't right now.
I've got a feisty little wildcat
on the hook.
I'm about ready to -- Zz! --
Reel her in.
I'll introduce you.
De--
Starla.
Starla, hey.
This is my shuttle copilot,
major tom.
Major tom -- Starla.
[ Chuckles ]
enchant?
Hi.
Sorry. Just trying to keep
my liquor down.
Yeah. Good job.
Hey, good news.
She's got a sister.
Dean:
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on a minute.
What?
Come on, dude.
That's not how it happened.
No?
So you never drank
a purple nurple?
Yeah, maybe that, but...
I don't say things like,
"feisty little wildcat."
And her name wasn't starla.
Then what was it?
I don't know,
but she was a classy chick.
She was a grad student,
anthropology and folklore.
We were talking
about local ghost stories.
Here's to --
Here's to us.
My god,
you are attractive.
Thanks.
But no time for that now.
You need to tell me
about this urban legend.
Please.
Lives are at stake.
Sorry. I just --
I can't even concentrate.
It's like staring...
Into the sky.
Dean, what do you think
you're doing?
Sam, please.
If you wouldn't mind,
just give me five minutes here.
Dean, this is a very serious
investigation.
We don't have time for any
of your blah blah blah blah.
Blah blah blah-Blah.
Blah blah-Blah-Blah blah!
Blah blah-Blah blah-Blah
blah-Blah-Blah.
Blah!
[ Sarcastically ]
right.
And that's how
it really happened.
I don't sound
like that, dean.
That's what you sound like
to me.
Okay.
What's going on
with you two?
Nothing.
It's nothing.
Come on.
You're bickering like
an old married couple.
No, see, married couples
can get divorced.
Me and hme?
We're like, uh, siamese twins.
It's "conjoined" twins.
See what I mean?
Look, it --
We've just been on the road
for too long,
Tight quarters, all that.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
So, anyway, we figured
it might be a haunting,
So we went to check out
the scene of the crime.
So, how long have you been
working here?
Janitor: I've been mopping
these floors for six years.
There you go, guys.
What the heck's that for?
Just find the wire
in the walls.
Ah. Well.
Not sure why you're wiring up
this office.
Not gonna do the professor
much good.
Why's that?
He's dead.
Oh.
What happened?
He went out that window
right there.
Yeah? Were you working
that night?
I'm the one who found him.
You see it happen?
Nope.
I just saw him come up here
and, uh...
Well...
what?
He wasn't alone.
Who was he with?
Come on!
I ate one, maybe two.
Just let me tell it,
okay?
He was with a young lady.
I told the cops about her,
But I guess they never
found her.
You saw this girl
go in, huh?
But did you ever
see her come out?
Now that you
mention it, no.
You ever see her before,
around?
Not her.
What do you mean?
I don't mean to cast aspersions
on a dead guy, but, uh...
Mr. Morality here?
He brought a lot of girls
up here.
Got more ass
than a toilet seat.
One more thing.
This building -- It only
has four stories, right?
Yeah.
So there wouldn't be
a room 669?
Of course not.
Why do you ask?
Ah, just curious.
Thanks.
Sure.
Well, no traces of emf,
that's for sure.
And that room 669's
a load of crap.
So, what do you think?
The professor's just a jumper?
A legend's just a legend?
I don't know.
The girl that
the janitor described --
That's pretty weird.
Yeah.
We ought to check out
the history on the building.
See if any coed
ganked herself there.
Yeah, you're right.
Dude,
were you on my computer?
No.
Oh, really?
'Cause it's frozen now
On -- On
bustyasianbeauties.Com.
Dean...
Would you just -- Don't touch
my stuff anymore, okay?
Why don't you control
your ocd?
But did you dig up anything
about the building,
Or on the suicidal coed?
No. History's clean.
Then it's not a haunting.
Maybe not.
Tell you the truth,
we're not really sure.
What do you mean
you're not sure?
Well...it's weird.
What's weird?
This next part, we, uh...
We didn't see it happen
ourselves, exactly, but...
It's pretty friggin' weird,
even for us.
Aaaaaah!
Aliens?
Yeah.
Look,
even if they are real,
They're sure as hell not coming
to earth and swiping people.
Hey, believe me.
We know.
My whole life
I've never found evidence
Of an honest-To-God
abduction.
It's all just
cranks and pranks.
Yeah, that's what
we thought.
But...we figured we'd at least
talk to the guy.
Hey, you ought to give
those purple nurples a shot.
So, what happened, curtis?
You won't believe me.
Nobody does.
Give us a chance.
I do not want this
in the papers.
Off the record, then.
I, uh...
I blacked out, and...
I lost time,
And when I woke up,
I don't know where I was.
Then what?
[ Voice cracking ]
they did tests on me.
And, uh...
They, uh...
They probed me.
They probed you?
Yeah, they probed me.
Again and a-- Again
and -- And again.
And again and again and again
And then one more time.
Yikes.
And that's not even
the worst of it.
How could it
get any worse?
Some alien made you
his bitch.
They...
They made me...
Slow dance!
You guys are
exaggerating again, huh?
No
Then this frat boy's
just nuts.
We're not so sure.
I'm telling you, dean,
This was made by some kind
of jet engine.
You mean some saucer-Shaped
jet engine?
What else could it be?
What the hell?
I don't know.
Seriously, dude --
What the hell?
I don't know.
I mean, first the hating.
Now this?
The timing alone --
There's got to be some kind
of connection.
You mean between the angry
spirit and the sexed-Up e.T.?
What could the connection
possibly be?
But what could we do?
So we just kept on digging.
So, you and this guy,
curtis --
You were in
the same house?
Yeah.
You heard what happened
to him, right?
Yeah, he says it was aliens,
but, you know, whatever.
Look, man, I --
I know this all
has to be so hard.
Um, not so much.
But I want you to know...
I'm here for you.
You brave little soldier.
I acknowledge your pain.
Come here.
You're too precious
for this world.
I never said that!
You're always saying
pansy stuff like that.
Well, um...
Yeah, uh, thanks.
Thanks for the hug,
but, uh, I'm okay.
Really.
To tell you the truth,
Whatever happened to curtis,
he had it coming.
Why is that?
He's our pledge master.
Put us through hell
this semester
And got off on it.
So now he knows
how we feel.
It's okay.
Still doesn't make a lick
of sense.
But, hey, at least
there's one connection.
Between what?
The victims.
The professor
and the frat guy --
They're both dicks.
That's a connection?
You got anything better
to go on, i'd love to hear it.
Where's my laptop?
I don't know.
Think about it.
A philandering professor
gets a dead girl.
A pledge master gets hazed.
I left it in here.
You obviously didn't.
I mean, these punishments --
They're almost poetic.
Actually, it'd be more like
a limerick, but still --
Okay, hilarious.
Ha ha.
Where'd you hide it?
What, your computer?
Yeah, where'd you hide it?
Why would I take
your computer?
Because no one else
could have.
We keep the door locked.
We never let any maids in.
Looks like you lost it,
poindexter.
Dude, you know something?
I put up with a lot from you.
What are you talking about?
I'm a joy to be around.
Yeah? Your dirty socks
in the sink,
Your food in the fridge.
What's wrong with my food?
It's not food anymore, dean!
It's darwinism.
All I ask from you,
the one thing,
Is that you don't mess
with my stuff!
You done?
You know, how would you feel
if I screwed with the impala?
It'd be the last thing
you ever did.
Did you take
his computer?
Serves him right,
but, no.
Well, I didn't lose it.
'Cause I don't
lose things.
Oh, that's right,
'cause he's mr. Perfect.
Okay, okay.
Why don't you just tell me
what happened next?
There was one more
victim.
Now, we didn't see this one
ourselves, either.
We kind of put it together
from the evidence.
But this guy -- He was
a research scientist.
Animal testing.
Yeah, you know -- A dick,
which fits the pattern.
Hey.
Well, this ought
to be quick.
Ok
That is just nasty.
Uh, yeah.
Mutilated?
Looks to me like something
was hungry.
They identify him yet?
Yeah. A research scientist
at the college.
Guess where his office was,
by the way.
Crawford hall,
same as the professor.
That's right where the frat boy
had his close encounter.
Yeah.
Hey, grab me that thing,
would you?
Thanks.
What is it?
Looks like a...
A belly scale?
From what?
Uh...
An alligator?
An alligator in the sewer.
Come on.
What? Well, dean,
it's a classic urban legend.
A kid flushes a baby gator
down the toilet,
And it grows huge
in the tunnels.
But no one's ever
really found one.
They're not real.
Neither's alien abduction,
But something chomped
on this guy.
This couldn't get
any weirder.
Maybe we should get some help.
I'll call bobby.
Maybe he's run into something
like this before.
Oh, I'm sure he has.
Just your typical
haunted campus,
Alien abduction,
alligator-In-The-Sewer gig.
Yeah, it's simple.
We decided to search
the sewer anyway,
So we split up,
each taking one end of campus.
Did you find anything?
Yeah, I found something,
just not in the sewer.
Dean: son of a bitch!
Sam!
You think this is funny?
It depends. What?
The car!
What about the car?
You can't let the air
out of the tires.
You're gonna bend the rims!
Whoa, wait a minute.
I didn't go near your car.
Oh, yeah? Huh.
Then how'd I find this?
Hey, give me back my money.
Oh, no, no.
Consider it reparations
for, uh, emotional trauma.
Yeah, very funny.
Now, give it back.
No.
Dean,I have had it up
to here with you.
Yeah?
Right back at you!
Get off me!
Give it back!
Okay, I've heard enough.
You showed up
about an hour after that.
I'm surprised at you two.
I really am.
Sam, first off, dean
did not steal your computer.
But I --
Shh, shh, shh, shh!
And, dean, sam did not
touch your car.
[ Chuckling ] yeah.
And if you two bothered to pull
your heads out of your asses,
It all would have been
pretty clear.
What?
What you're dealing with.
Uh...
I got nothing.
Me neither.
You got a trickster
on your hands.
That's what I thought.
What?!
No, you didn't.
I got to tell you...
You guys were
the biggest clue.
What do you mean?
These things create
chaos and mischief
As easy as breathing,
And it's got you
so turned around
And at each other's throats,
You can't even think straight.
The laptop.
The tires.
It knows you're onto him,
And it's been playing you
like fiddles.
So, what is it --
Spirit, demon, what?
Well, more like demigods,
really.
There's loki in scandinavia.
There's anansi
in west africa.
Dozens of them.
They're immortal,
And they can create things
out of thin air,
Things as real as you and me.
Make them vanish just as quick.
You mean like an angry spirit
or an alien or an alligator.
The victims fit
the m.O., too.
Tricksters target
the high and the mighty,
Knock them down a peg,
usually with a sense of humor --
Deadly pranks,
things like that.
Bobby, what do these things
look like?
Lots of things,
but human, mostly.
And what human do we know
Who's been at ground zero
this whole time?
Janitor:
oh, that's a good one.
Come here
Could you eat?
I could eat.
Come on.
Something's missing.
That's better.
Mmm!
Sorry I'm dragging
a little ass today, boys.
Had quite the night
last night.
Lots of sex,
if you catch my drift.
Yeah, hard not to.
Listen, we won't be long.
We just need to check
a couple offices up on 3.
No problem.
Oh, damn.I, uh, forgot something
in the truck.
You know what?
I'll catch up with you guys.
Okay.
Just 'cause he reads
the weekly world news
Doesn't mean he's our guy.
You read it, too.
I'm telling you,
it's him.
Look, I just think we need
some hard proof.
That's all.
Another thing bobby mentioned
was that these suckers
Have a metabolism like
an insect, a real sweet tooth.
I didn't find
any candy bars or sugar.
Not even equal.
Probably missed something.
I don't miss things.
Oh, right,
'cause you're mr. Perfect.
What?
Are you really still
pissed at me
'Cause of what
the trickster did?
You been a tight ass long
before that trickster showed up.
Look, just...stay here,
keep an eye on the janitor.
I'll go to his place to see if I can find
any actual evidence
Before you go barging in
and staking the man!
Just wt till
I get back, okay?
Okay?
Okay!
Eh, screw this.
We've been waiting
for you, dean.
Y-Y-You guys aren't real.
Trust me, sugar,
it's gonna feel real.
Come on.
Let us give you a massage.
You know, I'm a --
I'm a sucker for a happy ending.
Really, I am, but...
I-I'm gonna have to pass.
Janitor:
they're a peace offering.
I know what you
and your brother do.
I've been around a while.
Run into your kind before.
Well,
then you know that i...
Can't let you just
keep hurting people.
Come on!
Those people got
what was coming to them.
Hoisted on their own
petards.
But you and sam --
I like you.
I do.
So treat yourself...
Long as you want.
Just long enough for me
to move on to the next town.
Yeah, I don't think
I can let you do that.
I don't want to hurt you.
And you know that I can.
Look, man, I --
I got to tell you,
I dig your style,
all right?
I mean [chuckles]
I do. I mean
And the slow-Dancing
alien --
One of my personal
favorites.
Yeah.
But, uh,
I can't let you go.
Too bad.
Like I said, I like you.
Sam was right.
You shouldn't have
come alone.
Well, I'll agree
with you there.
That fight you guys
had outside --
That was a trick?
Hmm.
Not bad.
But you want to see
a real trick?
Ohh!
Aah!
Ha!
Nice toss, ladies!
Dean...
Dean, dean, dean.
I did not want to have
to do this.
Me neither.
You guys okay?
Yeah.
I guess.
All I got to say...
He had style.
Ohh.
Bobby, thanks a lot.
Hey, save it!
Let's just get the hell
out of dodge
Before somebody
finds that body.
Yeah
Look, dean, um...
I just want to say
that I'm, uh...
Um...
Hey.
Me too.
You guys are breaking
my heart.
Could we please
just leave?
Transcript : www.1000fr.com
Mofication transcript : Flolo pour www.seriessub.com