Dad wants us to pick up
where he left off.
Saving people, hunting things.
The family business.
You still running credit-card scams?
You think credit-card fraud is easy?
- Okay, Mr. Burkowitz.
- Federal marshals.
- Environmental study majors.
- I'm father Simmons.
U.S. Wildlife service.
Nigel Tuffnel.
- Dr. Jerry Kaplan. Art dealers. Rangers.
- Reporters. Students.
- Fraternity brothers.
- Homeland security? Pretty illegal, even for us.
S.W.A.T. team discovered
a local woman bound and gagged.
Her attacker, a white male
approximately 24 to 30 years of age,
- was discovered hiding in the home.
- Shapeshifter?
Every culture in the world
has a shapeshifter lore,
legends of creatures who can transform
themselves into animals or other men.
Cops are blaming this Dean Winchester guy
for Emily's murder.
- Sorry I'm gonna miss it.
- Miss what?
How many chances am I gonna have
to see my own funeral?
Under what name?
Oh, yeah, that's my favorite so far.
Possible I.D.S in three states
that we know of.
I got to call you back.
Wow.
First I thought
you were just stepping up your game.
Credit-card fraud,
breaking and entering.
This one,
a puzzle...
Grave desecration.
But still, these are a long way from murder.
Then we get a fax from St. Louis...
where you're suspected of torturing
and murdering a young woman.
However, no one could prove anything,
of course, because
supposedly you died there.
But I got to tell you something.
You look pretty healthy to me.
So, now we know Karen Giles
wasn't the first person you murdered.
Going somewhere, Sam?
But I guarantee you she's the last.
Transcript : Raceman
Titelilie
www.forom.com
Thought you might be thirsty.
Okay, so you're the good cop.
- Where's the bad cop?
- He's with your brother.
Okay. And you're holding us why?
He's being held on suspicion of murder.
- And you? We'll see.
- Murder?
You sound genuinely surprised.
Or are you that good of an actor?
Who is he supposed to have murdered?
- We'll get around to that.
- You can't just hold us here
- without formal charges.
- Actually, we can for 48 hours.
But you, being a prelaw student,
would know that.
I know all about you, Sam.
You're 23 years old.
No job, no home address.
Your mother died when you were a baby.
Your father's whereabouts are unknown.
And then there's
the case of your brother, Dean,
whose demise was, well,
just a little bit exaggerated.
Feel free to jump in whenever you like.
Shy?
No problem.
I'll keep going.
Your family moved around a lot
when you were a kid.
Despite that, you were a straight-A student.
Got into Stanford with a full ride.
Then about a year ago,
there was a fire in your apartment.
One fatality...
Jessica Moore,
your girlfriend.
After she died, you fell off the grid,
left behind everything.
I needed some time off...
to deal.
So I'm taking a road trip with my brother.
- How's that going for you?
- Great.
I mean...
we saw the second-largest ball of twine
in the continental US.
Awesome.
We ran Dean's fingerprints through iafis.
Got over a dozen possible hits.
"Possible" hits, which makes them worthless.
But  makes you wonder,
what are we gonna find
when we run your prints?
Yeah, well, uh...
you be sure to let me know, all right?
May I?
- Please.
- Great.
Sam, you seem like a good kid.
It's not your fault Dean's your brother.
We can't pick our family.
Right now detectives in St. Louis
are exhuming a corpse.
They're trying to figure out
how your brother faked his own death
after torturing all those young women.
Dean's a bad guy.
His life is over.
Yours doesn't have to be.
You want me to turn against my own brother?
No.
We already caught him cold,
red-handed at the Karen Giles murder scene.
We just need you
to fill in some missing pieces.
Why would I do that?
Because I can talk to the D.A.,
make a deal for you.
You can get on with your life.
Dean's as good as gone.
My dad and Tony Giles were old friends.
They were in the service together.
We've known him since we were kids,
you know?
So we came as soon as we heard
about his death.
Here you go.
- Anthony Giles.
- Who's Anthony Giles?
The Baltimore lawyer.
Working late at office. Check it out.
"His throat was slit but the room was clean"
- Huh. No dna, no prints.
- Keep reading. It gets better.
"Security cameras failed to capture footage
of the assailant"
Either somebody tampered with the tapes...
or it's an invisible killer.
My favorite kind.
What do you think, Scully?
We check it out?
I'm not Scully. You're Scully.
No, I'm Mulder.
You're  a redheaded woman.
So...
It would've been hard for Dean
to kill Tony,
considering we weren't in town
at the time.
So, tell me what happened next.
Okay, uh,
that's when we went to see Karen.
She was barely holding it together.
We just wanted to be there for her,
you know?
Insurance.
I totally forgot about the insurance.
We're very sorry to bother you
right now, but
the company is required
to conduct its own investigation.
- You understand?
- Sure.
If you could just tell us anything
you remember about the night
your husband died.
Tony and I were supposed to have dinner.
He called and said that he was having
computer troubles
and that he had to work late.
That was it.
Do you have any idea
who could've done this to him?
No. It's like i told the police. I...
I have no idea.
Did Tony mention anything
unusual
to you in the days before his death?
Unusual?
Yeah, like strange.
- Strange?
- You know, Karen, weird.
Weird noises,
visions, anything like that?
He had a nightmare the day before he died.
What kind of a nightmare?
Uh, he said that he woke up
in the middle of the night,
and there was a woman standing at
the foot of the bed.
He blinked. She was gone.
I mean, it was just a nightmare.
Did he say what she looked like?
What the helle difference does it make
what she looked like?!
Uh, it's just our company is very thorough.
He said she was pale,
and she had dark, red eyes.
So I gave Karen a hug,
told her to call me
if she needed anything, and
that was it.
End of story.
Sam, I am trying to help you here,
but you have got to be honest with me.
Now, we have an eyewitness,
someone who saw two men
fitting your and your brother's description
breaking into Giles' office.
Ok, look,
Karen called us later, said that there was
some stuff she wanted from Tony's office,
but the police weren't letting her in.
Like a picture of the two of them in Paris
and some other stuff.
Look, it was wrong to enter a crime scene,
but
she gave us the key.
Hey.
Anthony Giles' body was found
right about here.
"Throat slit so deep,"
"that part of his spinal cord was visible".
What do you think?
Vengeful spirit?
-  Underline "vengeful"?
- Yeah. Maybe.
I mean, he did see that woman
at the foot of his bed.
Look at this.
"danashulps"
What's that, a name?
I don't know, but it's everywhere.
"All work and no play makes Jack
a dull boy"
I'd say we've officially crossed over
into weird.
Maybe Giles knew her.
Maybe it's the name of our pale,
red-eyed mystery girl.
Well...
let's see what we can see.
There's not a single mention of
a Dana Shulps anywhere.
There's not a D. Shulps
or any other kind of freaking Shulps.
Great.
- What do you got?
- Nothing.
No Dana Shulps has ever lived or died
in Baltimore in the last 50 years at least.
- So, what now?
- Well,
I think I'm pretty close
to cracking Giles' password.
Maybe there's something
in his personal files, you know.
By "close" you mean...
30 minutes maybe.
Awesome.
So, I guess I just get to, uh,
hang out.
T hat's
awesome.
Dude, seriously.
Alright. I'm gonna go talk to Karen again,
see if she knows anything about
this Dana Shulps, huh?
Great.
Keep going, sparky.
Then Dean went back to Karen's place
to check up on her.
I mean,
you know,
she had been pretty upset earlier.
So why didn't you go with him?
I just went back to the motel.
How did you know I was there,
by the way?
We found the motel matchbook on your brother
when we arrested him.
Let's quit fooling around.
Now, you were with your brother
the whole time you were in Baltimore.
Why separate now?
Because your brother left you
to go murder Karen.
- He didn't kill anyone.
- I heard the 911 call!
Karen was terrified!
She said someone was in the house.
- Emergency services.
- Hello?
I think I saw somebody in my house.
What is your address, ma'am?
It's 421 Clinton avenue.
Please...
Hello?
Karen, are you in there?
Oh, god.
Seriously, what the hell?
Freeze.
Stay on your knees.
Hands where I can see them.
Now!
Cuff him.
You getting anywhere with him?
No.
Just a lot of wise ass remarks.
You?
Sam's story matches Dean's
to the last detail.
Yeah, well, these guys are good.
I'll give them that.
If we don't get Sam to flip, we have nothing
but a lot of circumstantial evidence.
We got Dean at the crime scene
with blood on his hands.
Juries have convicted for less.
Yeah, but, I mean,
where is the murder weapon?
What's the motive?
You talk about reasonable doubt.
Diana...
do you
have reasonable doubt?
We keep leaning on these guys,
one of them will tumble.
And don't forget about St. Louis.
I'm telling you,
this Dean guy
is our guy.
I know Tony Giles was a friend of yours.
Yeah,  he was. He was a good friend.
I know you want to clean this mess up quick,
but come on.
Tony knew a lot of criminal types.
- Maybe we just...
- "Criminal types"?
He was a defense lawyer, for god sakes.
Of course he knew criminal types.
Okay.
- All right. Let's get back at them.
- No. You know what?
Let them stew in their juices for a bit.
Come here.
Dana Shulps, Dana Shulps,
Dana Shulps...
Maybe it's not a name.
Maybe it's not a name?
Anagram maybe?
Mr. Winchester?
Yeah.
I'm Jeff Crouse.
I'm with the public defender's office.
I'm your lawyer.
Oh, thank god. I'm saved.
Can I, uh, steal a pen from you
and some paper?
Sure.
Well,
the
police haven't found a weapon yet.
So that's good.
But, uh,
they got your prints
and literally
blood on your hands. And
with your police record...
Mr. Winchester,
- what are you doing?
- I think it's an anagram.
- A what?
- An anagram. Same letters, different words.
Could you do me a favor?
See if you recognize any
of these words, you know.
Local names, places, anything like that.
Do you understand how serious
these charges are?
I'm handcuffed to a table. Yeah. I get it.
Humor me. Take a quick look.
Well, S-U-P?
I don't know about that, but...
Ashland is
is a street name.
It's not far from here.
Street?
Let's start with where you were
the night that Anthony Giles died.
Can you get in to see my brother?
Mr. Winchester...
you could be facing
the death penalty here.
Hey, thanks for the law review, Matlock.
But if you want to help me...
I need you to see my brother.
I hope that was meaningful.
But I'd like to discuss your case now.
Sure thing, Matlock.
You two really are brothers, aren't you?
Now...
as you know,
the D.A. might be interested in...
We need you with the other one.
This should be nice.
Counselor...
your boy decided to confess.
Mr. Winchester,
I would advise against that strongly.
Talk  directly into the camera.
Start by stating your name for the record.
My name is Dean Winchester.
I'm an aquarius.
I enjoy sunsets, long walks on the beach,
and frisky women.
And I did not kill anyone,
but I know who did.
Or rather what did.
Of course, it can't be for sure
because our investigation was interrupted.
But our working theory
is that we're looking for some kind of
vengeful spirit.
Excuse me?
You know, Casper, the bloodthirsty ghost.
Tony Giles saw it.
I'll bet you cash money Karen did, too.
See, the interesting thing is the word
it leaves behind.
For some reason,
it's trying to tell us something.
But communicating across a veil
ain't easy.
And sometimes the spirits,
they get things jumbled.
You remember "Redrum".
Same concept.
You know,
it could be word fragments.
Other times...
It's anagrams.
See, at first we thought
this was a name, Dana Shulps.
But now
we think it's a street.
Ashland.
Whatever is going on,
- I'm betting it started there.
- You arrogant bastard.
Tony and Karen were good people,
and you're making jokes.
I'm not joking, Ponch.
You murdered them in cold blood
just like that girl in St. Louis.
Oh, yeah, that wasn't me, either.
That was a shapeshifter creature
that only looked like me.
Pete, that is enough!
You asked for the truth.
Lock this guy off.
What the hell?
Where is he?
How did he do it?
The fire escape's way over...
- What?
- These two guys.
Hilts and Mcqueen?
What is that?
Hilts is Steve Mcqueen's character in
"The Great Escape".
Can we make this quick?
I'm really tired.
It's been a long day, you know,
with your partner assaulting me and all.
I want to know more about that stuff
- you were talking about earlier.
- Time life,
"mysteries of the unknown".
Look it up.
Let's pretend for the moment
you're not entirely insane.
What would one of these things
be doing here?
Vengeful spirit?
Well, they're created by violent deaths,
and then they come back for a reason,
usually a nasty one,
like revenge on the people that hurt them.
And, uh, these
spirits...
They're capable of killing people.
Where did you get that?
I don't know.
It wasn't there before.
You've seen it, haven't you?
The spirit.
How did you know?
Because Karen had the same bruises
on her wrists.
I'm willing to bet that if you look at
Giles' autopsy photos, he's got them, too.
It's got something to do with the spirit.
I don't know what.
I know.
You think you're going crazy.
But let's skip that part, shall we?
Because the last two people
who saw this thing
died pretty soon after.
You hear me?
You think I'm gonna die.
You need to go to Sam.
He'll help.
You're giving your brother up.
Go to the first motel listed
in the yellow pages.
Look for Jim Rockford.
That's how we find each other
when we're separated.
You can arrest him, if you want.
Or you can let him save your life.
These showed up after you saw it?
Yeah,
- I guess.
- All right.
You're gonna have to tell me
exactly what you saw.
You know, I must be losing my mind.
You're a fugitive.
I should be arresting you.
All right, well,
you know what?
You can arrest me later, alright?
After you live through this.
But right now, you got to talk to me.
Okay?
Okay. Great.
Now, the spirit, what did it look like?
She was, um,
really pale...
and her throat was cut.
And her eyes, they were like this deep,
dark red.
It appeared like
she was trying to talk to me,
but she couldn't.
It was just...
a lot of blood.
You know what? Here.
I've been researching every girl who has ever
died or gone missing from Ashland street.
How did you get those?
Those are from crime scenes
and booking photos.
You have your job. I have mine.
Here. I need you to look through these.
Tell me if you recognize anyone.
This is her.
I'm sure of it.
Claire Becker?
28 years old, disappeared about
eight or nine months ago.
But I don't even know her.
Why would she come after me?
Well,
before her death,
she was arrested twice
for dealing heroin.
- You ever work narcotics?
- Yeah,
Pete and I did,
before homicide.
You ever bust her?
Not that I remember.
Says she was last seen entering
2911 Ashland street.
Police searched the place,
didn't find anything.
Guess we got to check it out ourselves,
see if we can find her body.
What?
Well, we got to salt and burn her bones.
It's the only way to put her spirit to rest.
Of course it is.
So, what exactly are we looking for?
I'll let you know when we find it.
Sam!
Hey, I'm here.
What is it?
- What happened?
- Claire.
- Where?
- She was here.
Did she attack you?
No. No, she was just like
reaching out to me.
She was over there by the window.
Here, help me move this.
All right.
I got it.
Our little mystery word.
Now the extra letters make sense.
What is that?
Spirits and certain remains
give off electromagnetic frequencies.
So, if Claire's body was here,
- that would indicate that?
- Yeah. Well, that's the theory.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's definitely something in there.
You know,
this is bothering me.
Well, you are digging up a corpse.
No, not that.
That's, uh, pretty par for the course,
actually.
Then what?
It's just...
I mean, no vengeful spirit
I've ever tussled with wanted to be wasted,
so why the hell would Claire
lead us to her remains?
Doesn't make any sense.
All right. Here.
Give me your hand.
Her wrists.
Yeah, they'd be bruised just like yours.
That necklace mean something to you?
I've seen it before.
It's rare.
It was custom-made over
on Carson street.
I have one just like it.
Pete gave it to me.
Now this all makes perfect sense.
I'm sorry?
Yeah. You see,
Claire is not a vengeful spirit.
She's a death omen.
Excuse me?
Claire's not killing anyone.
She's trying to warn them.
Sometimes spirits,
they don't want vengeance.
They want justice, which is why
she led us here in the first place.
She wants us to know who her killer is.
Detective, how much do you know
about your partner?
- Oh, my god.
- What?
About a year ago,
some heroin went missing from lockup.
Obviously it was a cop.
We never found out who did it.
But whoever did it would need someone
to fence their product.
Somebody like a heroin dealer.
Somebody like Claire.
So, I'm being extradited to St. Louis, huh?
You just decided to transfer me yourself
800 miles at 2:00 in the morning?
This can't be good.
All right. Thanks.
What is it?
Pete just left the precinct.
- With Dean.
- What?!
He said the prisoner had to be transferred,
and he just took him.
Dispatch has been calling,
but he won't answer the radio.
Radio?
- He took a county vehicle?
- Yeah.
Then it should have a lojack.
You just got to get it turned on.
Pee break? so soon.
So soon?
I think you might want
to get your prostate checked.
Son of a bitch.
Hey, I'm cool in the van.
You go do what you got to do.
You're a cocky son of a bitch.
You think those people in St. Louis
are gonna buy that crap you're paddling?
Here's the thing.
You're not gonna make it to St. Louis.
You're gonna die
trying to escape.
Wait! Wait!
Let's talk about this.
You don't want to do something
that you're gonna regret.
- Or maybe you do.
- Pete!
Put the gun down.
Diana?
How'd you find me?
I know about Claire.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Put the gun down!
No, I don't think so.
You're fast.
Pretty sure I'm faster.
Why are you doing this?
I didn't do anything, Diana.
It's a little late for that.
It wasn't my fault.
Claire was gonna turn me in.
I had no choice.
And Tony?
Karen?
Same thing.
Tony scrubbed the money.
Then he got skittish.
And then he wanted to come clean.
I'm sure he told Karen everything.
It was a mess. I had to clean it up.
I just panicked.
How many more people
are gonna die over this, Pete?
There's a way out.
This Dean kid is a friggin' gift.
We can pin the whole thing on him.
Okay? No trial, nothing.
Just one more dead scumbag.
Hey!
No one will question it.
Diana, please.
I still love you.
Thank you.
Then why don't you buy me another necklace,
you ass?
Don't do it. Don't do it.
You're doing all right?
Not really.
The death omen, Claire,
what happens to her now?
It should be over.
She should be at rest.
So, uh,
what now, officer?
Pete did confess to me.
He screwed up both your cases royally.
I'd say there's a good chance
that we can get your cases dismissed.
- You could take care of that for us?
- I hope so.
But the St. Louis murder charges?
That's another story.
I.. I can't help you.
Unless
I just happened to turn my back
and you walked away.
I could tell them
that the suspects escaped.
- Wait. Are you sure?
- Yeah, she's sure, Sam.
You could lose your job over
something like that.
Look, I just want you guys out there,
doing what you do best.
Trust me.
I'll sleep better at night.
Listen, you need to watch your back.
They're gonna be looking for both of you
right now.
Get out of here.
- I got to radio this in.
- Hey, uh...
You wouldn't happen to know where
my car is by chance?
It's at the impound yard on Robertson.
Don't
- even think about it.
- It's okay. It's all right. Don't worry.
We'll just improvise.
We're pretty good at that.
Yeah. I've noticed.
- Nice lady.
- Yeah, for a cop.
Did she look familiar to you?
No. Why?
I don't know. It's nothing.
Hey, you hungry?
No.
I have some reason
I could really go for some pea soup.