Dr. Brazzel?
Yes.
Considering everything,
I suppose I was lucky.
I woke up in the bathtub.
The place was on fire.
I crawled out.
A few days later,
I woke up in the hospital.
The fact that I actually
wasn't dating Francie,
I thought
that was the number-one
most insane story of all time.
But yours actually tops it.
She survived.
Allison Doren.
The woman you thought
was Francie.
She's working with a group
called The Covenant.
We think they're the ones
responsible for kidnapping me.
For setting the fires.
You know, I've always thought
of myself as a pacifist.
The idea of taking someone's
life is just inconceivable.
If I had the chance
to kill Allison...
I never would have come here
if I didn't have to.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, my God, you're the most
beautiful thing I've ever seen.
I went to see a doctor.
He had this
sort of dream therapy
he thought might help me
remember what happened.
I was hoping you could
help make sense of it.
You were sitting
in my apartment.
There was a box
of cereal on the counter.
The box had a name
written on it.
Something I kept seeing
in the dream.
St. Aidan.
St. Aidan was a contact of mine
when I was an analyst
at the Agency.
Yeah, St. Aidan
was his code name.
What was his real name?
I never knew it.
An arms dealer
put me in touch with him.
Do you remember
how to contact him?
Yeah.
He would only meet with me.
You know, I can go in again.
- No, you're not.
- Well, maybe I am.
Assuming you can even get him.
He would only meet in person.
I've spent the last two years
of my life
pretending to be
somebody that I'm not.
It's not your fault.
You weren't sleeping with her.
When you made contact
with St. Aidan,
what was the protocol?
I'd dial a number.
An answering machine
in Bucharest.
When it picked up,
I'd dial a confirmation code.
I'd hang up and wait
for him to call me back.
Yes?
If you can, we need to meet.
Tuesday night, 11.00.
Same location.
Listen to me
very carefully, Doctor.
I need to know
what Sydney Bristow told you.
The brunette.
Wasn't she the brunette?
Yes.
She was the brunette.
You helped her recover
her memories.
Tell me what she found.
The morphine was very good.
Like the old days, when I --
Oh, but don't turn it off.
No.
Answer the question.
Well...
Answer, and then
you'll get more.
She said she fought herself.
And that she saw her friend.
She saw Will in her dream?
Yes.
The father.
He said he would call a witness.
No, he'd call
the Witness Protection division.
Yeah. Yeah.
Meaning Tippin's still alive?
Meaning I really need
some more morphine.
I've earned it, don't you think?
And I --
Yeah, but...
Not so much, because I could...
I could --
I could over--
O.D.
As you know, a number
of the cameras were shot out.
Those that remained functional
provided us
with only marginal images
of the men who took Sydney.
We ran the video
through our database
and came up with eight matches.
Two weeks ago,
one of those suspects
rented an A-Star helicopter
from a dealer in Austin.
Where he'd also recently
purchased a warehouse.
We went there, but the building
was only being used for storage.
Boxes of fishing equipment.
It was a dead end.
Fishing equipment?
Nice detail.
The bullets that The Covenant
used are untraceable.
The manufacturer hasn't actually
made these shells for 15 years.
Oh, I re-read your file.
I forgot.
You were captured by East German
Intelligence Agents.
1982?
Yeah, it wasn't your fault,
of course.
They'd gotten a tip that
the CIA was on their tail.
But you were unprepared.
No backup.
No resources.
Still, you convinced them
your name was Aken Ostburg,
a history professor from Sweden.
They held you for two weeks.
Never identified you
as American.
That's impressive.
We are talking
about the fate of my daughter.
Where do you think she is?
Don't do this.
Jack, Jack, let him go.
Get him out of here!
Take him into custody now!
If St. Aidan does show,
what am I supposed to tell him?
You've just been given
Code Six clearance.
That you want information
about The Covenant.
Last chance to bail out.
What, are you kidding me?
I love this stuff.
Based on my analysis
of the calls
The Covenant made about
trading the Rambaldi device
for Sydney, sir.
The voiceprint analysis
was unable to I.D. the voice,
because they were using
an anti-speech signal
parameterization device.
You're telling me
you've got nothing?
Well, at the moment, yeah,
I lack everything, sir.
We've got no way to verify
that it was The Covenant
making the demand for the trade?
You could say the fact
we can't confirm it was them
is confirmation it was them,
because it does look like
stealthy Covenant behaviour.
Sir?
Mr. Lindsey, one more thing.
Sorry.
Listen, I know I'm just the tech
guy, and I'm no one to you.
Well, Sydney Bristow
means a lot to me.
I just wanted your opinion.
Is she gonna be alright?
I am doing everything
in my power
to bring this to a safe
and swift conclusion.
You have my word.
Thank you.
Is he always this late?
We just might have
gotten blown off.
Mr. Tippin?
What happened to your hand?
Another time, perhaps.
Oh, my God, it's Lazarey.
It's good to see you again.
I wasn't sure you'd come.
I would not have come at all,
except money's something
I could use.
Well, I'll see what we can do
about that.
You should know I've been given
Code Six clearance.
And I need to know
about The Covenant.
Why are you asking me
about The Covenant?
I thought you --
How do you think I even know
anything about them?
Obviously you know something.
I cannot talk about Covenant.
Wait a minute. Excuse me.
Lives are at stake.
Yes, they are.
We have nothing further
to discuss.
Tell him Julia Thorne sent you.
Julia Thorne sent me.
No.
I don't believe you.
- Yell out the name Lazarey.
- Lazarey.
Tell him Julia told you
his name.
She needs to see him.
She trusts him,
but she's in danger.
It was Julia Thorne.
She told me your name.
She needs to see you.
She trusts you,
but she's in danger.
Did they find it?
I don't know
what he's talking about.
Have they been to Graz?
I need to know.
Will, get out of there.
They're after Lazarey.
I can't make sense of it.
How we got to Lazarey.
What he meant.
What The Covenant wants.
But they don't kill Lazarey.
They tranq him.
They abduct him.
They wanted him.
Lazarey asked if they got it.
So whatever's going on,
there's a thing.
And there's someone else
who's trying to find it.
Things really don't get
more vague than that.
It's Sloane.
I mean, it's obviously Sloane.
Syd, you've been going over this
since the beginning of time.
You'll figure it out.
What makes you say that?
Because you're you.
Think that was the best move,
punching Lindsey?
Based on the comments
he was making,
it was obvious you and I
were going to end up here
no matter what we did,
whether I hit him or not.
I wasn't about to pass up
the opportunity.
We shouldn't have let Sydney go.
- Vaughn.
- What?
Sydney can no longer be
your primary concern.
What the hell's that mean?
I didn't bring this up
to start a petty fight.
The fact is, you and I
have something in common.
We've both suffered through
the death of the woman we loved,
only to discover
she was still alive.
I know it's hard,
but this isn't about you.
And I will not allow my daughter
to become your mistress.
If that's where you think my
concern for Sydney is headed,
you are more cynical
than I thought.
If lightning strikes and you
and I get to walk free again,
if you care about my daughter
as you claim to,
then push her away.
Be cruel if you have to.
Make her despise you.
Because your kindness
tortures her.
I can see it,
what it does to her.
And I won't have it.
You and Vaughn's wife
work together?
- Okay, how the hell did that --
- Let's talk about you.
A beautiful painter
lives in your building,
and you haven't asked her out.
Why?
Because Jonah's recovering from
a post-traumatic dating syndrome
after his last girlfriend
dumped him
by ramming a bayonet
into his lungs.
Let's go back to you.
Okay, you and Vaughn's wife.
Yeah.
I hate her.
I mean, I don't.
She's nice.
- You hate her.
- Yeah.
That's okay.
But not 'cause of her.
It's just...
I still love him.
God.
That sucks.
You know, Will,
considering everything,
I think I'm pretty normal.
I'm emotional.
I try to be honest, but I've
never been a depressed person.
Until now.
I get it.
I mean, nothing has felt
the same this year,
and it's not just Vaughn.
It's you.
And Francie.
I don't know.
What?
I'm just alone.
Hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
Your target.
A government employee.
When and where?
When I know, you'll know.
Just when I was
beginning to believe
the glowing press about you
being such a humanitarian.
You're a smarter man than that.
Who are you?
You abandoned me as a child.
The vague memory I have of you,
you were physically abusive.
Later in life,
you left me $800 million.
Should I go on?
Hello, Daddy.
You were not grateful?
Your inheritance was not enough?
I know the truth,
and therefore I show no remorse
seeing you like this.
I was an apparatchik
by profession,
but a Romanov by blood.
So are you.
In part, that's why
I staged my death.
To give you the inheritance
that is rightfully yours.
That's wonderful spin.
You should know the inheritance
you hoped would buy my affection
now finances my employer.
The Covenant.
They are true evil.
The man you were meeting with.
I want to know exactly
what you said to him.
Every word.
Pathetic.
I'll give you a moment.
To remember exactly
what you said.
I'll ask you one more time.
What exactly did you tell
the man you were meeting with?
You wouldn't do something
like this.
Not to your own father.
Oh, my God.
I know, it's weird.
I've been waiting to do that
for eight years.
No, no.
What you said before.
About me being me.
I don't remember.
Lazarey asked if they have it.
"Have they been to Graz?"
Whatever it was that was hidden,
whatever he was talking about,
I obviously had it.
I must have had it in Graz.
Whatever I did, if it was me,
the choices I made
were my choices.
Oh, so if you had something to
hide, where would you hide it?
Exactly.
That depends on what it is.
Assume for a second
that it's information,
data, a video, something
that can be stored.
Well, if it's small,
it could be hidden anywhere.
Somewhere safe.
Well, when Lazarey spoke,
it didn't sound like
it was someplace protected.
I know.
That's why I'm thinking bank
or hotel safety-deposit box.
Well, how come?
Because that's where I'd put it.
Where would I hide something?
Wait a second.
What?
Hotel Verlustzeit.
We're going to Graz.
Hello.
Checking in?
Yeah, of course.
I'm here, she's here.
We made it.
And you are?
We're the next big thing.
This way, please.
This is one of
our finest suites.
Yeah, yeah,
it's not bad, not bad.
The bar is over there.
The gym is on the sixth floor.
Open 24 hours.
Of course you have a balcony.
Fantastic view.
That should be it.
Is there anything else
I can get for you?
Yeah.
Thank you for asking.
Yeah, you're a lovely
little man.
Thank you.
Sweetheart, two bottles?
Of what?
Champagne.
Four? Two?
Two bottles?
One's good.
One.
Alright.
We're gonna get
four bottles of champagne.
I'm gonna tip you
like I ordered five.
Do you know what I mean?
You do, don't you,
you cheeky bastard?
- Yes.
- Cheers.
What? What?
Come on, if we're gonna do this,
we got to be legit about it.
It was a little over the top.
Over the top?
I'm wearing seat covering.
There is no over the top.
Plus, I like champagne.
You keep forgetting,
I live in Wisconsin now.
I'm not squandering this.
Call up the on-screen checkout.
You have to admit,
my accent was pretty good.
It was like early Stones.
I thought it was Australian.
Shut up.
I was like, "Yeah, I'm here.
She's here.
We made it."
I mean, that's good.
Take a look at it.
Right, that's enough.
Carry on.
Let's get past these firewalls.
Let's see if I was ever here.
We're in the system.
What are we looking for?
Long-term storage contracts.
The names of people who have
things in safety-deposit boxes.
Unbelievable.
Box 23.
Let's see if they have
a floor plan online.
What if they don't?
Think positively.
Here we go.
Subbasement, just past
the northeast corridor.
What about security?
I'm almost done looping
the surveillance cameras.
Let's move.
- I assume you're not primping.
- Not exactly.
Stand back.
What is that?
Sark's got it.
Go.
You can't.
You're not trained.
Go.
I guess we have
unfinished business.
This is for Francie.
We got to get out of here.
Let's go.
Set the time
and place with Lindsey.
I'm ready to be traded back.
Sydney, Lindsey's taken your
father and Vaughn into custody.
Dixon's in custody as well.
But we need to proceed
with this trade as planned
so that Lindsey believes you
were being held by The Covenant.
The Rambaldi device
is being delivered in San Pedro.
I've hired a team to pick it up.
They'll appear to be working
for The Covenant.
As soon as they've left
the area,
you're to drive yourself
to meet Lindsey.
You are never ending up
with the Rambaldi device.
I want it put inside the van
and taken directly
to the parking lot
at Hill Street and 9th.
I want the van to remain
visible at all times.
No one is to enter
or exit the vehicle.
Sydney, you have my word.
That's a relief.
Listen very carefully.
I need a favour.
Where are you?
Just listen and tell no one
about this call.
The Rambaldi device
being traded to The Covenant
is actually going to Sloane.
He needs to be watched from
the moment he gets the device.
Grab the feed from a satellite
that has a view of the trade.
Track their van.
Any suspicious stops,
anyone gets on or off,
have a team bring them in.
Alright, I got it.
Whatever the hell
you're up to, good luck.
Status?
The Covenant's representatives
have taken possession
of the Rambaldi device.
Syd, I'm tracking the van.
The package is inside.
Copy that.
Follow the van
to the rendezvous point.
Anything unusual,
you let me know.
Roger that.
I'm heading toward Lindsey.
Wish me luck.
Sir, we have a 20
on Agent Bristow.
She's approaching the dock.
Bristow's arrived.
On behalf of the government,
I want to say how relieved I am
at your safe return.
Seal off the perimeter now!
- Shots from the west!
- Man down!
Stay down!
You murdered Robert Lindsey.
I think you already know
my response.
Let me guess. You don't know
what I'm talking about.
Not a word.
I did everything as you asked.
I followed your protocol
precisely.
This was your endgame
the whole time.
Now, you can go on
blaming me if you like.
Or you can accept the truth.
Which is what?
The deceiver was Lindsey,
not me.
His team might have thought so,
but apparently Lindsey never
gave us the Rambaldi device.
It was a setup.
I don't know how you did this.
But you're not gonna
get away with it.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
It seems like everything
is falling back into place.
Thank you, by the way.
For everything.
Yeah.
I got to go.
I'm meeting Lauren.
Now, I'm not exactly sure
what this means.
What is that?
What was inside the box.
It's human tissue.
Vital.
Still active.
Oh, and there was a name
etched inside the box.
Milo Rambaldi.
I've been looking for you.
You feeling alright?
Yeah.
Seeing Allison again.
Killing her.
You know,
I must have dreamed about it
I don't know how many times.
When you told me
that she was still alive,
I thought if I had the chance,
that ending her life
would be satisfying.
You know, there'd be closure.
It would be cathartic.
It's just as empty
as the dreams.
It's horrible.
There's no satisfaction.
There's nothing.
I know they talked to you.
Now that The Covenant knows
you're still alive,
you might want to move again.
Maybe somewhere
outside of the country.
No, I'm not gonna run anymore.
I'm gonna stay in Wisconsin.
I don't know, maybe when I get
back, I'll ask out that painter.
We're gonna see
each other again.
Love you.
You too.
Yeah?
We never talked about that.
Yeah.
I kind of like that.