Previously on "Alias."
Bomani's become the largest
arms dealer in Africa,
with strong ties
to The Covenant.
I could help you
become more powerful than ever.
You know about The Passenger?
Excuse me?
The Passenger.
Dixon, it's me.
I'm at the Naval Hospital.
There's a sniper.
Lazarey's been shot!
Our superiors
would like to know
how your efforts in securing
a scapegoat are progressing.
I've already taken care of it.
Jack.
To what do I owe this pleasure?
I take no pleasure in this,
Arvin.
I've got the artefact.
I'll meet you
at the rendezvous point.
I know you removed an artefact
from Project: Black Hole
to trade with The Covenant.
Based on
recently acquired intelligence,
we know Sark was promoted
to co-command
The Covenant's
North American operations.
Senator Reed, it's imperative
we learn the identity
of his associate.
I enhanced the audio.
It turns out our friend Mr. Sark
made a phone call.
Notify the extraction team.
Not if I see you first, love.
See you later?
Lauren's parents
have been married for 34 years,
and they still love
being together.
I had one day off this month,
and I spent it playing hockey
at the rink
with high school kids.
That must be fun.
If I need it,
can I crash on your couch?
Yeah.
You just have to wipe off
the Cheese Nips.
Hey, I'm sorry, man.
Hello?
I may have a lead
on the box from Lot 45.
Not where it is,
but a map that'll lead us
to the key that opens it.
Project: Black Hole has had
the Rambaldi box for two years,
and hasn't been able to do that.
Without the key, The Covenant
won't be able to, either.
That's why we have to get it.
I'm getting the intel
from Mexico City.
Plane's waiting on you at Dover.
- I'd like to go with him.
- Is that a good idea?
Sloane was clear.
Whatever is in the box presents
a significant threat to you.
Sloane could be lying.
Even if he's not, the box
has one inscription on it.
"Irina."
I need to find out why.
You'll report to me as soon as
you get back from Mexico City.
Lauren.
Your father has ordered
an official enquiry
into the disappearance
of the box
from Project: Black Hole.
I've already been questioned
about what I know.
Which is nothing.
I appreciate that.
Not at all.
You know where my loyalties lie.
The box you lost
has not been opened
since the time of Rambaldi,
though there is a legend
Joseph Stalin
made the greatest effort.
Stalin knew about Rambaldi?
He, too, was a believer.
The Rambaldi box
is of particular interest,
because it was rumoured
to contain the strain
of a plague-like bioweapon
capable of killing millions.
Stalin obtained the box.
But the key to opening it
eluded him.
He sent teams of archaeologists
around the globe
in search of the key.
As legend has it, in 1941,
a discovery was made
in the Karoo desert.
What they found was a map
made of crystal.
The etchings in the crystal
were a guide to the key
that opened the box.
Unfortunately,
obsessed with gaining
sole credit for the discovery,
the archaeologists
turned on one another.
And the map,
along with the two men,
were reclaimed by the desert,
never to be heard from again.
Until now.
I received this two days ago
from a contact in South Africa.
Bomani.
Where are they?
The Karoo desert.
My contact surveilled Mr. Bomani
with a hidden camera
as he discovered the bodies
of the men and the map.
That's the map?
There are etchings
in the crystal.
A route of some kind.
This bioweapon.
What do you know about it?
Only that The Covenant
refers to it as The Passenger.
Where is your contact now?
Can we speak with him?
I am afraid not.
Bomani discovered
he was being surveilled.
Son of a bitch.
You see those trucks?
Omnifam.
Explain this to me.
Kazari Bomani using your trucks
to do The Covenant's work.
I entered into
a relationship with Bomani
at the insistence of the CIA,
who forced me to partner
with him
so I could stay close
to The Covenant.
Your job was to provide us
with intel,
not offer material
assistance to The Covenant
in their search
for The Passenger.
In order to maintain my cover,
I had to grant Bomani access
to certain Omnifam resources.
Check the report, Sydney.
I detailed all of this.
You committed treason
by spying on your country.
I won't put much stock
in your reports.
I'm not the mole
you're looking for.
You know what will happen
if your pardon agreement
is revoked.
The death penalty
that was commuted
when you entered into it
will be reinstated.
Then I will die knowing
that I have honoured
my agreement to the letter.
Where is Bomani?
I have no idea.
But in exchange for certain
creature comforts...
When I was falsely accused,
I was reading "The Iliad"
in the original Greek.
I'm listening.
All Omnifam trucks are equipped
with global positioning
transponders.
If I give you
the corresponding codes,
you can track Bomani's
movements via satellite.
You have such
a beautiful smile, Sydney.
I miss it.
If you're executed,
I'll be a witness.
I'll smile then.
So, how was your trip?
It was good.
Well, what happened?
You know, we...
We got what we needed to get,
and we're just waiting
to see how it pans out.
Michael.
I got you something
while you were gone.
Open it.
I realised I forgot
the anniversary
of your father's death.
I felt terribly,
and I wanted to do something
special to make up for it.
It's the watch he gave you.
I had it fixed.
This isn't working.
It's not?
Not the watch.
Us.
This isn't working for me.
I'm not happy.
I see.
I don't know.
I guess for a while,
I thought I could be again.
But I don't think
that's gonna happen.
I think we should separate.
This is about Sydney, isn't it?
No, it isn't.
Did she give you an ultimatum?
This is about us, our problem.
She is our problem.
Michael, if you're going
to destroy my life,
the least you can do
is be honest about why.
We have a problem.
Have you been made?
Of course not.
If he knew I was Covenant,
he would arrest me,
not break up with me.
Well, he's obviously
grown tired of you.
Perhaps because
of another woman?
My access extends
beyond my husband.
Perhaps.
But Vaughn is central
to the CIA's efforts
regarding The Passenger.
So you must do everything
possible to keep him close.
What are you proposing?
The last time Sydney Bristow
induced your husband
to stray from
a committed relationship,
he was dating Alice Williams.
When her father died...
Vaughn recommitted.
I am not going to kill
my father.
Need I remind you
that you expressed
no such compunction
about killing my father?
You asked me to kill Lazarey.
And now I'm asking you
to kill Senator Reed.
The answer is no.
Mrs. Reed,
my name is Jack Bristow.
I'm here to see your husband.
Please, come in.
George tells me
you work with Lauren.
Yes, I do.
What you all do is so important.
Forgive me for saying so,
but I think the country's
lucky to have her, don't you?
Absolutely.
The omnibus reconciliation bill
is snagged on the intel budget.
Can you believe that?
In this day and age.
Well, I'm off to give a speech
at the central library.
Olivia chairs
the largest literacy programme
in the country.
Does more good in a year
than I do in a 6-year term.
I'll be back after dinner.
Remember to take your pill.
It was very nice to meet you.
Okay.
Let's see it.
What I have is a paper trail.
Not definitive proof,
but the beginning of what
Director Dixon and I
believe to be a strong case
for the existence of a mole.
Other than Sloane?
Or instead of him.
At this point, that is unclear.
Is it that hard to identify
a traitor?
Honestly, sometimes I think
you people just get too close.
I don't understand.
Unauthorised by either
NSC or Central Intelligence.
Covert ops often go unrecorded.
60% of the flights listed
coincide with dates
and locations
where verifiable
Covenant activity occurred.
My daughter is
a committed public servant
who, despite my objections,
insisted on government service
because she felt
the responsibility
to give back to her country.
I understand this is difficult.
No, it's not.
Because there is nothing here.
Lauren is a patriot.
And I will not allow you
to ruin her reputation
based on innuendo
and supposition.
As I said...
...my findings are preliminary.
These are duplicates.
If, after reviewing them
more thoroughly,
you have any questions, call me.
Based on the transponder codes
Sloane gave us,
Marshall tracked
the Omnifam trucks
to the Russian consulate
at Gaborone.
The consulate general,
Petr Berezovsky,
has strong ties to The Covenant.
Upon your arrival, there'll be
a state event in progress.
You will proceed
to the second floor,
where we believe Sark and Bomani
may be analysing the map.
The second floor
of the consulate
is like a vault.
Satellite-resistant shielding.
Copper-lined walls.
Electrically conductive
concrete.
This is where you think
the map is located?
How do we gain access?
Sydney will be going in
as a Russian couture designer
interested in the local
diamond trade.
Vaughn, you and Weiss
will run backup.
Marshall's analysing the
security system and passwords.
He will brief you
on countermeasures and op-tech.
You leave in one hour.
Okay, Mountaineer.
Comms are hot.
I'm entering the party.
Copy.
Now locate Berezovsky.
I see him.
Firing up the microphone.
This choker will get you
to the second floor,
because the elevator controls
are password-operated by voice,
so you're gonna have
to talk like Berezovsky.
I designed a high-resolution
miniature microphone
that I placed inside
of the choker.
The password is "mockingbird."
In Russian.
That will be easy
to get him to say.
You won't have to.
I designed a voice-construction
software program
that will allow you to
reconstruct the password
once Sydney gets Berezovsky to
say enough phonemes.
Piece of cake, right?
I'm Paulina Alexandrova.
Yes, Madison Avenue.
This guy sounds like a frog.
Is this thing gonna work?
I don't know.
We'll find out.
On my way in, Syd.
I'll reconstruct the password
and have it uplinked
by the time
you reach the elevator.
Okay, stay sharp.
Sark and Bomani
could be upstairs.
With our computer scan
of the map,
we have narrowed our search
to a radius of 100 square miles.
The rendering should
pinpoint the location
by this time tomorrow.
Well done.
Thank you.
The guards are doing
a 2-minute sweep.
Bomani and Sark might be
in the building.
The elevator will take you
to the second floor.
You might run into
Sark and Bomani.
It's no good.
Got it.
Let me try something.
Gun.
Try it now.
No, it's still red.
Watch it. Got a guard
approaching from the south.
I think I got it.
Try again.
We're on our way up.
You will go to Vienna
and get everything ready.
I will meet you there,
and we'll retrieve the key.
Very well.
Well, that was extravagant.
I trust no one, Mr. Sark.
And it is best
you remember that.
There it is.
We're in.
Whoa, whoa!
It looks like you
triggered a silent alarm.
Get the crystal and get out.
Yes?
Somebody's here.
Got it.
Go!
Take my gun.
We're going over.
- Ready?
- Ready.
They have the crystal.
I'll get them.
The Covenant may have
discovered how to read this.
Even if we figure out
where it leads,
Bomani may get there first.
Dixon forwarded the picture
of the crystal
on to Project: Black Hole.
I'll call and ask if they have
the device that can read it.
Lauren and I are separating.
When we get home,
I'm on Weiss' couch.
Are you sure that's
what you really want?
It is.
Can I help you, Ms. Reed?
Run a check
against a user account.
Number DY692.
I'm sorry.
Those records are sealed.
I have S.C.I.
Ievel-nine clearance.
You can check
with the office of security.
- Protocol.
- I understand.
Here we go.
Jack Bristow accessed my files.
My intrusion-detection program
logged his user account.
What information was
he interested in specifically?
My travel itinerary
for the last five months.
Expense reports,
rental car receipts.
My phone logs.
I can't risk being exposed.
Well, then I strongly
suggest you reconsider
eliminating your father.
How will that help
this situation?
We can associate him
with the breaches.
If you have another suggestion,
now is the time to make it.
Good.
Then we're agreed.
It operates under
the same principles
as a kaleidoscope.
It contains loose pieces
of coloured glass
reflected by mirrors
set at certain angles
that create patterns when viewed
through the end of the tube.
In this case,
the pattern is a map.
Made up of three crystals.
All of which are required
to properly read the map.
Sloane had collected only two.
Now that we have all three,
what does the map look like?
Check it out.
Do we know where that is?
I ran the image through
every known land chart.
I adjusted for erosion,
acid rain, natural disaster.
I couldn't find a match.
The map revealed nothing?
Not to me, sir.
Sorry.
Based on your intel,
we were able to acquire
what we were looking for
from Bomani.
I'm happy I could help.
The problem is,
we can't interpret
the data it generated.
Excellent.
"The Iliad."
So, how may I be of service?
You found the third crystal.
Thank you.
Tell us what you see.
Rambaldi encrypted
many of his discoveries.
Or divided them into pieces
so that if the authorities
discovered any single piece,
the true meaning of his work
would not be revealed.
That's true of the crystals.
And the keys they lead to.
- Keys?
- Disks, to be precise.
There are four disks that
fit perfectly into the slots
carved into the Rambaldi box.
We know the crystals are a map.
We don't know to where.
What you've been
looking at doesn't sync up
to any known topography.
You know better
than anyone, Sydney.
There isn't anywhere on Earth
that Rambaldi
or his followers wouldn't go
to hide one of his creations.
We've looked
everywhere on Earth.
Really, Marcus?
Have you?
Or is it simply that you've
looked everywhere on land?
Okay, now this
is what I was looking at.
It's your basic land mass.
But then...
if I compare the topography
with oceanic mapping...
Sloane is a genius.
I mean,
an evil, horrible genius.
Bad man.
But still a genius.
The Yonaguni rock formation
off the coast of Okinawa.
I want you two
in flight immediately.
There's time to spec out
the mission en route.
Op-tech will be waiting for you
when you land.
Senator Reed called.
He's reviewed the documents
and wants to meet.
We owed him the courtesy
of informing him in advance.
As soon as your conversation
is complete,
we need to inform the FBI
and have her taken into custody.
Hello, Father.
I didn't hear you come in.
I've been here a while
talking to Mom.
Shut the door.
There's something
we need to discuss
that I don't want
your mom to hear.
She's a great woman, your mom.
Put up with a lot.
Me being away.
Congress all these years.
It's a burden.
Don't think I don't know it.
On you, too.
It'd break your mother's heart
if she ever found out
about this.
I know because it broke mine.
If it's any consolation,
I believe the cause
I am working for is just.
I feel like I let you down.
Like it's my fault,
and that if I help you
get out of it,
we could start over somehow.
Get out of it?
I could tell the Agency
I had learned there was a mole
in the Rotunda six months ago,
and that I've been conducting
my own investigation.
I'm a Senator
on the Intelligence Committee.
No one would say a word.
You would do that for me?
Of course I would.
I love you.
It's a clever plan,
and I'll definitely use it.
However, it only solves
one of my problems.
Lauren, what are you doing?
Get on your knees.
You can't do this.
Hands behind your head.
Do as I say!
Lauren, please, don't do this.
God, what are you doing?
Give me the gun, Lauren.
Sark said you might back out.
Send them up.
I'm so sorry.
Tell me what happened.
I'd been out shopping,
and I...
I came back, and...
George was there.
He was just sitting,
gazing out the window.
He started talking,
saying something
about our country.
That our government
was ineffectual.
He said he'd made
certain choices.
That when they came out,
no one would understand.
I told him
whatever was going on...
...we could get through it.
He said Lauren
would be implicated, too,
that he'd asked her
to do things...
I don't know,
access records on his behalf.
I went to the kitchen,
and that's...
That's when I heard the shot.
I mean, I'm his wife.
I should have known.
These people
he was talking about.
The Covenant.
He made it sound like
they were terrorists.
Mom.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
Alright, Mountaineer,
just course 6 degrees southwest.
Target acquired.
They'll be out of radio contact
until they resurface.
What is this place?
Looks like it's been
fortified over the years.
Probably by the followers
of Rambaldi
to protect his artefacts
from ever being removed.
Well, next time they'll have to
do a better job.
What's that?
I'm not sure.
What is that?
Hold on a second.
I'll enhance.
It's a helicopter.
With divers.
Four of them, sir.
Syd, Vaughn.
You've got four incoming bogeys.
I repeat, four bogeys.
Do you copy?
As long as they're in that cave,
the signal's down.
These never have to
see the surface.
What do you mean?
If what's in the Rambaldi box
is a danger to you,
and these keys are the only
way to open it,
maybe they should be destroyed.
Thank you for saying that.
Put down your weapon.
I could never have found these
without your help.
I thank you for that.
You remind me of your mother.
I'm sure she would be
pleased to know
I got the keys from you.
After all,
The Passenger is Irina's legacy.
Bring me the satchel.
Bomani's got the keys.
Vaughn, our hose has been cut.
The DPV's shot.
How long can you hold
your breath?
A free swim?
No way. We'd never make it
out of the tunnel.
It's too far.
We don't have a choice.
There's got to be something
in here we can use.
There.
The tank's full.
The regulator's broken.
It's compressed air.
If we could release it properly,
it can act
as a propulsion device.
Hang on.
There they are.
How can you be sure?
The tracker they're wearing
emits a specific GPS frequency.
Nothing on the satellite feed
or from Naval Intelligence.
It's like Bomani
just disappeared.
And took the key
to The Passenger with him.
Vaughn.
I am sad for you.
For you and Lauren.
That you have to go
through this.
But I'm also hopeful.
That's what scares me.
I understand.
When we get home...
...you want to get
a cup of coffee?
Yeah.
I want to extend my condolences
on behalf of
the entire task force.
Thank you.
I have arranged
to make grief counselling
available at your convenience.
And a leave of absence
should you want one.
What's this?
My letter of resignation.
My actions violated the oath
I took to this country
and your trust.
Agents were put at risk
because of what I did.
Your behaviour,
while unacceptable,
is nevertheless understandable.
You were acting
at your father's instruction
in accordance
with what you believed
was approved
government protocol.
He told you he was conducting
an independent security check,
and you had no reason
to believe otherwise.
Many of us have suffered tragedy
on the job or at home.
When that happens,
we pull together.
This time will be no exception.
Your resignation
is not accepted.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'd like to go
and find my husband.
Did the forensics check out?
Yes.
The official cause of death
was suicide.
Do you accept that?
At this point,
I have no reason not to.
I assume this means
we no longer have reason
to hold Sloane.
Not necessarily.
You are here because we believed
you hacked into this office
and removed classified files.
We were wrong.
And those charges
are being dropped.
So, am I to understand
that you have apprehended
the mole?
Yes.
Senator George Reed.
George Reed admitted
to working for The Covenant?
He did.
And then he killed himself.
I wish to be released
immediately,
with apologies,
and my pardon agreement intact.
I'm sure you would.
But in going through
the senator's personal effects,
we discovered evidence that,
for the past year,
he has been consulting with you
regarding Rambaldi's work.
And, further,
that in direct violation
of your pardon agreement,
you handed over certain
Rambaldi artefacts
not to the DSR,
but directly
to the senator himself.
As a result,
we have been given authority
to officially revoke
your pardon agreement.
Meaning the sentence
you received
prior to the agreement
is being reinstituted.
In two weeks...
...you'll be executed
by lethal injection.
- Hello?
- Hi.
Hi.
I'm sorry about how
I got pulled away earlier.
How is she?
It's hard, dealing with
her father's death and betrayal.
Are you at Eric's?
No.
I see.
Well, I guess we won't be
getting that cup of coffee.
No, we're not.
Okay, I'm going to go.