Previously on Alias:
Something you should know.
I spent three years studying you
for my postdoctorate dissertation.
And to some degree
I understand you, Arvin.
And I can help you if you let me try.
I lie. I keep secrets.
I divulge only what I must
in order to elicit the reaction I need.
One of those secrets affects the
only two people I care about in the world.
Sydney and Jack Bristow.
This watch belonged to my father.
It's broken now,
but it used to keep perfect time.
He said,"You could set your heart
by this watch."
It stopped October 1, the day we met.
We will find each other.
We always find each other.
You two are gonna
continue working together.
You're gonna be heading up
our new North American cell.
That sounds just about right.
Now, of course, this doesn't absolve you
of your responsibilities.
Working overtime
as an agent for Uncle Sam.
Of course.
But in the meantime, may I suggest -
and this is just a suggestion -
that you put the kibosh on
your husband's extracurricular sextivities?
Lauren. Hi.
I see what's going on between
you and Michael, so let me be clear.
Stay the hell away from my husband.
Michael, what are you doing?
Sometimes I hate my job.
Baby, what's going on?
You know how doctors
always make you wait?
What?
When you go in for an appointment.
My dad hated that.
He used to say
he always kept his appointments
and everyone else
should do the same.
Are you OK?
Yeah.
I just... I was looking for my house keys
and I found this.
Why were you looking
for your house keys?
I couldn't sleep.
I thought I'd go for a jog.
What time is it?
I dunno. It's broken.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
I'll see you later.
Will he ever open his eyes?
Well, babies sleep, Weiss.
That's what they do, you know?
Except when they're screaming.
Last night from midnight to six.
- He's gorgeous, Marshall.
- Thanks.
Isn't he beautiful?
Looks like he has my nose.
- Oh, look at him.
- Thanks.
You know, last night he looked at me.
He barely opened his eyes,
but... I swear to God, guys,
Mitchell's a genius.
Oh, Mr. Bristow.
Take a look.
It's Mitchell. He's my guy.
- Cute.
- Thanks.
- Your tie's on backwards.
- Oh, I didn't get a lot of sleep.
You're familiar with the Shining Sword?
Fundamentalist terror network
based in the Philippines?
They've been dormant
since the Bali bombings of '02.
Are they operational again?
Earlier today we intercepted
a burst transmission
which indicates
that an operative of Shining Sword
has acquired a plasma charge.
Plasma charge?
I thought those were only theoretical.
According to the burst transmission,
the operative is shipping the bomb
to one of their European cells.
The transmission included specs.
Now, believe it or not,
these schematics are two times scale,
meaning this device is only six inches
in diameter. But it packs a wallop.
Now, this is a conservative interpolation
of the damage it would cause if detonated,
and this doesn't account for fires
or collateral explosions.
And...
Sorry. Dunno how that got in there.
That was at breakfast... Mitchell.
Is the bomb being shipped transpacific
or via the Atlantic?
We don't know,
but we traced the transmission
to a digital storage facility in Vancouver
where the Shining Sword operative
maintains his database.
Were we able to hack in?
Well, DigiStash is basically
a self-storage facility for digital files -
corporate records, medical databases,
that sort of stuff -
so their firewall's state of the art.
I wouldn't be able to hack the database
unless someone on the inside
were to open up a port.
Sydney, Vaughn. You'll go to the facility
looking to lease vault space.
Once inside you'll uplink with Marshall.
Now, if we're lucky, the operative will
have archived the details of the shipment
and we can intercept the bomb
before it's delivered.
Shall I tell them the idea I had?
I had a great idea what you guys should...
I think you should pose
as radio astronomers.
You know, looking to back up
your recordings of interplanetary noise.
Now, I came up with a little cheat sheet
that should help you,
and you can review this en route.
And one more thing.
The Covenant may have intercepted
CIA intelligence
regarding our mission in North Korea
and our pursuit of the Doleac agenda.
Langley has assigned
a counterintelligence team
to determine whether someone within
the agency has been leaking information.
Jack will run point on their investigation
inside this office.
Marshall, Lauren, I've scheduled you
in the first round of interviews.
You'll be available later this afternoon?
Actually, I'm due in DC tonight
for an NSC briefing,
but I'll call them
and let them know I can't make it.
That's OK. As soon as you return, then.
Weiss, you'll go instead.
Good. Let's get moving.
Lauren, we need to talk.
Lauren?
- How you doing?
- I'm fine.
Hey, guess what? It's me.
Come on. How you doing?
I'm hanging in there.
How was Lauren about it?
- She didn't remember.
- And you didn't say anything?
Nah. I mean, she's got a lot on her mind.
Yeah, that's probably it.
- Hello?
- Dr. Barnett, this is Arvin Sloane.
I'm calling to apologise for my discourteous
behaviour the other day when we met.
I'm not accustomed to just
simply sitting around and talking.
- Well, not everyone is.
- Yeah.
Actually, it would have been
much more simple
if there had been a bottle
of Château Haut-Brion on the table.
Excuse me?
I'm suggesting that we talk over dinner.
You know? In vino veritas?
I know a lovely little
out-of-the-way restaurant
in a former sewing machine factory.
It's called Brasserie Al Pontile.
I'm hoping you enjoy French cuisine.
Well, that wouldn't be very professional.
Well, why don't you consider it
an office with food?
After all, psychoanalysts do eat dinner,
don't they?
Zurich is such a lovely city.
It would be criminal for you to dine alone.
At any rate, you know the name of the
restaurant. I shall be there at eight o'clock
and I am hoping you'll join me.
Goodbye, Dr. Barnett.
So you're looking for alien life?
In a manner of speaking.
Our radio telescopes inspect the cosmos,
Iooking to detect artificially generated
signals. Basically, anything below 300Hz.
But don't worry. The alien invasion
is still a few months away.
As we discussed over the phone,
our telescopes gather over 350 gigabytes
of information per day.
Not a problem. Our vaults are designed
to accommodate teraflops.
You could store 20 years of data
in the vault you've leased.
Number 2289 please, Luc.
Data is backed up twice daily. The servers
are monitored around the clock.
Climate control, fire suppression,
all state of the art.
- The interface is hot-swappable.
- Oh, great.
If you need anything, you can call me.
Thank you.
Luc?
OK, guys. Let me know when you're
connected to the mainframe, OK?
Copy that.
OK, now, once we download
the shipping information
we should be able to pinpoint
the location of the plasma charge.
Connection established.
Oh, listen, I wanted to
ask you something. The truth, now.
Your science-geek character -
was that supposed to be me?
- Your son.
- Funny.
Although that would have been pretty cool,
don't you think?
Little Mitchell working
side by side with his old man.
- We're downloading now.
- I see it. Another 15 seconds.
Marshall, what's happening?
I don't know. There's someone else
in the system with you.
Here, from our end?
It has to be.
There's no other way to access the files.
I think they just planted a virus.
It has to be the Covenant.
The mole must have leaked our intel.
They beat us here.
You guys, listen to me.
Disconnect from their system
before their virus affects our copy.
- Did we get the shipping information?
- I'm not sure.
I'll have to see if I can reconstruct the data
from what we've got.
Let's get out of here.
Please. Don't do this.
The shooter.
There! Vaughn!
The F-150.
Vaughn!
How much of the data
did we get our hands on?
Looks like 63 percent,
give or take a few megs.
Oh, I slept 20 minutes last night, FYI.
How long before
you can extrapolate the rest?
Well, I ran the code through a high-grade
decryption algebra... algorithms, I mean.
Oh, but you should look at this,
stare at this, right here. It's like a lava lamp.
- If you look... I passed out before when I...
- Marshall, how long?
12 hours?
We don't have 12 hours. If the Covenant
gets their hands on the plasma charge...
Sydney. I know.
The decryption program will work,
but it just requires a little time.
I'm out of coffee. I had 12 cups
and I'm not feeling anything.
You'd think it would... Caffeine...
I'm gonna check if it's the real deal.
- Do you guys want?
- No, thank you.
Oh, by the way, after six hours
in the hot seat
from the boys from counterintelligence,
Langley has declared me exhausted,
but free from suspicion.
Never had a doubt in my mind.
Is something wrong?
- No. No. Just getting old, I guess.
- You expect me to believe that?
Just had a lot on my mind lately,
that's all. It'll pass.
Yesterday was the day,
wasn't it?
The anniversary
of your father's death.
How could you remember that?
I remember what missing him
does to you.
Sorry.
Hey.
How was your day?
- Oh, frustrating. Hit a bit of a roadblock.
- Anything I can help you with?
No, but thanks for asking.
Michael, would you mind
holding a second?
No, go ahead.
Sweetheart, I'm sorry,
but I'm being called away. I love you.
Uh, you too.
Glad you came.
So that we're clear, I'm here
for professional reasons only.
Oh, we're clear.
Although I must say
I don't necessarily believe you.
Well, I told you that I was writing about you,
but I haven't told you
the premise of my thesis.
Aha. Well, I would say I'm fascinated,
but that would sound egomaniacal,
wouldn't it?
Salud.
You certainly have given proof
that anyone can change for the better.
Given the proper stimuli.
You look beautiful. Beautiful.
That's just a layman's opinion, Dr. Barnett.
All I'm saying is that
you made a remarkable transformation.
Master spy to humanitarian.
Yeah.
Well, sometimes I wonder which is harder.
The Rambaldi device was instrumental
in your transformation.
Oh, yes, it was critical.
It only revealed one word to you.
- "Peace."
- That's correct.
And yet there were eight yards
of parchment scroll
before the message appeared.
- What was on that?
- Oh. It was nothing. Blank paper.
Sort of the equivalent of leader tape
on a cassette.
I discarded it.
I'm not quite sure why you did that.
You could have studied it,
sold it, kept it for antiquity.
It's hard to believe
that you threw away something
that you would normally consider holy.
Are you calling me a liar?
You almost revealed something
to me the other day.
A secret.
That wears on you.
Those were your words.
I am not your patient...
your client...
or your lab rat.
Now, we can speak in generalities,
have an elegant meal,
perhaps laugh together,
but there are some truths
you will never learn from me.
Do you understand that?
You must be ravenous. I suggest the
Barbary duckling. It's their signature dish.
This was a mistake. Sorry.
Now, there are still several hundred
gigabytes to decipher,
but I was at least able to decode this.
Freighter. Liberian registry.
Will dock in Lisbon, 14 hours.
- How do we locate the bomb?
- With this.
It is a modified explosives sniffer.
Now, I've added plasma to the list
of detectable compounds that it detects.
You know, like Semtex,
dynamite, HMX, you know.
It works just like
a normal tracking device.
When you're within 100 feet,
"bling, bling, bling".
- Found the prize in the Cracker Jack.
- 100 feet.
Sorry, I would have done better
if I'd had a little more sleep.
Base Ops, this is Mountaineer.
We're on board.
We have you five-by,
Mountaineer.
Perimeter is clear. Now let's fire up
that sniffer and find the bomb, baby.
- Hot or cold?
- Freezing.
Wait, I think we've got something.
Towards the stern, 30 yards below us.
We've got tone below deck,
possibly the engine room.
Copy that. Proceed.
Mountaineer? Boy Scout? Report.
- Sydney, do you copy?
- Vaughn, are you OK?
Michael, what are you doing?
Sometimes I hate my job.
Baby, what's going on?
I was looking for my house keys
and I found this.
Why were you looking
for your house keys?
I couldn't sleep.
I thought I'd go for a jog.
What time is it?
I dunno. It's broken.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
I'll see you later.
- This better be good.
- And a good morning to you, too.
You paged me on my NSC cellphone.
You know that they track
all incoming numbers.
This cellphone's been cloned,
so you have nothing to worry about.
We've just learned that
a freelance munitions expert
has created a cutting-edge technology.
One that he's since sold
to one of our rivals.
We need you to filter back any CIA intel
that might help us get a lock on it.
You called me to remind me to do my job?
Darling, it's not like that.
Yeah.
You're familiar with the Shining Sword?
Fundamentalist terror network
based in the Philippines?
They've been dormant
since the Bali bombings of '02.
Are they operational again?
Earlier today we intercepted
a burst transmission
which indicates
that an operative of Shining Sword
has acquired a plasma charge.
Plasma charge?
I thought those were only theoretical.
According to the burst transmission,
the operative is shipping the bomb
to one of their European cells.
Is the bomb being shipped transpacific
or via the Atlantic?
We don't know,
but we traced the transmission
to a digital storage facility in Vancouver
where the Shining Sword operative
maintains his database.
Sydney, Vaughn. You'll go to the facility
looking to lease vault space.
Once inside you'll uplink with Marshall.
Now, if we're lucky, the operative will
have archived the details of the shipment
and we can intercept the bomb
before it's delivered.
Lauren, we need to talk.
Lauren?
Everything I needed to say
I've already said.
Then here's my turn.
The implication that somehow I've set out
to undermine your marriage
is wrong and unfair.
I've done nothing but respect
the relationship that you and Vaughn have.
You were saying?
Vaughn and I have a history,
a complicated one.
I can't deny that,
but I won't apologise for it either.
If your marriage is in trouble,
if you and Vaughn are having problems,
I suggest you leave me out of it
and take it up with your husband.
Are you ready for our first job
as senior management?
You're so ambitious. I love it.
The job's in Vancouver. It requires
a breach of a digital storage facility.
- Really? What's the prize?
- A plasma charge.
Next-generation destructive power.
- I thought those were just theoretical.
- Apparently not in Vancouver.
- All right. I'll meet you there in four hours.
- Three.
We have to be first in line.
The CIA are sending agents.
- Who?
- One guess.
Oh, sweetheart. This should be fun.
I'll see you in Vancouver.
Don't be late.
Or call me "sweetheart".
Ambitious and domineering.
Fantastic.
How long before
Sydney and Vaughn get here?
20 minutes, if that.
Well, you'd better show me
the meaning of haste.
Once we have the transport information,
I'll corrupt the files, leave the CIA blind.
It looks like another black mark
on your husband's record.
How does it feel to systematically ruin
a man from the inside out?
It wouldn't be the first time.
Buzz me into 2201.
As we discussed over the phone,
our telescopes gather over 350 gigabytes
of information per day.
Not a problem. Our vaults are designed
to accommodate teraflops.
You could store 20 years of data
in the vault you've leased.
Number 2289 please, Luc.
Data is backed up twice daily. The servers
are monitored around the clock.
Hurry. Hurry.
..his former sweetheart are early.
They're headed for room 2289.
Planting the virus now.
Get out and get the car ready.
You are so controlling.
Move it. I'm right behind you.
If you need anything, you can call me.
Thank you.
Luc?
Marshall, what's happening?
I don't know. There's someone else
in the system with you.
Here, from our end?
It has to be.
There's no other way to access the files.
I think they just planted a virus.
Luc?
Has anybody seen Luc?
God.
Drop the walkie.
Please. Don't hurt me.
You think about pointing that gun at me
and I'll shoot you in the heart.
The couple in room 2289, when they
come out, I want you to kill them both.
- What?
- Or you die. It's your choice.
But I haven't shot a gun...
- This isn't a negotiation.
- OK. OK.
Let's get out of here.
Please. Don't do this.
The shooter.
There! Vaughn!
- They're right behind us.
- Yes, thank you, I can see that.
Vaughn!
Stop the car.
- What are you talking about?
- Stop the car now. Pull in here.
How was your day?
- Oh, frustrating. Hit a bit of a roadblock.
- Anything I can help you with?
No, but thanks for asking.
Michael, would you mind
holding a second?
No, go ahead.
I'm working.
Sweetheart, I'm sorry,
but I'm being called away. I love you.
Uh, you too.
- Tell me, did they spot us?
- No, I don't think so.
According to the transport order,
the ship docks in 16 hours.
We should get going.
You should know...
you were amazing.
Before, I mean.
Typically, this is where
you return the compliment.
I am not your patient...
your client...
or your lab rat.
But there are some truths
you will never learn from me.
Do you understand that?
This was a mistake. Sorry.
Hi.
Could I get my coat, please?
Until I turned into a complete son of a
bitch, we were having a wonderful evening.
Something we can both agree on.
Though I am now known
as a humanitarian...
Your words, not mine.
I sometimes regress.
Dr. Barnett, I'm sorry I snapped at you.
Trusting you, trusting anyone,
will take time.
You know so much about me.
I know almost nothing about you.
I want to. Very much.
I'm not sure I can understand
how your manipulating this date
can help you gain my trust.
Would you excuse us for a moment?
Thanks.
You want my secret?
I'll tell you. But only you.
I have betrayed people,
many of whom deserved it.
But only one didn't.
It was a long time ago.
I sometimes try to convince myself
that it was worth it, that she was worth it.
What is this? You had an affair?
Yes.
It was Irina Derevko.
Sydney's mother.
Jack never knew. Emily, my wife,
she never knew.
Irina and I pledged to take that secret
to our graves.
Are you telling me
Sydney... is your daughter?
I never tried to prove it,
one way or the other.
But the strength that Sydney finds within...
I like to believe that comes from me.
Well, how about that?
The world didn't come to an end.
Base Ops, this is Mountaineer.
We're on board.
We have you five-by, Mountaineer.
- Hot or cold?
- Freezing.
It's a tranquilliser dart.
The humanitarian work of the CIA.
Let's go.
Towards the stern,
30 yards below us.
We can't let them go below deck.
Mountaineer? Boy Scout? Report.
Vaughn, are you OK?
Yeah. I'm fine.
But I'm glad I wore the vest.
We have to get the bomb.
- Meet me in the engine room.
- I'm going to the upper deck.
It's just ahead.
Go to the engine room.
I'll cover.
It's secured.
I'm gonna need a minute.
Freeze.
Drop the gun.
Put your hands in the air.
Put your hands in the air!
Now turn around. Slowly.
Turn around.
Take off the mask.
Do it. Take off the mask.
Put the gun down, Agent Vaughn.
- Drop the gun.
- Not a chance. You drop yours.
- Put the gun down now. Drop it!
- No, Vaughn, don't!
If you love her,
you'll put the gun down now.
Vaughn, don't!
Sark's got the bomb.
OK, you go after him.
I'm gonna cut off Sark.
Got it!
I've lost mine.
Freeze!
Give me the bomb.
Give it to me.
With pleasure.
Sark activated the bomb.
I've got to defuse it.
OK, describe it to me.
All right. It looks sort of like a
VS-5 land mine, but with a timer attached.
We have 40 seconds.
- Vaughn, find the power source.
- A battery, something like that.
All right. There's something here. It looks
like a cellphone wrapped in fibre optics.
- No, no, no. Don't touch that.
- He's right. It's a secondary trigger.
33 seconds.
OK, find the blue wire
attached to the screw
and then open up the valve
near the stem.
I did that. It's still ticking.
We have 14 seconds.
Listen. You're gonna short it.
Strip the black wire and the red wire
and then attach them together.
I don't know if
I'm gonna have time to do that.
No, you can do it. You can do it.
You can do it. You can do it, Vaughn.
You can do it. You can do it.
You can do it.
Plasma charge is secure.
See? Told you you could do it.
- You're an angel for waiting.
- Hey.
No problem. I've had good company.
How was Washington?
Awful. I'm happier now that
I'm home with you.
Me too.
- I'm sorry.
- It's OK.
Hello?
It killed you, didn't it?
Seeing him drop the gun for Sydney.
No, it isn't a good time.
Can I call you in the morning?
He's there with you, is that it?
Though he'd rather be with her.
You know, it's quite a charade
you two are engaged in.
I think we both know how dedicated I am
to this assignment.
If you have any issues,
take it up through the proper channels.
Don't mistake me.
It's not your dedication that I question.
We'll talk about this later.
Sorry about that.
Work is officially over.
What was that for?
I just miss you.
- I thought you'd be home by now.
- I was about to say the same to you.
The plasma charge.
It's in our hands.
Sark isn't.
The Covenant.
Have you had dinner?
If memory serves,
you always liked Michelli's.
I haven't eaten there since I was eight.
I do eat, you know.
I'd like that, actually.