Merry christmas, grandpa.
Oh, merry christmas to you, stevie.
Did you bring me any presents?
Now, why would i want to do that?
'Cause it's christmas.
Oh, i thought santa claus
Brought the presents at christmas.
You have been a good boy
this year, haven't you?
I have, i swear.
Well, then, who
knows?Maybe he'll come.
Santa!
Reindeer.
Santa?
Um, my daughter and
i were in our beds.
Mike was downstairs
decorating the tree.
I heard a thump on the roof,
And then i-I heard mike scream,
And now i'm talking to the fbi.
And you didn't see any of it?
No, he was... he was just gone.
The doors were locked?There
was no forced entry?
That's right.
Does anybody else
have a key?My parents.
Where do they live?
Florida.
Thanks for letting me have
a look around, mrs. Walsh.
I think we, uh, got just
about everything we need.
We're all set.
We'll be in touch.
Agents...
T
- The police said my husband might have been kidnapped.
Could be.
Then why haven't
the kidnappers called
O- Or - Or
demanded a ransom?
It's three days till christmas.
What am i supposed
to tell our daughter?
We're very sorry.
Find anything?
Stockings, mistletoe... this.
A tooth?Where was this?
In the chimney.
No way a man fits up a
chimney. It's too narrow.
No way he fits up in one piece.
All right, so, if dad
went up the chimney -
We need to find out what
dragged him up there.
So, was i right?
Is it the serial-Killing
chimney sweep?
Yep.
It's, uh, it's
actually dick van dyke.
Who?
"Mary poppins. "Who's that?
Oh, come on -Never mind.
It turns out that walsh
is the second guy in town
Grabbed out of his
house this month.
Oh, yeah?Yeah.
The other guy get dragged
up the chimney, too?
Don't know. Witnesses said
they heard a thump on the roof.
So, what the hell do you
think we're dealing with?
Actually, i have an idea. Yeah?
It's, uh, it's gonna sound crazy.
What could you possibly
say that sounds crazy to me?
Evil santa.
Yeah, that's crazy.
Yeah... i mean, i'm just saying
That there's some version of
the anti-Claus in every culture.
You got belsnickel,
krampus, black peter.
Whatever you want to call
it, there's all sorts of lore.
Saying what?
Saying back in the day,
santa's brother went rogue,
And now he shows up
around christmastime.
Instead of bringing presents,
he punishes the wicked.
By hauling their ass up chimneys?
For starters, yeah.
So, this is your theory,
huh? Santa's shady brother?
Well, i'm just saying,
that's what the lore says.
Santa doesn't have a
brother. There is no santa.
Yeah, i know.
You're the one who told
me that in the first place
Remember?
Yeah, you know
what?I could be wrong.
I...
...got to be wrong.
Maybe, maybe not.
What?
I did a little digging
- Turns out both victims
Visited the same place
before they got snatched.
Where?
It does kind of lend credence
to the theory, don't it?
Yeah, but anti-Claus?
Couldn't be.
It's a christmas miracle.
Hey, speaking of, we
should have one this year.
Have one what?A christmas.
No, thanks.
No, we'll get a tree,
a little boston market -
Just like when we were little.
Dean, those weren't exactly
hallmark memories for me.
What are you talking about?
We had some great christmases.
Whose childhood are
you talking about?
Oh, come on, sam.
No, just... no.
All right, grinch.
What is that?
A present for dad.
Yeah, right.
Where'd you get
the money -Steal it?
No. Uncle bobby gave
it to me to give to him.
Said it was real special.
What is it?
A pony.
Very funny.
Dad's gonna be here, right?
He'll be here.
It's christmas.
He knows.
And he'll be here -Promise.
Where is he, anyway?
On business.
What kind of business?
You know that.
He sells stuff.
What kind of stuff?Stuff.
Nobody ever tells me anything.
Then quit asking.
Is dad a spy?
Mm-Hmm. He's james bond.
Why do we move around so much?
'Cause everywhere we go,
they get sick of your face.
I'm old enough, dean.
You can tell me the truth.
You don't want to know
the truth. Believe me.
Is that why we never
talk about... mom?
Shut up!
Don't you ever talk about mom
- Ever!
Wait. Where are you going?
Out.
You'd think with the 10 bucks
it costs to get into this place,
Santa could scrounge
up a little snow.
What?
Nothing. What are we
looking for, again?
Lore says that the anti-Claus
Will walk with a limp
and smell like sweets.
Great. So we're looking
for a pimp santa.
Why the sweets?
Think about it, dean.
If you smell like candy
The kids will come
closer, you know?
That's creepy.
How does this thing know
Who's been naughty
and who's been nice?
I don't know.
So, ronny, come
sit on santa's knee.
Ah, there you go.
You been a good boy this year?Yeah
Good.
Santa's got a special gift for you
Maybe we do
Welcome to santa's court.
Can i escort your child to santa?
N
- No. No.
Uh, but, actually,
my brother here -
It's been a lifelong dream of his.
Uh, sorry. No kids over... 12.
No, he's just kidding. We
only came here to watch.
I- I didn't mean that
we came here to w-Y
Thanks a lot, dean.
Thanks for that.
Check it out.
Are you seeing this?
A lot of people walk
with limps, right?
Tell me you didn't smell
that. That was candy, man.
That was ripple
- I think. Had to be.
Maybe. We willing
to take that chance?
What time is it?
Same as the last time you asked.
Here.
Caffeinate.
Wonderful.
Hey, sam...
Yeah?
Why are you the boy
that hates christmas?
Dean... i mean, i admit it -
We had a few bumpy holidays
when we were kids. "Bumpy"?
That was then. We'll
do it right this year.
Look, dean, if you
want to have christmas
Knock yourself out.
Just don't involve me.
Oh, yeah, that'd be great -
Me and myself making
cranberry molds.
What's up with saint nicotine?
What?
Nothing.
It's just that,
uh... well, you know,
Mr. Gung ho christmas might
have to blow away santa.
What the hell are you doing here?
I'm really not interested, okay?
Jingle my bells...
S
- Silent night
Holy...
...night... night
* all is well * all is well
* all is dry
* bright
* 'round and 'round
* the table...
Santa, you're early!
So, that's how your son
described the attack?
"Santa took daddy up the chimney"?
That's what he says, yes.
And where were you?
I was asleep.
And all of a sudden...
...i was being dragged
out of bed, screaming.
Did you see the attacker?
It was dark, and he hit me.
He knocked me out.
I'm sorry. I know this is hard.
Yeah... um, mrs. Caldwell,
Where did you get that
wreath above the fireplace?
Excuse me?
Just curious, you know.
Wreaths, huh?
Sure you didn't want to
ask her about her shoes?
I saw some nice
handbags in the foyer.
We've seen that
wreath before, dean.
Where?
The walshes'.Yesterday.
I know, i was just testing you.
Yeah. All right. Well,
keep looking, would you?
Thanks, bobby.
What did bobby say?
Uh, that we're morons.
He also said
That it was probably
meadowsweet in those wreaths.
Wow! Amazing.
What the hell is meadowsweet?
It's pretty rare,
And it's probably the most
powerful plant in pagan lore.
Pagan lore? Yeah.
See, they used meadowsweet
for human sacrifices.
It was kind of like
a... chum for their gods.
Gods were drawn to
it, and they'd stop by
And snack on whatever
was the nearest human.
Why would somebody be using
that for christmas wreaths?
It's not as crazy
as it sounds, dean.
I mean, pretty much every
christmas tradition is pagan.
Christmas is jesus' birthday.
No, jesus' birthday was
probably in the fall.
It was actually the
winter solstice festival
That was co-Opted by the
church and renamed "christmas. "
But the yule log, the
tree, even santa's red suit
That's all remnants
of pagan worship.
How do you know that?
What are you gonna tell me next?
Easter bunny's jewish?
So, you think we're
dealing with a pagan god?
Yeah, probably hold nickar,
god of the winter solstice.
And all these martha
stewart wannabes,
Buying these fancy wreaths...
It's pretty much like putting
a neon sign on your front door
Saying, "come kill us. "
Great.
When you sacrifice to hold nickar,
Guess what he gives you in return.
Lap dances, hopefully.
Mild weather.
Like no snow in the
middle of december
In the middle of
michigan. For instance.
Do we know how to kill it yet?
No, bobby's working
on that right now.
We got to figure out where
they're selling those wreaths.
You think they're
selling them on purpose?
Feeding the victims to this thing?
Let's find out.
Help you boys?
Uh, hope so.
Uh, we were playing jenga with
the walshes the other night,
And he hasn't shut up since
about this christmas wreath.
I don't know. You tell him.
Sure.
It was yummy.
I sell a lot of wreaths, guys.
Right, right, but you see,
This one would have
been really special.
It had, uh, it had, uh, green
leaves, um, white buds on it.
It might have been made
of, uh, meadowsweet?
Well... aren't you a fussy one?
He is.
Anyway, i know the one
you're talking about.
I'm all out.
Seems like this meadowsweet
stuff's rare and expensive.
Why make wreaths out of it?
Beats me. I didn't make them.
Who did?
Madge carrigan a local lady.
Said the wreaths were so
special, she gave them for free.
She didn't charge you? Nope.
Did you sell them for free?
Hell, no. It's christmas.
People pay a buttload
for this crap.
That's the spirit.
How much do you think a
meadowsweet wreath would cost?
A couple hundred dollars, at least.
This lady's giving
them away for free?
What do you think about that?
Well, sounds pretty suspicious.
Remember that wreath dad
brought home that one year?
Do you mean the one he stole
from, like, a liquor store?
Yeah, it was a bunch
of empty beer cans.
That thing was great.
I bet if i looked
around hard enough,
I could probably
find one just like it.
All right...
Dude...
What's going on with you? What?
I mean, since when are you
bing crosby all of a sudden?
Why do you want to
do christmas so bad?
Why are you so against it?
Were your childhood
memories that traumatic?
No, that has nothing to do with it.
Then what?
I mean, i-I just
- I don't get it.
You haven't talked
about christmas in years.
Well, yeah.
This is my last year.
I know.
That's why i can't.
What do you mean?
I mean i can't just sit around,
Drinking eggnog,
pretending everything's okay
When i know next
christmas you'll be dead.
I just can't.
Thought you went out.
Yeah. To get you dinner.
Don't forget your vegetables.
I know why you keep a
gun under your pillow.
No, you don't. Stay
out of my stuff.
And i know why we lay
salt down everywhere we go.
No, you don't. Shut up.
Where'd you get that? That's dad's!
He's gonna kick your
ass for reading that.
Are monsters real?
What?You're crazy.
Tell me.
I swear, if you ever tell
dad i told you any of this,
I will end you.
Promise.
Well, the first
thing you have to know
Is we have the coolest
dad in the world.
He's a superhero.
He is? Yeah.
Monsters are real.
Dad fights them.
He's fighting them right now.
But dad said the monsters
under my bed weren't real.
That's 'cause he had
already checked under there.
But, yeah, they're real.
Almost everything's real.
Is santa real?
No.
If monsters are real,
then they could get us.
They could get me. Dad's
not gonna let them get you.
But what if they get him?
They aren't gonna get dad.
Dad's, like, the best.
I read in dad's book
that they got mom.
It's complicated, sam.
If they got mom, they can get dad.
And if they get
dad, they can get us.
It's not like that.
Okay, dad's fine.
We're fine.
Trust me.
You okay?
Yeah.
Hey, dad's gonna be
here for christmas...
Just like he always is.
I just want to go to sleep, okay?
Yeah, okay.
It'll all be better
when you wake up.
You'll see.
Promise.
This is where mrs.
Wreath lives, huh?
Can't you just feel
the evil pagan vibe?
Yes?
Please tell me you're the madge carrigan
who makes the meadowsweet wreaths.
Why, yes, i am.
Ha! Bingo.
Well, we were just
admiring your wreaths
In mr. Sylar's place the other day.
You were?
Well, isn't that meadowsweet
Just the finest-Smelling
thing you ever smelled?
It sure is.
But the problem is, is all
your wreaths had sold out
Before we got the chance
to buy one. Oh, fudge!
You wouldn't have another one
that we could buy from you?
No, i'm afraid those were the
only ones i had for this season.
Tell me something -
Why did you decide to make
them out of meadowsweet?
Why, the smell, of course!
I don't think i've ever
smelled anything finer.
Yeah, um, you mentioned that.
What's going on, honey?
Well, just some nice boys
asking about my wreaths, dear.
Oh, the wreaths are
fine. Fine wreaths.
Oh, care for some peanut brittle?
We're okay.
I knew it!
Something was way
off with those two.
What'd you find?
The carrigans lived
in seattle last year,
Where two abductions took
place right around christmas.
They moved here in january.
All that christmas crap in their
house wasn't boughs of holly.
It was vervain and mint.
Pagan stuff? Serious pagan stuff.
So, what, ozzie and harriet
are keeping a pagan god
Hidden underneath their
plastic-Covered couch?
I don't know. We got
to check them out.
So, what about bobby?
He's sure evergreen stakes
will kill this thing, right?
Yeah, he's sure.
See? Plastic.
Hey, dean.
Sam!
Gosh, i wish you boys
hadn't come down here.
Dean?
You okay?
Yeah, i think so.
So, i guess we're dealing
with mr. And mrs. God.
Nice to know.
Ooh, and here we
thought you two lazybones
Were gonna sleep straight
through all the fun stuff.
Miss all this? Nah, we're partyers.
Isn't he a kick in
the pants, honey?
You're hunters is what you are.
And you're pagan gods.
So, why don't we just call it
even and go our separate ways?
So you can bring more
hunters and kill us?
I don't think so!
You should have thought about
that before snacking on humans.
Oh, now, don't get all wet.
Oh, why, we used to take over
a hundred tributes a year.
And that's a fact.
Now what do we take?
What, two? Three?
Hardy boys here make five.
Now, that's not so bad, is it?
You say it like that, you
guys are the cunninghams.
You, mister, better
show us a little respect.
Or what? You'll eat us?
Not so fast.
There's rituals to
be followed first.
Oh, we're just
sticklers for ritual.
And you know what kicks
off the whole shebang?
Let me guess -Meadowsweet.
Oh, shucks -You're
all out of wreaths.
I guess we'll just have to
cancel the sacrifice, huh?
Oh, don't be such a gloomy gus.
There.
Don't they just look darling?
Good enough to eat.
All righty-Roo. Step number two.
Sammy.
Sammy!
D
- Don't!
Leave him alone,
you son of a bitch!
Hear how they talk to us? To gods?
Listen, pal, back in the day,
we were worshiped by millions.
Times have changed!
Tell me about it.
All of a sudden, this jesus character
is the hot new thing in town.
All of a sudden, our altars
are being burned down,
And we're being hunted
down like common monsters.
But did we say a peep?
Oh, no, no, no, we did not.
Two millennium.
We kept a low profile.
We got jobs, a mortgage.
We -What was that word, dear?
We assimilated.
Yeah, we assimilated.
Why, we play bridge on
tuesdays and fridays.
We're just like everybody else.
You're not blending in as
smooth as you think, lady.
This might pinch a bit, dear.
You bitch!
Oh, my goodness me!
Somebody owes a nickel
to the swear jar.
Oh, do you know what i say
when i feel like swearing?
"Fudge. "
I'll try and remember that!
You boys have no idea
how lucky you are.
There was a time when
kids came from miles around
Just to be sitting where you are.
What do you think
you're doing with those?
You fudging touch me again,
i'll fudging kill you!
Very good.
No, don't.
Oh, we've got a winner!
What else, dear?
Well, let's see. Uh,
fingernail, blood...
I forgot the tooth!
Oh, dear!
Merry christmas, sam.
Open wide... and say, "ahh. "
Somebody gonna get that?
You should get that.
Come on.
Merry christmas!
I told you i smelled fruitcake.
You shouldn't have.
Oh, bite your tongue.
It's my pleasure.
It looks scrumptious!
Neal and i are going
caroling. You care to join?
You know, we would...
It's my back
- Darn thing's giving me fits.
Oh, well, that's a shame.
- Oh, well. Merry christmas.
- And to you, too, dear.
- Hey, are we still on for bridge tomorrow?
- With bells on!
- Yes! Okay,
bye. -Bye-Bye.
Now, where were we?
What do we do now?!
The evergreen stake's
in the basement!
Well, we need more evergreen, dean!
I think i just found us some more.
Help me get this.
Go!
Come on!
You little thing...
I loved that tree.
Madge!
Merry christmas.
Sam, wake up.
Dad was here. Look what he brought.
Dad was here?
Yeah. Look at this.
We made a killing.
Why didn't he try to wake me up?
He tried to, like a thousand times.
He did?
Yeah. Did i tell you he would
give us christmas or what?
Go on, dive in.
What is it?
Sapphire barbie?
Dad probably thinks you're a girl.
Shut up.
Open that one.
Dad never showed, did he?
Yeah, he did, i swear.
Dean... where'd you
get all this stuff?
Nice house up the block.
I swear i didn't know
they were chick presents.
Look, i'm sure dad would
have been here if he could.
If he's alive.
Don't say that.
Of course he's alive.
He's dad.
Here. Take this.
No. No, that's for dad.
Dad lied to me.
I want you to have it.
- You sure?
- I'm sure.
Thank you, sam. I-I love it.
Hey. You get the beer?
What's all this?
What do you think it is? It's
- It's christmas.
What made you change your mind?
Here, uh...
Try the eggnog.
Let me know if it
needs some more kick.
No, we're good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Good. Well, uh, have a seat.
Let's do christmas
stuff or whatever.
All right, first thing's first.
Merry christmas, sam.
- Where'd you get these?
- Someplace special.
The gas mart down the street.
Open them up.
Well, great minds
think alike, dean.
Really?
There you go.
Come on!
Skin mags!
And...
Shaving cream.
You like?
Yeah. Yeah.
Look at this
Fuel for me and fuel for my baby.
These are awesome. Thanks.
Good.
Merry christmas, bro.
Here, merry christmas.
Do you feel like watching the game?
Absolutely.
All right.