Dad wants us to pick up where he left off --
saving people,hunting things...
the family business.
You were the bank robber on the 11:00 news, not me.
-Yeah.
-This is special agentvictor hendrickson.
It's my jobto bring you in
--alive's a bonus but not necessary.
I've been looking for you for weeks now.
And, yes,I know about sam, too.
I know about the murder in st. Louis,the
houdini act you pulled in baltimore.
I know about the desecrationsand the thefts.
I know about your dad.
You don't know crap about my dad.
We are so screwed.
NOW
Green River County
Detention Center
so, this makes a lot of sense.
First, they close down this cellblock,and
now they open itback up again.
There's your tax dollars at work.
****
Yes
Would hate to have gotten thrown in here.
Hey, you feel that, man?
Who is that?
Hey!
Hey, guard! Hey!
Come on, man!
Hey! Guard!
Come here! Hey!
-Going down to "b" block.Randall again.
-Copy that.
-Hey! Guard, hey!
-Shut up
Come on, randall,I'm trying to sleep.
You're telling me you didn'tsee that?
Are you blind?Hey!
-Randall, cool it.
-"Cool it," my ass, man.
-There's somebody out there.
-Randall, turn out your light and go to sleep.
I'm not gonna say it again.
-Lights out, "b" block.
-Copy that.Lights out
No.
No! No!No! No!
Help!
No! No! No!
No! No! No-o-o!Aah! No-o-o-o-o!
-=WWW.YDY.COM/BBS=-
Ptoudly Presents
Sync:YTET-angie
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Supernatural
Season 2 Episode 19
Three Months Later
This way.
-I hate this plan, dean.
-Yeah, I got that the first 10 times I heard it.
"FOLSOM PRISON BLUES"
Freeze!
I said, "freeze"!
Put your hands behind your head!
Get down on your knees.
Now!
***
I call this one the blue steel.
****
Okay, back to the line up.
-Wait, who looks better,me or nick nolte?
-Shut up.
Well, it's about time.I'll have a cheeseburger.
Extra onions.
-You think yo***.
-I think I'm adorable.
It is a pleasure to
finally meet you in person, dean.
I'm special agentvictor hendrickson.
This is my partner --special agent reidy.
Hendrickson.
-Not the milwaukee agent hendrickson.
-Live and in person.
Oh, nice shot.
You can hang that upin your cell at supermax.
Maybe we can just forget the cheeseburgers, huh?
Oh, yeah.Keep that game face on.
Try and cover up how cornered you are.
Read him the charges.
You got mail fraud,credit-card fraud.
grave desecration.
Skip to the good ones.
Armed robbery, kidnapping,and, oh,
three counts of first-degree murder.
And after milwaukee,your brother is
now a suspect in a murder case himself.
I'd say, for you two
"screwed to hell"is a major understatement.
Well, where there's life,there's hope, huh?
Aw. See,that's what I kept thinking as I was
searching for your asses all over hell and gone.
Your dad taught you well.
The way you cover your tracks,and,
after milwaukee,the way you
...Vanished.
Near went nuts trying to find you. Ask him.
He near went nuts.
And after all of that,you get
tripped upon a motion detector.
Pretty rookie move.I got to say, I was...
surprised.
-Dean winchester?
-In the flesh.
-And you are?
-Mara daniels --public defender's office.
I've been assigned you and your brother's case.
-Are you hendrickson?
-Yeah, and we're not quite done here.
Uh, yeah, you are,and if you don't mind...
I would like to meet with my clients privately.
Unfortunatly,Your arraignment
on the breaking-and-entering charge
won't be until tuesday.
-They'll keep us in county jail?
-That's right.
-Green river county detention center?
-Yes
and considering the charges you're facing,
no judge in his right mind is
going to grant you bail.
Yeah, we figured that.
Extradition papers have already been
filed from five separate states,
missouri and wisconsin being the biggest
concern --the bank robbery and the murder raps.
How long can we stall extradition?
A week. Maybe less.
All right.Let's go.***
***
***,baby.
Don't worry, sam.I promise
I won't trade you for smokes.
I call top bunk.
Okay.
My roommate doesn't say much.How's yours?
Just keeps staring at me...
in a way that makes me really uneasy.
-Sounds like you're making new friends.
-Dean...
this is, without a doubt,the
dumbest, craziest thing we've ever done
and that's in a long,
storied career of dumb and crazy.
-Calm down.It's all part of the plan.
-Oh, really?
Hendrickson showing up was part of the plan?
Yeah, that guy moves a little faster than I thought.
All we got to do is find this ghost
put the sucker down,then grab ourselves
a couple of those tear drop tattoos.
That's not funny.
Dean, what about this escape plan?
It's a sure thing. I
wouldn't have gone in if it wasn'T.
I mean,come on, man.This place
has all the signs of a haunting.
-Innocent people are dead --four so far.
-Oh, yeah.Innocent.
What, are you from texas all of a sudden?
Just 'cause these people are in
jail doesn't mean they deserve to die
and if we don't stop this
thing,people are gonna continue to die.
-We do the job wherever it takes us.
-Look, dean.
Just be straight with me, all right?
-You're doing this for deacon?
-Damn right.
But we barely even know the guy.
We know he was in the corps with dad.
We know he saved dad's life.We know we owe him.
Yeah,all right.But don't you
think he's asking a little much?
Doesn't matter.
We may not be saints,but we're
loyal,and we pay our debts.
Now, that means something
to me,and it ought to to you.
I'm not thrilled about this either, man,
but deacon asked upto hunt this thing down.
That's exactly what we're gonna do.
-You know,this chicken isn't half bad.
-Great. Finish mine.
All right, so let's go backover this, dean.
Spirit suspect number oneis mark moody, right?
Yeah, psycho killer extraordinaire --
satanism, ritual murderer,died in jail.
-You sure it's him?
-Pretty sure.
Dean, considering our circumstances,I'm
gonna need better than "pretty sure."
Really pretty sure.
Moody diedof a heart attack,which is
what all the victims in here are dying of.
He diedin the old cellblock,which they
closed after he croaked, 30 years ago.
They just opened that back
up.That's when the killings started.
So you think his spirit was released somehow?
But what if he was already cremated?
I'm guessing there's something in the
old block that's keeping him around.
And whatever it is,we got to find it.
And, uh, you know the rest.I'm done.
-Sorry. I --
-watch where you're going.
Yeah. Sure.I just --
-he said he was sorry.
-Dean...
you talking to me?
Are you talking to me?
Great, another guy who's seen"taxi driver"
too many times.Yeah, I'm talking to you.
Trust me.Let it go.
Dean, come on.
See, that's how you got to talk to these guys.
Instant respect.
You were saying?
Oh, great.
***That's right, pal.
That's enough!
On your feet, lucas.
Yes, sir, boss.
-What's your name?
-Winchester.
Well, winchester...not a good start.
Solitary.
-You too, lucas.
-Yes,sir.
Are we having fun yet,huh?
I wish I had a baseball.
What?What'd you say?
I said, "I wish I had a baseball."
-You know, like --like steve mcqueen.
-Yeah?
Well, I wish I had a bat so I
could bash your fricking head in.
Okay.
Well, so much for the bonding-in-solitary moment.
Crap.
Lucas, listen to me.Stay very still.
-Hendrickso
-Hey, daniels.
-Can I have a word?
-Have a seat.
-What's on your mind?
-I've been going through the winchester charges
and I got to say
-there aresome weird in consistencies.
-Welcome to my world.
I talked to a cop in baltimore
who swears up and down
these boys saved her life and
helped her catch a killer.
And there's a witness to your bank robbery in milwaukee.
She swears sam and dean saved her life.
-Saved her from what?
-She was a little unclear on that.
That's because she's nuts.
Look,I was in milwaukee.I spoke
to her.I spoke to all the witnesses.
-And?
-And
all I know is,wherever these guys go,people die.
-It's that simple.
-I don't know that it is.
They just don't seem cut-and-dry guilty to me.
-I think there's more to this.
-Like what?
I don't know.
Can't put my finger on it.
It's just...
-Strange.
Yeah. Okay.
Grown-ups are trying to
get some work done here, so...
if you don't mind...
How you doing?
I'm 54 years old,mopping the floor
of a crapper with bars on the windows.
How you think I'm doing?
All right.Bad icebreaker.
-I'm sam.
-Randall.
Nice to meet you.Randall.
-Hey, weren't you there the night that guard died?
-Yeah.
Well, what happened?
-They say the stress of the job got him.
-Yeah?
What do you say?
Why are you inside, kid?
'Cause I got an idiot for a brother.
-That'll do it.
-Yeah.
Well,this place ain't so bad.Compared to
the old cellblock,this is the damn hilton.
-You spent time in the old block?
-Oh, yeah,I was a regular customer.
-Didn't they have mark moody there for a while?
-He was there.
I was there, too, the night that lunatic bought it.
Yeah?It was a heart attack, right?
Sure, his heart stopped right after the guard
stopped using his head for batting practice.
The next morning,I was in his
cell,mopping up the blood.What a mess.
Wait. So he -- he was beaten
and nobody reported it?
You kept your mouth shut,unless you wanted
to die from the same heart attack,you know?
Randall, exactly how much blood was there?
-Call.
-Three aces.
That's a bad beat.
That is a bad beat,but, see, I'm full...
3s over aces.
Sorry.Hey, it's a cruel game,my friend.
Sorry, guys.
-It's like picking low-hanging fruit.
-You don't even smoke.
This is the currency of the realm.
-Look. I got a good lead on moody.
-Me too.
-His spirit paid a little visit last night.
-What?
The clock stopped,the flickering lights,cold
spot -- I mean, he did everything but yell boo.
-Well, what happened?
-He walked right by me.
Lucas wasn't so lucky.
I mean,the way he was screaming...
guy was a jerk, but he
didn't deserve to go like that.
What'd you find out on moody?
Yeah, I think I know where we
might find his remains --
-blood in his old cell.
-The blood?I thought it was a heart attack.
It was, after the guards worked him over.
**There was so much bloodin
there,they had trouble mopping it out.
-How we gonna get in?
-I got a plan.
That's the sammy I know.You're like
clint eastwood from "escape from alcatraz."
****Even if we do find
something,how are we gonna burn it?
We don't have any accelerant.
Good thing I'm like james
garner from "the great escape."
Hey, fellas!Who's ready to deal?
-You sure about this?
-Pretty sure.
Yeah, well, considering our circumstances,
I'd like a little better than "pretty sure."
Okay --really pretty sure.
I'd like mine al dente.
Perfect.
Save room for dessert,tiny.
Hey, I wanted to ask you, 'causeI couldn't
help but notice that you are two tons of fun.
Just curious -- is it likea thyroid problem,or
is it some deep-seatedself-esteem issue?
'Cause, you know, they're,
uh --they're just dough nuts.
They're not love.
Guys, give me a hand.
If we'd waited any longer,you'd be dead.
You waited long enough.
Do yourself a favor.Don't talk.
Take them both up to the infirmary.
-Hey, tiny.
-Yeah?
Hey, sorry about the things I was saying earlier.
Can't really tell you why
but I had to get you angry.
So, uh...
-anyway, sorry.
-It's okay.
Truth is, I have low-self-esteem issues.
My old man treated meand my brother like crap,
right up till the day he died.
-How'd he die?
-My brother shot him.
Okay.
-Oh, crap.
-What is it?
What is going on?
What is it?
-Oh! No! No!
-Tiny! Tiny!
Guard!
Wait. So you're telling me it wasn't moody?
Not unless he liked going
around dressed like a nurse.
-Poor tiny, man.Poor giant tiny.
-Wait, so this is --this is, like
-the ghost of some nurse who worked here or something?
-I don't know, man.I guess.
***At this point, "I don't
know"isn't working for me.
See, uh,I thought we were done.
I called Deacon.It's happening.
We're getting out tonight.
I guess we got to do some quick research, then.
How?!I mean, maybe you haven't noticed --
we're in jail.
You want to know about some nurse?
-Why you want to know?
-We got our reasons,
but, uh, we'll make it worth your while.
So, this nurse,she would have white hair,one
screwed-up eye --is that ringing a bell?
-Yeah.Yeah, I remember her.
-You remember her name?
No, that's still kind of fuzzy.
Give it to him.
-I earned these.
-Dean.
Glockner --nurse glockner.
Nasty old bitch worked here in the '70s.
-You knew her?
-I met her once.
Had to geta tetanus shot.She damn
near jabbed the needle through my arm.
-At least I got out of there alive.
-What do you mean?
I've heard these stories.I
don't know if they were true.
-Cons love to talk,but we're all liars.
-What kind of stories?
Guys would go up with a cold.
Next thing you know,they're in a body bag.
A whole rash of heart attacks
--young guys, old guys.
-Heart attacks?
-Yeah.
The story was glockner had it out for cons
and she did this, uh,charles
bronson thing with a hypodermic.
Anyway, that was the rumor.
Nobody ever proved anything.
-Whatever happened to glockner?
-I don't know.
I finished my bitand left.Next time
I landed back in here,she was gone.
Okay, so let's say those
stories on glockner were true.
It's a thought.
-In life, she's a vigilante.In death, same thing.
-Right
but how is she tied in with the old cellblock?
And if she's going after
cons,why kill that one guard?
I did hear in the yard that that
guard wasn't exactly squeaky clean,so
maybe she's going after anybody
that breaks a law,like me.
-You heard in the yard?
-Yeah.
Does it bother you at all
how easily you seem to fit in here?
No, not really.
All right. Either way,we
need more info on glockner.
If she's buried --if so, where?
And we got five hours to get it.
No, no.Don't give me that "we got
to see this thing through" look.
We are leaving tonight,no matter what.
-I don't want to let Deacon down.We do owe him.
-Yeah,but we don't owe him our lives, dean.
Where you going?
I'm gonna go talk with our lawyer.
-You want me to what?
-Her name was glockner.
She worked here as a nurse in the '70s.
I need you to find out everything you
can about her but, most importantly
-how she died and where she's buried.
-Are you nuts?
Do you have any idea the kind of trouble you're in?
-I have a vague notion.
-Good
so let's forget about some random
nurse and talk about your case.
-Mara --it's mara, right?
-Yeah.
I get that you're trying to help me.
I do, but believe me when I say that
this is the best way that you can help.
-Really? How?Explain that to me.
-I wish I could,but I can'T.
I'm just gonna have to
ask you to trust me on this.
Why should I?
-Hendrickson says you're a monster.
-I'm a monster?
Well, h-he's wrong, okay?
I'm not what they say I am.
-Everybody says that.
-Yeah.
If you're as smart a P.D.As I think you are,
then you can tell with just one look whether
or not your clients are guilty, just like that.
So I want you to look at me,really look,
and you tell me --am I guilty?
We're not the bad guys.
-Did she go for it?
-No. No, not so much.
-But maybe she'll still come around.
-We can't wait to find out.
-We could give it another day.
-No, no, no. We're leaving tonight, and that's it.
-So we're just gonna let these people die?
-Don't give me that,all right?
This was your stupid plan.I went along
with it,but we're sticking to the plan.
Okay.Uh, you leave.I'm gonna stay.
-Don't turn away.Don't turn away from me.
-Screw you.
What?!Screw you!
All right, hard case.I see the usual
methods ain't gonna work with you.
You too, sweetheart.
Take off.
I want to handle this alone.
Deacon, you are beating the holy hell out of me, man.
Sorry, dean.
I thought I was going easy on you.
-Just, uh,trying to make it look real.
-Yeah. Well,mission accomplished.
-Thanks.
-So, is it over?
-No.Turns out, it wasn't moody.
-What?
-Yeah.
-Then who?
Uh, we think it's some nurse who used to
work here,but we're shy on all the intel.
Which is why we should stick around.
Until we find it.
-Oh,hey guys.
-You want to have this fight for real, dean?
We got to go.We've got to go now!
-Guys.
-We are leaving dean.
Otherwise, we'll be leaving in shackles
for milwaukee,with hendrickson as company.
-Oh, come on.
-Guys!
-What?!
Your lawyer left this for you.
-Would you look at that.
-Man, I am freaking velvety smooth.
You want to, maybe,open it up after
you're done patting yourself on the back?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Wow.
-What?You want to share with the class, dean?
Glockner died in the
old cellblock after moody bit it.
Seems they had a little inmate uprising.
She ****
They dragged her to a solitary cell
gave hera severe cerebral edema.
-Someone bashed her head in.
-Yeah.
-Does it say where she's buried?
-Yep.
All right, then, let's get you the hell out of here.
Don't worry, Deacon.We'll get rid of this thing.
Good, 'cause I want it out of my prison.
Boys, uh...
I can't thank you enough for this.
I know it was asking a lot
but you still came through.
Your daddy raised you right.
-Well, we owed you.
-Right.
-Hope to see you again,huh?
-Just not in here,okay?
Yeah, we'll do our best.
Oh...
-where do you want it?
-What?
Yeah, um...um...
make it look real, son.
oh, man, are you a sight for sore eyes.
You know, I almost wish I
could see hendrickson's face.
Really?'Cause I'd be happy if
I never saw him again.
-We're not really out of the woods yet, dean, you know?
-Yeah.
Good point.
I told you.One of them came up behind me.
-You let them get the drop on you.
-Yeah.
I screwed up, all right?
What do you want me to say?
I want to know where they're headed.
-How the hell would I know?
-Let's start over again.
-For god's sake.
-Again --
I want to know everything they did
today,from the minute they woke up.
Got up...
breakfast,visiting hours,rec time.
-Any visitors?
-Just their lawyer.
It's an easy question.
What did you and Dean talk about?
I have already told you.It was a private
conversation between me and my client.
Right, and three hours later
he just happened to bust out.
Now,tell me what he said.
We got to move it.If
hendrickson gets to the lawyer...
I thought she couldn't say anything --
you know, that whole lawyer-client-privilege thing.
-The privilege doesn't apply, dean.
-So she'll talk?
She has to.
That's freaking super.
Let***
You don't come clean,I will put you
on the hook for aiding and abetting.
-That is ridiculous.
-You don't think that I can?!
You think this is some kind of game, lady?!
I am the last person you want to screw with.
Now, tell me...
what he said.
He wanted me to do some research...
-...on a prison nurse that died in 1976.
-What? Why?
-I don't know.
-What else?
-They wanted to know where she was buried.
-Did you find out where?
-Yeah.
-Did you tell them?
yeah.
Tell me.
Mountainside Cemetery
Got her.
You let those two go.
Are you sure this is the right damn cemetery?
She said mountainside --mountainside cemetery.
GREEN VALLEY CEMETERY
- thought we were screwed before?
- Yeah, I know.
- We got to go deep this time.
-"Deep," dean?
- We should go to yemen.
- Ooh, I'm --
I'm not sure I'm ready to go that deep.
-=WWW.YDY.COM/BBS=-
Ptoudly Presents
Sync:YTET-angie
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Supernatural
Season 2 Episode 19