Supernatural
Seasone 3 epsiode 11
Back in 1835, samuel colt made a gun.
They say this gun can kill anything.
Bela talbot's her real name.
Is she a hunter?
She's pretty freaking far from a hunter.
The colt. Bela stole the colt.
I need your help.
Help with what?
-With sam.
-You need to help me get him ready
To fight this war on his own.
Rise and shine, sammy!
Dude. Asia?
Come on. You love this song and you know it.
Yeah, and if i ever hear
it again, i'm gonna kill myself.
What?
Sorry. I can't hear you.
Whenever you're ready, dean.
This yours?
Bingo.
Now, who's ready for some breakfast?
Drive safely now, mr. Pickett.
Yeah, yeah.
Can't stay unless you order something, cal.
You know the rules.
Some coffee.
Hey. Tuesday. Pig 'n a poke.
Do you even know what that is?
Are you boys ready?
Yes.
I'll have the special,
a side of bacon, and a coffee.
Make it two coffees and a short stack.
You got it.
I'm telling you, sam, this job is small-Fry.
We should be spending our time hunting down bela.
Okay, sure. Let's get right on that.
Where is she again? Shut up.
Believe me, i want to find her as bad as you do.
In the meantime, we have this.
All right, so this professor...
Dexter hasselback. He was passing through
town last week when he vanished.
Last known location?
His daughter says he was on his way
To visit the broward county mystery spot.
"Where the laws of physics have no meaning!"?
Two coffees -- Black,
And some hot sauce for the...
Whoops.
Crap. Sorry.
Clean up!
Sam, you know joints like this
Are only tourist traps, right?
I mean, you know, balls rolling uphill,
Furniture nailed to the ceiling.
The only danger's to your wallet.
Okay, look. I'm just saying
there are spots in the world
Where holes open up and swallow people --
The bermuda triangle, the oregon vortex.
Broward county mystery spot?
Well, sometimes these places are legit.
All right, so if it is legit --
And that's a big-Ass "if" -- What's the lore?
Well -- Excuse me.
The lore's pretty freaking nuts, actually.
I mean, they say these places,
The magnetic fields are so strong
That they can bend space-Time,
Sending victims no one knows where.
Sounds a little "x files" to me.
I told you it wouldn't fit!
What do you want, a pulitzer?
All right, look, i'm not saying
this is really happening,
But if it is, we got to check it out,
See if we can do something.
All right, all right.
We'll go tonight after they close,
Get ourselves a nice, long look.
Wow. Uncanny.
Find anything?
No.
Do you have any idea what you're looking for?
Uh...yeah.
No.
What the hell you doing here?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. We can explain.
You robbing me?
Look, nobody's robbing you. Calm down.
Don't move. Don't move!
I'm just putting the gun down.
Dean!
Call 911.
I -- I didn't mean...
Now!
No. No. No.
Not like this.
Dean.
Supernatural season 3 episode 11
Rise and shine, sammy!
Dude. Asia.
Dean.
Oh, come on.
You love this song and you know it.
What?
I don't know.
You all right?
No. I think i...
Man, i had a weird dream.
Yeah? Clowns or midgets?
Drive safely now, mr. Pickett.
Yeah, yeah.
???????????  ??
Can't stay unless you order something, cal.
??????
You know the rules.
????
Coffee.
???
Hey. Tuesday.
Pig 'n a poke.
????
It's tuesday?
??
Yeah.
Are you boys ready? Yes.
I'll have the special, side of bacon, and a coffee.
Uh, nothing for me. Thanks.
Let me know if you change your mind.
I'm telling you, sam, this job is small-Fry.
We should be spending our time hunting down bela.
You with me?
What?
You sure you feel okay?
You don't...
You don't remember any of this?
Remember what?
This. Today.
Like -- Like it's -- Like it's happened before?
You mean like déjà vu?
No. I mean like it's --
Like it's really happened before.
Yeah. Like déjà vu.
No. Forget about déjà vu.
I'm asking you if it feels like --
Like we're living yesterday all over again.
- Okay, how is that not déjà vu...
- Don't!
Don't say it! Just don't even...
Coffee -- Black,
And some hot sauce for the...
Whoops! Crap.
Thanks!
Nice reflexes.
Sam, i'm sorry.
I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
Okay, look. Yesterday was tuesday, right?
But today is tuesday, too.
Yeah. No. Good. You're totally balanced.
So you don't believe me?
Excuse me.
Look, i'm just saying that it's crazy, you know?
Even-For-Us crazy. Dingo-Ate-My-Baby crazy.
Hey, maybe it was another one
of your psychic premonitions.
No. No way. Way too vivid.
Okay, look. We were at
the mystery spot, and then...
And then what?
Then i woke up.
I told you it wouldn't fit!
What do you want, a pulitzer?
Wait a minute! The mystery spot.
You think maybe it...
Maybe what?
We got to check that place out.
Just go with me on this.
All right. All right.
We'll go tonight after close,
Get ourselves a nice, long look.
Wait. What?
- No.
- Why not?
Uh...let's just go now.
Right now. Business hours.
Nice and crowded.
My god, you're a freak.
Dean.
Okay! Whatever. We'll go now.
Dean!
Dean. No. No. No.
Come on. Dean.
Hey. Dean.
Dean. Dean.
Rise and shine, sammy!
Hey. Tuesday. Pig 'n a poke.
Would you listen to me, dean?
Cause i am flipping out.
Are you boys ready?
He'll take the special, side of bacon, coffee -- Black.
Nothing for me. Thanks.
You got it.
Sammy, i get all tingly when you take control like that.
Quit screwing around, dean.
Okay. Okay. I'm listening. So...so...
Now, you think that you're in some kind of a what?
Time loop.
Like "groundhog day."
Yes. Exactly. Like "groundhog day."
So you don't believe me?
It's -- It's a little crazy. Even-For-Us crazy.
You know, like...
...dingo-Ate-My-Baby crazy?
How'd you know i was gonna say that?
Ecause you've said it before,
dean. That's my whole point.
Coffee -- Black,
And some hot sauce for the...
Whoops! Crap.
Thanks.
Nice reflexes.
No. I knew it was gonna happen.
Okay, look.
I'm sure that there's some sort of an explanation.
You're just gonna have to go with
me on this, all right, dean?
You just have to. You owe me that much.
Calm down.
Don't tell me to calm down!
I can't calm down. I can't because...
Because what?
Because you die today, dean.
I'm not gonna die. Not today.
Twice now, i've watched you die.
And i can't.
I won't do it again, okay?
And you're just gonna have to believe me.
Please.
All right.
I still think you're nuts, but...
Okay. Whatever this is, we'll figure it out.
Excuse me.
I told you it wouldn't fit!
What do you want, a pulitzer?
And you think this cheesy-Ass tourist trap
Has something to do with it.
Maybe it's the real deal, you know?
The -- The magnetic fields bending space-Time or whatever.
That all seems a little too "x files" for me.
Well, i don't know how else to explain it, dean!
All right! All right.
We'll go tonight after they close,
Get ourselves a nice, long look.
No, no, no, no. We can't.
Why not?
Because you...
I what?
I die there?
Blown away, actually.
Okay. Let's go now.
Get out of the way!
What, did he...
Yesterday. Yeah.
And?
And what?
Did it look cool like in the movies?
You peed yourself.
Of course i peed myself.
A man gets hit by a car,
You think he has full control over his bladder?
Come on!
Boys, i can't tell you how much i appreciate this.
We could use all the good ink we can get.
How long have you owned the place, mr. Carpiak?
Well, my family's been guarding the secrets here
Since you don't want to know when.
So you'd know if anything strange happened?
Strange?
Strange happens here all the time.
It's a mystery spot.
What exactly does that mean?
Well, uh...
It's where the laws of physics...
Have no meaning.
Okay. Like how?
Take the tour.
The guy who went missing -- Dexter hasselback --
He take the tour?
Hold on a minute. What kind of article is this?
Just answer the question.
The police scoured every inch of this place.
They couldn't find that man. I never seen him before.
- We're a family establishment.
- Listen to me.
There's something weird going on here.
Now, do you know anything about it or not?
Okay, look.
Guys, um, give it a break.
I bought the joint at a foreclosure auction
Last march, all right?
Hell, i used to sell bail bonds.
Okay, kojak. Let's get some air.
I hate to say it, but that place
Is exactly what i thought -- It's full of crap.
So what is it, then, dean?
What the hell is happening to us?
I don't know.
All right, let me just...
So, every day i die.
Yeah.
That's when you wake up again, right?
So let's just make sure i don't die.
If i make it to tomorrow,
Then maybe the loop stops and we can figure all this out.
Do you think?
It's worth a shot.
I say we grab some takeout, head back to the motel,
Lay low until midnight.
All right, good.
Who wants chinese?
Rise and shine, sammy!
I still think you're nuts.
But whatever this is, we'll figure it out.
Thanks.
So, uh...
If you're stuck in "groundhog day, " why?
What's behind it?
First i thought it was the mystery spot.
Now i'm not so sure.
What do we do?
Well, we keep you breathing, try to make it to tomorrow.
I mean, that's the only thing i can think of.
Shouldn't be too hard.
Yeah, right. Dean, i've watched you die a few times now,
And i can't ever seem to stop it.
Well, nothing's set in stone.
You say i order the same thing every day, right?
Yeah. Pig 'n a poke, side of bacon.
Excuse me, sweetheart.
Can i get sausage instead of bacon?
Sure thing, hon.
See? Different day already.
You see, if you and i decide that i am not gonna die,
I'm not gonna die.
Thank you.
Dean.
You mean we can't even go out for breakfast?
You'll thank me when it's wednesday!
Whatever that means.
Do these tacos taste funny to you?
Everybody's fine. Nobody's gonna get hurt, okay?
Sammy?
Maybe you should drop the ax and let this guy go.
What do you say?
Something's got to be going on here.
I intend to find out what.
Place is tore up pretty good, dude.
Time to give it a rest.
No!
I'm gonna take it down to studs.
Sammy, that's enough. Give me the ax.
Give me the ax! This is crazy!
Leave it, dean!
Come on!
Get off!
Oh, my god, dean!
Drive safely now, mr. Pickett.
Yeah, yeah.
Can't stay unless you order something, cal.
You know the rules.
Coffee.
Hey. Tuesday. Pig 'n a poke.
What are those?
The old man's.
Trust me. You don't want him behind the wheel.
You boys ready?
Yes, we are.
I'll have the special, a side of bacon, and a coffee.
Hey, doris.
What i'd like is for you to log in some more hours
At the archery range.
- You're a terrible shot.
- How do you know --
Lucky guess.
Okay, so, you think you're caught
In some kind of what again?
Time loop.
Like "groundhog day."
It doesn't matter. There's no way to stop it.
Jeez. Aren't you grumpy?
Yeah, i am. You want to know why?
Why?
Because this is the 100th tuesday in a row
I've been through, and it never stops.
Ever. So, yeah, i'm a little grumpy.
Hot sauce.
What?
Coffee -- Black,
And some hot sauce for the -- Whoops!
Crap. Thanks!
Nice reflexes.
I knew it was gonna happen, dean.
I know everything that's gonna happen.
You don't know everything.
Yeah. I do.
Yeah, right.Yeah, right.
Nice guess.Nice guess.
It wasn't a guess.
Right, you're a mind reader.
Cut it out, sam.
Sam!Sam!
You think you're being funny,
But you're being really, really childish.
Sam winchester wears makeup.
Sam winchester cries his way through sex.
Sam winchester keeps a ruler by the bed,
And every morning, when he wakes up...
Okay, enough!
That's not all.
Randy, the cashier?
He's skimming from the register.
Judge meyers?
At night, he puts on a furry bunny outfit.
Over there -- That's cal.
He's gonna rob tony the mechanic on the way home.
What's your point?
My point is i've lived through every possible tuesday.
I've watched you die every possible way.
I have ripped apart the mystery spot,
Burnt it down, tried everything i know to save your life,
And i can't.
No matter what i do, you die,
And then i wake up.
And then it's tuesday again.
The dog.
There's got to be some way out of this.
"Where's my dang keys?"
Where's my dang keys?
"Excuse me."
Excuse me.
She's kind of cute.
All the times we've walked down this street,
I ever do this?
Excuse me. Miss?
No.
100 tuesdays, you never bothered to check
What she was holding in her hands?
This the guy who went missing?
- Yeah.
- That's his daughter back there.
Hey, buddy. Somebody need a friend?
So, the police report says dexter hasselback
Is a professor, but that's not all he is.
What is he?
I talked to his daughter. The guy's quite the journalist.
Columns in magazines, a blog.
He writes about tourist attractions --
Mystery spots, ufo crash sites.
He gets his kicks debunking them.
I mean, he's already put four of these places out of business.
Here.
Truth warrior"?
More like a pompous schmuck, you ask me.
Yeah. Tell me about it.
I mean, i've read everything the guy's ever written.
He must have weighed a ton, he was so full of himself.
When did you have time to do all this research?
Come on.
What?
It's funny, you know.
I mean, this guy spends his whole life
Crapping on mystery spots and then he vanishes in one.
It's kind of poetic, you know? Like just desserts.
You're right. That is just deserts.
What's wrong?
Guy has maple syrup for the past 100 tuesdays --
All of a sudden, he's having strawberry?
It's a free country.
Man can't choose his own syrup, huh?
What have we become?
Not in this diner. Not today.
Nothing in this place ever changes -- Ever.
Except me.
Rise and shine, sammy!
So, you think you're caught in some kind of what again?
Eat your breakfast.
What's in the bag?
Hey!
- Hey.
- I know who you are.
Or should i say "what"?
- Oh, my god. Please, don't kill me.
- Uh, sam...
-It took me a hell of a long time, but i got it.
-What?
It's your m.O. That gave you away.
Going after pompous jerks, giving them their just deserts.
Your kind loves that, don't they?
Yeah, sure. Okay.
Just put the stake down.
- Sam, maybe you should...
- No!
There's only one creature powerful enough
To do what you're doing --
Making reality out of nothing,
Sticking people in time loops.
In fact, you'd pretty much have to be a god.
You'd have to be a trickster.
Mister, my name is ed coleman. My wife's name's amelia.
I got two kids.
For crying out loud, i sell ad space!
Don't lie to me! I know what you are!
We've killed one of your kind before!
Actually, bucko, you didn't.
You're joking, right?
You chuckleheads tried to kill me last time.
Why wouldn't i do this?
And hasselback -- What about him?
That putz?
He said he didn't believe in wormholes,
So i dropped him in one.
Then you guys showed up.
I made you the second you hit town.
So this is fun for you?
Killing dean over and over again?
One... yes, it is fun,
And two... this is so not about killing dean.
This joke is on you, sam.
Watching your brother die every day.
Forever.
You son of a bitch.
How long will it take you to realize
You can't save your brother...
...no matter what?
Oh, yeah?
I kill you, this all ends now.
Oh, hey! Whoa. Okay.
Okay. Look.
I was just playing around.
You can't take a joke, fine. You're out of it.
Tomorrow, you wake up, it'll be wednesday.
I swear.
You're lying.
If i am, you know where to find me --
Having pancakes at the diner.
No. Easier to just kill you.
Sorry, kiddo. Can't have that.
- What, are you gonna sleep all day?
- No asia.
Yeah, i know. This station sucks.
It's wednesday!
Yeah, which usually comes after tuesday.
Turn that thing off, would you?
What, are you kidding?
- This isn't the most beautiful song you've ever heard?
- No.
Jeez. How many tuesdays did you have?
I don't know. I lost count.
Hey, wait. What do you remember?
I remember you were pretty
whacked out of it yesterday,
Then i remember running into the trickster.
But, no, that's about it.
All right. Pack your stuff.
Let's get the hell out of town -- Now.
No breakfast?
No breakfast.
Are you sure we should just
let the trickster go?
Give me your wallet.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, buddy. Just relax.
I am relaxed!
Okay. All right.
Nobody wants this to end the wrong way.
Let's talk about it a sec.
Dean!
No. No, no, no, no.No no
Hey. Hey. Come on.
Not today. Not today.
This isn't supposed to happen today.
Come on.
I'm supposed to wake up.
This is sam. Leave a message.
Sam, it's bobby.
Heard about that demon thing
You took care of in death valley.
Nice job.
It's been about three
months we talked, though.
It'd be nice to hear your voice.
Give a call. I'm here.
Sam? Bobby again.
Look, i'm worried about you.
Just tell me you're not sitting alone somewhere,
Obsessing over this damn trickster.
Call me, sam. We can find it together.
No one man should take
something like this on alone.
You hear me?
By the way, that vampire nest in austin...
Hell of a job.
Sam? It's bobby.
I found him.
It's good to see you, boy.
What are we doing here, bobby?
This is the last place, for sure,
The trickster worked his magic.
So?
So, you want this thing?
I found a summoning ritual
to bring the trickster here.
What do we need?
Blood.
How much blood?
Ritual says near a gallon. It's got to be fresh, too.
Meaning we have to bleed a person dry.
And it's got to be tonight,
Or not for another 50 years.
Then let's go get some.
You break my heart, kid.
What?
I'm not gonna let you murder an innocent man.
Then why'd you bring me here?
Why?
Cause it was the only way you'd see me.
Cause i'm trying to knock some sense into you.
Because i thought you'd back
down from killing a man.
Well, you thought wrong.
Leave the stuff. I'll do it myself.
I told you, i'm not gonna let you kill anyone.
It's none of your damn business what i do!
You want your brother back so bad...
...fine.
What are you talking about?
Better me than a civilian.
You're crazy, bobby. I'm not killing you.
Oh. Now i'm the crazy one.
Look, sam.
I'm old.
I'm coming near the end of my trail.
But you can keep fighting, saving folk.
But you need your brother.
So let me give him back to you.
Bobby...
You and dean, you...
You boys are the closest thing i have to family.
I want to do this.
Okay.
Good.
Just make it quick.
Do it, son.
Yeah, okay, bobby.
But you want to know why?
Because you're not bobby.
Bobby.
Bobby!
You're right. I was just screwing with you.
Pretty good, though, sam. Smart.
Let me tell ya.
Whoever said dean was the dysfunctional one
Has never seen you with a sharp
object in your hands.
Holy "full metal jacket."
Bring him back.
Who? Dean?
Didn't my girl send you the flowers?
Dean's dead. He ain't coming back.
His soul's downstairs doing
the hellfire rumba as we speak.
Just take us back to that tuesday
-- Or wednesday
When it all started, please.
We won't come after you. I swear.
You swear?
Yes.
I don't know.
Even if i could...
- You can.
- True.
But that don't mean i should.
Sam, there's a lesson here
That i've been trying to drill
Into that freakish, cro-Magnon skull of yours.
Lesson? What lesson?
This obsession to save dean.
The way you two keep sacrificing
yourselves for each other.
Nothing good comes out of it.
Just blood and pain.
Dean's your weakness.
The bad guys know it, too.
He's gonna be the death of you, sam.
Sometimes you just got to let people go.
He's my brother.
Yep.
And like it or not,
This is what life's gonna be like without him.
Please. Just...
Please.
I swear, it's like talking to a brick wall.
Okay, look.
This all stopped being fun months ago.
You're travis bickel in a skirt, pal.
I'm over it.
Meaning what?
Meaning that's for me to know and you to find out.
What, are you gonna sleep all day?
I know. No asia. This station sucks.
It's wednesday.
Yeah. Which usually follows tuesday.
Turn that thing off.
Dude, how many tuesdays did you have?
Enough.
Wait.
What do you remember?
I remember you were pretty whacked out yesterday.
I remember catching up with the trickster.
That's about it.
Let's go.
No breakfast?
No breakfast.
All right. I'll pack the car.
Wait. You're not going anywhere alone.
It's the parking lot, sam.
Just...
Just trust me.
Hey, you don't look so good. Something else happen?
I just had a really weird dream.
Clowns or midgets?