Previously on The Kill Point.
This's a bank robbery.
Follow these simple instructions,
and we can all walk out of here,
safe and sound.
Pull back!
This is now a hostage situation.
Who's this?
- Captain Horst Cali.
- I'm Wolf.
Alan Beck is indeed at the scene as his
daughter Ashley is one of the hostages.
One hour or a hostage.
Follow these instructions.
If you don't, your daughter
and my son
aren't gonna make it out of the bank.
- Platoon 10-13.
- Let's get our boys home.
It's time
we took matters into our own hands.
- We're coming out.
- Sniper on the roof.
I'm gonna put blood on your hands.
Oh, my god!
Oh, man!
Back up...
Back up!
- What'd you do?!
- Back, move!
- Jesus!
- Move!
You son of a bitch!
Let him go.
This is bad.
We need an ambulance now.
My guy said they heard screaming inside.
Call him.
Find out what happened.
Come on, come on.
We heard a shot.
What's going on?
We got a woman shot in the face.
We need emts in here now.
Unarmed, got it?
- What did you just say?
- It's an accident.
Look, I don't have time for this.
Get the emts in here now.
Send in the emts.
- She gonna make it?
- Don't know.
Somebody in there worked on her.
Bought her some time.
A 20-year-old girl, Connie.
- It's not your fault, cap.
- Not my fault?
I'm assuming that Wolf's in control.
If I was wrong,
if he's not in control...
Then all bets are off.
Episode 1x04
Transcript: swsub.com / Sync: DarKsh
Is that my daughter?
Is that Ashley?
God damn you,
you tell me if that's my daughter!
It's Cass Conforth, Alan.
What's the play, Sarge?
Look, I don't know what he's capable of.
So we'll just hold our posts
and be ready to roll, all right?
Come on, Mike, come on.
Don't hold it against yourself, man.
It was just an accident.
She was 20, Sarge.
20 at best.
And it was no accident.
Yeah.
We brought violence
to these people, okay?
We did bad shit over there,
and now we're doing bad shit here.
Can't you see, man?
We're like...
a traveling virus.
Just spreading our shit
all over the world now.
Here, Mike, you're gonna need this, man.
Chloe, come here.
Can you do me a favor?
See if you can help out
with those two over there.
Cali, I've got every news channel
running that girl being wheeled
out of the bank over and over again.
Everyone ask me
why we do nothing about it.
The more I'm talking to you,
the less I can spend talking to Wolf.
I cover you with the press,
but if it doesn't feel right soon,
- we're going in.
- All right.
Okay.
- What happened, sergeant?
- An accidental discharge.
Girl caught a stray.
- It's nobody's fault.
- That is debatable.
- Yeah, it is.
- We've had a good understanding so far.
You control your people, I control mine.
I am in control.
My men follow my orders at all times.
It was just an accident.
I just pray that the girl makes it.
If that's true, and you are in control,
and this was, in fact,
an accident, then this shooting
is even more troublesome than I thought.
Because it means
that it can happen again.
Hey, look, it's not gonna happen again.
You can't guarantee that an accident
won't happen again, can you, Mr. Wolf?
No, I can't guarantee it.
Then you have to accept
the fact
that another hostage can get shot
no matter what you do.
Cap.
- Cass may not make it, sergeant.
- I thought she was stabilized.
She's critical.
Jake...
I know you went in that bank
because you want something back.
Now you wanna make a statement
with your demands,
about the country, about the war.
Making a point about this government's
hypocrisy is worth this girl's life?
I don't know anymore.
You thought you could control it...
You can't.
Do the honorable thing, sergeant.
Walk out the door, save lives.
You have that power.
Look, captain, I...
I never wanted this to happen.
I just... I'm open...
We lost him... Get him back.
Come on, now!
What are you doing?
We'll call you back, captain.
Who was that?
I need you
to understand something, Sarge.
- Explain.
- Okay...
I will never surrender.
There were civvies killed in Fallujah.
We didn't stop the ops there.
Why stop here?
These people's lives
worth more than iraqi civilians?
That girl was an acceptable casualty.
All of these people are.
You understand that I was trying
to keep 'em from storming the bank?
- Do you understand that?
- Yes, sir.
- What are you trying to prove?
- Nothing, sir.
- You're trying to prove something, uh?
- No, sir.
- Don't ever grab that phone again.
- Yes, sir.
- Know your place, corporal.
- I will, sir.
Beck's back.
Cap, we gotta talk strategy.
Can't buy more time, Cali.
The press is in a feeding frenzy.
The hostages' fam...
We're going in.
Good.
What's the time line?
Wait, hold on.
Are you sure?
Wolf sounded defeated...
- Talk to him.
- Doesn't matter.
Somebody else hung up that phone.
Our plan won't work
if I don't know who's calling the shots.
- We're going in.
- You know
he's looking for us to move in.
We take no action,
we lose more hostages anyway.
The last incident proves it.
I'll get the press and civilians
pushed back. Let's go.
Get your team in place, Connie.
- Come up with a breach plan.
- Cap...
God damn it,
am I asking your opinion right now?!
We're going in.
Teams,
prep for full tactical breach.
I feel like I'm being punished, Jim,
for every duplicitous deal
and lie I've ever told.
And Ashley's been dragged
into my penance.
Real question is,
what happens if I get her back?
Alan, answer the phone.
Do what you do best.
Worry about the rest later.
Is my daughter okay?
Yeah, yeah, she's fine.
How are we gonna resolve this?
I want you to find the weak spot, okay?
Every system's got a weak spot.
You finance our exit, and you'll see
your daughter's face again...
without a hole in it.
Okay, I can find a weak spot.
But know this, sergeant,
if you hurt my daughter,
I'll have that god damn bank nuked,
so help me God.
Just call me when you make progress.
What does he want?
He wants to buy his freedom.
- I'm gonna handle this one, Jim.
- Alan...
No, no.
I'm gonna handle this one.
What's the deal?
We're in business with Beck.
He's gonna finance our exit.
You happy, Rabbit?
Yeah, that sounds good, Sarge,
but I just took a peek outside, and...
we might not have time.
There's a lot of movement and SWAT.
Something's up.
Cap...
All due respect, I think you should
pick up the phone.
I know you're hurt, and this makes you
question your tactics.
Shit, I'm your SWAT commander.
I'm supposed to be hopped up for action,
but I got a feeling this ain't the move.
I'm not saving them one at a time,
I'm risking them.
I read Wolf wrong.
I have to correct my mistake now.
Dude, these guys
are willing to go all in.
- We breach, they shoot to kill. Who...
- I know the situation.
I know the risks
involved in my decision.
Face to face.
Outside,
now.
- I thought you gave up on me, cap.
- Shouldn't I?
'Cause I thought we had a business deal.
Now,
I don't know if the man
I'm speaking to is in control in there.
Come on, that was just
a miscommunication, that's all.
A miscommunication?
I'd say that a hostage shot in the face
is a more than a miscommunication.
It seems to me
like you lost control, sergeant.
This thing is over now.
It's time to give it up.
It's not an order that I know.
All right.
Makes my decision a lot easier.
Hey, cap, let me just ask you...
Did you actually kill somebody?
- Did you really?
- How is that relevant?
This could be
our last conversation together, right?
Were they all righteous shootings?
They were justified.
- Justified?
- Yeah.
- That help you sleep any better?
- This is bullshit.
- This is not about me...
- No, it is about you, completly,
and you know it.
Why become a negotiator?
From bullets to blab, why?
Because you didn't feel bad?
Did that freak you out?
- You don't know me.
- You don't think so?
Your propensity for violence is
what's getting you in trouble, isn't it?
I'm gonna walk back.
If I get back there, and I don't know
that you're in complete control...
- The deal's done.
- I'm in control, man.
That was an accident.
But if you give the order, it's the same
as you pulling the trigger.
Can you live with that?
You wanna be that guy, go ahead.
Go ahead and give the order.
Go ahead, man.
Go get a little taste of power.
If you're in control, I want two.
You get two because I say so.
Hey, Piggy, go get Karen.
Karen, you're going.
I'll pray for you, okay?
Good-bye.
Come on, sweetie.
Marykim,
you're going home.
Rabbit.
I'll be okay, all right?
I'm right behind you.
Okay.
You better be.
Let's go.
Come on, come on.
First team alpha, stand down.
Bravo, Charlie, fall back and hold.
Sarge, they're withdrawing.
Let's get an emt...
Come on!
It's all right.
No, no, no, please don't let me go.
Please, please.
It's all right.
Hey, babe.
No, no, I'm fine.
Tell me about your day.
No, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
What did you eat?
No, you're not fat.
I must say, this is unexpected.
You said
you wanted a private conversation?
The hostage situation downtown...
My daughter is in that bank.
I need you to find someone
who can have an influence
on that situation.
I don't care how far you have to go
or how deep you have to dig.
Just get what I need.
I can probably help you out with that.
But they're expensive connections.
You'll be compensated for your trouble.
Count on that.
Get it done.
Let me know what the cost is.
It's that simple.
You can ride this car back down.
I'll pick up the fare.
Hey, help me.
Take her over with the others.
Come on.
Hey, Bernard...
Aren't...
Aren't you scared?
How do you...
How do you let all this
just wash right over you?
It doesn't wash off, Abe.
Scares the bejesus out of me.
I fill my thoughts with something else.
Something that brings me strength.
Like what?
All those things that were said...
done to me my whole life...
I use them.
Use the anger that they bring.
Anger is better than fear.
Pissed off is better than terrified.
But she was shot right over there!
Right there, she was shot!
I mean, I don't feel angry.
That's not what I'm feeling.
I'm... I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
I'm overwhelmed by it.
That's why you're bald.
What?
Your bowel movements must be revolting.
Your insides
are rotten from all this fear.
- What are you talking about?
- You're probably
gonna piss your pants, and eventually
have a massive heart attack
and die suddenly right here.
You...
God damn son of a bitch!
You are one mean, gay bastard,
you know that?
Why don't you just take your advice and
just shove it right up your ass, huh?!
Right up yours!
Yeah?
What's so funny?
You afraid right now, Mr. Shelton?
Mr. Wolf?
You know I can wiggle my ears,
Johnny Boy?
Cross my eyes.
Shit, I can even do one eyebrow raised.
Tricks of the face trade,
you know?
53 muscles rule the human mug.
Each one buys us limitless expression.
I'm the hijacker
of all those expressions.
Like a ghost in my subjects' world,
robbing them of their final headmark.
Yet they know nothing of me.
So therefore, how can they perform
their final masterpiece?
That expression of pure,
unadulterated fear.
I see you assholes.
This is all very exciting, D.
They got a lot of firepower down there.
Relax, Leon.
They ain't lookin' at us, brother.
We're looking at them.
Lock down the scene.
I wanna know
when we I.D. the body. Hey, cap,
I think we may have found our shooter.
They got a body on the roof.
White male, 30s.
No I.D, he had a sniper rifle.
My guys think he's a pro.
And he had a clear line of sight
to the bank.
Who the hell contracts
a sniper to pick off Wolf?
Who has the means?
The motive and the connections
to hire a professional sniper?
My guess...
if you shot him
while he's holding your daughter,
there's a good chance
she's gonna run free.
- Son of a bitch.
- Yeah, son of a bitch is right.
Let's get Beck in here,
interrogate his ass.
That's a waste of time.
He won't talk.
Bring me Teddy Sabian.
Time to break the fat man.
You go home to take a piss?
I spoke to Lou.
The breach is completely dead.
Negotiations back on.
This might be
the shittiest day of all time.
- What now?
- God damn pirates.
They blew it in the ninth.
I take yet another bath.
Pirates?
- The bank's right upstairs, Hawke.
- Augie, relax, man.
Getting all hepped up is what got us
ripped off the perimeter.
Is that what you want?
You just want to wait it out?
Look, you know how Cali works.
We're never gonna get payback.
Zing's gone, at their hand,
and we're gonna sit and wait?
I'm not saying we bust in blazing.
I'm saying
we find the right way in.
They ain't breaching
'cause they can't find a hole.
So let's find a hole.
- Let's find a hole.
- Let's get in there.
You'll be getting a call in
the next five minutes with more details.
- Can we count on this guy, Mr. Doyle?
- He knows the repercussions
if he doesn't come through for me.
Hey, Mikey,
how's it going?
I'm proud of you, man,
hanging on in there like that.
What do you got for me?
Man on our side.
Waiting on the final details.
Your daughter's coming with us.
Got that?
When we're free and clear,
she's free and clear.
I figured that.
I'll call you back
once everything's set.
Clear the observation deck.
Why am I up here again?
I... I told you everything.
You ever hear
of a cuban cocktail, Teddy?
- What?
- A cuban cocktail.
It's a mixture...
of blood, urine, semen,
excrement.
This appetizing blend
is then placed in the sunlight for days
so it ages, ripens.
It's then thrown in a newbie's face.
You know what a newbie is?
It's a newcomer in prison.
Now, here's the interesting omit.
The blood ingredient,
that's usually taken from one
of the many prisoners infected with HIV.
- Why are you telling me this?
- Because you're going to prison.
I don't understand.
Stop bullshitting me!
Why did Wolf
let you walk out of that bank?
He needed you, didn't he?
See, when a man walks out of that bank,
not a boy, not a woman,
but a fat, disgusting,
worthless, piece-of-shit slob of a man,
such as yourself...
I just can't shake that.
It makes me think Wolf needed leverage.
He's got plenty with you, hasn't he?
I haven't done anything wrong.
- I've done nothing wrong.
- Keep denying it.
It's all gonna come out now.
I've got a dead sniper a block away.
I'm gonna tie that sniper to Alan Beck,
and guess what he's gonna do?
He'll tell me everything I need to know
- about you.
- I don't know anything about a sniper.
I swear on my life.
I never said you knew.
I'm gonna give you
one last chance to talk to me...
Okay?
You do that, Teddy,
there's no charges,
no cocktail...
Nothing.
For chrissake, Teddy,
help me get you your boy back.
Talk to me.
I can't do this.
Get out of my face.
Now!
I don't know where all these vents lead.
Me neither.
We need a grid map.
You know they ain't gonna give us that.
That's totally against protocol.
Well, go up and ask Tonray
if he can at least take a look at 'em.
We got no case to breach
if we can't find a safe access point.
Okay, I'll go up and I'll ask him.
But if he thinks something is up,
- I'm out.
- Alright.
We're on rotations.
Go take a break...
A half hour.
Any idea on the snipers?
Not yet.
My guys are still working on it.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I... I never committed
a crime in my whole life.
- But he's... He's got my son.
- What did you to, Teddy?
It's okay, my offer's still good.
I gave
these frequency codes to Alan Beck.
Robby is hoping the robbers
find a way to talk to him.
He threatened my son.
I didn't know what to do.
Get Mr. Sabian anything he wants.
- Son of a bitch! They talk.
- Wolf and Beck are talking...
Tap into it.
Hey, Beck, I'm getting impatient
over here.
There'll be a knock in a vent.
I'm told it's the same spot
the SWAT team entered once before.
There'll be a clear path out.
You can check it out,
but it's legit.
I got him...
- The line's in use.
- Okay, I'm going over there right now.
- Where?
- I don't know. Get it back.
- You alone?
- Yeah.
Come on, give it to me.
What, we have a problem?
- No.
- I'm gonna check
the out first, and then my guys
are gonna follow me, so move!
What the hell am I doing?
Alan, he said he would call you.
I need to know if he made contact.
Hang on.
Who's that?
It's the guy who hired you.
Wait, wait, the line's in use.
Yeah, I'm with the SWAT guy now
in the subbasement tunnel.
Just checking it out.
No, Ashley's still inside.
Look, I'll call you when we're out.
Go ahead, move it.
- What's he mean he's with a SWAT guy?
- Let's go!
- He's with a SWAT guy.
- Delta team...
Wait, wait...
Don't...
He's with a SWAT guy, one from your
team. If they leave through the tunnel,
- we'll get them there.
- Fine, let's go.
Augie, I got him, I got him!
Don't do it, man.
Don't do it.
You point your gun at me,
and you hang out with this scumbag.
Remember, it's the guy that killed Zing.
- Make him lower his weapon now.
- Walk away.
Walk away, H.
Trust me, please. I have to do this.
You're pointing a gun in my face, man.
How am I supposed to trust you?
If you don't let us go,
your friend's a dead man.
Nobody's talking to you, asshole!
Augie, what's going on?
I got in over my head
with the wrong people.
They know where my family is, man.
My sister, her kids.
Do this...
Please, for me.
Nobody has to know.
I'll make it right.
Just let me walk with him,
- please!
- Who the hell are you?
I don't know what you're talking about,
and why you point
- your gun in my face!
- Sorry, H,
- I never thought this would touch you.
- I'd listen to my friend if I was you.
I can't let you go.
You know I can't let you go.
Put your weapons down now!
Wolf!
Augie, go easy, man.
Easy, easy, Aug.
Ease up, Aug.
Just put it down, man.
Put it down, man.
Not like this, man.
No, Augie, stop.
Come on, Aug.
Don't go out like this, man.
We've been through too much...
Give me the gun, come on.
I can't take two in one day.
Come on, give me your gun.
Come on...
Give me the gun.
Come on.
You broke my heart, son.
Hold it!
I can confirm
that Alan Beck is in custody,
though I cannot elaborate
on the details of his arrest pending
a full investigation. What I can
tell you is that our hostage negotiator,
Captain Horst Cali, along with
Pittsburgh P.D. and our SWAT team,
are in full command of the situation,
and focused on the task at hand.
Getting the hostages
out of harm's way remains our priority.
I won't take questions at this time.
You'll all be briefed again
at the appropriate moment.
We've also just received word
that Cassandra Conforth,
who was shot earlier in the bank, is out
of surgery and is in stable condition
- at this hour.
- Mikey, you hear that?
Mike, you hear that, little brother?
She's gonna be okay, man.
Yeah, but we're not okay, Sarge.
None of us are okay.
And we'll never be okay again.
Okay, everybody, let's hit your posts.
Come on.
Hold on.
What do we do now, Sarge?
- I don't know, we just wait.
- What do you mean you don't know?
What was that?
I don't know.
But it's getting dangerous now, baby.
- We gotta get out of here.
- There's no way out.
Maybe it's nothing.
Maybe there was no banging, you know.
Maybe we were hallucinating.
Explain that, baby?
Not...
Not hallucinating, but maybe, like...
audi-u-nating.
We don't have any food or water.
What are we gonna do?
What is that, water?
I don't know.
- No, don't do it, I'm scared.
- I'll protect you. I promise.
They were like brothers to me, Con...
They were like the brothers I never had.
This mean I'm going home now?
Are you taking me off?
Hell no.
I need you, kid.
I need all the good cops I can get.
How's he doing?
He's all right.
You calling Wolf?
No, I'm gonna let him
stew in his defeat.
- He'll realize he's out of moves.
- You heard about Cass?
- No.
- She's gonna make it, Cap.
Your watch is clean.
Thank you.
I'm on my way to go deal with this
Beck debacle. Should take some time.
I know how much you're gonna miss me.
- Oh, yeah.
- Just remember,
I'm not really gone.
I'll speak to you.
Okay, Chief.
How can you look at me like that?
How can you do that?
After everything I've done to everybody.
Everybody else sees me
for what I really am, except you... Why?
I watch you...
I see the way you are with us,
with that boy.
I hear it in your voice
when you come over here, when we talk.
Maybe I just see
a different side of you.
I'm really sorry
about what happened to your friend.
I wish that would have never happened.
I wish...
I wish a lot of things never happened.
I'm just glad she's gonna be okay.
I didn't mean to yell at you earlier.
I was...
I was just upset.
Why do you keep coming in here for?
Close the door.
I dug a hole to the ladies' room.
What...
What is that?
What do you have there?
This is a life source, brother.
Republican guard.
Fifth Baghdad mech division.
I did...
things to him, Alby.
Things that...
no man should bear,
or bear witness to.
He never broke.
Not once
did he waver
in his undying loyalty to his country.
Well, it was my hope
that by taking a piece...
just a piece of this great man with me,
that maybe I, too, could,
you know, one day achieve that kind
of courage, or that kind of honor.
Yeah.
I want you to put this away.
All right.
Look at me.
- What?
- You're okay.
You're okay.
- All right?
- Yeah.
- I'm okay.
- All right.
Yeah.
You guys need to see this.
Come on.
You see?
You see that?
I noticed it before, but
I didn't really pay it any attention.
I thought it was some sniper laser,
but look at it.
- It's morse.
- Yeah, that's right, Hank.
That's morse,
and you see what it's saying?
Pro patria.
"For our country," man.
That's our motto. It's 1013.
Deke is out there.
Yes, he is, boys, that's right...
Yes, he is.
Guys...
I think I got it.
I found a way to get our boys out.