Vic's Noah Valiquette.
32. Lives a few blocks away.
The local P.D.
says a clown shot him,
- cut off his finger.
- A clown? Which finger?
- Right index.
- Witnesses?
The convenience store owner
heard the shot,
glimpse the suspect taking off.
I'm thinking that shooter
forced him into the alley, to kill him.
He took the finger?
Looks that way.
Uses for a detached
index finger.
Sending a message?
You from CBI?
Agent Teresa Lisbon.
This is Patrick Jane.
Ellis Hindon.
Glad your office is close.
This is a little out of our league.
We tried not to screw it up.
Preserved the crime scene,
canvassed the area for witnesses
and put out a description
of the attacker.
It sounds like you guys know
what you're doing. Why call us?
This is who we picked up
off the description.
They're all crying on the inside.
2x21
~ 18-5-4 ~
You're all disguise, why?
There was
this casting notice online.
Said they were holding auditions today
for a circus movie.
They were looking clown,
specified we should come in costume.
Was there a name on the ad?
Contact information?
No, just the address and time.
What's your name again?
Well, Miss Van P...
What's this?
You've got my heart in your pocket.
Thanks for your time.
- I hate clowns.
- Get in line. Same story?
They were here for an audition.
Keep up the interviews. Get a solid ID
on every one of these guys,
and go back to the office
and see if you can trace placed the ad.
You.
- Where have you been?
- Farmers' market.
Delicious apples,
if you like that kind of thing.
Keeping the clowns?
I don't want
that the shooter slipping away.
Too late. He's slipped.
These ones are just a smoke screen.
Why else would he place the ad?
It's a lovely day,
to waste your time here.
We have to.
Maybe Bozo made a mistake
and got caught here
with the rest of'em.
I knew a clown once.
Catastropho was his name.
A card thrower.
He could stick the ace of clubs
into a melon at 50 feet.
- We need to talk to the vic's wife.
- 50 feet.
If the...
If the zeta-function is defined
for all complex numbers
where S does not equal 1,
- then we can...
- To your audience.
Look at me. Talk to me.
I know you're just trying
to help, Daph.
Tell me more
about the zeta-whatever.
- You can do it.
- I'm not cut out for this.
- You're doing fine.
- I'm sorry.
We made this about two year ago
just before we got married.
Noah was trying
to get a tenured teaching position.
How'd that work out?
Not so good.
He has trouble addressing crowds.
My brother was,
a mathematical genius.
He finished high school at 15,
got his first degree in, like...
two years.
But he wasn't good with people.
He was good with me.
"Selected issues
"in the fourth order
"differential equations."
I guess that was Noah's.
Love's Tender Passion.
Yours?
Go ahead and make fun.
I wouldn't dream of it.
No, it's okay.
I get it.
I know how it looks.
I'm no brainiac.
If you met him, you'd probably think
he was king of the geeks.
What can I say?
I always had a thing for the smart guys.
My girlfriends thought I was crazy.
But when he opened up,
Noah had a beautiful soul.
I was good for him.
I helped him with the world.
What did he do for a living?
He published a few papers
in mathematical journals,
which...
obviously, do not pay much.
But he was gonna do fine.
He was always discovering...
What do you call 'em?
Proofs.
And, inventing stuff.
But one day it would've paid off.
I know it would.
And in the meantime?
We pretty much lived
on my waitressing.
I think that bothered Noah,
because he said,
he wanted to help out more.
He started day-trading
a few months back,
- but don't think it went so well.
- Why is that?
I don't know.
He wouldn't talk about it.
He never talked about anything.
Where was he going this morning?
A coffee place downtown.
Ariel's.
He spent most days there
on his laptop,
doing his day-trading stuff.
- He liked the background frequency.
- What's going on?
You couldn't sit down.
Guilty conscience?
My little brother just died.
And he was terrified of clowns,
- so whoever did this was sick.
- Did you know
about his thing
with clowns?
Yeah, Noah had his quirks.
And for the record,
where were you this morning
- at 7:30?
- I was here, asleep.
- I worked a late shift last night.
- And you?
In my car,
on the way to work.
Tough game Noah had going here.
He wasn't playing either of you?
- Who did he play with?
- Mostly one guy.
Tolman Bunting.
He runs a store, The Puzzle Nook
not too far from the Valiquette.
There's a lot of calls
between the store and the house.
We'll go and talk to him.
How's it going with the clowns?
Kenmore P.D. found a clown's outfit
about 3 miles from the crime scene.
- No trace of DNA.
- We'll put the clowns aside for now,
but keep the files nearby,
in case of.
Okay, boss.
You got it.
Noah's mind
was exquisite.
A few years ago,
I published a book of number puzzles,
and, shortly after,
Noah e-mailed me.
He'd solved all the puzzles,
of course,
but he had also found
a few logical flaws in two of them.
That's when I realized
that I had to have a person
of his intellectual caliber
in my orbit.
Then we started playing
a regular game of chess.
How often did you see him?
Once a month, i'd say, but...
We'd play on the internet
or on the phone...
I think you'll...
You'll like that one.
It's rather tricky.
Doesn't this just kinda go
like that...
Around there.
That goes around there.
Over there like that,
That's it?
Very good.
That was fun.
Do you know anybody
who was angry with Noah
or maybe somebody
who's held a grudge up against him?
Not at all, but, see,
Noah was a bit oblivious
to people's feelings,
so sometimes
that would come across as rude.
But he's honestly
the gentlest person
that you can imagine.
I can't fathom
anyone wanting to kill Noah.
Were you aware
that he was clourophobic? That means
- that he was afraid of...
- Fear of clowns.
- You sure?
- Quite.
- Where were you this morning at 7:30?
- I was out for a run.
- Was this the game with Noah?
- As a matter of fact, it was.
He might have had you.
You play?
A little.
We should have a game sometime.
That works.
I'll open with pawn to C4.
Pawn to E6.
Knight to F3.
Pawn to D5.
Declining the gambit.
Interesting.
Pawn to D4.
- Really?
- Scout's honor.
Could we continue,
- please?
- Of course.
My apologies.
You're gonna regret that open.
- We'll see.
- Did you see anything
unusual in Noah's behavior recently?
There was one thing.
When we actually started that game,
Noah was quite intent on betting,
- which he had never done before.
- Did you take the bet?
No, I like my money too much.
- You're sticking with that open?
- Why not?
Knight to F6.
Knight to C3.
Bishop...
to E7.
Your funeral.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you for stopping by.
By the way,
bishop... G5.
Mind your queen.
You got a message
from somebody named Tolman.
"King side castle."
As he leans toward his doom.
Chess, the game of kings.
Kings with too much time
on their hands.
Hey, boss?
What's up?
Valiquette's wife
said that he was bringing in money
- by day-trading?
- Yes.
They had a little money in the bank,
I checked his web browser history.
There isn't a single trade, so...
I ran his social,
he's never owned a stock.
- What was he doing then?
- I can't tell.
There's a lot of files that seem like
random numbers and letters.
Every week, he e-mailed a bunch of them
to the same address, "Beastslayer 949".
Contact Noah's ISP.
Make them tell you
who beastslayer is.
Daphne Valiquette on 2.
She sounds freaked.
You have to come.
There's somebody inside my house.
I called as soon as I saw the door.
- It's all right.
- I was gone less than an hour.
I should've called the police.
I wasn't thinking.
- How many entrances?
- Just the back door.
- Got it.
- You guys take the front.
Somebody forced it open.
Kitchen's clear.
Bathroom's clear!
Living room's clear.
Bedroom's clear.
You need to see this.
Somebody really wanted something.
Safe in the floor.
That's pretty old-school.
A high-end sensor lock.
Tough to bust into.
I'll call tech services,
we need a locksmith.
Don't bother.
I found the key.
No, this type of safe
doesn't use a key.
Yes, it does.
Bag it.
You're telling me
that somebody killed my husband,
cut off his finger
to get into some safe?
Yes, and this is all
we found in there...
A chessboard, a comic book
and some papers.
Have you ever seen this stuff before?
- Did Noah ever mention the safe?
- No. Never.
This was his house
before we got married.
I just moved my stuff in.
You can tell volunteering
information wasn't Noah's strong suit.
We think whatever the killer
was looking for wasn't in the safe.
That's why they ripped up
the rest of the house.
Would you excuse me?
Cho got in touch
with Valiquette's ISP.
"Beastslayer 949"
is Alec Mosca.
He lives 15 miles away.
- Cho and Rigsby are on their way now.
- Splendid.
Did Noah have
any other hiding places?
Maybe. Yeah, sure.
I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore.
How many secrets did he keep?
Why put all this junk into a safe?
It's not all junk.
This is a Spider-man 46.
In this issue,
he takes on the shocker.
Very good.
Worth a pretty penny.
What I find
is interesting,
is that the chess set
that your husband has set up
on the table is expensive,
and this one, on the other hand,
is made in China...
Not so expensive.
So one has to wonder why
he had the cheapo set
hidden away so carefully,
unless...
there's something inside.
Locker key.
Locker 42.
I wonder where that is.
It's this one?
Alec Mosca?
Who are you?
Agents Cho and Rigsby, CBI.
- Please open the door.
- Who?
CBI, sir. Let us in.
Sure. CBI, no problem.
Look, I'm in my skivvies,
so, give me a second
to get presentable.
He's gonna put his pants on
before he hits the window?
No, I do not.
Let me see your hands!
- Get away from here!
- Let me see your hands!
No problem.
There's $14,000 in it.
Take that to Mike.
Tell him I'm good for the rest.
On my sister-in-law's grave,
I swear!
What the hell...
Mike sent you, right?
To collect
on the boston-philly bet?
Crap.
Face the wall.
Put your hands on your head.
Who are you guys?
Remember the badge?
CBI.
- What is that?
- California Bureau of Investigation.
- We're like the FBI,
only more conveniently located.
Let me say
I'm very sorry
for the misunderstanding at my door.
I had no idea you were cops.
We showed you our badges.
Never watch movies?
That's how the bad guys do it.
No, it's not. Sit down.
How do you know Noah Valiquette?
Coffeehouse.
Noah likes vienna roast.
I'm partial to the sumatran blend.
Is that
what he's e-mailing you about...
Coffee orders?
You should tell the truth.
Easier to remember.
This is how it is.
I occasionally place a wager.
- Meaning you're a degenerate gambler?
- Yeah, okay.
A couple months back, I'm in
the coffeehouse going through my picks
when Noah asks what I'm doing.
Long story short,
he says he can give me
"rational analysis" on the ***
so I threw him
a couple games.
They all came through.
That caught my eye,
so we made a deal.
He gave me picks.
I gave him 10% of the winnings.
Picks, huh?
Noah said he had to send them in code.
Don't ask me. Just who he was.
When did the arrangement go south?
- It did?
- You did. You've been nervous
- since I mentioned him.
- From three weeks back,
every one of Noah's calls is a bust.
Guy couldn't pick a bear to crap
in the woods. I asked what was going on.
All he'd say was he had a problem,
- couldn't focus.
- Must've made you angry.
You think? He's got a problem?
I'm the one bleeding money.
But anything
that you might have heard
about angry words between us
bears no relation
to deeds carried out.
I never touched the guy.
Mosca's got two arrests
for assault.
I could see him going after Noah.
In a bar fight, maybe.
Not in a clown suit.
The question is,
- why did Noah's picks go sour?
- Anybody can have a bad run.
But Noah wasn't anybody,
a day here, a day there.
But three weeks?
According to Mosca, he had a problem.
He couldn't focus. Troubles at home?
Doesn't sound like problem
he'd even notice.
It must have been some kind of
intellectual challenge.
Agreed. But who could present that kind
of intellectual challenge, that kind...
of puzzle?
Did you come here
to concede the game?
Not at all.
Bishop takes E7.
Interesting.
What problem
was Noah working on for you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Noah and I played chess.
Liar.
I am not a liar.
What makes you think
I can't tell that?
Enough, Mr. Tolman. Start talking
the truth or I'm gonna pop ya.
- Don't even think about it.
- Put the gun down.
Down.
It's soft. It's just a hand.
There's nothing there.
Just a hand.
We're good.
Annika,
put the gun down.
Why do you have an armed bodyguard?
Why don't we, step into my office?
Sweet.
Do you understand how important
puzzles and codes are to you agents?
They protect your e-mails.
They stop credit card fraud.
Puzzle making and breaking
is the preeminent security issue
of our day, and I run
a consulting firm that deals
specifically with those issues.
Who do you work for?
We're not prejudiced.
- Whoever needs us.
- What was Noah doing for you?
That's delicate.
Mr. Bunting, unless you give us
your full cooperation,
I'll have the CBI computer crimes unit
in this office
in an hour.
I was grooming Noah
for a, pet project...
Something special.
What for?
A device that could decipher
virtually any encrypted information.
The universal hack.
That's the crude way of calling it.
I identified three people
that I thought could pull it off,
Noah was one of them.
I offered each one of them $2 million.
Last week,
Noah called me and told me
that he had built the device
but that he wasn't
going to give it to me.
Why?
He said he had second thoughts.
He was worried about the device
falling
- into the wrong hands.
- That doesn't worry you?
I'm a businessman, not a moralist.
Kind of annoying, though,
- Noah holding out on you like that.
- Not really.
You see, I decided that Noah
didn't really build the device,
that he couldn't,
embarrassed by his failures.
What if he had built a device?
What you'd do to get your hands on it?
Anything...
Short of killing him, of course.
I found a locker key
at Noah's house, very well hidden.
A locker 42.
Interesting.
Any idea where that locker is?
- We're looking.
- If you find it,
you must let me know,
because that device is mine.
Not yet.
You haven't paid for it.
I have a handful of lawyers
looking into it.
Before I forget...
queen to E7.
Taking your bishop.
We need to talk to the people
you're working on this project with.
Fine. No problem.
There's an Alex Kromm
who lives in Amsterdam,
and then the third person is local...
a Oliver McDaniel.
But I doubt that he killed Noah.
Why?
Oliver Simon McDaniel.
Your file says that
you finished college at 16,
graduate school at 19, and...
you were sent here after nearly choking
your father to death.
He's not my father.
He's a cyber clone sent by
the galactic quantum lords.
Them. You know, they're
always up to something shady.
Yes. They're trying to drive me mad.
But they won't succeed.
Have you heard about Noah?
I did.
Sad. Can you do a shiatsu massage?
Shame. I'm tight.
So tight.
And my skin is
just so dry and flaky.
The visitor log says that
Noah was the only person
who came to see you.
How did you know him?
Grad school.
I felt sorry for him.
He was a little off.
My guess was radiation.
How did he die?
Gunshot wound,
which, suggests it wasn't
the quantum lords that killed him.
Duh.
They'd use a lorax beam.
Why would they want
to kill Noah anyway? Big wuss.
Quite. His killer
wore a clown costume.
Any ideas who that might have been?
Assuming, of course, that it
is a carbon-based life-form.
But the clown thing's clever.
Noah hated them.
We understand that youere working
on a problem for Tolman Bunting?
My doctors wanted to nix it,
but I convinced them
it was good therapy.
Don't touch that!
Did you know that Noah
was working on one for him, too?
Which makes him a big-ass hypocrite.
Why is that?
Back in grad school, we got offered
a gig writing code
for some defense contractor.
Noah passed. Said he didn't want
to do anything that could harm someone.
Like this thing for Tolman
is any better!
It's worse.
You could destroy the world,
practically, if you wanted to.
Noah may well have
completed that project.
How are you doing with it?
Fine.
So not even close.
I could gouge your eyes out
with a spoon.
I'll take a rain check on that.
It appears Noah may have
hidden the device in a locker
that this key belongs to.
Do you have any idea
where that locker could be?
Sir, I'm a mental patient.
I don't know anything.
Nobody does.
But see, I know I don't know.
Paradox.
Interview over.
Yes, it is.
Thank you.
It's funny how well
you two get along.
I have the same kind of trouble
with those pesky quantum lords.
Noah's ethics should've
prevented him
from taking on the project
but he took it on.
- Why?
- Noah loved puzzles,
he couldn't resist the challenge.
- Plenty of those to choose from.
- Thanks.
The prospect
of lots and lots of money?
- That's a boring motive.
- It's still pretty popular.
Inmate escape.
Open that now!
I repeat, an inmate escape.
Alert the quantum lords.
Have the Kenmore police
put out an APB
and get me everything you can
on Oliver McDaniel.
I'm impressed.
Oliver made his own key pass
using information stolen from one guard,
trips the alarm to create a distraction,
a hides in the guards locker room.
- Last place they'd search.
- Turns out
it's not the first time. Multiple exits
for stretching back more than a month.
Hospital security didn't flag this?
Exits came up under the guard's name.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
Oliver could come
whenever he wanted.
But he was gone for
4 hours at the time of Noah's murder.
- Bumps him up the suspect list.
- One thing.
Why now? Why not stick to routine
and slip out at night?
Because he was going
after the device.
He must have figured out
where it was when he saw
the key, would've done
anything to get it.
- You talk to Tolman Bunting?
- He had no idea where Oliver could be.
If Oliver leaves a trail,
it's not gonna be his.
Check the guard's name
and run his credit cards.
Security pass may not be
the only thing Oliver copied.
Okay, you got it.
If I wanted to go away by the ocean,
you know, somewhere close,
- kind of a resort-type thing...
- Spa treatments?
That kind of thing, exactly.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Is there any places you'd recommend?
I'm kind of busy here, Jane.
Can you look on your computer?
- It'll take ten seconds.
- Why don't you do it?
I'll get you a nougat bar
from the machine over there.
Give me five minutes.
You are the queen
of my heart, Grace.
I'll wait.
Welcome to Tidewater, sir.
Thank you.
Very, lovely place.
We like to think so. Is there
something I can help you with?
Yes, there is.
How is your staff at procuring,
- things for guests?
- What do you mean?
- You know, special things.
- If it's company you're looking for...
No, it's... it's not
company I'm looking for.
But thank you,
if you're offering company...
Gary.
Got a hit
on the guard's credit card.
Somebody used it to buy a ticket to
Brazil departing out of SFO in an hour.
Tell the airport police
we're on our way.
What, Jane?
- What's up, Lisbon?
- Nothing much. Might make a run
to the San Francisco airport
to pick up Oliver McDaniel.
You may want to rethink that.
Where is he?
Isn't this lovely?
Smell of the ocean air,
sand beneath your feet.
We should move our offices here.
Oliver... Jane, where is he?
You'd be so much happier...
do wonders for your stress levels.
He's ticketed on a flight to Brazil.
Cho and Rigsby are on their way
to the airport.
Oliver has been in an insane
asylum for about six months.
He asked you for a massage.
He's in need of a little pampering.
- The flight's a misdirect.
- How can you be so sure?
The sound machine in his bedroom
was tuned in to the ocean.
That, and the fact that room 6-4-4
has already ordered six cans
of spaghettio's from the concierge.
- You can't arrest him yet.
- Yes, I can.
No, you can't.
He escaped because he knows
the location of the device,
and if we follow him,
- he'll lead us to it.
- I don't care about the device.
You don't care about
a code-breaking device
that could hack into our government's
national security system?
That's not very patriotic, Lisbon.
Pina Colada?
Rook to b8?
Poor, deluded fool.
Bunting will be resigned
before lunch, the way he's playing.
Great.
Bishop...
to
C4.
There he is.
Cho, we have a visual. We'll take point.
You and rigsby hang back.
He's headed in now.
Let's see where he's going.
Who was that?
- I don't know.
- Watch Oliver. Cho, come on.
Need a paramedic at the pier.
CBI. Don't move!
42.
Don't move!
Four and
two.
Nice work, tailing us to the pier.
But I guess for a guy who's after
the universal hack,
listening in on police radios
is no big thing.
It was, an unseasonably warm day.
I wanted to cool off by the water.
It was pure coincidence
- that Drew me there.
- This isn't funny, Mr. Bunting.
You're in trouble.
We've got a big handful
of felonies for what you did today,
and we are this close
to nailing you for the murder
of Noah Valiquette.
- Really?
- Really.
The clown costume, the ad...
sounds like the work of a man who likes
to play games, doesn't it?
AG on the phone, says it's urgent.
Do me a favor and,
send my best
to the attorney general.
And tell Mr. Jane queen to D8.
Queen to D8!
Thank you.
You knew where Noah hid the device.
How?
In grad school, Noah and I would go
to the pier. Noah liked the rides.
I liked the beach,
all those young women
in wet bathing suits.
I knew Noah hid the device there
as soon as I saw that key.
So you decided to escape
and get it for yourself.
I wanted the money.
There's an intergalactic war coming.
Yes, I'm aware.
If you take the device,
you know we're waiting for you.
I wanted the device
so I could see how it worked.
After that, I could make my own,
sell 'em wherever,
have enough money
to build my bunker.
The hospital security logs have you out
the morning of the murder.
- War preparations?
- Breakfast at my favorite strip club.
They have an open buffet,
all you can eat.
And Noah's killer planned
an elaborate diversion
to get away from the crime scene,
like your ticket to brazil stunt.
I wasn't aware it was a crime
to be intelligent, agent Cho.
The AG insists I let Bunting go,
drop all charges.
The man must have serious juice.
It stands to reason.
He knows where the skeletons are buried.
I don't know what to do.
How do you build the case?
It's not so hard.
Talk to the girls at the strip club.
Someone's gotta remember.
He speaks the truth, Cho.
Oliver here would have trouble killing
a light beer...
- Much less Noah Valiquette.
- That's not accurate.
I could mess you up badly
if I wanted to.
But you don't want to.
Before we let you walk out the door,
I need a favor.
- Not a chance.
- Consider it.
It'll give you the chance
to work with this,
then when you're done,
a gift from the planetary league.
Rook takes F6.
Your very friendly assistant
let me in.
Rook takes F6.
King to G8.
What you doing here?
I came by to see
if Noah's doohickey here
actually works.
- That's it?
- Yes.
- So he did build it.
- Yes, and I'm here
Yto return it...
For $2 million, of course.
You expect me to pay you?
Well, not me, no,
but its rightful owners.
Have you met
Noah's wife daphne and brother Rafe?
Legally,
Noah's property
is passed on to daphne,
including this.
You ever seen this before?
- No.
- What is it?
It's a code-breaking device
designed by Noah for Mr. Bunting,
in return for $2 million...
Your $2 million.
My god.
I'm sure a cashier's check will be fine,
Mr. Bunting. Yes.
I think
we first have to make sure this works.
At was part of our arrangement.
As you wish.
We're gonna need an encrypted file.
How about
agent Lisbon's personnel file?
I happen to have it on disk right here.
It has some great photos.
Fine.
It seems to be working here.
- What does that mean?
- It means
that it's not working.
It seems Noah was unable
to complete the project.
I am sorry, Mrs. Valiquette.
He needed more time.
Wait. How do we know it doesn't work?
Maybe he's
playing us,
trying to save himself a couple million.
Don't be absurd.
Why wouldn't I want this to work?
Try it again, 'cause my husband's
a genius. It has to work.
I'm afraid your,
husband's genius had its limitations.
Humor us.
Okay, fine.
What's happening?
It's working.
It's working!
What the hell?
- Turn it off.
- Wait.
- It's right, isn't it?
- Of course not.
You said you didn't know anything
about the device.
You were lying.
I had Oliver change the settings
so it wouldn't work.
But you knew how to change them back.
You watched Noah work.
You knew that he decided not
to give it to Tolman for any price.
So you did what you felt you had to...
You played on his fear.
You'd take the device
and turn it in to Tolman yourself.
All you had to do was open the safe.
The problem...
it wasn't in the safe.
That movie
with the crazy math guy
and the woman who loves him...
Yeah, I thought Noah
and me would be like that.
"Love's tender passion."
Yeah, you go ahead and make fun.
Life with Noah
was nothing like that.
It was silence...
days of it,
and books I could never understand
the title of,
and no sex when he's thinking,
which, by the way, is all the time.
I work 50 hours a week scrounging
for tips just so we could have food.
Anyway, so then
Noah told me about this guy who would
pay him
$2 million to build this thing...
$2 million.
I begged him,
and finally he said he would do it,
which was only right
because it was his turn.
But he wouldn't hand it over,
and you couldn't live with that.
He said it was too dangerous.
I tried to make him,
but he said that...
He said I wasn't able
to understand the implications.
So I decided to show him
I could be smart, too.
Or a whole lot dumber.
I'm not sure which.
Get up.
Hands behind your back.
What put you on to her?
I came to it very late.
I could have kicked myself.
The kitchen of her house was left
unsearched because that was her domain.
She knew the device wasn't there.
Perfect timing.
Pawn
to F
four.
Shrewd.
But I gather you're here
for more than just to pin my queen.
Actually, I came here to collect
my property.
Given daphne's condition,
ownership of the device
goes to Noah's brother.
But when I contacted rafe,
he wanted nothing to do with it.
So according to my attorneys,
that passes the device...
to me.
I've all the documents.
If you have any questions...
No need.
It's all yours.
I hope you don't mind,
I did have a little fiddle with it.
I just wanted to see how it worked.
- Easily fixed, I'd imagine.
- Easily?
What's that?
That may be part of it.
You are gonna be hearing
from my attorney.
Tolman, one last thing...
Bishop...
to C4.
Forced mate
in three moves.
I win.
Come and take a closer look.
You'll see it.
We should do this again!