You clean up very nicely,
if you don't mind me saying so.
I don't mind you saying so.
Thanks.
You look...
Pretty much the same
as you always look.
- Really?
- Yes.
- This is my date outfit.
- Really?
Is this your first date?
I mean, since your wife died?
Do I seem out of practice?
My name's Gerard.
I'll be your server this evening.
- Would you like to hear our specials?
- Sorry, but I'm getting a message
from... your mother.
Janet...
I'm sorry for your loss.
She's happy now.
And she wants you to know
that she sends her deepest love.
And...
your uncle...
says,
"roll tide."
Does that mean anything to you.
Roll tide?
My mother's brother Edward.
He died five years ago.
He was a tight end at Alabama
in the '60s.
They're called the Crimson tide.
That's their rallying cry, "roll tide."
I'd like to have the soup du jour
and the lamb, medium,
and the arugula salad
and the fish for the lady.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
What?
Come on.
You're so ferocious
in your lack of faith.
Is it so hard to imagine
that I'm not putting on an act?
That I really am what I say I am?
His mother sent a message.
I'm meant to help.
That's all.
It happens to me all the time.
I'm sorry.
Roll tide.
Bad guys just keep on coming, huh?
I hate the Internet.
If you like, I can deal.
- You go.
- No, it's okay.
It's just a web alert for when a name
we're interested in pops up.
What is it?
This is not good.
Relax,
It's just a hoax.
It's staged, almost certainly.
My God.
I didn't put... no.
- Yes.
- No.
You went to jail, really?
- I did. What's so hard to believe?
- For how long?
Two days
and two very luxurious nights.
And how'd you get out?
I just escaped.
I don't believe you for one second.
It wasn't that difficult.
It's all timing.
I'm not kidding.
Excuse me.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry.
It's work.
Jane, you need to come
to the office right now.
JJ Team
2x23
~ Red Sky in the Morning ~
It was posted
on the Internet an hour ago
on a popular notice board.
There's a message that goes with it.
"I am becoming
what I was meant to be.
"Your children's children
will worship me."
We don't know
where the video was made.
There appears to be an '08 Silverado
parked outside the house,
so it's gotta be at least that recent.
Has red john made videos
or issued statements like this before?
- No.
- Thank you.
Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt.
Hi, Kristina.
Good to see you.
That poor girl.
For what it's worth, I'm getting a sense
that she died very recently.
Her body
will be discovered very soon.
She's near water.
Does this feel like Red John to you?
I'm not getting a read on that.
The whole Internet aspect
is interesting, though, isn't it?
Why put it up there?
This clip's had over a million viewers.
A desire for fame?
Patrick, you're being very quiet.
What are you thinking?
I'd have to see the crime scene.
CHP just reported a homicide
in the bay area.
Smiley face on the wall.
College student named Marley Sparrow.
Roommate found her,
called it in about a half-hour ago.
Let's get ready to go.
Bay area?
Yes. That is close to water.
That's uncanny.
Come on.
That's pretty good.
I am feeling a strong connection
to this case somehow.
Can we have a word, please?
Excuse us.
She's gonna ask
if she can come along with us.
Now obviously, that's your call.
But I hope that you refuse,
'cause I won't work with her.
I will quit.
What's your objection?
If she can help us, why not?
Nothing she says
is more than clever guesswork.
So she has essentially
the same skills as you,
without all the drama.
What's the deal?
Red John is mine.
I hear you.
Sorry to interrupt.
Please.
I was going to offer my services,
but I get the sense Mr. Jane is
telling you that he won't work with me.
The last thing I want to do
is upset this investigation,
but if I have any more feelings
about the case, could I call you?
Of course, Kristina.
Always be glad
to hear your thoughts.
Have a good night.
- Listen...
- I completely understand.
No hard feelings.
That was an unusual date, though?
I'll see you soon, I hope.
- Would you...
- Yes, sure.
Guys, give me a minute, please.
Thank you.
Hey, Marley.
We'll get this sorted out for you.
Long time.
So qué pasa, dude?
My people need to do their thing.
I won't be long.
You hoovering up the, ol'psychic
ectoplasm?
Yeah, that's exactly what I'm doing.
We have a schedule to keep,
amigo. Ticktock.
Sooner you're done fooling around,
sooner my people can find
actual clues.
She's from Iowa.
She played the guitar.
She liked dark chocolate,
sudoku
and snowboarding.
Shy, but strong.
Honorable, modest.
Didn't drink or smoke.
Parents died
when she was very young.
And, she wanted to go
into family law and help foster kids
like herself.
Or become a singer.
She hadn't made up her mind yet.
Yeah, that's great, dude.
But where's Red John?
This wasn't Red John.
So you say.
So I say.
Make sure you have your people
send those papers and journals
to the CBI office.
Will do.
Thank you.
Marley was the best.
The best person.
A beautiful soul.
Ruth, you found her body, yes?
When you entered,
did you notice anything unusual
before you found the body?
- Something missing or out of place?
- No, I don't think so.
- How long had you been gone?
- Two days, snowboarding.
Marley was supposed to come,
but then her boyfriend was coming over
to see her, so she stayed.
His name?
Grady Shipp.
He's a policeman in San Francisco.
They've been dating for, like...
a month.
Okay. What was he like?
Nice guy?
Marley really liked him a lot.
Said he was super nice.
But I don't know.
We never actually met him.
She'd go to his place, mostly.
And when he came by here,
he'd wait for her in his car.
Weird?
I think Marley was a bit embarrassed
for hooking up
with a cop, you know?
So she kept him on the down low.
Embarrassed?
Marley was cool.
And cops are sort of nerds with guns,
aren't they?
Hello?
No offense.
Sorry.
Marley Sparrow?
Yes, I was her academic advisor
for two semesters.
Nice enough girl,
but not as clever
as she likes to think she is.
But none of 'em are, are they?
Did you notice any changes
in her behavior recently?
No. But nor do I pay
close attention.
They're all empty vessels
to be filled
with knowledge.
Here is
a horrible coincidence.
Last semester, I taught
a criminology elective.
Murder, myth and marketing...
The serial killer as commodity.
Red John
was actually mentioned in our class
discussions. Isn't that eerie?
Who mentioned him?
What'd they say?
Damned if I know.
It was eight or nine months ago.
Do you have a student list?
You know, I do.
I do. Somewhere.
We would love to get a look
at that list.
No Grady Shipp
with any San Fran police agency.
No Grady Shipp, period.
There was a Grady Shipp once.
He ate his neighbors
in little rock back in the '90s.
He was lethally injected
in Arkansas in '02.
So Marley's boyfriend
doesn't want anybody to see his face,
and he named himself
after a cannibal.
- That's two strikes against him.
- We don't have a name or other.
The roommate,
said that he never got out of his car.
Maybe we can get a make
and model from her.
In 1989,
he did a 6-month spell
in the same wing at Lompoc
as Orval Tanner.
- Tanner?
- Red John's friend.
You have the entire Lompoc
prison registry
in your head?
Only the relevant sections.
What does it mean? Is it a joke?
- Marley's boyfriend is Red John.
- Senseless.
In the hunt for this beast
known as "Red John".
Well, he...
he's not a beast, Jackie.
He's a human being.
Now he has done terrible things,
but he is still capable of
redemption...
Like all of us.
Red John...
if you're listening to us now,
I urge you to reach out
and get help.
You can change.
What the hell are you thinking?
Don't you understand
who you're dealing with?
- I do understand, yes.
- No, you don't.
Clearly, you don't understand.
I asked miss Frye here
so that I could fully express
my deep dismay.
- I was speaking from the heart.
- That may be,
but you were also hustling for business.
And that's okay,
but you
present me now with a problem.
We don't have any obligation
to protect you, but...
I wasn't asking.
Completely unnecessary.
- Red John is not coming after me.
- Are you blind?
You've done exactly what I did.
I went on television and talked
about him as though I knew him,
and he killed my wife and child.
Patrick, he was punishing you
because you lied about him.
I was telling the truth.
He won't take offense with me.
He might even listen to what I said.
In fact, I believe he will.
People do change, Patrick.
It's possible.
Agent Hightower, I'm truly sorry
for dismaying you.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have some other appointments.
She needs 24-hour protection...
The best that you can provide.
The Sac P.D. Special protection unit
will provide security,
the CBI will be on the inside,
bodyguarding miss Frye.
Jane and I will take
the first shift.
The next 24-hour rotation
will be split among us,
alternating with the Sparrow case.
We're gonna have
to stop protecting her.
That's when he'll go for her.
He'll just wait.
Van pelt, what do you got?
We're looking for Grady Shipp?
Marley's address book.
Different writing.
Maybe Grady Shipp himself.
- Can I?
- Keep digging.
- Take Cho with you. Check it out.
- Yeah, you got it.
Blood.
Pig's blood, maybe.
For practice?
I'll call it in.
What is it?
A lens cap.
Interesting.
Practicing the Red John symbol,
and not just watching us pursue him,
but filming the pursuit.
What does it mean?
It means Marley Sparrow's killer
loves cameras. He's a voyeur...
A fanboy, a slasher movie geek.
Great.
But where does that take us now?
Like in a car?
- Try the campus film club.
- All right.
Nice place?
Tasteful.
It looks like we're about to pay
too much money to get our legs waxed.
Would you like something to eat?
Sure, thanks.
I'm good.
On reflection, I'm truly sorry
for the situation I put you in.
I hadn't thought through
your involvement.
I'll eat some lunch.
Just please don't make a fuss.
Miss Ketchum?
Policemen.
I knew I'd forgotten something...
There it is.
- I thought for sure I'd sent that.
- Sent what?
The class list of the students
in my criminology class.
- Your colleague had asked for it.
- You're chair of the film club also?
I have that honor.
You know what? I have
the film club register here as well.
Yes. Would you like to see it?
Yes, that would be good.
Okay.
Here you go.
Where were you Tuesday night?
Thrilling!
- Am I a suspect?
- Are you?
Well...
I'd like to think I can still summon
that kind of passion.
So where were you?
Home. Alone.
Reading a murder mystery, actually.
Now there's only one name
on both lists. Wesley Blankfein.
You just made a face.
Well, he is a sweet boy.
Rather a good actor, actually.
But, strange.
Strange? How?
I can't really put my finger on it.
It's a look in his eyes.
Yep, that's him.
I remember when he moved in.
I mentioned to him he was a little older
than most of our students,
and he said he needed to escape
from his mother.
Which I thought was an odd response.
- And when did you last see him?
- Three weeks ago, maybe.
I figured he had a girlfriend.
- Nothing here!
- Hey Dylan.
Quick question.
You said Marley's boyfriend
waited in a car?
- Do you recall what type of car?
- It was black, I think.
- I'm bad with cars.
- It was a black SVU.
- What car did Blankfein drive?
- He didn't have a car.
Try locating Blankfein's mother.
Maybe she knows where he is.
Let me know.
Wesley Blankfein's in the wind.
He might be good for this.
I don't think so.
Marley made contact with me.
The name "Blankfein" doesn't resonate.
He made contact with you?
Of course.
I think we might have had enough
of your crime-fighting skills, Kristina.
Might be best to stick
to the crystal therapy and the...
foot massages?
- Reflexology.
- Right.
Reflexology.
- This is Lisbon.
-
We got a case here in Lake Tahoe.
Looks like your boy Red John.
The victim's name is
Jacqueline Sandoval.
You wanna come take a look?
You can smile your arrogant smile
and act like you know everything
about everything, but you don't.
There are whole worlds
you can't even begin to understand.
Synchronized swimming is the only world
that springs to mind.
But I'm sure you're right.
There may be many others.
What's the matter?
Red John killed the woman
who interviewed you.
Oh, my god.
My God.
It's Red John, all right.
I'll reach out to the feds,
make sure they keep us in the loop.
We must go back
to Kristina Frye's place.
There are cops all around her house.
Van Pelt is with her,
and there's other CBI agents
on their way. She's safe.
I am confident
Red John won't go there.
- That is exactly why he might.
- If he does, we'll get him.
You wanna hang out at Kristina's
house, waiting for Red John to show up?
Let's go back to the office,
work the Marley Sparrow case.
There's nothing useful
that I can do there.
This Blankfein character,
he looks good for it, right?
Fine. Go and wait for Red John.
It's not a good idea, though.
We're in Nevada. You can't just
walk off and leave me here.
Wesley Blankfein's mother
is Myra Hauser-Blankfein.
Address in Franklin Heights.
She owns a black SUV
like Grady Shipp drives.
- Good. Go check her out.
- Now?
It's a long drive.
You leave now,
you'll be there by the morning.
Grace, thank you.
How you doing?
I'm doing fine.
Red John certainly made his point.
Quite possibly,
he'll leave things be now.
I know he will.
I have a clear vision of him.
He needs to create fear, that's all.
He's done that now,
and he feels calm.
I'm perfectly safe.
Will you just stop that nonsense?
You wanted to promote
your psychic business,
and you made a big mistake.
- Now will you please just own it?
- Why are you here?
I am here
because I want to protect you.
And how are you gonna protect me?
If he comes right now,
what are you gonna do,
- hypnotize him?
- What I need to do.
If Red John wants to reach me,
he will.
I choose to believe
that he doesn't want to.
- Now please, go away.
- I'm gone.
You're wasting your time.
We're looking for Mrs. Blankfein
and her son.
Gone. And left the cats to starve.
It's not right.
- Do you know where they went?
- No.
Never leaves before. Never.
Every day, 11:00,
like a machine,
she's watching her tv shows.
Three days now I hear nothing.
Quiet like the grave.
- Her son wesley? Have you seen him?
- Nope. Gone, too.
You know
Mrs. Blankfein might be dead?
Yes, it did.
But there'd be a smell,
wouldn't there, if she was dead?
Step back inside please.
Bedroom's clear.
Jeez.
"G.S."
- Grady Shipp.
- Bingo.
Inside the mind of Wesley Blankfein.
Aka Grady Shipp.
Not pretty.
What it looks like, he's obsessed
with Marley, so he builds a shrine,
fakes up all these photos
of them together,
tries to turn the fantasy into reality,
and posing as Grady Shipp,
he asks her out, and she says yes.
Big mistake.
Fantasy and reality collide,
- and she dies.
- Sounds about right.
Where the hell is he?
Where's his mom?
You find anything useful
in the apartment? No computer?
No. A lot of cats.
The pictures of Marley were taken
at different times and places.
The pictures of Wesley
were taken in the same place.
Nowhere we've been.
- Maybe it's a safe house.
- Nothing to say where it is.
You take a look,
if you see anything useful?
Sure.
If you like.
And...
There's a photo of Wesley
with a sign in the distance.
A yellow "KC" backward on a pole.
His shadow is pointing right to it.
Yeah. It's way small
back there, but I see it.
That's the logo for Kenny's Chili.
Southern California fast food chain.
- There's about 50 or so outlets.
- You memorize trademarks?
With Wesley's long shadow
and the golden light,
that would say afternoon.
And sun is in the west,
so that puts Kenny's
due east of this location,
about a block and a half, I'd say.
He's right.
50 or so outlets?
Hardware store
and a liquor store next to it.
- That should narrow it down.
- I'll get on it.
Thank you.
You should make that call.
What call?
Right.
Like I'm not a detective, too?
Hey, Jane. It's Grace.
Kristina's taking a nap.
I can get her for you if you like.
I'd appreciate that, Grace.
Thank you.
Kristina?
It's Jane for you.
Open the door.
How did Kristina
get past the guards?
We don't know. But she also packed
a bag, she took her passport
and her credit cards, so we can
assume she wasn't abducted.
You can't assume. Red john could've
gotten in and taken her.
Maybe. The likelihood that she's panic
and ran somewhere to hide.
Or maybe he lured her out somehow.
We'll check the phone records.
Let's start contacting her relatives
and friends. She's out there.
Forgive me, but belay that order.
The search for Kristina Frye
will be conducted
- by the missing persons unit.
- What?
They're the best at what they do.
They will find her
if she can be found.
And, Van Pelt, snap out of it.
Wasn't your fault.
- Yes, ma'am,
- Move on.
Where are we
on the Marley Sparrow case?
We have a suspect at large
by the name of Wesley Blankfein.
He's been obsessed with both
Red John and Marley Sparrow.
He seems to have created
an alter ego
by the name of Grady Shipp.
It's after a killer
with Red John connections.
Any leads?
Off photos he took,
we've ID'd 6 possible locations
for what we assume is
Blankfein's safe house.
It's much a long shot,
but it's all we have.
Go to it.
Let's start divvying up
the locations.
Cho, you take riverside county.
Bring Rigsby with you.
Van Pelt and I will take
the san bernardino locations.
You stay here.
Take a break.
- I don't need a break.
- I think you do.
I'd rather keep active.
You're too hyped up to be out
in the field.
- That's nonsense.
- I agree with Lisbon. Get some rest.
Some rest?
Just lie down
and catch up on some z's.
Kick back with a good book.
Rest?
- I'm fine.
- Debatable.
Do you want me to ask
the psych counselor for an evaluation?
Leave a message.
I'll call you back.
Lisbon, it's Jane. I found it.
It's 52 North Esperanza.
Hotel Del Corona in Salinger Mill.
I am gonna...
I'm gonna wait for you
at Kenny's, okay?
Give me a call
when you get this message. Thank you.
Welcome, Detective.
I'm Grady Shipp.
So good of you to come visit me.
You're a lucky man.
Very lucky.
Tonight...
You will have the dying honor...
Can we do that again?
Tonight...
You will have the honor of dying
as a sacrifice
to the holy master.
Behold...
The blood sacrament
of the master.
Stop.
You wanna try that again?
Just try it again.
Say it like you mean it.
Where's the passion gone?
Behold the blood sacrament
of the master.
No. I'm not...
I'm not buying it. Come on.
Just stop of a second and think...
Think about what you're doing,
and we'll start again from the top?
I know what's going on.
They've got your mother, don't they?
How'd you know?
They're forcing you to play a part
in their sick little movie.
You're playing the part
of grady shipp, right?
It's okay. It's okay.
We need to talk.
Thank you very much
for totally ruining
a freaking brilliant scene,
you jerk.
Hush, Dyl.
How did you know?
You were the only people
that mentioned Grady Shipp.
He was your creation.
And it was you that killed Marley,
wasn't it, Dylan?
Wesley couldn't hurt a fly.
It was a truly sick individual
that did that.
It was me, actually.
Dyl's much better with the camera,
and Marley...
Deserved what she got,
pious little bitch.
Keep the camera running.
This is all good stuff.
You wouldn't know good stuff
if it smacked you in the face.
This is just a corny slasher movie.
But real, dude.
Real blood.
Real guts.
Yours. Wesley, let's,
wrap this scene up now.
Gonna pick it up right at the end...
"behold the blood," etc...
and then stab this sucker.
I don't know.
What are you... Not... No!
This man is dead.
The only question
is whether you and your mom
want to live
or you want to die like him.
That's your choice here.
These people are nuttier
than a fruitcake.
They're gonna kill you regardless.
You don't have to do this.
We are not monsters, Wesley.
We're artists.
We are making art.
When the movie's done, of course you
and your mom are free to go,
with our gratitude for your help.
Stay calm.
"Behold the blood." Wesley.
I'm sorry.
- Behold...
- No, wesley.
The blood sacrament...
- It's okay.
- Of the master!
If there's one thing
I can't tolerate,
it's cheap imitations of my work.
Do you know who I am?
"Tiger, tiger, burning bright...
"in the forests of the night,
"what immortal hand or eye
"could frame thy fearful symmetry?"
I almost forgot.
Kristina would want me
to send her love.
She's very fond of you,
despite your differences.
Roll tide.
You okay?
I'm fine.
You're sure he said nothing?
Nothing at all?
Nothing.
"Tiger, tiger,
"burning bright...
"in the forests of the night,
"what immortal hand or eye
"could frame thy fearful symmetry?"