Rigsby.
You got it, boss.
- We're up.
- Lisbon?
She's gonna call here next.
She'll know. Get out.
Grace, wake up.
How is Lisbon gonna know i'm with you?
Right.
Leave it.
Get out.
Get out,
Agent Grace Van Pelt.
Hi, boss. What's up?
All right.
Bosco.
And to what do i owe this pleasure?
- You're up. Where are you at?
- Crime scene. Why?
- Coffee run? Usual for you, boss?
- Tall drip, black.
We need to talk.
- About what?
- Come see me when you get back.
Okay. Look forward to it.
Okay, boys,
did one of you see Hicks?
Morning. Well, almost morning.
Morning, everyone.
We got a caucasian male
50s, gunshot to the head.
And tastefully garnished
with an explosion of yellow roses.
Security guard saw the body,
called sac PD,
but this is a state cemetery,
which is why we're here at,
- dark-thirty.
- Swell spot.
Check out the stippling.
Looks like he was shot at close range.
And fibers in the wound indicate
clothes were removed postmortem.
You smell nice.
Is that Lilac soap?
- Something, Jane?
- Yes, i do. He's naked.
- Let me write that down.
- It makes him look kind of sad,
vulnerable.
- A little comic, even.
- Meaning what?
He was posed like this,
not just dumped here. It's a statement.
Doctor, the mark on the hand...
Is that a burn?
Looks more like
freezer burn, actually.
That explains it.
His liver temp is 45 degrees,
it's only around 58 in here.
Somebody froze his body
in that position, then dumped him.
Could be a signature, maybe
a serial pattern.
We'll talk to Bosco about that,
see if he has any similar incidents.
- Come on. Let's get out of here.
- Let forensics do their thing.
You smell lovely.
What is that? Is that Lilac?
Thanks.
It's pretty.
Morning, Rebecca.
They look good.
One of those for me?
It's all right to like me now.
Your boss and i made up.
That's okay, Rebecca.
I don't like him, either.
She's a liar. She loves me.
In your dreams.
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god, no!
He's gone!
No pulse.
- This guy is dead too.
- Jane, some help?
Get over here now!
Press as hard as you can
right there, there.
We've got agents
down on the fifth floor.
Inside the building.
We're in lockdown on my authority.
I have 3 agents down. I need EMTS
and roll SWAT, sac PD. and CHP.
And have them set up a perimeter.
Suspects may still be here.
Lock this place down!
5, 6, 7, 8,
9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15...
24 hours earlier
Hicks? Bosco?
Stealing major crimes' food...
Violation of penal code
section 484, i believe.
It didn't have a name on it.
This one does.
It's mine. It's from Cornaro's.
Meatball sub is really
their best thing.
Hope i don't tell Mandy
you went off your diet.
She's in New Hampshire
with her sister.
There you are.
Agent hicks, your form 41s.
Boss, the attorney general's office
called about the armenian cartel thing.
And you better hope i don't tell
your wife about you going off your diet.
Breathe, breathe.
Clear!
He's back.
He's bleading out.
No breath sound on the right side.
- His pulse is really weak.
- Run IV. Wide open.
We're code three. Let's move,
You okay?
What do we got?
Lockdown's in full effect, buildingwide.
Same with the Capitol and the DOJ.
Cho's liaising with the sac PD.
They're setting up a 2-block perimeter.
Now nobody gets in or out.
All civilians are sent
to the downstairs lobby for holding.
Swat's on the way up.
We're gonna do a sweep room by room.
Suspects could still be here.
Get with security.
Check the camera footage,
and set up teams to interview guards,
janitors and everyone down in the lobby.
You got it.
He's gone. Go on now.
You may be in shock. Look at me.
There should be three bodies.
There only two.
- Where's agent Hicks?
- I'll get Cho on that.
Maybe we should just wash up first.
- So you saw Hicks this morning?
- I haven't seen him since yesterday.
And yesterday,
was he angry or upset?
You think Marlon Hicks
could have done this?
We have to check every angle,
Rebecca.
Let's back up.
When you went out to get coffee,
did you see anything unusual?
Somebody who didn't belong here,?
Everything was fine. It was normal.
- God, I'm sorry. I'm not helping.
- It's okay.
I was gone maybe 10 minutes and I...
I didn't see anything weird.
Bosco called the team this morning,
you know why?
Well, I thought that maybe
it was the armenian cartel arrests.
You were that close
to making an arrest?
There was...
a break this week.
An informant came through the boss said.
It was something about...
- a warehouse.
- Lisbon.
Did forensics come up
with an I.D. on the frozen man?
I haven't checked in with them.
It's not really a priority right now.
I guess.
- You were saying?
- Camera four, also nothing.
Just an ordinary day.
- Weird, huh?
- These guys are like ghosts.
No kidding. We cleared the building
top to bottom, there's no sign of them.
B.F.S. are dusting everywhere
for prints,
it'll take days
to go through them all.
Lisbon said I should see
if you needed a hand here.
Jimmy, go to camera 5 now.
Lobby entrance, same time code.
That's Rebecca coming back.
She was gone 9 minutes 30
altogether.
I don't recognize hat guy here. Put him
on the list of people to check out.
OK Jimmy, camera 6...
the garage entrance.
Hang on.
Something's screwed up here.
Some files are corrupted
on this data drive.
- That's not possible, our firewalls...
- Have been breached.
Camera 6 and 7.
That's the garage.
They were disabled remotely.
Looks like at least a 30-minute gap.
So, we have no way of knowing
who went in or out via the garage.
Jimmy, get somebody from I.T. down here,
figure out what we're dealing with.
I'll tell my boss.
Ten minutes.
It was all over in 10 minutes.
Got it.
Thanks, Avila, I owe you one.
Agent Lisbon,
I spoke to the governor. I told him
that I have my best team on this one.
- I know you'll do us proud.
- Thanks, boss.
I reached out to sac P.D. narcotics
about that armenian drug cartel...
In a minute.
- I just got word from the hospital.
- He's not dead?
No, Bosco's in surgery,
but I wanted you to prepare yourself.
His injuries are extensive,
critical.
Teresa, I'm sorry to ask this,
but need to know that you're gonna
be able to go on with this case,
no matter what happens.
If you can't,
just let me know,
and I'll put someone else on point.
Not necessary.
You think Sam Bosco
is gonna let a little lead stop him?
Please.
I hope you're right.
Good luck.
Nothing on Hicks.
I had a uni run by his house,
he's not there, no car in the driveway.
I've got something.
You know that armenian drug cartel
that Bosco was close to nailing?
It's run by a guy named M. Assanian.
Bad guy.
Outside of the mexicans, biggest heroin
distributor on the west coast.
Bosco must've spooked him.
He left the country 3 days ago.
So maybe he leaves town to keep himself
clean while his people kill Bosco.
It makes sense.
Kill the team, kill the case.
- It's worth checking out.
- Lisbon,
did we get an I.D. on the man
from the cemetery yet?
- What is with you and this case?
- It's just a feeling.
You think it's connected to Bosco?
- Maybe.
- How?
Hard to say.
Fine. Cho, call it up.
Forensics may have posted something.
- Thank you.
- Run down this informant.
See if he's got anything for us.
Lauro in narcotics
- said you could use his name.
- I will do.
Forensics says cemetery guy's
fingerprints belong to a Dr. T. Morning
- age 55, Stockton.
- Towlen Morning.
Cho, with me.
River Medical Plaza, Stockton CA
How did you know it was Red John?
Towlen Morning was the family doctor
for Janet and Carter Peak.
The Peaks were Red John's
third and fourth victims.
Carter presumed to be the fourth.
They never found his body.
That was 9 years ago.
- Why attack the CBI today?
- It's puzzling.
I'm Red John, why do I kill Morning
and Hicks and attack Bosco's team?
Carter and Janet Peak.
Nine years ago.
Carter and Janet Peak. Nine.
Nine years ago,
I'm a lot less experienced.
Something went wrong
with Carter and Janet Peak, a mistake.
Now he fixed it,
but somehow it's come undone.
Hicks came to see the doctor
for a reason.
- He was checking something out.
- And Red John killed him for it,
killed them all.
Except for Bosco, I mean.
Bosco had a lead
in the Red John case.
Cho, go inside. Check the doctor's files
for Carter and Janet Peak...
X-rays, labs, everything.
Why did Bosco
want the medical records?
What did he know?
He's in I.C.U.
in a medically induced coma.
- He's not gonna tell us anything.
- I know.
The case files will.
Van Pelt, have B.F.S.
search Bosco's office
for any new evidence or notes
in the Red John file.
You and Rigsby
start working the secretary, Rebecca.
Hey, boss.
Nothing from Rebecca.
The B.F.S. techs are still taking apart
Bosco's office, but so far...
Is Jane back?
- I haven't seen him.
- Find him, would you?
Special agents
Nick Martinez and Mark Dyson
died at the scene here.
And special agent Marlon Hicks
was found dead
at a secondary crime scene.
Special agent Samuel Bosco
remains in critical condition.
We are devoting every resource
to this investigation, and I promise...
I promise the agents' families,
we will not rest
until we bring the perpetrator
to justice.
Special agent Minelli,
our condolences.
Would you describe your feelings
at this terrible time?
Wow, Meredith. That...
you media guys, that's just...
You know, for eight years,
I've put up
with the idiotic questions of the media,
and I've never said squat.
But today...
i must tell you, Meredith,
you've really set a new standard
in horse's assery.
You people have no concept
of what we do.
We go into dark,
horrible places, alone
and afraid,
and we do it with no money,
broken-down vehicles with...
computers that have more
viruses than a $10 whore.
How?
Good people.
I lost three good people today,
and a fourth
who's in critical condition,
and you ask me how i'm feeling?
I'm feeling sad...
You...
moron.
Any other questions?
Good day to you.
Elizabeth, carry on.
Horse's assery.
Nice.
I shouldn't have.
- You told them the truth.
- I did.
It felt good.
Stick with us, boss.
We need you.
I gotta run. You got this?
Evening, gentlemen.
- You are?
- I'm sorry.
I'm a friend of his.
How's he doing?
He's not good.
The next two days
should tell us a lot.
He was in such pain.
- Is he getting enough morphine?
- He should be.
Looks good.
Call me if you need anything.
Will do. Thanks, doc.
What are you doing?
Unplugging his morphine.
I'd ask a doctor to do it,
i think i know what they'd say.
Are you crazy?
That's exactly what they'd say.
They wouldn't understand
the moral imperative.
Bosco is the only person
that can tell us
what he found on Red John.
Now he may die.
We need to wake him up and have him
tell us everything he knows,
while he still can.
- You can't do that.
- Why not?
Morphine doesn't make him any better.
It just stops the pain.
Yes, that's what it does.
Pain is nothing.
Pain means he's still alive.
We need him now, Lisbon,
now.
He's useless to us when he's dead.
- Shut up. He's gonna live.
- Maybe
and maybe not.
God, you're a cold bastard.
You need to think logically.
He would want us to do this.
How could you know what he would want?
You don't even know him.
But you do. If he had
to suffer pain to stop Red John,
he would do that.
And you know that.
- You know that.
- What's all the commotion?
What the...
did you touch that machine?
Good people.
I've lost three
good people today...
Is Lisbon with you?
What's going on?
We got a hit
on Bosco's cell phone records.
Before the attack,
Bosco called a cop in Cloverville,
not far from Stockton.
The cop told me when they tore down
an old strip mall last week,
- They found a body in the foundation.
- A body?
The cop who posted the bulletin
said he got a call from Bosco,
- saying he'd go and check it out.
- What body?
This one.
Cloverville P.D.
E-mailed a copy of the x-rays.
John Doe, 30s.
See here?
His head was almost cut off.
Vicious.
Then there's this.
What's that?
- His leg.
- He's missing a leg?
The Coroner told
it was not part of the attack.
A much earlier amputation,
he said. Distinctive.
The files we got from
Dr. Morning's office...
This matches an X-ray
we found there.
Carter Peak.
Carter Peak retired army,
lost his right leg
during the first gulf war.
They found
the missing Red John victim.
Better still.
This is Red John's mistake.
This is it.
He made a mistake, and this is it.
Killing Carter Peak
wasn't Red John's M.O.
He was a man
who was killed with his wife.
His body was removed from the scene.
Is unlike any of Red John's
14 other murders.
Maybe Carter returned unexpectedly.
Maybe there was a struggle.
So Peak's body resurfaces.
Red John hears about it somehow,
and it upsets him.
A, how does he hear about the body?
Off the bulletin, i guess.
It was statewide.
And B, why does it upset him?
There's evidence on Carter Peak's body.
He tried to make it disappear.
Damning evidence, like DNA.
Let's go to Cloverville.
The cement matrix
preserved the body remarkably well.
We were able to run
a full DNA crime kit.
Hair, skin,
under the fingernails, ect...
We need someone on this place 24/7
until we can move the body
to Sacramento.
My bad.
That's weird.
Yeah, it is.
Where's the body, doc?
Let me check the log here.
You guys gotta get your signals
straightened up in Sacramento.
CBI already picked up the body
night before last.
CBI did?
Yeah, night shift
logged it right here.
California Bureau of Investigation,
an agent Rojo.
The body, samples,
everything we had, it looks like.
See for yourself.
Arrived at 2:15 a.m.
with meat wagon.
The night before the attack.
I can get you photos, though.
We usually keep a set.
But the crime scene kit,
the DNA samples. What about it?
I'm telling ya,
it should've all gone with your guy.
- That's procedure.
- He wasn't him.
- Red John?
- Call in your night shift person.
It's important that we get an idea
of what this, agent Rojo looks like.
- You wanted to see me, boss?
- Sit down, please.
Bosco's doing better.
I talked to his doctor.
That's good.
You okay, boss?
Is this about before,
the press conference?
I have something to tell you,
Something important.
What is it?
Sorry to interrupt,
but i've been going through
the security footage, trying to ID.
Everyone going in and out.
This is timecoded for this morning,
right before the attack.
According
to employee support services,
that's Amblyn Demott,
an analyst on four.
So what?
Demott went on maternity
leave last month.
She had her baby yesterday.
There's no way she could be where
that camera says she was.
Someone switched the footage.
We can't trust
anything on any camera.
You transferred the body
to the custody of a CBI agent?
Describe this agent.
Dark hair, not that tall,
kinda dumpy,
olive-complected,
- wore these heels that clicked...
- A woman?
Wore a thing,
- whatsit, in her hair.
- A barrette.
Right. Barrette.
Hey, sweetie.
Have a nice day.
Hello, Barney. How you doing?
Weren't you heading to Cloverville?
As soon as i brief Jane.
Samuel Bosco, Jr.
Getting soft.
Screw you, Martinez.
Look what i have.
You're the best.
Did you get the coffee?
- You okay?
- A-okay, boss.
Red John says hi.
Hey.
Don't move. Drop your gun.
Bitch.
You bitch.
Don't move
Don't breathe
and don't you smiled me.
What the hell's
with all the balloons?
What are you doing here?
Get her outta here.
How long are they sit there?
What's your favorite kind of music?
Mr. Jane,
please.
I know your games.
You don't care
what type of music i like.
I'm just making conversation,
getting to know you.
You want to know how i could do
such terrible things for Red John.
I know that stuff...
unhappy childhood,
sexually abused by a close relative,
cutting or some other self-abuse,
self-medicating, self-loathing.
Everyone you ever met
made you feel ashamed,
ashamed of that
ugly
darkness
festering inside you.
But he didn't.
He made you strong.
He made you feel proud of that darkness.
Yes, he did.
He gave your life
purpose and meaning
and...
love.
You're very much like him,.
The way you look at people
and see right through them.
That is just spooky.
I want you to think of this tonight
before you go to sleep.
You are nothing to him
but a useful object.
He is not a good man.
You are so wrong.
He is a very good man.
He's on a mission...
of love and enlightenment.
He tortures and kills women.
Don't you see?
Without death,
there's no life.
Without darkness, there's no light.
- Look at you.
- Me?
Well, until your
wife and your daughter were killed,
you were blind, weren't you?
You were living an illusion.
Red John opened your eyes.
And now you see the world
for what it truly is.
How did you first meet him?
I'm not telling you anything
about him.
You will.
You'll wake up one day,
horrified of what you've done,
- and you will tell me everything.
- No, never.
I love Red John.
And he loves me,
i will never betray that trust.
One day.
But i will tell you
that i like all kinds of music.
Especially country.
And i have a cat named rex.
And i collect porcelain frogs.
Don't ask me why.
It's just a quirk, really.
The psychologist
want to talk to you next.
He'll have a field day with that.
I'm as sane
and as healthy as can be.
- I really am.
- I know.
Have one question before you go.
After you took Carter Peak's body
and all the DNA samples...
Why did Red John
have you attack Bosco's team?
There was really no need.
The evidence was destroyed.
You know why.
You don't?
Red John thought you'd understand.
I got rid of Bosco and his team
so that you could have the case back
Red John misses you.
It's what you wanted, too.
Isn't it?
We're done here.
Interesting talking to you, Rebecca.
Likewise.
I guess i'll see you around.
Officer needs assistance.
She's down. She's down.
Don't touch her!
He poisoned her.
Mandy... you get ahold of her?
All the flights out
of Boston were delayed.
She's in the air now.
She'll be here soon.
It's all right.
You're gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Don't lie to me.
I can tell when you're lying.
You are.
Look, you will be...
you'll be okay.
I'm a cop.
You're a bad liar.
Your eyes give you away every time.
Honest eyes.
Tell me the truth.
You lost a lot of blood.
The doctors don't think
you're gonna make it.
I'm gonna say it, then.
The doctors better be right.
I love you, Teresa.
I love you, too.
No. I mean, i love you.
I know what you mean.
It had to be said.
Is Jane here?
For the record,
i'm very pissed off about this.
Can't blame you.
We don't have time to be nice.
Red John makes mistakes.
This proves it.
- You will catch him.
- Yes, i will.
Do me a favor.
When you catch him,
don't arrest him.
Kill the son of a bitch.
That's the plan.
Good.
Listen...
UNE SEMAINE PLUS TARD
- You weren't at the funeral.
- I was there.
I stayed in the back.
You're quitting?
I tried to tell you before.
Anyway, i prefer "retiring."
Full pension.
I got my 20 and then some.
Okay, then.
We'll stay here and catch the bad guys
while you go fishing.
In my eight years as SAC,
i've lost four agents...
all of them this week.
You should have quit last week.
It's too late now.
It's time.
You take care of your people.
They're good kids.
Keep an eye on Jane.
If he screws up too bad,
shoot him.
There's not a court in the land
that would convict you.
Out Minelli.
I'm sorry.
You and Bosco,
at the hospital...
What'd he say?
He told me to look after you.
That's all?
He said that if i didn't look after you,
he'd come back and haunt me.
Total nonsense, of course,
it wasn't the right time
to correct him.
Bosco's favorite.
Pint of scotch, left of the fridge,
top shelf, behind the ramen.
To Sam Bosco.
A damn fine agent.
It was a nice service.
Nice music.
- Not a fan of the bagpipes.
- Really?
I love 'em.
They're so...
Lonely.
It was a nice service.