MENTALIST
/'men-t3-list/ noun
Someone who uses mental
Acuity,hypnosis and/or suggestion.
A master manipulator of
Thoughts and behavior.
Morning,captain. Agent
lisbon. Jane,consulnt.
What do we have here?
thanks for stepping in.
Homicide unit owes you one.
- Jane. You're that psychic fella.
- Right.
Me? I don't buy into that e.S.P. Crap.
- No offense.
- None taken.
Here we have ivor rassmussen,age 34,address
river park no sign of the murder weapon.
Store ri was onhe scene pretty fast.
We were ableo detain everybody
who was in the section at the time.
We're holding them over in
the furniture department.
So,carnac,what does ivor say?
He tell you who done it?
leather pants,musky cologne,phallic
jewelry. A ladies' man.
Went after high-end cougars
with moderate success.
Casual cocaine user.
Plays guitar--not well.
Works in the noncreative
end of a creive business.
Advertising,maybe. Nothing
worth killing anyone over anyway.
So hdied r romantic reasons.
Where are those suspects you mentione
- the witnesses?
- Whatever.
Ta it down a notch. Take
it down three notches.
Okay. Under contro we'll get
this done quic and be on our way.
Hello. We're from the cbi.
May well be that one
of you is the murderer.
If that's so,i'm gonna find out who.
These two are innocent. Th can go.
Uh,stick around. We're
gonna need atatement.
Neil.
What's the worst mistake
you've ever made? Quick.
- Uhfirst marriage.
- Good answer. Why so nervous?
I'm not.
I just--i...
You. Youname?
- Candice.
- Caice. That name.
Here. Thank you.
It's okay. I'm a consultant.
Candice,take my advice. Forgive your
mother.Maybe the headaches will s
- i love my mother.
- Oh,i'm wrong. Ignoreadvice.
You. Your name.
- Reed.
- Excuse me.
- This is a joke,right?
- A joke?
A man has been kled . Is that
funny to you? Are you amused?
- No,but--
- then sit.
Reed,quk question. Green
lantern versus thor--
- who wins?
- Thor.
Oh,yeah. Why'd you kill rassmussen?
- I didn't.
- All right.
Now,you,miss grumpy and
entitled,what's your story?
My name is mandy shultz.And
i'll havyou know that my--
let me guess. Your husband
is a very important person.
He is,as it happens.
John's on the modesto city council.
And this is totally
unprofessional and disrespectful.
I'll have my husband take
thp with your superiors.
Mandy,mandy,mandy. The diet
pills are messing with your mind.
This is sacramento,the big city.
Your husband means nothing here.
Okay,that's enough. Agent lisbon?
- Give him another moment.
- Don't need a moment. Ca is all but closed.
- Mandy here is gonna lead us right to the murder weapon.
- What?
Take my hands. I need physical
contact to read your mind.
- You're nuts.
- Ove it.
If i'm wrong,if we can't find the
murder weapon,then i look like an idiot.
Yes,you will.
- What are you--
- don't speak.
The murder weapon.
This is crazy. I had
no idea that was there.
How could u direct us right to
it if you didn't put it there?
I didn't. I-i don't know.
But i-i didn't kill
that man. I-i didn't!
- She's right. She has nothing to do with the murder.
- What?
I just used her as a decoy to lull the real
killer into giving me clean directional cues.
Oh,come on. What are
you talking about now?
Whatever way he didn't wants
to go is the way that we went.
- The real killer.
- Yeah,you wanna guess who it is?
Come on,jane.
Neil.
Excusee. No,i--it wasn't.
I-i dot even know thatan.
Oh,is that rit?
I'm guessing that he was having
an affair withour current wife.
You found out and you
forgave her like a sucker.
He saw you here,probably smirked and said
something very clever,made you feel... Small.
Humiliated you!
- Nice work.
- What? Case is closed,isn't it?
Put it down!
I sa drop it now!
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
The Mentalist
Season02 Episode01 Redemption
A dead suspect,quarter-million
dollars worth of damages,
formal complais of
misconduct from the s.P.D.
And the modesto cityouncil.
Those damages wereay padded.
All due respect,virgil,i
was trying to close the case.
It was my feeling that red
john should be our priority,
- given the dozen frh
leads-- - Stop!stop.
That's the nub of the
problem righthere--red john.
Ever since the tanner incident,you've
been runnin' way too hot.
I fear a terminal screw up coming.
That's not gonna happen. I can hand him.
Can you?
Maybe since he saved your
life,you're going easy on him.
Maybe you feel compelled
cut him somslack.
No,sir. Ths absolutely not the case.
Hey,sam,get in here.
- Lisbon.
- Bosco.
Agent bosco and his unit are
taking over the red john case.
What? No,no,no.
You have always been too close to the
case,and now both of you are way o close.
We need to make a change.
- Can we talk about this?
- No.
You've worked for agent bosco.
You ow that heill do the job right.
You ed to let my team
finish what they started.
Teresa,no offense,but you guys aren't
even close to catching this guy.
Fresh set of eye gotta be aogd idea.
What do you know about the case?
Not much. He's a serl killer.
15 victims,including
your wife and child.
I can imagine your pain.
Maybe that pain is
clouding your judgment.
And me,sam? What's clouding my judgment?
Good question. You tell .
What happened?
We're off red john.
- What?
- Forever?
- Rrwill we get reprimanded?
- Who gets it instead?
Quiet.
Look,this is my fault,but it's
a wake-upall for all of us.
We've grown slack and unprofessional.
We neeto earn back e
trust thatewve lost.
From now on,we work 100% straight.
No more shortcuts.No
more ga--
what are you doing?
You're leaving?
Well,frankly,if i can't use this job to
seek some kind of personal revenge,thenuh,
there's not a whole lot here for me.
But i-i... I don'make anything better.
I can't brindead people back
to life. What good do we do?
We drive around california
visitingappy people.
We're fighng evil and injustice.
And how's that going?
Any progress lately?
We put bad guys away where ey
can't hurt people. That's gd enough.
I was doing more good as a psychic.
I was givingeople hope,at least.
- False hope,but hope anyway.
- Van pelt.
You're right. Best you leave.
That way you can go back to bei a full-time fraud
and we can continue our useless jobs in peace.
- Well,that's actually not what i said.
- Yes,it was.
- We're up. Twenty palms.
- Let's go. Yocome,too,an pt.
We'll take two vehicles
in case need to split up.
I'll see you when you get there.
Boss,disrespect,but i ink we need jane.
'Ll manage.Maybe we
don't cse as many cases,
but the ones we do close will
be closed right,by prossionals.
Vapelt,it's not a jet plane.
Okay,okay,okay.
S-sorry.
Oh,i'm t gonna leave you in the lurch.
I'll do one more case.
Do up your seat belt.
*****
Van pelt,you come with me.
You guys talk to the first
responders,see what they got.
Hey,the apartment's upstairs.
We have a female caucasian,late 3.
ran license down alrdy. It a
fake. We're calling her jane doe.
Who found the body?
The building manager noticed
her door was open overnight.
Last one down to the left.
Thank you.
What's your take?
Hit with a stun gun en
suffocated with the cushion.
And they were looking
for something,obviously.
Did they find it,grace?
It's impossible to tell.
Well,it seems they look
everywhere possible. Yes?
Yeah.
So we can assume that they
didn't find it,whatever it is.
How so?
Well,let's say there's a
ndred places to look r a thing.
How likely is it that you will
find it in the hundred pla you look?
- Not very likely,right?
- What else you got?
No drug paraphernali no condoms or
other items suggesting prostitution.
So... Maybe a personal
crime? A husband or lover?
Bravo,grace.
Wrong,i expec but very
welreasoned nonetheless.
Thank you,all. Appreciate it.
Thing off the car,but we'll
have the lab boys take a look.
It's still registered to the previous
owner,sold it for cash six months ago.
So basically we know nothing
about her. Nice start.
She's a law-iding middle-class
housewife that did something bad,
something she feels
terriblyuilty about--
guilty enough to make
her run away and hide.
That's evidence. Yoknow the drill.
You put "bullfrogs win high schbasketball
trophy" into a search engine,
we will find jane doe's home.
- Can i take a look at that?
- Sure.
It's a working truck. Dad must be
in construct something like that.
Bayshore courier,ril 2006.
"county finals--la bulrogs
dominate inju-plagueders.
If they list the players,cross-check
the surnames with the other arcles
from the same newspaper in the last
year using the word disappearae."
" if we leave now,we can be i
bayshore in a couplef hours."
oh,we need a ttle more than
lady bullfrogs to go on.
"bayshore courier" of june this year.
Headline is "pice no
closer to dunninger."
"since her disappearance last month,bayshore
p.D.Have been unable to locate"
"43-year-old monica dunninger,the secretary
accused of stealing nearly $1 million"
from her employers,the
jaffe printing group."
Okay. Bayshore it is then.
So the killer must've been
looking for the million bucks.
If she had a million bucks,why
would she live in a dump like this?
Before we get on the freeway,it'd be good to
take a little drive around the neighborhood,
be good to find anmpty house for sale.
Why would that bgood?
I'm thinking of moving here.
No secrets,jane. No lies. No
tricks. No surprises. The truth.
Since when is that thrule?
Since i said so.
- Else what?
- You're off the unit.
That's not leve. This
is my last case,remember?
Thonly reason i'm still here is 'cause i'm
worried about how you guys would cope withoume.
Oh,really? So wre lost
without you,are we?
Wellyeah. Let's be honest here.
Let's go.
Wait. This...
What'd you say to em?
Nothing,really. Totaerreaction. Yeah.
We need to find a house for sale.
Ok.
Ah,there's a sign.
Perfect.
****
You gonna tell me what that's about?
- Wouldn't you rather it be a surprise?
- No.
Oh,look. Look,look,strawberries.
****
Strawberries?
See? How good is that?
Gd. Cho,rigsby,start
canvassing the neighbors.
Van pelt,come with me.
Uh,i... Lisbon,uh...
I'm sorry for what sayou before.
Can i please connue working with you?
I thought you were quitting.
You know i dn't mean that.
So the job is worthwhile,is it?
Eh,it's not that. I mean,it's
not that at all. It's just...
I have nothing else to do.
No jokes. From now on,there
have to be boundaries.
Agreed.
I need to know that you can do your work and be
effective withoucreating a mess th i have to clean up.
No mess,i swear.
On that basi you can
remain with the unit.
Thank u.
Here.
So how did she die?
It s a hocide,but she didn't suffer.
We don't have any suspects yet.
Where was she?
She was ling alone in a small
apartment in twenty palms.
I thought she'd be living
it up inexico or somepla.
- She was
always-- - stop it.
I need to lie down.
Okay,champ,let's roll.
- I'm making some tea. Would you like a cup?
- Noank you.
Oh,oh,i-i'd love a cup. Thanks.
Ansel,uh,had cancer. He's
totally better now but still weak.
- It's in remission?
- Gone.
100%. We were blessed. Even
the doctors were amazed.
Oh,thank you. Tell mabouyour mother.
Sure. I'll tell you.
Ng all that money and running off--
that was just the icing on the cake.
When ansel got cancer,her wa coping--
painkillers and a sleazebag lover.
That's mom.
Did u know her lover's name?
Bodhi andros.
How fou out?
Ansel goes to meet his mom
at her yogarobics class.
He finds her banging
the teaer in his office.
Can you imine?
- Then wt happened?
- She did her dance.
She's so ashamed,she's so
sorry,she's changed. Whatever.
And d was halfway to fgiving her.
He c't help it. He loves her.
But yodon' love her?
She... Never had time for me. So.
I cod always see through
her chm. You know?
To the selfish
cow beneath--
kessie!Don't talk that way. E loved you.
Look,she's dead. Show some respect.
She was a beautiful soul,full
of joy an-and big dreams.
And reality just kinda beat h down.
But here's the thing. It was only
because the robbery was in the news that
the doctors at cedars of zion heard
about ansel anreached out to help us.
They took him on for free
and they sav his life--
saved his life when everybody
id there was no hope.
You know,god works inysterious ways.
Well,you kn,god doesn't
necessarily,uh,answer--
- thank you very much for you time.
- Yeah. Thank you.
Very nice tea.
Oh,uh,i almost fort. Do e eher
of you know a miles thorsen?
- Uh,no,i don't thso.
- No.
You sure?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
All righ.
ansel.Hey,ans!
- You know miles thorsen?
- No.
Okay. Bye.
Thank you.
Who's miles thorn?
- No o in particular.
- This is what i'm talking about.
Nome,too. Y-you want
no fuss,no mess,right?
I am casting a wide,inble ne the killer won't
even know he's in it until it's too late.
- Miles thsen is an invisible net?
- Yes,he is.
We got an address on bodhi andros.
Cho,rigsby,go and check him out.
Van pelt,get on the money trail.
Somebody's got tt $1 million.
Start with the dad and the daughter.
See if either of them's been
spending money they shouldn't have.
They looked clean me.
Oh,did they? Okay,eat.Just let them be .
i don't... I'll check 'em out.
Okay,come on.Let's get
back to sacramento,grump
at's the hurry?
I have a meeting with bosco.
Good luck.
Great class,gs.
Hey,and let's use that cus we
found throughout the week,okay?
Namaste. Namaste. Okay,thank you.
- I'm looking for bodhi andros.
- Oh,crap!
Yeah,his office is
upstairs,to the right.
Thank you.
- Rememb that time you saidou'd been in juvie?
- Yep.
Yonever said what you
got sent there for.
It'sang stuff.
You were in a gang? What
was the name of the gang?
Avon park playboys.
- Avon park playboys?
- I didn't choose the name.
And,uh,what ki of stuff
did the playboys do?
- Nothing good.
- Like what?
Nothing you need to know about.
Mm,fair enough. Your call.
See,i don't think partners
shld have secrets,but your call.
Likeon't have any secrets.
- What's the supposed to mean?
- U know what i me.
Hey,you in there. Police.
Cbi. Very slowly,stand up.
I'm unarmed,man. I have no weapons.
Well,that's great.
So come out slowly with your hands on
your head,and i won't hurt you. Promise.
Okay,i'm coming out now. Don't shoot.
Morning,sir. You bodhi andros?
- Yes,i am.
- Turn around.
Sorry i'm late. Bad traffic.
- What are you having?
Well,i'llave a bottle of water,nks.
A dog with kraut,bottle of water.
Thank you.
Well,i'm not gonna lie. I'm
not happy i'm off the red case.
You might be right.
Fresset of eye may be what's needed.
Now here's the thing,sam,if i may.
I know this case.
I can be a vy good resource for you.
If we could just come to
some kind of understanding...
- You wante to,uh,keep you up toate on the case?
- Yeah,sure.
Tell you about fsh leads,etcetera.
Yeah,let's just keep an
open line ocommunication.
Od?
Wife has me on a diet.
This is like committin' adultery here.
Let me communicate this to you.
You're a party entertainer,a clown.
Fresh leads?
I wouldn't tell you where the
bathroom is if your ass was on fire.
Do we have a good understanding now?
I untand you. It may take you
some time to understand me.
You're filled with equal parts
self-loathing and self-love.
You're addicted to control.
You're terrified of confinement.
who's my favorite beatle?
Your wife wanted you to
quit the psychic trade.
She begged you to stop,but
you were making too much money.
You were havin' too much fun.
You can still hear her eading with you.
How am i doin'?
You read the interviews in my caseile.
You can read very impressive.
Looktrick,i'm sorry to
be so blunt with you.
Really?
You're not a detective. You're a victim.
****
- You never sa. How was your meet with bosco?
- What? I can't hear you!
- I said,how did it go wi bosco?
- I can't...
How did it go with bco?
Good. It was,uh,itas very good.
We had a frank exchange of views.
- So he's gonna keep us in the loop?
- No.
- No?
- Wouldn direct me to the bathroom if my ass s on fire.
Think that's funny?
So that'mrs. Jaffe er there.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- what are you gonna do?
- Nothing.
Nothing?
If you sown byhe riverbank
and wait long enough,
you will see the bies
of your enemies float by.
Shall we?
Agent lisbon,is it?
I'm rhonda jaffe,company chairwoman.
- Th is my colleague mr. Jane.
- Hello.
Thank you so much for taki
the time to talk to us.
Oh,not at all. And you wanted to meet
with my finance direcr greg humphrey?
- Yes,ma'am.
- All rit. Well,let's speak in my office.
Did u know monica dunninger?
Oh,yeah. I know everyone on staff.
So sad. The whole thing is
just so sad. The poor woman.
More troubled than conniving,i'm sure.
And you know,it's not the money.
It's more the loss of trust.
This is very,very mh a family firm.
And my father always used to say,jaffprinting
is aboulues,not about machinery.
Do you knomiles thorsen?
Miles thsen? No.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- Seriously,stop it.
- Relax.
I saved her life. She resents me.
Oh,really?
Jill?
Jill? Jill,where has greg humphre
gone to? He's supposed to be in here.
Hello?
Humble apologies.
Small crisis on the
inventory desk. Solved.
Uh,greg humphrey. Good to meet you.
Patrick jane.
We're investigating the
murder of monica nninger.
Yes. Terrible. Horrible.
You were her direct
supervisor,ishat right?
I know wt you're gonna say,and ye
yes,it was my fault that shetole from us.
Mea culpa. I-i should've known.
Greg is like family
ticall we all make mistakes
we live,we learn,we move on.
Uh,can you explaito us w
she did ? In layman's terms?
Been there,done that with the top
men from the fbi financial unit.
Do we really need to ger it again?
- Yes.
- No problem.
Ank you.
What exactly was her position he?
Assistant office manager.
She kept the petty ca accounts.
Coffee and doughnut monitor essentially.
This was her office.
How did she manage to
steal so much money?
When the accounting and
finance systems were integrated,
nobody thought to firewall
the tty cash accounts.
Monica acquired user access to the
transactional sites and created a false vendor.
I didn't think s had the brains,to be .
We don't know exactly how she did it
because she frd her hard drive and
e took her accountsook with her.
Are we about to look at
a ole bunch of numbers?
Probably.
- All right. I'll wait in the car.
- Go.
Do you know a man named miles thorsen?
- No.
- You sure? Think about it.
- I'm sure. Who is he?
- Never mind.
Please continue.
Would you excuse me?
Ss,i think i found something.
The victim's daughter,ssie dunninger--
shhandles the family money,pays the bills.
Five months ago,she stopped paying the
rent by standing order,switched to cash.
Me thing with the utity
bills. Paid in cash.
Nice work. A andalto her. She doesn't
have a good answer,bring her in.
Will do,boss. Yes!
Y did you hiderom us,bodhi?
Fear,man. Fear.
I've been frightened for
my life er since i heard.
- Why?
- Who killed her?
Either it was her goober hnd finally
snapped,ich puts me next in line,
or it's whoever she went into business
with,and maybe they think i know too much.
She was in business with someone?
Just before she disappeared,she
came by to see me,
told me she made a business deal with
someone that would make everything all right.
- A business deal? Were those the words she used?
- Yep.
She was starting a new day in
her life and wanted to make amends
and apogize for being such a
pain in theutt,which she was.
How so?
She was way too deep into her fily
and to her kids and all that crap.
Loved those kids.
Why do i want to talk to her about
her sick boy? Like i can help?
- You'reot a doctor.
- Exactly.
When we were caught
by that kid,she just...
Went to pieces,you know?
And i'm like,don't get
so down on yourself.
You gotta love u en if
you're a total screw up,right?
The greatest. Love... Of all.
Whitney was right,as usual.
Ight.
Y know a man named les thorsen?
- No. Who's he?
- I don't know.
is that enough sugar?
Ye thank you.
So,kessie,tell me abouthe money.
About a month after
shran off,mom called me,
said she wanted to help out,wanted
to know how ansel was doing.
She loves us so much,blah,blah,blah.
I told her to go to hell,and i hung up.
2 days later,i got a letter
with $5,000 in cash inside.
Any message?
Julove,mom." thth was it.
What was i supposed to
do,give it to the police?
Actually,yes.
Well,i didn't. We
really needed the money.
- Did you ever tell your dad about the mo .
- No.
How often did shsend you money?
$5,000 every month.
- Did you ever write back to her?
- No.
- I like h for this.
- How so?
She desp mom.
Mom's got $1 million stolen dolla,gets
in contact secretly. Do t eath.
- Maybe.
- No? What's your take?
I'd be guessing. Could be anybody.
Not anybody. Youidn't
do it. I didn't do it.
You're distracted. You're
thinking about bosco and red john.
Focus on the job at hand.
You're glad bosco has the
red john case,aren't you?
Bosco is good agent.
He's as gothey come.
It might not be such a bad thing that we're
off t case for a while. We got too ose.
- Is that what your shrink tells u?
- Everybody tells me that.
But your shrink didtell
you that,didn't he?
Okay,may--maybe you're right.
Maybe--maybe that's the truth.
Maybe we did get a little
too close. I'm not so sure.
- But i'll think about it.
- Liar.
I've got a deposition.
See that box ever there? It's got
mica dunninger's possessionin it.
- Go through it,see what you can see.
- Yes,ma'am.
Uh,whwants to come with me out
to twenty lms to catch the killer?
Did lisbon okay is?
Of course.
- What is this place?
- Guess.
- Mis thorsen's house.
- Exactly.
Who's miles thorsen?
- I haveo idea.
- ****
Isn't that your number?
Uh,yeah,that's my number. That's in
case the killer gets here before us.
That way,he'll call us.
Wh's that over there?
- Hey,we have no warrant.
- Don't you hear someone yelling in there?
- No.
- I heard something.
There's no yelling. I have perfect hng.
I could ear i heard someone.
Okay,so what are we doing here?
Erybody involved is
wondering who miles thorsen .
The killer will be doub
curious. Triply,even.
Maybe the mysterious miles thorse has what
the killer is looking for,what heidn't find.
When they look him up,ty'll learn there's a
miles thorsen who lives rind the rner from monica.
- Hey,resto.
- This is extly the kind ostuff the boss was tking about.
She didn't okay this at all,did she?
So shoot me.
"the fax machine revolution--the
little box that'sing our world."
why would monica dunninger
be reading this book?
You,cho,shouldn't
enable this kind of crap.
We're not doing anything
wrong. What's the problem?
Uh,burglary,espassing,willful
damage to property.
- Yeah,door was open.
- Uh,no,it wasn't.
- Of course.
- What?
Rigsby,you' right. You shouldn't
be here. Let us take this.
- You go find the nearest library.
- Why?
Your punishmfor being a wuss
is i'm not gonna tell ya.
- Oh,come on.
- Nope,i'm not gonna tell you.
Fine. Fine. Whatever.
Call when you're there.
So what's the gag?
Oh,there's no gag. I solved the case.
I thought you already dithat. I
thought that's why we're waiting here.
Nope. This is,uh...
Well... Thiss more of
a fishing expedition.
You know,maybe we get a bite. Maybe
we don't. That's the fun of it.
We just sit back,relax,dangle
our feet in the water.
This guy predicted th by the year 2000,
every american household
will have a fax machine.
Can u believe that?
I had a fax mach you?
Yeah.
Nostradamus of officequipment.
See,this is why i dot like fishing.
- E not goa catch ything.
- We have some very tasty bait.I'm ry confide
did you consider that the
killer found the money alrey?
I don't think it was money theyere looking
for. I don't think monica ever h it.
Then wt did she have then?
And who has the money?
Great bone original mid century
detail. Great new copper piping.
Hello. Did you have
a fax machine in 2000?
No cause for alarm,sir. We're
law enforcement officers. Cbi.
Kimball... Cho. Okay.
What are you doing
here,kimball? Is there a problem?
It's an ongoing investigation,sir.
Can give out any details.
Grisly homide,though.
N't we take a look at that
duplexn royston? Shall we?
That's a good call.
- Damn it.
- Relax.
He got my name.
Well,you spoke the truth. We
are an ongoing investigation.
Yeah,but we're supped to
be working 100% straight.
This isot that.
I'm--i'm sorry.
Wr-wrong address.
Rhonda! Come back.
I'm here out of curiosity,that's all.
Well,of course.
I've got nothing else
to say without my lawyer.
U don't need to say anything.
I knew it was you from the start.
Thanksor sring.
Well,when i say i-i knew it
was her,i-i mean,i-i guessed,
i subconsciously thought it was her
when i saw a photo of her holding
large check outside cedars of zion.
It was you that stole the $1
million from your own compan
why would i do that?
Well,degenerate gambling would be
my gu but whatever youproblem is,
when threatened with exposure,you
made a deal with poor monica.
If she'd take the blame and disappea
you'd get ansel into the best
cancer program in california
and pay her a monthly wage to stay gone.
That's absurd.
But then ansel got cured,and there's way
monica was gonna stay gone,not much longe
then you had to silence her.
That's pure fiction.
Yohave no proof at all.
We--we have
proof. Wait.
Yeah,we got--there
it is. Yep.
This is gonna be good.
Yep,i'm here. I know,i know.
The fax machine revolution is a library
book,and monica dunning swapped it.
Hold on. I'm checking it. All right.
Got it. Hold up.
Looks like an accountsook.
There's a dvd in it.
This is just to say that...
In case something happen to me,
that i swear on the bible
that everyg in the account book theruth.
I know that i've prettmuch lost
your love and respect for good.
But i hope that this dl at i've
made will help ansel get better
and will make up for some
of the hurt that i've caused.
I love you all so much,
especially you,keie,even
though you ink i don't.
I'm st so soy for this
mess that i've made.
Please forgive me. Goodye.
The book spells out the deal.
Monica took the fall for her boss so that
ansel would have the best possible treatment.
Nice work.
Sam bosco here. Cbi major
crimes program. Question.
How do i go about changing
my iuse access passcode?
I gostrong reasoto believe
it's been compmised.
Yeah,great. Sure. Sure,i can hold.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚