Welcome to the 23rd annual
westing resort best chef challenge.
I'm Bertram Duesterberg, your host.
Our competing chefs today are...
First,
from restaurant 182
in Sonoma,
The youngest winner ever
of the Schilling Palm de cuisine,
Chef Hannah Diaz.
From San Francisco, where they host
the acclaimed
public radio show Two top,
Chefs Arliss and Julia St. Germain.
Do you want the mousse?
Jeff?
Trained in Paris,
he is executive chef
at La Petite Maison,
Chef Adrien Ludo!
Where's my chives?
Let's go, people!
And first up
before our judges today...
Okay, let's move!
Come on, go, go!
Hurry up.
Jeffrey Barge.
Thank you.
My...
My first, dish
today...
is...
Is there a doctor in house, please?
Somebody call 9-1-1!
Jeffrey!
Somebody!
Say something!
Can you hear me?
- Anything from the deputy coroner?
- He can't tell us anything yet.
Tell him we need to know.
If this guy died of natural causes,
we're going home.
- Why so grumpy?
- I'm not.
Why are we here?
We don't know if it's a murder.
One of the chefs called her daddy
who's a state senator,
who called the AG,
who called the assistant AG,
who called me. So we're here.
I hate politics.
This might go quick.
Victim had a fistfight
- with the event organizer.
- Happy days.
I want to be clear.
What happened was sheerest accident.
I did nothing wrong.
Let's just stick to the facts.
You said you had a fight
with the victim. About what?
Truffles.
Truffles?
They're very pricey fungus.
I know what it is.
Jeffrey ordered a bundle
and he paid for them himself.
A few hours before the competition,
He couldn't find them.
He demanded replacements,
which would have cost thousands.
I said no.
He started yelling and then shoving.
- Naturally, I defended myself.
- Very gently, of course.
And then he, fell on his head?
Something like that?
- It's as I said it was an accident.
- We'll see.
Jeffrey sounds like a scrapper.
Quick with his fists?
Not really.
He was a genius.
Genius can be noisy.
But he's never laid hands
on me before.
Genius, really?
- Is he good for it?
- Not sure yet. What's that?
Some hors d'oeuvre
they're handing out.
- Want one?
- I don't eat anything I can't identify.
Excuse me.
Is this the victim's dish?
Pardon.
No genius there. Way too much salt.
Dr. Steiner.
Long time, new threads. Sharp.
The move from Sacramento
has been quite pleasant.
Fine wine, lovely weather,
no Patrick Jane.
Or so I hoped.
Cheeky. Have you checked his mouth?
For a possible head injury?
I don't think so.
Don't be alarmed,
I am going to touch you.
Please, I am in the...
Excuse me.
What made you think to look there?
Bad-tasting food
means bad taste buds.
So much for the head wound.
Duesterberg's off the hook.
He didn't die from a fall.
Let's huddle together,
divvy up the interviews.
What did kill him?
Poison.
2x15
Red Herring
Preliminary test, came back.
Deputy coroner says
that the poison is probably ricin.
Victim either ate it or drank it.
If it was airborne,
people would be dropping.
Ricin's easy enough to make.
Grind up some castor beans.
- Makes for a broad suspects pool.
- They tested the food.
There's no sign of it.
Ricin takes hours to work.
Must something he ingested a while ago.
No need to get your
stomach pumped then, huh?
Funny.
You search the room.
Test any liquid or food
that you find.
The victim's wife just arrived.
I'll handle it.
Talk to the other chefs.
Duesterberg says that the winner
gets 100 grand.
What are you doing?
Trying to get the taste of salty food
out of my mouth.
It's basically,
potential chocolate pudding.
- Very nice. You want some?
- No.
We have to talk
to the victim's wife.
Maybe she'll want some.
Comfort food.
Jeffrey was a dear friend.
We'd known each other for years.
Which is why I had my father
bring you on.
We want to find out who did this.
Interesting that you called us in
before anyone knew It was poison.
You know something
everyone else didn't?
I just knew
that something was wrong.
Now you're all in competition
for a large cash prize.
- Helps that one of you is dead.
- Helps?
We eat together and work together.
We're comrades.
Something to add, miss Diaz?
If we're all such comrades,
Why'd you steal Jeff's sous-chef?
Not true.
- Inquiries were made, that's all.
- Yeah, right.
- How'd you feel about the victim?
- I hated his guts.
Egotistical, manipulative,
Maybe half as good
as he thought he was.
Still make him twice
the chef that you are.
Go get another tatoo.
Bite me, Julia.
The delivery guy says
he left truffles this morning,
then they vanished.
- Who stole them?
- Stealing truffles
- makes one of us a murderer?
- It's a start.
What?
That is exactly the kind of thing
that he would do.
He and Jeffrey
never really got along.
You fat bastard.
Truffles are very expensive.
And you wouldn't throw them out.
- Where does he keep his food?
- Down on the left side of the pantry.
You know who would stop
at nothing to win?
Those two.
Ask them about the book deal
they've been chasing.
A competition prize
would help that, no?
Fine. Arrest me.
But I didn't steal
the truffles, okay?
I rescued them from a terrible fate.
I see.
Did Jeffrey have any problems
that you knew about,
personally or at work?
We were a problem.
We're separated.
- I haven't spoken to him in months.
- What was the breakup about?
What wasn't?
Drinking, mostly.
Occupational disease for chefs.
It's the pressure. It wants a release.
Don't listen to her,
whatever she says.
She hates Jeff.
- And you are?
- Victim's brother.
Cheekbones. Come on,
you can see that.
- Kevin, why don't we talk later?
- I don't think so, Abigail.
My brother was a freakin' genius.
You think anybody in my family
taught him how to cook? Please.
He wanted to be a great chef,
and that's what he was.
Did it all by himself.
And you?
You were perfectly happy
to spend his money, weren't you?
Your brother was a great man.
He elevated himself, didn't he?
But you didn't.
That must've been cause
for some friction, I would think.
Did he leave you anything?
Or did he leave it all
to the hated sister-in-law?
Money, restaurant...
- Why don't you step back?
- That's enough?
- You don't tell me what to do, okay?
- As you can see, drinking
- it runs in the family.
- See, that's how wrong you are.
Jeff was sober.
- He was in the program for 2 weeks.
- Right. I've heard that before.
- It's probably why he called.
- You said you hadn't talked to him.
I didn't talk.
Two weeks sober.
That's impressive.
And what else are you hiding
from us?
He called last night at 12:30.
- I hung up.
- What'd he say?
He said...
He said he was sorry.
Test for ricin.
"Yellow" means positive,
"nothing" means...
nothing.
- This place is quite a mess.
- What do you think the intruder wanted?
Nobody was looking for anything.
Jeffrey did this himself.
You know this, how?
The punched-in mirror
is an act of self-hatred.
Plus, all these drawers are closed.
A thoughtful ransacker
would close maybe one,
- but all of them? No.
- Anyway.
- Room's clear. We're moving on.
- That's nice.
Except you're not. What's up?
Jeffrey was recently sober,
but acting erratically.
Demolishing his room,
picking fistfights, calling his ex-wife
in the middle of the night.
- You know what that's called?
- Relapse?
And an addict on a relapse
will hide his stash.
What better way to poison a drunk
than through his drink?
- Let's check it out.
- Let's.
- There we go.
- Hold the applause.
Bingo.
Poison gin.
A smart way to eliminate a rival.
But not the act of a gentleman.
Is it...
Monsieur Ludo?
You joking?
Take him in.
This is not right.
I've done nothing.
- I've done nothing.
- Hang on.
- She's the one we need to talk to.
- Me?
You should've seen your reaction
when I accused Ludo.
Pure relief.
Come on, please.
At least
attempt denying it.
- I didn't do it.
- She's the one.
Thank you.
Merci.
Why would I want to kill Jeffrey?
Winning a contest would do a lot
for a young woman
trying to prove herself.
- I don't have anything to prove.
- You're a good cook.
Making ricin out of castor beans
wouldn't be hard.
But I didn't.
Take a look of this.
That's your credit card statement.
You bought gin.
I'm over 21.
It's not a crime.
You just happened to buy the same gin
we found at the victim?
Can I go or what?
We've enough to charge you
with murder right now.
You need to talk to us,
tell us your side of the story.
I'm 28.
I run my own kitchen.
I don't have any...
Food channel connections,
no cookbook with my name on it.
The westing is my way up.
Jeffrey was the one to beat.
We all knew it.
So I figured,
get him a drink.
Why not?
Level the playing field.
So yeah, I bought him the gin.
But I have no idea
how the ricin got in there.
Okay.
I just tried to get him drunk,
that's all.
No poison.
Without anything else,
we can't hold her.
What do you got?
Jeffrey's phone records.
Confirmed the call with his wife.
- How long did they talk?
- About five seconds.
Guess she did hang up.
There's a second call
at 2:00 AM.
That one lasted over an hour.
- Who'd he call?
- His restaurant.
Miss Barge, you have a minute?
Sure. What's up?
Money troubles?
How'd you guess?
It's a restaurant.
They always have money troubles.
This restaurant's drowning in debt.
Jeffrey was driving
this place off a cliff.
It was all about the food.
This is Eliza Greene.
Jeffrey's sous-chef.
She's keeping things afloat
while I get my bearings...
Now that I own a failing restaurant.
Sorry.
People would say
that the place is failing,
And... Jeffrey would say,
"Yes, but failing with style."
You're the one the others
wanted to hire.
You must be very good.
- I guess. I wouldn't know.
- False modesty?
Jeffrey called the restaurant
last night at 2:00 am,
- do you know who he spoke to?
- Me.
He was considering changing the menu
for the contest,
wanted to talk about it.
Couldn't that have waited
till the morning?
That was just Jeff being Jeff.
He was always after perfection.
Irritating, a phone call like that
when you're on your way home, isn't it?
Not at all.
If you want to make something great,
that's the job.
You should get these deposits posted,
or the checks are gonna bounce.
Thanks for your time.
- Thank you.
- Night.
Bye.
Bye. Bye.
Where are my keys?
You picked my pocket?
My turn to drive.
Don't be such an old lady. Get in.
Your fears are groundless.
You're right. The car has air bags.
Bad move.
- Victim's brother?
- Kevin.
I can't tell you how happy I am
that wasn't my car.
You're out of your freakin' mind.
I would never, ever harm my brother,
ever.
You assaulted and robbed a girl,
who ran your brother's restaurant.
You don't think that makes you
a little suspicious?
It had nothing to do
with what happened.
I don't believe you.
I can tell you why I went
after the money,
but I need some guarantees.
So we're negotiating now, are we?
I have valuable information.
I can help you.
But you're not gonna tell us anything
unless we cut you a deal?
We're talking
about your brother here.
That's pretty low.
You know what?
You go to jail.
You'll have plenty of time to think how
you could've done things differently.
Wait.
Sean Horlick.
Jeff owed him money.
He needed it for the restaurant.
Guy's a loan shark.
I actually put them in touch
five months ago.
I get a call yesterday from Horlick,
and he says unless
I want to end up like Jeff,
I'd better get him
the money he owed.
So you rob your dead brother's wife?
She was always trying
to turn Jeff against me.
Said I was
a bad influence or somethin'.
Imagine that, huh?
Crazy.
I knew their deposit schedule,
and they don't keep a gun.
I figured she screwed me before,
I screw her back.
Sean Horlick.
What else do you know about him?
Fraud, racketeering, extortion,
couple of violent
crimes sprinkled in.
Charges never seem to stick.
Horlick's smart.
- Track him down. Take Rigsby.
- Okay.
Cho, look into Jeffrey's restaurant.
The financial records,
see who else he owed money to.
I'll come with.
I'm a mite peckish.
What does that mean?
It means I'm hungry.
I can't read this.
That says,
"March '09 accounts payable."
This... this is just ridiculous.
This is delicious.
Thank you.
Let's hope you can keep the quality up
with the new boss.
Abigail seems more concerned
about the money than the menu.
Won't be a problem, I promise.
- For God's sake. Did you try this?
- You don't like Abigail much, do you?
Do it over.
You're obviously very talented.
You should've
struck out on your own
a long time ago, unless there was
some reason to stay.
I did try to strike out
on my own, actually,
Couple months ago.
- Failed with style?
- I wish.
State wouldn't
grant me my liquor license.
No license, no investors, so...
Luckily, Jeffrey took me back again.
So why not hook up with him?
He was separated, available.
I've never liked waiting in lines.
Excuse me.
I've got prep work to do.
Thanks for lunch.
I didn't see any other loans
on the books. Good thing.
Jeffrey wasn't taking a salary
the last few months.
He wasn't?
We'll have to make a stop
on the way back.
Magic brownies.
This is more...
Clean-cut than I'd expected.
Medical pot, it's a...
- growth industry.
- First timers?
I'll tell you
that I tell all the newbies:
Go for today's specials.
They're a couple bucks more
but between us,
it's the freshest herb we got.
Plus it's locally grown.
Who doesn't wanna support local formers?
Where's your boss?
Mr. Horlick? I couldn't say.
Our permits are
all up to date by the book, 100%.
Mr. Horlick's a suspect
in a murder investigation,
So if you know where he is,
you should tell us.
There a problem here?
We're here about Jeffrey Barge.
Who?
Yeah, Jeff. Sure.
- What about him?
- He died yesterday.
I know.
I saw that on the news.
Heavy.
Boom, he's here.
He's gone.
And how about that? Life?
We know you lent him money.
How do you know that?
I mean, who says?
- I'll take that as a "Yes."
- Frosty one, aren't we?
- I like it.
- You like jail, too?
That's right. Kevin told us everything.
It's about time you did as well.
Fine.
I called him about the money.
Obviously, he drew some sinister
and incorrect implications
from our conversation,
but it was
all a big misunderstanding.
Chalk it up to my...
poor communication skills.
- I think you communicate very well.
- Yes, you do.
You've "Sleazebag" written
across your forehead in big letters.
Why would I kill Jeff?
You don't off someone
who can pay you back.
The guy practically lived
at the Ritz.
What are you talking about?
He was broke.
That's what he wanted me
to think, too.
I got a buddy
who works security at the hotel.
He saw the deadbeat staying there
a bunch of times.
You don't stay there
unless your pockets are padded.
I'd like to take you sometime,
thaw you out a little bit.
Yeah, that'll happen.
We got something.
Jeffrey stayed at the Ritz
over a dozen times in the past 2 months,
paid in cash every time.
Looks like an affair.
But Jeffrey and his wife
lived separate lives.
Why would he care
if there was a record?
- Maybe his partner cared.
- Because she's married.
She had the money.
She paid for the room,
but in cash
so her husband wouldn't find out.
Keep digging.
Find out who the woman was.
Next round's tomorrow?
Keep workin'.
- You'll get there.
- Merci beaucoup.
Watch it.
Careful, careful.
That smells good. What is that?
Knock yourself out.
It's not for the competition.
It's my lunch.
- I'd advise against that.
- Don't listen to him. He's a coward.
- Is he?
- It's the red Savina pepper.
- It's kinda spicy.
- Kind of?
It's the hottest pepper known to man.
Trust me. Leave it alone.
It's good on everything:
meat, fruit,
soups.
Not that any of the people
would know. Babies.
- I'd love a little try of that.
- Mr. Jane,
our chefs are extremely busy.
Would you mind coming back another time?
You're quite the ghoul,
aren't you, Duesterberg?
Dragging on this meaningless contest
after a man has been killed.
This contest, Mr. Jane,
is an affirmation of life.
It's a testament
that appetite still exists,
- even in the face of death.
- And you need the money.
- Time for you to go.
- Fine.
I have all the information I need,
thank you very much.
He lies. He hasn't asked
one single question.
Why would I?
I can learn everything I need to learn
from watching you all cook.
You, for example.
Use lemon to the point of excess.
Tart, aggressive flavors,
sublimated aggression toward
an important figure in your life.
You're a daddy's girl,
so I'm gonna go with mother.
No, let me correct that...
Stepmother.
Ludo!
You were adopted, no?
No. I wasn't.
Took a shot.
Moving on.
You were having an affair
with Jeffrey.
Weren't you?
- What?
- You can tell all this by the food?
They cooked together every day,
yet their kitchen rhythms are off.
They're bashing into each other,
getting in each other's way.
You're not paying enough
attention to her.
- No wonder she strayed.
- That's nonsense.
Really?
Why did your wife have her father
put the state's best police force
on this case?
Look at her.
She's made no attempt.
No attempt at all to deny it.
Is it true?
I take it you know about Julia's affair
with the victim now.
Roger that.
Jeff and I got together
about five months ago,
after he separated from his wife.
But he ended it.
When?
The night before he died.
I went to his room at the resort.
He was drunk.
I thought he was trying to get sober,
but I guess not that night.
Jeff didn't handle stress well.
Must have made you angry.
I accepted it.
I loved him.
But he was a drunk.
Better left alone.
Wise of you.
I asked for a glass of water.
I'm sure it'll be here in a minute.
You think I'm entitled
and snippy and rich.
My father's a senator. I don't have
to take crap from people like you.
I'm just trying to figure out
who killed Jeffrey Barge, that's all.
- I didn't kill him.
- I don't believe you, Julia, not yet.
I really need
that glass of water.
I'll get it.
We still have
a few more questions for you.
9-1-1.
Can you hear me?
Are you on medication?
Come on.
Answer.
Yes.
I know.
Mr. Attorney general, sir, I...
I understand completely.
I will.
She's straightening.
Absolutely.
Coroner's office says
it was ricin poisoning,
Just like Jeffrey. Guess they were both
poisoned at the hotel.
Crap. Is she straightening?
Victim was a senator's daughter.
A.G. must be livid.
It's not our fault.
Ricin takes hours to kick in.
- Tell it to the A.G.
- What's going on with the search?
The sheriffis on it, taking food
and liquid off the resort to be tested.
Resort, the contest,
it's all been shut down.
News flash.
The A.G. wants this case closed now.
We've got 2 dead married lovers.
I'd say the killer's a spouse.
Let's start with that.
There he is.
Cinnamon, sage and coriander,
a squeeze of lemon, then butter.
No, no garlic.
Not at all. Ciao.
Idiot.
Your wife just died,
and you're talking about recipes?
What can I do?
We'd like to discuss
your wife's estate.
Yes.
Sorry.
Idiots. Garlic.
So Julia had money. So what?
You stand to inherit
all of it, right?
Yes. So?
She and her lover are dead.
Killed the same way.
You're our number one guy.
Or number two, I'd say.
- Have you talked to Abigail yet?
- Why?
Ask her about the fight
she and Jeffrey had
at the fairplex market two weeks ago.
It was quite a scene
You mention this earlier?
Interrogation focuses the mind.
What can I say?
Except you're lying.
Jeffrey hadn't seen his wife in months.
If Abigail said that,
she's the liar.
The market Clerk
confirmed the story.
You were in contact with Jeff,
and you were fighting.
I didn't kill Jeffrey,
if that's what you're getting at.
I didn't even know
about this thing with Julia.
- What were you fighting about?
- You've really changed your look.
Haven't you? Not that you don't look
lovely now. It's just
this old look,
accentuated your assets.
My husband just died, okay?
You're still putting in time
with the makeup though, I see.
So appearance is important to you.
What are you getting at?
She's put on 5 or 6 pounds,
doesn't fit
into the sleek outfits anymore,
So she wears this. She's pregnant.
Right? Congratulations.
First trimester.
Jeff's child,
right?
Right?
A few months ago, he
came by to pick up some stuff.
Things happened.
And two weeks ago,
I took a pregnancy test.
How did he take
the news of fatherhood?
That's what you were fighting.
I don't know why I didn't tell you.
I've been...
Confused.
My parents don't even know.
Do us a favor, Abigail.
We're gonna need to search your house.
Save us all some time
and grant us permission.
Did you know a full-grown elephant
can eat up to 495 pounds
of food per day?
Could you at least
pretend to be helping?
Got somethin'.
Found this in the garage.
Nice work.
And we care
about a bag of beans why?
Castor beans.
They're used to make ricin.
Of course.
Naughty Abigail.
We found traces of ricin
in Julia's favorite red pepper.
Her death was not accidental.
Both her and your husband
were specifically targeted.
Together with the castor beans we found,
It's not looking good for you.
My client denies any
involvement in these killings.
She bore no malice towards her
husband or Ms. St. Germain.
No malice toward her alcoholic
and fiscally irresponsible
husband and his lover?
She was not aware of
that relationship,
Nor did she ever set
foot in that resort.
- Which you can't prove.
- I didn't do this...
How do you explain the castor beans?
- She had no knowledge of them.
- That's convenient.
This is a grieving widow...
a pregnant, grieving widow.
You think that a jury
is going to convict on this
circumstantial traif?
We can make this stick,
and you know it.
Believe me,
you will feel much better if you...
Would you excuse me?
What?
- What emergency?
- Follow me.
I don't really have time for this.
I was working on getting a confession.
- This is more important.
- What is?
Agents, welcome. It's a relief to know
that the killer has been caught.
Just doing our job.
Thank you for coming
to this little memorial dinner
Dinner?
Honoring Jeffrey and Julia.
We're having dinner?
Gotta eat.
I certainly hope you enjoy yourself.
It should be delicious.
Excuse me.
Those serviettes are horrifying.
You have five seconds to
tell me what's going on.
First, we need a drink.
Is it that bad?
It's lovely.
Not bad, Ludo.
- Can we get the bowls ready?
- You shouldn't be here.
You're probably right.
You gonna make me leave?
- I hope not.
- Excuse me.
Excuse me.
I thought you'd be grateful.
I did just catch your friend's killer.
We're grateful.
Just a little busy.
Is that it?
- Thats smells...
- Not now, s'il vous plaît.
Fire!
Fire! Quick!
I'm just gonna leave you with that.
All right everyone, please.
Lift your glass.
To Jeffrey
and Julia,
friends,
colleagues, titans
in the culinary world.
You'll not
be soon forgotten.
Salud.
- Cheers.
To begin we have a melon soup.
Prosciutto di parma,
mint and basil.
A reinterpretation
of one of Julia's specialites.
Bon appétit.
Thank you.
Don't let your midwestern taste buds
hold you back.
- What is this spice?
- Spice?
I like a little heat,
but this is overpowering.
We didn't add any heat.
That would be me.
Sorry.
Fire! Fire!
The red Savina pepper.
I got it from Julia's...
pantry.
I thought it would be appropriate.
And I'm just mad for heat, so...
Obviously, I was a little heavy-handed.
My apologies.
What's the trouble?
What's the problem?
The peppers, it didn't go down well.
The pepper?
If you prefer,
we can go to headquarters.
- How long we got?
- 48 hours.
That's a stretch of time.
I have to leave.
- Right now.
- No, that would be rude.
What is wrong with you?
We all...
have to go to the hospital,
- right now.
- What for?
The pepper...
It was poisoned.
I saw Ludo put
- something into it.
- I did not. How dare you!
Maybe you're just cramping a little?
All right, all right.
I poisoned Julia's pepper.
- And Jeffrey's gin.
- Just bring me to a hospital.
Hospitals are terrible germ factories.
You don't wanna go there.
- Are you insane?
- Relax.
We knew about the ricin in the pepper.
We didn't know who put it there.
I don't understand.
Are we poisoned?
I switched the peppers.
Clever of me.
We know that your restaurant
didn't fail, Eliza.
Jeffrey and Julia, they killed it.
We did some digging
on Julia's father.
He's the one who squashed
your liquor license.
Jeffrey was a drunk.
He needed you in his kitchen,
so he asked his lover if he could have
her big powerful daddy
do her a favor.
He didn't call you that night
to talk about recipes, did he?
He called to apologize
for sabotaging your liquor license,
for ruining any chance you had
at opening your own place.
But I...
I am trying
to become a better man.
I am.
He told you what he did,
and then you...
decided to take your revenge.
So you got some castor beans,
mixed up a batch of ricin
and went to the resort to find him.
I went to his room.
I accept your apology.
Let me just... wash up.
Such a fool.
Like I was gonna let that go?
Like we were just gonna make up
and all be friends again?
That's...
ridiculous.
You went to the pantry
and you found Julia's pepper
and you dosed that, too.
One time
I was cleaning shrimp for Jeffrey.
There were like, 40 pounds of it
and it was still half frozen.
But that was the job.
I couldn't
feel my hands.
It was so cold.
I realized I was cutting the flesh
off my own fingers.
Carving it off.
And I didn't mind,
because Jeffrey had a vision.
I had a vision.
And he said: "Go babe.
"You deserve your own place."
But he was lying.
Him and his...
rich bitch girlfriend.
Like I was gonna let that go.
He said, "I'm sorry."
"I'm sorry."
What good is that?
A word.
Yes.
You framed me.
You put those castor beans
in my house, didn't you?
On my word of honor, I did not know
that those beans were planted.
Mr. Jane was responsible.
I should've known.
I should've stopped him, and I didn't.
I am really sorry.
Why?
He thought in order
to catch the killer,
that somebody else
had to be suspected of the crime.
He's probably right.
I know you must be angry.
Trying to leave the anger behind.
Though that's pretty much impossible,
isn't it?
It's hard.
Anyway.
Thank you for your honesty.
Tell Mr. Jane he's a mean,
irresponsible sadist.
I will.
Ms. Barge?
Living with an alcoholic is hard.
Some never change.
They don't even want to.
But your husband
checked into treatment two weeks ago,
right after you told him
about the baby.
I think he wanted to be there
for you and your child.
That's why he ended
the relationship with Julia.
For what it's worth,
it seemed like he wanted to change.
Thank you.
It's okay. She's gone.
Who?
Please, your guilty conscience
is obvious and well deserved.
Justice can be a harsh mistress.
Omelets and eggs, ends to means,
all's well that ends well.
A glib answer's no excuse.
And Abigail said to tell you
that you are a mean,
irresponsible sadist.
That's pretty accurate.
You okay?
- No point denying it to me.
- I'm fine.
Good night.