(patrick) oh, it's lovely.
(teresa)
it's a crime scene.
It's a lovely crime scene.
(wayne) hey. couple joggers
found our john doe
On their morning run.
body's still pretty fresh,
So it must've
happened last night.
No signs of an entry or exit
wound means cause was probably
A blunt force trauma
to the head.
and they brought in
the grown-ups
Because they couldn't decide
whose sandbox it was?
right. body's right on
the city line.
the only thing
they can agree on
Is that it was
a carjacking gone wrong.
Wallet, watch, wedding band--
everything gone.
Oh, not everything.
killer would have been
Very frustrated to not
be able to take this.
Looks like a wheel.
motorcycle wheel.
I don't buy it as a carjacking.
maybe the murderer was
Covering it up as one,
but if you're after
Someone's car and valuables,
you grab and bolt.
You don't waste time
taking off a cuff link.
right.
Carjacking--
a gunshot or a stab wound
Is more likely than a beating.
beating like this
takes time.
The murder
was personal.
no surprise there.
The haircut, the suit,
the cologne--
This man had enemies.
his cologne tells you
he had enemies?
Sure.
okay, confrontional.
Finishing touch
on a wardrobe that says,
"pay attention.
show respect."
This was an extrovert
tough guy, a professional,
A backroom politician
or a lawyer, a fixer,
The type
that's good with people,
Making people do things
they maybe don't want to do.
uh, what he is, is useless
until we know who he is.
Well,
i can do that, too.
Oh, no, jane. i, uh, i checked.
the phone's not on him.
The signal light's still on.
phone's in range.
His assailant probably
threw it in the trees.
What are you doing?
i'm making a call.
But you don't have
the phone.
i have my voice.
You still need the phone. want
to use the voice activation?
You need
its names and numbers.
there is one name
programmed into every phone,
Particularly into one
belonging to a middle-aged man
That was wearing
a wedding band.
Home.
(cell phone rings)
(woman) hello?
Hello.
this is patrick jane
From the california bureau
of investigation.
I was wondering if you knew
a man 6-feet tall, mid 40s,
Salt and pepper hair,
gray custom-made suit,
Weighing about 192,
give or take?
That's my husband
gordon hodge.
gordon hodge, hmm.
You said you're from cbi?
is something wrong?
Uh, just a sec.
It's for you.
(indistinct
police radio chatter)
Hello?
(woman) i knew something
like this would happen,
Sooner or later.
(teresa)
well, was your husband
Having some sort
of trouble lately?
Gordon was a criminal attorney
with a very special practice.
He had only one client--
the sinner saints.
Bikers, are they?
Yeah, they're one of the top
biker gangs in the state.
They run some legit businesses,
but mostly they're into
Drugs and prostitution,
low-rent protection rackets,
That kind of thing.
For years, i begged him
to get out, but gordon said that
A lawyer never abandons
his client. it's unethical.
It's what he always
called them--
Never "the gang,"
always "the client."
When was the last time
you saw him?
Yesterday morning,
before work.
Gordon used to meet
these people at all hours--
That's how they are.
so we didn't get worried
When he didn't come home
last night.
Had he been acting
differently lately?
He'd been more on edge
the last week or so.
I think something happened
at work, but i'm not sure what.
Did you ask him
about it?
No, never.
work was off-limits.
He said it was boring.
What was the real reason?
Do you think he was ashamed,
or he sensed your shame?
He wanted to protect us.
Would his colleagues
at the office
Have known
what was going on?
no.
he was a one-man shop.
Didn't even have
a secretary.
Gordon didn't trust anyone
with his business.
(teresa) any idea who might
have wanted to kill him?
Well, you might want
to ask his client.
He knew
all their secrets.
He probably learned something
that he shouldn't have.
Either of you ever meet
any of those scumbags?
No.
You two must be very torn--
living in such a beautiful home,
Driving nice cars,
going to good schools,
All paid for
by dangerous criminals,
Or, uh, "scumbags,"
as my colleague says.
Do i wish that gordon would've
defended civil rights leaders?
Yes, of course!
But he believed that everyone
had a constitutional right
To have a good defense.
he had his principles.
Thank you for your time.
Did you go to some interview
school i've never heard of?
Next time, get the facts,
save the editorial.
yes, ma'am.
I know.jane did it, too.
he's not a cbi agent.
From you, i expect
professional standards.
yes, boss.
That was the captain
of the local c.h.i.p.s.
Hodge's car was just fished out
of a lake about a mile from
The murder scene--
no good for prints.
He said that two weeks back,
they busted hodge
At a highway rest stop,
walking to his car with
2 ounces of coke and 2 ounces
of meth in his pockets.
Nailed him with
felony possession...
nice.
Only the d.a.
dropped the charges.
There was some
unlawful search technicality.
either hodge
is a great lawyer...
Or the d.a. turned him
in exchange for dropping
The charges--planned to
use him as an informant.
well, if the saints
found out--
yeah, they'd kill him.
they did know about the charges.
Their boss, von mcbride,
posted hodge's bail.
well, talk to your friends
at the d.a.
Find out what
the story is there.
Jane and i will go
talk to the sinner saints.
okay, be careful.
(rigsby) you want me to come
for backup?
uh, no. talk to forensics
about the car.
Jane, let's go.
now, please?
Come on.
(engines revving)
(birds chirping)
Beautiful, huh?
No, not really.
i fail to see the charm.
It's the glamour
of mobility.
That's why the girls
went for cain and not abel.
Is that right?
yeah. nomads--
sexier than farmers.
They have romance.
(cell phone rings)
(ring)
Lisbon.
I spoke to my friend
in the d.a.'s office.
They didn't make
a deal with hodge.
They let him go 'cause
the case was less than ironclad,
And they've already lost too
many to hodge and the saints.
Last 10 years, they've beaten
the rap in over 50 cases--
Murder, rape, drug-trafficking.
they're bulletproof.
Nobody's bulletproof.
Well, my friend says
to stay away from them,
That they're bad news.
Good, sound
lawyerly advice.
I'll take that
under advisement.
You ready?
Whew!
(heavy metal music playing)
There's romance
for you.
We're with the cbi.
We're looking
for von mcbride.
(sets glass down)
not here, which is where
you need to be.
Well, can you tell us
where he is?
No. i cannot.
Listen, we're here
for information,
Not trouble, boys.
Well, we've got
nothing to say.
(teresa) i can take you in
if you want me to.
I prefer to talk here.
(man) like i said,
there's nothing to talk about.
We're not doing
anything illegal.
Mr. mcbride?
(teresa) it was nice
talking to you.
Your focus on
this pressing matter
Suggests you're
the man in charge here.
yeah, well,
keep on walking, blondie.
We just have a few questions
for you. it won't take long.
Yeah, well, i'm sorry. i don't,
uh, talk to police officers
On the advice of my lawyer.
Your lawyer's dead.
Yeah, i heard that.
but his advice is still good.
(pool balls click)
means your business here
is done.
Oh. you don't want to know
who the informant is, then?
What informant?
oh, i'm sorry.
forget i spoke.
(patrick)
oh, i'm so sorry.
You messing with me?
yeah, i'm messing with you.
there's no informant.
Come here.
You touch him,
and i'll arrest you.
i would love to see you
try and do that.
What's your name?
Xander.
Xander,
your threats are empty.
She's a state agent.
You're not gonna
lay a finger on her,
And you know that,
so why play tough?
W-where's that come from,
this need to intimidate?
I'm a sadist,
and i bore easily.
Oh. me, i see
a difficult childhood--
Bad parenting,
a lot of torment.
But i also see how
that suffering gave you
Great powers of empathy
and a strong creative side,
And those are the qualities
You should try and nurture
in yourself.
Not this brutish character
you try to hide behind.
Oh, that's xander,
all right.
Full of empathy.
You guys want a drink?
Sure.
So what's this crap
about an informant?
How long have you know about
hodge's taste for coke and meth?
Couple years.
Guy liked to party,
but he could still do his job.
Couldn't have been too thrilled
when he got busted.
Case got dropped.
Must've wondered why.
Illegal search.
Yeah.
Either that or hodge,
uh, flipped on you.
That son of a--
hold on a second, diamond.
he didn't flip.
There is no informant.
Where were you
last night?
Right here.
And i got
30 other brothers
Who will vouch for me
and each other.
Look, man,
none of my guys did this.
We loved gordon, man. he was
like a member of the club.
You know, he couldn't ride
worth a damn.
no, he couldn't, huh?
He tried, though.
Who killed him?
My guess?
Probably some other
motorcycle club
Looking to put us
out of business--
Chaos brigade,
bolos plata.
(woman) get your hands
off of me! get off me!
Help! get your hands
off of me!
Get off of me!
let her go,
and back away!
Back away now!
get your hands off me!
(gasping)
You're murderers!
All of you!
Ma'am, take it easy.
i'm cbi.
Ma'am!
(engine revving)
(engine starts)
(tires peal)
Who was that?
she a friend of yours?
Never seen her before.
Mentally deranged,
seems like. poor thing.
You know, you're
a very good liar.
Most people subconsciously
signal dishonesty,
But you? there's nothing.
no inner conflict.
Usually, that's the mark
Of what shrinks
like to call a sociopath.
Well, if by "sociopath,"
you mean that if you cross me,
I would enjoy watching you
suffer pain before i kill you...
Then, yeah,
i'm a sociopath.
See ya.
Bye.
(wayne) so we talked to
the gang unit.
There's no other biker gang
would cross the saints
And run the risk of starting
a war that they couldn't win.
This is incredible.
you should see this.
Hold on. anything on
the woman in the parking lot?
Sinner saints have
their own web site.
Really?
yeah.
We cross-checked registrations
of the truck model and color
With driver's license photos
fitting her description.
No hits. truck must be
registered to her husband
Or other family member.
mcbride's clamming up about her
means he's hiding something.
He's merged two other gangs
into the saints in the last
Five years. it's the fastest
growing gang in the nation.
go to hodge's office.
See if you can find anything on
the gang's operation that pops.
And have the deerfield p.d.
Issue a bolo on
the woman's pickup truck.
okay.
You can buy logo merchandise--
sinner saints coffee mugs,
Decals, beach towels. whoa!
(telephone ringing)
And some various other
interesting little knickknacks.
nice.
Yeah. well, if they do it,
we should do it.
A range of casual wear,
maybe?
Sensible shoes?
I'll get right on that.
Okay. lisbon loafers.
(computer beeps)
found something, boss.
These are gordon hodge's
cell phone calls
From the night
of the murder.
All were routine
business calls--
Von mcbride, other lawyers,
court officials.
But it's the last call
that bumps.
(computer beeps)
7:23, incoming from
a constance hoyt.
"current address unknown."
must not want
people finding her.
Well, i went back
three months--
A lot of calls
between her and hodge.
Did you try the number?
twice. got one of those
computer voice mail messages.
Plus, i ran her name
through the d.m.v.
For registration
of a black pickup truck.
She's not
your parking lot woman.
check von mcbride's
cell phone records.
See if he had any contact
with this constance hoyt.
(typing on keyboard)
(computer beeps)
Bingo.
couple of chatty cathys.
talking three or four
times a day.
Either she's his mom, or...
his girlfriend.
(typing on keyboard)
(heavy metal music playing)
(sets bottle down)
(sighs)
(birds chirping,
tires crunch, door opens)
Constance?
(engine starts)
we just have a couple
questions for you.
I'll drive!
no time!
(door slams)
Boss, seat belt.
go!
(tires screech)
(engines revving)
Bike's got too much muscle.
you're gonna have to--
(tires squeal)
(thudding)
(tires rumbling)
(brakes squeal)
Do not even think
of moving.
I gotta get you
out of the office more.
(car door opens)
Got hodge's office key?
(keys jangle)
So what's your problem
with bikers?
I hate bikers.
Why's that?
My dad was a biker.
Really?
i didn't know that.
(keys jangle)
no? i thought you
read my file.
Well, it says he was
a big-time criminal.
Didn't specify
any affiliations.
Jimmy marks
on the doorknob.
Doubt that was part
of the original decor.
Door clear.
Clear.
Desk clear.
(sighs)
Cracks are on the outside
of the window.
Means a previous
break-in attempt.
Think they were
looking for something,
Or just trying to
send a message? (sighs)
Message was definitely
a part of it.
Do you prefer "constance,"
or "diamond"?
(sighs) i prefer
to get the hell out of here.
You ran from the police,
endangered the lives
Of two agents. you could be
here a couple of days.
i don't think that's right.
why'd you run?
i ran because i'm dead if
anyone sees me talking to cops.
The saints are all paranoid
about informants now,
Which is why
i'm not saying a word.
tell us about your affair
with gordon hodge.
(scoffs) i wasn't
sleeping with gordon.
Oh.
Uh... yes, you were.
It was only a few months.
we were just having fun.
It's not like von doesn't
sleep around on me and...
Gordon treated me nice.
You had genuine feelings
for him.
He was decent.
He never looked down
on you.
Just got sucked in
too deep with the saints.
Did you know he was
arrested for possession?
Told him a hundred times
to be careful,
But he got dumb
about it.
Ah, well, drugs simply
make people careless.
You had to be a little concerned
about mcbride finding out.
It would've
made things complicated.
"complicated"
is one way to put it.
So you called him that night.
then what happened?
Did you go and see him?
No! no.
I called to break it off.
i heard him answer the phone,
And i'd tried to talk to him,
but the line went dead.
What about the woman
in the parking lot?
i don't know.
Von doesn't talk
gang business with me.
Had you seen her before?
she's come around
a few times
Last couple of weeks,
same thing--
Lots of crazy yelling,
then taking off.
Look...
You, um...
You gotta promise
That von doesn't find out
about me and gordon.
He keeps
his cards close.
He could already know--
Killed hodge
out of jealousy.
(sighs) trust me.
If von knew, gordon's
wouldn't be the only dead body.
Only one other person knew.
And that was bad enough.
Who was that other person?
(sighs)
We have information
that suggests
You knew about gordon
and another woman.
Yes, i did.
How?
About four months ago,
i found a valet stub
On the driveway
from the deerfield inn.
So one night,
i followed him
And saw him go in
with that biker girl.
Did you confront him?
(slicing)
more like yell and hit him.
He promised
he'd stop seeing her.
I took him at his word,
And i never asked him
about it again.
why not?
Because i didn't want
to hear him lie to me.
Mrs. hodge...
(whispers) what?
If you picked up
on your husband's affair,
You must've suspected about
his other illicit activities.
I knew about
the drugs and the partying.
He was surrounded by it.
Why didn't you tell us
about this earlier?
Because gordon is dead.
Anything that i said or did
would not bring him back.
My son draws
stares and whispers
Because of his father,
agent lisbon.
Both of us--
we deserve to grieve
Without shame and scandal,
don't we?
Yes, you do.
And if she'd followed
her husband once before,
She could've tailed him again
and killed him.
no, she didn't do it.
she loved him.
She was a prisoner
of her husband's life.
She gets rid of him,
gets a fresh start.
People trapped
in miserable lives
Always talk about escaping.
few actually do it.
It's easier just
to close your eyes
And pretend the misery
doesn't exist.
Boss, you might want
to see this.
This is from a security camera
across the street.
It was the third incident
in two weeks.
Building owner said hodge didn't
want to report the earlier ones
Because he didn't want
deerfield p.d. combing through
His office and accidentally
finding something
In his sinner saints file.
there.
Magnify.
(teresa) the woman
from the parking lot.
***
(von) chaos brigade
controls distribution
Over in rancho rosa,
but i figure if we move
Right now,
we can move into stratton.
What's up, my brothers?
We just have one quick
follow-up question for you.
(sighs)
I've exceeded my quota of
answering cops' questions.
And my quota of crazy.
(laughs)
The woman
in the parking lot.
Uh, like i said,
she must've mistaken me--
She was seen
vandalizing hodge's office.
She find anything
she shouldn't have?
His files were intact.
she got nothing.
We have nothing further
to talk about, then.
The sooner this case is closed,
the sooner we're gone
And you're back
to business as usual.
Last name is guthrie.
She's the sister of a gentleman
i was accused of killing.
Falsely, of course.
Trial was
a couple of weeks ago,
Gordon hit a home run.
got me off.
And you weren't eager
to i.d. her
Because you didn't want us
poking around your case?
Hey, all i know is
that she's been coming around
From time to time, saying some
very offensive things.
Thanks for your cooperation.
You think she killed gordon?
Like i said,
thanks for your cooperation.
I've got one last question.
If hodge wasn't
the informant in your gang,
Who do you think it is?
I mean,
i tried asking the d.a.,
But he's kind of
a secretive bastard, huh?
What do you think?
Mr. jane,
we're a motorcycle club,
Not a gang.
And i can assure you
there is no informant.
Well, you'd know best.
Why does he keep going on
about this informant?
He's just talking.
Let's get down
to business.
Von mcbride should be
sitting here, not me.
Court docs say your brother rick
was an auto mechanic.
Mcbride blamed him
for screwing up a repair,
And your brother
refused to redo it.
Mcbride allegedly
got angry and killed him.
Not "allegedly."
he killed him.
He beat him to death
with a crowbar.
He murdered him.
and the jury disagreed.
Mcbride acted
in self-defense, right?
That's because
that lawyer hodge
Made it look like
it was my brother's fault.
He started throwing around
all these lies about my brother,
Saying that my brother
was a druggie,
That he was aggressive,
that he was mentally unstable.
So you get all worked up,
harass the gang,
Trash hodge's office,
right?
(scoffs)
You want to arrest me
for that, go ahead.
I'm not gonna fight you.
i'm too tired.
you ever try hodge's home?
Once.
But his kid came outside.
I don't have
a beef with him,
So i took off
before i could do anything.
And what were you gonna do?
i don't know.
I was...
I don't know.
I wanted hodge
to understand
What he had done to me
and to my family.
when was this?
Two days ago.
The day of the murder.
where were you that night?
home.
Can anyone verify it?
i live alone,
but i didn't--
Now six months ago,
You were arrested
in a road rage incident.
Got out of your car
at a red light,
Attacked a man
in an s.u.v.
What does this
have to do with anything?
You're an angry person
and you express it physically.
(sighs) i'm not angry,
i am sad.
My brother
was a good man.
The only crime he committed
Was standing up
to that bastard mcbride.
Hodge blackens the name
of your dead brother
And gets von mcbride off.
now maybe trashing his office
Didn't give you
enough satisfaction--
Perfectly understandable
if your frustration boils over.
And you can't touch von mcbride.
he's got 20 bikers around him
All the time, so maybe
you go for the easier target.
I didn't kill
gordon hodge,
But i'm sure as hell
glad that he's dead.
She'd been to his house
that day.
Could've laid in wait
and followed him later.
Plus, she was out for revenge--
no more powerful motive.
we don't have
nearly enough to charge her.
I say we hold her
on the vandalism.
Try to dig up something that
puts her at the murder scene.
Or you could release her.
she's obviously impulsive
And sloppy enough
to get caught on camera.
She'll think
she's bought herself some time.
And she'd try something
to cover her tracks
And implicate herself.
Cut her loose,
then let's shadow her.
Yes, boss.
(groans)
Where are you going?
Fresh air.
All this murder talk...
"is rank.
"it stinks to heaven.
(british accent) it hath
the primal eldest curse upon't."
Shakespeare.
(brakes squeal)
Little less pressure
on the brake pedal. (chuckles)
Is your mom here?
Market. that's why
i'm confined to the driveway.
Ah.
you want me to
have her call you?
We know felicia guthrie
trespassed on the property
The day your dad
was killed.
I-i just need to hear
what happened.
Uh, i was
leaving for school.
I saw her hop the gate and come
running up the driveway,
So i ran out
to try to stop her.
She was yelling
all this stuff about my dad
Lying about her brother
and getting von mcbride off.
Then she just ran away.
did your parents see her?
No. dad was already at work,
and mom was in the shower.
Huh. any reason you didn't
bring this up earlier?
I don't know.
I felt bad for her,
i guess.
Didn't want her
to get in trouble.
Well, just needed
to confirm. thanks.
(engine grinds)
Whoa!
(sighs) aw, god!
You need to relax.
It's not gonna help. i'm never
gonna get the hang of this.
That's an easy fix.
you need the right instructor.
All right. so now you can
speed up a little.
Excellent. i like how
you're keeping your distance.
Just trust your instincts.
they're always right.
You're a good instructor.
Yeah, i am,
probably because i have
Zero emotional investment
in how you do--
Unlike your father,
Who i'm guessing got annoyed
with every mistake you made.
He wasn't
the most patient guy.
Probably didn't help that
he was always on his cell phone.
Been living with his job
my whole life.
You get used to it.
You also
get used to the drugs
And the cheating
on your mother?
He promised he'd stop.
Yeah.
Can't be easy
going through life
Being labeled
the gang lawyer's son.
It wasn't
really that bad.
I mean, girls would
come up to me all the time,
Talk to me about dad
and the gang, like i'm cool...
(chuckles) instead of a geek,
which i basically am.
everybody is.
I am.
If he was my father,
i tell ya, i-i...
I'd be mad at him.
Dad didn't mean
to hurt anyone.
He was just
doing his job.
Right.
Well, i guess i'd still love him
if he was my father.
Can't say i'd cut him
the same kind of slack
If i was
married to him.
Are you trying to
blame my mom?
'cause if you are...
what?
You're wrong, that's all.
She loved him, too.
Well, that brings us
back to felicia guthrie,
Who didn't love him at all.
What exactly did she say
to you when you saw her?
It was hard to tell.
She was just, you know,
ranting, basically.
Didn't make much sense.
Very nicely done.
You'll be out cruising
on saturday nights in no time.
Just remember,
trust your instincts.
They're always right.
thank you.
And thanks for
the driving lesson.
(whispers) yeah.
(dog barking in distance)
Still no movement.
Looks like
she's in for the night.
Talk to van pelt recently?
Yep.
Any progress?
nope.
(engines rumbling in distance)
you hear that?
Yeah.
They're gonna
go after felicia.
Mcbride thinks
she killed hodge,
Wants payback.
Officers on hampton,
north of lexington,
Request
immediate assistance.
What the hell's
going on?
Go back in your house
and stay down!
Do the smart thing
and get out of here right now!
We're not doing
anything illegal.
(loudly)
disorderly conduct,
Concealed weapons,
blown exhaust pipes,
Probably a couple of
outstanding warrants in there!
(man) screw you, pig!
We could bust
half you clowns right now!
So what's it gonna be?
We'll be seeing you around.
(engines revving)
***
(felicia) if they think they can
intimidate me, they're wrong.
Felicia, temperatures
are running hot,
So i need you to stay away from
the gang's bar from now on.
(felicia) yeah. i'll stay away
when you arrest von mcbride.
And what were you people
doing out here, anyway?
Oh, we think you killed,
uh, gordon hodge,
So agent cho and rigsby
are watching you.
Oh, come on.
she was never gonna buy,
"we just happened to be
in the neighborhood."
I told you i had
nothing to do with that.
And who told you
that you could go in my house?
Oh, this? i just needed
some tea. cut through the chill.
Chill, my ass.
you were looking for evidence.
Felicia, take it easy.
don't tell me to
take it easy, when this guy's
Rifling through my underwear
drawer, looking for a weapon.
It was your closet, actually.
i was looking for
Blood-splattered shoes.
get off my property.
you're very touchy.
go.
(indistinct chatter
over police radio)
You really looked
through her closet?
laundry,too.
She's been angry and emotional
about her brother,
Which means that she was sloppy
about hodge's murder--
Dragged evidence
home with her.
It's just not inside.
Well, there's no garage
or toolshed.
Well, i looked
everywhere.
Well, everywhere
except the garbage.
Why not?
Well,
it's garbage.
(sighs)
you done with that?
Almost.
(tea splashes)
Yes,
the case is still ongoing,
And you are
a person of interest.
I'd advise you
not to leave town.
Boss?
Excuse me.
Do you see that?
What's goin' on?
Stay there. don't move.
(felicia)
i didn't do anything wrong.
Mcbride must've set me up.
Rigsby, put her
in interview one.
Boss, nina and lucas hodge
are here to see you.
She say why?
because i asked
them down here.
Rigsby, could you bring her
through here, please?
It'll just take a minute.
thank you.
are you gonna tell me
what this is about?
I'm just closing
your case.
(patrick) thanks for
coming down, mrs. hodge.
This woman's name is
felicia guthrie.
She murdered your husband
out of revenge for getting
Von mcbride off a charge
for killing her brother.
oh, my god!
No, i did not kill anyone.
Uh, we have evidence.
We just need
your permission for, uh,
Lucas to make a formal
statement, saying that
He saw her at your house
the day of the murder.
You saw her?
well, he can
fill you in later.
His statement will give us
a better chance at a conviction.
Absolutely.
anything you need.
great. thank you.
Lucas, if you can confirm
that this is who you saw,
Then you'll be on your way.
What's gonna
happen to her?
Well,
probably life in prison.
Uh, if she's lucky, she might
get paroled in 25 years.
I swear, i didn't--
i didn't touch him!
Shut up! you took
everything from us.
Lucas, we need to book her now,
so could you identify her?
no, she wasn't the one.
I mean, yeah,
she came to the house--
great. thanks.
that's all we need.
Take her away, guys.
thank you. thank you.
(felicia)
no, i didn't do anything!
I didn't do anything wrong!
trust your instincts, lucas.
they're always right.
(breathing heavily)
let's go.
(sighing)
she couldn't have done it.
what makes you say that?
I just know.
lucas,
they have evidence.
This bitch killed
your father!
don't call her that!
it wasn't her.
The only way we can know
for certain is if you tell us
Who did it.
okay, stop talking to my son.
you've got your statement.
Lucas, let's go.
come on! let's go!
no!
Lucas!
stop!
(sighs) it was me.
(sighs) we were out
for a driving lesson.
I was driving badly that night,
And my dad was
on the phone the whole time,
Like he always was.
(cell phone rings)
he'd get mad every time
i'd make a mistake,
but i just couldn't
seem to concentrate.
Because of your run-in
with felicia guthrie that day.
You didn't talk about her
until i asked,
'cause you
felt sorry for her.
You didn't want to
draw suspicion to her,
Because you knew
she didn't do it.
You were trying to do
the right thing.
I just kept seeing her
in the driveway,
Crying, yelling about how my dad
lied about her brother.
his phone
just kept ringing...
(cell phone rings)
and he'd get mad at me
and i'd screw up worse,
and i just...
i couldn't take it anymore.
next time his phone rang...
(cell phone rings)
i grabbed it from him.
i heard her voice.
(constance) hey, gordon baby,
it's me. can you talk?
That biker bitch--
diamond.
She kept calling him
"gordon baby."
Said she really
wanted to see him.
Felicia guthrie was right.
he was a liar.
i threw the phone
into the woods, and he got mad.
he promised me he'd stop
doing drugs
and cheating on my mom.
and like an idiot,
i believed him.
I called my mom.
she told me what to do.
I grabbed all the stuff
to make it look like a robbery,
But i couldn't get
that damn cuff link out.
So i ditched his car
in the lake.
She drove me home.
The lie gets heavy fast,
doesn't it?
I expect after a while,
You wanted to go to the police
and tell them the truth.
sometimes i wanted to.
mom said no.
She promised
it would be okay.
Well, it might be...
Someday.
Let's go.
(handcuffs jangle)
yeah, there we go.
(sighs)
(handcuffs clicking)
(voice breaking)
i'm sorry, mom.
You know, i have to wonder
how that cuff link rigsby found
Made its way
to felicia guthrie's house.
That is a conundrum.
Because i'll bet
a year's salary
That if i look
in the evidence locker,
The cuff link we found on hodge
will have mysteriously vanished.
Okay.
I needed lucas to see
felicia get arrested.
You needed hard evidence
to charge felicia.
So...
I made it happen.
By making
an innocent woman think
She was gonna go
to prison?
As if her life wasn't
hard enough already.
yes, you're right.
she does deserve some justice.
It's good to see
you care.
You know, sarcasm
is the lowest form of wit.
(heavy metal music playing)
(speaking indistinctly)
(cell phone ringing)
Yeah?
All right.
I'll be back
in a minute.
(man whispers)
hey, psst.
Over here.
What's up?
Uh, well, i thought
you might want to know
We caught
gordon hodge's killer.
It was his son.
Lot of issues
between 'em.
And you felt the need to
tell me this from the shadows,
Dressed in this getup?
Self-preservation.
I figured i'd worn out
my welcome with your friends.
That's it?
This is what
you had to tell me?
Well, no.
there's another reason.
You open that envelope,
And the rat in your gang
will be revealed.
oh, the rat.
Now turn around and try
not to look too guilty.
What was that about?
What, this?
this is, uh... (chuckles)
It's kind of funny,
actually.
yeah, funny?
Selling us out is funny?!
Hey, man.
you got it wrong, bro!
Come on! get over here!
hey! hey!
(scuffling)
(grunting)
(engine starts)
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com