We've got Claire Wolcott... female, Caucasian, 32 years old.
She was found shot to death in her room.
Her husband's got friends at the Governor's office,
so he called in some favors.
He wants the investigation to be kept discreet and low-key.
His wife gets murdered and his priority is discretion?
Oh. Okay.
Yep, Mrs. Wolcott was cheating on Mr. Wolcott...
Which makes Mr. Wolcott suspect number one.
Number two. Number one would be Mrs. Wolcott's mystery lover.
The room was registered
in Claire Wolcott's name, so no help there.
At 2:24 a.m., hotel staff and guests heard three gunshots,
but they didn't know where they were coming from.
15, 20 minutes later, they come here and call 911.
Whoa. Found a shell.
- Looks like a 9-millimeter.  - And another.
Mark 'em for forensics.
- So the lover didn't do it.  - Because?
The, uh, shell casing things
indicate the shooter was across the room here.
He or she stepped in from outside
and started blasting away.
If the lover had done it, he'd have been closer to the victim,
and he wouldn't have had to shoot as many times.
And look. Circular,
which means a vertical drip
from someone standing right here, bleeding. Right?
Not spatter from the victim.
You're a forensics expert now?
So Claire and mystery lover are asleep.
Someone comes in through the open door,
shoots them, leaves. Poor lover is woken by a bullet,
Claire dead next to him. "Aah!" Freaks out.
But nobody comes right away.
Mystery lover, who is only slightly wounded,
gets to thinking maybe the best thing to do is just...
slip away, out here.
You two finish up here.
Yes, boss.
Here.
There you go.
Clean one.
Anything else?
No.
"Doc lady."
The silver caddy arrived last night at 2:31.
Ah. That's about seven and a half minutes
- after the shooting took place.  - Name and room number?
Open it.
Psst.
- Hey. Wake up.  - Oh, my god. Who are you?
It's all right, ma'am. We're CBI.
- We need to talk to you, sir.  - What's this about?
- Take a wild guess.  - Put your hands in the air.
Okay. I'm, uh, I'm not under arrest, am I?
'Cause I've done nothing wrong.
Pants on. We'll talk after.
This is Kevin Haightly, resort manager.
Hi. Um, I know we can't expect to get the room back,
but when might the walkway be open for use, do you think?
That depends on when forensics is done. We'll let you know.
Okay. Thanks.
It was a cold night, so we lit a fire and made love.
We went to sleep afterwards, and suddenly there was,
like, a sharp pain and bang! I wake up,
and there's blood everywhere and I'm shot in the arm
and Claire's dead. You know, I freaked.
- You didn't see who did it?  - No.
Why'd you leave?
Claire was dead. I couldn't help her,
and I couldn't help you guys. I didn't see anything, so...
You know, what could I contribute?
She's a married woman.
Yeah, we know that. And Jill Rubenstein...
- what's your connection with her?  - The doctor lady?
I met her in the parking lot and asked her for help.
A complete stranger takes you to her room,
treats your wound and then has sexual intercourse with you?
What can I say? The hippocratic oath is a beautiful thing.
How well did you know Claire Wolcott?
Uh, I don't really know her that well.
I met her just a few weeks ago.
She was at a bar, and I picked her up.
- Since then, I've seen her occasionally for sex.  - Is that what happened last night?
Yeah. I called and asked her to meet me for a drink.
We came here.
- Did anybody else know you were here?  - Nobody. Just me and Claire.
And how long had you been in the room?
Um, a few hours.
I'd agreed to, uh, you know, stay the night.
I was fond of Claire,
and it's a long drive home, so I stayed.
- I don't normally do that.  - No? What... what's your normal procedure?
After lovemaking? Depends on the type of woman.
- So you've got it down to a science.  - I'm good at what I do.
Okay, Mr. Fricke, and what is it that you do?
I'm a pickup artist.
Mm.
A, uh, woman whisperer, if you will.
A pickup artist... that's your profession?
You sound like my mom.
Um, it's more of a total lifestyle kind of thing.
You know? I-I practice my art, of course. That's my passion.
But I teach and I blog also,
um, conduct seminars, workshops, that sort of thing.
- Is that good money?  - Not bad.
- And do you take money from the women you pick up?  - Sometimes, when I need to.
Did you take money from Claire Wolcott?
No. No. Like I say, I was fond of Claire.
Um, I planned to see her again.
You really only want to monetize as an exit strategy.
Paul, is your mother still alive?
I know where you're going with this, Dr. Freud,
And, uh, you're wrong.
My mom's dead, as it goes,
but, uh, I loved her dearly, and she loved me.
Who said anything about your mother?
- You just did.  - No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did.  - Didn't.
- What are you talking about?  - I'm just kidding. Just playing with you, Paul.
Just kidding, mucking around.
Yeah. Are we done here?
Do you know who killed Claire?
No.
Interesting.
He's either a habitual liar telling the truth
or he's an honest man lying.
Do you keep a list of your pickups?
Yeah, of course. I, uh, I have 'em here.
Names, numbers and a 1 to 10 grading system.
Nice. Something to show your grandkids.
We're gonna need you to forward a copy of that list to us.
Oh. Yeah, sure.
What, you think maybe this was a jealous ex-lover?
Could be.
Wow.
I say we bring him in anyway, for creepiness.
Which should be a criminal offense, but isn't.
He could have shot her, then shot himself to cover it up.
- He simply could have shot her and left.  - He didn't have the gun on him,
- local P.D. has searched every inch of this place and found nothing. He's clean.  - Maybe someone's trying to kill him, not her.
Not likely. The room was registered
- in Claire Wolcott's name.  No one else knew he was there.  - What was she thinking?
She was so beautiful, and he's so... creepy.
Yeah, that Dr. Rubenstein was hot, too. How does he do it?
All you need is a basic understanding
of the evolutionary psychology of women,
rigorously and fearlessly applied.
You gotta know what buttons to press.
- Like we're toasters?  - Like men don't have buttons, too?
Men are like toasters.
Women... a little more like, uh, accordions.
I thought that was a compliment.
Mr. Wolcott?
Thank you for coming. I'm so sorry for your loss.
The effects you requested...
photos, video of Claire.
We'll return this to you as soon as possible.
I was just upstairs
speaking with my friend the Attorney General,
And I told him that I will not rest
Until the man who did this is brought to justice.
I will not rest.
- I know I can expect the same from you and your people.  - I assure you
This unit does the best we can  with every case we run. Cho?
If it's convenient,
Agent Cho would like  to ask you a few questions.
Hi.
When did you speak to your wife last?
I was in San Francisco on a business dinner.
I called Claire around midday,
Told her I'll probably be staying in town that night.
- Did you? Stay the night in town?  - I did.
Did she say where she was going or who she was meeting?
- No, but I didn't ask.  - So you didn't know she was at the spa?
I wouldn't expect to know.
- She often went up there on a whim.  - Can you think of anyone who want to hurt her?
No. No, she was, um...   Harmless.
- Any friends or family that might be in any trouble?  - She's from back east.
She doesn't have any family or friends out here.
She shopped and she played tennis and she went to the spas.
No one would have any motives...
Yes?
I recall she fired an assistant last month.
Caught her stealing jewelry.
- I believe she was pressing charges.  - Name?
Natalie... Something. My people will have her details.
Are you aware that on the night of her murder,
Your wife was meeting a lover?
Yes.
The local authorities told me they suspected as much.
Did you know she had a lover? Prior to her death, I mean?
- No. Do you have a name? is he a suspect?  - We have a name. He is not the suspect.
- Who is he?  - I'm not at liberty to say.
- I want his name.  - You can't have it.
Are you sure, Agent Cho?
Because I can make one phone call,
- And your career is toast.  - That's impressive.
The best I can get with one call is a pizza.
Now this business dinner you were at in San Francisco,
What's the timing on that, and who else was there?
My people can give you times, names and numbers.
We're done here.
Thanks for your cooperation.
Wolcott's wife was so pretty.
What do you see?
Nice shoes, loneliness.
Where we going?
Natalie Edreau?
Yes?
- We're with the CBI. Can we come in?  - Look, I already told the cops
- I didn't steal anything from that bitch.   - By "bitch," are you referring Claire Wolcott?
- Yeah. So?  - Uh...
She was murdered last night.
How long did you work for Claire Wolcott?
About a year... Till she turned psycho.
She claimed that you stole jewelry from her.
Yeah. She was wrong. I didn't steal anything.
Claire pressed charges against you.
- How'd that make you feel?  - Excuse me, are you trying to say that I killed her?
- Do you own a gun, Natalie?  - Oh, my god. This is really stupid.
- Um, no, I don't own a gun.  And, no, I didn't kill Claire.  - Where were you last night?
I was hanging out with my roommate till about 9:00 or so.
Then, uh, then I went out for dinner.
What'd you have? For dinner?
What does that have to do with anything?
The chopped salad at pastucci's.
Ah. Yes.
There's something on this side of the room
- You don't want us to find. What is that?  - Nothing. There's nothing.
Look me in the eye and say that.
Whatever. Search all you want.
Meh. Too much stuff. You're not very tidy.
Good in bed I expect, yeah?
Messy women make good lovers.
- Can I hold your hand?  - I...
Shush.
Hmm...
Camera.
- Okay, those are personal, so...   - ooh.
- Uh-huh.  - Is it...
Claire Wolcott and her lover Paul Fricke...
Time-stamped two hours before the murder.
These are the photos we pulled from your digital camera.
A couple hours after these were taken, Claire Wolcott was dead.
That doesn't prove anything.
Opportunity and motive. You were close by when she died.
And the theft charge she laid on you dies with her.
That was a garbage charge.
- I wasn't worried about that.  - No?
No.
You didn't steal jewelry from her?
Please. She dressed like a mormon call girl.
- I wouldn't want her jewelry if you paid me.  - I didn't ask if you want her jewelry.
- I asked if you stole it.  - No, I didn't.
Why were you photographing her?
Now think this through, Natalie. We're investigating murder.
If you have an explanation for these
That doesn't involve killing her,
- You should tell us, get yourself off the hook.  - I thought
If I threatened to tell her husband about the affair,
Then she would drop the theft charges.
- That's what the pictures are for.  - How do you know she is having affair?
It was obvious. She kept sending me out to buy men's gifts.
You know, like, watches and ties.
I knew it wasn't for her husband. I'm not an idiot.
- What did Claire say when you confronted her about it?  - I didn't confront her about it.
She left with that flugly guy before I got the chance.
- Probably wouldn't have worked anyway.  - Why not?
Because keith Wolcott is, like, super controlling,
Especially about money.
He probably knew all along his wife was sleeping around.
- What's the verdict?  - I'm not liking her for this.
But we should talk to the roommate,
Make sure her alibi stands up.
The husband, on the other hand...
- He is the type to know about his wife's affairs.  - His business dinner at San Francisco
- Couldn't have made it back to calistoga to kill her.  - He's also the type
- That'll hire other people to do his dirty work.  - Yes. He is.
- And they don't take credit cards.  - I'll look into his finances.
- Boring.  - Okay, Mr. Entertainment. What do you want to do?
I wanna go back to the crime scene.
That hotel room... there is something that just isn't right.
Hey.
You're up.
Great.
Something's not quite right.
Don't take too long. I'm hungry.
Let's go eat.
Good to see you again. So... Is there any news?
The owner keeps asking me
When we'll be able to reopen the villa.
- No news.  - We're here for lunch.
Oh. Absolutely. Um...
One moment.
Oh, look who's here.
Ah, just the man.
I have a question I need to ask him.
Right this way.
- Oh. Thank you.  - Thank you.
Katie?
Table four needs fresh drinks, okay?
Yes, sir.
Hey!
My old friends from the CBI. Come, have a seat.
Surprised to see you back here so soon.
It's my number one hunting ground,
Loaded with my kind of women...
Beautiful, rich, married and unhappy.
So you specialize?
Sure. Yeah.
Some guys will tell ya hot, young singles are the real test.
But I'm not in this to win a points contest, you know?
Plus, I like the gratitude you get from the older ladies.
A woman died... a woman that you were close to.
- Doesn't that give you pause?  - Sure it does. Yeah, I have feelings.
But having this gunshot wound?
- Genius opener.  - An opener?
You know, a prop or a line you use to start a conversation.
- You can't just go up and say, "hey, what's your name?"  - No?
Duh.
So how do you do it exactly? You know, pick up women.
- Need some help, huh?  - No.
Big handsome dude like you? I got a few basic techniques...
... that will turn you into a freakin' sex machine.
A machine.
Well, I'm not looking to be a machine so much.
- I'm more of a steady relationship kind of guy.  - When you're scoring...
... with a different super fox every night,
what do you want a relationship for?
Do you ever fall in love...
- ... with any of these different super foxes you score with?  - No. Never.
Love is for guys who can't get laid.
Oh.
So, uh, what's your basic technique?
Oh, there's a thousand ways to seduce a woman.
All kinds of workable systems.
But they all boil down to three words...
... "contempt", "control", "excitement".
Contempt, control, e... excitement?
Women want men that don't need or want them.
They want to be told what to do,
... and they want edge, adventure, drama.
Whatever you wanna call it.
Present that package to them, and they will bite.
Guaranteed.
Ouch.
And then when you have one under your spell,
... then you get up and leave.
L... leave? But...
No, no, no, no. You leave. Trust me.
Next time she sees you, she'll tear your clothes off.
Guaranteed.
- What's going on with you two?  - Excuse me?
You and Katie here. You got something going on?
- No.  - No.
Just askin'.
I used to let her sleep with me once in a while. That's all.
No, you had feelings for her.
Years ago, maybe a little. Sure.
- You know, before I got my mojo working.  - Hmm.
Thanks for talking to us, Paul.
Oh, you had one more question...
- ... you wanted to ask.  - Ah, yes, that's right. Thank you. I forgot.
Uh, the night that you were sleeping with Claire,
... was the patio door open or closed?
Uh... Closed, I think.
Thank you.
OK, now I'm really hungry.
- Drive-thru.  - Done.
You think Fricke's right?
Was the door closed? Yes.
It was a cold night. They lit a fire.
Why would they leave the door open?
- No, I mean, is he right about how to deal with women?  - 100% wrong.
Unless, of course, you wanna have a lot of casual sex...
... with total strangers. Then he's right.
When did you first meet Paul Fricke?
At a wine tasting event a friend was throwing.
- And how long were you and he romantically involved?  - Um...
Three, maybe four hours.
So you didn't know Paul Fricke...
- ... prior to agreeing to spend the night with him?  - No.
And you haven't spoken to him since?
What attracted you to him in the first place?
Four times?
What exactly attracted you to Paul Fricke in the first place?
I don't know. I guess there was just something about him.
And were you at all hurt or angry...
... when the relationship ended?
Mm... no. I was disappointed more than anything.
We had a wonderful time together.
Thank you for your time.
- Oh, you'll, um, you'll tell him "hello" for me, won't you?  - Yes.
Hey, how's it going? Any potential suspects?
Nope. I'm bringing in the rest tomorrow.
There's more?
This is just "A" through "M." How's it going with you?
No unusual transactions for Mr. Wolcott.
But three days before she was killed,
... Claire Wolcott made a $200,000 withdrawal...
... in the form of a cashier's check,
... made out to none other than Paul Fricke.
Here's the best part... according to the bank,
Keith Wolcott set up the account, so he'd be notified...
... whenever a large transaction took place.
Meaning that Wolcott had to have known about the 200 grand.
Exactly.
- Nice work.  - Thanks.
Uh... Brandy?
Come on.
"Darn it, woman!" said the redneck.
"Ain't you never seen a goat before?"
- He's handling his grief well.  - Mm.
Excuse me, Mr. Wolcott?
Now's not a good time.
I'm sorry to intrude.
We need to ask you some follow-up questions...
- ... regarding your previous statement.  - I'll be happy to speak with you tomorrow morning in my office.
- Oh, this won't take long.  - I told you... tomorrow morning, my office.
Very good.
Mr. Wolcott, it's about your wife's lover.
We, uh, know about the $200,000 she gave him,
And we know that you know about it.
How dare you.
How dare I? Did I do something daring?
Am I supposed to be afraid of you?
You're supposed to be respectful.
Respectful? You contemptible little buffoon.
Your wife just died,
... and you're swanning around in a monkey suit...
... drinking punch and laughing with your idiot friends...
And you want respect?
There's your respect.
What?
You know damn well what. You assaulted a man.
- Oh, I just tweaked him on the nose.  - Technically, that's assault.
Technically, he's an ass. He deserved it.
Yes, he is, but this is not a school yard.
You simply cannot do stuff like that.
I did. I did it.
And the seas didn't boil and the sky didn't fall.
They will shortly.
Wolcott is on his way down here with a $1,000-an-hour lawyer.
If you give him a formal apology,
... he says he's willing to drop the whole matter.
Hmm, let me think... No.
Would you please be reasonable for once?
- I'm busy.  - Right.
I am. I'm just thinking that, uh...
He's gonna drop the whole matter in any case.
- Oh, really?  - I guarantee it.
He's a shallow narcissist. It's all about image.
And this whole business makes him seem small and silly.
Ooh!
Contempt, control, excitement.
What?
Nothing.
This place is so nice.
$800 a night, minimum. Can you believe that?
Huh.
Hello? What, you're not talking to me now?
You barely said a word the whole time.
I'll talk to you when you have something interesting to say.
Fine. Be a jerk.
I'd go in. But I'd have to keep my injury dry.
Gunshot wound.
- Oh.  - Don't worry. Uh, you're not in any danger.
I'm a lover, not a fighter.
Oh, not you guys again.
The old magic not working so good today, huh?
Just like baseball.
Most of the time, even in major leagues,
You, uh, swing and you miss. Gotta keep on swinging.
I hit on ten women a day.
I'm going to have sexual intercourse...
- ... with at least one of them.  - That is gross.
She's intrigued by me, this one.
She's just too proud to admit it.
Yeah, get your shoes on, Romeo.
Hey.
Focus on the shoes.
You know, I didn't notice before.
You're not bad lookin'.
Shoulders are a bit too wide,
but, uh, otherwise, pretty nice.
You're kidding, right? You're trying to hit on me?
What man in his right mind wouldn't want to hit on you?
Okay, leave her alone.
Get in the car.
I'm sorry.
My colleague, Agent Jane, refuses to apologize.
He says he's happy to see you in court.
And you refuse to talk to us,
so I can't rule you out as a suspect.
- I'm afraid this is gonna make a bit of a mess.  - Keith, I suggest...
No, no. I have nothing to hide.
What do you wanna know?
What do you know about your wife's affair with Paul Fricke?
I knew Claire was having an affair
with this Fricke person, and I knew about the money
- she was gonna give him.  - Then why did you deny it?
It's not the sort of thing one likes to admit, now, is it?
And I knew it would make me a suspect,
- and that would be tedious.  - Did you confront her about Fricke?
No. I stopped the check immediately, of course.
And that was the end of it? You weren't angry?
Not at all. I was happy.
I wanted to divorce her for ages.
Why?
She'd become irritating.
The cost of divorce always deterred me,
but her infidelity with Fricke
cut the payout she'd receive in half.
Now if Claire had lived, come Monday,
She'd be in for a nasty surprise.
I was all set to serve her with divorce papers.
Even cuckolded, she stood to get a big sum.
Rich man like yourself...
her death saved you a lot of money, didn't it?
Yes, it did.
But money isn't everything, is it?
I'm sorry she's dead... truly sorry.
But every cloud... as they say.
Well, I believe we're done here.
Seems so.
You'll be hearing from the attorney general shortly
regarding Mr. Jane's conduct.
Oh, I doubt it.
Really?
When you've thought about it,
you'll see that this business makes you seem small and silly,
and you'll drop the whole matter.
You misled us, Paul.
You were going to take money from Claire.
But I didn't, did I?
A business associate of mine
is opening up a new club here in town.
He, uh, offered me a role as partial owner
if I could come up with a share of the building costs.
- Claire was generous enough to offer me a loan.  - And?
I went to deposit it just a couple days ago
- and was told that the check had been stopped.  - That must have been disappointing.
- What did Claire say?  - She said it must be a mistake,
- and she'd take care of it Monday.  - Did you believe her?
Doesn't really matter.
- You know what the best part about being me is?  - No, I don't.
There are literally dozens of rich, needy women out there
that, uh, I could go to for financial help.
I didn't need Claire's money.
Hey.
Uh, what's the story with Katie the waitress?
I'm in the middle of something.
Oh. I'm sorry. I was just thinking.
I had a thought. Bear with me?
So Katie... tell me.
Nothing to tell.
Used to be if I, uh, didn't score for whatever reason,
I'd, uh, call her off the bench.
Can't sleep alone, huh?
Some people use cocoa and a good book.
I use beautiful women.
She must have been crazy about you
To put up with a deal like that, huh?
I guess so.
Difficult for her now to watch you pick up
a different beautiful woman every night.
- That's not how it is with me and Katie.  - Well, sure, it is.
She loves you. That much is clear.
Maybe that's what this is all about.
Your behavior got too much for her.
Katie has absolutely nothing to do with this.
How can you be so sure?
I know Katie. She's a good person.
She would never hurt anyone.
Okay, great.
Thanks. You can go.
- No.  - Ah, sorry. I'm sorry.
When agent Cho says you can go, you can go. Not a moment sooner.
Just give me one second.
Hey, you can't dismiss my subjects like that.
Oh, I know, and I took it back.
Besides, we need him back out there in the saddle.
You will agree with me 100% when I explain my theory,
my little plan.
Do you have any good clothes?
I'm wearing them.
Uh, do you have anything with a little more, uh...
zing?
No.
Okay.
Well...
I'm gonna have to take you shopping,
Just you and me.
I'll wait for you.
Right here.
I'm in position.
- Okay, look around for a likely target.  - Will do. Hey...
Bourbon on the rocks. Make it a double.
- Those two will do, I guess.  - Good.
Okay, now listen up.
Relax. I'm gonna talk you right through this.
Keep it smooth. You have to be calm and confident.
Yeah, you told me that already. I have the general idea.
Hello, ladies, I'll be right with you.
Start a tab for me, would you? Room 206. That's for you.
Hi. My name's Kimball. What are your names? You first.
- Darby...  - Darby.
- Sarabeth.  - Hey, Sarabeth. Tell me about yourselves.
Um...
What do you wanna know?
- Well, it's not exactly textbook, but he's figuring it out.  - That worked? "hello, ladies"?
- He's kicking it old-school.  - There's Fricke.
- Where?  - Let me see.
Cho, look, with the two blondes.
I don't believe this guy.
I give up. I do not understand women.
Never have, never will.
Seems like the dumber you treat them,
- the better they like it.  - They're Drunk Women.
- You can't generalize all women in general.  - This is your fault.
No, it's not. I'm just sitting here.
Katie? You've worked a double today.
- Why don't you clock out and have a drink on the house?  - Thanks, Mr.H. That'd be good.
Sure.
Here we go.
This is where we bring it.
- Time for phase two.  - Roger that. Phase two coming up.
What's phase two?
Let's go, Sarabeth.
What did he say?
- What did he say?  - I didn't hear.
Uh, he said, uh...
You don't wanna know.
Oh, well.
Struck out, huh?
I blew it, as usual.
I'm just unlucky in love. Always have been.
I know how that goes.
Same story, huh?
Same story.
That guy?
Him.
You know, no offense, but i've been watching him
Operate this evening, and he seems like kind of a creep.
A player, no doubt, but a creep.
This isn't who he is.
When we were together,
He was a sweet, caring, generous man.
It was me that screwed it up.
And we had this terrible fight,
And I said some mean things.
Mean things.
All this is an attempt to prove me wrong, I guess.
If I had a woman like you in love with me,
You could say whatever you like. I wouldn't be running around.
- That's nice of you to say. Thank you.  - You know what we need to do?
You need to make him jealous. Let him see you out and about,
- Enjoying yourself with another man.  - Are you hitting on me?
Yes, I am.
It's a good plan, isn't it?
The kid's a natural. Look at him. Look at him go.
The Cho. No business like Cho business.
206.
Here's the plan. Let's walk right past him,
Laughing and smiling like we're on our way somewhere cool.
- Get him thinking.  - And then what?
I'll think of something.
All right. Let's do it.
After you.
Okay, we're in the room.
Hey, Cho, that's some nice work.
Very nice work. So just sit tight.
- I don't think it's gonna take long.  - You hope.
Who are you talking to?
My colleagues.
Okay. Who are they?
I'm a state agent, Ma'am.
We're conducting an undercover operation
Regarding the wolcott murder case.
I... I don't understand.
I apologize for the deception.
You mean... You're not... You don't...
No, Ma'am.
Oh.
I'm so embarrassed.
That's understandable.
I...
Nothing is happening.
You have to have patience, woman.
She just doesn't have any patience.
I'm not touching that one.
There.
Come on.
- Drop the weapon.  - Drop it, Haightly.
Hands behind your back. Let's go.
Hi.
You set me up.
Yes, we did.
How did you know it was me?
Ah. It was a cold night.
Fricke told us that the patio door in his room
was closed when he went to sleep,
and I checked. You can't open them from the outside,
which means that the killer must have entered
by the main door, which requires a key.
Who has the keys? Staff.
Who on the staff would wanna hurt Claire Wolcott?
I don't know. Nobody.
Who would wanna hurt Paul Fricke?
Maybe you.
But what reason would you have for hating Paul Fricke?
Let me guess. Uh, something to do with a woman?
Katie?
You hated him because he used and abused her...
The woman you loved.
I'm not sorry. He's dirt.
The way he carried on with those other women...
Rubbing Katie's nose in it.
I never would hurt her like he did.
I wish I had killed him.
But you killed Claire Wolcott instead.
I never meant to do that. I wanted to kill Fricke,
Not Claire. But she shouldn't have been doing what she
was doing, should she? I mean, it's not like anybody cares.
- Her husband was going...  - I care. I care about Claire Wolcott.
- She was a living person.  - That's enough.
No. You took her life.
I...I just... I think he should be sorry.
You're right.
Well, do you wanna say it?
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
- Where's Cho?  - I don't know.
Called him a couple times. No answer.
The problem is, I really love Paul.
I know how he seems, and I know how he's been,
but at the end of the day,
when I think of who I really wanna be with,
it's him.
That's crazy, huh?
Love is crazy, I guess.
No, it isn't.
You should seek psychiatric help.
Ugh.
You mind?
Not at all.
Rough night?
Ah, not bad. Couple good phone numbers.
Hmm.
Yep. Two very tasty numbers.
I wish you'd stop being so damn stupid.
You have a good woman over there that knows you
and still loves you.
Excuse me.
Oh.
You looked kinda lonely.
My friend and I were wondering if you'd like to join us.
Hi. Um... I'm sorry. I'm... I'm married.
www.tvsubtitles.net