Excuse me.
What kind of tree is this?
Couldn't say.
Smells good.
So you're not a local?
Born 5 miles down the road.
Just don't give a crap about trees.
Thank you.
Name's Justin Prentiss.
Student at a private school operation
A couple miles from here.
They realized he was missing around 6:00 this morning,
Activated the electronic monitoring device
On his ankle, found him and called us at 8:00.
- Do they have an estimated time of death yet?  - Coroner puts time of
death
Somewhere between 10:00 and 1:00 last night.
I wanted to take him down the mountain
Soon as forensics were done, but as per your request,
- We didn't touch him.  - Oh, we won't be here long.
- You can have him as soon as we're done.  - What's with the ankle
bracelet?
Good question. Mr. Maclean?
This is the principal of the school... Asher Maclean.
These people are from the CBI. They want to know why
your student has an electronic monitoring device on him.
Justin had some truancy issues recently, hence the device.
What kind of school is this, exactly? Bright Arch is a wilderness program
for troubled youth.
- Like a summer camp?  - No, we're an accredited high school.
Students stay at Bright Arch for a year, on average.
We provide structure and discipline
Through close interaction with nature
Plus a regular high school curriculum, of course.
Uh, she doesn't like you, and you don't like her.
Why is that?
No comment.
Chief Brody?
- Why don't you like him?  - What has that got to do with anything?
- I'm just curious.  - Think you might show a little more respect.
- Respect for...  - There is a dead child here.
Yes. Yes, he's dead.
He doesn't care how I talk to you.
I've never worked with the CBI before.
- Do all your units come with a clown?  - We get the job done.
Well, how about getting it done now?
So we can take this kid out of here. How would that be?
Yeah. We'll do that.
Yep, you can take him. We've got the basic facts.
- Oh, is that right? That quick, huh?  - Uh, yeah.
- You want to enlighten us?  - Oh, forensics probably told you a lot of it
already,
I would guess.
Uh, his knuckles and his knees sugest
that he was overpowered in a hand-to-hand struggle.
The blow to the head was the coup de grâce.
But the ground around him is relatively undisturbed,
Which means that the struggle
would have taken place elsewhere... uphill, presumably.
Injured animals tend to move downhill, of course.
Do you have any actual facts?
Well, it's an actual fact that you dislike Mr. Maclean here
because he's a tree-hugging, liberal wacko.
He's probably running some kind of a cult,
and he dislikes you because you're a small-minded,
provincial hayseed... not that you are, necessarily.
- That's just what he thinks.  - Facts pertaining to this poor boy.
There was no moon last night, so it was very dark.
Justin wouldn't have been able to move very far,
injured as he was.
He had a lot of dirt in his hair,
a lot of dirt in his ears
and deep up under his nails.
So somewhere close by,
somewhere very close by,
there's a spot where someone, uh...
where someone buried him alive.
Oh, my god.
All right, all right, all right!
Settle down, folks.
Take your seats.
Let's go.
I know the last couple of days have been rough.
Losing Justin hurts.
But his death cannot become your crutch
for a negative attitude.
You can learn and grow from this experience.
Bryan.
Sir, do we still get to do the sacred fire ceremony
- On friday?  - I think there's all the more reason do it now.
We need healing. All right, listen, kids,
The strangers you see here are detectives
that will be investigating the situation with Justin.
They are here to find out what happened to him,
and I want all of you to answer any questions they have
as best you can.
Yes, yes, yes, people?
Yes, yes, yes!
Is it true that he was buried alive?
- Orrin.  - Oh, yeah, that is true.
- Who did it?  - That's enough, Elliot.
Let's all get back to our classes quickly.
We're wasting daylight!
You guys go and talk to the counselors.
We'll press the principal, see what he knows.
- We'll talk to the kids last.  - Okay.
- Mr. Maclean, I wanted to...  - Agent Lisbon, excuse me. Orrin.
We speak only when recognized as part of the discussion.
Okay? Get out of here.
I'm sorry about that. Well, welcome to Bright Arch.
Shall we, uh, convene in my office?
Yes, yes, yes.
Honey, just try to calm down a little bit, okay?
- We'll find everything out. Calm down.  - You son of a bitch. What
happened?
- What happened? What did you do?  - Mr. Prentiss... David, let's be calm
now.
Step back, sir. Now.
It's okay.
This man was supposed to look after my son.
It's his responsibility to keep his students safe,
and he didn't!
- He didn't!  - David!
Mr. Prentiss, let's go and talk. This way.
This way now.
How did you learn about Bright Arch?
One of David's colleagues
has a child who had gone way offtrack.
And they saw very positive results from the program.
Justin was misbehaving?
He changed a lot over the last year.
Suddenly he was always locked in his room, dour,
uncommunicative, violent on occasion.
Therapy didn't work.
What kind of violence did he engage in?
He often shouted at me and would threaten his father.
Just shouting?
No physical abuse, no criminal behavior?
No.
Please find out who did this.
Please.
Kids love to feed off the drama of things like this.
I hope it can be resolved quickly.
You know, you look like Burt Reynolds in this shot.
How long has Bright Arch been running?
Almost ten years now.
And that was all of the students?
Yes, we like to keep a low counselor/student ratio
so that everyone gets the focused,
individual attention that they need.
Right. What's the pitch?
I don't follow.
The pitch... the gimmick, the hook.
- How do you sell this place to prospective parents?  - Oh, we really don't
have to sell it.
They come by word of mouth.
This is a simple, natural healing community
where your, uh, troubled and underachieving
sons and daughters are encouraged to get in touch
- with their inner resources.  - Encouraged how?
By a code of honor and discipline,
by learning wilderness skills and teamwork
through an up-close experience with mother nature.
That's a good pitch. It's a good program.
- Yes, Cassie?  - Um, I got your tea.
Oh. Thank you.
One of our, uh, our great success stories.
Arrived here about nine months ago angry and withdrawn.
- She's blossomed wonderfully.  - Tell me about Justin.
Why was he wearing an electronic monitoring device?
- I looked around. I didn't see anyone else wearing one.  - Justin had only
been with us three months.
He was still in the rebellious phase.
Day before yesterday, he left campus without permission
for several hours.
He refused to tell us where he had been and with whom.
His punishment was eight hours in the reflection room
and the electronic monitoring device for, uh, two weeks.
Confinement and dog collars.
Yeah, that'll certainly, uh, encourage the discovery
of inner resources, I guess.
- But do the kids' parents know that's part of the deal?  - It's in the
brochure. Page three.
So you must get a lot of problem kids.
How do you handle the psychos...
The ones that just won't knuckle under no matter what?
We don't take 'em in the first place.
- I went thoroughly every acceptance.  - So no name jumped into your head
when you heard about the murder?
- No.  - You ever heard of z krew?
No. What's that?
I'd like to talk to Justin's friends.
- Of course. He was in missy Jenkins' teaching pod.  - Great.
Bear in mind that I or one of my staff members
need to be present before you talk with any of our students.
- Is that right?  - It's the law.
Really?
- Ohh. I hate the woods.  - Would you rather be playing desk jockey with
Van Pelt right now?
Who sends their kids to a place like this?
It's not cheap, either.
Eh, a little deprivation and discipline
- Is good for the soul.  - Yeah, but this is like a juvie prison camp.
No, this is like spring break in Cancun compared to juvie.
Wait. You were in juvenile hall? Seriously?
Yeah. You didn't read my file?
No. Why, did you read mine?
Of course.
What have we got?
Look at this.
Interesting, huh?
Maybe there's treasure involved.
Maybe not.
Follow the trail. Find out.
So over and under...
Over...
And under...
And through.
Simple. Again.
Over and under
And over...
And under.
Chris! Hit the reflection room.
One hour.
- Marley, give me 25.  - But he started it.
Yeah, I hear you, and I do not care. 25.
Hey, lady!
- Are you talking to me?  - Yeah, I'm talking to you. This is important. Look at me.
CBI. That's police. There'll be no backchat.
- You do exactly as I tell you.  - What?
Hold this.
CBI...
California Bureau of Investigation.
Well, ma'am, we have reason to believe...
Untie me this instant.
- Sorry, ma'am. Your boss Mr. Maclean told me to do that.  - No, he didn't.
Yes, he did. He's in his office right now.
Go and ask him.
Okay, my people, we have precious little time
Until our friend returns.
I need to know who knows the most about what around here.
Elliot's been here, like, two years,
- So he knows everything.  - Wow, that's a long time to be stuck out in the woods, huh?
- I like it here.  - Yeah? So what's the deal with Justin?
- Who disliked him?  - Nobody, He was fine.
- Oh, you say that like he was a prize jerk.  - No, He wouldn't win any prizes.
I mean, he was basically a good kid.
But he just fought a lot with everybody.
What do you think he was doing out in the woods?
Who knows?
- The woods are a bad place.  - Yeah? Why is that?
The axman Zachariah lives there.
Who's Zachariah?
There is no Zachariah.
It's... it's just a story.
- Yeah, I was just kidding.  - No, you weren't.
Come on, guys.
- Aren't you a little old to believe in stuff like that?  - A year ago...
They found a townie kid dead in the woods.
He'd been chopped up with an ax.
His head was 20 feet up in a tree
With a crazy look on his face.
Okay. Now does Zachariah have anything to do with Z Krew?
Was Justin in Z Krew?
Jane?
Jane! What the hell are you playing at?
You can't tie people up.
- Uh, yeah. Sorry.  - I should think you would be.
My apologies, Mr. Maclean.
We'll be back tomorrow morning if that's convenient.
See you in the morning.
I hope you got something useful for all the trouble you caused.
Yes, I did... the story of the mad axman Zachariah
- Who lives in these here woods.  - Ah, "z."
Yes, "z." I would have gotten more out of 'em,
- But you came back too quickly.  - Reality check... I'm your supervising agent.
I'm not your decoy.
So, uh, what did it say?
What?
You know, my file.
You haven't read your own file?
- No. It's against the rules.  - You're kidding.
What? I like rules. Why be a cop if you don't like rules?
- Come on. What did it say?  - You know what it says. It's your life.
I didn't know you were adopted,
- But other than that, no surprises.  - Adopted? What?
Kidding.
Ha ha, very funny.
So why were you in juvie?
You know. The usual reasons.
That has a mark on this map with a skull and crossbones.
So what are the usual reasons for being in juvie?
I'll tell you all about it sometime.
Hey, check this out.
Looks like Justin's shoe.
Yep.
- I'll call forensics, mark it up.  - Yeah.
Hello? CBI!
Anybody home?
Hello?
CBI!
Try the other side?
Yeah.
You move, you die,
You mameluke sons of bitches!
- Kneel down!  - Hey, we're cops.
Kneel!
I'm... a blow your damn faces off you, you hear?
Eh, eh, eh! Winston! Come on!
Winston, you fool. Put that gun down. Let go.
- Thank you.  - No problem.
- Yeah, thanks. What are you doing here?  - Winston called 911. Lucky I was close.
Can you please tell me why I'm still here?
I had nothing to do with that kid who died. Nothing.
You're here because you assaulted us.
- But if you want to talk about Justin Prentiss, that's fine.  - How am I supposed to know who you are?
You're bangin' on my doors, "CBI! CBI!"
Like that's supposed to mean somethin'?
Yeah, we do need better brand awareness
But your response was disproportionate.
You brandished a firearm. So here we are.
My security alarm went off.
I was loaded. I reacted.
- That's all.  - You're very security-conscious. Why is that?
Why not? Are there people out there who dislike security?
What's been your history of contact
- With the students from Bright Arch?  -Zero. I have a zero history of contact.
You know the kid who was killed, Justin Prentiss,
Who was buried close to your property line?
He had a sketch map that showed the way to your house
Marked with a skull and crossbones.
- I don't know what that means.  - How about Zachariah? That name ring any bells?
No.
Looks like it's gonna be a long night.
I just want to be left alone
And I want those kids to leave me alone!
They go up to my property, mess with my stuff.
They break windows. They spray paint my doors
pull all kinds of stunts all night,
Like a routine.
Okay. So what did you do in response?
I did everything to try and stop them short of actual violence.
I built fences.
I planted poison oak.
I installed alarms.
They just took it all like it was a game.
- Were they at your house last night?  - The night before...
Three or four of 'em, throwing balloons of red paint.
Would you be able to identify any of the kids involved
- If you saw them again?  - They always wore masks.
I want to apologize for the misunderstanding yesterday.
- Mr. Jane will comport himself properly today.  - Yes, I will.
Who's Zachariah?
- Who?  - Zachariah.
- Never heard of him. Who is he?  -Liar.
- "liar"?  - Pants on fire.
- They're ablaze.  - I want to cooperate with you people.
But this man is trying to... I don't know what he is trying
- To do, but I resent it.  - You should know that you sound more than a little paranoid
- When you talk like that.  -This is what I'm talking about. How is this police work?
Oh, I'm kidding with you. I get bored.
See, the thing is, you have heard of Zachariah.
You know who Zachariah is, and you're scared of Zachariah.
- And we're gonna find out why.  - Let's put a pin in that, shall we?
We have information putting Justin Prentiss,
At mr. Winston's house the night he went awol.
He went up there on a regular basis with a group of kids,
- To torment Mr. Winston.  - So says Mr. Winston. Has he any proof?
- Why would he lie?  - Because he's a crazy old man with a...
With a grudge against this school.
Perhaps he's crazy enough to do something.
He's complained plenty of times. There's never any reality to it.
Chief brody disagrees.
She thinks that some of your students are vandals,
And you're protecting them. Chief brody is a small town cop. She gets ideas in her head.
Look, the truth is that nobody around here likes us very much.
They think the kids are all drug addicts and delinquents.
They're scared. You don't mind if we sit down with some of your students
To ask them about mr. Winston's allegations?
Not at all...
As long as you follow proper legal protocol.
Of course.
Hey, hey, hey!
Agent lisbon of the cbi,
Would like to talk to you for a moment.
Let's all listen with respectful attention, all right?
Jane, they're all yours.
Hello, kids. Hey.
Uh, that's the best you got?
Hello, kids.
Hello!
Ah, thank you. Thank you.
Ahh. Who wants to see some magic?
Hands? Good.
Watch me closely.
Concentrate.
Make sure I don't do anything sneaky.
All right, this is ridiculous. Hush.
Watching my hands...
I'm gonna need a volunteer.
You.
Stand up. Come here.
Name?
Orrin.
Well, orrin, today's your lucky day.
I'm going to look into your mind,
And I'm gonna read your thoughts.
You're thinking, "gosh, I hope he can't read my thoughts,
"because then he'd know that I was up in the woods
"with justin prentiss the night before he died
Throwing paint bombs at the old crazy man's door."
Orrin, that was kind of dumb.
You should have thought of something
A little more innocent.
We're gonna have to have a little talk.
Follow me.
Sorry about that.
Tell me more about Zachariah.
- Orrin, you may ask for a lawyer at any time.  - Then my parents will know, right?
Yes.
That's okay.
Zachariah and the Z krew.
Why should I tell you? You know what I'm thinking.
Yeah. But it would be more polite
If you said it aloud for their benefit.
You can't really read minds, can you?
Shrewd insight. No, of course I can't.
Then how'd you do that, then-- call me out like that?
You scratched your poison oak rash,
And my colleagues tell me that only grows in one place
- around here-- up at Mr. Winston's.  - Fudge.
Yeah. So tell me more about zachariah.
I can't.
Really?
Orrin...
We can let this go, or we can take it to the next level.
And that's gonna involve your parents and lawyers.
Zachariah was a lumberjack...
Mm-hmm. Hundreds of years ago.
A log fell on him in the river and pinned him by the arm.
His logging crew tried, but they couldn't get him out.
The river was rising, and a snowstorm was coming.
They figured that he was done for anyway.
So they left him there-- left him for dead.
Zachariah was so angry at them for leaving him
that he chopped off his own arm to free himself,
then went back to the lumber camp
and hacked every one of his workmates to death,
then chopped them up and put their heads in trees.
Cool.
- The lumber camp where they died...  - Mm-hmm.
This is it.
Right here.
This school is the exact same spot.
- And z krew?  - It's like a secret club.
We go up in the woods and do stuff.
Zachariah is like our leader.
- Who's like the deputy leader?  - I don't know.
- No?  - Come on.
We wear masks. The only person you know
- is the person who asked you to join the gang.  - Who was that?
Bryan.
There he is.
- I got this.  - No, please. I got this.
After you.
Nice.
- Who initiated you to z krew, Bryan?  - The guy that jumped me in left last year.
- Who runs Z krew?  - I don't know.
I find it hard to believe you didn't recognize
- anybody's voice.  - There's no talking on Z krew ops.
We only communicate by note and sign language.
That's the whole fun of it. Look, z krew's about
running around in the woods, playing warriors.
Nobody gets killed.
Z krew's got nothing to do with Justin's murder.
Do you?
No!
You want my guess?
Guesswork is inappropriate for this sort of situation, Bryan.
Guesswork's okay.
Cassie.
She's in it somehow.
How so?
Justin was...
He was big in love with her.
She wouldn't deal, and he didn't like it.
I saw them arguing,
Both real mad, a couple days ago.
And now she's totally freaked out about his death.
- So, you know...  - Many of us are upset, Bryan.
- Does Cassie have a boyfriend?  - No.
So what do you think happened? Cassie killed him?
That's ridiculous.
Let him answer.
Hey... Ask her.
All I'm saying... It wasn't me.
Do you know where we can find Cassie right now?
I'm sure that she has nothing to do with this.
But I will have someone fetch her for you.
- Gave you a little trouble, huh?  - Nah.
Hey, guys.
- What happened to you?  - Old age.
Shut up, you.
- What are you doing here?  - Gee, thanks for the welcome.
- No, I mean-- you know what I mean.  - Lisbon wanted an extra hand
If we're gonna have to interview
- all the students and staff.  - Seriously? This is the biggest they had?
- Hey, Van Pelt.  - Hey, boss.
We're short a girl by the name Cassie Miniver.
Bryan says that Justin was in love the Cassie,
Recently saw them in a fierce argument.
Oh, Cassie. Yeah, she brought Maclean a cup of tea.
- Yeah. We wanted to question her, but she's gone.  - Hmm. Interesting.
- Anybody else missing?  - No, there isn't.
- So she's most likely running, not abducted.  - Precisely.
So what do you think, boss? Chief brody's setting up a full-scale search,
So we should probably start looking in the woods
- Around the school.  - Oh, that sounds horribly tedious.
Shout if you need me.
Go ahead, relax. Enjoy yourself.
God forbid you should do anything tedious.
Cassie!  Cassie!
Cassie!
Can I ask you something?
Would you-- have you ever read
Your coworker's personnel files?
Uh... No. Why?
No, uh, good. Neither did I.
Good.
Hey.
Hi.
Where are you headed?
Into town.
Excellent. That's exactly where I need to go.
All right.
Thanks. Grateful.
Would you shut the gate for me, please?
- Uh, nope.  - Why?
Well, 'cause as soon as I get out of the car,
then you'll drive away without me.
Why on earth would I do that?
The three Furies...
Fear, shame, guilt.
What?
The heart wants what the heart wants,
and it won't be denied. It makes us do bad things.
What are you talking about?
Cassie, I have a gift for you.
Cassie? Needn't be shy.
Hi.
Here.
Try it on.
Beautiful.
Ta-da.
What is this?
Mr. Maclean was helping Cassie run away.
- Why?  - He didn't want us to speak to her because...
- I have nothing to say.  - Nonsense. You have plenty to say.
He wanted her to go before we get a chance to talk to her
and find out that she and he were having
what you would call, uh... sexual relations.
Is that true?
I'm saying nothing. I admit nothing.
I want to talk to my lawyer. Cassie!
- Don't say anything.  - You miserable little pervert!
- That's enough, chief.  - She assaulted me!
I don't think so. We're going back to Sacramento.
Now you can either come of your own accord
or we can arrest you. Which is it?
Fine.
Good choice.
No. We didn't.
We... we weren't. No.
Cassie...
Look at me. It's very easy to see when you're lying.
You get a little pulse going in your neck just... there.
Yeah.
Always best to tell Agent Lisbon the truth.
Did Mr. Maclean have sexual relations with you?
It's okay.
Yes, he did.
One time or more than that?
More.
Maybe twice a week for a few months.
You know that by having sexual relations with you,
Mr. Maclean was committing a crime, right?
I guess.
Was it consensual?
You guess.
Uh, did you want Mr. Maclean to have sex with you?
No, ma'am.
So he coerced you.
I don't... understand.
I was scared.
Scared of who? Mr. Maclean?
No, he's just... a sad creep.
Who, then?
You can talk freely, Cassie. You're safe here.
Nowhere is safe.
Zachariah made you do it?
Zombie Lumber Jack made you sleep with mr. Maclean.
He told me I had to.
Cassie, you know that Zachariah doesn't exist.
You know that kid that they found chopped up in the woods?
He thought the same thing.
Okay, how... how does Zachariah tell you his wishes?
Through somebody from Zkrew, maybe?
I've said too much already.
I don't... I don't want to say anymore.
Please don't make me.
I'll be right back.
Cassie made a statement.
Charge Mr. Maclean with statutory rape.
Will do, boss.
Sex with a minor. Tell you what...
- things look very bad for you right now.  - I was kind and caring to a troubled girl.
- That... that's all.  - ... Yeah, that's what they all say...
until the lab tests come back.
See, the way we have to figure this
is that Justin Prentiss was in love with Cassie
- and found out that you were abusing her.  - Oh, please.
Abusing her, and he threatened to tell the authorities.
- So you clubbed him to death, you thought, and buried him.  - No. No!
No? Well, that's what we're thinking.
How are we wrong?
Did he attack you?
Was it self-defense, maybe?
I want my lawyer. I'm saying nothing more to you people.
We got nothing to put him with Justin that night.
We need a confession.
You won't get one.
Why won't we get one?
Prize for the first one to tell me the answer.
Just tell us your damn theory.
I will do that on our way back to Bright Arch.
We need to get there in time for the sacred fire ritual.
Rigsby, let's you and I have a quick cup of tea,
- then we'll go, huh?  - Explain first. Then we'll go.
Sacred fire?
Hello, kids.
Good to see you all again.
Pretty dramatic few days, huh?
You probably heard a lot of crazy stuff
about what's been going on.
Well...  Don't worry about it.
Life goes on.
Your teachers thought I'd be good to carry on
With the sacred fire ceremony as usual.
Everyone okay with that?
Excellent.
I thought we'd start with a ghost story.
You all know about Zachariah, yeah?
We do.
- But we don't talk about him.  - It's bad luck.
Meh.
Zachariah doesn't scare me.
So everyone knows about that terrible evening
When Zachariah hacked his former friends to pieces, yeah?
What a lot of people don't know
is what happened after that horrible incident.
As punishment,
The townspeople gathered together
And built a huge bonfire
Right here...
On this very spot.
And they burned Zachariah alive.
And as the flames melted the flesh from his body,
Zachariah didn't scream.
He just smiled at those watching.
And he made a solemn vow
That whenever someone does evil in these woods,
If you call Zachariah's name three times
And mark the ground with a "z,"
- Then he will rise from the grave and he will take them.  - Yeah, right.
And if the sinner doesn't confess his sins,
If he doesn't repent, then Zachariah will drag them down
Into his ghastly lair,
To suffer with him in black darkness
For all eternity.
That's it?
Yes, that's it.
That was weak, dude.
Well, it's only weak if the curse isn't true.
And we all know that evil has been done in these woods.
But is there anyone here willing to call Zachariah's name?
Anyone?
Zachariah!
Told you. Weak.
You forgot the most important part.
You have to mark the ground with a "z."
Guess he's on vacation.
- Elliott, was it you?  - Aah! Aah!
Did you kill Justin?
- Elliott, this is your last chance.  - Aah!
- Did you kill Justin?  - Yes! Yes, it was me!
Saved. That was close.
- Oh, hey, Rigsby.  - Hey.
I... I... I knew it was a joke.
I... I was just kidding.
No, you're a liar and a murderer, Elliot.
Everyone can see that.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, a little help here.
Give it up, kid. Come on. It's over.
Justin was an insect.
He shouldn't have interfered.
Yes. You had a sweet little system going.
You kept the kids in line with messages from Zachariah,
And you kept Maclean in line with blackmail.
Protect Elliot and let the Z crew rule,
Or be exposed as a habitual rapist.
- You're a very clever young man.  - Yes, I am.
That's why my parents abandoned me in this dump.
I'm too clever for them.
And for you.
You haven't really caught me.
I'm a minor. Nothing bad will happen to me.
Then why don't you tell us why you killed Justin?
For the record.
You know why.
Justin was always soft on Cassie.
But when he found out
What she was doing with maclean on my order...
He got angry, threatened to ruin everything.
And I tried to shut him up with a message from Zachariah.
He wouldn't back off.
He laughed at me.
He shouldn't have done that.
I don't like being laughed at.
Well, good-bye, Elliot.
H...hey.
How did you know it was me?
When Cassie brought Maclean tea in a cup with z's on it,
That was a warning from you to keep his mouth shut.
You were the first to bring forth the Zachariah story,
And you've been at this school longer than anyone else,
With no desire to leave.
The sacred fire ceremony confirmed my hunch.
Everybody else was scared that I was invoking Zachariah,
But you... you were contemptuous and cynical.
A true artist watching a cheap imitator...
Until fear made you a believer.
It can do that to you.
Bye.
Sit down.
I appreciate everything that you've done.
It's our job.
Thank yo yeah.
Oh, there he is.
Uh, here I am.
I was just telling Mr. and Mrs. Prentiss
It was you that found their son's killer.
Yes, uh, I'm very sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
We're very grateful.
It gives us some kind of closure at least.
Your son died bravely.
He saved a young girl in trouble.
You should be very proud?????«??????????????????????????????????????????
www.tvsubtitles.net