Get out
of the way.
Remember
to say please.
I can't
watch this again.
This is the dvd.
Eg.
This is
the advanced bootl
these are
the alternate takes.
What, are you gonna call coppola
with ideas on how to fix it?
I do not
believe this.
Ho!
Oh, c'mon.
The disk
is in there!
You know what scene
i love most?
"It was you, fredo."
Ton', you gonna
go see your uncle first
if you decide
to go over there?
Yeah.
That would be smart.
Fucking disk!
Somebody should tell
paramount pictures
to get their
shit together.
We're gonna be stealing
thousands more of these things.
So, how was junior
last time you saw him?
His life is about
motrin these days.
Ton', what's y
our favorite scene?
I can't have this
conversation again.
Hit eject!
Don ciccio's villa,
when vito goes
back to sicily.
The crickets,
the great old house.
Oh, it's
fucking beautiful.
Maybe'cause i'm goi
ng over there, you know?
I was in the army
signal corp.
What this thing needs
is what we call
a brogan adjustment.
What's tha
t, you know how?
Yep.
This is "1010 wins".
Ld.
You give us 22 minutes,
we'll give you the wor
temperatures are expected
to drop tomorrow
after another scorching
day in the city.
Right now it's 96 degrees
at caldwell,
laguardia's 94,
...
and it's 98 in central park
and on the upper east side
great.
It's like this
every sunday
and every sunday
you say "great",
like it's
the first time.
Could we please lo
wer the air conditioning?
I'm doing it
for godsake!
I just got this car.
I'm not familiar
with the instrument panel.
Get up out
the fucking car!
Take the car,
take the car!
Get the fuck
out the car!
You nasty bitch,
get the fuck out of here!
Smack the shit
out of you.
Go!
Okay, okay, okay!
Churchill,
churchill!
Damnit, man.
Sic'em,
churchill!
Evan, no!
Sic'em,
churchill!
C'mon,
churchill.
Churchill.
Fucking niggers.
Barry!
Who else, huh?
Who else?
West essex
orthopedic group.
Mr. Soprano?
Okay if
my nephew comes in?
He's got some
questions for the doc
about my hip and all.
Of course.
The doctor will be
right with you.
Perhaps your nephew ca
n help you with your clothes.
You want
some help?
I'm not gonna
take my pants off
until i know this pric
k is gonna x- ray me again.
Hurts like the fucking
pit and the pendulum
just t
o wipe myself.
So what do you
want to talk about?
Going over
to the other side.
See that friend of ours
over there.
On.
My car operati
lose the miserable puss,
it's mine now.
What's
your question?
Our friend, what's
he like to deal with?
What's he like?
Yeah.
I only met him
one time.
61.
He came over on
"the michelangelo", 19
now, that
was traveling.
Ne.
The fucking
italian li
the food, the service,
are you kidding me?
We had some bon voyage
party's on that boat.
He's a serious man,
zi vittorio.
Serious how?
You know
what i mean.
Heads up, sonny boy.
He don't listen to opera,
vittorio,
which is
a fucking break.
Isn't he like
a distant cousin of ours?
It's so far removed by now
tonto's a closer cousin to you.
We deal with him throu
gh a guy named furio giunta,
he speaks english.
Going to italy, huh?
Yeah.
Nt.
Nice,
i never we
it's not over yet.
And we don't
get to go?
You got school.
What about mom?
She knows
it's a business trip.
Don't you think she might
like a little interlude,
just the
two of you?
You know when we'd like
a little interlude,
just the two of us?
Right now.
Not my idea to have me
set the table.
Carm, you want me
to help with the roast?
It's right there
on the counter.
Carm, it's
a business trip.
Okay? It is,
it's not worth the jet lag.
Did i
say anything?
God!
Naples,
ri.
Ischia and cap
od.
And, oh,
the fo
it.
Sh
look, i know last year,
tom and barb,
the trip to the bahamas,
i said i didn't
have time.
You didn't.
It was football season.
Meadow, can you tell
your brother dinner's ready?
It's our
busiest months.
Junior's last shipment went
to naples two months ago.
30 containers,
two cars to a container.
Junior had to give the operation
over to who, specifically?
Ray curto.
Okay,
good work, sal.
There's something else
you should know.
They're talking like
the molitsanti kid
might get his button.
Tony, where's he a
t with junior these days?
They ain't
spoke in months.
Are you bein'
straight with me?
Oh, pussy!
What the fuck?
How's it going,
colonel?
How you doing,
jimmy?
What'd i hear,
you were in puerto rico?
I was playing there on
ce during the hurricanes,
never again,
i said.
Jimmy, let me introduce you
to a friend of ours.
This is joey
from dover,
delaware.
No shit!
I live in dover,
here, jersey.
That's right,
i forgot.
Joey, know where they got
the name dover from?
The cliffs
, i'm assuming.
That's right
, very good.
Jimmy, does it
fucking matter?
Joey, i knew this guy
when he had social graces.
It's for marisa's oldest's
sixth birthday.
The kids are all grown
, aren't they puss,
what are ya doin' here?
It's my daughter's
birthday.
I'm picking up some shit
for a bachelor party.
I'm trying to think.
Did i ever meet
any connected guys
from delaware?
That fucking box
looks heavy.
The answer is...
no, no, no.
Alright look,
i got to go fellows.
Joey.
Ou.
Nice to meet y
you, mr. Rude cocksucker,
see you around baby.
Motherfucker,
motherfucker!
Take it easy
, that went fine.
He saw me with you.
You come all the way
to a fucking party store
and still somebody's
got to see you?
Sal listen
, that went fine.
Just know this,
you're doing a good job.
You must be so relieved
pussy is back.
You must
be so happy.
Was a long time.
Did he ever tell you
where he was?
Oh, he don't like
to worry me.
Not even
a card?
That's got
to be a worry.
It's horrible.
Anyway, you must
be so happy.
We're back
to our old routine.
Ah, i lo
ve this song.
Mmm.
Oh honey, i know,
your jackie.
Listen to me, going
on about how happy
i am and you a widow.
Que sera sera.
What will be
will be.
God, he's so handsome,
this guy too.
He's blind,
you know.
Jesus christ!
Angie.
My god. I'm sure
he's adjusted to it.
Christ, you fucking idiot,
rosalie!
I'm not happy
sal is back.
Angie!
I'm sad
and depressed.
I've thought
of killing myself.
Fucking nosy?
Eat your monigott'.
God forgive me.
When he did come home that day,
i was upstairs,
i heard the door
and then his voice,
"i'm home."
I fucking wanted
to vomit.
After all that worrying
he might be dead,
praying
he was okay.
My heart just sank,
i wished--
he had died.
Oh.
To just come and go
year after year like that.
How dare he!
Have you reached
out to him?
That's a good one.
Listen,
and i don't want
my kids to know this.
They found a lump
under my arm.
Oh my god.
They biopsed it, i get
the results in a couple days.
Anyway,
i told sal,
he said,"jesus christ",
kind of alarmed a little.
Then he went back
to doin' whatever
the fuck he was doin'.
Spraying wd- 40
on his pocket knife.
Hasn't asked me
how i am.
Touch my face, or something
when he comes in.
So angie, what
are you gonna do?
Benign, malignant,
i'm getting a divorce.
Look at this place.
The mother country.
Here, they
make it real.
Vesuvius, jesus,
who's gonna tell artie
that mural he spent
that money on
looks like a used trojan
compared to this?
You notice
the women?
Know what i realized
on the plane?
Even the skanks
are worth fucking!
Those were
my feelings too.
Paison, tutto gli
whaddya call it.
..
Hey, you
did alright.
Two definite agendas i got
, hit the topless beaches
and see
that fucking crater.
I don't care what
anybody says, i'm there.
Look at
this fucking place.
It's been here
a thousand years.
Nk.
Hey t, che
ck out the ba
anthony soprano.
Ah.
Ye
hey how
are you?
This is the friend of ours
sil and me been talking to.
This is paulie
, this is christopher.
My boss nino say
you can fresh up,
maybe little sleep,
then we will will
pick you up at eight.
And he will meet us
for fare la business.
Whoa, whoa,
wait a minute.
Nino? I mean,
i never heard of--
i'm sure he's a nice guy
and everything.
But vittorio
will be there, right?
Maybe no.
Commendatori, you ar
e already checked in.
Commendatori,
like a commander,
i like that,
that's respect.
So did you hear?
You're talking about
the bonpenseiros, right?
Hang on gab, call waitin
g, it may be tony from italy.
Hello?
I didn't sleep
a wink last night,
my god,
isn't this awful?
Did you tell
franny altieri?
Ooh no, she's gonna shit
when she hears this.
What time christopher
say he'd get here?
He's got that titanium club
i wanted to give to don v.
Ow.
Any time n
he was just going down
to corso to buy a gift
for adrianna.
Nino say we always ask
your uncle for more cars,
but he was
no supplier.
Re.
That w
hy i'm he
tell him we ca
n fill any orders.
And also mention,
no offense,
we were hoping
zi vittorio would be here.
Anything you want
to talk to vittorio
about that i don't know?
No.
Nino is a little disappointed
in your attitude of him.
Mi dispiace, nino i'm sure
that i'll learn much,
doing business
with a man like you.
It's an honor.
He said--
nino is happy to be
at your disposal.
My uncle's problem was he went
to the russians in brooklyn,
rs.
Too much
for the ca
now, they kept
the best stuff
for themself,
shipped it off
to st. Petersburg.
Slovenia
and montenegro,
they got people
over there that profited
from those conflicts.
They got fuckin'
bails of liquid cash.
You got contacts
in the markets over there.
Ton', you try
this octopus yet?
I'm talking
here.
You're like
a fucking child.
With the food
and the pussy,
what's going
on here, paulie?
This is a bi
g thing to me, t.
I was never
over here, okay?
My brother was and
my other brother
the doctor was,
it.
With all
his bullsh
how mucha you
charge- a un car?
Mercedes ml series,
very popular.
In eastern europe
you can sell this car
for 110,
nd.
120 thousa
my price to you,
90 grand.
It's manufactured
in america.
What did
he fucking say?
Io.
That's
don vittor
anthony soprano.
Don vittor
io, it's an honor.
Wheelchair,
aboolebarda!
Think-- something's wrong
with the wheelchair.
He say
"wheelchair boulevard".
My name
is annalisa.
I am his daughter.
Piacere.
Piacere, tony.
Psst.
George- a washington- a,
bridge- a.
Ge.
Right, very good,
george washington brid
ub,
ton', you give
this guy a golf cl
he'll probably
try to fuck it.
I come three thousand
fucking miles,
you never said nothing
about this guy nino,
all of a sudden
he's my blind date?
Nino was in hi
de from the police
until two day ago.
I don't even think
mauro zucca now he's here.
Who the fuck
is mauro zucca?
Mauro zucc
a run this family.
Obviously,
zi vittorio.
Then i should be talking
to mauro zucca.
Mauro zucca is serving
a life sentence.
Hey you,
come here.
Re.
Yes, signo
can i just get some
macaroni and gravy?
Paulo, he doesn't
know what you says,
you mean grapes?
Uva?
Gravy, gravy,
tomato sauce.
Nino,
he's insecure.
It effects everything
he says, capice?
I will talk on the sid
e to the ear of annalisa.
What the fuck good
is that gonna do?
She is the wif
e of mauro zucca.
Camillo, where's
the pisciadood?
Down the stairs,
go left.
Ma- jor- digan
expressa- way.
Right, major deegan
expressway.
I'm sorry
if he's hassle you.
You spend a lot
of time in the states?
Papa went, i never been,
english from school,
e filmsa.
When could we
get a chance to talk?
Come to our house,
stay a while.
I will personally give you
a tour of the...
surroundings area.
Avellino?
Where your
family's from.
I don't want
to put you out.
No, you should have
been guest to our house.
But with my father
condition now.
I send you
the car at nine?
Ne.
Fi
ton'.
I look forward to it,
excuse me.
I'm gonna hoof it back
to the excelsior.
I got to take
a wicked shit.
Can you stop fucking
interrupting me?
We've been offered
a ride here,
you now how these peop
le are about formalities,
why didn't you u
se the one in there?
I didn't have
to go then.
It's just
a kid.
The kid only got
firecrackers on him.
We're gettin'
ready to eat.
Oh yeah, forgot
it was dinner time
for you.
How's italy?
The time change
and everything.
I forgot
, sorry.
How's italy?
Got to be honest
with you.
Od.
Pretty freaking go
we'll have
to come back here.
Yeah, right.
So how
's the food?
Sh.
It's okay,
lots of fi
sounds like you're
working too hard.
Ids
why don't
you take the k
down to great wall
, get some chinese?
Me.
You know tony,
don't tell me
how to spend my ti
if i want the excitement
of chinese food,
i don't need
your permission.
It's not permissio
n, it's just an idea.
You know what
? fine, i'll hang up.
Well if the trip
is as bland as
this phone call.
There's nothing
going on.
What do you want me
to say to you, seriously?
You better not say
what you saw, jimmy.
I shove that elvis shit
right up your ass.
I'll shove a rutabaga
in your mouth jimmy.
Keep you quiet.
Re.
A turn
ip in the
sal!
You're having
a nightmare.
I think it was the fuckin'
shrimp hors d'oeuvres
on the plane.
Get some immodium.
You want to get made
, this is no fucking way.
Tony wants us
to hang with nino,
work out
the dock facilities.
I hope we get
some spare time.
I'm gonna see
that fuckin' volcano.
Oh, ho
, gratzie.
Hey.
Us.
This song, jes
listen, i've bee
n to italy many times
and really, you're n
ot missing all that much.
The amount
of sexual harassment
that i was subjected to.
I went one tim
e with my friend zane.
Her, they
didn't bother,
me, they couldn't keep
their hands to themselves.
Much less the whistlin
g and the fucking hooting.
It's not italy.
Do you remember
angie bonpensiero?
Angie belfiore
married sal bonpensiero.
Right, she's thinking
of divorcing him.
Halle- fucking- lujeh!
Do you
know them?
No i don't know them
, but to be married
to a man like that.
A man
like what?
The'tude and the fucking
medieval outlook.
He is such an adoring
father though.
Three beautiful kids
they raised,
who are now from
a broken home.
Ilk
no sons i hope,
three more of his
we don't need.
He's very macho.
Macho, no, try
swaggering mama's boy,
fucking hypocrites,
shall we?
Hypocrites?
Carm, come on stop.
Just stop.
Is that how you
see your brother?
I thought we wer
e talking about angie.
I mean these o
. c. pricks especially,
with their goomahs
and their prostitutes,
emotional cripples.
And they expec
t their wives to live
like the fucking n
uns at mt. Carmel college.
It's not
that simple.
Of course not.
Madonna/whores is the full
equation i believe.
Clothes,
appliances, houses.
You are
talking about me.
About us.
No.
Carmella,
ow.
I don't kn
ce,
that a woman
of your intelligen
is content to ask so littl
e from life and from herself.
I don't know, it's none
of my business.
Marriage is
a holy sacrament.
Ay.
Ok
family is
a sacred institution.
Roger.
And you trying
to fan the flames
with richie aprile,
of all people?
Talk about
old school.
Carm, richie, because of h
is life experience in prison,
he has a sensitivity
to the plight of women.
Oh my god!
I am not even
gonna touch that one.
But you had me going
for a while there,
you really did.
Oh janice honey,
i got to love ya.
Nice shot.
I shank him.
It's
a man's club.
I'll send you
one your size.
Whole set.
So tony, you don't mind
me calling you tony?
What can
i do for you?
Well you can introduce
me to the boss.
You ca
n talk to me.
A fuckin'
woman boss?
So what
do you want?
Never happen
in the states.
Never.
Our men ki
ll each other.
All my brothers, for example,
they all got murdered.
Or they
go to prison.
Rome has a war
against us.
But our men are
in love to their mama.
So being a woman is not--
come se dic',
comes natural.
We'll i'll
be dipped in shit.
You go around like your
father's nursemaid.
I am my father's
nursemaid.
Well if an old man carries
the respect of troops,
you keep
him around.
I did something
like that myself.
We're cousins.
You hungry?
I could eat.
So, you wanted
to talk about business.
Can i ask
you a question?
We not gonna pay
the price on the mercedes.
Why do you save your
toenail clippings?
Why, you
want them?
Il,
if your enemy comes
into possession of your na
or your hair clippings,
they can make the evil on you.
I'm flattered you wouldn't
trust me with your toenails,
but can i pass without
ruining the moment?
I alread
y burned them.
Em.
Nobody gets th
commendatori.
Bon giorno.
Cocksuckers.
A lot of guys today,
they come soft
living in america.
One in five guys,
they're a fucking rat.
You can't find anybody
over there that believes
in the old ways,
keeping silent,
putting the family first.
Ys.
So you want
naples' gu
fucking clairvoyant
over here.
That way i get
guys with no ties
to anybody over there
they belong only to me,
110 percent.
What?
What do i get?
Well, you get an obvious
advantage to havin'
your guys in that end.
How much you
pay me for this man?
Pay you?
Your profitability
is gonna go way up.
What are
you thinking?
Furio to start.
Furio!
Back up,
take it easy.
I'm going to give yo
u one of my best men.
And all i get is a bunch
of numbers in air.
With all due
respect,
i think you're being
a little short- sighted
on this.
He's my cousin,
he's one of my best men.
Forget about it,
it's not going
to happen.
I'm asking
you nice.
Or what?
Hey look, i don't even
think you understand.
I want you to talk
to your husband about this.
My husband
, fuck you!
He is neve
r coming back.
So you have to fucking
deal with me!
Up your ass.
Oh, you're up.
Where's
my other belt?
You look
under the bed?
Fuck, yeah.
I just came from
the doctor's office.
Ah.
Ye
the biopsy
came back negative.
Yeah good, i'l
l be back later.
Pussy.
Ah.
Ye
what the fuck
you doing here?
I was
in the neighborhood.
That bachelor party,
they're looking
for some entertainment.
A sett',
you want coffee?
Nah,
i'm good.
C'mon, it'
s on the boil.
Ah.
Ye
boss say to tell you one hour,
manigamo, dinner.
Manigamo, i want to get
the fuck out of here.
You drive me
to the city?
Sure,
absolutely.
I have to ask.
What's it like,
working for a woman?
Whaddya
gonna do?
A woman boss!
In america
you don't have?
No.
What?
Ayy! Tony!
Tony!
Yeah, come
down to eat.
Jesus christ, is that
all your people do?
The lunch we had
would jam a wood chipper.
We need to finish
our business.
I said all
i'm gonna say.
Alright,
i'm coming down.
Vincenzo!
Indigestion,
right?
Cheers.
So what
is this place?
My father was born
in this house.
Later we m
ake the new one.
You're born here,
and your kids
are raised next door.
That's
a nice thing.
You take good care
of your father.
Do,
what are
you going
send him
to a ospizio?
Hey, listen...
this one has to stay
with until he goes
to sleep.
I'll take you
back in the morning.
Goodnight.
It was horrible
what he did.
I might as well
have fucking cancer.
So what did
the lawyer say today?
He said i have
a good case,
we're filing tuesday.
So your gonna take monda
y to think, that's good.
Monday's
a jewish holiday.
Oh.
I'm finished
thinking.
Hell, i thought myself
into fuckin' nonexistence.
Well, you ar
e not nonexistent,
ay.
And pussy does
n't see you that w
fuck what
he sees!
Not anymore,
it's what i see.
God gave me
more years, carmela.
This very morning
god gave me a gift,
and i will
use that gift.
I won't
waste it,
like i wasted
24 fucking years
with this man.
You know wha
t the church say
s about divorce.
Oh please, let
the pope live with him.
Well, what about
the kids?
Up.
They're 19, 21, and 24,
it's time we all grew
kevin is just
starting his sophomore
year at college.
Aren't you worried
he's gonna realize,
the two stayed together
waiting for him to leave?
Long as he don't
loose his privileges
at our house down
the shore,
that's all kevin
cares about.
He's so fond of his father,
that's all i'm saying.
And terry and scott
with the money problems,
and the pregnancy,
this is really the example
you want to set,
when your daughter
is struggling very hard
to keep her new marriage
in one piece?
Why you workin
' this hard, carmela?
Why?
For all of the reasons
i just said.
Because you're my friend,
i'm not even sayin' don't.
I'm just sayin'
at the very least,
you got to ask
yourself these questions.
Terri, they're not even sure
she's gonna be able
to have children
of her own.
Sal began to cry
when he heard that.
Oh, honey.
In the end, i know
you're not gonna leave him.
I know you
won't do that.
Commendatori
, bon giorno.
I'm from
america.
Hey cara mia,
on the way back
bring me one of those plums
from the breakfast tray.
Cosa?
Never mind.
I got to hand
it to ya.
Re.
Great fruit
you got he
che bell
a fruti.
Ds.
None of them
fucking steroi
come se dic'
, steroids?
Steroide.
There ya go.
Who said you're not
a great conversationalist?
Ya fuckin'
twat.
There's my little
fragolin'.
Ah- ah.
Ah.
Hey, the custo
mer is always right.
Did i say
you should leave?
You know my grandfather
was napoletan',
gran- pappa mio.
He went to america
in 1910.
Three thousand
miles.
Un ragazzo, un piccolo bambino,
all by himself.
Yep, i'm napoletan'.
Th.
Me and tony bo
some of the gu
ys are sigilian'.
Sigilian', se.
Hard- headed bastards,
am i right?
So, what part
of naples you from?
Ariani el pino.
Ariani el pino
? your shitting me!
That's where
my grandfather's from!
Ariani el pino, se'.
We come fr
om the same tow
n.
Our families probably
knew each other.
The island back there
is called progeda.
Is.
Madonn',
look at th
got to bring
my kids back here.
Show'em
all this.
In the olden tim
e the sibylla of cumae
was the second most
important oracle
after delphi.
I thought delphi
was in greece.
The gree
ks were here.
Way before the romans,
and before the greeks
there were somebody else,
and before them somebody else.
"The rulers would
come from across
the ancient world,
"to hear the sibyl's
predictions of the future.
She would sit inside
the cave inhaling gases."
I think
i dated this broad.
"Possibly volcanic
though no longer active,
"and would speak
in a voice not her own,
delivering unto them
their fates."
Let's go
into the cave.
The sibyl sat way back there,
see that shaft of light?
Some
fucking trip.
The sibyl were
very beautiful,
in most case.
Oh yeah, got
a premonition for me?
You, you're no
problem to read.
You are your
own worst enemy.
Oh, is that right?
Tell you right now
you remind me
of somebody
from back home.
Not your wife,
your girlfriend?
Oh, i got one,
to answer your question.
But no,
not her.
But, she's someone
you want to fuck.
I can tell.
Oh really.
You know, everybody's
their own worst enemy.
So maybe your
psychic power has been
overrated a little bit.
You don't want
to fuck her?
to fuck me?
Yeah, i do.
But i don't shit
where i eat.
Que cosa?
Non fare
la merdo dove...
it's bad business,
we're in business.
Not at
those price.
Alright.
You give
me furio
and i'll work down
the price of the cars to 85.
Posto,
okay.
I get more guys,
on my timetable.
75 thousand.
Okay.
Hey, thanks!
So, how the
fuck was it?
Fabulous, i fe
lt right at home.
At.
That's gre
real good
business- wise.
I feel sorry for anyone
who hasn't been.
Especially
any italians.
Someday.
Don't put it off
another second, pus.
Alright, i fucking
heard you.
Where the fuck
is christopher?
He's in the duty f
ree buying a gift for ade.
Four days, he's a block away
from the greatest shopping
district in the world.
Why the fuck didn't
he think of it then?
A broad.
An.
He found out who got
eight great tomatoes
in that little bitty c
oh fuck him,
leave him here.
Go, let's drive.
What's the matter, tony?
Nothin'.
I tell you we do
real good business- wise?
I got fuckin'
double on those cars.
Here he comes.
Hey, c'mon!
Hello, i'm home!
Captions copyright 2000
home box office
a division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.
Captioned by
hbo communications center