Our undergrad
student body at brown
only numbers
about 6, 000 people.
That's from every state
in this country
and from over 60 countries
in the world.
Admission is
extremely selective.
So, again, get all
of your academic
and extracurricular
ducks in a row.
Leave nothing to chance.
Hey, buddy.
Davie.
Saw your wife
out there alone.
I figured you
for the trotters.
Not tonight.
Had a customer
i couldn't shake.
Guy spends a half hour
deciding between
a $20 soccer ball
and a $22 soccer ball.
So, who do you like?
I don't know.
That guy from bowdoin seems to
be making some sense, i guess.
No, i mean
the game tonight.
Whoa!
You guys want
to be alone?
I saw that refreshment
table out there.
I knew you'd be lurkin
g around here somewhere.
I don't know how i always
get roped into this shit.
Charmaine's no fool.
She's knows one of your
shfooyadell in the right mouth
and her daughter can go
anywhere she wants to go.
So far, the janitor's
the only one going near them.
Well, that's a nice
career path for a young lady.
Fuck you.
I want to go get one
of them belly bombs.
Have i said
"fuck you" yet?
Freakin' delicious, artie.
Glad i didn't
eat tonight.
Thanks, davie.
It's nice to be appreciated
by your friends.
Oh, the sensitive chef.
Hey, eric,
they all done?
Yeah, i guess.
Um, dad,
can i have 20 bucks?
Are you like this?
What, did you think
he was coming over to say,
"gee, dad, thanks for
taking the time
to come to
this important event."
Ha, ha.
How you doing, eric?
Pretty good,
mr. Soprano.
You guys want
something to eat?
Ah, no, we're going
to starbucks.
I hear you're thinking
of going to brown, right?
Yeah, it's a good school.
Lot of star fucking,
though.
Hey, latrine lip...
he's right.
This jamoke'll go
wherever his mother tells him.
No different than
his old man.
You, too?
You know, in high school,
these guys were like
joe namath and y. A. Tittle.
Yeah, i've heard.
And now, they're like
phil donahue and alan alda.
Listen, uh...
i heard through
the grapevine
that you're taking over
your uncle's game.
You know,
the big one.
Grapevine.
Yeah.
You know, if you listen
close to that song,
it says believe none of
what you hear and a
half of what you see.
No, it's just,
you know me...
i like to play a little.
A little.
Forget it.
This game'
s not for you.
No, it's just, you know, i was
thinking it would be a kick.
David.
You're a nice guy,
i like you, okay.
But trust me,
this game's not for you.
I don't want to
see you get hurt.
These guys,
they play deep.
You know how many jockstraps
i sold last week.
Not enough for
this game, okay.
Forget it.
C'mon.
Let's go see what the wayo
from bucknell's got to say.
Do you want to tell me
what you're thinking?
Believe me, you don't
want to know.
You want to know
what i'm thinking?
Seriously?
I'm thinking i'd like
to take a brick
and smash your fucking face
into fucking hamburger.
Okay.
I'm not--
don't worry.
I know i broke your
coffee table and it's
not gonna happen again.
You asked, i told.
But you'd like to
smash my face.
Not really.
It's just the way of
describing how i'm feeling.
Do you think making
hamburger out of me
would make you
feel better?
Mother of christ,
is this a woman thing?
You asked me
how i'm feeling.
I tell you
And now, you're gonna
torture me with it.
I don't know who
the fuck i'm angry at.
I'm just angry, okay.
Why the fuck
am i here?
I even asked
to come back.
I got the world
by the balls
and i can't stop feeling
like i'm a fucking loser.
Who makes you feel like
a loser, your mother?
Oh, please, we wasted
enough oxygen on that one.
It's everythin
g and everybody.
I see some guy walking
down the street,
you know,
with a clear head.
You know the type.
He's always fucking
whistling like the
happy fucking wanderer.
I just want to
go up to him
and i just want to
rip his throat open.
I want to fucking
grab him and pummel him
right there for
no reason.
Why should i give a shit
if a guy's got a clear head?
I should say "a salut",
good for you.
Let's get back to
smashing my face.
Jesus christ.
Oh!
No, i think it
all ties in.
Alright.
Sometimes i resent you
making me a victim,
that's all.
I make you feel
like a victim.
Yeah.
Remember the first
time i came here?
I said the kind of man
i admire is gary cooper,
the strong, silent type.
And how all americans,
all they're doing is crying
and confessing and complaining.
A bunch of
fucking pussies.
Fuck'em!
And now, i'm one of them,
a patient.
Your parents made it impossible
for you to experience joy.
Yeah, see,
there you go again.
You said yourself you're
not the happy wanderer.
Well, i'm more like
one of those assholes
than i am the fucking
jerkoffs and douchebags
i see leaving this office.
Stop with the faces already,
what do you got?
Three eights full.
Santa maria, yes!
Santa maria.
More like fucking
santa claus.
Did you cut the pot?
Twice.
Here.
Make sure you spend it in
my restaurant, you prick.
One chip.
Ah, va'napola.
He can't even buy
mcdonalds with that.
No, no, that's it,
i got to go.
Oh, c'mon, artie,
another hour.
I can't.
Charmaine'll have my balls
on the menu tomorrow.
Cash me out.
Look at all the money.
Hey, rich,
can i get another dime?
We only got
three players left.
So, what,
vito's up for it, right?
Where the fuck
do i got to be?
Only...
let's up the ante.
Are you sure?
You're into me for
seven g's already.
Is that all?
I'll make that back
from vito in an hour.
Count this chooch
out another dime.
Well...
we have our work
cut out for us.
Gudren?
Meadow.
I'd like to talk to
you for a second.
It's really sounding
pretty good.
I know you're
disappointed, but...
it's just when you try
out for cabaret night,
the form asked,
what you want to do,
and i checked off solo.
You're seniors.
This is your last
chance at cabaret.
Gudren hasn't had
a solo in four years here.
I'd like to give
everybody a shot.
Mrs. Gaetano, i was a sophomore
when i did "spider woman".
Now, it's important
because of college and all.
You okay with this?
Do i have a choice?
Yeah, you got a choice.
You can continue
to run the game.
You know i'm under fucking
house arrest, you cute fuck.
Then take the bite
i give you and be happy.
Either way, i'm having
the executive game.
You know, your father and me
started that game
over 30 years ago.
We were talking one day about
how the credit card companies,
you know,
they work their angle.
They didn't care
what the fuck you bought
as long as you didn't
pay all at once.
They juice you to death.
And you thank them for letting
you have a card.
You'd rather be juiced
then pay all at once.
That's a certain
kind of player.
That's why we call it
the executive game.
My brother, johnny,
was one keen motherfucker.
Oh, yeah, that's why he
left us with chi- chi beans.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
Your father left livia
with a fuckin' package
that could choke
a fucking elephant.
I got to tell you?
She's like a woman with
a virginia ham under her arm,
crying the blues
'cause she has no bread.
Please...
they don't make'em
like johnny.
And keep in mind that
he paid the freight
for your uncle eckley.
That was a major
fucking nut.
Who?
Who the fuck is eckle?
Forget it.
Keep thinking
you know everything.
Some people are so far
behind in the race
that they actually
believe they're leading.
Yeah, that's cute.
Who the fuck is eckle?
Eckley, eckley.
Let's talk about
something else.
No, you opened this clam,
my friend.
Who is he?
You don't know him.
It's water
under the bridge.
Just know that me and your
father looked out for him.
He wanted
for nothing.
Fuck you, fuck eckle.
I don't got time
for this shit.
He was my younger brother.
He was between me
and your father in age.
His name was eckley.
Actually, ercoli-- hercules.
Named after
my grandfather.
What are you saying?
I got another uncle?
Sharp as a fucking
cue ball.
Yeah, i'm saying.
Your father and
me had a brother you
didn't know about.
'Cause he was...
it was different
in those days.
Mother and father didn't
even speak the language.
They couldn't take
care of a kid like that.
God bless your grandmother.
She went to every charity home
in this fucking state
till she found one
that she felt would
take good care of him.
What are you saying,
he was retarded?
Why don't you
go fuck yourself.
He was slow.
He was strong
as a fucking bull,
handsome like george raft.
If it was today, they migh
t have trained him to be a...
whatever or something.
Get him a job.
They didn't understand
these things back then.
Jesus.
What were we thinking?
Un- fucking- believable.
I remember my mother
and my father arguing about--
something, i don't know.
And, uh...
she kept talking about my
father's feeble- minded brother,
but i always thought
she meant you.
What a kick
in the balls.
When did he die?
Not long before
your father.
Past is the past,
this is the present.
Let's talk about
this game.
What's my end?
I don't know.
Ten percent.
20.
15.
Call your friends.
Let them know
the game's happening.
Can i help you
with something, sir?
Yeah, i want to buy
a boat with three propellers.
What?
Kid, you see m
e here every week.
When are you
gonna stop asking?
Ho, rich.
There a problem?
No, i'm just breaking
your kid's balls.
Like the pimp says to his'hos,
"keep'em coming."
Hey, rich.
That envelope's
two c shy.
I'll catch up on
it next week.
It's no problem.
I just got caught a little
off guard this month.
You know, i took
a second on the house,
didn't calculate
into my budget.
No biggie.
No good, davie.
It's just a stutter step.
Like i said,
it's no biggie.
The difference gets
tacked onto the principle.
And you know that.
Yeah, i understand.
Don't take
this personally.
But i don't want to see
your face at any of my games
until you're caught up.
C'mon, rich,
that's not necessary.
Kid, you think i started
this life ten minutes ago?
A guy hands you
a light envelope,
it's just the beginning,
nothing personal.
Yeah, i know,
but it's just this week--
i know.
It's just a stutter step.
What kind is that?
Brazilian snapper.
Is it fishy?
It's fish.
You know what i mean.
It's for pizziola.
Let me smell it.
You want something
or what?
Yeah, give me some of that,
enough for 15 people,
10 pounds of shrimp.
It's gonna be some
serious money there.
This is no
nickel- and- dime shit.
These motherfuckers
can play for two
days straight sometimes.
Now, once you start work,
you don't go till
the game breaks up
and that fucking place looks
like an operating room.
You mean, we're like
cleaning guys.
Oh, what the fuck
are you doing?
Something ain't right.
Fucking "a".
I just saw you put
your finger on the scale.
No, i didn't.
You pull that shit with
the old ladies, not with me,
you fucking hump.
I didn't put my finger
on the scale.
I don't believe this shit.
Where are you going?
Wrap that up.
I got to weigh it.
You got to what?
You got to rob me.
Yeah, you serve some booze,
empty the ashtrays.
Oh, oh, that reminds me.
Whatever you do, don't engage
silvio in conversation.
He can be a sick fuck
when he's gambling.
One night, he was
down like 50 large.
At some point he sneezes,
fritzi says "salut".
Fritzi neste
from hoboken?
Yeah, you know him?
No--
then shut the fuck up
and let me finish, alright.
Anyway, fritzi says,"salut",
silvio thinks he says
something else,
forget it.
For the rest of the night,
silvio's blaming fritz
i for his losing streak,
the fucking nut.
What do you
think he said?
Are you listening
to me or what?
He's a fucking nut,
who knows?
Here.
But i didn't put my finger
on no fucking scale.
Put that shit in the trunk
so it don't stink up the car.
Pay for the fish.
This guy for real
or what?
What, are we
fucking piss boys?
C'mon, let's get
the fuck out of here.
We want the room with
the stove and the refrigerator.
The efficiencies have been
booked to paying customers.
Muovono.
And the two rooms
on the sides.
We may be here
for some days.
You people are ruining
this place.
That's your father fault.
He made it
a business deal.
We want a lot
of clean towels
and the bathroom's
fresh- smelling.
I should work
for nothing?
Guernica.
You ever
suck his dick?
I make that beanie spi
n when i work his thing.
Am i right?
Don't bitch to me.
What do you hear?
What do you say?
License and registration.
How about if i give you
one of these instead.
I'm wearing a vest.
Oh, yeah?
If i shoot,
it's going in your brajol.
You're a real sick fuck,
you know that?
Danny boy.
How's your family?
Not bad, paulie.
We had to move my father
to another old folks' home--
hey, i got my own
fucking problems.
You're a fucking hard- on,
you know that?
How many times am
i gonna fall for that?
Here.
Hey, listen,
do me a favor, alright.
Your friends,
players or no,
they don't fuck
with the tourists
and the hotel guests,
keep the noise down
and no gunshots
or we got to
take the call.
Yeah, yeah.
Go play cops
and robbers.
Make it four.
Change coming.
To you.
Mike.
Hey, mike!
Matt.
Tony wants you.
Yeah, t.
Tony.
You got the macanudos?
Yeah, you want one?
Yeah, give one to me
and one to dr. Fried.
Alright.
Alright, gentlemen, frank.
Yeah, i'm in.
Me, too.
Thanks.
$400 to you, sil.
What's in the pot?
About $2400.
Too early to chase
an inside straight.
Doc.
Call'em.
Macanudos,
you want one?
Go ahead,
take a walk.
Don't let him scare you.
He's not really
a nasty fuck.
He's an incredibly
nasty fuck.
Hey, chair boy
of the board,
read your
fucking cards.
$400 to you, john.
Shakespeare
straightening out.
Paulie doesn't
have shit as usual.
And the prick doctor
may be flushing.
Put the tv trays out,
one between two players.
And put some of
this shit on them.
Don't give anybody booze unless
they ask for it, alright?
Okay.
Yeah.
I heard tony was here.
Soprano.
I'm a friend of his.
Do i know you?
Yeah, you know me.
I own "ramsey's sports
and outdoor".
Doc.
And you, sir.
Davie.
What the hell
you doing here?
Hey, i was just driving by,
i thought i'd stop
and say hello.
Some place
you got here.
Yeah, regular taj mahal.
So, have you heard
the kids, not bad?
Bad enough carmela
dragged me to that play.
If i never hear
that song again,
it'll be too soon.
The only area eric's light
in is the arts.
This performance stuff's gonna
put him over the goal line.
Most schools
he's applying to.
So, what's the game?
7 card.
Was that frank sinatra, jr.
In there?
Yeah.
He's a friend
of my uncle's.
He flies in.
Wow, this really i
s an executive game.
So, what do you think?
There's a resemblance.
No, no, no,
i mean the game.
You think i can take
these guys or what?
Davie.
This isn't
a game for you.
Oh, c'mon.
What are the chances of me
getting close to a game
like this again?
C'mon, anthony,
let me sit in just once.
I don't do business
with outside friends,
you understand.
Hey, do i have to show
your high school prom picture
to these guys?
All kidding aside,
i appreciate your position, but
c'mon, tony, i'm a big boy.
What are you holding?
I didn't really
expect to gamble tonight.
You need five g's
just to sit in this game.
Oh, c'mon,
can't you float me?
You know, short term.
Davie, don't say short
if you don't mean short.
All kidding aside.
You understand
what i'm sayin' to you?
Yeah, of course.
Hey, you don't have to
explain business to me.
I got no business
in this game.
$800.
Christopher.
Say hello to
davie scatino.
How you doing?
Give him five
boxes of ziti.
Good luck.
Okay, fella's,
make room.
New blood coming in.
So, there's a lot of money
in sporting goods, huh.
Yeah, frank,
but i tell you, you know,
nike has its stores,
the nba has its own stores.
It cuts in.
It's just
temporary though.
I got some ideas
for next year.
Hey, davie, ask the do
c what his specialty is.
Hard- ons.
I wanted him to ask.
Really?
Penile implants.
Hey, doc.
Please, i've heard
all the jokes.
Pot's right.
Sixth street,
here we come.
No help.
Mysteries abound.
Shut the fuck up
and deal, will you.
Nine of spades,
thank you.
Six clubs.
Get a broom and sweep up some
of that shit over there,
especially under
silvio, alright?
Pair of kings.
What's the bet?
$800.
What the fuck could
you possibly have?
Incredible luck.
You're telling me,
you miserable fuck.
Bet or check.
Don't rush me, sunshine.
You've been rushing me
all fucking night!
He didn't study this
hard in school.
John, please,
the bet's not to you.
Good.
Dealer controls
the game.
Thank you.
Do you fucking mind?
Jesus, do you ever
shut the fuck up?
And blow that fucking
smoke somewhere else!
What the fuck
are you doing?
Sil, take it easy.
I'm losing
my balls over here!
This fucking moron's
playing hazel.
Get the fuck
out of here!
I was just trying to
sweep the cheese away--
why?
Why now?
Leave it there.
I don't know,
i was just--
what?
Where do you get
these fuckin' idiots, huh?
Where do you get them?
He's sweeping the cheese,
i'm trying to get--
leave the fucking cheese
there, alright!
I love fucking cheese
at my feet!
I stick motherfuckin'
provolone in my socks at night,
so they smell
like your sister's
crotch in the morning.
Alright?
Leave the fucking
cock- sucking cheese
where it is!
Here, here, here.
Go ahead.
Have a good time.
$800.
Call.
Hey, why don't you go
fix a fucking dick
or whatever the fuck
it is you do.
Hey, dr. Fried, you know
about that viagra shit?
He won't quit,
this fucking guy.
Go ahead.
I heard they were
sinking a crate of it
down to the titani
c to try and raise it.
Very good, very good.
Alright, down and dirty.
Last card,
automatic $1200 bump.
Kings rule the realm.
Kings talk.
Check.
Door's wide open,
dr. Fried.
Check.
David.
He checks.
Bet $1200.
I'm gonna call.
Because you ain't
got dick.
Can i steal
this fucking hand?
I think i can.
I'll raise 12.
See, you should
have checked.
You got shit.
Now it's gonna cost
you another bet.
Call'em.
Oh, fuck.
Let's see'em, boys.
Trips.
Three deuces.
Cry me a river.
Three beautiful kings.
Flush.
You motherfucker.
You slow rolled me.
What the fuck were
you doing in that hand?
His money's good.
He wants to sail,
it's his business.
Fuck you, too.
I should have stayed
with my goomah tonight.
Hey, cheese fuck,
get me some food.
I'm so pissed.
Good morning.
Hunter just called me
and told me rachel weiss got an
early acceptance to wesleyan.
And you didn't
expect it?
No.
Think about it.
Did you ever
see her mom?
Please, i'm blacker
than her mother.
Well.
Should have mentioned
that on your application.
What time is it?
It's almost nine.
How we doing?
Slowing down.
Alright, see if they want
to close the lights.
Thanks.
Anybody want
more coffee?
Yeah, please, tony.
Put a little'buca in it
for me, would you?
Anyone want to
close the lights?
Is that a game?
He's a pisser, this kid,
is it a game?
Closing the lights means--
it means, do you want to admit
that you lost and pack it in.
Me?
No.
Alright, cut please.
Here you go.
Thank you, francis.
Coming out.
To sil, to the doctor,
how about a winner this time?
How much is he
into us for?
About 45 boxes of ziti.
What?
He grabbed another ten
while you were asleep.
He said you okayed it.
Go get that.
Look at this
fuckin' line up.
Ho, johnny sack.
Must've had free
tokens at the tunnel.
How'd you expect to make a dim
with this fuckin' stonewaller.
How did you
get in here?
Same as you.
Through the front door.
Hi, rich.
Hi, rich?
You want some lox.
I got some nice,
fresh lox.
You got some fucking balls,
you know that?
What'd i do?
I should stab you in
the fucking eye.
Hey, c'mon, rich.
Get your hand off of me.
I'll put one in your head.
Hey, don't fucking
threaten me, richie.
Don't threaten you?
I got a hard- on
for you already.
Give me a reason.
Don't let me fucking
embarrass you.
Outside now,
i want to talk!
Christopher,
get everybody a drink,
i'll be right back.
That's it, cash me out.
No, c'mon, frank, doc.
Sit down.
You know,
it's a misunderstanding,
right, richie?
No, no, tony, i'm wiped.
I'll settle up
with you next game.
Give my regard
s to your uncle.
Let me get you a little
breakfast, c'mon.
Nah, no really.
I got tickets for
the rueles- harris
fight tonight.
Oh, yeah.
Matt, thanks a lot.
Here's one
for your pal.
Cash me out,
will ya, sunshine?
Thank you,
mr. Sinatra, jr. , sir.
I shut him
the fuck down.
He comes here
and he sticks it up my ass!
What's that got to do with you
disrespecting my game?
Like you wouldn't do
anything different?
You're fucking right.
You know, tony,
i'm getting sick of this
"holier than thou" act.
And i'm not the only one.
Oh, really.
If anybody wants
to make a move...
c'mon, tony.
Don't get so
fucking dramatic.
All i'm saying
is sometimes you act
like you're in
a different business.
Now, send that
little prick out, so
i can talk to him.
No.
Do you realize
this motherless fuck
is into me for
over eight large?
He's got money
to play here?
Let him pay me my money.
Send him out.
You go home, richie.
This ain't gonna happen
to one of my players.
Everything alright?
He was pissed.
I'm gonna let
you sleep one day.
Then you're gonna
get the fuck up
and you're gonna
go get my $45, 000.
Hey, no problem.
Jesus, how about the luck
on that silvio, huh?
Why don't you
shut the fuck up?
I could use a schvitz.
You want to
go for a schvitz?
If after one day,
you don't give me every penny,
i'm gonna send somebody
down to your joint
every saturday for
five percent interest.
If you don't have it,
it gets tacked onto
the principle.
Do you understand?
Listen, tony, i had a good
run there for a while.
I should have quit
then though, huh.
So, you never told me how
your kid made out at bowdoin.
How my what?
How your daughter
made out at bowdoin.
Would you like
anything else?
No.
Tony, did i do
something to insult you?
Two days.
How'd we do?
Not finished countin',
but it's up there.
At least 80 boxes of zitis
after expenses.
Two boxes came
out of my pocket.
Fellas.
Salut.
You fuckin
g believe it?
We now run
the executive game.
Oh, yeah.
Sil, you remember
when me and you
used to look through that
crack in that painted door
while my old man and
uncle junior had it?
Yeah, i remember.
Junior was a fucking prick
even then.
He'd come out and
he'd chase us down the street.
Executive game.
Do you mind?
God.
Trying to get some sleep,
i've been working all night.
How you doing, eric?
Pretty good.
Sounds good.
Thanks.
Are you awake now?
Yeah.
Good.
Close the door.
Hey.
Where's your mother?
The store.
Oh, aunt barb called.
Uncle tom'
s father died.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Tom, sr.?
When?
I don't know.
What the hell happened?
The guy's here almost every
christmas eve, you don't ask?
Somebody says,
"joe blow died,"
normal people ask,
"how? What happened?"
Jesus.
This gust of wind comes,
knocks him off the roof.
All for a satellite dish.
That's very sad.
Yeah.
How old?
65.
Guy works his whole life,
takes care of his family,
does the right thing.
One day after he retires.
One day.
It's freaky.
Carlos casteneda said,
"live every moment
as if it were your
last dance on earth."
Who the fuck listens
to prize fighters?
Ali, maybe.
He had a little wisdom.
Well, at least tom, sr. Isn't
the happy wanderer anymore.
What the fuck is that
supposed to mean?
He got his.
You don't have
to pummel his ass.
He's joined the ranks
of the unlucky.
Maybe you know what you're
talking about, but i don't.
Found out i ha
d another uncle.
A retarded uncle.
My father's brother,
that nobody told me about.
You believe this shit.
Was he seriously
developmentally disabled?
Serious, no, he had everybody
in stitches back then.
Now that you found
out that you have a
retarded family member,
do you feel better
about coming here?
What?
Is it permissible now?
Is it enough of
a sad tragedy
that you can join
the rest of the douchebags?
I was just talking to him
a couple days ago.
Yes, he was
a wonderful man.
We're here
for you, barbara.
Va f'ancula tu.
You knew we were bound to
see them at some function.
Just relax.
Oh.
Fuckin' betty davis
back there.
No scenes.
Oh.
C'mon, get up,
we're leaving.
Thank you, god.
I will fucking
kill you!
We paid our respects,
now, we're leaving.
This may come as
a surprise to you,
but these people
are not here
to see the sopranos
kill each other.
Now, show respect
for tom's father,
will you, please?
Hi, carm.
Hi, richie.
Do i give the boost
to your sister?
C'mon, i gotta
give mine too.
How you doing?
I'm sorry.
Appreciate it.
How many rooms
this place got?
It's a big joint.
Pretty good racket.
I don't think you
can smoke in here.
Who's gonna complain, huh?
Him?
Hey.
You mind?
He don't mind.
Listen, anthony, i'm sorry
about blowing up in your game.
You were out of line.
What am i supposed
to do with you?
What?
Back off and respect the title,
you fucking jerkoff.
It's your ball.
You make the rules.
No, no.
I don't make'em,
they've always been there.
Now, you get this.
David scatino doesn't
pay you a fuckin' penny
until i get mine first.
That's the tax you get for
raising your hands in my game.
I get mine first,
then you get yours.
That's the way
it's gonna be.
I don't do something,
how's it gonna look?
If everyone could please
take their seats,
we are about to begin.
In the name of the father
and of the son
and of the holy ghost, amen.
Since it has pleased all mighty
god to call back our brother
from this life to himself,
we commit his body
to the earth,
that it may return to that
from which it was made.
Christ was the first to
rise from the dead...
i'm just saying,
i don't think you should
take any shit from him.
I heard you
the first time.
Let's drop the subject.
Alright.
Tony put me back
in action.
He gave me 50 g's
to put out on the street.
What is that, nothing?
Please, i know
how things work.
Don't forget, i wa
s daddy's little girl.
What the fuck are
you talking about?
You're his responsibility.
He didn't do you
any favor.
When my father was
in tony's position,
he gave romeo martin $50, 000
when he got out of jail.
I'm talking about
30 years ago.
Today, that's half
a million dollars.
$50, 000, hmm...
mailmen make
more than that.
So, what's this fucking
doctor's appointment you had
all of a sudden when
my friend comes
to see you, huh.
What do you think?
I'm still the kid
on the school bus.
Please, tony,
i'm doing my best here.
I fucked up, okay.
I'm gonna make it all work
out somehow, i swear.
What do yo
u got for me?
I'm tapped.
Stand up.
Why?
'Cause i just said so.
Get up.
Get up or i'm gonna ri
p your fucking head off.
Get up.
C'mon.
I'm sorry, tony, i wouldn't
do anything to insult you.
Our kids go to the same
school together.
Ah!
Tony, i'm sorry, i'm sorry,
i'm just having some bad luck!
Yeah, it just
got worse.
I'm gonna come back.
My luck's gonna change.
Tomorrow.
I want something tomorrow,
you understand me?
Whoa, david.
Hey.
Where's the wife?
She's home.
Can i talk to you?
You alright?
Sit down.
Talk to me.
I got myself
in a little bind.
Jesus, i feel ashamed.
What's going on?
What happened?
I'm in a jam,
artie, a bad one.
This could cost me big,
my marriage, my business.
Alright, alright, relax.
I'm sure there's
something we can do.
What kind of jam?
Oh, jeez, you didn't
knock up that tae- bo broad
you had working,
did you?
God, no, artie.
Talk to me,
i'm your friend.
I need money.
Money, artie.
Not much, just...
i swear on my kid,
i'll get it back to yo
u before you even miss it.
How much money
we talkin'?
Not much, just enough...
to give me
some breathing room
till i can get
the rest together.
It's $20, 000.
Davie.
Shit.
Bad timing.
Man.
You're not gonna
believe this.
I got to put a new roof
on this place.
God forgive me
for sayin' this,
but did you consider
chapter 11?
I don't think tony
soprano's gonna buy that.
Tony.
Oh, jeez, davie.
Jesus christ.
Eric, give me
your keys.
Why?
There's mud al
l over the tires.
Dave, what's wrong?
Say good- bye
to your truck.
What?
Dave.
This is bullshit.
Eric, eric,
get back in the house.
I warned you.
No off- roading,
i gave you enough chances.
Dave, this is
not the place.
Dad, i didn't
do anything.
Eric, accountability
is everything.
Off- roading!
I drove it onto
the field at school
to bring some girls to
cheerleading practice.
There's mud al
l over the doors!
I warned you
and warned you, eric.
I didn't do anything!
I didn't do
anything, mom.
Eric, get in the house!
I fucking hate
all of you!
You apologize right now.
Jesus.
Open'em.
I knew it was a car.
It's a sports
utility vehicle.
You like it?
This is eric's jeep.
Oh, my god.
Is this eric scatino's jeep?
Yeah, but it's
yours now.
His dad sold
it to you?
Yeah, you know.
Something like that.
What do you mean,
something like that?
You know.
Jesus, tony.
She don't want it, fine!
Don't take it!
But i'll eat it
before i give it back.
What am i, a sucker?
What does eric have to do
with his asshole father?
He didn't do
anything to you.
The guy owed me money,
and he did the right thing.
He offered that car up
as partial payment.
Yeah, right.
You see this?
You see,
this is you talking.
I just hope you know
his wife is very close
to the brother- in- law
of a provost at georgetown.
The who?
Oh, great.
Go ahead, you want to act
"holier than thou"?
You go right ahead,
but i'm not giving it back.
I'm gonna take that car
and sell it to pussy
and i'm gonna buy clothes
and food and shoes
and cd players and all
the rest of the shit
that i've been buying since
the day you were born.
Everything this family has
comes from the work i do.
Alright, tony,
that's enough.
A grown man made a wager.
He lost.
He made another one.
He lost again.
End of story.
So, take that
high moral ground
and go sleep in the fucking
bus station if you want!
Oh, jesus.
Where?
A few rows back.
Tony...
almost didn't make it.
Where's janice?
Didn't i see those at
the wake the other day?
That's funny.
They're behind.
I'll see you
after the show.
Just keep
thinking "meadow."
Eric, c'mon,
let's talk.
You're gonna
leave me here.
I thought you
were my friend.
I am.
I can't stop my dad
from selling it.
Yeah, well,
your dad's a fucking asshole.
You know that?
He's a real low- life
fucking asshole!
And i suppose yours is
innocent in all this.
For your information,
he gave it to my dad.
It's not like
my dad stole it!
You know what, meadow?
Fuck you, fuck your gangster
father and fuck this!
Welcome, everyone, to verbum dei
high school's "cabaret night."
As we are recording
tonight's performance,
we'd like to
remind everyone,
please, no talking,
no pictures or videotaping.
And please remember to turn off
those pagers and cell phones.
If you're worried
about coughing
and feel a nice
lozenge might help,
may we suggest that now would
be the time to unwrap it
as opposed to
during the performance.
A program note:
In the second act,
"sun and moon"
to performed by eric scatino
and meadow soprano
has been canceled.
Regretfully, mr. Scatino will
not be performing tonight.
Instead miss soprano
will perform a solo, singing,
"my heart will go on",
the theme song from "titanic".
Enjoy the show.
Well, that's a lucky break.
I wonder what happened.
Captions copyright 2000
home box office
a division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.
Captioned by
hbo communications center