Stop!
What are you doing?
What are you doing
, you closing me up?
Mister, where do you
suppose you are going?
Stop!
I demand you stop!
I demand you come back here
this instant!
This instant, you motherfucker!
You motherfucker!
Motherfucker!
Yeah.
Zanone brothers.
This fuckin'
series, huh?
Your driver,
he comes here,
he dumps the garbage
all over the place!
He did, huh?
What "he did"?
How about
those nets, huh?
You come
get it know!
Get what, sir?
The goddamn,
goddamn garbage.
We thought you
wanted it back.
What?
The raghead
from the deli.
Hello,
where are you?
You called yesterday
to complain?
That's our policy,
it's written on our trucks.
Double your garbage back
if you're not satisfied.
I complain because you
didn't make full pickups
on 12, 16, 20th.
And then i get
charged double for it!
Right, we had to
come out twice.
You charge me double
for pickups you miss?
My dispatcher asked you
if you're not satisfied
did you want
your garbage back?
Of course i don't
want garbage back.
Then you're satisfied.
You are speaking
shit to me.
We'll try to send
a truck out tomorrow.
What are we talking,
eight to ten?
For godsake alan, i can plea
him out of three to five.
Alright, talk to mike gendler,
see what he says.
What's all this?
You looked thirsty
last time i saw you.
Oh yeah, you know what?
I knew i left this someplace.
New?
Ah you know,
keeping busy.
Carmela, the kids?
Good.
You know,
school shit.
You bet that
game last night?
Yeah.
What do you think
i need this for?
So what do i
owe you, counselor?
You'll pay me when i actually
have to do something.
Let's hope that fuckin' day
never comes, right?
It almost did
very recently.
Here we go, the neil mink
lecture series.
We'll isn't it fair to say
we were staring into the abyss?
A very close call, that brush
with a murder beef.
I told you
i was home alone.
You and macaulay culkin.
Except that neither one
of you would have been alone.
Champagne's nice.
But you want
to give me a real gift?
Insulate yourself
from these shenanigans.
I told you
once already.
I do.
I am.
What the fuck
you want from me?
Use one of the businesses
we've got you in,
for something besides
showing income on a tax return.
Spend time
at garden state rendering.
Oh please, you know what
boiling fat smells like?
You have an office
at barone sanitation.
Get your ass out of that
strip club and go there.
Alright, i hear you.
The feds are
a business, anthony.
Millions of tax dollars
invested in watching your ass.
Sooner or late
r just like you,
they're gonna want a return
on that investment.
Mother of fucking mercy.
What'd you take
a sledge hammer to my balls?
That's just the incision
where i inserted the stent.
You're gonna feel
a little tenderness.
Okay, almost there.
Easy.
You should use
the bedpan next time.
I'm not a cat.
I don't shit in a box.
You have to watch
your heart.
My heart's fine.
When i get out of here
we're going to a discotheque,
you and me.
Discotheque.
What's so funny?
Mr. Soprano.
I'm michael mcluhan from
the u. S. Marshall service.
Here to reattach
your electronic bracelet.
They you give you
the important jobs, huh?
Excuse me.
Your name's really
mcluhan?
Right.
So that makes you
marshal mcluhan.
That's right.
What?
What's the fucking joke?
Alright, you may feel
pressure in your chest.
That'll go away
as the blood flow
to heart increases.
Just stay in bed,
plenty of fluids.
Get you home tomorrow.
Lucky fucking me.
Sandwich
or something?
Did you hear me with my balls,
who can fucking eat?
...new york's only
classic rock station, q104.
What are you
looking at?
Nothing.
Just looking
out the window.
Gettin'
my eyebrows done.
Remember...
one mouth, two ears.
Listen
to each other.
I'll see you next week.
Okay.
So, what's up?
I don't know,
i'm...
i'm bored
or something.
I don't want
to come here no more.
Well...
not the first time
we've heard you say that.
No offense
but let's face it,
this is starting to feel
like a waste of time.
I'm sure for
the both of us.
I don't feel that way.
Like the other day
i'm watching this movie
with brad pitt and
that blonde, gweneth paltrow.
"Sliding doors"?
Fuck no,"seven".
It's a good movie,
and i never seen it before.
But halfway through it,
i'm thinking, this is bullshit.
A waste of my fucking time.
Why do i give a shit
who the killer is?
What difference
is that information
gonna make in my life?
Very true.
So i shut it off.
Good for you.
What did you
do instead?
I went out in the yard
and burned ants
with a magnifying glass.
A little sense
of humor here.
What's the matter?
You still in mourning over
the coming of managed care?
Go on.
What's the point?
You go to italy,
you lift some weights,
you watch a movie.
It's all a series of
distractions'til you die.
I hear
depression talking.
Yeah well, i'm not
up on my dosage.
Medication
, medication,
medication, what do i
got to show for it?
Who knows where you'd be
without the medication?
Anyway, some people take
pleasure in the simple
doing of things.
Yeah well, the things i
take pleasure in, i can't do.
Currently trying
to change my business profile,
if you kno
w what i mean.
So it's all about
your legal problems.
I'm gonna
get the car.
Don't disappear,
meet me out front.
Corrado?
I thought that was you.
Catherine...
romano.
Catherine.
Mr. Soprano, you have
to stay in a wheelchair
until you leave the building.
Hospital rules.
So call a cop.
A little procedure,
you'd think that they'd
worry about the sick people.
It's all about
the insurance.
You remember my chuckie?
Little chuckie,
you drove the bike
for the butchers.
I got to call karen, ma.
He's a cop now
, like his father.
A detective.
He's a good egg, your lou,
a real straight shooter,
he had a lot of class.
Hodgkin's, no?
It's been
almost 15 years.
That long?
The week
the shuttle exploded.
The pension helps.
The grandchildren.
You look good, corrado.
You healthy?
A little heart trouble,
nothing much.
You broke your ankle?
Bunions.
You still
in belleville?
Same house,
watsessing avenue.
I'm right on ampere parkwa
y near our beloved alma mater.
Maybe we could
have coffee.
Catch up.
There's an ihop
by the dry cleaners.
The doctor says i'm not
supposed to leave the house.
Too much stress.
Sir.
The chair.
What the fuck, i don't
show up for eight years,
all of a sudden you turn
my office into a storeroom?
No, i'm gonna get
this shit cleaned right out.
Connie!
This is mr. Soprano.
Tony.
How ya doing?
Connie desapio.
What happened
to diane?
A little self indulgent when
it came to office supplies.
Connie, mr. Soprano's
been out the in field,
but he's gonna be spending
some time with us here at hq.
So let's get ralphie
in here and danny too.
And let's move these
boxes out, the books.
What should
i do with them?
I don't know,
make room.
I'll put them
by the copy machine.
Nice rack.
Born- again christian.
Oh yeah?
Listen, while
i have you here,
we may have
a little problem.
Richie aprile.
Yeah i know,
i heard.
He tipped a truck
at a deli in nutley.
That fucking guy.
But that's not it.
One of zanone's drivers,
the illustrated man.
Richie's got him
running an operation,
selling blow
along the routes.
Now the department of sanitation
i can handle, tony.
But if the d. E. A. Gets involved
we're gonna lose our 901.
Sonofa- fuckin'- bitch.
I'm sorry, i don't like
to break your balls.
You know that piece of shit's
gonna be my brother in law?
Nice, huh?
The rico act, elliot.
We sat there and we talked
about the fucking rico act.
You treat
different patients.
Your base
of knowledge expands.
Two years ago i thought
rico was a relative of his.
Cards- on- the- table time.
How's the drinking?
I don't know.
Worse, i guess.
Are you an alcoholic?
I am drinking
in between sessions.
That's very serious.
Just on the days
that i see him.
I can't take it.
Finally, thank you.
Are you taking steps
to seriously end it?
He wanted to end it.
He said last time
he wanted to stop coming.
But i talked
him out of it.
Why?
If i was at sloan and
he had a pituitary tumor,
would i stop
him from coming?
Elliot, it's like that thing
with watching a train wreck.
I'm afraid and repulsed
by what he might tell me.
But somehow i can't stop myself
from wanting to hear it.
Okay.
All set.
It'll ramp up
to eight pounds per cubic inch.
Keep your airway open
when you're sleeping.
I don't snore.
Ah, don't be embarrassed.
Obstructive sleep apnea
is serious.
Every time your airway
closes down and you wake up
fighting for breath,
it puts tremendous strain
on your heart.
Dr. Schreck is absolutely right
in prescribing this for you.
Makes me look
like a sick man.
You're not sick.
But testing shows rem- wise,
you have 40 arousals per hour.
More since i met you.
Such a thing to say.
Arousals mean a change
in your stages in your sleep.
You are such a flirt.
I'll stop by tomorrow okay?
See how you did.
Be counting the beats.
Who's that?
Judge crater,
how should i know?
The one who ordere
d the house arrest?
Answer the door,
it's a goddamn expression.
I'm gonna go
wash my hands.
Hello, i'm catherine,
a friend of corrado's.
Fuck me.
Oh catherine,
what a surprise.
I would've called,
you're unlisted.
I brought manicott'.
How's your foot?
It's better, thanks.
Heart?
Better.
Is this a bad time
for a visit?
Actually, the nurse
just got here.
We were about to
have my examination.
Oh well,
maybe friday then.
I volunteer at the bingo
since louis past.
Well...
enjoy the manicott'.
Thank you,
i will.
You're awful.
Neighbor lady,
she went to school
with my older brother.
I'll see ya tomorrow.
What did you send
that lady away for?
I thought you were bored.
Talking to that
dreadnought would help?
She seems alright.
What the hell would
we have in common?
Bunion, you know how
i feel about feet.
Look at this.
You believe this one
with the cleavage?
Finger food is better
than last year.
It's not the landfill,
the problem is the limit.
Right know we're
at two grand a day,
but with dos breaking our ball
i got to fuck with ins and outs.
Oh yeah, what's that?
The paperwork,
you know?
List the gross tonnage.
I got to file it
in triplicate every day.
Right.
How ya doing?
Is that your wife,
dickie?
Yeah, c'mon,
i'll introduce you.
I'm getting
engaged myself.
Hey some place, huh?
That landscaping
is gorgeous.
Janice, you're
completely transformed.
What can i say?
You look good, janice.
You look
pretty good, janice.
You are a giant asshole,
you know?
C'mon.
...nirvana.
You got a minute?
Jesus christ,
let me get a drink.
Naw, we'll grab
a waiter, c'mon.
I'll see you.
Excuse me ladies.
Have you met
helen barone?
Hi, jan soprano.
Nice to meet you.
Got any blow?
What?
Blow, you know coke.
What, you don't
keep it on you?
I got to go
to the deli in nutley?
Tony.
You don't sell that shit
along those routes,
you understand me?
I'm working
with junior on this.
I don't give a shit
if you're working with walmart,
knock it the fuck off.
Trying to earn here,
we're saving for a house.
You got enough in your plate
just picking up garbage.
Not if you and
that fucking association,
and that cocksucker barone
don't let me expand.
Are you fucking
stoonad or what?
After five years.
The cops are finally
leaving garbage alone.
A drug bust on one of
those routes is different story,
you got the fbi, the d. E. A. ,
those fucking pricks
are gonna be breathing
down our necks again.
It's only coke.
What is the big deal?
You and my uncle,
you want to deal drugs,
that's your business.
You do it on
association garbage routes,
it's my fucking business.
It stops today,
you got it?
Don't give me your
fucking manson lamps,
just fucking stop.
Another thing, don't tip
a truck on a problem customer.
I fucking hate the way
you make me fucking ride you.
Now get the fuck
out of here.
...municipality
went private,
so now we're
bidding on a landfill
down in west virginia.
I started reading
the epa's new guidelines,
on curbside recycling.
I'm telling you,
listen, i'm telling you.
Just liste
n to me, guys.
I got it right through
the transfer station.
And listen to this, it
scaled out at nearly 3, 000 tons.
3, 000 tons.
...talking about instituting
a yard waste ban,
in half the states
on the eastern seaboard.
Oh.
Oh my god, tony.
Call an ambulance.
Jesus christ.
Turn him over,
carmela.
Tony.
Watch his head
, watch his head.
The pills,
the analysis.
You pay her a fortune,
what is she doing for you?
Will you leave me
the fuck alone?
If it was a man
you'd ring his neck.
I got a fucking rash now,
last a week or two.
Leave me alone.
Putting a wing
on her house.
Mr. Soprano.
I have your results.
Yeah.
Just preliminary, but as far
as i can tell, it's...
nothing physical, right?
For chrissake,
i just passed out,
if it's nothing physical,
then what the fuck
is wrong with me?
I would think
you'd be relieved.
I'll be relieved when
somebody puts their finger on
whatever the fuck it is
that's wrong with me.
I wish it was physical,
so i can have it
ripped the fuck out.
I'm sorry, it's just
very frustrating,
i know you're only
trying to help.
You know, losing
some weight wouldn't hurt.
Shit.
Did you get
the lady fingers?
Nah, they were out.
I got crumbcake,
the entenmann's.
Disposal again?
Leave it,
i told you, i gotta
get the flange.
When, st. Smithen's day?
Who was at
the door before?
That lady from
the other day.
Catherine?
The one with
the manicott'.
I said you
were sleeping.
Why didn't
you wake me?
Roberta sanfilippo
didn't call back, did she?
I got to be honest,
junior,
when i ran into her at
fountains of wayne that time,
she was very cold.
What was she buying?
Fountain,
kid pissing.
Must've bought a house.
Great ass.
Jesus.
Talk too much, but
what a piece she was.
And game as they come.
Listen, i'm gonna go.
Got to take
my kid to karate.
No i read it, i did.
That's it,
that's the way of life.
But in "angela's ashes" you
were laughing with him at least.
Every paycheck
squandered on alcohol.
Please, you know
the irish and their liquor.
The "weakness"
he calls it, right?
How he can make such
heartache funny is beyond me.
My god,
with that father?
It's true, we don't know
what poverty is in this country.
Did you feel in this one
the mother came off
a little nicer?
It's all
in the writing.
It's like he makes
certain choices about
how he is going
to portray people.
Like the nuns
in that convent.
Please, catholic school here
wasn't any better.
He used to be
a school teacher, you know.
Some school
in manhattan.
My god, the way
he treated that wife.
She'd be better off
if he beat her.
Hello.
Yeah t, it's me.
Hey.
Listen, that
container came in.
From the other side.
Supposed to
go to that guy...
great,
about fucking time.
It's better than she said,
it's un- fuckin'- believable.
It's all original
world war ii shit.
You're fucking
kidding me.
I know nothing!
Nothing!
I'm looking at the fucking
history channel here.
You got to
come down here.
You'll love this stuff.
Nah.
We got eisenhower's
dinnerware
from allied headquarters
in london.
We got a couple
of herman goerings personal
pearl handled lugers,
and get this...
we got the jeep that patto
n drove around in, in sicily.
We have ways of dealing
with you mr. Soprano!
Aaaah!
Put that thing down.
Put that down,
it's expensive.
No, i better
listen to the lawyer.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
You guys go ahead
without me.
Alright,
talk to you later.
Alright.
How'bout a mystery?
The mystery
is that rosalie read...
what? I liked it.
What about something like
"cider house rules"?
Yeah, but not so sad.
So, how's that
english class going?
Comparative literature,
whatever.
Comp lit
was last semester.
I told you i'm taking lacan,
deconstructive theory.
Ooh, deconstructivist,
excuse me.
Incredible,
they could care less.
This is delicious.
And your grandfather
a contractor.
Deconstructivism.
Ah.
My droll mom.
Excuse me, could you
move your cigarette?
Pardon me?
It's blowing
into my son's face.
Thank you.
We're allowed to smoke.
Unfortunately an area where
new jersey is woefully behind,
but could you move it?
Mom, it's no big deal.
It's no big deal
to move it either.
I don't think so.
I'm sorry?
I'm not
gonna move it.
Why not?
Because you're very rude.
I said excuse me,
quite clearly.
Your tone.
It's a health hazard,
move it.
No.
I'm a physician,
do you know what you're
doing to the rest of us?
My son has taken the trouble
in his own life,
to live in
a smoke- free dorm.
My salutations.
Mom.
This isn't
a smoke- free restaurant.
Look, this is silly, could you
just move the fucking thing?
Not when you
talk like that.
Just move
the cigarette, please?
No.
No?
Mom!
Well?
You bitch.
She must be drunk.
Excuse me,
what did you say?
Ma'am, c'mon.
I saw what happened
let's just, shall we?
Will you
call the police?
I don't think that's warranted,
but ma'am--
oh no, please,
call the police,
because i'm not the one
with a lethal weapon here.
Ma'am, i'd like
you to leave.
C'mon jason.
I'm outta here.
Hello.
In here.
Uncle jun'?
In here,
the kitchen!
Where you been?
I've been calling you
all afternoon.
My fucking hand
is stuck down the drain.
And i can't reach
the fucking phone.
Good thing i'm nice,
'cause i can start tickling you.
Jesus christ.
How long you
been standing there?
Six hours!
Now get the fucking detergent
and lubricate my wrist.
Motherfuckin'
sonofabitch.
I thought
you were bobby.
Why didn't you
just call a plumber?
With what,
my fucking toes?
Relax.
Let it go limp.
Limp, you're flexing!
Limp.
That's it,
you're flexing.
Limp, that's it
simmer down.
Simmer down.
Easy.
Oh, jesus
fucking christ.
Oh, this fucking house.
I'm dying here.
Just take
it easy, okay?
You're coming to
the engagement party
at least, right?
We'll special
permission.
I'll make
some coffee.
I don't give a shit
if you do or you don't.
It's light.
You got your nephew
to thank for that.
What do you mean?
I ran into him the other day
at the garbage man's ball,
whatever
the fuck it is.
He said we can't sell coke
on the route anymore.
What?
That's what he said.
I guess nobody
should eat, but him.
You should have seen him
in the golf outfit,
he looked like
wallace beery.
Where does he
get the effrontery?
He's the boss.
Whether he has
grand mals or not.
And this shit
is okay with you?
I know how much
you love him, jr.
I don't want to say
anything disparaging.
You know how it is
, they're bureaucrats,
they nit, they pick.
It's passive- aggressive,
pure and simple.
They have their lives,
themselves.
I know, i know,
they're not out in the field.
What can i do
? it's mandatory.
Okay, hold on.
Connie, get me the paperwork
on the separation requirements
for new jersey.
Where is it?
I don't know, i put them
with the recycling files.
Can i get
you something?
Coffee?
No.
No, i'm alright.
I'll be going home soon.
I embarrassed my son.
How's he supposed
to know,
where this type
of behavior is coming from?
Think it's time you considered
a 12- step program?
I'm not an
alcoholic, elliot.
Besides i have you, this.
Therapy isn't a substitute,
you know that.
I won't drink
with my son anymore.
We're bargaining now?
I'll go
to a meeting.
I'm also
prescribing luvox.
Luvox?
Is for ocd.
Among other things,
i've had success
with it treating other
compulsions as well.
Compulsions?
Elliot, c'mon.
You're patient,
jennifer,
your inability to bring
the therapy to a conclusion.
Elliot, i honestly believe
that he's not ready.
Refer him
to another doctor.
You really think
that i'm--
obsessed?
Luvox.
Jesus christ.
That coke provides
a nice income stream.
Do you have any ideas
the bills i got?
Just keep it away
from the garbage routes.
The lawyers, the doctors,
the prescriptions,
a double sawbuck
for a plastic pillow,
just so i can
sit comfortably.
Why don't you just sit on that
nice pile of cash you got?
My finances are nobody's
goddamn business.
And that garbage
is my business.
I don't want you and that
other shit- bird fucking it up.
Your business.
Yeah, why don't you get that
true that bald dome of yours?
Why does everything
have to be so difficult?
You know, back in the'50s
we worked together.
Even rival families settled
their differences, amicably.
Oh yeah, i remember that picture
of albert anastasia lying there
all amicable
on the barbershop floor.
There were exceptions,
i'm just saying.
Oh i'm sorry,
should i come back?
It's alright.
We're done here.
Bad night
last night, huh?
Let's see if we can't
get you a more comfortable
fit on this mask.
That little cupcake,
she never came back.
The one with the mask.
Tracey?
Sent her a bottle
of shalimar.
She never mentioned it.
You should
be happy at least,
the stent was
a complete success.
Let's not tempt fate
by taxing the heart.
How many migs
you shoot down last week?
Where's that
fucking manicott'?
It's gone.
Half a fucking
tray in there!
I was hungry.
Sonofabitch.
It's not my fault
you got your hand caught.
Why do you have
to be so nasty?
Directory assistant,
what listing?
Belleville, i need a number
for a catherine romano.
Thank you,
for what city?
Cocksucker, belleville!
Please hold
for an operator.
Any allergies,
shellfish, perhaps?
No, i eat shrimp
all the time.
Msg? Any change
in medication?
No.
A new laundry detergent,
something like that?
I don't know,
i don't think so.
Have you been under
any undue stress lately?
Is that the only word
you people know?
Sometimes pressure can result
in contact dermatitis.
Oh is that what
that is?
See know i knew
that was bad.
It means rash.
Look at it,
it's bleeding, for chrissake.
You've been
scratching it.
You said you work at
a sanitation transfer station.
Dollars to donuts,
you're being exposed t
o an irritant in the air.
I sit in an office.
I'll write you a scrip
for cortisone cream.
Dr. Cusamano says you've
been seeing a psychotherapist.
So?
I suggest you talk about
stress management with him.
To tell the truth,
i was surprised
to hear from you.
I was sorry we
missed our visit.
I had the feeling
you weren't interested.
No.
I stopped by the other day
but i guess you were out.
It was odd.
I thought i heard
you hollering.
Funny how life works.
The different paths.
Yeah.
All leading
to the cemetery.
Can i ask you
something, corrado?
Was my lou ever...
you know,
on the take?
No, of course not.
Why would you ask
such a thing?
Sometimes you know,
i'd find money.
Hundreds of dollars, cash,
in his pockets at night.
Probably won it
at the racetrack.
You think so?
Sure, why not?
Somebody has to win.
Well the kitchen needs
some work but, you know,
a little marble,
maybe some new fixtures.
It's nice.
You think he'll come
down on the price?
I don't know.
Tony,
it's your sister,
would it kill you to
take a little interest?
I'm here,
ain't i?
Sorry we're late.
The paper says
fox hill lane,
she takes me
to stag trail road.
Not bad, huh, carm?
Oh, wow.
If we have kids, ma's house
is just not big enough.
And like tony says,
it's not our house anyway.
Come here, you gotta
see this bedroom.
You can make a den
out of the closet.
Talked to my uncle
the other day, rich.
Yeah, i heard.
So we're clear on this
drug shit, right richie?
Now the reason i'm asking you,
850 grand's a pretty big nut.
I don't know
if your parole job
at the fish market's
gonna cover it.
Tell me about it.
These walls,
skim- coat.
Not that plain
sheetrock shit.
They put in a lawn
this year, it's new.
When did you
put your lawn in?
Richie.
This is a great
school district.
Are you alright?
I got to go.
What's the matter?
Nothing, just--
i feel hot.
Oh my god, your all clammy,
let's get you home.
No, no, you stay with them
and help them.
I'll see you later.
Oh, you poor bastard.
Hey tony,
you got a minute?
Yeah, sure,
what's up?
What are you doing?
Organizing
a basketball pool,
for the people
in the office.
Yeah sounds great,
should be fun.
Yeah.
I got a call from
a friend of mine in nutley.
Guy's a cop.
They got richie's
driver on video.
He sold three ounces of coke
at an arcade down there.
It's alright,
i talked to richie.
This was last night.
Guess we'll have to
torch a truck or something.
Oh, but you don't
want to hear that.
I sure as shit
didn't say it.
Dick, i'm trying to work
on this office pool.
Sure, i'll
leave you alone.
Hello.
Corrado?
What the fuck are you doing
calling my home?
Now listen,
i'm the only person in
this family who doesn't curse,
so just do me the favor.
I want to see
how your feeling.
Is that so horrible?
I'm fine.
It's not easy being
abandoned, is it?
Look to yourself.
I had a stroke, corrado,
did you hear?
Of course i heard,
i don't live in oshkosh.
I heard you're keeping company
with that catherine romano.
What the fuck?
Never you mind
about that.
Aw, she's so sweet.
I remember
my johnny told me,
she let him feel her up
behind "the sons of italy" hall.
Listen livia, what you
don't know could fill a book.
Is everything
alright?
My brother's wife.
Oh livia,
how is she?
I heard she
wasn't well.
She never was well.
Let's face it.
That woman's
life is very sad.
If she fell
into a sewer pipe,
she'd come up holding
a gold watch in each hand.
This was my father's.
Actually it
was his uncle's.
It's a little sweet, but there's
nothing like homemade wine.
The vinegar eggplant.
From four years ago.
Take some home.
I can't handle
the acidity.
If you like, i can
make us some lunch.
Why go to the bother,
there's a friendly's
on bloomfield avenue.
I can't.
Don't you enjoy
going out corrado?
It's not that
i don't enjoy it.
Well, what is it then,
your heart?
No, it's certain
legal difficulties.
The truth is
i can't go out.
I'm under house arrest.
Oh my god,
does it hurt?
It beeps.
Sends a signal
if i leave the house.
You can't go anywhere?
The choices
we make, huh?
Occasionally i can
get special permission.
Banking, the doctors,
certain family obligations.
For most part though...
i understand if you
don't want to stay.
I enjoy you, corrado,
i always did.
You stay,
i'll bring food in.
Trying to keep a low profile,
what's the fucking point?
I'm still a miserable pric
k and i'm still passing out.
Thing on the history channel
the other night,
on the american revolution.
You know we're the only
country in the world
where the pursuit of happiness
is guaranteed in writing?
You believe that, hmm?
Bunch of fucking
spoiled brats.
Where's my
happiness then?
It's the pursuit
that's guaranteed.
Always a fucking
loophole, right?
Well, you seem
very mellow today.
Let's talk about you.
You seem like you're on drugs
and i'm boring myself to death.
I'm ready for
the george sanders
long walk here.
Do you know why
a shark keeps moving?
They got to keep moving
or they'll die,
they can't breathe
or something.
There's a psychological
condition known as alexithymia,
common in certain
personalities.
The individual craves
almost ceaseless action,
which enables them
to avoid acknowledging
the abhorrent things they do.
Abhorrent?
What certain
personalities?
Antisocial personalities.
My future
brother- in- law...
ran over a guy,
no reason.
Guy's paralyzed, has to
piss into a cathode tube.
What happens when thes
e antisocial personalities
aren't distracted from
the horrible shit they do?
They have time to think
about their behavior.
How what they do
affects other people.
About feelings of emptiness
and self- loathing,
haunting them
since childhood.
And they crash.
Which one
of them knew?
Knew what?
Jerry grill
had asthma...
he never was one
to let common sense
get in the way of
whatever he wanted to do.
What about
chris newman?
Grale's house was
the last thing standing
in the way of that new deli.
I'm sure chris is glad
to see him gone too.
What about howard?
Corrado.
Hmm.
I got caught in
the middle of the fight...
and you have
no broken bones?
Actually they
ignored me.
Fucking thing.
Shh,
with that talk.
...that he'd been
cheatin' on her
where'd you
hear that?
Her father told her while
i was standing there.
Every one of them
had a motive.
The thing is who
had the opportunity
and who was it
who knew he had asthma?
I threw.
C'mon.
Ho, our long
lost leader.
Somebody most
owe him money.
Tony, how you doing?
How's the clay pigeon?
I'm getting there.
You could knock cardoz
o law school all you want,
but his lawyer says
the gun charge will not stick.
Yeah, congratulations.
We were talking about
you know, down the docks.
Driving off some off
that japanese technology.
Hesh knows a guy.
Oh yeah?
So what else
is going on?
Nothing.
I'm having good luck
with swiss basics'
moisturizing formula.
Maybe i'll try it.
Oh!
Yeah!
What the fuck?
Holy shit.
Look at that.
It's that dipshit
carmine again.
Sil, go tell him no speeding
in neighborhood.
I'm on it.
C'mon.
What an asshole.
Carmine, what the fuck's
the matter with you?
How many times
we gotta tell you,
do not speed in this
fucking neighborhood!
C'mon, you hurt?
That's too bad,
you should be fucking crippled,
you fucking asshole!
Don't do that again
you understand me?
Understand me?
People could be fucking hurt,
you know that?
You know that?
You alright?
You sure?
Tony.
Oh, agent harris.
How are you?
Good,
good to see you.
I was in the neighborhood,
i wanted to introduce you
to my new partner.
Joe marquez,
tony soprano.
What's the matter,
no openings in the post office?
How'bout
those nets, huh?
What a series.
It's that guy,
williams.
Yeah, he's good.
That fourth quarter
was amazing.
How'd the knicks do?
It was close,
really close.
Look at this asshole.
Friend of yours?
He drives too fast, and he's
always fucking hitting shit.
Captions copyright 2000
home box office
a division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.