NARRA TOR: Previously on Stargate SG-1.
TEAL 'C: According to those
who witnessed the battle,
the enemy is led by a young woman
of extraordinary powers.
You want Merlin's weapon for yourselves.
A weapon capable of destroying
not only the Ori, but the Ancients as well.
I did find one reference in that library
that might prove to be useful, Atlantis.
You think the location of Merlin's weapon
is hidden in their database?
I think it's worth checking out.
We're looking for the names
of two planets
known on Earth in ancient times
in the dialect of Old English
as Castiana and Sahal. Satisfied?
Taoth Vaclarush and Valos Cor.
Hey, Jackson, what are you doing?
Oh, just trying to figure out
the location of Merlin's weapon,
so we can find it in time to defeat the Ori,
hopefully save our galaxy. You?
We're going for Szechwan.
You want to come?
No, I'll pass.
How is your search coming,
Daniel Jackson?
Slowly, but I think I'm onto something.
Here, take a look at this.
These are the locations of the planets
that Arthur and his knights set off to
in their quest for the Sangraal,
Castiana, Sahal and Vagon Brei.
Now, we searched all three
and came up empty,
so I thought it was a dead end,
until I noticed this.
Their coordinates form
an equilateral triangle.
Now, add their departure point,
the Camelot planet, and you get
a tetrahedron.
A perfect pyramid.
Well, that's a hell of a coincidence.
Exactly, and it means something.
I'm just not sure what.
(VALA PANTING)
I have the answer. I've figured it out.
- Those three planets are part of a puzzle.
- This much I already know.
The pyramid is a visual representation
of "three into one."
Three addresses into one.
That's what Morgan
was trying to tell you,
that the Sangraal is located on a planet
the address of which is made up of
symbols from each of those three worlds,
Castiana, Sahal, Vagon Brei.
It just came to me in a dream.
Okay, this program will cross-reference
the addresses in the database
with those of Castiana,
Sahal and Vagon Brei,
searching out planetary designations
made up of symbols
from all three addresses.
Given the number of symbols and
the amount of addresses in the database,
we could be looking at dozens,
maybe hundreds, of permutations.
(SIGHS)
(BEEPING)
Or maybe just the one.
JACKSON: The culture and
level of technology looks similar
to what we found on the Camelot planet.
MITCHELL: Yeah, I'm going to assume
that's a good thing.
I think some of these folks have
figured out we're not from around here.
Excuse me?
I was wondering
if we could get some help.
A little information?
We've come in search of the Sangraal.
It's a red thing, about yea big.
We know what the Sangraal looks like.
It's been many generations
since anyone has come in search of it,
and now you're the second group
of adventurers in less than a week
to take up the quest.
The second group?
A number of Jaffa passed through here
three days ago.
Were they accompanied by anyone?
Yes. They were led by a man who clearly
commanded their fear and respect.
Ba'al has been here.
And he's got a three-day head start on us.
If you truly seek the Sangraal,
you must consult with the
Parchment of Virtues in the village library.
It will prepare you for the journey to come.
Over there? Thank you.
But I should warn you,
no one has ever returned
from the quest alive.
If you value your lives,
you would do well to reconsider.
We appreciate that,
but that is quitter talk.
Hello!
Right, Parchment of Virtues.
Do we look under "P" for "parchment"
or "V" for "virtues"?
I'd say look for any and all materials
related to the Sangraal.
Or you could simply ask me.
I am Osric, keeper of the village archives.
Hi. We're looking for something called
the Parchment of Virtues.
Another band of stalwart heroes
come to tempt fate
in the hopes of claiming
the legendary prize.
- What do you know of the Sangraal?
- Only what I have heard from legend.
That it is located in a cave
beyond the outlying forest,
but that the journey there
is fraught with peril.
Ages ago, Morgan Le Fay
enchanted the area with a terrible curse.
Since then, it has claimed countless lives.
Well, we don't put much stock in curses.
Yeah, well, neither did Phaedra,
the cobbler's wife.
Several weeks ago,
she set off in search of her son
who had strayed too far from the village.
Neither have been seen nor heard
from since.
This parchment was purportedly
left behind by Morgan herself
as a guide for knights of noble spirit,
since it is said that only the most virtuous
will succeed in claiming the Sangraal.
"Only those of virtue true
may win the prize concealed.
"Beyond the reach
of the flawed and tainted,
"the Sangraal shall instead belong to he
who speaks the guardian's name."
The guardian's name?
They say that the Sangraal is protected
by the most powerful of magical beasts.
A dragon.
Dragon?
You doubt the legend?
Well, I'm sure the Sangraal is protected
by something very powerful,
but I don't think it's an actual dragon.
OSRIC: (SCOFFING)
Believe what you will.
With luck, you may have the opportunity
to prove the truth for yourselves.
"Prudence, wisdom, charity,
kindness and faith.
"Let these be your guide
on this perilous quest."
Well, I'm sorry, but I think we're going to
need a little bit more than that to go on.
No, all Morgan left behind
was this parchment
and the map.
- There's a map?
- Yes.
- May we see it?
- No.
Why not?
I showed it to the last group
of adventurers
who came in search of the Sangraal,
and they rewarded my trust
by trying to take it.
Yeah, we know the guy
that runs that operation.
We're not like him.
Well, I'm sorry.
It's not for public view.
Hey! We wouldn't dream
of trying to steal it.
(OSRIC CHUCKLES)
- We have to steal it.
- We are not stealing the map.
Nightfall, sneak in
under cover of darkness.
Maybe I can just talk to Osric and
convince him that our cause is virtuous.
That's brilliant,
and while you're distracting him,
the rest of us can steal it.
For the last time, we are not...
Are you certain I cannot tempt you
with a final meal?
What is it with this town
and the "no-can-do" attitude?
Every time we turn around, someone's
trying to write us off or scare us away.
I apologize. I should have said, "A final
meal before you set off on your journey."
Well, that's better.
Although, it need be said,
in the many thousands of years
that adventurers have been seeking
the Sangraal, not one has succeeded.
(PEOPLE CLAMORING OUTSIDE)
What is this? What do you want here?
We are soldiers of the Ori,
and we have taken this village
as part of their holy crusade
to rid this galaxy of evil.
Cooperate, and you won't be harmed.
Go through the buildings.
Bring everyone out.
Who are these men?
Well, that is a long story.
Look, I know you have no reason to trust
us any more than you do those guys...
I have not seen you shoot anyone.
That's an excellent point.
We're going to need your help.
They've got a dozen men
guarding the gate,
another 50 or so in and around the village.
- Is that what I think it is?
- The contents of the library.
You have spent your time
ignorant to the truth,
stumbling aimlessly through the darkness
cast upon your world
by the trappings of the past,
but now, the path to fulfillment
stands revealed,
and the time has come
to embrace a new faith.
Let the light of Origin show you the way.
You've encountered them before.
Many times and on many different worlds.
And how did the inhabitants
of those other worlds resist them?
They didn't.
They either surrendered
or they were slaughtered.
What are you saying, there's nothing
we can do? We are doomed?
No, no, not necessarily.
We believe they can be defeated.
That's why we're here.
We think that's why they're here as well,
to destroy the one thing
capable of stopping them.
The Sangraal.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
OSRIC: Please, I know they're here.
Please...
I must speak with you.
The soldiers are looking for me.
Why?
Because they believe
I can lead them to the Sangraal.
- Can you?
- Well, of course!
What... You saved the map?
No, they unwittingly burned it
with the rest of the village archives,
but a copy still exists.
Where?
Here.
I will lead you to Merlin's treasure.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
We want the old man.
He has information we seek.
Not today, fellows.
Wow, this is awkward.
Our army has taken this village.
If you resist, there will be no escape.
Now, stand aside.
Oh, I think somebody
must have heard that.
This way. Come quickly.
You should come with us.
My place is here. I'll be fine.
I'll blame everything on you.
Good plan.
This way.
What the hell?
(BEEPING)
What's the matter with them?
I don't know. I'm picking up
varying anomalous readings.
Stronger here. Weaker here.
And then rising again.
Well, this is weird.
They're temporal fluctuations.
Meaning?
Meaning these people are trapped
in a time distortion field.
Are you sure?
If it's a time distortion field,
why are the leaves moving in the trees?
CARTER: It could be an illusion designed to
reproduce the standing weather pattern.
These readings indicate the time
within the field is extremely decelerated.
I mean, these people may look like
they're standing perfectly still,
but, in fact, they're moving,
imperceptibly slowly.
Are they aware
of what is happening to them?
Doubtful.
Several years may pass
on our side of the field
in the one or two seconds
it takes them to take even one step.
Why don't we just go around it?
Well, the outer edge of the field extends
as far as I can tell in either direction,
and it has a slight curve to it.
I mean, for all I know,
it could form a complete circle.
We could walk for miles
and never find a way through.
Sam, if you've got another idea,
I'd love to hear it.
Well, I'm definitely picking up
varied readings. It's almost as if...
I think I may have found a way in.
There's a circuitous path of real time
winding through the temporal field.
- It's a maze.
- Yeah.
It's a maze.
These readings are unmistakable.
I can use them to guide us through.
Follow my lead.
If you stray off the path, you could
wind up trapped in the distortion field.
(BEEPING STOPS)
- Uh-oh.
- What do you mean, "Uh-oh"?
"Uh-oh," you left your stove on, right?
The temporal distortions
are affecting these readings. We're blind.
MITCHELL: Okay, here's a stupid question.
You did check the batteries in that thing
before you left Stargate Command, right?
It's not the batteries.
We could just retrace our steps
and try our luck with the Ori soldiers.
Do you know the way back?
That way.
We have to be exact.
Any deviation from the path of real time,
and we could wind up frozen
like the rest of these people.
If Morgan Le Fay left clues
as to the whereabouts of the Sangraal,
then it is safe to assume
that she believed
that someone would eventually reach it.
It also stands to reason that our task,
though challenging, is far from impossible.
Teal'c's right. She set this trap
to weed out those she deemed unworthy.
There is a way out. We just have to be
resourceful and carefully think it through.
Well, Arthur and his knights wouldn't have
had access to this advanced technology
to guide them through,
so, presumably,
the answer could be deceptively simple.
Follow me.
Dead end.
You're right. Deceptively simple.
All right, we're through.
We'd better pick up the pace
if we want to cut into Ba'al's lead.
OSRIC: You say that these Ori
are possessed of god-like abilities,
and yet they are not gods?
JACKSON: No, they're very powerful beings
who would have their followers
believe as much
because faith is the source of their power.
Faith is something that cannot be won
through intimidation and fear.
If their followers have faith,
then they must truly believe.
No, they only believe
because they've been misled.
You see, to many
less-developed civilizations,
certain advanced technologies would
strike them as supernatural in nature.
Merlin wasn't a wizard,
and Morgan Le Fay was not a sorceress.
- Ridiculous.
- They simply used their advanced abilities
to fashion seemingly magical creations,
like the Sangraal,
or that time dilation field we encountered.
So you would have me believe that
you are possessed of a complete
understanding of these amazing feats?
No, but just because I don't know how
the trick is done doesn't make it magic.
And I would argue that your inability
to comprehend such feats
does, in fact,
prove their supernatural nature.
Their army just ran roughshod
over your village, forced you into hiding,
- now you're defending them?
- Hardly.
I condemn the actions of their soldiers,
but I'm in no position to judge the Ori
or their message. Not yet.
Truth is elusive to those
who refuse to see with both eyes.
What?
(MALE VOICE
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
BA'AL: I don't believe they abandoned me.
They're going to pay.
All of them are going to pay.
Wait!
(SIGHS)
Well, make yourselves comfortable.
We're going to be here a while.
It won't do you any good.
Believe me, I've tried. It's a one-way door.
How long have you been trapped in here?
Three agonizingly tedious days.
Which reminds me,
I don't suppose you have any food?
What's that?
That's bait.
When I approached to investigate,
I unwittingly triggered the trap.
CARTER: You've had the Ancient database
for months.
Why did it take you so long to get here?
I can't think clearly on an empty stomach.
(CHUCKLES)
I only possessed two of the three
addresses needed to complete the puzzle.
As a result, I had significantly
more possibilities to investigate.
By a process of elimination,
I was left with one prospect,
and when I went in search of the planet,
it wasn't there.
What do you mean it wasn't there?
It wasn't where it was supposed to be.
I calculated its position, I sent my ships
to its approximate location,
but they couldn't find it.
In the end, my only recourse
was to access it via the stargate
and secure the device
with a handful of my Jaffa,
and when I became trapped in here, they
set off in search of a means of freeing me.
They have yet to return.
Something must have come up.
Obviously, Morgan must have rendered
this planet inaccessible to ships
to ensure that enemies such as the Ori
could not destroy the Sangraal from orbit.
You're wasting your time.
I've had three days to search for a way out
of here. There's nothing inside.
Well, that's the point, isn't it?
The Parchment of Virtues told us
that we'd have to rely on five things
in order to reach the Sangraal.
Prudence, wisdom, charity,
kindness and faith.
You're saying the parchment
was intended to be interpreted literally?
Why not?
We were able to make our way
through the time dilation field
by patiently and carefully
negotiating the maze.
In other words, we demonstrated
prudence, as opposed to recklessness,
which would have stranded us.
So ask yourselves,
"What does this trap exploit?"
- Curiosity.
- Greed.
A person approaches a chest
expecting to find treasure inside,
but instead finds nothing
and gets trapped for his trouble.
So in order to reverse the trap,
you have to reverse the impetus.
Right. The opposite of greed is charity,
one of the virtues mentioned
in the parchment.
Instead of taking something,
something must be sacrificed.
(CHUCKLES) Well,
that was an interesting theory.
Well, we're all trapped,
so we all have to contribute something.
No, wait!
(CLEARS THROAT)
I have nothing to donate.
That particular item
holds great sentimental value.
Well done. Another day in there,
I would have gone mad.
Guess that makes it time to say goodbye.
- It would be foolish of you to kill me.
- How so?
Amongst the information I obtained
regarding the Sangraal
is the name of the protector.
- Protector?
- The dragon.
You see? I told you there was a dragon.
I'm sure there's something
guarding the device.
Maybe it's a hologram.
Holograms can be dangerous, you know.
It could be a ship.
Flies, breathes fire, has armored skin.
It's a mistake a medieval storyteller
could easily make.
Then if it's based on technology,
the name is no doubt a password
or a command code.
Either way, if you want it,
you'll have to take me with you.
You know, I hate to say this,
but he could prove useful.
MITCHELL: Come on.
Yet again, we find ourselves
the unlikeliest of allies
joined together in common purpose.
You know, the word "allies" implies
some sort of partnership,
and that just isn't the case here.
You see, we are going after the Sangraal,
while you are tagging along for the ride.
According to the map,
the Sangraal is hidden in a cave
beneath a lone mountain.
Right. We're getting warm.
This is it. The cave entrance.
The Sangraal is located within.
It's too bad you won't be coming with us.
I thought I made it clear. You need me.
I wasn't talking to you.
Well, allow me to get out
of your line of fire.
Have you lost your senses?
"Truth eludes he who does not seek it
with both eyes wide."
It's a quote from the Book of Origin.
You paraphrased it earlier today.
Now, I might not have noticed, but I spent
the past year studying the good book, so...
Surely, you're not basing your suspicions
on this mere coincidence?
And when it came time to give up
a possession to free ourselves
from the force field trap,
I noticed the designs on your ring,
not Celtic as one might expect given
the cultural background of this planet,
but distinctly Ori.
The ring was a gift
from a traveling merchant.
You're making a mistake.
You're the one who screwed up.
Now drop the act.
It would have been so much easier
if you had remained oblivious.
But now, things will be
much more difficult.
Especially for you.
You're doing something new
with your eyes.
So the troops in the village,
the shoot-out in the tavern,
that was all a set-up.
More than you know.
I grew impatient waiting for you
to discover the location of the weapon,
so I gave you a little help.
The dream I had, "three into one."
That was you?
- Yes.
- So you planted the solution in Vala
knowing it would lead us right to you.
Apparently, Morgan put safeguards
in place
to ensure the weapon
could only be secured by...
What was the term again?
"Those possessing truth of spirit."
I can't think of anyone more appropriate
than a former Ascended.
With your help, I'll secure the device.
Hate to disappoint.
You've seen a demonstration
of my powers.
You know what I'm capable of.
So I'm offering you a choice,
either we work together
to reach the device,
or I'll start killing off members
of your team.
- Starting with her.
- All right!
We'll work together.
For now.
ADRIA: We thwarted all efforts against us,
crippled your fleet,
met with little, if any resistance,
on the worlds that we redeemed.
Opposition to the Ori is clearly hopeless,
but you continue to struggle
against the inevitable.
JACKSON: Yeah, well, what can I tell you?
We're optimists.
Your only hope lies with Merlin's weapon.
Once I take that away from you,
your defeat will be complete.
Now look who's the optimist.
You disappoint me, Mother.
I would have expected you to see reason
by now, but it doesn't matter.
Eventually, you'll have no choice
but to accept the truth.
And when you do, I'll accompany you
on your path to enlightenment.
You know, the second we find that thing,
she's going to kill us.
- Not if we kill her first.
- That could be a bit of a problem.
I don't know, we're pretty resourceful.
I'm sure we'll think of something.
Yeah? Just don't do it too soon.
She may not be true of spirit
and all that jazz,
but she has done her homework.
I hate to say it, but...
- She could prove useful.
- For the moment.
"Choose the way that is just and true."
It's a riddle. I'm good at these.
"The way that is just and true."
Just and true...
It's telling us to go that way.
"The way that is just and true,"
that is, the "right" way.
What...
- The writing's in Ancient.
- So?
So in Ancient, the word meaning
"Just and true" is very different
from the word meaning "right,"
as in, "opposite of left."
(CHILD CRYING)
Did you hear that?
It sounds like a child.
- This way.
- VALA: A child in here?
- It's obviously a trap.
- Or quite possibly a test.
A test of what? Our stupidity?
(WHIMPERING)
Hey, kid.
Kid, wait up.
Hey, slow down, little guy.
ADRIA: We're walking right into a trap.
JACKSON: No, we're not.
The parchment provided us with clues
to reaching the Sangraal.
It mentioned kindness as one
of the virtues that would guide us.
So if we show kindness
by helping this child,
it should bring us one step closer
to the device.
The parchment also mentioned wisdom,
which we would be demonstrating
by avoiding this trap.
(METAL GEARS TURNING)
MITCHELL: Hang on, kid.
We'll get you out of there.
Little help here.
He's tiny.
Have him squeeze through the bars.
Assist us, or I will squeeze you
through these bars.
JACKSON: Want to use
your powers to lift it?
We're wasting our time. Let's go back.
Well, how's about that.
We did pick the right way.
- It's a dead end.
- We have to go back.
No, it doesn't make any sense
that we would have progressed this far
only to come up empty.
Daniel.
It's another riddle.
Oh, goody.
"I'm struck and cut, shaped and cooled,
"then bound by rings
to release what's stored."
(RUMBLING)
You might want to pick things up
a little bit here.
All right, well, we have to think it through.
What's struck and cut and shaped
and cooled and then bound by rings?
- Bound by rings...
- Key! The answer is key.
Clavia!
(RUMBLING)
"I shake the earth with booming thunder,
fell forest whole and homes complete.
"I influence ships, topple kings,
sweep down swift, yet remain unseen."
Oh, wait, I've got this.
Suggesting a strong yet invisible force...
Wind.
Ventio!
MITCHELL: Oh, for crying out loud!
"Battle-scarred in times of strife,
resistant to... Resistant to..."
- VALA: To what?
- I don't know.
I can't translate this section of the text.
Nevertheless, "battle-scarred"
would suggest...
Contegia!
(RUMBLING STOPS)
Looks like that's done it.
You know, come to think of it,
riddles never really were my strong point.
Visual puzzles, like, "Which of these
symbols does not belong with the others,"
or, "Reconfigure the tiles
to make the hidden picture."
MITCHELL: Is it just me,
or is it getting hot in here?
VALA: Well, now that you mention it...
It is a tad toasty.
- Hey, you got anything?
- No. You?
No, but I'm getting a good tan.
- Let's take a break.
- Okay.
There's no hidden triggers
or secret passages.
If there's a way through, we didn't find it.
Then I suppose we should head back.
Not an option.
The passageways have re-sealed
behind us.
Then I was right. We walked into a trap.
No. We made all the right choices
to lead us to this point.
I know the Sangraal lies
beyond that wall of fire.
We just have to find a way through.
Why don't you do something?
You're the Orici. You're supposedly
possessed of significant powers.
So snuff out the flame
and get us on our way.
My abilities don't work that way.
Of course. How does the saying go?
All flash, no photo.
Actually, it's "All flash, no substance."
I prefer my version.
Would you care for a demonstration?
Taking your life would be
a waste of my time.
Which I suppose would be put
to better use complaining.
Oh, jeez, why don't you two
just get a room?
It's the only one left.
Daniel?
The parchment told us
that five virtues would guide us
in our quest for the Sangraal.
Prudence, kindness, charity,
wisdom and faith.
Now, we displayed prudence
in finding a way out of the temporal maze,
charity, in escaping the force field trap,
kindness, by helping the child
and finding the hidden passageway,
and wisdom, in solving the riddles.
The only virtue left is faith.
- Daniel!
- Jackson!
Well, after you, Muscles.
There it is. We've found it.
Ours for the taking.
Hang on.
Yeah, that's pretty deep.
- I'll go.
- We'll both go.
I think I'll stay here
and support you from a distance.
We should all go.
No, only Daniel and I will go.
The rest of you will stay.
It's all right.
Take it.
- After you.
- I told you.
Morgan put safeguards in place to ensure
that someone such as myself
couldn't claim the device.
Is that why you didn't just use
your powers from back there?
What are you talking about?
Well, you have telekinetic abilities.
I've seen you use them.
You should have just snatched
the Sangraal off the dais
without taking a step, but you didn't.
Probably for the same reason you didn't
use your powers to lift the portcullis
or kill Ba'al the second
he stepped out of line.
- You can't.
- Of course I can.
No. My guess is Morgan
did put safeguards in place,
and that those safeguards
are neutralizing your Ori-given powers.
You saw me withstand
the bullets fired against me.
Yeah, thanks to your personal shield.
The only powers you can manifest
originate from that pendant,
and they're purely defensive in nature.
Do you really want to test me?
Yep.
You know what?
I changed my mind about helping you.
Knock yourself out.
What's the holdup?
Thought so.
Well, I guess I'm not as true of spirit
as you thought I was.
(RUMBLING)
Jackson, move it!
What the hell is that?
We agreed there's no such thing
as a dragon, right?
Yeah.
(WINGS FLAPPING)
(SCREECHING)
Because that looks pretty real to me.