NARRA TOR: Previously on Stargate SG-1.
I'm not just interested in outer space,
I'm from outer space.
ANNOUNCER ON TV: Four excellent heroes
in an extraordinary new sci-fi series,
starring Nick Marlowe
as the wry Colonel Danning.
As a matter of fact, it does say
"Colonel" on my uniform.
Wormhole X-treme.
It's what I do.
HAMMOND: He sold the idea to the studio.
He obviously got the whole thing from
his knowledge of the Stargate Program.
No, if the Air Force
didn't want it to happen,
they wouldn't have let it go this far.
Come on out.
FURLING: We are the Furlings.
We thought we'd never get to meet you.
We led them straight here.
- Sam!
- I thought I could make it work.
The thermodynamic loop is
feeding back into the planet's core.
(FURLINGS SPEAKING
FURLING LANGUAGE)
CARTER: Well, that never happened.
Well, you've got to open big,
catch people's attention,
make them think
the whole thing is going to be jam-packed.
I love jam.
Oh, I get it, it's yet another playful twist
on words in your Earth language.
It makes us look stupid.
JACKSON: You realize it's not actually us.
Okay, okay,
it makes the characters look stupid.
I mean, do you really think
the best way to introduce the heroes of
the story is to show them
causing a massive catastrophe?
That's realistic.
- I don't care.
- Come on. It'll be fun.
You know, you say that about everything.
Come to think of it, why am I doing this?
To make sure that the Air Force
is being properly represented
and because General O'Neill
has requested you specifically.
Of course he did.
Jackson, how often do we get to give
notes on a big Hollywood feature script?
I believe this is intended to be
a television movie.
A fictionalized, albeit slightly ridiculous,
version of Stargate Command
is an excellent cover for the real thing
in the event of a security leak.
Plausible deniability.
I'm sorry, sir,
did you say slightly ridiculous?
You're doing this. You have no choice.
Just give the man five minutes.
I'll get you out of this
when the time comes.
VALA: I've been looking through this,
and there doesn't seem to be
any mention of
a sexy female alien anywhere.
I'm not even in this.
CARTER: You know,
the really unbelievable part
is that anyone would consider spending
millions of dollars on this thing.
I mean, seriously, all these writers
and they couldn't come up
with anything better?
I don't know, I've been watching a lot
of television lately
and, apart from one glaring omission,
it doesn't seem to be that bad.
Maybe we can make it better.
No, I'm with Sam on this one.
I mean, who makes a movie out of
a series that only lasted three episodes?
It allegedly performed well on DVD.
No, I'm not using any shots
from the series.
It's a movie, not a clip show.
The budget is the budget.
They are a bunch of pencil-pushing,
bean-counting idiots.
You tell them if they don't like it,
I'm going to take it somewhere else.
You know not to say that last part, right?
Yeah, movie, not clip show, is fine.
Yeah, I've got to go. Yeah.
Your cell coverage is just terrible in here.
How's it going? You done?
Well, it certainly seems to be
packed full of jam.
I knew I should have given you
my first draft.
The producer brought in the other writers.
- I thought you were the producer.
- Yeah, the real one.
Look, just be honest.
I trust you guys. That's why I'm here.
Just tell me what you think.
MARTIN: Come on,
you must have some ideas.
Don't be afraid. Just pitch them out.
We call it spinning.
Don't worry. No one's going to judge you.
Okay, for starters, I think you need
a strong opening title sequence.
Are you serious?
No one does that anymore.
You just throw up the title and
get on with it.
(ALARM BLARING)
(SCREAMING)
Walter! Dial 447.
The only way to stop this is to
get the device back to the planet.
(SCREAMING)
Look, no offense,
but zombies have been done to death.
No pun intended.
Besides, this is science fiction, not horror.
Did I mention the Tel'chak device?
'Cause that's what turned them
into zombies.
(MUSICAL CELL PHONE RINGING)
Sorry. Go for Marty.
(WHISPERING) Hey, Charlie. What's up?
It's the studio.
What kind of problem?
Just out of curiosity, what was
the rest of the team doing
while your character was
fighting the zombies?
- MARTIN: Son of a bitch!
- Studio executives, huh?
What? No, Charlie, he's a great guy.
He's the only one I trust.
So, what's the problem then?
Our lead backed out.
How am I supposed to tell a story
without my lead character?
Easy. You just bring in a character
to replace him.
What?
MARTIN: You guys have to help me.
I mean, how can I keep
the main character in the story
without actually having
the actor who plays him?
Well, you could have the other characters
refer to him all the time,
maybe get him on the phone
once in a while.
Yeah, right. I mean something cool,
like face-switching or body-swapping.
As if anyone would believe that.
Come on, you guys must have
some real-life experiences I can draw on.
Well, there was that time that
Colonel O'Neill was invisible.
So, essentially, what I think happened
is that you were bombarded by
the particle field being emanated
by the cloaking generator.
See, you were in the engine room
standing right next to it
when the device was turned on.
That would account for
the minute traces of radiation
we've been picking up from you.
But the good news is, I think
I've found a way to reverse the process.
We have to go back to the mothership
and get the cloaking generator.
- Sam, who are you talking to?
- Colonel O'Neill.
I was just explaining to him how
we're going to make him visible again.
No, you're not.
Jack's in Hammond's office.
- I can't believe he did that to me again.
- Yeah.
You know, getting that cloaking
generator off that mothership,
that's going to be
the least of our problems.
Now, getting Jack to help,
that's going to be the hard part.
- Oh, don't tell me.
- Yes. He likes being invisible.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
And so, by translating this tablet,
we should be able to determine
the most important thing in the universe.
(O'NEILL SNORING)
Everyone just want to poke around,
see if you can find him?
Sir, are you there?
O'NEILL: Nope.
- You cannot remain this way, O'Neill.
- Why not?
It gives us an advantage over the Goa'uld.
I can sneak around all I want
totally undetected.
I give us the element of surprise.
The bottom line is
I can do more for this planet invisible
than I ever could
as my own sweet, salient self.
I assume I'm staring at you stoically.
- Not buying it, eh?
- No.
You are most transparent, O'Neill.
I get it. Good one.
I can see right through you.
Don't push it.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
O'NEILL: Hello? Hand signals?
I'm waving you over.
Okay, I've made
the necessary adjustments.
All you have to do now is
initiate the sequence.
Okay.
Let's do it.
O'NEILL: Oh, yeah. This is better.
It might feel like kind of a cheat.
Maybe it's best just not to
mention the guy at all.
Yeah, besides,
invisibility can be very powerful.
You might not want to
open that can of worms.
You don't want your heroes to
become too powerful.
Well, you could always invent
some negative side-effects.
That's how we talked Colonel O'Neill
into becoming visible again.
Okay, that's it, SG-1,
you are cleared to leave.
- Thank you.
- MARTIN: They can't leave!
They haven't finished reading my script!
That's funny, I thought it said
"General" on my uniform.
- We owe you one, sir.
- You mean another one.
What are you talking about?
I thought you said it was going to be fun.
Not after his zombie idea got shot down.
So, where are you guys all off to?
Someplace pretty important, huh?
It's just a recon mission, isn't it?
"Just" a recon mission?
This is no simple recon mission.
This is no less than my 200th trip
through the gate.
Really?
- You're counting?
- You bet.
TEAL'C: I have been reflecting
while changing into our gear.
I believe this is far from
your 200th mission, Colonel Mitchell.
I didn't say 200th mission.
I said 200th trip through the gate.
That's counting off-world gates,
back and forth, pretty much anytime
I crossed the event horizon.
Yeah. This is going to be huge.
The big 200.
(INAUDIBLE)
- Fix it.
- Quickly.
- I'm on it.
- Indeed.
Gotta go!
We've got 10 seconds before
the time dilation field is activated.
If we don't make it through the gate,
we'll be stuck here forever!
Okay, this could be a problem.
- That was close, huh?
- Oh, yeah.
JACKSON: Are you serious?
MARTIN: What?
How did we escape?
- They.
- Fine, they, they, they.
- How did they escape?
- Isn't it obvious?
Even if the valley wasn't filled with Jaffa,
we could never have made it
to the gate and dialed out
in under 10 seconds.
Good. See, that's why we're here.
So, what do you think? 30 seconds?
Maybe not such a round number.
How about 38?
What difference does it make?
I mean, it's not like you're going to have
an actual ticking clock on the screen.
- That's brilliant!
- That's ridiculous.
Trust me, jeopardy plus ticking clock
is box office.
It's the E=MC-squared
of the entertainment world.
Ask any executive.
Except I think you've replaced jeopardy
with certain death.
Oh, come on. You guys have escaped
situations more dire than this before.
- He has a point.
- So show the actual escape.
No, no, no.
You can't give away too much, too early.
It'll step on the ending.
Maybe if my character doesn't say,
"This is a problem."
He could say something like,
"This should be easy."
How many times do I have to tell you?
It's not you.
Colonel Danning
is based on Colonel O'Neill.
Please tell me
you have the gate working again.
We're running another diagnostic,
but right now, we're stumped.
The power's getting through
to the capacitors,
but, for some reason,
the charge isn't holding.
That's causing the control crystal to
send feedback into the interface
and reset the programming code
of the base computer's dialing protocol.
Whoa! That was awesome. Say that again.
No.
Oh. Everybody, take five.
I've got to get that down before I forget it.
MARTIN: The power getting
to the flux capacitor,
but feedback is not feeding back
into the feedback face.
This is gold!
Forget about the techno talk.
No one's really interested in it.
You're an alien, right?
Exactly, and I know
just what this movie needs.
So how would you know what sci-fi fans
from Earth would be interested in?
- Aren't you also an alien?
- Yeah, but I've been here quite a while.
Right. Look, I think I know a good story
when I hear one.
Don't you want this movie to appeal
to a broad range of people?
- From Earth.
- I have all kinds of fabulous adventures,
none of which have been classified
by the Air Force.
- Okay, shoot. Give me your best one.
- Right.
I was in a stolen cargo ship,
on my way home,
when a solar flare from a nearby star
wreaked havoc with my navigation system
and I was forced to crash-land
on the nearest planet.
In a bizarre twist of fate,
I crashed right on top of the Goa 'uld
who ruled that planet,
which was fortunate because
my ship was too badly damaged to repair
and I needed help.
The local villagers were very grateful.
They introduced me
to a lovely fair-haired Tok'ra
who had been hiding out on the planet.
She told me the legend
of a powerful Ascended being
who supposedly lived in some distant,
far-off mountains
through a treacherous forest.
Look, I don't have all day.
Cut to the chase.
All right. I met up with a number
of my friends along the way,
and after a dangerous
and eventful journey,
we finally come face to face
with the Ascended being.
What can I do for you?
Well, at first I thought
I just wanted to go home,
but now I've decided
I'd quite like to be a part of something.
A regular part, if you catch my drift.
Oh, and these guys have
their own issues. Boys?
That's The Wizard of Oz.
- Oh, you've seen that one?
- Yeah.
Oh, that's my phone. Martin Lloyd.
- I didn't hear it ring.
- It's on vibrate.
MARTIN: Yes, go ahead.
I can sing.
- So how's it going?
- Not well.
Samantha, 200 is waiting.
Right now, I'm just hoping
we haven't done something
to permanently damage the gate.
How can something work perfectly fine
for 10 years
then all of a sudden
it doesn't work anymore?
I don't know. Okay, try it now.
We're getting some strange
power readings here, Colonel.
- Shut it down.
- It's not responding.
The gate's drawing massive amounts
of energy into its capacitors.
Close the blast door and the iris.
I can't shut it down.
Siler, manually cut the power!
(SCREAMING)
Why does this always happen to me?
Sir, we have to evacuate the base!
This is General Landry.
I'm declaring a code red emergency.
All personnel,
evacuate the base immediately.
(ALARM BLARING)
Sir, the capacitors are overloading.
We have to get out of here now.
Hurry.
And that is the end of act two.
- The mountain blows up?
- No possible hope for survival.
Cool, huh? I just wrote it
based on what's going on with the gate.
I love it when art imitates life.
Hang on. We're alive in the next scene.
Oh, I just haven't fixed that part yet.
I'm thinking I can back-sell it and say
you were beamed out at the last second.
- JACKSON: Beamed out?
- Sure. Why not?
- Is that not too convenient?
- MARTIN: Not if you hang a lantern on it.
- What's that?
- It's a writer's term.
Another character points out
how convenient it is.
Dr. Levant can say,
"Well, that was great timing."
That way the audience knows
I intended for it to be convenient,
- and we move on.
- Really.
- Okay, where were we?
- Scene 24.
Oh, great, one of my favorite scenes.
Go ahead.
(VALA CLEARS THROAT)
"Interior Bridge.
VALA: "The crew mans their stations."
I'm picking up
a strange energy anomaly, Colonel.
It appears the singularity
is about to explode.
Weapons are at maximum.
Damn it, Captain! Solar flare.
We've got a shockwave
heading straight for us.
Can you reverse the polarity?
I'll do my best.
Engine room. Warp speed!
MITCHELL: Take us out of here now.
I'm giving it all I've got, Captain,
but you're expecting a bloody miracle.
- JACKSON: Hang on, hang on, hang on.
- What?
Okay, one, that's Star Trek.
And two, it's ridiculous.
What's wrong with it?
- The singularity is about to explode?
- Yes.
Everything about that statement is wrong.
How exactly is having weapons
at maximum going to help the situation?
The audience isn't going to
know the difference.
They love weapons at maximum.
Never underestimate your audience.
They're generally sensitive,
intelligent people
who respond positively
to quality entertainment.
TEAL'C: I do not understand
why everything in this script
must inevitably explode.
MARTIN: Look, you guys may all know
how things really work out there
in the galaxy,
but I know the film business.
Explosions make great trailers.
Simple fact.
More explosions, better trailer.
Better trailer, more viewers.
(MUSICAL CELL PHONE RINGING)
Yeah, go for Marty. Oh, hey, Nora.
What? That's ridiculous.
Tell them to stop panicking.
We're going to sign him. Don't worry.
I already put in a call to his manager.
We'll get back to you. Yeah. Bye.
- So, trouble with Nora?
- MARTIN: No. Nora, she's great.
But since Nick Marlowe is holding out,
one of the new junior executives
at the network has suggested
we re-cast the whole movie
with younger, edgier versions of the team.
Can you imagine that?
Yo, dawg, what did you do that for?
Dude, that hot chick
was so totally a Goa'uld!
- Duh, I was still gonna tap that.
- You don't appreciate me, do you?
I think you're so totally awesome.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yo, Wonderbread,
you got that address figured out yet?
Chill, T.
I'm, like, translating as fast as I can.
I'm so sick of being treated like
some sort of object to be worshiped.
I'm a real person with real feelings.
You know, I don't think
Mitchell likes me anymore.
I'm pregnant.
- No.
- Nope.
I need a latte.
How about this one?
We were in a cloaked cargo ship
on a simple,
three-hour reconnaissance mission...
Gilligan's Island, right?
You got that from
"Three-hour reconnaissance mission?"
Piece of advice.
If you're going to rip something off,
think of something a little more obscure.
Oh, okay.
Call me fahrbot, but they're gonna have
our mivonks on a platter if we don't
starburst the draz out of here.
The cluster's been damaged.
We're not going anywhere.
Oh, dren.
Hezmana!
(GROANS)
Frell!
Son of a hasmot!
Yotz!
Okay, you got me.
I have no idea what that is.
(MUSICAL CELL PHONE RINGING)
Oh, for crying out loud, what now?
Oh, give me a break!
I just a got a text message
from the studio.
The foreign distributor went bankrupt.
They're slashing my budget.
In a text message?
This totally screws up the end of act three.
- What happens at the end of act three?
- With these cuts, not much.
Act three just ends.
What's so bad about this?
- Any idea when we'll be able to go?
- Sorry.
We're trying a full reset of the system, sir.
Hey.
If you want this to be more accurate,
why don't you just give him
your mission files?
- They're classified.
- So?
Didn't you say that no one on your planet
would believe this was all real anyway?
Even still, do you know
how many mission files there are?
MITCHELL: 1,263.
Hopefully 64 by the end of the day.
Actually, it's 1,264 already.
No, it's 63. Pretty sure.
I've read all the files recently.
Actually, you haven't read 30185.
30185? What's that?
We can't tell you.
What do you mean you can't tell me?
I have the highest security clearance
known to mankind. What is 30185?
We were sworn to secrecy.
Well, why even mention it to me
if you're not going to tell me what it is?
Sorry.
- Can you tell me?
- Oh, yeah, we can tell you.
It has to do with the time that
the gate sent us back to 1969.
Well, that can't have anything
to do with me.
I wasn't born till a year later.
Actually, it was nine months
before he was born.
What?
You have to remember, it was the '60s.
JACKSON: Come on,
you have to have known that Jack's
always taken an interest in your life.
Jack O'Neill?
Indeed.
CARTER: Do you remember when you were
chosen for the 302 program
even though you didn't think
you should get in?
How about when you were chosen
for SG-1?
- Wait, are you saying that Jack O'Neill is...
- My daddy?
All starting to make sense now, isn't it?
Oh, I'm being punked, aren't I?
We honestly can't tell you about 30185.
MARTIN: I can't believe it!
The whole cast heard
Marlowe is holding out for more money,
and now they're all joining in.
Where do they think it comes from?
How am I supposed to do a movie
without any actors?
MITCHELL: Carter, correct me if I'm wrong
on this, but is it not
a fact of parallel dimension physics
that each of us exists
somewhere in some universe in whatever
way, shape, or form we can imagine?
Any way, shape, or form we can imagine.
We've seen it for ourselves.
There you go.
Use your imagination.
All right, people.
We created this multi-billion dollar
facility under Cheyenne Mountain
so that we can use this thing.
Anyone know how?
Sir, we thought you knew.
I do know this, we need to put
together a team,
starting with the most beautiful,
battle-ready scientific genius I know,
- Captain Doctor Samantha Carter.
- Reporting for duty, sir.
What can you tell us, Captain?
Well, at first glance, I suspect the device
creates a stable wormhole
between superconducting rings that
have been placed in fixed positions
elsewhere in the galaxy...
...converts matter into energy
at the event horizon,
once the initial vortex has subsided,
of course.
And just because my sex organs
are on the inside instead of the outside
doesn't mean that I can't handle...
Provided, of course, that sufficient energy
has been channeled to the device
and that the correct coordinates
have been calculated.
Okay, get to it.
Next, we need a bookworm adventurer
who can say "brains" and "guts"
in 27 languages.
Dr. Daniel Jackson.
Why have I been brought here?
This is not...
What is that?
The reason you're here, Doctor.
This big ring was discovered
in the sands of Egypt, near Giza.
Then I was right.
The pyramids really were landing sites
for interplanetary starships that
enslaved primitive human populations
by posing as their gods.
Well, we found the ring in the sand.
These symbols, they look familiar.
They're like constellations.
Don't you see? Here.
If each symbol represents
a specific point in space,
then six of them
would create a sort of box.
The intersection point between those
six points would indicate a destination.
Maybe, just maybe,
the seventh marks the starting point.
Is there a monitor that shows
these symbols in detail?
Over here, Dr. Jackson.
Wait.
This one seems different.
You found the ring in Egypt.
The pyramid represents Earth.
This symbol has to be the point of origin.
It was under our noses the whole time.
I feel so stupid.
And now what this team needs is a leader,
someone who'll laugh in the face
of his enemy,
even when it's inappropriate.
Colonel Jack O'Neill.
I thought I told you I retired.
I thought you said you were tired.
Well, as a matter of fact, I am a little tired.
There's no time for that now.
You have a mission to lead.
Right!
Sergeant? Make it spin.
Spin?
Sir, it doesn't spin.
What?
It has to spin. It's round.
Spinning is so much cooler
than not spinning.
I'm the General.
I want it to spin. Now!
Yes, sir.
Hey, look at that.
HARRIMAN: Chevron one is lit up.
I wonder what we're going to find
on the other side.
Whatever it is, I'll bet it's amazing.
Well, don't get too excited.
It's just a simple recon.
Aren't you the least bit curious
about what's out there?
Well, I'm just hoping we find
some new meat for the team,
preferably something bald, mysterious,
you know, the warrior type,
with lots of, you know, muscles.
Sir, the odds against any alien life forms
we encounter looking remotely human
are astronomical.
Yeah, well...
We'll see.
Chevron seven, also lit up.
- Holy...
- Colonel O'Neill, you have a go.
Godspeed.
Easy for him to say.
Okay.
We're all gonna do this together
on three, all right? Okay?
Okay.
One, two, three!
Dear God in heaven.
(SIGHS)
I feel so stupid.
(LAUGHING)
Yeah, that'll work.
A whole movie made with puppets.
Hey, I'm just saying...
MARTIN: Maybe we can
have puppet O'Neill
jump over a puppet shark
on a one-third scale motorcycle.
I don't get it.
Look, you don't know the business
like I do.
I don't have any money, so I have to
give the actors something else.
- Bigger trailers?
- I can't afford that either.
No, I have to give them something that
costs me nothing but no actor can refuse.
And what's that?
A good ego-stroking.
I have to make them think that
I re-wrote the script just for them.
In this draft, there has to be something
that makes them want to do this movie
even if it's for scale.
You know, we've been trying here.
You're not listening.
I'm talking about a twist,
something nobody's expecting.
O'NEILL: You mean something like this?
Wow, I don't think
anyone will see that coming.
- No, but there'll be spoilers.
- Are you kidding?
Lt'll be in the commercial.
ANNOUNCER ON TV:
When it comes to fighting crime,
there's only one man keeping
the streets safe, while keeping it real.
Indeed.
Teal'c, P. I. Coming this fall.
I love it.
I'm just not sure if the network...
(STAMMERING) But I'll pitch it to them
next week and we'll see what they think.
(MUSICAL CELL PHONE RINGING)
I have to get that. We'll talk later.
You got Marty.
So what brings you this way, sir?
What, a guy can't just stop by
from Malibu to say hi?
- Malibu?
- Sure.
I was there on business.
Exactly, sir. You're an Air Force General
with enormous responsibilities.
Ostensibly, I just stopped by to see
how you were doing with Marty.
Well, truth be known that
lately I've been feeling a little...
What? How do I say it?
It's okay to say that you missed us, sir.
No, not that.
- Like you have unfinished business?
- Okay.
You need closure,
and I have the perfect thing.
We were about to go on
a mission to commemorate
my 200th trip through the gate.
Really? 200, you say?
That's 200 times he's stepped
through the gate, sir, not actual missions.
To be honest,
I wouldn't mind one last jaunt
through the old orifice.
What?
We call it that sometimes, don't we?
Orifice?
Stupid focus groups.
They hate the ending.
I have to think of something new.
They could go fishing.
- Fishing?
- Yeah, it'd be the perfect ending.
I mean, after that,
anything else would seem pointless.
CARTER: This is great.
I told you.
Yup, it's good to be here.
You weren't there.
So, what's the twist? No fish?
No, I need something with more impact,
something more...
Moving.
Everyone loves a wedding.
(ORGAN PLAYING)
(SNIFFLING)
It's just a summer cold, sir.
- A bit of a wait.
- Indeed.
(CLEARS THROAT)
You know, if she doesn't show,
people are gonna think that you and I are...
What?
(ALL APPLAUDING)
- Nice entrance.
- Sorry, sir.
Carter.
Jack.
Thank you.
KVASIR: Shall we begin?
Yeah, right, if I want to
torture the audience on purpose.
- The gate is back up and running. General.
- General.
With permission?
But I still don't have my ending.
You keep these kids out of trouble, Jack.
Here's an idea, Hank.
Why don't you come along with us?
No, it's all right.
- No, seriously.
- I don't know.
Yeah, come on.
It'll be kind of like a special occasion deal.
- Well, what the hell.
- Yeah, that's it.
Hey, Walter! Come on, we're all going.
I don't have the right outfit.
You look fine!
Everything ready?
SGs 3 through 18 are waiting, sir.
- The cake?
- It's all set.
Balloons, streamers, the works.
All right, let's go check out
the mysteries of P2C-106.
Hey, Marty.
Why don't you come with us?
Maybe find a little inspiration for
the end of your little movie.
MARTIN: I can't.
I just heard from the studio.
The movie's been canceled.
There's some heartbreak.
- That's too bad.
- Not for me.
They decided to renew the series instead!
Okay.
Let's move out.
DIRECTOR: And, cut!
(BELL RINGING)
- Good job, Doug.
- Here, here, here.
- Ocean.
- Thanks.
Well, that wasn't so bad.
DIRECTOR: And that's a cut, everybody.
That is a wrap on the 200th episode!
(ALL CHEERING)
Nice job, everybody.
So, did you ever think
a show like this would go on for 200?
Well, sure.
What do you mean, "A show like this"?
(MUSICAL CELL PHONE RINGING)
Martin Lloyd. Yeah.
Are you kidding?
Hey, everybody. Guess what?
The movie's back on!
(ALL CHEERING)
Ten seasons, seven Saturn Awards
for Best Cable or
Syndication Science Fiction Show.
Who would have guessed?
I think, first and foremost,
it has to do, you know, with the writing.
I mean, obviously
we don't take ourselves too seriously.
The writers are really great guys,
all of them.
Men, you know.
Yeah, it's a bit of a boys' club.
The real challenge was coming up
with a good catch phrase.
"It's what I do."
That was so, you know, good.
It defined Colonel Danning.
I just don't think they know
what they want to do with my character.
I probably should have taken up golf
a long time ago.
Just... Just kidding.
And I needed something even better
to make you forget about the guy
that fans loved to watch
for the first seven years of the show.
I know he was here for eight,
but, you know, a lot of people say
he just kind of phoned it in
that last season.
Yeah, well, that's ancient history.
We don't talk about that around here.
The fact of the matter is, I don't
really even know what happened there.
You know, to me, it never felt like
I was leaving the show.
I just needed a little space,
a little time, you know?
I wanted to get back to my roots.
Theater, right?
So I go to New York, do a little Broadway,
off-off-Broadway.
Either way, it doesn't matter.
Acting, you know?
Acting without having people hurling
papier-mch boulders at you all (BLEEP)
Day. It was great, you know?
I like them both. I like boulders.
I'm fine with that.
This production runs
like a well-oiled machine,
and, sure, that starts from the top,
but, I mean,
we all love the show.
The gaffers, the lighting guy, the medic,
the makeup and the caterers.
It's like a family.
The writers were trying to come up
with a catch phrase.
"I can get behind that,"
was something we tried for a while.
Anyway, I mean, I'd actually like
to do some writing.
Maybe have a baby.
(EX CLAIMS)
It just hit me.
Sweet...
(BLEEPING)
And we can get away with that,
too, because it's cable.
You can't get there without the fans,
right? I have to thank them.
I've got to thank specifically the ones...
Oh, God, what's it called?
SaveDrLevant. Com.
Have you seen the site?
I mean, it's insane.
Apparently they get dozens of hits
a month, whatever. I think that's a lot.
But between them and the ad in Variety
that they put out, I'm pretty sure
that went a long way towards convincing
the producers to take me back.
Have me... To invite me back.
It wasn't their decision, you know.
They called, said, "Hey, do you want it?"
You know, and I was ready.
What I think really makes this show
what it is,
is the chemistry with the cast.
(MUSICAL CELL PHONE RINGING)
Yeah. Oh, could you hold on?
Stop the tape.
Who does he think he is?
Well, you tell that ungrateful little (BLEEP)
Bag to shove it up his (BLEEP)
Yeah, yeah, let him try to get a job
that pays this much.
You weren't rolling, were... Okay.
What... What was I saying?
Oh, yes, the cast.
Holy...
(BLEEPING)
That would be, like, a 19.
That's it? You're good? All right.
Can I get my (BLEEP) sandwich, please?
All right. Hey, thanks, man.
Science fiction is an existential metaphor
that allows us to tell stories
about the human condition.
Isaac Asimov once said, "Individual
science fiction stories may seem
"as trivial as ever to the blinder critics
and philosophers of today,
"but the core of science fiction,
its essence, has become crucial
"to our salvation,
if we are to be saved at all."