Hello, and welcome to Sol's Diner.
I'm Val. I'll be your waitress today.
Have you had a chance
to look over the menu?
Might I suggest the meatball sandwich?
It's the owner's personal favorite.
WOMAN: Sounds good.
- Sir?
- Hi.
Two Junior Meals for the kids,
and I'll have the club sandwich.
- Okay.
- Oh, can I get some extra pickles on that?
- No problem.
- Thank you.
VAL: Waters all around?
- Sure.
Okay.
WOMAN: Okay, once the food comes,
that's it for the games.
All right! Wallets and purses
on the table in front of you, now!
Valuables in here.
Hey! You listening to me?
(GROANING)
What did you do?
I don't know.
(WOMAN CHATTERING)
Thank you.
Your menu.
WAITRESS: And for you, sir.
Fancy.
Well, I know you don't
get off the base much,
except for official business,
so I thought I'd take you somewhere nice.
Well, I don't mind telling you
I've been looking forward
to this little date all week.
I wouldn't exactly call it a date. It's...
Oh, I've watched enough of your television
to know what a date is, Daniel.
It's a romantic event typified
by dinner, movie, and/ or karaoke,
and usually culminating in a night of...
Okay, this is definitely not a date.
It's two friends and co-workers
out for dinner.
- Oh, well, I...
- WAITER: Hi.
Hi.
- Can I start you off with a drink?
- Absolutely.
Well, tonight's feature martinis
are the chocolate, passion fruit,
and shochu plum.
They all sound wonderful.
So one of each, then?
Yeah, I think
we're going to pace ourselves.
She'll do the passion fruit.
(EX CLAIMS)
And I'm going to have the bottled water.
Sure.
Listen...
- Let me start.
- Okay.
Look, I know it hasn't been easy for you,
adjusting to your new life here,
learning to trust other people,
and, most importantly,
refusing the temptation
to fall back on your old ways.
But you have worked hard
to make a place for yourself with us and...
And dinner tonight
is my way of saying thank you.
Thank you for proving me right
when I said we could
take a chance on you.
I don't know what to say.
Just say what you were going to say
before I interrupted.
Okay. I need to use the bathroom.
Yeah. It's...
Okay.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
(GRUNTING)
(MOANING)
She needs some fresh air.
Your friend has taken ill.
What? Where is she?
She was escorted outside
by another gentleman.
ATHENA: I apologize for that.
The surgery was performed
in a moving car.
They were more concerned about
removing the subcutaneous transmitter
than being gentle about it.
Do I know you?
You did, a long time ago.
Qetesh, the Goa'uld
that once occupied your body,
was a rival of mine.
She was a very intelligent adversary,
which is why I eventually decided
to partner with her.
In retrospect,
it's also the reason I should have
been more careful about trusting her.
VALA: As the host to her Goa'uld,
I was an unwilling participant
in many of Qetesh's thoughtless actions.
So, if this is a revenge thing,
your anger is, well, misplaced.
This isn't a revenge thing.
Oh.
This is a search for answers.
My position in the Trust
has afforded me considerable resources.
(GROANING)
Ever since I heard
that you joined Stargate Command,
I've been watching and waiting
for an opportunity,
which finally presented itself tonight.
What exactly do you want from me?
The code to an Ancient tablet
that I helped Qetesh locate long ago.
A treasure map of sorts.
She was supposed to share it with me,
but instead decided to keep it for herself.
From what I understand,
she was never able to decipher it.
I'd like that opportunity.
To be honest, it doesn't ring a bell, so...
That's because you've suppressed many of
the details from your time as Qetesh.
The full genetic memory of the Goa'uld
would drive
your inferior human mind insane.
Luckily, we have this device
to help us find what we're looking for.
This'll take a while.
I'll leave you to it then.
We've got the local authorities
searching the area
and conducting interviews
with every possible witness.
So far, they've come up empty.
General, there's no question
the Trust is behind her disappearance.
I mean, they're the only ones
with the resources
capable of pulling something like this off.
Agreed. I've already put a call
through to Agent Barrett.
He's got his people working on it.
We'll find her.
KAKALIOS: We're starting to get images
from her suppressed memory.
Dial it down.
(GRUNTING)
How are you feeling?
A little dizzy.
A little tired. And very, very angry.
Oh, that's because the flashbacks
you're experiencing
are dredging up
some long-buried emotions
that may be coloring your conscious mind.
I'm going to kill both of you
in the most painful way possible.
Things will go a lot faster if you just relax.
Whenever you're ready.
(GROANING)
Jackson, rise and shine.
What is it? What's going on?
Barrett, he came through for us.
He just sent over a list of
suspected Trust safe houses.
Hopefully our girl's in one of them.
LANDRY: Team One, what's your status?
Team One is in position.
Team Two?
Team Two in position.
- Team Three?
- LEADER: Team Three is in position.
(SHUDDERING)
- Do you know what I think the problem is?
- That I can't strangle you?
You're fighting the process.
In the end, all you're really doing
is delaying the inevitable.
Why don't we try and keep an open mind?
All five teams are in position.
You have a go.
Who was that?
Turn it down.
Damn.
Maybe they'll have better luck
at the other locations.
- Cover the door.
- Right.
(GROANING)
(GASPS)
It's all right. We're here to help.
CARTER: Four out of the five safe houses
we hit were empty.
Only one, it turned out,
was still in play, and that was SG-15's.
We lost them and three members
of the local team.
One Trust operative survived
the explosion with minor injuries.
He confirmed that the place was rigged
to blow in the event it was stormed.
He also confirmed
that Vala was being held at that location.
So, it's possible they moved her
before the place was raided?
Unlikely. They wouldn't have had the time.
Besides, the guy we caught claims
he saw Vala making a run for it.
Then she could've gotten out on her own.
If that were the case, why has
she not yet attempted to contact us?
JACKSON: So, what did you want with her?
I mean, what exactly was going on
in that warehouse?
Look, I already told you. I can't say.
It's not that I don't want to help you,
but right now,
I'm more concerned for my well-being.
We can protect you.
No, you can't.
Okay.
He's all yours.
Where are you going?
I'll be out in the hall.
Just yell loudly if you need me.
Don't bother.
Your Jaffa interrogation tactics
won't work.
Believe me, I've seen
some pretty horrible things in my life.
You can't break me.
(INAUDIBLE)
A member of this facility
gets kidnapped unchallenged.
It's no wonder
he doesn't think we can protect him.
But we can protect him.
Yeah, by locking him away
for the rest of his life.
What can you say? There's a downside
to working for super villains.
Well, this is probably going to
take a while.
What do you say we grab a bite to eat?
You're done?
He was surprisingly forthcoming.
Whenever you're ready, honey.
How you doing?
- How are you doing?
- Terrific.
I'm Sal, the owner.
Sal, the owner of Sol's Diner?
Yeah, Sol was the original owner.
I bought the place from him.
Oh.
- So, how was lunch?
- Delicious.
Delicious enough to pay for it?
Yes. If I had the money, I would
certainly have paid for that meal
and given the lovely waitress
a sizeable gratuity.
The service was impeccable.
Look, lady, everybody's got problems.
I got rent on this place,
a mortgage, a wife, three kids,
and a Shih Tzu
with a recurring gastrointestinal condition
that requires a very specialized diet,
all right?
That requires a very specialized diet,
Okay.
I'm sorry for trying to cheat you.
Okay. All right, look, if I let you leave,
can I trust you to come back
with the money you owe me?
No.
No? What do you mean, no?
What, you're telling me
you can't be trusted?
Truthfully?
I don't know.
I... I don't remember.
I have no idea who I am,
much less what I'm capable of.
All I know for certain is that about
an hour ago, I was lost, hungry,
and drawn to the delightful aroma
of the blue plate special.
Is this a joke?
I have absolutely no memory of my life
prior to wandering in here.
If that's true,
we need to get you to a hospital.
No hospitals!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hang on.
Hey.
- Everything okay here, Sal?
- Yeah. Everything's fine.
Don't worry about it.
- Let me go.
- Go where?
Please?
- What, you got a home, you got a family?
- I don't know.
I would pay you back. I would.
Just right now,
I just don't have the means.
Maybe I can do something to help you.
Jackson, how's it going?
Well, from what we learned
from the Trust operative
and the information provided to us
from the Jaffa and the Tok'ra,
this is what I've been able
to piece together so far.
Athena, the Greek goddess of war,
a.k.a. Charlotte Mayfield,
a.k.a. The Goa'uld responsible
for kidnapping Vala.
Now, according to what I've learned,
she was a minor player
who rose to mid-tier status
by pursuing alliances
with more powerful rivals:
Cronos, Camulus, Svarog, and even Anubis
when he was first on the outs
with the System Lords.
So, her partnering up with Ba'al
is just her latest power play?
No, it's more than that.
You see, we know Athena was once allied
with Qetesh,
the Goa'uld that formerly inhabited Vala.
See, apparently,
Qetesh double-crossed her
when they partnered up to search
for the Clava Thessara Infinitas,
the key to infinite treasure.
Now, according to legend,
it will allow he who possesses it entry
to a vast storehouse of riches hidden away
by the Ancients prior to their ascension.
Wow, that's big.
Yeah, and by all indications,
nothing but an elaborate hoax.
- So, they didn't find it?
- No, but for some reason,
Qetesh wanted Athena to think she had.
Athena believed her,
which is why she went after Vala.
And she used Ba'al's resources
here on Earth to get her.
Which reminds me, I'm supposed
to check in with Major Harper.
He's got people querying hospitals
in the area where Vala disappeared.
It's possible she may have been injured
and has been unable to contact us.
Hey, listen,
I spoke with the medical examiner's office.
They're doing DNA testing
on the remains recovered at the blast site,
but it's going to take a while.
You know, when Vala first disappeared
when the Ori gate was destroyed,
I refused to write her off.
Although the odds were against it,
I believed somehow
she'd found a way to survive,
and it turned out I was right.
I want to be right again.
Sure.
- I just figured you should know.
- Yeah. Thank you.
Major Harper, please.
I don't care what the so-called experts
have to say.
I want you to free up the capital
and move it into a company
called Beringer Consolidated.
I have it on good authority
that they'll be announcing
a major breakthrough before week's end.
All right.
The DNA results are in.
They were able to ID 12 victims,
none of them our girl.
My guess is there wasn't enough
of her left to run tests on.
Or there wasn't anything left
because she didn't die in that explosion.
If she got out, she would've gone
straight back to Stargate Command.
They wouldn't still be looking for her.
I don't know, maybe you're right.
Maybe she is dead.
But until we have confirmation,
I want you to keep looking for her, too.
(CLEARING THROAT)
Okay, dead cow on a turban,
hold the yellow, extra spud mush.
Listen to you. You've been practicing.
Very nice.
Val, you okay?
Hey.
You all right?
Is it that visions thing again?
Look, I told you, you should
go get yourself checked out, honey.
No.
Sal, what am I doing,
working here, sleeping out the back,
watching reruns of The X-Files
in my spare time?
I appreciate everything
you've done for me,
but I've got to tell you,
I've been thinking about leaving.
So, where are you going to go?
I don't know, but this isn't my life.
It just doesn't feel right.
Trust me, sweetheart,
running away isn't
going to make things better for you.
Working tables here may not feel right,
but at least you've got a roof
over your head
and some friends who care about you.
It may not feel like your life right now.
Just give it some time, okay?
- Okay.
- Good.
Now, get back to work
before I fire your butt.
Hello, and welcome to Sol's Diner.
I'm Val. I'll be your waitress today.
Have you had a chance
to look over the menu?
MAN: All right! Wallets and purses
on the table in front of you, now!
(MAN GROANING)
(UTENSILS CLANGING)
What did you do?
I don't know.
Okay. Name?
You know my name.
You're a regular at the deli.
So, what, is "Val" short for "Valerie"?
Okay.
Yes. Valerie.
Last name?
Todad.
Valerie Todad.
Look, Val, is there any reason
why you don't want me
to know your real last name?
No, of course not.
I'm just a very private person.
Would you mind
if I took a moment to freshen up?
Sure. I need a coffee anyway.
Straight ahead, second door on your left.
Oh, sorry.
Oh. Hello.
I didn't know how long
we were going to be,
so I was just going out
to get us some lunch.
Run it through the channels,
see if anything comes up.
I don't understand.
I didn't do anything illegal.
I didn't hurt anyone.
Well, apart from those two fellows who,
from what I understand,
I was totally within my rights to hurt.
Witnesses say you took them both down
without even breaking a sweat.
How did you manage that?
- Instinct.
- No. I think training.
Don't suppose you want to tell me
where you learned those moves?
That's what I thought.
- Sir.
- What is it, Chief?
I thought you should see this.
A THENA: Listen to me.
This is what you're going to do.
You're going to sell all of our
remaining stock in Beringer Consolidated.
I have it on good authority
that they're about to be rocked
by a major accounting scandal that will...
Nathan, I'm going to have to call you back.
- What is it?
- We got a call.
Apparently, some people,
they're looking for you.
- Who?
- The United States Air Force.
They're sending a Colonel Carter
to pick you up.
No.
- What do you mean, no?
- I'd rather stay here.
If you need me to commit a crime,
I'd be happy to oblige.
Look, Val, I don't pretend to know
what you're all about,
but when people start throwing
around words like "national security,"
there's not a lot I can do.
All right, I'll be honest with you.
The reason why I can't tell you who I am,
is because I don't know.
I don't remember.
I don't know where I'm from.
I'm not even sure if Val is my real name.
My memory only goes as far back
as that day, two weeks ago,
when I wandered into the deli for a lunch
I couldn't pay for.
I don't remember any of
my life before that,
although I do have flashbacks.
Occasionally, they're terrifying,
like something out of a horror movie,
but they don't make much sense.
I was hoping that, sooner or later,
my memories would just come back,
or that something would help remind me
of who I really am,
but after what happened today,
I'm not sure I want to know anymore.
You know, Val, it would be a lot easier
if you'd just be honest with me.
I'm Colonel Carter.
I'm here to take custody of the prisoner.
Prisoner?
Would you mind telling me
what this is all about?
The government has been looking
for Miss Mal Doran for a while now.
RYAN: Why? What did she do?
WOMAN: I'm sorry, Detective.
That's classified.
Don't let them take me away.
We appreciate your cooperation
in this matter, sir.
No. No, no, please.
Mr. Ryan...
Detective Ryan?
Hi. Lieutenant Colonel Samantha Carter,
United States Air Force.
We're here for the Jane Doe
you've been holding.
Another Colonel Carter just picked her up.
- When?
- About a minute ago.
Yeah, there were two of them. You must
have passed them on your way in here.
Black sedan, government plates.
They were headed for the freeway.
CARTER: We need you to move that car!
I'm commandeering your bike! Get off!
Why won't you tell me where we're going?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
You all right?
Hey, everything's going to be okay.
(SCREAMS)
Son of a... Mother...
(GROANING)
Is anybody hurt?
Throw me the keys.
Run away.
Vala, wait!
What did you just call me?
Vala.
Get up.
Get up!
- Where are we going?
- Just drive.
- You know, I'm bleeding here.
- Shut up.
Oh, boy.
What are you doing?
Checking to see
if I still have both of my kidneys.
Vala, what the hell is going on here?
- You know me.
- Yeah, of course. Why?
You don't remember me?
I don't remember much of anything,
least of all who I am,
or why everyone is after me.
That's why I brought you here.
You're going to supply me
with some much-needed answers.
You know,
maybe we should call the rest of the team.
They're generally better at answers.
Okay, here goes.
Your name is Vala Mal Doran.
You're a member of Stargate Command,
a top-secret facility located
beneath Cheyenne Mountain.
It's the command center
for a military organization
responsible for off-world exploration
and reconnaissance
by means of a device known as a Stargate,
a portal which allows near-instantaneous
transport between planets.
How am I doing so far?
Not good.
I know it sounds crazy, but it's the truth.
Okay. So, we're space explorers?
Well, technically,
me and my team are the explorers.
You're just along for the ride because...
Well, you're not originally from this planet.
You're an alien.
And I mean that
in the nicest possible way.
You know, when you say "alien,"
people think green skin, four eyes,
tentacles, what have you,
but the reality is very, very different.
I'm borrowing some more money.
Look, take you, for example.
You're human.
Hell, you're more human than most of
my neighbors, especially that guy in 304.
I'll be back.
Look, since you're part of the team,
maybe you should think about...
Won't be long.
...trusting me?
Or un-cuffing me?
Or giving me my pants back?
Okay, just wait right here.
I'll be right back.
Well, he's of no help.
All he remembers was the gun,
then he was off to the races.
Presumably, you are searching
for the missing vehicle.
We've got all available units looking.
In the meantime, it turns out the deceased
in that overturned sedan
were all carrying phony ID.
The license plate was also bogus.
As for the car itself,
it was a company vehicle registered
to a Forsythe Chemicals.
But that's a dead end because, apparently,
they reported the car
missing this morning.
Of course they did.
(MOBILE PHONE RINGING)
Carter.
All right. Thank you.
We've got a lock on Cam's transmitter.
Thank you, Detective.
Yeah. Sure. Any time.
Okay, I think I've figured out
what happened to you,
why you don't remember anything.
Oh, good.
Does it involve an alien abduction?
Well, in as much as that you're an alien
who was abducted, yes.
You were undergoing a procedure
which was designed to dig up
some of your suppressed memories.
The scientist that we captured told us
that during the procedure,
the device was destroyed,
which allowed you
the opportunity to escape.
From the aliens.
No, they weren't aliens.
They're working for an alien,
but that's not really important.
Vala isn't a particularly alien name.
So, I'm thinking that this device
was in the middle of digging up
these suppressed memories
when it overloads and fries your brain.
So, instead of helping you remember,
it actually made you forget.
Everything.
Disodium guanylate.
That would make a great alien name,
don't you think?
I can understand
why you might be having difficulty
believing what I'm telling you,
but there is one thing you cannot deny.
There are some very, very bad people
after you.
And how do I know
you're not one of them?
Because I saved you from them!
What if they were trying
to save me from you?
How am I supposed to know?
Let me take you back
to Stargate Command.
We have a device that
can help you remember.
I thought you said
the device was destroyed.
It's a different device.
It's one I brought back
from another planet last year.
Oh, good. Were they having a sale?
Understood.
We intercepted a communication
from Stargate Command.
They found him. Turn around.
This isn't what it looks like.
(MAN CHATTERING ON POLICE RADIO)
- What?
- Nothing.
I just think it's funny
how you're always losing your pants.
I'm not "always losing my pants."
It's happened twice.
Twice is not always.
DANIEL: Okay, thank you.
We've got something on Vala.
DANIEL: Vala?
Vala, it's me, Daniel.
We know you're in here.
There's nowhere else you could've gone.
Vala?
DANIEL: Vala?
I know you're scared,
but we're not here to hurt you.
We can help you remember.
Colonel Carter!
(GUNFIRE)
Get out of my way.
Get out of my way or I will shoot you.
You don't remember who you are, but I do.
You won't shoot.
(GROANS)
If I let you go, I know
you're going to make yourself disappear.
You've been running so long,
it's almost second nature to you.
You don't remember it,
but you made a decision to stop running.
It's over.
Now it's time to come home.
Daniel.
(SIRENS WAILING)
You know, I don't mind getting shot,
but I pulled a hammy
when I took out that last Trust operative.
At least you didn't lose your pants.
You wanted to see me?
- Hey, what did Dr. Lam say?
- I've been cleared for active duty.
LANDRY: Glad to hear it.
What's this?
Let's just call it a welcome-back present.
- These are...
- Team badges.
You're now officially a member of SG-1.
Congratulations. You earned it.
Perhaps a celebration is in order.
That's a great idea.
We can check out that new rib joint
near my place.
Excellent.
Of course, that means we'll have to wait
until next week to complete our date.
It wasn't a date.
(STUTTERING) It was two friends
and co-workers out for dinner.
Seriously.
It wasn't a date.