Previously on Jericho...
Bonnie's dead.
Goetz is off limits.
No threats, no retribution,
no exceptions.
Stanley!
I'm declaring Jericho to be
an open insurrection.
Western states have
all fallen in with Cheyenne.
Texans are getting close
to siding with Cheyenne.
If that happens, it's a ball game.
I have one of the bombs.
That bomb is the key
to bringing down this Government.
- They'll never let you get it to Texas.
- Okay, John Smith.
We found a package.
You're not just
some innocent whistle-blower.
The last time I blew the whistle,
I took out 23 American cities.
The man behind
the September attacks
is pretty confident that he can
use it to destroy the city of Cheyenne.
When do we leave?
Mary arranged for us
to meet one of her runners
this side of the checkpoint
on Route 309.
He should be able to
get us through to Wyoming.
Hopefully just outside
of Cheyenne.
We're on our own from there.
The streets are going to be crawling
with soldiers from Cheyenne
and mercenaries from
Ravenwood on police patrol.
And as I am enemy number
one right now,
we're going to need
someplace safe fast.
- What about your contact there?
- Who, Cheung?
Yeah.
I got a lead on his location, but
it might take awhile to track him down.
We're going to need
something more immediate.
- Look, Jake.
- Yeah.
When we get out there,
the mission is everything.
- Yeah, I get it.
- No, no, see...
I got to be sure.
I'm asking for your help,
but I can't afford for you to go off
book out there and I don't
have any room for debate,
so if you've got any questions,
now's the time.
- Yeah, I've got a question.
- Go ahead.
How are we going to find the bomb?
No idea. Anything else?
Insurgent activity
in your piece of the world
has reached
unacceptable levels, Major.
The Cheyenne government
will not tolerate this.
Your orders are to begin
Phase Three operations immediately.
Sir,
with all due respect,
I believe it's premature
to move to phase three.
This place is still salvageable.
Two prisoners escaped
your custody yesterday.
You've lost three supply convoys
through raiding parties the past week.
The time for restraint has passed.
You have your orders.
This insurrection must end.
20-minute orientation,
an hour roundtable discussion,
two hours for lunch?
A thousand person
town hall meeting and boom,
the Second Amendment's gone.
It's a lot easier
to pacify a country
when its citizens can't shoot back.
I'm sick of people telling me
I worry too much.
This is the Constitution we're
talking about, not a stereo manual.
We'll just keep raising our voices.
I don't see
what other choice we have.
Hey, Mr. Mayor.
How are you, Gray?
Well, you mean aside from
the embolism you just gave me?
Let's take a walk, I'll explain.
Yeah, I-I'd appreciate that.
- Didn't take them long, did it?
- For what?
For J&R to build their
own private country.
Season 2 - Episode 07
- Patriots and Tyrants -
Transcript: Raceman - Forom
Sync: ¤AkaZab¤
Subtitle: A²S Team
www.All-about-Subs.fr
I can't believe things
got that bad that fast.
I should've been there.
I'm wasting my time here.
What do you mean?
This convention is a Sham.
And when it's done,
I'm don't think there's anything
this government is not going
to have the power
to do in the name
of national security.
How long till they vote to ratify?
I don't know. They're talking
about speeding things up to coincide
with Texas joining
the Allied States.
They're that close to a deal
with Texas?
Well, Cheyenne's pretty confident.
And they've done a real good job
of painting the Texas into a corner.
But, Jake,
you...
you still haven't told me
what you're doing here.
You need to go home, Gray.
The town, they need somebody that
they can look to who's not in hiding.
Someone to speak for them.
But they need you back.
You spelled "Cheyenne" wrong.
Hey, Cheung.
I've spent the past few months
infiltrating J&R's secure data pipeline.
You know what's floating
around that pipeline right now?
That the last loose nuke from the
September attacks is here in Cheyenne?
The last loose nuke from the September
attacks is here in Cheyenne.
- Want to explain how it got here?
- No.
Not really.
I'm here to get it back.
Hell of a lot's happened
over the last few months.
I'll try and fill you in.
Start with that.
What's "Phase Three"?
As of 11:00 a.m. Tomorrow,
they are going to declare whole
sections of town centers of resistance.
Anyone caught inside them after the
deadline will be considered insurgents.
We're talking neighborhoods.
We're talking Main Street.
Come tomorrow, Beck's men
are going to start shooting at people.
We're running out of options.
Our options are pretty clear.
Either we start shooting back,.
or we give up our homes.
- You don't have to fight them alone.
- What are you talking about?
What's happening to you guys right now
happened to us in New Bern weeks ago.
We know what you're up against.
Constantino knows how to fight it.
Not a chance in hell.
With an enemy this big,
you really don't have the luxury
of being picky about your allies.
We can help each other.
Eric, are you kidding?
What am I supposed to say?
You say no.
You say you're not interested
in shaking hands
with an animal
like Phil Constantino.
Say something.
I'm done with this.
Stanley!
Bonnie has been dead
for four days,
and her body's still sitting in a box
in the medical center
because I'm hiding out
in some garage!
Stanley, where are you going?
To bury my sister.
I need to do this.
Go with him.
Get it done.
Bring him back here
as soon as possible.
Set up the meeting.
Sit down.
I'd rather not.
Can we make this quick?
I have to move out
of my house by 11:00 tomorrow.
Someone declared my street
a center of resistance.
Why'd you do it?
What are you talking about?
Yesterday, a terror suspect
was located not far from here:
Robert Hawkins.
He evaded capture, but we recovered
a nuclear weapon from his possession.
The same kind used
in the September attacks.
What does that have to do with me?
There was an aerial search
of this town.
Should've exposed the bomb,
but didn't.
We checked the original data,
and found a page missing
from the copy kept in my office.
You took it.
You had access to this office
I trusted you.
- I stood up for you.
- You're right.
I took it.
Why?
He told me the people
you're working for are wrong.
And I believe him.
Do you realize I could have
you imprisoned, possibly executed?
He said this government
is corrupt and illegitimate.
That it lied about who attacked
us so it could seize power.
You're naive.
- And you're a coward.
- Excuse me?
You know there's something wrong
with this country.
And you refuse
to open your eyes and see it.
- My eyes are open.
- No, they aren't.
And everyone in this town
is suffering because of it.
Lieutenant!
This woman is under arrest.
Get her out of here.
Here's what I got.
It won't take them long
to inspect the bomb,
verify it is what they think it is.
To make it disappear for good,
they're gonna have move it to disposal
facility somewhere outside of town.
It'll be easier for us to hit it
when it's on the road get the transport.
That's the problem.
There's nothing scheduled.
No convoys out of the
military base in the area.
No shipments in or out
of the secure J&R facilities.
No nothing.
You know what?
There wouldn't be.
Security draws attention.
So less security, less attention.
We need someplace off the books.
In Afghanistan, there were a few supply
routes that would get really nasty.
They would shoot at anything
with a J&R logo on it.
So we started making our runs
in ambulances.
Check the local hospitals.
- St. Francis Hospital.
- What?
They reported a gas leak
a little while ago.
They're closing
the doors for the afternoon.
How many paramedics
carry a nine millimeter?
It sure looks like
they're expecting someone.
Yeah.
- Let's go.
- Not him.
- What?
- Sorry, Jake,
I don't know you...
... I don't trust you.
Hey, hey.
You keep the engine running.
If something goes wrong, we're going
to need to get out of here fast. Right?
Jake?
Yeah.
Green light from the colonel,
we're moving out ASAP.
Double-check that,
make sure it's secure before we go.
Stay right there.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- You?
- Yeah,
I'm okay.
Hello, Hawkins.
Smith?
I d... I didn't think
that you did
your own dirty wo-work.
I wasn't supposed to.
I had hoped
you were going to help me.
Now, I need that bomb.
Hawkins!
I'm okay, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Jake, Jake,
the ambulance.
I got you.
Get in.
How bad is it?
I've had worse.
What the hell
are we going to do now?
Just keep driving.
Just keep driving and...
and let me think of something.
Sir, can I get your signature here?
What is it?
Inventory of the evidence retrieved
from the terrorist Hawkins' vehicle.
Sidearm, fake IDs, laptop.
Transport's waiting outside
to take it to Camp Liberty.
The evidence is here?
Yes, sir, boxed up
and ready to ship.
I want to see it first.
Sir, it's catalogued and sealed.
Then I'll unseal it.
Yes, sir.
Hawkins.
We got to get off the street
or they're going
to be on us in no time.
We're not going
to make it to Texas like this.
Yes, we will.
Okay.
You'll keep going south...
for about...
- ten blocks.
- Why?
You just do it, Jake.
Hey, Chavez, I'm gonna need a favor,
and I'm going to need it fast.
Hello, Eric.
Strange meeting.
I'd have figured you
and I ever got this close again,
It'd be at the end of a gun.
A few weeks ago, I was on my way to
New Bern to put a bullet in your head.
What stopped you?
Beck.
Interesting.
Is that something
you still want to do?
Every day.
Something to be said for honesty.
Russell told me
about your situation.
If you and I are going
to be able to help each other,
there's something you're going
to have to understand.
I'm listening.
We win by making them
lose their desire to fight.
It's the only way.
I know.
Then, when you take out a convoy,
you got to stop leaving soldiers alive.
Every soldier
we take out costs them,
forces them to train replacements,
saps their will.
It's not going to happen
in a day or a week.
It's a process
that could take years.
I need to know if that's something
you're willing to undertake.
Hawkins.
Yeah!
Hawkins, I need to know
where we're going!
Okay.
That way.
They're not just going
to open the gate for us.
Straight in there.
Hang on.
Don't shoot, don't shoot.
Don't shoot.
We need help.
All right, we need help.
My friend's been hurt. Please.
Sir, this is a Texas embassy.
You don't understand.
My friend's been shot.
This isn't a hospital,
this is sovereign Texas soil.
Please.
On the ground now!
We are seeking political asylum.
Sir, we've got a situation
at the gate.
Go ahead.
I've got Cheyenne military here.
They claim a terrorist entered the
embassy. They want us to surrender him.
- Stand by.
- Yes, sir.
I want those gates closed now,
radio down.
Tell 'em if anybody from Cheyenne tries
to breach, consider it an act of war.
Ambassador Sam Travis.
You got important friends.
I just got off the phone
with San Antonio.
The governor's instructed me
to accept your request for asylum.
Get this man immediate
medical attention.
I need a medic out here ASAP.
Right away, sir.
Sir.
Yeah, I know.
Let's get it inside.
What are you doing here?
We came to help.
You were right.
Right about what?
Constantino.
There's something he lost
that I don't want to ever give up.
I mean, we're right
and Cheyenne is wrong, but...
the moment we start killing
American soldiers,
all that changes.
So what do we do
when they start shooting at us?
I got to believe Beck doesn't
want that any more than we do.
But if he wants to make that decision,
I'm not going to make it easy for him.
So I'm gonna be standing
on this hill in
the open with my friends...
doing something I know is right.
Hey, guys.
This is about all I can do from here.
We're going to have to find a way
and get you to an ER.
What do you mean, "no"?
Could you excuse us, please?
Jake...
... I am not important.
What is is getting that bomb
to Texas
with no detours.
Now, you tell me
that you understand what it is
- you're in the middle of right how.
- I understand it's important,
Yeah, it's important.
Like whatever happens
in the next few hours
could determine
the course of things for...
for years to come.
You know, maybe our history
for the next hundred years.
That is the responsibility
we got here.
And if that comes at a terrible cost,
then so be it.
Because that's the only way
that things get better,
and it's the only way
that people stay free.
That's why I do what I do.
Yes, sir. Stanley Richmond
and a group of Rangers.
I'll bring 'em in.
- Ma'am, you need to clear this area.
- Please.
My fiancé is burying his sister up
there. He's waited four days to do this.
- Please, let him finish.
- We've already called it in.
- We have orders to apprehend him now.
- Corporal Adams, but you have him.
We have nowhere to run.
Just let him put his sister
in the ground.
It costs you nothing.
Do-Do you have sisters?
Or a girlfriend?
A wife?
Please.
You have 30 minutes.
After that,
they're all coming with us.
So say your good-byes.
Thank you.
ID, sir?
Excuse me?
Who are you, sir?
I'm Gray Anderson.
I'm the mayor of this town.
I don't how much longer we
can keep 'em talking at the gates.
We're going to have
to get you out of here.
Okay.
We're going to take you out
back to the property next door.
Bomb's ready in a car
with diplomatic plates.
Should get you through to the airport.
The plane's in Hangar 22.
We'll...
I've had a bad feeling
about President Tomarchio.
I'm glad somebody's gonna finally
show the world what he's really about.
That's the plan, so...
Yeah.
The bomb's stored.
Let's get out of here.
- No. I'm staying.
- What?
It's at least an hour's
flight from here to Texas.
Is no way it takes them that long
to find you in the plane.
- You don't know that.
- It's the only way, okay?
I got to buy you some time,
draw their attention.
You don't stand chance
you stay here on your own.
And it doesn't matter, because
the mission is everything. I told you.
No, it isn't.
Come on.
Damn it, Jake!
I am not debating this.
I'm not debating, either.
I'm ignoring you.
- Wait here.
- Yes, sir.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
You're all free to go.
Wait a minute.
That's it?
About 20 minutes ago,
I notified my company commanders.
That I'd no longer be taking orders
from the Cheyenne leadership.
I believe this government
is corrupt at its core.
Its actions are criminal,
and I no longer recognize
their right to lead.
So what happens now?
My company commanders
are deliberating,
trying to decide whether
to report me up the chain of command.
In all likelihood, I'll be...
charged by the end of the day.
Sent to Cheyenne to face
a court-martial for treason.
But until then,
I'm still in charge,
so you take your time.
And then go home.
Unidentified Cessna
on heading zero-eight-six,
identify.
Unidentified Cessna
on heading zero-eight-six,
identify.
Cessna on heading zero-eight-six:
Sierra-Tango-Nine.
This is Allied States
Air Force Whiskey-Two-Three.
We have orders to intercept
and escort you back
to Rogers Field in Cheyenne.
Sierra-Tango-Nine,
confirm transmission.
Sierra-Tango-Nine, negative.
This is a Texan diplomatic flight
out of Cheyenne en route to San Antonio.
Sierra-Tango-Nine, either put down,
or we will put you down.
You have 30 seconds to comply.
This is a consular flight flying
the flag of a sovereign nation.
This is your last chance,
Sierra-Tango-Nine.
We will put you
in the dirt if we have to.
You've got ten seconds.
Time's up.
We're going weapons hot
to engage. Out.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute!
Sierra-Tango-Nine, do you copy?
Sierra-Tango-Nine, affirmative.
Jake Green, this is Colonel Thompson,
Texas Air National Guard.
I've got orders direct
from Governor Todd
to make sure you arrive safely
at Lackland Air Force Base.
Copy that, Texas ANG.
Son, I don't know
what you're carrying,
but whatever it is better be good,
'cause I think I just declared war
on Cheyenne.
Stanley...
What is it?
I thought I lost you.
No way. You could never lose me.
When those soldiers
were coming for you,
all I could think was,
"He doesn't know
what he means to me.
"He's going away forever,
and I haven't told him."
Well, I'm here now.
You are everything to me.
I want to...
I want to walk down this hill
and make a home with you.
I want to make a life with you.
Through anything and everything.
From this day forward,
for the rest of my life.
That sounded a lot like a...
It was.
Well, what do I say?
Just say I do.
I do.
I told the lieutenant
to release you without condition.
You don't need to be here.
I know.
What's happening in there?
They're trying to decide
what to do about me.
Gave 'em Hawkins' laptop.
Let them see the evidence
for themselves.
You were right.
About everything.
Thanks for not giving up on me.
Sir...
... your orders?
Pass the word to your men.
Tell them there's a fight on its way.
I thought I told you to stay
out of trouble while I was gone.
Welcome back.
Thank you.
- How was the convention?
- Terrifying.
The government
we find ourselves living under
is in dire need of replacement.
Well, that oughta make our
feelings pretty clear about it.
That?
Yeah, I just...
thought it's been a little
too long since Johnston Green's
had anything to say about
the way things are going around here.
Now seemed like a good
time for him to be heard.
Hey. We made it.
What now?
There's a team of engineers waiting
for delivery of this thing right away.
Once they inspect it,
things in this country
are goin to change pretty fast.
Cheyenne's cover-up
will be exposed.
Texas sides with Columbus,
throws its weight behind them,
and then the main event.
The next American civil war.
Yeah. And thanks
to you and Hawkins,
looks like the good guys
are going to have a fighting chance.
Thank you.
Hey, don't take this
the wrong way.
But you look like crap.
You all right?
I think we started a war today.
Let me guess not your first?
Jake, this war is coming
with or without us.
I just hope we did enough
to make it a fair fight.
Yeah.
How does it feel?
What?
Making history.
Subtitle: A²S Team
- www.All-about-Subs.fr -