Previously on Jericho...
Jake, this is Ted Lewis.
- Hey, how you doing?
- We grew up together over in New Bern.
And this is Russell and Mike.
Hey. Yeah, we met.
I'm Major Beck,
10th Mountain Division.
I want you to be my liaison
to the people of New Bern and Jericho.
I'm sending you a private contractor
who knows the area.
He'll take care of the day-to-day
administration of the town
while you find the terrorist.
Western states have all fallen
in with Cheyenne.
They're strong and getting stronger.
This is our new mission.
Expose Cheyenne's secret
before they take over the whole country.
I have one of the bombs.
What is this?
Targets, specifications,
contingencies.
Jennings & Rall
put it all in one place.
How do you know about this?
Because... I helped write it.
Mimi, this is Trish Merrick.
She's with Jennings & Rall.
I'm so glad we have you on board,
I can't even tell you.
There's a $10,000 discrepancy.
Someone took it.
I'm the chief administrator of this town
and I want your ledger.
Bonnie, right?
Is Mimi Clark inside?
Mimi going to be okay?
She's lost a lot of blood.
What do you got?
Weapons were nine millimeters.
The tire tracks out front...
look like a Humvee.
Ravenwood.
But why?
What would they want here?
Whatever they wanted,
Mimi wasn't supposed to survive.
What do we do?
Gather the rangers at the med center.
She needs protection.
Ravenwood does not get near her.
Major.
Tell the other squad to get moving.
We'll rendezvous in 30.
What is it?
There was a shooting
out at Richmond Farm.
- I heard from Goetz already.
- What'd he say?
Said he went out on J&R business,
someone opened fire on him,
killed three of his men.
You believe that?
Do you know something I don't?
There's a survivor.
- She's unconscious but when she...
- Sir, we're ready and standing by.
- I'm sorry, Jake, I've got to go.
- Where are you going?
20 minutes ago, a pipe bomb went
off outside the J&R office in New Bern.
Took out six of my men.
I'll be back in 12 hours.
- It's not going to wait 12 hours.
- It's going to have to.
Things are coming apart at
the seams in New Bern right now.
And you have my word,
tomorrow I'm going to get into this,
but for tonight I'm trusting that
you can keep things under control here.
That means Goetz is off limits.
No threats,
no retribution, no exceptions.
Do you understand?
One entrance.
Small exit.
Is she going to be okay?
I'm going to need this room clear now.
- Please.
- Come on. Come on.
Beck's gone to New Bern.
We're on our own.
Bill, Marty,
you take the front.
Greg and Dave, you take the back.
Any sign of Goetz,
you let me know
before you do anything, all of you.
Stan.
- Taking her to the morgue?
- Yeah.
I'm going.
He shouldn't be alone.
I'll keep an eye on him.
They just checked Mimi Clark into
the medical center for a gunshot wound.
She was in the house?
Mrs. Hawkins, here's your prescription.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Well, everyone under the age of 18
in your house is running a fever, and...
Jake!
Goetz is outside.
Stay here.
Jake.
I understand Mimi Clark is inside.
I'm going to need to see her.
Jake, don't do something stupid.
Mimi Clark is a witness to
the killings of three of my men.
She may have even
been one of the shooters.
- She's got some questions to answer.
- You not getting inside this building.
Then I think we have a problem.
"Season 2 - Episode 05
"Termination for Cause"
Transcript: Raceman - www.forom.com
- Synchro By: ¤AkaZab¤
A²S Team
www.All-about-Subs.fr
Be very careful about this decision
you're making, Jake.
Because if you kill
a Ravenwood contractor,
Cheyenne will classify this town
as an insurgent enclave.
When they crack down, everyone suffers.
You don't want that.
Then it looks like it's going
to be a long night.
Is this a road you
really want to go down?
You come inside this building
you'll find out.
Thank you, ma'am. We'll get back
to you at 0200 with another update.
Red One out.
Good night.
Heather.
Russell?
How did you get in here?
It wasn't easy.
We had to slip past the
checkpoints and armed patrols.
Things are bad in New Bern, Heather.
And you are making matters worse for us.
What are you talking about?
The resistance in New Bern
has placed a bounty on your head.
We were sent to collect it.
Is there a place we can talk?
So based on this report,
I'd say you were
a former J&R employee, right?
Looking to make sure the
company's sins are exposed.
Something like that.
So why not just blow the whistle?
- What do you need me for?
- I don't need you.
I need your bomb.
It's concrete evidence
that cannot be refuted
as easily as words on a page.
Taking on both J&R and the Cheyenne
government will require nothing less.
And how high up is the connection
between the two of them?
How high do you think?
I think Valente.
Think bigger.
You mean the president?
Ten years ago John Tomarchio
was a young star
within the Jennings & Rall Corporation.
The company was a major donor to
his first campaign for elected office.
His cabinet,
his advisers,
all littered with former J&R employees.
At the highest levels,
that government and this company
are one and the same.
The barricades are about halfway there.
Another ten mi...
I guess we knew this was coming.
Let's get the other barricades done now.
We don't have much time.
I need an extra pair of hands.
Someone to hold a light.
All my guys are on the doors.
Excuse me, madam...
- Darcy.
- You're hired.
Armed civilians, possibly hostages, sir.
Four hours, copy that.
Thank you, sir.
Looks like it's just going
to be the 12 of us for awhile.
Should we start planning for a breech?
Or should we just go to phase two?
By the time Beck gets back here
this thing will be over and done with.
Let's start banging on some doors.
Got it.
Is she okay?
Well, she has been shot.
The bullet entered
the pectoralis musculature,
and missed the subclavean
vessels and the chest cavity.
I'm sorry,
I have no idea what any of that means.
It means, all things considered,
this situation
could have been a lot worse.
Eleven blade, please.
Hey, Stanley.
Stanley, this isn't your fault.
What are you talking about?
Well, when...
when April died...
all I could think about was
I hadn't done enough, that...
that it was my fault.
When my parents died I did that.
I... I blamed myself.
I hated myself for being alive.
But there was this little
girl to take care of.
I sort of pulled myself out of it.
I know.
This is harder.
Your parents, that...
that was an accident...
an act of God.
Aren't they all?
I don't blame myself.
Jake.
What? What is it?
I don't know, but Goetz is getting out.
He's got someone with him.
Fred.
Hello.
Gary, it's your wife.
Hey.
Okay, okay. All right, calm down.
Yeah. Okay. All right.
I love you, too.
It's Chloe.
She's outside.
They just went into
the house and got her.
Look, I'm with you guys.
I am, but...
She's scared out of her mind.
You should go.
- It's just that she's out...
- It's all right.
Go.
It's okay, Gary.
They're going after our families?
D?
Darcy?
Hey!
D?
Mr. Hawkins?
Can I help you?
Is it all right if we come in?
Well...
We stopped by a half hour ago.
I guess you weren't home yet.
What can I do for you?
Sir, are you related to
Darcy Hawkins?
Yeah.
What's happened?
All right,
a group of armed men
has taken control of the medical center.
We believe she's among
the hostages inside.
Really?
Okay, so...
what can I do?
Well, we need you to come
down and talk to her on the phone.
Just try to convince her to leave
a very dangerous situation.
I don't understand.
If she's being held hostage, how can
me talking to her get her out of there?
We'll explain all of that on scene,
but...
we do need to go now.
Okay.
Okay. I'm parked out front.
I just... Let me just get my keys.
Sir?
It would be best if
you just came with us.
Okay.
Where is my wife?
Hey, Mimi.
Where am I?
You're at the med center.
You're going to be fine.
Where are Stanley and Bonnie?
The nurse...
She'll be back in a minute.
I told her I'd keep an eye on you.
Let me go get her.
Wait, please.
Where's Stanley?
Stanley's downstairs.
And Bonnie?
I'm sorry.
As soon as Beck declared us the
aggressors in the fight with Jericho,
he put us in a choke hold.
Curfews, military courts,
armed checkpoints.
The resistance came
together soon after that.
For weeks, we were a step ahead of him.
Then, all of a sudden,
he was on to us.
Some of those tips
you've been giving Beck,
they've made things very difficult
for us.
They've cost us lives.
The moment Constantino figured
out it was you, he issued the bounty.
So wait a minute.
You're working with Constantino?
Russell, he's a murderer.
You think I don't know that?
A lot of reasonable people
are lining up behind him.
Beck's left us no alternative.
So, if you came to kill me,
why am I still alive?
I came here to convince you
to stop doing what you're doing.
And to bring back a little trophy.
What kind of trophy?
Goetz.
Will you go up and check on Mimi for me?
Don't you think we should both go up?
I'll be right up. Just...
give me a minute or two.
Thanks.
I know, I know...
I love you.
What are you doing here?
We're switching posts?
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Who is it?
Jimmy, open the door.
Mr. Hawkins?
Yeah.
I come bearing gifts.
We've got 12 men. From the looks
of it, they've got about the same.
They've got three less
than they had before.
And that one will come in handy if they
try and threaten anybody else's family.
- They tried to use you as bait?
- They tried.
- Where's my wife, Jake?
- She's helping with Mimi.
Tell me what the hell's going on here.
We did a sweep of the area.
We found Burke and
Sloan by the rear entrance.
- They're dead.
- Dead?
- What about Stanton and Bulger?
- Still no sign of them.
All right, do another sweep.
I want to know what's going on.
Fred.
You okay?
Yeah. Yes, ma'am.
Yeah. Why don't...
why don't you go get some water?
Yeah. Thank you.
Hey.
Where's Stanley?
He's with Bonnie.
He'll be up soon.
Excuse me.
Do you have any idea why
all this might be happening?
Because Goetz is embezzling
money from
Jennings & Rall.
I have the proof, my ledger.
Killing civilians they can excuse,
but you put your hands in their pocket,
suddenly J&R's a lot less forgiving.
Zero tolerance.
My ledger was at the house.
I'm sure he has it by now.
Is there any way to
recreate that information?
If you had access to the system?
Maybe.
Hawkins.
I need your help.
Isn't that what I've been doing?
Well, this is a little bit different.
It's outside the scope
of our usual conversation.
I have to be very careful
about sticking my neck out
when, where
and for whom.
Now, listen to me.
I don't know what
it is you want from me,
but I know you are not feeding
me information for my own benefit.
So I will promise you this
if you do not do this favor for me,
then our relationship will end
right here and right now.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Is there anyone in the J&R
office that you think you can trust?
Why?
Because we need to reconstitute
the information from that ledger.
Now, is there anyone that
could help you to do that?
Well, there is someone.
Good. Make the call.
What do you want me to tell her?
Tell herto gather all the information
and send it to this address.
This is the personal e-mail
for the director of operations
of Ravenwood. How did you get this?
Don't ask.
Jake.
We got a problem.
Are you all right?
He came at me out of nowhere.
Frank, where's your gun?
There's no way he cut through that tape.
No. Not without help.
- One of us.
- Yeah.
Be First, we gotta find
our Ravenwood friend.
How many men have you
got guarding the exits?
Two at each.
But if he starts picking them off,
then Goetz can get in,
and we can't afford to
pull anyone off of Mimi's door.
- Jake, we have got to find him.
- We'll find him,
but after that, we gotta find a way out.
Jake...
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Yeah, pretty sure.
Well, there's a way
that may become useful.
Jimmy. Bill.
You guys are just gonna
snatch Goetz off the street?
Execute him in cold blood?
I got a handful of guys
out looking for him right now.
Russell.
What happened to you?
Goetz executed three of my neighbors
in New Bern a few months ago,
and this government promoted him.
Beck has been strangling
my home town for weeks,
And this same government
tells me that I'm in the wrong.
I've had enough.
We punish Goetz in New Bern,.
And we show Beck that we're
not going away any time soon.
I know things are bad,
but the minute you guys
threw in with Constantino,
you gave up the high ground.
Beck's going to fight you.
I'm sorry,
but I'm gonna be helping him do it.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Word of advice?
Pray I can get Goetz
because if I don't,
it's not gonna be me that Constantino
sends after you next.
Hello.
Trish.
Mimi?
Trish, Bonnie's dead.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
It was Goetz. And his men.
They killed her for the ledger.
Trish, I need your help.
What can I do?
I hope this works.
It'll work.
Just have to make it a little bigger.
It's too small?
What, you don't think
I can fit through that hole?
You're gonna want to make it bigger.
Go through
the backup folders in that directory.
That's where you'll find the numbers
that Goetz altered.
Okay. I got 'em.
Now what do you want me to do with them?
I'm gonna give you an e-mail address
and a code for the subject line.
Mimi, I am so sorry.
It's not your fault.
Mimi, I am the one who told Goetz.
I know.
Will you do this for me?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Hey.
I'm so sorry.
Mimi, stop.
No.
I never should have opened my mouth.
I should've kept my mouth shut.
Listen to me.
You were in danger.
Bonnie did what she needed
to do to protect you and...
you're alive.
Wherever she is now...
I swear, she's glad she did it.
Yeah.
What kind of gun?
- What?!
- What kind of gun did Frank have?
Nine millimeter Beretta.
Seven!
Five!
Four! Three! Two!
What do you want to do with him?
You're never getting out of here alive.
All the exits are covered.
Sure about that?
What was all that?
We got a fix on him and traded fire.
Did you get him?
No, he got away.
He's probably still inside.
Let's pull Marty and Dave off
the front entrance to help guard Mimi.
Fred, take their place.
They've been there all night.
They need some rest.
Yeah. Yeah. Sure.
Goetz.
The back door is gonna be clear.
Really?
- Five minutes.
- Got it.
Out.
We're in!
- Tell me what the hell's going on here.
- They're gone, sir.
I can see that. Where'd they go?
I don't know. Another exit
somewhere off near the pharmacy.
There are no exits over there.
Sir,
I think you should see this.
- What the hell's through this hole?
- Farm equipment store.
Apparently, it's all one structure.
It doesn't make any sense.
Got the whole perimeter covered.
Didn't say anything to me about this.
No kidding.
They made you for the mole, genius.
I heard them say something
about moving the woman to her farm.
Hide her there until Beck returns.
What do you want us to do?
Mount up.
Redirect the reinforcements
to the Route 23 junction.
- Catch up with them on the move.
- Let's go.
Are they gone?
- Jake, wait.
- Are they gone?
All clear.
Let's go.
Jake,
Jake, I had no choice.
He said he'd take my farm.
He threatened my wife.
Go home, Fred.
- Jake, please...
- Go home, Fred.
Go home.
Jake, they've got reinforcements coming.
They said they're meeting a
hundred Ravenwood men at the crossroads.
8:00 a.m. At Route 23
and Cherry Valley Road.
Let's go.
Hey, not yet.
Check your mags.
Are those reinforcements?
No.
Watch this.
I'm Director Jamison,
Ravenwood Regional HQ.
All you guys saddle up.
We're moving out.
Sir, I'm in the middle
of an operation here.
No, you're not.
Take their rifles!
Let's move!
Where we going?
They're being redeployed.
You're fired.
What are you talking about?
You can't fire me.
No, I can't, but he can.
In fact, he already did.
Feel better?
I hope you rot in hell.
Leave 'em here.
They can walk back.
Roll out!
Now?
Yeah, now.
Goetz!
Goetz, I want to see your hands!
Remember, we need him alive!
No way.
Who is that?!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
Hold your fire!
What the hell are you doing here?!
I came for him.
I've had my guys tracking him all night,
waiting for their chance
to make the grab.
- Thanks.
- No way, Russell.
You can't have him.
Want to bet?
- I'm handing him over to Beck.
- Handing him over?
If he winds up dead,
Beck will wreak havoc
on both these towns.
He has three killings
to answer for in New Bern.
Yeah, well, he's in Jericho,
and he's under arrest
for Bonnie Richmond's murder.
We're fighting an army
that has more guns than we do,
more men than we do.
What we need is resolve.
And Goetz,
he's the fuel for that resolve.
Stanley.
Stay back.
Jake, that doesn't matter.
Whether Goetz goes missing
or his body's found,
Beck is gonna put the pieces together.
You know he will.
The minute that body hit the ground,
this became
a whole different deal.
So what's your status, Cap?
This sector's clear, sir.
No sign of insurgent activity.
Roger that. Out.
- What is it?
- Sir...
you're gonna want
to see this for yourself.
A²S Team
www.All-about-Subs.fr