Previously on Jericho.
So I hear you and I
are going to be partners now.
Where'd you get that?
You're running the store,
you're going to need protection.
Don't make the same mistake
that Gracie made.
Or those people out there
are going to be putting
flowers and candles
on the sidewalk for you.
Who the hell is that?
Remember,
the gas tank on this thing
is on the left-hand side,
so if somebody decides
to start shooting at you,
make sure it's not on that side.
Okay. Anything else?
So, are we going to see you
for Thanksgiving?
Well, I think Mary and I
are going to spend it together.
Well, you're always welcome.
Thanks, but I don't want to put
you guys in an awkward position.
You could have thought of that before
you moved in with your mistress
and left your wife with us.
Some of them were on planes
that landed in the middle of nowhere.
They've been walking for weeks.
They must have gone through hell.
Oh, my God.
Is it really you?
I need you to keep the kids
in the house for a while
until I can sort something out.
Are we in danger, Robert?
You have moderate frostbite
on your toes and fingers.
You need to keep them
clean and warm.
Do you have a place to stay?
Do you know anyone in Jericho?
Actually,
I do.
It's freezing in here, too.
Mr. Bintner?
Joe?
The temperature dropped so fast.
It's going to be a long winter.
All right, everyone!
Everyone, please!
Please!
Right now,
we're using the generator
to power the town hall
for three hours a day,
and the Med Center for six.
And this is how much fuel we have,
and this is how much we need
to get us through the winter.
At current levels of consumption,
we will be completely
out of gas and diesel
in two weeks.
I wonder when the dancing girls show up.
Stop.
There's a way of doing this without
scaring the crap out of everybody.
He was elected.
Guess he's going to do it his way.
I'm going to need a hobby.
So here's what we're working on.
All right, we got
organized firewood crews...
- Mr. Hawkins?
- Yeah.
There's a woman
in that group of refugees
that Bill is processing,
I think you should talk to her.
Why?
She said she used to be
a cop in Saint Louis.
Especially with 53
new people among us,
we have got to start rethinking things,
fast,
or the people we lost last night
won't be the only casualties
of this coming winter.
What about the windmills?
She's right.
Wind power.
We should be building windmills.
Harry?
I think you all know Harry Carmichael,
our chief engineer
down at the mine.
We've been looking into wind turbines
for weeks now with Mayor Green.
But in order to build anything
that can be connected to the grid,
it's going to take time.
Time I'm not sure we can afford.
- She's in here.
- Thanks, Jimmy.
Hello, Rob.
Any parts we don't have...
we simply don't have
the maching capabilities.
What kind of parts?
Mechanical governors to regulate output.
With the EMP damage, we're figuring
out a lot of this from scratch.
- It's still a long way off.
- Black Jack Fairgrounds.
We walked through it
on our way back here.
It's become a trading post.
People from all over
the region are trading...
food, information,
machine parts.
They may have what we need.
That's got to be a 200-mile drive.
That's a lot of gas for a "maybe."
If we can get one windmill working,
we'd save that much gas in a month.
If we get enough of them,
we could be off gas for good.
It might not be a bad idea
to put a small party together
and go check it out.
Is anyone interested
in volunteering?
Season 1 Episode 13
Black Jack
[ Transcript ]
swsub.com
[ Synchro ]
Loky
[ www. seriessub.com ]
I know it was you.
- What?
- Those men that grabbed me.
They said that someone
on my team sold us all out.
They said it was you.
And you believe them?
Tell me why I shouldn't.
Come on!
You're smart enough to know
that they will say anything
to get you to talk.
Because you know
I owe you my life
as much as you owe me yours
and because you just...
You just punched me in the face,
and I didn't hit you back.
- Who else is here?
- No one.
Victor showed up
just after D-day.
But he only made it
for a couple of hours.
Did you kill him?
It was the radiation...
from Denver.
No one else made it back here
to the rally point?
You going to tell me
how you got out of that room?
Three armed guys, cuffs.
Three guys and cuffs
keep you in that room?
One of them got too close.
Then there was only two.
Two was easy.
From there,
I drove as fast as I could.
Saw the clouds
from D. C. and Baltimore.
Ran out of gas in West Virginia.
Went from refugee camp
to refugee camp
however I could.
I'm glad you made it.
You left me.
I know.
So what now?
We caught wind of some raiding parties
at interchanges here and here.
But if you're careful,
you should be safe
the rest of the way.
Once you're at Black Jack,
watch your back.
Thieves?
It's not the thieves you got
to worry about, it's the guards.
They've got a reputation
of being really ruthless.
Without the cops
or the National Guard,
it's the only way they
guaranteed it's safe enough
to keep commerce going there.
You'd better take two or three
of the border patrol guys with you.
Just in case you run
into any surprises.
I'm coming, too.
Not a chance in hell.
Would you know
a working mechanical governor
for a wind turbine
if you saw one?
I'm not taking
passengers out there.
Jake, Mr. Carmichael has a family.
I can help.
You need me.
Mrs. Green?
What?
Eric told me that
April's pregnant.
I just...
- If there's anything that I can do...
- Mary...
I think you've done quite enough.
Always got to be the first one
to jump in the fire, don't you?
Somebody's got to go.
Yeah, well, just seems
that someone is always you.
Gray's having a few bags of salt
packed up for us to trade.
Smart.
Who else is going?
Apparently Heather.
Gray thinks I should take
a couple of guys from border patrol.
That's it?
I'm not so sure
pulling them off patrol
just to watch my back
is such a good idea.
Besides, only a handful of them
even know what they're doing.
You don't think
I can watch your back?
Why? You want to go?
Look, you've already seen
what it's like out there. I just...
need to see it for myself.
Besides, I'm unemployed.
I'm not obsolete.
Did you ask Mom?
Son, I am 59 years old.
I was mayor of this town
since the Carter administration.
I'm a retired U. S. Army Ranger
and a combat veteran.
Of course I asked your mother.
I could go downstairs and...
warm some water
for a bath for you.
I didn't think I was ever
going to finish this.
Hey, uh...
we have a guest.
This is Sarah.
Hey, Dale?
Hey. What are you
doing back there?
Uh, inventory.
Is it that bad?
Well, Mr. Houghton just showed up
with Mrs. Leigh's cut of the produce.
- What the hell is that?
- Yeah, exactly.
Well, did you point out
that it's rotten?
They're all screwing me.
Hardly anyone's honoring their deals.
My dad used to have to deal with stuff
like this all the time
down at the salt mine.
- Well, how did he do it?
- He just...
did whatever it took
to keep things running.
I'm not shutting this place down.
Actually,
I may have
good news about that.
But you might have
to take a little trip.
I need to talk to you.
All right.
I shouldn't have sprung this on you.
This is too weird...
What? What's weird?
I kissed you.
A month ago.
And we haven't spoken since.
Generally, people speak
after something like that.
I'm just going to...
You know...
I know, I'm, uh...
- I'm sorry, really...
- You don't have to apologize.
I'm not upset.
I understand
why it happened.
Look, I want to go
because I think I can help get
this place back up on its feet.
That's it.
It's not a date.
Mr. Mayor?
I'm not the mayor anymore, Dale.
What is it?
I need to come with you.
I want to take it all.
Trade it for something
I can actually use
to build this store up again.
Whatever I don't use,
I'll put towards
supplies the town needs.
You're just going to give it
away to the town for nothing?
It's the right thing to do, isn't it?
I just want to help.
Well,
this is one hell of a crew
we're putting together here.
All right.
Yeah, we'll leave
first thing in the morning.
You just happen to know
someone who just...
happened to wander into town?
Look at me.
I'm not going to lie to you.
But I can't...
I can't tell you any more
than I already have.
So she's a friend, okay?
The last time you let someone
from that part of your life
- into our home, it was 4 years ago.
- This is different.
Well, you couldn't tell me
who he was.
But you told me not to worry.
Two weeks later, you left.
I didn't see you again
until two months ago.
This is different.
Sam cried for weeks.
I mean, he was four-years-old.
He didn't understand why
you'd want to leave him.
I just...
I don't know if I can watch him
go through that again.
What is going on here?
Come here.
What is this?
So I'm being watched.
By who?
My guess...
The Old Man.
Why...?
You still have the package, don't you?
He's been coordinating
this thing from the beginning,
feeding us information.
Why would he turn on us now?
I don't know.
You still have
a way to reach him?
And have you...
told him that you
made contact with me yet?
- Not yet.
- Then do it.
You do it...
and you see what he says.
"Thieves will be strung up."
We need your guns.
Pick them up on the way out.
Go ahead.
They're kidding about
the "strung up" thing, right?
They don't mean that literally.
Looks like everyone
checks in here at the main tent.
They try and match
buyers and sellers.
They gave me three
possibilities of sellers
that might have the part
for the windmill.
It's like eBay.
Not like eBay.
All right, look, um...
see if you can find the governor,
I'm going to stick with Dale.
See what he can trade for.
Let's do this thing quick
then we're out of here.
Morning.
Good morning.
Last night,
you fell asleep mid-sentence.
- I did?
- Yes, you did.
Standing up right there
at the sink, shaving.
You were going to tell me
what you've seen out there and...
Roger, I...
I don't want to push.
I can't even imagine how awful
it was for you out there. I just...
A lot of it was.
Listen.
If I tell you something,
will you promise not to think...
I've lost it?
Of course.
Out there...
I saw... something.
I haven't told
anybody about it. I...
can't explain it.
The thing is...
it was the most beautiful thing
I've ever seen.
From there I ended up
in a tent city outside of Lexington.
So, what are they like?
The camps?
Each is, uh... different.
Some are overcrowded, dangerous.
Some are better run.
Did you see people
with radiation poisoning?
Some, yes.
What do they look like?
Lots of burns,
tissue loss, some vomiting.
Allie, Sam.
Upstairs.
How do you know my dad?
We worked together.
Do you know how
to play football?
Of course, I do.
Doesn't everybody?
Not everybody.
Hey, Samuel, now.
Come on.
You know, these kids
have been through enough.
I... I'm sorry.
Look, I don't know you.
I really don't want to.
I know the kind of people
my husband works with.
No matter how close
the two of you are,
I don't need my kids
exposed to that world.
I've been married to
this man a long time.
I got pretty good at reading
between the lines.
Thanks, Mary.
Why don't you and I sit down
together and have a drink?
Hey, how much?
- Beg pardon?
- How much?
How much for what?
I don't know.
An hour?
An hour of what?
Wait, what?! No!
- How about a half hour?
- Is everything all right?
- I'm not a hooker, pal!
- Then what are you doing here?
All right, that's enough.
That's enough, man.
- Is there a problem here?
- Hey, no. No.
No problem. Everything's fine.
No kidding, buddy.
You don't want to mess with
the guards here, it gets ugly, fast.
Thanks for the help.
Heather.
Oh, my God, Ted.
I can't believe you're here.
Jake, this is Ted Lewis.
We grew up together
over in New Bern.
This is Russell and Mike.
- Hey.
- Yeah, we met.
I was so worried about you.
We were going to send a party
to make contact with you guys,
but the roads were
just so dangerous.
What are you guys doing here?
We're looking for parts
for a windmill generator.
Unsuccessfully.
Hey, there's a guy
we deal with here...
who doesn't always
report to the main tent,
but sometimes he's got
those specialty items
nobody else has.
You want to see him?
- Yeah, let's check it out.
- All right.
Get this stuff out of here
before somebody sees it.
Why, what's wrong with it?
Nickel...
the silver stuff
is all alloyed with it.
So?
So nickel absorbs radioactivity.
Stuff that's been looted
from hot zones
is making a lot of people sick.
No one wants it.
This stuff was nowhere
near the fallout.
Look, kid,
if I can't sell it, I can't sell it.
What do you want me to tell you?
What else do you got?
So what does have value here?
Not much of what you got.
Check the board over there.
Why salt?
It's a preservative.
An antibiotic.
You need 1,500 milligrams
of it a day to survive.
The Romans actually
used it as currency.
Whole African empires
were based on the control
and supply of it.
Wars have been fought over salt.
Food, medical supplies,
a generator, all air-dropped,
all from China.
What?
Yeah, we got an airdrop, too.
The thing is...
it was from Germany.
It's aid. It must be coming
from all over the world.
Well, if aid's coming
from all over the world then...
who did this to us?
A group of thugs a few weeks back,
guys claiming to be
government contractors.
So the mayor thought
we should make security a priority.
He resigned his office and...
appointed Sheriff Constantino
acting city manager.
The contractors,
who were they?
A security detail from a...
company called Ravenwood.
They came in looking for supplies.
A few of the shop owners resisted
and they got violent.
They killed three,
they injured eight.
They drove off with
a truckload of our diesel.
But since then,
the sheriff's managed to
keep control of things.
Crime really isn't a
problem for us anymore.
How'd he manage that?
- What is this?
- The news.
Where does all this come from?
People pass through here
from all over.
Everyone brings
a little piece of the puzzle.
Do you have
something to write on?
You guys don't
get out much, do you?
It gets better.
What are the stars for?
Capitals.
Of what?
The federal government.
Federal government? But...
There are six stars up there.
Where's the president?
Which one?
Six presidents, I...
I don't understand.
Who's in charge of the military?
You're assuming
there's only one of those, too.
All right, come on, let's go.
Isn't there a line of succession,
so there's only one successor?
The word is HHS.
Secretary Charles is supposed
to be next in line,
but there are five other guys
who seem to think
the attacks changed the rules.
Senator Morrisette in Oregon,
Senator Tomarchio in Wyoming...
They're all staking a claim,
gathering support.
Then what happens?
How do they figure out who's in charge?
Either they start making deals,
- compromise...
- Or?
Or they fight.
Six bags of soybean seed,
and still it's...
It's not enough.
Maybe this whole thing
was a bad idea.
It's a start.
Dale, wait up.
It'd be a lot easier for you
to close the store, wouldn't it?
But instead, you're out here
trying to keep it going.
I think Gracie
would be proud of you.
I think your mom would
be proud of you, too.
When my mom died,
there was nothing I could do about it.
But then after Mrs. Leigh...
Mitchell Cafferty
is going to get his due
whether Gray finds him or not.
Sooner or later, he's going
to cross the wrong person.
One of these days,
it's going to catch up with him.
I don't like to drink
while I'm working.
To be honest, I have
difficulty understanding
how many ways I dislike you.
You made a list?
Mrs. Green, I don't think I...
This will work a lot better
if you just sit there
and listen to what
I have to say.
What you and Eric
did to April was awful.
But she's going
to get through this
because she is
one strong woman.
But there's a baby on the way,
and it happens
to be my grandchild.
And I intend to do
everything I can
to protect it from this world.
But what you've done,
I can't protect it from.
You've divided the family.
And as hard as that child's
life was going to be,
you have made it
so much more difficult.
I don't think that's something
I'll ever be able to forgive.
When I was a kid,
my mom split on my dad and I.
She left with the guy
she met in Denver...
This isn't about you.
This will work a lot better
if you just sit there
and listen to what I have to say.
I lay awake at night
terrified that I have
put April in the same
position my dad was in...
Terrified that I have put this child
in the same position that I was in.
My mistake was falling
in love with your son,
I never should have let
it happen, but I did.
I know the cost.
I know how wrong it is.
But the problem is,
he loves me, too.
And I don't know
how you undo that.
So if you want
to go on hating me,
if you never accept me...
I can't say as I blame you.
So I went to find help.
I was more messed up
than I thought.
I wandered for days.
Eventually...
passed out in this... field.
So there I was,
the middle of Nebraska
feeling like that was the place
I was going to die.
And then,
the strangest thing happened.
There was a...
light in the sky.
A bright light with a...
ring around it.
I...
went... towards it.
Two miles later...
I stumbled into
the refugee camp.
That light...
saved my life.
Been looking all over for you.
Did you find the part?
I think so.
Did you see the news?
You looking to trade
for a mechanical governor?
Okay, let's talk trade.
Eight bags of salt
at 35 pound per.
Russell, what did they think?
That they're the first ones
to think of this?
These parts are in high demand.
I'm not giving it away.
- What more is it going to take?
- What more?
I turned away a guy
just this morning,
and he offered 80 gallons
of diesel for the thing.
Listen...
We have more salt
than you can imagine.
We have the largest
salt mine for 400 miles
and we've got men to mine it.
But if you ever want
to see any of it,
we need to make
this deal right now, today.
You understand?
Okay, listen,
I'll vouch for him.
All right?
All right.
We got a deal.
Wait here. I'll go get it.
These things aren't
easy to make, you know.
Not the good ones anyway.
Dad, this is Russell.
Hi. Good to meet you.
Mr. Mayor?
No kidding, Dale,
I am not the mayor anymore.
There's blood on them.
- You need some help there?
- What the hell is this?
Are you conducting an inspection
or are we doing a deal?
No, we're not supporting that.
We'll find another solution.
Well, then we're all done here,
aren't we?
Why don't you get out?
Get out of here.
Get out!
You, too!
Get out of here!
Guys, I'm so sorry.
We had no idea.
We need that part.
- And we're going to have to figure out
a way... - Where's Dale?
Dale, where'd you get off to?
Don't just wander off like that.
Did you steal that?
He's a bad guy.
He can't get away with that.
We got to get that back before
they realize it's missing.
It's okay I went out
the back. No one saw me.
Hold it!
Hand him over.
He made a mistake, all right?
He'll give back what he took.
It's no harm done, all right?
Excuse me. You know,
he really is sorry and
the property is back
where it belongs.
He can explain it to management.
I'm just asking you,
use a little discretion,
that's all, please.
Excuse me, but could I talk
to whoever's in charge here?
Look, old man, I told you...
That's enough!
How long have you been
with the FBI?
14 years.
Started right out of college.
It's dangerous out there, isn't it?
I don't think your mom wants me
talking to you about that.
I'm not a kid.
It's pretty bad.
My dad's been teaching me
how to shoot.
I wonder if that's why.
He's been teaching you
how to shoot?
A little.
I'm not sure if I like it.
It's a weird feeling, but...
it's the first time I can remember
the two of us actually doing
something together.
Where's your father?
It's the old man.
He's coming for us,
using us against each other.
He knows where you are.
We need to go.
We need to move now.
No, I don't know.
You don't know?
This country is going
to be what we make of it.
There are only a
handful of other people
that know what we know.
We have to keep fighting.
We have to stay alive.
We go see him, and if,
if he is behind this,
we take him out.
Take him out?
Yeah, I mean,
how long can we run?
How long can my family run?
We pay him a visit,
we eliminate the threat.
We go straight at him, there is
a chance we don't come back.
You're leaving.
She walked in that door,
I knew right away you'd be leaving.
You have nothing to worry about.
It's not me that
I'm worried about.
Our children need a father.
Whatever you're going to do,
it can't be more important than that.
Do you trust her?
I have to.
If she's a threat to this
family's safety,
if she's a threat to you...
you kill her.
You understand?
Get in!
Hurry!
Stop the car.
Jake, this car will not fit
through that barricade.
Stop the car now!
Thanks. I, uh,
I don't know how this would have
turned out if it weren't for you guys.
- Well, you'll make it up to us someday.
- However we can help.
Those windmills you're looking
to build... I was thinking.
Guys down at the
old brake assembly,
maybe they can convert
part of their plant,
help build what you need.
I know the town could use
a good source of salt.
Looks like we're going
to be seeing a lot of each other.
- Thanks again, guys. Take care.
- Thank you so much.
What?
Jake, I saw the governor.
I saw how it's put together.
I was talking to Ted,
and I think between the two of us,
we can help to make more of them,
but I have to go with him.
- Go with them? Wait a minute.
- No, think about it.
We don't have the resources
to do this the right way.
They've got the machines
and the guys who
know how to use them.
With a dozen full-sized windmills,
you could power the whole town,
run the med center,
forget about gas.
You're just going to leave?
Right now?
It won't be for very long.
Just a few days.
But I know I can help.
I think I need to do this.
You think this is a good idea?
You know why things
didn't work out between us?
I'm not dangerous.
I'm crossword puzzles
and flannel pajamas and
the occasional lite beer.
I was never going to be
hazardous to you.
- That's how you tick.
- No, it isn't.
Of course it is.
But it's okay.
If it wasn't, your dad would
probably be dead right now,
you and I would have
never met on that bus.
So I'm taking a page out of your book.
I'm throwing caution to the wind.
I'm gonna help turn the lights
on for everyone back home.
Just for a few days.
You worried about me?
Come back in one piece.
Dad?
We're out of the good toothpaste.
Oh, well, here's the...
The new stuff that Mr. Daley made.
- This isn't toothpaste.
- Yeah, it is.
Are you playing a joke on me?
Hey, you know, uh,
when you were teething,
you never cried.
See, 'cause most babies,
they cry, but not you.
And your...
mom was worried and the...
doctors were worried,
but not me.
Because I knew you weren't sick,
you weren't hurt,
you were just brave.
'Cause you're
the bravest person I know.
You always have been.
Dad?
What are you talking about?
Sam,
I have to go to work tomorrow.
It's a very important meeting,
but it's quite far away,
so I might not be back
for a day or two,
and I just wanted you to know that.
Are you mad at me?
What?
You're leaving.
You listen to me.
There is nothing that
you, your sister or your mother
could ever do that would
make me want to leave you.
I, uh...
I, I love you.
You understand that, right?
Hey, welcome home.
Success?
- You get the part?
- We had it...
and we lost it.
Uh, where's Heather?
Getting the lights back on.
You do realize that
what happened today
was unnecessary?
And stupid?
You got a lot
of responsibility now.
You're going to have to learn
how to be smart.
I understand.
And you,
you knew that this car
was not going to fit
through that gate?
I know.
I heard you talking to me,
and I knew you were right.
Why didn't you stop the car?
I don't know.
What'd you get?
Look at all this stuff.
Oh, you did great.
This is nothing.
Skylar, how much of the salt mine
does your family own?
I don't know. Why?
'Cause I think we may be rich.
You okay?
Look, uh...
I am glad you made it.
We leave first thing
in the morning.
[ www.seriessub.com ]