- Hey, baby.
- Where have you been?
- You were supposed to call...
- I probably won't be home
for another few days.
You making another one of your
pit stops? What's her name this time?
- There's no girl.
- Really?
I got to get this load to Punxsutawney.
Look, Shirl, I got to go.
Why?!
Because I drank a gallon of coffee,
and I got to go!
Oh, really? If I find that...
Bones, wakey-wakey.
Bones?
Wakey-wakey.
Eggs and bakey.
- Do you have any idea what time it is?
- 6:30, which is why I brought you this.
Nice, bed head there.
So... Seeley Booth, Mark Gaffney.
Hey.
- What do you want, Booth?
- My partner.
Got some pre-breakfast remains for you.
You...
getting a little chilly there, Mark?
- I think I'll put some clothes on.
- Excellent choice.
- It would be good if you called first.
- Who knew you were even dating?
Well, I wouldn't call it dating. We...
occasionally make arrangements
to spend time together.
I'm just surprised
you're not more picky.
My relationship
with Mark is purely physical,
and I am very satisfied
with him in that area.
Did you see his chest and his thighs?
- Bones.
- What?
Haven't you chosen someone `cause
they were satisfying sexually?
There has to be more than sex.
Not really.
Our interests and professions
do not intersect.
Well, what is he? Bricklayer?
You know, truck driver? Tango dancer?
He is a deep-sea welder.
I wouldn't even think
to put that on the list.
They work on oil derricks, repair boats.
After being at sea for months at a time,
he seems to...
enjoy having a sexual
relationship, so...
I'm sure. I am sure.
Deep-sea welder.
He can hold his breath
for three minutes down there.
Underwater?
Of course.
Come on, seriously,
who thinks it's a good idea
to blow up an outhouse?
Probably accidental.
Assuming a minimum
methane level of five percent,
a simple spark
could trigger the explosion.
Of course, that would depend on
the level of fecal deposit in the tank.
Just stop.
Your aversion to feces is irrational.
It's three-quarters water.
Don't mention that to the guy who
almost got his ass blown off.
He survived?
Kind of, but he ain't gonna be making
any contributions to the gene pool
anytime soon.
The victim is alive,
why are we here?
Take a look. Go ahead.
Yeah.
Bones - Season 04 Episode 03
"The Man in the Outhouse"
Synchro: ShalimarFox, Icefreak
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--
Gunshot wound to the frontal lobe.
Where's my new assistant?
She's at security
getting her ID and badge.
There's powder residue on the bone
indicating that the victim
was shot at close range.
These suits are so cool.
I am a robot.
Sorry.
Dead for about 72 hours.
No lividity on the legs.
Wait. Poop will do that
to you in three days?
Actually, it's the fecal
coliform bacteria, streptococcus
and maggots.
Guy you're looking for has major issues.
He deposits the object of his rage
in a literal pit of poop.
Excrement being the symbol
for that which we
reject and hate about ourselves.
Do we need to take lessons
in toilet training issues?
Front teeth are shattered.
Shot in the head,
punched in the face,
and dumped in the poop.
Whoever did this
did not get enough therapy.
Victim has veneers on the maxillary
central and lateral incisors,
and there's reshaping of the gum tissue,
as well as the underlying bone.
Take a look.
Yeah.
Looks like
there's something in his throat.
Looks like a photograph
after the decomp
and stomach acid got to it.
He wasn't punched.
The killer crammed that down
the victim's throat so hard,
it broke his teeth.
There's a motive in that. You're gonna
want to see what's in that picture.
I'll call Angela.
Bless you.
Thank you.
This is really a lot of feces.
Stop making that face.
It's just sewage, Ms. Wick.
I realize that.
Six barrels worth.
- I'm fine.
- Good.
I just thought for safety's sake,
perhaps a Hazmat suit...
We got the all clear.
No danger, no suit.
- You got a problem with that?
- No. No.
Where's Dr. Brennan? I thought
I'd be working with Dr. Brennan.
She's with Agent Booth.
She asked me to tell her
all about how you're doing.
Please tell her that I liked the smell.
No pedicle laminae or spinous process
means we're not talking vertebral arch,
which is cool, 'cause I'm seeing thin
lateral borders with small eminences.
Makes it one thing and one thing only.
A chunk of truck driver coccyx.
My work here is done.
Hand it over.
What have we here?
It's human hair.
Distinct color variations.
I'll turn it over to Hair and Fibers.
I know Dr. Brennan
is a stickler for protocol.
There's no root bulb, which there
should be if it was torn out.
Cross-section is round,
which suggests it's Mongoloid in origin.
Wait. Dr. Saroyan determined
that the victim is Caucasian.
He couldn't have hair
that's Mongoloid in origin.
Yeah. Not bad. But he could if he used
this keratin glue to stick a wig
on his little bald head.
Start sifting through the sewage
and isolate the strands of hair.
I scanned the skull,
and I factored in age and build.
I found the toupee.
- They know, Ms. Wick.
- I wasn't sure if you'd mentioned it.
He didn't have to.
You did everything but hire a skywriter.
Have you gotten anywhere with
the picture we pulled from his throat?
No, not yet. I'm... how can I put this,
depoopifying the fragments now
to piece together some kind of image.
He looks familiar.
Let me add the fatty tissue
and his new, expensive teeth.
He does look familiar.
- Put on his toupee.
- Which I found.
Oh, my God.
That's why he looks familiar.
What?
Be careful. If you cheat on your wife,
you just might get Busted By Bill.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
That girl's the bait
they use to lure the cheaters.
Wait. What is this?
Swing around. Get the wife.
- You son of a bitch!
- Joseph Marilla,
I'm Bill O'Roarke,
and you've been Busted By Bill.
Wait. No! My back hurt.
- I thought she was a masseuse.
- I'm gonna kill you.
You are dead! Dead!
Next time, ask yourself this:
"Am I getting lucky,
or have I just been Busted by Bill?"
Our victim is Bill O'Roarke.
Okay great, thanks.
O'Roarke and his wife
live in Cherry Ridge.
Old Bill
must have been making a tidy sum.
He shouldn't have been rewarded.
He was perpetuating a primitive
and prurient morality by
parading victims
for the purpose of entertainment.
You know what? You cheat on your spouse,
you get what's coming to you.
Anthropologically,
83 percent of societies are polygamous.
Now you sound French, okay?
Look, being faithful is what
separates us, you know, from the chimps.
No, actually, it's a gene called HAR1F.
We're talking about the
10 Commandments here.
"Thou shalt not commit adultery."
One down from your personal favorite,
"Thou shalt not kill."
So you also believe that Moses
wandered the desert for 40 days,
climbed Mount Sinai,
at which point a supernatural force
carved a convenient list of behavioral
guidelines on two pieces of rock?
Yeah.
That's why it's on the Supreme Court.
Fascinating.
I was supposed to be home this weekend.
Bill and my 20th anniversary
is in five days.
Why weren't you here?
Our daughter is away
at college in Raleigh.
I try to spend
as much time with her as I can.
She adores her father.
I mean, how am I going to tell her this?
I told Bill not to do that stupid show.
You were worried about him?
Bill was a serious journalist
until he met Arthur.
Arthur produces the show.
And at first Bill said no,
but the money was unbelievable.
I was just always so worried about him.
- Bill have any enemies?
- Have you seen that show?
There isn't a man he caught
that wouldn't want him dead.
Amanda always resented the show,
but it didn't stop her from
spending the money Bill made.
I'm telling you, if I thought this show
had anything to do with Bill's death,
I'd never forgive myself.
You know, just getting us the footage
that we need should be enough.
Pete's pulling the cheaters
the moment they were caught.
And you are?
I'm the producer, Veronica Landau.
Agent Booth.
This here is, Dr. Brennan.
Hey, is it true?
Where they found him?
Upright and inverted
in the refuse-filled
pit of an outhouse? Yes.
God.
I'm sorry but it's very difficult
to paint a pleasant picture
of his demise right now.
Look, who was the last person
who saw Mr. O'Roarke alive?
Me. 9:18, Friday night.
- That's specific.
- We had to shoot wraparounds.
9:20 would have put us into
time-and-a-half, so I pulled the plug.
I was, I was supposed to pick him up
on Saturday morning
for the promos we were shooting;
knocked on the door, wasn't there.
Pete called me, and I called Arthur,
we cancelled the shoot.
No one was worried that he disappeared?
Bill and I had a small disagreement
Friday night.
He wanted to go visit his kid
at college,
but we had a shoot scheduled.
Promos.
- Anyone else hear this argument?
- No. It was personal.
We walked away from the crew.
Actually, it was,
it was pretty loud, Mr. Lang.
Mr. O'Roarke threatened to quit.
He was just blowing off steam.
That's why I wasn't worried.
Figured he'd just gone off
with Amanda to see the kid.
This is a popular show. It's probably
worth millions of dollars, am I right?
- Why do you ask?
- Well, money like that,
you must insure
your star for quite a bit.
Of course, but
I think you're taking this all wrong.
See, Bill and I were best friends.
We played tennis together
all the time...
If he quit, you'd lose everything.
And if he was found dead,
you'd end up with a nice payout.
Wouldn't you?
Why don't you get Agent Booth
everything he needs, Pete?
I believe I should call my attorney.
Arthur Lang will only talk
through his attorney,
who says he was in Atlantic City
all weekend playing Keno.
- We're checking out his story.
- He could've hired a hit man.
No, this was not a contract job,
this was personal and violent.
Okay, Sweets is on his way up
with the show tapes to
profile for a revenge killer.
- Okay, see you later.
- Bones, wait a second.
Where you going? I thought maybe
we could, you know, help out Sweets.
- To a film.
- This is much better than a movie.
Hours of fascinating video. Hey,
great stories for the deep-sea welder.
Actually,
I'm going to the film with a botanist.
I get it.
You dumped Mark.
It's too bad, I kind of liked the guy.
No, I didn't dump Mark,
I'm seeing both of them.
- At the same time?
- Mark and I have a physical connection.
The botanist,
while brilliant and fascinating, just...
just doesn't appeal to me in that way.
OK, so all that stuff you said
about monogamy being unnatural,
- you're just making excuses.
- I do not make excuses.
Only people
who are ashamed make excuses.
Bones, two guys at the same time,
it's not right.
I mean,
that's why they invented dueling.
Hey, you guys ready?
I know what I'm doing, Booth.
My gut says you're going
with your gut on this one,
and we all know how that ends up.
Not good.
Is there something we need
to discuss before getting to work?
No, no.
Just call me when
you find something of value.
No, it's nothing.
It's just, she's got a date.
- Oh, and how do you feel about that?
- It's not about me, OK?
Let's go look at those videos.
Do you have any idea
how good it smells in here?
It's Eau de Formaldehyde,
glad you like it.
There are hairline fractures
at the base of the skull.
Probably made when the photo
was jammed down his throat.
Dr. Hodgins could probably
pull some particulates.
Very good.
My boyfriend thinks it's weird
that I love doing this. But,
I think it's weird
that he loves the accordion.
- I'm with you there.
- Dr. Brennan is my hero,
always has been.
I just, I hope she loves, she likes me.
Well, bonjour.
Ante-mortem fractures
to the lumbar vertebrae.
- Maybe two weeks old.
- Try to find what caused it.
On it.
It's just, Dr. Brennan and I are,
like, the same, you know?
We just, we understand
that the dead don't talk back
or want the window open
when it's freezing out
or pick at your plate or
pee on the toilet seat...
You might want to keep
a little mystery about yourself.
Sure.
But you're gonna put in a good word
for me, right? I mean,
wouldn't it be fun
if I were here forever?
Yeah.
Brush abrasions.
Can you hand me a swab?
I managed to get some
usable pieces of that photo.
Just fragments, but it's a start.
Okay. I used an infrared camera
and I excluded all the visible light.
If I had to take a guess,
I'd say the mystery couple
were knocking boots.
I always love your clinical assessments.
Sorry. I'm so sorry. "Sorry"?!
But nothing was gonna happen.
- Nothing was gonna happen?
- Nothing...
- You're in your under... Don't!
- God, please don't cry.
- Don't cry? Don't cry.
- You're in your underwear.
- What do you want me...
- Nothing...
- What'd I miss?
- Six men crying,
two insisting they'd gotten lost,
four saying they were trying
to show the poor, young woman
how dangerous the Internet could be.
Parade of saints?
The murder was premeditated
and filled with rage,
not the act of someone
apologetic or ashamed.
Did you find any rage?
Well, I know you don't have the benefit
of years of psychological traing,
but, check out one Jim Dodd.
Come on, baby, I can't wait.
You bastard!
You're never gonna see this child, ever!
Do you hear me? Ever!
I'm Bill O'Roarke, and, Jim Dodd,
you've been Busted By Bill!
- Oh, God! Stop it! Stop!
- I'll kill you!
Stop!
Come one, stop!
Serious impulse control issues.
Very good, Agent Booth.
I've marked a few other possible
suspects that match the profile,
but I think Dodd exhibits
the right amount of rage and
and self-justifying vengeance.
So, Dodd's our guy.
Let's go tell Bones, come on.
Well... couldn't we just call?
No. Let's go.
Open City might be
Rossellini's best film.
Rossellini had nothing, no sets...
1945, the country had barely started
rebuilding after the war.
Yes. Of course,
I'm also a big fan of Meatballs,
Bill Murray's paean to anarchy.
Hey, Bones.
Hi. Special Agent Booth, her partner.
- Hi.
- I'm Dr. Lance Sweets.
- I'm their therapist.
- Jason DeFry.
DeFry.
Do you follow them around all the time?
No. No, no, no. I'm also a profiler.
I help with the cases.
- Did you know that she was on a date?
- Slipped my mind.
Spiffy suit, man.
Thanks. Picked it up in Italy.
Little tight? It's the style.
- You ever been married?
- No.
Have a kid?
Never been married, remember?
I have a kid.
He's never been married.
I should get to work, Jason.
We've got a murder to catch,
you understand?
Of course, of course.
You know, it's getting late anyway.
Listen, I have Coldplay tickets
for tomorrow night.
Thought maybe we'd grab a bite first.
Any interest?
Absolutely.
I might have to leave from work.
No problem.
I'll meet you at your office at 6:00?
I'll be there.
Nice meeting you all.
Yeah.
- No wonder you two are platonic.
- What is that supposed to mean?
Well, look, I'm fine with it, Bones,
really. I have zero problems with it,
but... that guy is gay.
- He is not gay.
- Please.
- Double cheek kiss, tight Italian suit,
- Coldplay.
- never married,
Jason is as heterosexual
as either of you.
Then how is it that he's okay
with not having sex?
What?
We share an intellectual bond.
I don't have physical feelings for him.
He understands that.
Not if he's straight. Right? Am I right?
You are hot.
You're here for a reason?
We got something off the DVDs...
Mint tea, fruit tart...?!
- Okay, speak, Sweets, please.
- Okay,
most of the cheaters
were essentially cowards,
seeking alternate
sexual experiences because
they're too afraid to confront
the problems in their own lives.
Just because someone seeks
an alternative sexual outlet
doesn't mean that they're a coward.
- She has issues.
- I do not have issues.
Case in point:
Deep-sea welder and a botanist.
What, did they go into a bar?
No.
Brennan's two boyfriends.
Right. Let me guess,
that one's the botanist.
Yeah.
- So you have nothing.
- Show her.
This is Jim Dodd.
The photograph that
you pulled out of O'Roarke's throat,
turns out that
Jim Dodd used to be a mall
photographer at Tiny Tots Photography.
- Motive and means.
- Yeah, I mean,
his landlord said he disappeared
five days ago, no forwarding address.
And you think he left because
he was planning to kill Bill O'Roarke?
Yeah, it fits, okay?
Landlord also said he has a drinking
buddy by the name of Chris Gutman.
We're looking for him.
What?
This couldn't have waited till after
I said good night to Jason?
I'm just looking out for you, all right?
You don't have the best taste in men.
So you're going to hire
a stalker to find Dodd?
Perfect undercover move.
- So you think this is a good idea?
- Of course I do, it's mine, okay?
Gutman was lying through his teeth.
There he is right over there.
This way, we'll be able to find out
what he really knows.
Yo, namaste, guys.
- Hi, Noel.
- Think they have mung beans?
- I'm on an ayurvedic cleanse.
- What?
I do mung beans till Sunday,
then I start the enemas.
Listen, Noel, we'd like to harness you
for your natural abilities.
- You want your chart done?
- No.
Stalking.
You like to stalk people.
Observe them.
Hey, Noel, eyes over here.
Okay?
Eyes on him, not her, him.
Noel.
Chris Gutman.
- So not my type.
- It's not recreational.
I want to find out where he goes,
who he sees, who he talks to.
Okay, listen, he hangs out with
a guy by the name of Jim Dodd.
Want me to write that down for you?
- I got it.
- What's his name?
- Jim Dodd.
- Right.
Jim Dodd. I want details.
I'll give you 50 bucks.
50 bucks?
Sure, but I got to be done by Sunday,
because I got this...
Right, the enemas.
Nomaste.
Namaste.
Everything you never wanted
to drain from outhouse sludge.
Two toy cars, three cell phones,
a doorknob, a rubber casing,
plastic Easter bunny head, and...
drumroll...
optional...
one slightly used 40-caliber bullet.
Excellent.
If Booth can find the murder weapon,
we can match it.
We may not have to wait that long.
I took some initiative
and checked out the lumbar fractures
I found on O'Roarke
figured he'd have
to be treated for them.
He was treated at Providence Hospital.
The police brought him in.
The wife of a guy he busted rammed Bill
with her grocery cart at Food King.
You did this without my approval?
And why shouldn't I toss you out
of here right now?
Dr. Brennan says that in an intellectual
pursuit, therer are no limits.
In fact there are.
Produce section road rage is a long way
from shooting a man dead.
Not if you're a police officer
who carries a gun
the same caliber as the bullet
you found in the poop pit.
"Capitol Police Sergeant
Francis Diamond."
Doesn't it feel as
if I've always been here?
I hate Bill O'Roarke.
He tried to destroy my marriage.
But I didn't kill him.
You don't think your husband
cheating might have
put a wrinkle in your relationship?
What my husband did was not cheating.
See, this is a woman enlightened enough
not to expect a monogamous relationship.
He'd never cheat on me.
Okay, then why did you turn your husband
in to the Busted by Billshow?
I didn't, it was my sister.
She called up their tip line.
Kept insisting that he was messing
around, but it wasn't true.
Sergeant Diamond, we saw the video.
Your husband met the young woman
at the motel...
- with flowers.
- And then took off his pants.
He went there to warn her that it could
be dangerous meeting someone online.
Perhaps she's not so enlightened.
Okay, Ballistics is going to need
to see the sidearm.
Please.
Now.
I want to show you what I found lodged
in Bill O'Roarke's lower intestine.
I can't understand why Booth has
an issue with me seeing two men.
Guys like to think they're the only ones
who should sleep with more
than one person.
They like to be in control.
Doesn't take a lot to throw
the little darlings off their game.
Oh, yeah, then you end up lying in bed
holding them while they say,
"I don't know what's wrong, this has
never happened to me before."
He should be happy that I've found
a way to satisfy myself.
It just happens to require two men.
I've done that.
I miss college.
And the botanist,
no biological imperative?
He's flirted with the intent
to become intimate,
but Mark keeps me quite sated sexually.
You've really got to learn
some girl talk, sweetie.
Okay, look at that.
How did a wire get lodged
in his intestine?
Not sure yet.
The tox screen's even stranger.
Tetrahydrozoline hydrochloride.
- Eye drops?
- And sildenafil citrate.
Viagra.
Bloodshot eyes and wood in a pill.
Party time.
Dr. Brennan, I'm Daisy Wick,
your new grad assistant.
I'd rather not learn your name
until I've assessed your work.
Oh, of course.
I'm the same way.
We're two of a kind.
You're like a hero to me.
Hero worship exposes a lack of
independent intellectual examination.
I'll tell Booth what we found.
She is so smart.
Yeah.
So Sergeant Diamond's firearm
wasn't a match.
She wasn't even in town
Friday and Monday.
She was with her husband fixing her
marriage at some tantric sex workshop.
I've heard that if practiced correctly,
tantric sexual techniques
can extend orgasms
by 400 to 500 percent.
They actually teach that?
Teach what?
Extended orgasms through tantric yoga.
- No, Bones, don't encourage this guy.
- It's a godly pursuit, man.
Noel?
What do you have for us?
I followed Gutman from
that gas station where he works.
Are you embarrassed to talk about...?
Gutman went off shift at 7:00,
beelined for the roach coach.
Dude actually ate a hot dog.
You have any idea how many toxins
are in your hot dog?
- Yes, I do.
- Jim Dodd, Noel.
He caught the M Street bus.
Sat next to a girl wearing
a Led Zeppelin tour T-shirt.
Not a real one.
One of those fakes where Jimmy Page
has a Stratocaster instead of a Gibson.
- Where did he go?
- To a church, St. Xavier's.
Goes down to the basement
where they store all these awesome
Christmas decorations.
The Jesus is like...
you could sit down and share
a doobie with Him, you know?
I really hope this has something
to do with Jim Dodd.
Not only did he meet up with Dodd,
he sat next to him for two hours.
With the life-sized Jesus?
No, man!
They were in divorce support group.
They're breakup buddies.
Getting busted by O'Roarke must've
ended Jim Dodd's marriage.
Would you say that these divorce
support groups were angry?
No way.
The guys are all sad and weepy.
The dumped chicks eat it up.
The Dodd dude, he's hooking up
with at least two of them,
which is probably
why he goes there every day.
Which I know...
'cause I photocopied the sign-in sheet.
- Right, that's great.
- So how'd I do?
Oh, right.
You did great.
Here you go, pal. Get all the mung beans
and the enemas you want.
Boy, here you go.
See ya.
The loan shark's got me down
for five G's plus the vig,
so I told Gutman to keep his mouth
shut if anybody asked about me.
How was I supposed to know
it was gonna be the FBI?
So, why'd you do a runner last week?
I owe two grand back rent,
child support,
alimony, plus the loan shark...
I mean, wouldn't you run?
And all this hard luck is because
of Bill O'Roarke, right?
What?
No. No, it had nothing to do with that.
Where were you Friday and Saturday?
I didn't kill him.
I swear.
Where were you?
I drove to Jersey to
borrow money from my mom.
She pawned her engagement ring because
the loan shark was gonna
rip my ears off.
Pathetic.
Mother's contact information.
Hey. So...
it takes over two hours for this
computer to render each new image, but
this last pass gave us a little
more detail in that photograph.
- What is that on her back?
- A tattoo?
- It's a tramp stamp of some kind.
- Cool.
Useful, I hope.
Anyway...
I was starting to enhance the resolution
when Sweets brought me the videos.
O'Roarke was talking to his producer.
Appeared upset, but the sound
was distorted and barely audible.
They were Busted By Bill.
I'm Bill O'Roarke.
Okay, let's get a tail slate.
Arthur, a moment... now.
What's up, Billy?
Okay, I sampled Bill's voice and
I removed all the extraneous noise.
Arthur, a moment... now.
What's up, Billy?
This thing with Veronica, it's over.
- I can't work with her anymore.
- Just kiss and make up.
No, I want her gone.
I'm serious.
Sounds like Viagra-popping Billy
might have gotten himself
a bit too involved with someone at work.
So that could be
Veronica in the picture.
Fits the profile:
jilted and vengeful.
That's a wrap.
Sorry to interrupt.
I'm just packing up some things
for our daughter.
I don't know if she wants them,
but maybe someday.
If you don't mind, Mrs. O'Roarke,
we'd like a word with Veronica.
Sure. Excuse me.
Is there a problem?
Did Mr. O'Roarke ask Arthur Lang
to fire you?
I'm still working here, aren't I?
- Because O'Roarke is dead.
- See, I'm thinking that you got fired,
then you got angry,
which led to revenge.
Is he serious?
Why would O'Roarke want you fired?
I sold a new show... on my own.
Bill accused me of stealing
the idea from him.
Did you?
No. I didn't.
I knew he'd be mad when he found out,
but the idea was mine.
And now that he's dead, we're just going
to have to believe you, right?
I worked with Bill
every day for two years.
We were incredibly close.
We would've made up.
How close?
What is that supposed to mean?
I believe Agent Booth is asking if you
had sexual intercourse with O'Roarke.
But I agree, he could have phrased
the question more clearly.
No.
I was not sleeping with Bill.
Do you have a tattoo on
the small of your back?
If there are no more questions, I would
like to help Amanda with Bill's things.
Excuse me.
I'm done with the culture you swabbed
from the wound on the victim's thigh.
What'd you get?
A trace of enameled iron,
a fleck of silver plating.
Maybe from a knife?
Don't think so.
The wound's too jagged and
I found amylase activity.
He had saliva and iron
in a wound on his thigh?
And I found candidiasis in the saliva.
Okay, so somebody with
a thrush infection
scratched him with something metal,
and then licked him?
You're getting warm.
Look.
Come on, you can do it.
Distance between peaks is irregular
and about two inches apart.
- Hmm... wavy thigh scratch.
- Oral thrush.
Wiggle your tongue side to side.
- You serious?
- Oh, yeah.
Infected tongue piercing.
You want to see it?
Silver-plated iron.
Come on, was it something
that Bill did to you?
I mean, he was older than you?
- Probably took advantage of you?
- No. No, Bill was a good man.
You two were sleeping together,
weren't you?
I don't have to answer
questions like that.
I know my rights.
Your stud, please?
- You're kidding.
- You really
should consider some nystatin for
that infection, by the way.
We found saliva in the laceration
on your boss'thigh.
And we can prove that it's yours.
Your stud.
- Forget it. No way.
- Well, we have a court order.
We know our rights, too, so...
Your stud, please.
That wasn't too hard.
You're sure you don't want
to talk to us?
It is not what you think.
- What do I think?
- We loved each other.
I didn't kill him.
Why would I kill a man that I loved?
Is that how you got the job,
sleeping with O'Roarke?
No!
No, it was...
it was Pete, the camera guy.
Okay, Pete and I met at a club one night
and we went out for a while.
Anyway, we still have a place together.
And Pete knew that I wanted
to get into TV,
so he got me a job as
a production assistant,
and, um... Bill just kind of...
took me under his wing.
I'd say so.
Didn't bother you that he was married?
Perhaps he wasn't fully satisfied
in a long-term relationship.
What? It's understandable.
Needs change.
When did you last have intercourse?
- Is she for real?
- I'm sorry.
We have to ask these kind of questions
in a murder investigation.
Intercourse?
Friday night.
Just before he disappeared.
What happened, Holly?
You were lying there in his arms.
You tell him you're tired of
his wife getting all the money, the...
No, I never cared about the money.
So... you tell him
that he should leave her,
but he says he's got a life with her,
he's got a daughter, and right there,
you snap, you realize you've been used.
So you show him a picture
of the two of you.
Oh, my God.
You cram this down his throat.
Then you shoot him.
Do you have any body modifications other
than the... piercing, Ms. Markwell?
- What, like fake boobs?
- No, like tattoos.
I have to, right?
I'm afraid so.
You know, I loved Bill.
I didn't kill him.
And there you have it.
You are busted, Billy.
Holly admits it's her in the
picture but insists she didn't kill him.
If denial is severe enough,
she might actually believe that.
I know what was used to cram
the picture down his throat.
Because of what I found.
Hi, Dr. Brennan.
I don't fraternize at work.
Daisy found the fractures
on the sagittal suture,
- which contained some particulates.
- Told you.
They are chlorinated polyethylene.
It's the rubber used on
the tail of a microphone.
The copper wire found in his intestine
was from inside that rubber cap.
Putrescent gases forced
the wire into the esophagus,
and the buoyancy of the outhouse sewage
caused it to migrate up
the digestive tract to the intestine.
Holly had access to the microphone.
She's small. Do you think she could have
upended a 180-pound man and
placed him in a poop pit?
You're her size. Pick up Dr. Sweets
and turn him upside down.
What?
That's not going to happen.
I have to.
Oh, no, no, no, no, you don't,
you don't, you don't, it's fine.
Nice.
So it's probably not Holly.
Anyone else have access
to the equipment?
The print was e-mailed to somebody.
The murder was surprised
and enraged by that image.
I minored in psychology.
Really?
Yeah.
Holly wouldn't be surprised.
She knew she slept with Bill.
Right, but someone who was sleeping
with either O'Roarke or Holly
might have seen this.
The image triggered the killer's rage.
There was only one way
to avenge that violation.
The killer had to make sure
that this image died with O'Roarke.
That's brilliant.
I know who did it.
- So, you sure?
- Yeah, it's the only person...
who makes sense.
Mark, wha-what are you doing here?
Well, you told me to pick you up.
- With dinner?
- I... am so sorry.
I... there's been an emergency.
Okay, do you want me
to reschedule, or...?
- Temperance.
- Jason!
What are you doing here?
- We're going to Coldplay, remember?
- You remember Coldplay.
Coldplay?
Sorry, I've been distracted by the case.
Why don't we ever go to a concert?
As a matter of fact, why don't
we ever leave your bedroom?
- Can we talk about this later?
- We're about to arrest...
- You're dating this guy?
- I don't like that term.
It has an antiquated moral and
needlessly restrictive connotation.
And who are you?
Obviously, a guy who is not doing
as well as you.
This is Jason.
Jason, Mark.
Mark, Jason.
Please understand, Jason, you're very
good-looking, but sexual attraction
is an involuntary hormonal response
involving an increase
- in neutrophins and testosterone.
- So you get to go out?
Mark, you are a strong
and attentive man,
but Jason is more stimulating
intellectually.
That's not the only
way I could be stimulating.
- Murder?
- Murder, yes.
What do you do with this one?
Oh... this...
Booth is my partner, that's all.
We should go.
Yes, okay. All right. Oh, Jason,
we can talk at the concert.
I'll meet you out front by 8:00,
and Mark, we can...
talk later at... my apartment.
Oh, yes. See you, boys. Thanks.
I'll grab one of those.
Thi-This is crazy.
Why would I kill him?
I mean, B- Bill and I were like family.
Because he was sleeping
with your girlfriend.
Although not only did
you lose your girlfriend,
you lost your job.
It was not a good choice.
What is she talking about?
No, Holly and I are,
we're just roommates.
Yeah, but you used to be a couple
and you were in love with her.
And you felt that Bill ruined
it for you.
No, no.
You said that O'Roarke wasn't home
when you went to pick him up
Saturday morning, but that's not true.
You brought him
his usual cup of coffee,
but this time you put in
something a little special.
Tetrahydrozoline hydrochloride.
That right there is squint talk
for eyedrops.
Old bartender's trick, guaranteed
to give ll the runs.
You guys don't know
what you're talking about.
Really?
- Where did you get that?
- What'd you do, Pete...
set up your own camera, shoot
your own show so you could bust Bill?
I just lost it.
Look, I'm a nice guy.
I am.
You can ask anybody.
I just lost it.
Hey.
Come on in.
You look nice, Dr. Brennan.
Oh, thank you, uh...
I was supposed to go to a...
gallery opening tonight.
What, did Jason get a new tight suit?
- With Mark.
- Yeah, the two amigos.
I thought he was more of your,
"stay at home" kind of a guy.
I was visiting the possibility
that I might enjoy him
in a strictly conversational setting.
And?
Since the murder, I'm considering
the argument for monogamy.
Write that one down, Sweets.
I have a positive influence on her.
- No, you don't.
- Yes, I do.
Mark broke up with me.
Sorry. Well, what about "gay Jason"?
Him, too.
I guess they weren't as accepting
of each other as I thought, so...
Is it typical for you two to discuss
your love lives?
Well, I mean, only when she has
naked men in her apartment.
No, that's not true. I'm very open about
my relationships, as opposed to you.
Okay, what's that supposed to mean?
You're very secretive,
as if discussing your sex life would
somehow be offensive to me.
- I assume you are sexually active.
- I do fine.
Does it seem that your partnership
provides a surrogate relationship,
making it more difficult
to form other bonds?
A surrogate relationship wouldn't
necessarily be such a bad thing
because then I could avoid the sting
of rejection, which, however fleeting,
is still uncomfortable.
Right.
Okay, look, I'm sorry.
You know what?
If Mark and Jason don't know
how lucky they are,
they don't deserve you
in the first place.
All relationships are temporary.
No, that's not true, Bones.
You're wrong.
Okay, there is someone for everyone,
someone you're meant to spend
the rest of your life with.
All right?
You just have to be open
enough to see it.
That's all.
Come on, I'll buy you dinner.
Hey, I can be fun in a strictly
conversational setting.
See?
Surrogate relationship.
Surrogate nothing.
Okay? It's a meal. With drinks.
- Just strictly conversational.
- I can come, too.
Actually, our partnership does make
it difficult to form other bonds.
No offense.
- Our session isn't over yet.
- How about Chinese?
I love Chinese.
Love it.
- I feel more like Thai.
- Thai?
I got coupons to Hop Li.
What, you're gonna take me out
for a discount meal?
What? There's two for one,
and then they throw in some...
Hi, is this Daisy Wick?
Hey, this is Lance.
Uh, the shrink.
Yeah.
Listen... sorry you got fired.
Nothing.
What are you doing?
The accordion?
No, no, no, I...
I play a little bass, though.
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--