- Hi.
Try this one.
- Emily.
- Yes ?
Come here.
They haven't called our number yet.
I know.
Relax agent Fornell.
She's fine.
I didn't expect to see
you again until... 2067 ?
I got a reprieve.
you're not going to use that
in front of your daughter.
I don't need a gun to take you down.
- You wouldn't hurt a innocent man.
- I'm not looking at one.
That's where you and agent Gibbs got it wrong.
Agent Gibbs is retired.
I know. Why do you think I'm talking to you ?
I have no idea. Why don't you enlighten me.
I told you. You got the wrong guy.
And if there's a shred of decency in you,
and brains...
...you'll re-open my case and find the right one.
Now I'm going to walk out of here.
You'll want to follow.
But you'll realize something
and end up just reaching
for that cell instead.
- Really ?
- Yeah.
What's that ?
I might not be alone.
- See you, sweetie.
- Bye.
T
Te
Tea
Team
Team-
Team-N
Team-NC
Team-NCI
Team-NCIS.com presents :
NCIS Season 4 Episode 2
Escaped
Script : FRM
Synch : BadGOne & Pit for www.Team-NCIS.com
The basement needs some work.
But if it doesn't showed "wine cellar,"
...I don't know what does.
Have a look.
And I'll be right back.
- First my wife, now my house ?
- No.
No, I learned lesson.
I'm through with your leftovers.
You're going to need a
bigger box for that boat.
You come all the way out here to give me packing tips, Tobias ?
Actually, I came to tell you that
Petty Officer Derrick Paulson escaped form prison yesterday.
No.
I haven't asked
you anything yet.
You caught him last time.
Figured you might like
to catch him again.
You thought wrong.
He came to see me, Jethro.
When I was with Emily.
She okay ?
For now.
He just wanted to tell me
that I got the wrong man,
and strongly suggested that
I reopen his case to prove it.
He's risking a lot for something
he's knows can't happen.
You think ?
I don't know what his game is.
But I'm not going to get
a good night's sleep
until that S.O.B.
is back behind bars.
You don't need
me to find him.
Need ?
A convicted killer was two
inches from my daughter !
Handing her crayons.
He touched her!
We're way beyond
need, Jethro.
Nice tan.
It's really not that bad, McGee.
For a spy, you're
a horrible liar.
Ziva's right.
You can hardly notice.
But...
But ?
I wouldn't let Agent DiNozzo
see it if I were you.
Let Agent DiNozzo
see what ?
Nothing.
Why are you mumbling, McGee ?
I'm not mumbling.
Well, you either just said
"mimes aren't rumbling"
or "I'm not mumbling."
And I don't see
any mimes.
Agent Lee,
why is Agent McGee
mumbling ?
He over-bleached
his teeth, sir.
Apparently, he fell
asleep while wearing
his bleaching tray, sir.
You don't watch
Friends, do you ?
Same thing
happened to Ross.
You could have learned
from our friend's mistake.
But you
choose to read instead.
Better let me
see the damage.
As team leader, people,
I need to be aware
of any condition
that might affect
an agent's ability
to perform
his or her duties.
And what does having
embarrassingly
white teeth have to do
with performing his duties ?
You said it was
not that bad.
She lied.
- Open up your mouth.
- No.
- Let me see the Chiclets.
Let me see 'em.
- No.
- Open your...
Gibbs.
What is... ?
I have no idea.
Agent Gibbs !
I mean, Mister...
Just as I was
getting used to
my door being
treated as a door.
I'll call you back, Todd.
I need a temporary
reinstatement.
I assume you're here
because of ex-Petty Officer
Derrick Paulson.
I read
Agent Fornell's report.
Why the sudden, if temporary,
interest in
bank robbers ?
If you've read Fornell's report,
Jen, then you already know.
We're wasting time.
It's not that simple, Jethro.
You left.
I appreciate
what you did for Ziva,
but this is not
some gym membership
that you can turn on and off.
No, I can't ; but I'm not
director of NCIS.
And the director of NCIS
already filed
your retirement package
with Navy Human Resources.
Un-file it.
It doesn't work that way,
Jethro.
It would take weeks
to reinstate you.
And that's even if
you managed to pass your...
My psych evaluation ?
Or are you talking about
my firearms proficiency exam ?
No.
That one I'm not worried about.
Wait.
Let me at least...
...validate your parking.
That's strange.
I could've sworn
I filed this.
Your retirement package.
I must have
accidentally put in
for your unused
leave time instead.
Of which, it seems,
there are
six days left
until it has to be filed.
Come on, don't tell me you
don't eavesdrop, Cynthia.
Every director's
assistant eavesdrops.
He's coming.
Hey, Gibbs.
Just visiting
the neighborhood or...
taking your desk back?
Let's go.
You should've been here
half an hour ago.
Yeah, i'm just
getting Emily settled
- ... at my mom's place.
- Want me to send an agent over ?
How many can you spare ?
Okay, I've got an idea.
Maybe he lost his memory again
and forgot he quit his job.
Wouldn't he be sitting
at his old desk then ?
If Gibbs wanted us
to know what he was doing,
he would've told us.
Oh, right.
Because he would
never expect us
to figure it out
for ourselves.
Gibbs is back...
on temporary assignment.
The Paulson case.
Paulson ?!
Petty Officer Derrick Paulson :
knocked over a bank,
killed two of his accomplices,
money was never found.
Paulson's
prison cell.
I want to see what was in it.
I've already sent
the contents over.
Maybe your techs can find
something mine didn't.
Bye, Daddy !
I'm worried.
She'll be fine, Tobias.
Paulson isn't after her.
I ruined his life, Jethro.
We don't know what he's after.
Anything good ?
Yeah.
It's a jailhouse appeal
from some escaped convict.
The guy really knows
his forensics.
I knew it ! I knew it !
Won't need these anymore
now that you're actually here.
I knew you'd come back.
I'm not back.
Of course you're back.
I can feel your badge.
That is your badge, right ?
You are back.
Reinstatement's
only temporary, Abs.
Until I can find Paulson.
We'll see about that.
So what can I do for you,
temporarily reinstated
Agent Gibbs ?
Process the contents
of Paulson's cell.
What am I looking for ?
Oh, right.
Anything to help you find him.
I want to know what he was
up to before he escaped.
Unless the three of you
have any other suggestions.
Uh...
Hey...
We were, we
were just, uh,
eavesdropping like little girls.
But we do have
suggestions.
Prison records show
that only one person ever came
to visit Paulson in jail.
Mickey Stokes, 72.
Former Navy sailor.
And since Paulson
has no family,
we should assume that he'll try
to contact Mickey.
And I already
have an address.
Tony, Ziva, you're with me.
McGee, stay here and...
McGee, stay here, help Abby.
...help Abby...
...process Paulson's
belongings.
Then gargle this.
Before the rest of
us go snow-blind.
Gibbs seemed awfully
quiet in the car.
It's not like you were giving
him a chance to talk, Tony.
What, are you nervous he's
going to want his old job back ?
No. I'm just
bringing him up to speed
on the latest
protocols.
What took you hotshots
so long ?
He's been waiting
over an hour.
Hey, shoes off !
Clear.
Where is he ?
I never said he was here.
Gibbs.
Didn't expect
to hear your voice.
I heard you quit.
Retired.
At your age,
that's quitting.
Why don't you turn yourself in,
you can tell me
about this in person.
Turn myself in for what ?
I'm an innocent man.
Try broken record.
So you're not
going to reopen my case ?
We both know what I'll find
if I do, so why don't you
tell me what you really want.
I already got it, Agent Gibbs.
So what does he really want ?
Our Car.
They appear to
be close.
Well, they say the way
to a man's heart
is through his stomach.
Meals on Wheels.
Looks like Paulson was a volunteer.
He volunteered to
put... meals on wheels ?
They bring food to the elderly, Ziva.
Of course I helped him !
Derrick was like
a son to me.
I was the closest thing
he had to family.
What would you do if it
was your kid in trouble ?
I would've told him to give himself up before he got hurt.
I'm glad you ain't my old man, Fornell.
Shoes off !
And I certainly wouldn't let him
steal my car.
Didn't. It was DiNozzo's car.
He just wants you
to reopen his case !
You been reading my
letters the past four years ?
You bozos got the wrong guy.
Paulson took advantage of you, Mickey.
He only brought you food because you lived near the bank he was casing.
You wasted your life savings
defending the wrong guy.
Hey !
Not my computer !
I got an online date tonight.
Where is he, Mickey ?
He doesn't know.
You sure ?
Want to hit him
for aiding and abetting ?
He did shelter Paulson,
he gave him money.
I say we
use him as bait.
Give Mickey a pass, put a man on him in case Paulson comes back?
You're the boss.
Yeah ?
Where ?
Anything in it ?
D.C. Metro just found our car
half a mile from here.
The only thing missing
was my laptop.
And every file
we had on Paulson.
I told you, he just...
he just wants
to work on his case.
Except he's had all his
case files since the trial.
Perhaps ours have
something his didn't.
They do.
The addresses
of the witnesses
who testified against him.
He's not a threat to anyone !
He's on the run
and unarmed.
Do you keep any
weapons in the house ?
Oh, great.
Now you're going to pin
another crime on him ?
Just my old Colt.
Where is it ?
Paulson could be after any
one of a half dozen witnesses.
I've never seen a convicted
felon file so many appeals.
It's an abuse
of the system.
We're all entitled
to our day in court.
Not according
to Agent Gibbs.
I've been going over
his case files.
He seems to prefer
a more biblical
approach to things.
If you ask me,
the agency's better off
without him.
Oh.
I like you, Michelle,
so I'm just going to pretend
like you didn't
say that.
NCIS is lucky
to have Gibbs back.
Except he's not staying.
You do realize...
You can kill me without leaving
any forensic evidence behind ?
Yeah, you mentioned that.
Good, then.
It's settled.
Gibbs is staying.
He has to.
Right, Gibbs ?
What do you got
for me, Abby ?
Paulson's fingerprints
on the gun case
and on Mickey's computer.
And he's also visited over
a dozen People Search sites.
I think he was looking
for someone.
Yeah, I got
that part.
No names yet,
but I'm using the FBI's
mainframe to decrypt
the search cache.
Oh. You always did have
really good timing.
Mickey ?!
Where the hell
is Mickey, you tramp?
Mickey isn't here.
It's Mickey's
online playmate.
She keeps tunneling
through my firewall.
Russell Nash.
Apparently, he's...
The only accomplice
Paulson didn't kill.
Yeah, and the one
he really should have.
Nash copped a plea and testified
against Paulson.
Paulson got life,
and Nash walked
in 18 months.
Skipped out on his parole.
Hasn't been seen since.
Well, if the money was
never found, then maybe
Paulson is looking
for Nash
because he thinks
Nash has the money.
Or maybe Paulson is looking
for something a little more...
biblical.
Thank you.
I'll let Agent Gibbs
know immediately.
And I'll see you Saturday.
Okay.
Hey, was the FBI able
to warn all the witnesses?
All except
for one.
Is that your third
Caf-POW!, McGee?
It's my fourth.
How do they look?
Hmm. Maybe you should
switch to blueberries.
Anything good on
our tip hotline?
Is there ever?
Half our callers don't know
what a tip is.
Have you spoken to Gibbs yet?
What about?
You're not
wondering why he's back?
Help Fornell like he helped you.
Taking a little
break, DiNozzo?
Oh, I think you know
exactly what I'm doing,
Agent Gibbs.
Why do you think he's back?
I don't know, but I'm
hoping it's more than just Fornell.
Let's just say I'm getting
sick of the campfires.
Showtime.
Wouldn't let Tony
hear you say that.
Say what, Agent McGee?
Yeah, I was just telling
McGee the FBI was able to...
Warn all the witnesses from
Paulson's trial, except for one?
Right! The only one
they couldn't find was...
Russell Nash.
I have much to
learn still, Master.
Campfire!
There you go.
Sort of a new thing
that I like to do.
I find it focuses the group
better than just, uh,
you know, shouting
across the bullpen.
Not that there's anything
wrong with that.
Let's focus on Russell Nash.
The inside man.
Worked for the bank
that Paulson knocked over.
Our only
missing witness.
According to Abby,
he's the one Paulson's after.
- We find Nash...
- We find Paulson.
Campfire over.
And the last question.
"In your own words,
the difference
between ethics and morals."
Well, the ethical man knows
he shouldn't cheat on his wife,
whereas the moral man
actually wouldn't.
You're going to ace
your oral exams, Doctor.
Going back to school?
I never stopped.
The doctor's getting a degree
in Forensic Psychology.
Yes, and with it,
I'll be able to add
the Psychological
Autopsy to my arsenal.
I'll not only be able
to uncover the hows
of our patient's demise,
but the whys, as well.
I mean, what motivates us
can be a very tricky thing.
I was wondering
when you were going
to come down
and see me.
I've been busy.
Or avoiding me.
I wonder
why that could be.
I'm not staying.
Oh, I didn't
think you were.
I'm aware that when Leroy
Jethro Gibbs makes up his mind,
his mind's made up.
So...
why are you here?
The Paulson case--
how much do you know?
Well, I took the liberty of
examining the M.E.'s reports
on Paulson's two
murdered accomplices.
Anything bug you?
It's about as watertight a case
as I've ever seen,
pathologically
speaking-- why?
Do you suspect foul
play in the foul play?
No.
Yet you're down here asking me
if anything "bugs you"
about the case.
Are you getting one of those
famous gut instincts again?
I've already had that, and
it said that Paulson was guilty.
And when Leroy Jethro Gibbs
makes up his mind,
his mind's made up.
Too bad
for Petty Officer Paulson.
Let's hope
things work out
better for you in Mexico.
Uh-huh.
No word on the Russell Nash
BOLO, but we got something
off the tip hotline on Paulson.
What?
Paulson.
Hey, Jethro.
Hey, you got a tip hotline
to find me,
but nothing on my original case.
Not cool.
Gonna have to do something
about that.
But for now,
just calling to say thanks
for the car.
I left you a token
of my appreciation in return.
I'm sure you'll find it soon.
Called his own tip hotline.
I'm starting to
like this guy.
We're getting an address
from the back trace now.
We got it!
It's in the city. 4242...
Adams Boulevard?
You been there before, boss?
Yeah.
That's where Paulson killed
his two accomplices.
Is Agent Gibbs aware
our warrant hasn't
officially come through yet?
Yeah, I think he got it by the
fifth time you told him, Lee.
Got my teams
out front.
Any idea what his
game is this time?
Not a clue.
Okay, McGee, Ziva,
fire escape, Lee...
Watch the cars.
Get back.
I imagine you'd rather be
enjoying a nice drink
in a cantina
right about now.
The thought had
crossed my mind.
Mine, too.
Any bets on Paulson's
token of appreciation?
Let's hope it' s not
Russell Nash's head on a stick.
Federal Agents!
It appears
ex-Petty Officer Paulson
is attempting to highlight
the discrepancies
in this crime scene.
Yeah. Picked up on that.
For a guilty man,
he's unusually
intent on trying to convince us
of his innocence.
Picked up on that, too.
No one heard the shooting?
Well, it's not exactly
a Neighborhood Watch
kind of place.
And the fact that
Paulson's DNA was found
under this victim's
fingernails,
but there was no other
sign of a struggle?
Mm-hmm. See that about
a quarter of the time, Ziva.
Why isn't he running?
That's a good question.
What's that gut of yours say?
Four years ago?
That Paulson was guilty.
Didn't mean
four years ago.
Paulson isn't after Nash
for the money
from the bank job.
He's after Nash
because Nash
is the one man
who can exonerate him.
So was your gut wrong
four years ago,
or is it wrong now?
Our job is not to
reopen Paulson's case.
Just catch him.
Paulson's already
reopened his case, Ziva.
Doesn't matter
what our job is,
if we want to figure
out his next move.
Now we're have to
reopen it, too.
Smart kid.
The public defender
who represented Paulson
is out on maternity leave.
- Prosecutor?
- Naval reservist.
Deployed to Iraq
two years ago.
Killed by an IED last month.
Unless we find someone
familiar with the Paulson case,
it'll take us days
just to catch up to speed,
much less anticipate
Paulson's next move.
Relax.
Gibbs brought in Mickey Stokes.
No one knows Paulson
better than him.
Is he even a lawyer?
Well, we can't
all be lawyers,
Agent Lee.
So what changed your mind
about my boy?
Great Oz finally give
you guys a heart?
Who said I've
changed my mind?
Ah, definitely
wasn't a brain.
If Paulson was framed,
we need to find out how.
Maybe it was a brain.
Either way, thank you.
I've waited a long time
for someone to listen.
Don't thank me just yet.
Jury had two weeks,
they didn't buy
that Paulson was framed.
You have one day
to convince our forensic
scientist otherwise.
You must be Mickey.
Well... I'll be
whoever you want me to be.
Mickey will do just fine.
I like your outfit.
Thank you.
My dog has a
collar like that.
So, for the sake
of argument, let's say
that Derrick Paulson
was framed.
That makes Russell Nash
your prime suspect.
Exactly, Director.
Hey, Gibbs.
Why don't you come
on over and join us
for a little campfire?
Where's he going?
Basement.
Fornell.
- Whiskey.
- Not tonight.
His real estate agent's
fumigating his house.
Apparently, Gibbs
got termites.
I'd offer you the sofa,
but when I told Emily
you were staying over,
she insisted you
take her room.
Even said you can sleep
with her Raspberry Rumtart doll.
Daddy, watch.
You may now kiss the bride.
So, it was four wives.
Unless there's anything else
you want to tell me.
Something you
want to know, Tobias?
You had a family, Jethro.
I know you like to play it
close to the vest, but...
Hell, I was married
to your second wife.
I tried to warn you.
I know, I know.
I didn't listen.
If I did, I might
still have a house
with a guest bedroom for you.
I know it's not our usual stuff.
So we screwed up?
Let's wait and see
what Abby says.
We screwed up. Big time.
I'm sure it wasn't
the first time,
and I know it's not
gonna be the last.
My last.
Least we can still
make it right.
If Russell Nash
did frame Paulson,
he's not going to come clean
when Paulson finds him.
He's going to kill Paulson.
I know it.
I said we screwed up, didn't I?
It's funny how things work out.
When I was a kid,
all I ever thought about
was being an FBI Agent.
Now...
not a day goes by I don't
think about being a kid.
I don't pay it
much attention.
The way I figure it,
anyone who doesn't
want to quit this job...
isn't doing it right.
My mother'll kill
me if she sees this.
It's a henna tattoo;
It'll come off in a few days.
Looks good.
Of course,
I love a girl with tattoos.
I've noticed.
Can we just get
this over with?
Go over there.
Could you move around a bit?
All right, how about just
walk back and forth?
Try a... a little attitude!
A little attitude.
You know, swing the hips,
you know.
Hey, give us something
to dance to.
Kick it up.
Swing the pelvis, look.
Like you're walking
down the stage.
Come on, get the
shoulders going...
Stop it.
Huh, the shoulders?
Okay.
Come on, do it.
Okay, only 'cause
it's you, Mickey.
Yeah.
This is not what
it looks like.
Abby, please turn the music off.
Now, please, off.
I'm so...
This is what we were doing, sir:
we were working on the Pauls--
We were...
We were establishing
a baseline
of henna ink's
optical reflectivity.
You want to know why?
Glad you asked.
We're trying to figure out
if the evidence was
planted to frame Paulson.
Yeah, like the DNA they found.
That could easily have
come from some... uh...
Why is he looking
at me like that?
He's kind of
a bottom line guy.
Bottom line: the more Mickey
told us,
the guiltier Paulson looked.
Until we looked at video
from the bank job.
Paulson was identified
by his custom tattoo.
One of a kind,
unique as a fingerprint
and pretty cool.
With the corroborating evidence,
it was more than enough
for a jury to convict.
You think it's a copy?
That's why we were
taking the pictures.
It looks like
a henna tattoo.
But if Russell Nash had
a copy made to frame Paulson...
- There'd be a color-mismatch.
- Can you prove it?
Yeah, but...
I'm gonna have to see Paulson's
original tattoo for the test.
He'll never go for that.
Not unless he believes
you're serious
about reopening his case.
And he won't believe that
until you haul in
that bastard, Russell Nash.
We're working on it.
We've got a lead
on that, too.
The FBI has been doing
background checks
on all of
Nash's buddies.
Meet Gary Silverstin.
Russell Nash's old roommate.
He used to work
at a tattoo shop.
It could just
be a coincidence...
Wow, he hates me.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Careful, Gary.
I told you, stand
five steps back.
Insurance reasons.
You can get insurance
to be a flipper?
Human Directional.
You're a sign, Gary.
Yeah, I'm the future.
You know what, man?
I brought in an
extra ten grand
last month to
Broadbus Burger.
In a couple years, this'll
probably be an Olympic sport.
You think you could be
happy flipping a sign all day?
I don't know.
I think you'd get bored.
You've got to stop
doing that-- stop it!
Am I under arrest?
No.
Then, no, man.
I work by the hour.
Gary...
I can think of a lot
of ways to arrest you.
A lot of 'em.
All right, well, what
else is there to say?
Yeah, I worked
at a tat shop.
Yes, I lived with Nash.
No, I don't know
where he is.
And I don't know nothing
about no bank robbery.
That all went down
after he moved out.
All right?
Sorry, dude.
Good luck in Beijing
in '08, Gary.
I'm just saying,
a man of your drive
and ambition needs
a certain kind of...
I'm not staying, Ziva.
That obvious?
So, how'd it go?
I'll tell you
in 20 seconds.
He's already making a call.
Putting it on speaker.
NASH
Hey, you got Nash.
Leave me a message
after the beep.
I'd say
that went well.
Hey, Nash, it's Gary S.
Now I know you told me
to call you here never, man,
but there was some feds here
and they were asking
questions about that tat.
It's a Baltimore prefix.
At least I think they were Feds.
I never heard of no N-C-
C-I-S...
Got it.
82 West Pratt Street,
apartment 12.
I know it-- 40
miles north of here.
Not bad for rush hour.
Only you could make it 40
miles in 30 minutes, Boss.
Something's wrong.
Maybe Paulson
beat us here
and found out the
hard way that Nash
wasn't willing to
change his testimony.
Stay right where
you are; don't come closer.
Yes, all right.
It's Nash.
The end is
never pleasant.
For this young
man, doubly so.
At least he had a great view
on the way down.
I doubt that
he enjoyed it,
seeing that his
jaw was broken
as well as six
of his fingers
and his knee.
And all this
before he fell.
Killer beat him first.
More like he was
interrogated.
This damage is
too methodical,
too calculated to
be a simple beating.
Whoever did this was
after information.
And when he got it...
he repaid his victim
with these.
Guess we can rule out suicide.
Yes, unless Mr. Nash
was able to shoot
himself in the back
three times in a row.
Ugh...
do we have to do this now?
The slugs are
Winchester hollowpoints.
Hey, Gibbs. Gibbs.
Cool, huh?
They were fired from the Colt
that Baltimore P.D.
found near the scene.
Abs, did you run
the serial number?
It's the same gun that Paulson
took from Mickey Stokes' house.
He tried to wipe it,
but I found
a partial print.
So the gentleman who asked us
to prove his innocence...
just killed the one man
who could exonerate him.
Nash didn't frame Paulson--
they were partners
until Nash double-crossed him.
Our ex-Petty Officer
didn't want to clear himself,
he was looking
for the money.
And he used us to take him
straight to the bank.
Smart kid.
But if your gut says
Paulson's innocent,
then maybe we're
missing something.
The only thing that I am
missing right now
is happy hour
at Carlos' Cantina.
But you're Security, right?
Don't let Gibbs leave
the building.
I already told you why, Tom!
Abby. Never mind. False alarm.
Gibbs, oh, my God.
I was so sure
that you'd be halfway
to Mexico by now.
Sorry, you're a flight risk. Abby!
We're going to figure
this case out, Gibbs.
We always do!
You already
figured it out.
No, but you're going to.
I want to know
how Paulson knows.
Knows what?
Everything.
Everything that we seem to.
Russell Nash hid the money
from the bank job somewhere.
Paulson gets to it before us...
He's gone for good.
So where is it?
Nash was using
an assumed name.
All transactions
were cash-only.
Money's not in a bank.
Storage, maybe.
A third
party could be
holding it.
I'll look at properties
under an alias.
Maybe he hid the money
in a mattress somewhere.
Campfire over.
Where's Gibbs?
I don't know.
Anything wrong?
Uh, well,
actually, yeah,
there's quite a lot wrong, Ziva.
Aside from McGee's teeth,
we have a dead man
who shouldn't be dead,
an innocent man who
isn't really innocent
and a trail that's
about to run cold
because our perp has managed
to stay one step ahead of us
since this whole thing started!
You're just noticing
that now, DiNozzo?
Oh, no, it's kind
of been a theme.
Careful that's, um,
easy to...
...break.
It's a shortwave RF bug.
Paulson probably
planted it in your Dictaphone
when he stole your car.
And I've been burning
campfires to CD.
The Dictaphone has been in my
lab pretty much the entire day.
At least now we know how Paulson
tracked down Russell Nash.
There's the little bugger.
Can you backtrack it, Abs?
It's impossible
without a private cipher.
But... I think I know
where we can get one.
Paulson's crew bugged the bank's
general manager for two weeks
before the robbery-- it was a
custom job, just like this one.
The cops interviewed
the bug-maker.
Cleared him
of any involvement.
I would bet a Caf-POW! that this
came from the same guy.
How can you tell?
He signed his name.
"It is a crime for any person
"acting under color of the law
to deprive any citizen
of their legal rights."
Title Eighteen, U.S. Code.
No one is depriving you
of your rights.
We're simply asking for a copy
of the cipher you made.
"No one shall be compelled
in any criminal case to be
a witness against himself."
That'd be the Fifth Amendment.
And no one has accused you
of a crime, either.
Then why'd your goon
confiscate my files?
Goon?!
Told you to stop hunching
your shoulders.
How do you know he wasn't
talking about you?
It's called
a mirror, McGee.
No, I said every exit,
not every other exit.
For same the reason you don't
floss every other tooth.
Where's that cipher,
DiNozzo?
We hit
a little snafu, boss.
Gibbs.
The federal
code also states Yeah.
that not only have the right
to remain silent,
but to withhold
any information I see fit.
If this keeps up,
we may be forced
to unleash Agent Lee.
- Now, this should be quick.
- Better be.
We got a fugitive on the run
with a pretty big lead.
The Fugitive...
You can stare at me
all day, G-man.
I ain't talking.
You got something to hide?
What, so I refuse to talk
and that means I'm guilty?
You ever heard of
Miranda v.Arizona, 1966?
And here, all this time,
how could
I have missed it?
It's that simple.
Missed what?
Gibbs is clearly
Tommy Lee Jones.
Right, I mean there's
no argument there.
Which makes me Joey Pants;
initially, I was a little...
What happened?
We've been avoiding the word
fugitive for the last two days.
He made the connection himself. Oh.
The bottom line, Eyeballs,
I run a lawfully
licensed spy shop.
I'm not responsible
for what my clientele does
with my product.
I don't have to
answer any more
of your questions,
no matter what you say.
I got this little girl...
who wants to go home to her dad.
And that's not going to happen
without your help.
So...
please.
Did Gibbs just say...?
Mm-hmm.
What-What did you, uh, what'd
you want to know, again?
Signal's
strong, no movement.
Got eyes on the
target, Ziva?
I did; suspect's in the
house and he's not alone.
You sure?
I heard Paulson's voice.
Let me give you some
more money, in case you need it.
I won't.
In position, boss.
Then here, take this.
Gun.
Move, move.
Please, just take it.
Hold it!
Don't do it, Derrick;
we will shoot you.
Tony, McGee,
put your weapons down.
I was wrong.
I know you're innocent,
Petty Officer.
But you're not, Mickey.
DiNozzo.
You're under arrest for the murders of Russell Nash,
his two accomplices in the
Greater Virginia Bank robbery.
And last but
not least
the Greater Virginia
Bank robbery.
Is your porch light on?
First, you wrongly accuse
Derrick and now me.
We also found the
bug you planted
in our forensic tech's lab.
We were almost as
surprised as you look now,
when the guy
you bought it from
pointed you out in that
photo, instead of Paulson.
This is ridiculous.
Do I look like
I got five million bucks
laying around?!
If he set me up,
where's the money?
They don't know what they're
talkin' about.
It's here.
It's been here
the whole time.
It's a Rosewood Bureau
Plat desk,
19th century. That's 38 thousand dollars
First edition of Huckleberry Finn
20,000 dollars
Looks like in the bedroom,
You've got a Chipendale-Mahogany case clock
That's six fingers easy !
Mcgee, you don't collect all these stuff on a Navy pension.
Wow! wow!
Agent Gibbs.
Don't talk to me, I think he should shoot you.
Except he's never been a killer.
And I don't think you're gonna start now.
And miss his trial? Not for the world...
You're a real piece of work, McGee.
Antiques roadshow.
I just came by to tell you that Derrick Pauleson has been cleared of all charges.
- You saved that boy's life.
-Yeah boss *****
Don't sell yourself short.
- Or is it too late for that?
-There's supposed to be some sort of pep* dog,
came here to stay Jen?
You don't want me back.
No I don't.
Or you won't be able to handle me, Director?
No Jethro.
I'm afraid you won't able to handle yourself.
You've already been in two comas.
You might not come out of a third.
The fact is you're good.
The best.
When you're as good, it's something as you are when you
can make a difference like you can you just don't quit.
You know, you used to be a nice person, McGee.
I think sitting at Tony's desk is affecting your personality.
For the better, mcGee picked up a girl all by himself.
- Yeah, at a funeral.
-You didn't tell me that.
Well, you were right.
Because when women are vulnerable,
Get right in there.
What?
www.Team-NCIS.com