She's on the phone right now
with Matt Saracen?
It's becoming that thing
that we always knew
was gonna happen
with our little girl.
We kind of been going out.
But we never
really made it official.
Will you be my girlfriend?
I am here to inform you
that you have been invited
to training camp
in Austin.
The quad rugby
national team
is having tryouts in Austin.
And if I go
and I make the team,
possibly be going to Beijing
later this year.
- Tyra?
- Your mom is the greatest.
She volunteered to help me
finish out tonight.
What is your problem?
Your dad, Buddy Garrity.
His dirty hands all over my mom,
his employee.
Your Dad is down
in Corpus Christi.
He's working on
a driving range.
Do not believe a word
that that man says.
And do not
get drunk with him.
I'm on the wagon now.
Sobered up.
Six weeks next Tuesday.
Tim!
- What are you doing?
- Dad's here.
How about another round,
sweetheart?
Let's go three, corner.
My cue is on fire!
Nice shot!
Oh Lord,
that was nice.
Yes!
Nice shot!
I don't know
what's gotten into him.
I really don't.
I'd say his game's
improved quite a bit
in the last half hour,
wouldn't you?
It's weird, huh?
Yeah, I'll say.
Thank you, darlin'.
Watch your back, sir.
Don't wanna hit you.
This is for all the money.
Who's the winners?
All the way home!
Oh, now you're up against it.
Hey, you wouldn't be hustlin'
us here now, would ya?
Hustlin' you?
Yeah.
Hustlin' you, beating you
with one hand
tied behind my back.
Either way, you still owe me
100 bucks.
Who the hell do you think
you're talking to?
Talking to a guy
that owes me 100 bucks.
The loser
who owes me 100 bucks.
- Oh, really?
- Mm-hmm.
Then how is it
you come into this place
and that boy
can't hit a shot...
Boy, you just...
Who the hell threw that?
No idea.
Did you throw that?
Me? No.
Hey!
You wanna fight me?
Huh?
Take me down?
Aren't you gonna
do anything about this?
My boy can handle himself.
I'll take you outside.
There's gonna be
no fightin' here, Buck.
You lost.
Now pay up and leave.
100 bucks.
There's your money.
You wanna take me out,
you come back and you find me.
Get out.
Hablar.
Hablo, hablas, habla,
hablamos, hablan.
That works.
Matt?
- Matt?
- Yeah?
Did you eat
the last of that pudding?
What?
Now you know I like
a little pudding
at the end of the day
to settle my stomach.
- Hi, Julie.
- Hey.
Now hands off
my tapioca, Matthew.
Yes, ma'am.
So you wanna maybe
try and study again...
I think we should have sex.
- ...morning?
Well, I think it's time,
don't you think?
Yeah, me too.
So, um...
Let's get on that.
Good night.
Hi, Matt!
H-hi, Mrs. Coach.
Friday Night Lights 1x17
I think we should have sex
Transcript: Raceman
Synch: Tauri41
..:: www.forom.com ::..
Matt, this is a watershed moment here.
I mean, you're going
into an entirely new realm.
I got a--um, look...
I've got
just a little gift for you.
- I found this in my dad's glove compartment.
- Landry...
I found it, I was--
Get that nasty, raggedy-ass
thing out of here.
Look, come on, come on.
Excuse me one second.
Now look, you got her
at first and inches.
But you still gotta
read the coverage,
okay?
Now, I ain't trying to encourage
sex out of wedlock.
Don't put it on
on Smash.
Okay.
But if you're gonna do it...
you're gonna need
to think about logistics.
You're gonna need a time,
you're gonna need a place.
And you're gonna need
some fresh protection.
Yeah, he is right.
You got some work
to do, son.
All right, this is
6th street, Austin.
Party central.
Eyeballs deep
in beautiful women.
I don't care about
being up to your
eyeballs in women.
I care about
getting to practice.
This is a big deal.
Hey!
How you doin', baby!
Whoo!
Hey darlin'!
Oh, my Lord.
- We're gonna hit that later.
- We're gonna be late, Herc.
- Relax!
- We're gonna be late--
I told you--
We're gonna be late--
Yeah, I am mad at you.
I am very mad at you.
You wanna know why?
'Cause this is a big deal to me.
And to you, it seems like
you don't wanna pay attention.
You don't wanna...
- Herc, you--
- How you doin'?
I need to know everything
about you right now.
Your full name.
What's your favorite color.
Hi, uh, Jason Street.
Nice Job!
Let's go!
Is this your
first time here?
Actually, I don't really
have time for a conversation.
So if you could just
sign me in, that'd be great.
It's not me asking.
It's a question
on the form.
Jason Street.
There's your welcome packet.
And your room key.
There is your jersey.
Favorite number?
Have fun.
I'm already
having fun, Mo.
I'm gonna get me
some Mo later.
I'll be here
for some mo'.
All right.
Did you really
fall for that?
- Kind of.
- Push!
Where the hell
have you guys been?!
I don't wanna
hear any excuses.
What are you lookin' at?
Nothing, sir.
Quit lookin' around.
Get in the chair!
Yes, sir.
What are you guys
looking at? Let's go!
Let's play some rugby!
Let's go!
Yeah?
Hi, is Billy in?
Billy, some chick's here
to see you.
Sweetie, I'll be in
in a second.
What's up?
I'actually
here about Tim.
Well, he's uh...
He's drinking again.
That's...
Deal or No Deal
ison, Billy!
Yeah.
Uh, that's right on schedule.
Yeah, well, Tim doesn't
see anything wrong with it.
And it just seemed like
he was doing so much better.
So I just thought
that maybe you could...
you can't help him, okay?
Okay.
I've done everything
I could for him.
He chose Walt
in this situation.
He's made his bed,
now he's gotta lie in it.
He's just gonna have
to live with the decision.
All right?
Eric, you're my friend,
right?
I can talk to you
about anything, right?
Yeah, well...
I'll just put it
point blank.
I strayed outside
my marriage.
I mean...
and the problem is,
now she thinks
it's more than it is.
- Uh-uh. Uh-uh.
- Yep.
No, no, I'm saying uh-uh,
I don't wanna know who it is and
I don't wanna know anything about it.
I mean, we had
a wonderful time.
She's a wild cat,
you know what I mean?
But it's just--I can't...
- I mean she--
- Hush down.
I may have said some things
in the heat of passion...
you know, I may have said
I was unhappy in my marriage
in some ways,
but you know how it is.
No, Buddy,
I don't know how it is.
Well, it's not
the only problem.
She also...
she works for me.
I know.
Hey.
Eric, hey,
I'm a weak man.
- You're a stupid man.
- No, I'm a sinner, you know?
I'm just looking
for a little guidance here.
Just a little advice
is all I'm asking.
- You want some advice?
- Yeah, I do.
Number one...
you should tell this woman,
whoever the hell it is,
I don't wanna know...
that under no uncertain terms
that it's over.
Number two...
you need to go home
and take care of your wife
and think about
those kids of yours.
That's all I got to say.
I'll let you
cover the bill.
Oh, I got it, I got it.
Thanks.
Okay, let's see
what we got here.
We got, um...
Endure...
Lasticon,
True Fit...
We can cancel out Mega,
I believe.
I think you should
think about Lasticon.
- Let's just--
- Hold on, wait.
God, I mean, this is
an important decision here.
Matt, you gotta
look at everything.
Didn't you hear
what Smash said?
It's all in the details.
None of this is gonna matter
if I die
of embarrassment first.
You're not gonna die.
Quit being a baby.
Can we just get something
that protects
everyone from everything.
Like--yes, those.
Let's get those.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Okay, fine.
You sure you don't need
like a back-up or something
just in case those don't...
There's like 12 of them
in here.
I know, but...
- Hi.
- Hey.
I saw Matt Saracen
buying condoms today.
Oh.
You know anything
about that?
No.
Really? Nothing?
Well, he was either
buying 'em for you
or he was buying 'em
for somebody else.
I think you better
come talk to me.
Okay.
Are you and Matt Saracen
having sex?
No.
We're thinking about it.
You're thinking about it.
Are you thinking
about pregnancy?
Are you thinking about
sexually transmitted diseases?
Well, I mean, obviously.
That's why
he's buying condoms.
Oh, I see.
So you're just
buying condoms.
And then when
you buy condoms,
that just makes you ready
to make love to somebody.
- Making love?
- Don't do that.
Don't you smirk at me
right now.
I am very upset!
You are not allowed
to have sex!
You're 15 years old!
I just--I don't see
what the big deal...
It's just one body part
going into another.
No, it's not.
It's not just one body part
going into another body part.
And the fact that you think
that it's just
one body part
going into another body part
makes me real
clear on the fact
that you really
are not ready for this.
And I need you
to be able to hear that.
I need you to be able
to hear me say that to you.
I'm listening to you.
Let me tell you
what the big deal is.
what can happen.
What can happen
is that you can be hurt.
And you can be
degraded.
And you can become hard
and you can become cynical.
And I don't want that
to happen to you.
This is something
that's special.
It's something that's meant
for people who are in love.
Okay, I-I understand.
And you can wait.
I want you to be able
to talk to me about it.
Okay.
I mean, we're talking, right?
Matt.
- Hey.
What's up?
What's going on?
So my mom saw you
buying condoms last night.
Are you ser--
Did she--
is she gonna tell your dad?
No, she said
she wasn't going to.
So then we're not
gonna do this.
- We're not gonna have sex.
- No, we are gonna do this.
And I just don't understand
what the whole hysteria is
over losing your virginity.
Uh, well, I got us
Bradley's lake house.
You told Bradley?
So Brad--
does the entire team know now?
No, just--
just Bradley.
And Bradley's Bradley,
so Bradley won't say...
Bradley's good.
You don't need to worry.
He won't say anything.
- Okay.
All right, so here's
the thing, Matty-boy,
180 seconds.
Anything else is failure.
180.
I can do 180.
I can do that.
Hey, look, man, you gotta
use your camera phone.
I don't even
have a phone.
You don't--
I'll let you use mine.
But you gotta
have something...
All right, 7, don't let those rookies
tell you what's going on.
You remember the first time
you drove a car?
Yeah, I crashed
my grandma's car
and now Landry
drives me around.
Good look to you, 7.
Yeah, baby!
Dig! Dig!
That's my boy!
Hey, Riggs,
that's real cute.
You got your pop
cheering you on.
Mr. Riggins,
can I help you?
Hey, Coach.
First team over the ball!
Why don't you give him
more carriage?
He's as good
as that Smash kid.
I tell you what,
we're right in the middle
of practice right now--
if you'd like, you can stand
over there on the sidelines...
I'm serious, why don't you
just give him more carriage?
That's all.
I'm thinking maybe we can
talk about this
at more appropriate time.
I'm in the middle
of practice right now.
You're more than welcome
to stand on the sidelines.
Hey, Coach, Coach.
You're really king of
this castle, aren't you, huh?
You think you're
better than me, is that it?
Over on the sidelines'll
be fine.
All right, let's go!
Get 'em, son!
- Coach.
- Yeah?
Uh, you know that camera
that we got from Boosters?
- Yeah.
- It's missing.
What do you mean
it's missing?
Can't find it.
It's a $3,000 camera.
You better find it.
It's just that...
it's great to feel like a part
of a team again, you know?
I've got
the least experience,
but I'm pretty sure I'm a better
athlete than two of'em.
And that just
leaves this one guy.
- Hello.
- Ta da!
What?
You know, I think
I can take him, you know?
Babe?
Lyla?
Am I boring you?
Are you with me?
No, I just...
my dad just walked in
and started
making out with my mom.
What the hell you doing?
You on a phone?
You're at a party!
Are you at a party?
No, no party.
No, it's a par-tay.
It's not a party.
I thought it was
gonna be all work stuff.
Well--it is.
It's just a couple
of the boys, baby.
It's no big deal, okay?
Buddy, you're crazy.
You are beautiful.
Could you, uh--I spilled
a little.
Will you get me
a paper towel out
from underneath that sink?
Right over there.
What are you doing?
Oh, I...
Hey.
I'm just...
I was designated
to pick the next CD.
And we're kind
of out of options.
- Well, what do you got?
- God, you know...
I don't even recognize
half of these.
What's right there?
That one you just touched?
- I don't know.
- That's a classic.
Gotta go with that.
Loretta Lynn.
Nice.
So,
look, I just wanna say
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I didn't mean to come off...
Oh, no no. Me.
I...I'm sorry.
I was such a bitch.
It was...
a long day.
I'm sure it was.
I'm Jason Street.
Uh, Suzy Quinnlen.
Nice to meet you.
So, uh...
so do you work for the team?
Oh, no, that was,
you know,
just a day job.
I'm trying to get my business
off the ground.
And you know,
every little bit helps.
What's your--
what's your business?
Ink.
I'm a tattoo artist.
Seriously?
Seriously.
That's awesome.
Are these yours?
All right,
there's four of 'em.
- Thanks, man.
- Hey, Coach.
Yeah.
We got a problem.
It's about the camera.
What about the camera?
Uh, one of the assistant
coaches saw
Walt Riggins
going in the AV room
right before the camera
went missing.
Which coach?
Crowley.
Saw Tim Riggins' dad
come out of the AV room.
Yep.
The camera was there.
He goes in the room,
he comes out, it's gone.
What do you want me
to do?
Don't do anything.
I'll take care of it.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
How you doing?
Fine, how are you?
Good, good.
Sorry to bother you at home.
It's not a bother.
What can I do for you?
Well, uh...
We're missing a camera
from the AV department.
Are you going door to door
and asking all the parents about this?
No, I'm not.
Well, I don't know--
Well, I'll tell ya,
we had a coach
over at the school
and he saw you walk out
of the, uh,
the AV room.
So...
He said he doesn't know
where the camera is, Coach.
What else do you need?
All right,
I'm sorry to bother you.
Thank you.
Thank you for your time.
- Hey, Coach!
- Yeah?
You go to Bradley's place
and ask his dad
- if he stole the camera?
- No, I didn't do that.
I'm just curious why
you'd come to mine then.
I didn't know
you were there, I'm sorry.
Granted, he's made
some mistakes, Coach,
but that's
my father in there.
You're right, I apologize.
I'll see you at practice.
Angela, please.
Earl Stackhouse,
he's my buddy.
He needs
a front office girl.
I told him
how great you were.
I'm sorry.
I mean, I know what I said,
but I mean,
in the heat of passion...
Here's hundreds.
Here's $600, $700.
Just walking around money,
okay?
Can we just
make this easy?
I'm sorry.
You're gonna be all right.
So what was it like,
your first time?
You ever
watch the nature channel?
I'm... I'm really--
I'm just kidding.
- Okay?
- Oh, okay.
You don't have to do this.
You know that, right?
Yeah, I know that.
I just--I want to.
Because there will always
be a steady stream
of horny football players
in Dillon, I can guarantee.
No,
I mean...
Matt's different
and I really like him.
And he likes me.
And it's just
the perfect opportunity
for me to control
the whole experience.
You know...
Get the information
and gather the data.
Wow,
that sounds real hot.
For Matt.
Throw the guy a bone while
you're gathering your data.
As soon as if left my hands
I knew it was bad.
I saw him running,
and I was the only one
that had a clean shot at him.
And the only thing
going through my head
was that I just wanted
to kill him.
Just wanted
to obliterate him.
I put my head down
and I went...
right into him.
I guess the next thing was...
I came to
a couple minutes later,
and my parents
were just standing over me.
And my dad
was just holding my mom.
She was screaming
and he was crying.
First time I'd ever
seen my dad cry.
And he just kept on saying,
"Get up, son.
Get up.
Get up, son."
And
I wasn't.
I couldn't.
Couldn't do it.
I think if--
if it was me,
I would spend my whole life
wondering why.
Yeah, there's--
there's a lot of that.
There's a lot of that.
You just get angry,
you know?
And
you start wondering,
you know,
"God, did you do this
to me?"
You know, was it fate?
Was it just some dumb accident?
Was it my fault?
And I prayed and prayed
and prayed,
and the only answer
I ever got was that...
I couldn't walk.
I can't walk.
So...
I'm just ready
to get rid of that, you know?
Get rid of that anger,
you know, and just--
just have some peace.
Hey, after-school special!
Let me show you something!
This is the best jukebox
in town.
Casino!
You got that right.
How about that?
Let's go,
after-school special.
Dance party.
You wanna get out of here?
Yeah.
What's this one?
Oh, that's the Chinese symbol
for "wealth."
It's also the Chinese symbol
for "douche."
Do they have a Chinese symbol
for cripple?
No Chinese symbols,
no barbed wire, and
no naked ladies.
Just hold on there,
shooter,
I'm looking for something,
I just can't find it.
Is this your station?
Yeah, right there.
What's, uh...
what's this one?
Which one?
The red, yellow, and blue...
Oh, that was the wallpaper
in the hallway
at my grandma's house.
- Y'all were close?
- No!
She was a bitch on wheels
and everyone was glad
when she died.
- Nice.
- I think the wallpaper was pretty.
Oh, here it is.
Found it.
It's Sanskrit.
This top one.
It says "peace."
It's perfect.
How you feelin', buddy?
Want me to cook you up
an omelet?
No, I'm good, Dad.
Gonna fix my headlight.
I was gonna take that back,
I swear.
I defended you, Dad.
- Timmy, this is no big deal.
- No, it is.
And you know that.
I want you to leave.
Get out.
Okay, you see
how easy this is, son.
Just watch this.
Nu-uh.
- Hey!
- Hey.
Did Tyra drive you?
Uh, yeah, okay,
so my parents
think I'm at Lois'
and I need to be home
by 11:00.
So we should get
right down to the sex then.
Right?
Good.
Where in the bathroom
is the aspirin?
Look-- look in the--
underneath the sink.
Poured you some wine.
That might help.
Hey,
were you planning something
special for tonight?
Yes, I'm making you
a beautiful dinner.
Just poured you
a glass of wine.
And if you get rid
of that headache,
you may get lucky, darlin'.
What's this?
These yours?
No.
Well, they're sure as hell
not mine,
so what would our 15-year-old
daughter be doing with these?
Yeah.
I think I need to talk to you
for a second, hon.
I...
I saw Matt Saracen
buying condoms
earlier this week.
I'm sorry,
say that again.
You heard what I said.
Oh, I'd love to hear you
say that again.
No, I'm not saying it.
And you were gonna
tell me this when?
I talked to Julie
about it.
- Oh, you did?
- Well, yeah, I did.
And did you also tell her
that if he even
touches a hair on her head
that she's gonna be sent
to a nunnery in Rome,
and I'm gonna rip his head off
right afterwards.
No, but what I told her
is she's too young
and she's not ready.
And then I tried to make
the best case that I could
- against it.
- Oh, that's good.
It might even help if we just
get her her own apartment.
'Cause that's
pretty darn stern.
The reason that I didn't
consult with you
and that I didn't
talk to you about it
is because I felt
that you might
start to freak out.
Which is I think
what you're doing right now.
Where is she right now?
She's at Lois' now, studying.
Wait a second.
Hey, how you doing?
This is Coach Taylor.
Uh, sir--
Yeah.
Hey, this is Coach Taylor.
I was just wondering
if my daughter's over there.
Yes, sir.
Do you know if she was planning
on coming over there?
No, everything's fine.
Okay, thank you.
Why don't you find out
where our daughter is?
Hey.
What are you doing
back here?
You're not supposed to be
in the kitchen.
Can you take a break?
No, no.
It's the dinner rush.
And, you know, my manager's
breathing down my back.
I got a table full of
crazy, middle-aged women.
No, I can't take a break.
I'm sorry.
What?
Forget it.
Tim!
What?
The deer's staring at me.
The deer's...
Well, just, uh...
don't look at it.
I just--I feel like
it's judging me.
Can--can you cover it up
or something?
Yeah.
All riht.
Good, see?
He's sleeping.
See, it's hard not to look at you
'cause you're so good-looking.
Damn?
- Is it really hot in here?
- Um,
yeah, I guess. Do you want me
to open a window?
Yeah, that'd be really great.
Yeah, okay.
Good.
Now it's cool.
Does it just
smell like wet dog?
You know what?
Let's not do this.
N-no, no, no.
No, no, no.
I told you, I really wanted to.
No, no, no, no, no,
you really don't.
And that's okay.
'Cause
we don't have to.
We--we don't?
No.
We can just hang out.
Or eat.
Or I don't know, whatever.
Really?
Yeah.
But don't touch me right now.
That's--
just give me
a minute, please.
Oh, alright.
Yeah.
What time is it?
You know, you and I
have the exact
same amount of experience
being parents.
We've been doing this job
the same number of years
and months and days
as each other.
And the truth of it is
that we just don't
have any control.
You know, for the most part
we're just winging it.
And, you know,
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do
in this situation.
But I'll tell you what,
the most important thing
to me...
is that my daughter be able
to talk to me.
A girl is entitled
to that with her mother.
My mother used to tell me
that I was gonna hell
if a guy ever even touched me.
And you know that didn't work.
I'm sure as hell not gonna
do that to Julie.
And we raised a smart,
responsible...
moral girl.
And I have faith in us.
And I have faith in her.
Now we just gotta
let her go.
I'm sorry
if I hurt you.
One...two...three.
Hup, see...
Wait, no, hey...
No, you're cheating.
I can't win
if I don't cheat.
Oh, those are very good
ethics right there. That's great.
Oh, wait.
You have the ugliest feet
I have ever seen.
Oh, shut up!
I do not.
Because, look,
your second toe
is all bigger
than your first toe.
It's a sign of royalty.
Oh, yeah--
what are you, like,
the royal duchess of Dillon
or something?
Okay, look who's talking,
Mr. I-have-dirt
all-over- my-feet.
Well, I mean...
Oh, my God. We were gonna
have sex tonight
and didn't even
clean the bottoms of your feet?
- I was gonna keep my socks on.
- Ew!
Whatever.
Ready, let's go.
One more time.
Okay.
- Ready?
- All right.
One...two...three.
Hey, Buck.
It's amateur hour here.
It's that punk kid
from the other night.
Yeah.
Come on, fellas.
Let's have some fun.
Yeah!
He fire you?
Thank you.
Mr. Garrity fired you?
Why?
I really don't
want all these questions...
- Did something happen?
- Everything.
I don't wanna
talk about it right now.
Hello?
Hey, Tyra.
Teresa.
Your boy Tim's here
fixing to get his ass kicked.
Okay, I gotta go.
I'll be back.
We're gonna finish this later.
Come on, boy!
What's it gonna be, huh?
- What do you got for me?
- Give him hell, Buck!
Boy wants to do
professional wrestling!
Come on, man.
What's the matter?
Your daddy ain't here
to help you out, huh?
Come on,
you need a hand?
Get the hell
off him, man!
Get the hell off him!
- What are you doing?
- He was the one that kept it going!
He's just a kid, man!
He's a kid.
He's just a kid.
Where's that beer?
Hey, uh...Jules.
- Uh-huh.
- It's...
kind of...
It's kind of...
Oh, my God.
We are so dead.
Um...
Kill the lights.
Do you want me to walk you
to the door or something?
Are you kidding me? My dad's
gonna kill you if he sees you.
Where are my keys?
Julie, I love you.
Uh...what?
I love you.
Um...uh, me too.
I love you too.
I'll...I'll call you later.
Okay.
Bye.
- Uh...
- Are you all right?
Are you all right?
Uh, yeah.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
And I know I'm late.
And I know I should have called
because that's the whole reason
you guys bought me this cell phone
and I'm probably grounded
for the rest of my life,
but I was with Matt.
And then
we fell asleep and...
And--no, no, no, no.
Nothing like that happened.
Not what you're thinking
happened.
Because that didn't happen
and I swear to you guys
that nothing happened.
Good night.
And, uh, yeah.
Uh, but, uh...
thanks for the talk.
Good night.
Seeing the cross
of sacrifice
and the empty tomb.
We rejoice in the awesome
love of our Lord Jesus.
And we take comfort
in the eternal forgiveness
that God gives to all
who believe in Jesus
and walk with him.
Let us go in peace
and serve the Lord.
- Amen.
So I was thinking, you know,
when we're at the, uh,
the, uh, store...
we could get a newspaper,
look through the want ads.
Or, you know, we could
go see a movie.
That might, you know,
make you feel a little better.
Where are we going?
Mother, what are we
doing here?
Mom...
Just stay in the car.
- What...
- Stay in the car, I said!
What are you...
Mama...
Mother.
Hey, Buddy!
Oh, God.
You lyin' son of a bitch!
Lyin' son of a bitch!
You son of a bitch!
You could have at least
let me keep the job!
What were you thinking?
Pam.
What the hell
happened to you?
I, uh...
I brought you something.
You all right?
Why don't you
come inside?
I'll see you in practice.