Grandma's going through one of
her good spells right now.
So that's-- that's good.
But I keep hearing that like they're
trying to bring in this Katrina refugee.
This quarterback
from New Orleans.
We got ourselves
a quarterback, coach.
Welcome aboard, son.
If I get in that car right now,
I'm never coming back. Do you understand?
I get it.
My legs are never
gonna get better!
Football, over.
You and me, we're not
getting married.
Don't say that, Jason.
Lyla, get out!
What is wrong with you?
Jason is in the hospital
and you won't even go and see him.
Why don't you go and see him?
He's never gonna walk again.
Oh, oh--that is nasty.
God help me.
That's disgusting!
Hey, Julie.
You finally came
to one of our parties.
Yeah.
And if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go see if vomit
comes out of suede.
Hey, good luck.
Tim Riggins has been gawking
at us all night.
I don't think he's--
I always suspected
he was into me.
Oh...
Word on the street
is he totally dumped Tyra.
What's up, man?
What up, Voodoo?
Voodoo!
Have you Googled that guy?
What?
He won State last year
in Louisiana.
Broke like five school records.
You're history, Saracen.
But you and your girlfriend
have a nice night.
He's a nice guy.
Yeah, he's the best.
Hey, who changed my tune?
Hey, Doo-Doo.
What the hell you think
you're doing, man?
Seriously, son.
You gotta climb
some trees, brother.
Touch something.
You ever touch me again...
I'll break your fingers.
Friday Night Lights
104 - Who's Your Daddy
All right, let's go!
Let's do it, let's do it!
Now, everybody knows
that the Dillon Panthers
and the Arnett Mead Tigers have
been rivals for a long time.
So we are looking forward
to another great football game.
And to make it
even more interesting,
we've got a little
wager going here.
Winner takes all.
Isn't that right, Mayor?
"All" being Sally here.
Now, Sally is mine.
My prize heifer.
Um, honey, when are you
gonna be able to get home on Friday,
- what time?
- Friday?
We've got a scrimmage,
so I don't know.
It'll end when it ends.
I'll be in the car.
Hey!
What?
What did I do now?
Honey, Friday is her dance recital.
You know that.
Damn. I--I know.
And you know
they plan those things
on bye weeks just so
maybe somebody'll show up.
I understand that.
- I just messed up the dates a bit.
- All right, I love you. Bye.
- Tell Julie--
- I'll tell her.
I don't want her mad at me.
One, two, three.
There you go.
Hey, when you're done
putting the newbie
in that gay wheelchair
let me know.
You are talking
to a gay man, Herc.
I don't mean "gay"
as in "homosexual".
I mean "gay"
as in "retarded."
Maybe I have
a retarded son.
Is he gay?
I'm joking.
Though there can be a genetic
component to homosexuality.
Watch the Discovery Channel, Phil.
When you're done,
the bench press on the floor gym
is busted again.
I need a walkie
to help me fix it.
Welcome to paradise, kid.
Who the hell was that?
Your roommate.
Rivalry.
Tradition.
Bring that knee up to your chest
as far up as it'll...
Okay, Grandma, I'm going to school
to talk to Dad.
Any messages
you want me to give him?
Mmm.
Thank you, honey.
Oh, is he coming over
for dinner tonight?
Um, I'll ask him.
Be sure he's taking
his vitamins.
I will.
You be sure to take
your pills, okay?
- I love you.
- Mm-hmm, I love you too.
- Have a good day.
- All right, sweetie.
Hey, boy, how you doing?
Doing good. I'm doing good.
How you doing?
Well, I'm hanging in here, man.
Pretty hot.
Yeah.
You get to play this week?
I did. I started.
Very good.
Yeah, it was my first start.
We didn't win, but--
Oh, that's all right.
You got to start, though.
I threw pretty well.
I hit my receivers pretty well.
So what about next week?
You gonna start again?
Well, I--
We'll have to see, 'cause...
we got--we got
this new quarterback.
He's supposedly, like,
this big star from Louisiana.
Is that right?
Yeah, but we'll just have to wait
and see what Coach decides. You know, so...
Well, I guess it takes
the pressure off, don't it?
Yeah. Yeah, Dad.
I guess.
Jason, try and take
a bite of food, okay?
I'm really not hungry.
That's all right.
I just want you
to try to use your hands.
Well, I can't...
use my hands, all right?
Yeah, Jason, you can.
You know, you're gonna get
the use of your hands back.
Not everybody around here
can say that,
so you're gonna
have to work at it.
And you're gonna have to try.
I'm really feeling
tired right now,
and I'd like to lay down.
Jason, I know you're tired.
But if you work at it,
you're gonna get to be
able to do almost everything
that you were able to do
before your accident.
Look, I'm not hungry,
and I'm tired,
and I'd just like
to lay down.
He said he's tired.
Why don't you let him rest?
Hey, babe.
Hey.
Listen, I know you'll do it
when you're ready, Jason, but
you do have to eat.
All right?
Let me help you.
Come on.
Come on, babe.
There you go.
Hey, y'all.
This is Corey.
Ah, the girlfriend.
Hi.
It's all right.
You can shake it. I won't bite.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
Hey, Herc, you want
to get out of my food?
Excuse me.
Don't worry.
He ain't gonna be
eating any of it soon.
Yo, Corey,
we're out of here.
Later on, Sparky.
I've gotta get out of this room.
One, two, three, four.
One, track, two.
Around.
Sharp. Eight.
And big. Hit, hit, hit!
Big, big again. Bigger.
Boom! And hit, hit, hit.
In, out, in,out.
Hit.
Good. Good job, y'all.
Let's go.
Bring it in, get in here.
Come on, let's hustle up now.
I gotta tell y'all something.
I'm pissed at these boys
from Arnett Mead.
I know you're pissed, too,
but let's get one thing
straight right now.
This ends here.
There's not gonna be any retaliation.
There's gonna be no getting back.
Rivalry week ends now.
Tell you what we are gonna do.
We're gonna take this energy we have,
and we're gonna take this anger that we have
and we are gonna use it to kick their ass
where it counts... on the field.
- Is that understood?
- Yes, sir.
- Who are we?
- Dillon Panthers!
All right, let's have
a good practice now.
Hey, where's Voodoo?
I don't know, Saracen.
He's probably jerking around
in front of a full-length
mirror right now.
Get off the ball.
Get your heads in the game, boys,
Get your heads in the game!
Beware. Watch 'em coming in.
29!
Hut!
Get up there!
Hey.
Let's go.
Bring it in, bring it in.
H ey.
Practice starts at 4:00.
I want you here at 4:00.
You hear me?
Hey!
You hear what I said?
I hate him.
Hate him.
All right,
let's huddle up, guys.
Bring it in.
All right, let's go, baby.
Get off the ball now.
Let's go.
Set! Red eight!
Red eight!
Hut!
Pretty good.
There it is.
There it is, it worked.
He just looks good every time.
Good play.
Hustle back.
Voodoo, Voodoo.
- Let's go!
- Looked good, Coach.
He's doing something
with that chance
you gave him, isn't he?
I love this boy.
Got my Voodoo working.
Got that Voodoo working.
Ray, what were you thinking all those days...
when you were entraped
inside the Superdome,
not knowing if you were
gonna live or die?
God wasn't gonna let me die.
He told me to war up,
dance with fear.
Now you see,
I knew that the heavens
had opened up
when this young man
landed here in Dillon
after his family had been
through that devastation
with Hurricane Katrina.
I mean, I just
thought to myself,
"This just might be our
new starting quarterback."
Now are you saying that Coach Taylor's
given the nod to Voodoo
to start next Friday
against the Tigers?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
That's not my department.
You'll have to talk to
Coach Taylor about that one.
What are you pounding
around about?
Nothing.
It's just this guy.
- Voodoo?
- Well...
Don't let Voodoo get
into your mind, babe.
I'm not, I just got
a bad feeling about this.
Well, you should play
Matt Saracen.
Wish I could play
Matt Saracen,
- but I can't play Matt Saracen
- Why not?
'cause Matt Saracen's
self-destructing on the field.
Are we having
some kind of party?
Hey, monkey noodle,
come here.
- How you doing?
- What did you say, sweetie?
Some football party?
'Cause Lois told me about this party,
and she's definitely the last person
in the entire state of Texas
to find out about anything.
That sounds just like a vicious rumor to me.
I mean, I can't imagine
we'd be having
any kind of football party.
I mean, 'cause if we were having
some kind of a football party,
that would involve food,
and drink,
and a lot of advance notice.
It's a weekend rivalry.
I didn't know anything about it.
It's a tradition.
Everyone comes over to the coach's house.
- When is this?
- A couple days.
You mean, like,
Thursday couple days?
All right, for how many
people, sweetie?
Just the team.
- Just the team.
Well, I mean, it'll be the team,
and it'll probably be
a few others.
- How many people?
- I'll help. It'll be fine.
It's gonna be a lot of fun.
- Grandma?
- Hmm?
Did you forget to take
your pills yesterday?
No, I took 'em.
Well, then how come they're sitting
right here where I left 'em?
'Cause you're mistaken.
I took 'em just like I always do.
You might've made a mistake.
Ok.
Well, how about, um--
Would you mind maybe today
taking 'em while I'm standing here?
Matthew, give me those pills.
Give me that juice.
Don't take your eyes off my face.
Now watch.
Pills.
Juice.
Ok.
- Now you go to school.
- Yes, ma'am.
Hey, hey, I saw that
game tape of yours again,
and I know what your problem
is--it's your feet.
Oh, yeah?
What's wrong with my feet?
They're slow.
Slower than molasses.
Need to move 'em faster.
- All right.
- Let me see you.
I'll work on that.
Hey, we need to talk.
I've been having these feelings.
Like, a flood of feelings.
Me too.
For Jason, Tim.
What happened with us
came from all these
feelings about Jason
and what he's going through.
I know it doesn't make a lot of sense,
but do you understand?
Yeah.
What I'm saying is,
I don't feel aything for you, okay?
That wasn't even me that night.
That was...
I don't even know who that was.
But it will never happen again.
No one can ever know about it,
and it meant nothing.
Do you understand me, Tim?
Yeah.
I hate myself for the other night.
I just hope I don't go
straight to hell.
I really do.
Heads up.
Let's go, linemen!
Beware, watch 'em coming in.
- Get off the ball, linemen.
- Let's go, fire off.
Saracen, concentrate.
Get your heads in the game!
Hut!
For God's sakes, Matt!
Whoa, whoa!
Show me your right hand.
Show me your left hand.
Well, that's a relief, he knows
his right from his left.
Brush with your right,
wipe with your left.
Listen to me.
90% of this game
is between the ears, son.
Mental errors are unacceptable.
You got that?
Play smart.
Mom says you're supposed to give me
a head count for the party.
- Oh, hey, babe.
- Hey, Reyes, get your head out of your ass
while you're at it.
Nice, Dad.
That was very elegant.
Head count?
Hut!
There you go, there you go!
You almost look like
you know what you're doing.
Fifty-ish.
Is that more like 50
or more like 100?
60, say 60.
- All right.
- Love you, Daddy.
- I love you, too, baby.
You have a good day.
Hey, hey!
- Sixty-ish.
- Right.
Yeah, sixty-ish.
That's good.
Play!
Son, you're a mess out there.
Yes, sir.
You need to get
more focused, son.
Yes, sir.
Now I know what's distracting you.
- You do?
- Yes, I do.
And I'm gonna
tell you something.
You forget about Voodoo.
You understand me?
This is within your reach.
But not if you don't
attack the opportunity.
I mean, attack the opportunity
every day, every practice.
Yeah.
You got a girlfriend?
Uh, no, sir.
Do you have someone
you're interested in?
- Uh...sort of.
- Sort of?
Well, forget about sort of.
You know what?
Take her out.
You understand me?
- Sir?
- Movies, dinner.
Get her in the backseat
of your car.
I don't care.
Whatever.
But I'm telling you, you need
to get loose out there.
You're wound up tighter
than a rubber band, son.
Yes, sir.
Good.
So tomorrow, you come to practice
loose and focused.
- Loose and focused.
- Yes, sir.
Get out of here.
Y-yes, sir, sorry.
Thanks, Coach.
You're welcome.
Hey, Grandma.
Grandma?
Oh, hey, Mrs. Johnson.
I'm really sorry to bother you.
Have you seen my grandmother?
No.
Matt, is everything okay?
Uh, yeah, I'm sure
everything's fine.
Thanks.
I'm really sorry.
- I'm sorry I woke you.
- Well, let me know.
I will.
How many do you want, like, seven?
I don't know.
I think I've got enough,
sweetie, of the ribs.
All right, let's go.
Come on, come on.
- Hey, how are you?
- Hey, Mrs. Taylor.
Got a big pile
for you here today.
Oh, honey, did we get onions?
I don't know, that was
on your part of the list.
Well, I can't remember
if I got 'em.
Can you see 'em?
Are they over there?
- Just will you please--
- I'm just gonna go get some more.
Will you please?
Thank you. I appreciate that.
You're welcome.
Put the gum in there, too.
Now, if it's all right
with you...
- Hey!
Looks like rivalry week team
dinner at the coach's house.
- That's right.
- Wow.
Anything I can bring?
Oh, no, I think
I've got it under control.
Thank you, sweetie.
Well, we'll see you there.
Okay. Oh, are y'all coming?
Are the parents coming?
- Oh, we wouldn't miss it.
- Oh, great.
- Go Panthers!
- Okay, see you then.
- Bye!
Wh--what happened?
What happened?
- Matt Saracen?
- Yeah.
Looks like she wandered
into a neighbor's house
around the block.
They came home
and found her taking a bath.
- She's fine?
- Fine. She's all right.
Grandma, are you all right?
Matt.
I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Let's go in.
Don't let anybody see me.
Okay.
It's all right, you're home now.
You're home.
It's okay.
Let's go inside.
Well, they said it's dementia.
But she's okay now.
Well, yeah, I guess.
Good.
Look, son, you're just gonna
have to hold down the fort.
I've got my hands full here, Matt.
Yeah, well, I'm fine.
She's--
She's fine.
She's--she's just Grandma,
you know?
Man, I shouldn't be around here
too much longer anyway.
I just re-injured myself.
Here for a little tune up.
Another couple weeks,
I should be getting out of here.
You, you're here for quite some time.
I hope you get better real soon.
Lord have mercy.
Where have you been
all my life?
Hey.
Tyra.
Um...
Look...
I know we were never
close buddies.
And I can only imagine
the load of fake crap
that you've had to put up
with from people
you hardly even know,
and I am so not doing that.
I just, um...I came by to tell you how sorry
I am that Tim hasn't been in to see you.
He wants to.
Although, you know,
we won't admit it.
But he just can't do it.
Yeah, why is that?
He's scared.
Oh, he's scared?
Yeah, well, that's Tim for you.
It sure is.
- Well...
Thanks for coming.
Yeah, yeah.
And you tell Tim whenever
he's ready he can come on by.
Jason...
I'm really sorry.
No, I mean...
Something like this shouldn't happen
to a good person like you.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Who in the hell was that?
That's Tyra.
Hey! Sparky.
Come on, line, get off the ball.
Give him some protection.
Let's go.
All right,
86 change.
Blue 25! Blue 25!!
Hut!
There it is. Good run.
Huddle up, come on.
Let's go!
Huddle up. Geti it up,
Get it up.
Let's go!
Let's go.
Hey, y'all, how are you?
Come on in. Good to see you.
Come on in. Welcome, welcome.
Hey, how are you? Oh.
Hey!
Girls, I--
It is so good to see you again.
You too.
Great to see you there.
Honey, go to the market.
Buy all the steaks.
Buy all the ribs.
Buy--buy all the barbecue sauce.
Buy it all.
Sweetie, go now.
Go now.
Honey, can you please help me
put some ice in this cooler?
Yeah, just a second.
Oh, good.
Honey, where's the ice?
The ice?
The ice I was supposed to pick up?
The ice that you forgot to get.
Get my wallet.
I know, I know.
Buy the ice.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, honey.
You know what? I gotta go smoke
some more meat.
- Hey, I got cranberry juice and caramel apples.
- Oh, good. Fantastic.
Excuse me, sorry.
Hey, Julie. How's it going?
Hey, um, it's great.
Really, really great.
Okay.
I mean, this Tatom kid can bust
the season wide open for us,
because, I mean, he's got great vision.
He's got great feet.
He runs like a running back.
And he can throw the football.
Well, has Coach decided
who's gonna start next week?
I don't know.
There he is, right there.
We'll just ask the man.
- Coach.
- Hey.
Who are you gonna start next week?
Who am I gonna start?
Tell you what, gentlemen.
I'm thinking about revolutionizing
the whole offense.
What I'm gonna do is
I'm gonna get rid of the quarterback,
and I'm gonna have four running backs,
do a hell of a lot of reverses.
That's what we're gonna do.
What are you doing
down there?
Cleaning up some beer.
When you get done, would you help me
try to host up here?
Well, no, actually I think I'm gonna
stay down here for a little while.
That man's got a fine jaw line.
Yes, he does.
Hey, listen, I got the address
in Arnett Mead.
The QB's car is a red '02 Mustang.
We going tonight.
- Where'd you get it?
- I got my ways.
- Well, I'm sorry you're upset.
- Well, yeah, I'm upset.
Well, you know what?
I should've given you more notice, all right?
But I was a little bit busy.
I know, I know.
Your job is really stressful.
You know what, honey?
I'm doing it, all right?
I threw the party for over 100 people
in two days' time.
I did it with no help.
And I'm cleaning up
after your football stars,
who by the way happen to be pigs.
I'm doing it, but I'm not
gonna pretend to like it.
Not right now.
Not down here.
When I go back up there,
I'll give you a big smile.
All right, just like I know you need.
But down here, I am pissed.
And I am going to stay down here
until I can get back up there
and give you your smile. All right?
When you're done down here,
it would be really great
if you'd come up and help me host.
Hey, Coach.
I know this is kind of not done,
but I was wondering if maybe,
off the record,
you could maybe tell me
who you're thinking about
on the game on Friday,
starting at quarterback--
Seriously, you know who I'm gonna start?
I'm gonna start who I have to start.
If you want it to be you,
you're gonna have to show me a lot more
than what you've been showing me on the field
this week, all right?
Hey, you need to be take
a deep breath and calm down
before you go out there and you say something
that you're not gonna be able to take back.
Something like what it's really like
to be the wife of the Panthers coach?
- Like sometimes I hate it? Like right now?
- Hey, let me tell you something.
This is my job.
This is what I do.
It's a job--
Oh, my--
What the hell was that?
Hey, QB baby, you coming?
I--I don't think so.
Oh, come on.
Later, Bambi!
Saracen, let's go.
You're coming.
Come on, get in the car.
All right.
Nice.
Oh, yeah.
Last piece of the puzzle,
gentlemen.
Let's go.
All right he's right there. Come on.
Come on now, let's do this, baby, come on.
All right, let's go.
Wait up, wait up, wait up.
Let's go, man!
Come on, let's go!
QB, get in!
Saracen!
Saracen, come on!
Saracen, Saracen, now!
Dad, get out here!
Saracen!
Saracen, get in the car!
get in the car!
Go, go, go!
Take this course
and you'll be just fine.
Great job. Thank you.
Hopefully I won't be
seeing you again soon.
- I'll see you in the halls.
- Okay.
Hey, I'm next.
What are you doing here?
It's very uncomfortable
sitting out there.
I'm sorry that you're mad at me.
Hmm.
I don't--
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure that
that counts as an apology.
"I'm sorry
that you're mad at me."
I'm not sure that
that's actually officially--
- You see what I'm saying?
- All right, come on.
Listen, you know what I got
going on out there.
I've got a very stressful job.
You know, everybody's got
a stressful job.
All right, yeah, but--
Oh, you don't think
I have a stressful job?
No, I'm not saying that.
I'm just saying--
- You know what?
- I just am here to apologize
- You know what I would love?
- For the party--
I would love for you to try to talk
to a bunch of confused young kids
who are all hopped up
on hormones and anxiety and stress.
Not just, you know,
bark at 'em,
or tell 'em where they need to carry the ball
for the next 30 seconds,
but just to really sit down
and talk to 'em.
- Okay.
- No, I mean seriously.
You sit down and you do that,
and then you get back to me.
Next!
Watch out. She's a little
pissed off this afternoon.
Where's that beautiful little girlfriend?
You don't know anything
about my girlfriend,
and you don't know
anything about my life. So...
How about we just leave it alone
and you stay out of my face, okay?
Actually, I know
everything about your life.
Let me run down
the next two years for you.
See, you're still in the golden,
"everyone rallies around you" phase.
Yeah, they'll start to get
bored with that
in about six weeks.
And then all the letters and cards
and visits and prayers will
die down dramatically.
Herc, just shut up.
You know, another three months after that,
the girlfriend is gonna tell you all about
how you're different people now.
And how you need to find out
who you are apart.
That'll be the end of her ass.
Then maybe about two months after that,
the lawsuit will be in full swing,
and you will lose people
who mean the world to you.
- Herc, don't--
- So you can pay
for fun things like colostomy bags.
Get out of my face.
And about maybe three, maybe
four months after that...
- Get out of my face.
- Your parents will announce...
Shut up.
- that the stress of all this..
- Shut up!
has driven such a wedge between them
- that they've decided
- Herc, I'm warning you.
- to go ahead and get a divorce because--
- Will you shut the hell up?!
Good...
I knew you had some fight in you.
When I say there will be
no retaliation,
I want you to remember
how you feel right now.
That's ten.
Now, is there anybody
that wants to tell me
who went on this
little raid last night?
We can end this all
right here and right now.
Anybody want to 'fess up?
All right, let's run ten more.
- Let's run ten more!
- Let's go!
Whoo, it's hot.
Get up there!
Well, look who it is.
Mr. Alamo Freeze himself.
That's a real cute hat
you have on there.
Who was with you?
Uh...no one.
Heh. No one?
There was no one else.
I, uh...
I had the bat.
And the crow bar.
I--I even drove the car
that I jumped into.
Any of y'all want a Swizzler?
This is what it's gonna
be like on the field.
Hey, Coach, can we go
over some special teams sets?
Mac, it's gonna have to wait.
I've gotta get to my daughter's dance recital,
or Tami's gonna have me neutered.
All right.
Coach Taylor.
Coach...it's Saracen.
I'm at the hospital.
Thank you, sir.
I wouldn't get too excited.
You and I are going
to a dance recital.
You want to tell me what happened?
Some of the Tigers players
wanted to know
who trashed the QB's car.
Why would they think that
you'd know about that?
Because I was there.
Did you name names?
No, sir.
And with all due respect, sir,
I still won't.
Look, I'm sorry I put you
on the spot the other night
asking you about
who you're gonna start.
Just seems like the whole
town wants you
to make Tatom QB1.
Even feels like my dad expects that.
Let me tell you something.
Your dad's not able to see what I see.
You're a different kid
than you were two weeks ago.
- I am?
- You are.
You may have been
happy sitting on the bench
letting Jason take the pressure.
I don't know.
I don't need to know.
But I'll tell you what.
I'm a firm believer
in you can do anything
you put your mind to.
And yourself, you,
I believe you can do anything
you put your mind to.
- You really believe that, sir?
- I do.
Thanks for coming to get me.
You're welcome.
Excuse me.
Could you scoot down one, please?
Hey.
Hi, Matt, how are you?
What happened?
Are you all right, Matt?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Julie hasn't gone on yet.
Okay.
Do you wanna get with me
You'll forget all the rest
'Cause ain't no girl out like me
Has got what I got
I'm trying to get through
I'll show you what to do
Boy, I'll make you so, so, so addicted
What I got
I got that something
that you want
What I got
I got that something
that you dream about
I was wrong.
All right?
Well, of course you were wrong.
I mean, you gave me
no advance warning.
- You know, and you just assumed--
- No, not about that.
Listen, just what I'm saying is...
I know how hard it is
what you do.
I know it's not easy
talking to those kids.
I know it's difficult.
And I know my job has put you
through a hell of a lot.
I understand that.
I just wanted to make sure
you knew that I'm...
thankful for everything
that you do.
And I know you do a hell of a lot.
Thank you.
Friends?
Mmm. Hey.
Oh, wow.
What happened?
Oh, yeah, I just got beat up a little bit.
Just a little.
But you were really--
Or that was--
I really liked it.
- Thanks.
- The music, too.
The music was really cool.
I don't know why, but for some reason
it kind of--
it kind of reminded me
of this painter that I really like.
Uh-huh, which painter would that be?
Uh, this guy, um... Jackson Pollock.
Yeah.
I've heard of him before.
You ever seen any
of his stuff?
Some of it, but I don't
really see the connection.
You don't?
Not really.
Yeah.
I gue--I guess it is
kind of stretch, huh?
Maybe a little bit.
What?
- What, what?
- What?
I think I told that kid
to get our daughter
in the backseat of a car.
Mama, Daddy.
Aah!
You were amazing.
Come here, come here, come here.
Thank you, Mom.
I can't believe it.
I love you very much. Very much.
- Mm-hmm.
- Good job. I love you.
Good job, good job.
What are you doing here?
Lyla...
My father is right downstairs.
I know.
Lyla...
I can't...
I can't stop thinking
about you, Lyla.
I can't.
No.
This is Slamming Sammy Mead
signing off on the worst kind
of Friday in Dillon, Texas,
and that's a Friday without a game.
Well, next Friday night,
I don't need to tell you, is the biggie.
And I'm not the only one saying
it could be the biggest
game of the season.
The moment where this team
either gets past the loss of Jason Street
and moves forward,
or we watch the whole season
crumble right before our eyes.
Now, I gotta believe we'll win
because this town wants
that win so bad.
And didn't Daddy tell us,
"Winning goes to the one
who wants it most?"
www.forom.com
Capture: Raceman
Sync: Tauri41