Son, you all right?
- God, contraction! Go to the hospital.
- You're seven months pregnant...
She're going to need
to go on bed rest
- until the baby's full-term.
- I don't exactly have insurance.
I'll figure out something.
Got an opportunity
that could make you rich.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
I thought he was the one.
I know, sweetie.
I'm sorry, babe.
Do your thing, Skeeter.
That's pretty great.
Texas forever.
I think either one of them
says college interview.
This one still has a tag on it,
brand-new.
Honey, you've got
to put your toiletries
- into the plastic travel bag.
- These are ugly. I'm not bringing them.
- Have you seen my bright blue shirt?
- Gracie doesn't have any pants.
It's in with the dry cleaning.
Let me get it.
Do you know
where Gracie's pants are?
- Do you know where they are?
- Hi, sweet angel.
They're in the bottom drawer.
Help your daddy find your pants.
The bottom drawer.
None of my outfits are gonna work
unless I have that shirt.
Getting it right now.
It's...
- They're not in the bottom drawer!
- Check the dryer. We can't miss this...
Come on, bring your spaceman.
I know, we got to get your pants on.
Mom, every outfit you packed
I look like a realtor in.
Hey, y'all need to pack up
and let's get going.
- Give 'em hell up there, understood?
- See? You found the pants. Great.
- I know...
- Alright.
Time to go, you were five minutes late
five minutes ago.
- Bye.
- You'll be great for your daddy.
Oh, shoot, I got to grab
my briefcase. One sec...
And not that anybody cares,
but we have the league's two
last-place teams facing off this friday.
That's the East Dillon Lions
versus the Campo Park Timberwolves.
Now folks, some of you * this game
the toilet bowl and I cannot disagree,
but I tell you what,
if you're coach Taylor,
you've got to see this game
as a singular opportunity
to get a "w" on the books this season.
Hey, ma?
- Do I have a follow-up with the doctor?
- He said he didn't need to see you
unless it's still hurting
in a couple of weeks.
It's doing good? You've been going
to practice and everything.
Yeah.
No, I'm good.
I've been driving
by this property...
Yeah.
It doesn't have a price on there,
and I was...
A steal.
$85,000.
$75,000 if you could pay
half the purchasing price upfront.
Might that be an option?
Hey, yeah, I know
that we hang out all the time...
Exactly.
So why we got to call it a date?
Because there's a very distinct
difference in just hanging out
and an actual date.
I would be wearing
a nice button-up shirt
and you would probably
be wearing, like, a nice skirt
or something like that.
It would be nighttime.
When you say a nice shirt, though,
you don't mean the one
with the periodic table?
I have other really nice shirts.
- I have a bunch of really nice shirts.
- Yeah...
- I have Wednesday night off.
- Perfect.
- Wednesday night?
- I love wednesdays.
That's great.
Good night.
- It's cool.
- Okay.
Full-pad Monday.
Everyone ought to be happy.
You know what, it doesn't matter
whether you win or lose,
it's how you play the game...
Who's heard that before?
Well, that doesn't apply
to this team anymore. Listen to me.
Individually, we ought to be damn proud
of where we come from
and where we are right now.
Collectively, I think we've got
a hell of a football team here.
But we're not scrappers anymore,
we're Lions.
And this is our time.
This is your time.
We got a week
for this game coming up.
I want you to know
I'm proud to take the field with you.
Let's practice.
What's going on?
4x08: TOILET BOWL
Subtitles: Team Lions
With the participation of:
Benj!, Collioure, DarKsh,
GillesSilb, Ju, Nam, Ouazo
So we have
a fabulous contradiction here.
Chaucer is the founder
of modern english poetry,
but he also uses words
like "ass" and "fart."
So what does Chaucer's very deliberate
use of language tell us?
Anyone?
Someone?
Come on, really.
Yes, ma'am?
Do you want to answer?
No, I'm just observing.
Oh, no, that's okay.
It seems you have a thought.
Please, share.
Oh, well, would it have to do
with the context?
You know, who's speaking?
Exactly.
Context. Who's speaking.
Think about the knight's tale.
A story of romantic love...
Let's see you throw it like that
without tipping off the safety
with your shoulders.
All right, looking good.
Looking good!
- Let's blitz.
- Here we go. Hit to hurt, gentlemen.
Down the field.
That's it, that's it...
Fours, come here.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
You sure?
All right, let's go.
Grab the ball, Luke.
Here we go.
Look what the cat drug in.
Ain't got any need
for a toilet, do you?
No, I don't. I've never heard
such malarkey in my life. Hey, Eric.
- Good to see you.
- You too.
Joe, keep the elbow up.
"Toilet bowl", god help us.
I just want to tell you that I...
I used to be something
for the Dillon Panthers.
And I want to be that way here.
I can help you.
I'm gonna do that,
I just want to let you know that.
All right.
Keep your hands...
No, no, put it back.
Look, look.
We're gonna run a post-route
with the sunflower seeds. Go.
Are you seriously teaching them
to throw food?
You can't teach that.
Great job.
- What's wrong with you?
- That's talent.
Look at all you boys. I haven't seen you
in such a long time. You've grown!
Darius, did anybody tell you
you look more and more
- like your daddy?
- Yes, ma'am.
I bet they do.
You know, I tell you what,
I'm cooking dinner next week,
and I want you to be there.
Me?
Oh, no, I wouldn't want
to impose on...
No, you're not imposing.
I'm gonna cook for us,
and I expect you to be there, okay?
Final answer.
You boys be good now.
Listen to what she tells you to do,
- okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
I'll see you.
Come on, baby.
Keep those.
Let 'em have the pancakes.
- Can I get the pancakes, please?
- No, you can't.
Stop. You hush.
Honestly, before you, I don't think we
got any applications from your district.
Well, you know, I think once y'all came
down to the fair, it just put a face
to the school and let the kids realize
it's not so far away,
and it's a real opportunity for 'em.
- I'm just so glad you came up to B.C.
- We are too.
Julie, how do you like it so far?
- It looks exactly like the brochure.
- Beautiful.
Did you get a chance
to sit in on any classes?
- Yeah, an english class.
- Oh, great. How was it?
It was good.
It was great, we had so much fun.
It was professor Paulson's class.
Oh, Vanessa.
Her class is like being
at some fabulous dinner party.
It made me wanna read The Canterbury
Tales, just for fun all over again.
Jules loves to read too,
don't you, honey?
I think she got that from me.
This place is so gorgeous.
You have a big game
coming up this weekend.
What do you got to say about it?
All right...
Some chick named Mindy's
on the phone for you,
she sounds really crazy,
do you want me to just blow her off?
- No. Here.
- Hey, Skeeter.
Hey, Tim, I can't get a hold of Billy,
and the toilet's backed up,
and I need you to get over here.
See, I've had a few too many,
so I can't drive.
Actually, this isn't
about you and your drinking problem.
It's about me and my baby,
and the toilet is toxic.
And I pee every five minutes.
And I don't know where your brother is,
- and I really need you to be here.
- So go in the bathtub.
I won't go in the bathtub!
I am on bed rest.
Get your ass over here!
Can you drive stick?
Remember, the clutch
is your best friend, okay?
I'm not really sure what you mean
when you say that.
Just let...
You unders...
I'm sorry.
I don't have airbags, by the way.
Relax.
Relax...
So why were you in a suit today?
Oh, that's a good question.
Some guys aren't meant
to be in a suit,
and some guys are.
It's green.
The light's green.
Here we go.
Wrench me.
Where is Billy anyways?
Doing some big job down at the rig.
This late?
You didn't know that?
Yeah, I knew that.
He's been working
a lot of nights lately.
Yeah, well, it's getting busy, Min,
- which is a good thing.
- It's not a big deal, right?
- What do you mean?
- Like, if I call him,
and he's all distracted,
and he's tired all the time, and...
if I walk into a room
and he's on the phone,
then he hangs up really quickly?
Mins, what you're saying
is not happening.
He is having an affair, isn't he?
No, he's not.
I don't even want to know.
That's the sad part.
How pathetic am I?
I don't even want to know
if my husband's cheating on me
because I'm a total mess.
Yeah, I mean,
this is an emerging team.
Equals emerging opportunity.
He thinks you want free time.
I understand.
I'm a businessman, I understand that.
This is a new demographic for you...
Football.
- Football.
- American football, yeah.
- No, no, I understood that.
- Buddy.
- American football.
- And I understand you.
Uno momento.
Yeah, what?
This is truely necessary? If they wanna
talk trash about us, the hell with them.
- Let's just get out of here.
- I'm an investor. They understand that.
This is a chance for us
to have a voice.
We can stop the trash talk
that's going on.
This can make a difference.
Do you think we can do this
within another 5 minutes maybe?
All right, just...
keep going.
- Señor?
- Yes.
You say you want english
on a spanish station?
Just for the football games.
What the hell you doing?
- Mornin'.
- Yeah, morning.
You can be honest with me, man.
I'm just...
Are you messing around on Mindy?
No.
'Cause I know
you've been working late
and all that stuff, and I was over there
and she's all worried and stressed out,
- and maybe...
- I'm not cheating on Mindy, all right?
What's all this
late-night stuff then?
Just doing...
a little after-hours work,
that's all.
What kind of after-hours work?
It's the kind of after-hours work
that you can't really
do in the daytime, you get it?
No, Billy, I don't get it. That's why
I'm asking. What do you mean?
- After-hours...
- Okay.
A couple guys came to me
a couple weeks ago,
and they gave me
a little proposition, and...
What kind of proposition?
Once or twice a week,
they come by with a car, and I break
it down to its component parts.
They need it turned around
in a quick time,
- and they pay really well...
- Chop shop.
That's the stupidest...
Yeah, well, it's a plan, Tim.
You got a better plan?
Yeah, Billy.
We had a plan.
I mean, we just had a party here
- and raised buckets of money.
- Buckets of money?
- Where's all that money then?
- You wanna know where it is?
One meeting with a specialist.
That money's gone.
- Any other plans, tell me about 'em.
- Yeah, Billy.
This!
This was our plan, Billy!
Riggins' Rigs.
- Tim, it's a temporary thing.
- Temporary thing...
- It's temporary.
- You have no idea what you're risking.
Nobody's getting hurt here, man.
You keep reminding me,
like, every week that you have a family,
and this mechanic shop
is some dream of yours.
That's the whole reason
I'm doing this, okay?
The whole reason
I'm doing this is for my family.
This is gonna prevent
me from going bankrupt.
It's gonna make sure that Mindy
and my baby are gonna be okay.
All right? And once it's over with,
everything will go back to normal.
I love this school.
I know.
It's your favorite.
Did I ever tell you
this was my first-choice school?
Only, like, a million times.
But no pressure or anything, right?
What do you mean?
Of course, no pressure.
You'd have disowned me
if I didn't apply to this college.
What are you talking about?
You've been staring over my shoulder,
looking at every syllable
that I've put into every application
since I started the college process.
Wait a minute.
You decided where you wanted to apply.
I have been trying to help you
in that process.
But, honey, it's up to you
what school you go to.
It's not up to me.
All I'm trying to do is...
Is support you as you're making
that decision, that's all.
You get me?
You sure about that?
I can't hit that note.
I'm sorry.
- Is something the matter today?
- No, I just couldn't hit that note...
- He got stood up.
- I did not get stood up, Jimmy!
Actually, the date was rescheduled
because of conflicts.
And that might be
a good thing, because...
thursday is more of,
like, a sexual night anyways.
So we're just gonna go through
the whole psychoanalytic breakdown?
No, I'm saying, by 7:00 P.M.
on thursday, your brain
has basically clicked in
that it's pretty much the weekend,
but wednesday's closer to monday,
and no one's getting
busy on monday, but...
Get busy?
Every now and then,
people want to get busy.
Ms. Howard,
can I help you out in there?
Oh, no, no, no, you stay put.
I know you've been working hard.
- You need help with that?
- Oh, no, baby, I got it.
So, Jess, I must say
bless your heart for joining us
'cause I ain't never seen this boy
wear anything but a t-shirt.
How you been?
Well, you know, I can't complain.
Well, I lost my job down at the hotel,
but that was because it was closing
and whatnot, but, you know,
I'm keeping myself really busy, so...
I did some part-time work
for this...
cleaning company, and, you know,
that just really didn't pan out.
I think it was just because of doing
the night school thing down at Tech.
- You know, things start changing...
- These mashed potatoes are delicious.
Yeah, I know, baby.
- So I'm planning, and...
- That's good.
Yeah. My aunt said
to tell you hello.
She's working down at this...
for this new company...
You know what, honey?
Do you know how amazing you are?
I mean, do you know
how amazing you are?
'Cause, when you were a little girl,
I mean, this light would
just shine through you.
And... now look at you.
You've become
a beautiful young woman.
- Thank you.
- Vincent, isn't she beautiful?
I mean, look at her.
Isn't she beautiful?
- Stop it.
- She's gorgeous.
Coach, you know you doomed,
unless you can come up
with some kind of passing game.
Hey, why don't you let
coach worry about his game?
Y'all need to worry about buying
some of this radio airtime.
Buddy called me the other day.
That man is on a mission.
The roto-rooter talk's not
exactly morale-boosting, is it?
Who are you telling? I bought
60 seconds, I'm a damn preacher.
Hey, sure hope you make it
worth my while, come friday.
We'll do our best.
Hey, this is pretty good brisket here.
Thank you.
Now I can die happy.
He's warming up to me.
Great.
The internet's not working.
I'm sorry, honey.
Want to call downstairs?
You all right, honey?
I know I should be excited
about this trip, and...
I know that we've been planning it
for a really long time, and it's...
Everything's just...
- Just happening so fast.
- I know.
I know it seems like it.
I know I'm letting you down.
No, ma'am.
Don't go there.
How could you be letting me down?
I feel like such a stupid mess.
Like, hi, here I am.
I got dumped, and I'm hanging out at all
these universities where I don't belong.
Of course you do.
You belong anywhere you want.
I don't know. It's like,
all these interviews, it's like...
I'm expected to recite
all these factoids about myself
and tell 'em how perfect I am
and why I'd be
a good student, and it's just...
It just seems fake.
Well, I'll tell you what.
The only thing you need to do
in all these interviews is go in
and just be you.
Just, you know,
look at this as an opportunity.
This is an opportunity
for your future.
It's exciting.
I'm gonna go take a shower.
Yo.
What's up, man?
- What up, C?
- Chillin'.
Another day.
I know you hungry.
Go ahead and eat something.
What's up?
Getting kind of boring
stealing these cars without you.
I need my road dawg.
I can't, man.
I wish I could, but, you know,
gotta study these plays, you know.
Right, right.
Plays, plays, yo.
Ty and some of his boys are gonna
be down at the park hooping later, man.
You should roll.
We could take 'em.
I mean, you ain't that good, but you
got me on your team, so we solid.
Yeah, man.
Can't do it.
Practice, you know.
Coach is on my butt about it, so...
Coach come first, huh?
All right.
It's not even like that, man. Listen,
look, we gonna be hanging real soon.
I just can't get caught up,
you know, my P.O.?
You know how it is.
Yeah, I know how it is, man.
All right.
Okay, so when you walk in,
you want to have a presence.
- So smile... Are you paying attention?
- Yeah.
Walk tall, come in...
sit.
With your shoulders pulled back, like
there's energy coming out of your chest.
I don't think I'm trying
to be a superhero here.
I just want a job.
Okay, now, get up,
and let's do it from the beginning.
It's my turn.
- Okay. You ready for this?
- I am so ready.
Walk tall.
Walking tall.
That's my resume, sir.
So, Mr. Riggins, I understand
you're applying for a job here.
What kind of situation
are you looking for?
I'm looking for a situation
where I can achieve something,
be proud of it,
and do it, start to finish,
on my own.
You know what I think?
What?
I think you're a strong person,
an honest worker,
and I think
you can grow up to be
whoever you want to be, Tim Riggins.
I'm guessing that's for you.
What are you doing here?
Just came to talk to Tim Riggins.
It's for you.
- How are you doing?
- Fine.
Good.
Fours.
What can I do you for?
I got hurt real bad at the farm.
It's like, when I push off
and when I get hit, it's like someone's
trying to rip my leg off
with a crowbar.
What about the meds
the doc gave you?
It's like three weeks of meds.
I went through 'em in one.
All right.
This is what I need you to do.
Doctor Cooney.
Mental note this, all right?
When you see him,
first thing you got to do,
tell him how great he was at TMU.
Bring up your hip. And then there's
four questions, one-word answers.
No,
no,
yes,
- no. That's it.
- All right.
Great.
Well, the joke is on you, Mr. Kangaroo,
for my sword
was dipped in poison.
Yay, thanks, Landry, for the story.
- Now it's bedtime.
- What? Come on...
Now be careful with those swords.
And start the...
You're trying to scare me.
Aren't you gonna kiss?
Go inside. Start the bath.
Vince is gonna kick your butt.
He's gonna kick who's butt?
What did he say?
Jess likes the punter!
She's gonna kiss him!
Smoochy!
What'd he say about Vince?
I don't...
I don't know.
I think they like...
Yeah.
Either way,
I had a really good time tonight.
I did too.
I'll see you tomorrow at school.
- Thanks for the sword.
- Be careful.
And for the story, that...
Thanks.
All right.
Good night.
Well, I got a toy...
All right, it's a vegetarian place,
and it's around here somewhere.
It's supposed to be great.
I read a review about it.
Can't we just go back
and order room service?
What are you talking about?
This is gonna be fun.
I just want to go back.
Hey, hon, come here, come here,
come here, come here, listen.
I know you're sad
about Matt leaving,
and I am sorry for that.
But we're here, all right?
This is a great opportunity for you.
I just want to make sure
you're seeing the bigger picture.
I don't know
what that big picture is.
It's you, it's your life,
it's your future, it's...
getting into the school
of your dreams.
You mean the school of your dreams.
Stop acting like you're here
because of me, like I've been
masterminding your applications
and all that.
You've always wanted to go
to a great school your whole life.
I am just here to support you.
You get that?
Well, I'm sorry I'm not giving you
the command performance
that you deserve.
You got an opportunity tomorrow. You can
either show up and be your best self,
or you can just blow it off because of
a break-up, you are gonna regret that.
So what do you want me to do?
I want you to pull
it together, girl.
- I'm trying to pull it together, okay?
- Well, try harder!
Try harder?
Yes.
Thanks for your support, mom.
Jules, come...
Jules, come here.
Come here.
We were assigned
a christmas memory last year,
and, after that, I started reading
all of Capote's short stories.
They're really great.
That's impressive.
You know what I think
is really amazing?
Is that he and Harper Lee
were best friends.
That in a little town, two great artists
found each other when they were kids.
I never thought of it that way.
Now, Julie,
is there anything else you wanna say
about yourself, something that...
we wouldn't pick up
from reading your transcript?
When I started high school,
I couldn't wait
to get out of Dillon.
I thought that every book I read
was like a rung on a ladder
that I built to escape this town
that was all about high school football
and nothing else.
And now that I'm actually
getting close to leaving,
I'm starting to appreciate that...
I was shaped by my town,
that I have different viewpoint
than every other person.
I guess what I'm trying to say
is that...
I'm surprised by how happy I am
to be from where I'm from.
Does that make any sense?
Yes, it does.
- Thanks for coming in.
- I appreciate you taking the meeting.
- Absolutely.
- Great.
So anything you want to add
before we're done?
Resume seems pretty up-to-date
and, I mean, the state champ
is on there and stuff.
Impressive, man.
I know I could really come
into this kind of workplace
and have a sense of achievement.
Tim, I think you'd be
a good fit here.
Awesome. Great.
And so we'll be in touch.
You take care.
You too.
So?
Is that you asking me how it went?
I mean, you know,
I'm not pressuring you.
You tell me if you want to tell me.
It went well.
Good.
Actually...
It went great. And I went in there,
and I totally kicked ass.
I'm so proud of you.
But you know what, hon?
You know I'd be proud of you
no matter what, right?
- I know.
- And this whole thing about
the fact
that I applied to this school...
- I know, I know. It's your dream.
- No, honey, honey, that's the thing.
I got my dream.
I went to a good school,
I got the degree I wanted,
I met your dad,
and I had you.
You're my dream, baby.
I got what I wanted.
I got it all.
And now it's your job to dream up
whatever you want,
and I will support you
to the ends of the earth to do that.
Our plane's not till tonight.
We could go to a museum or...
go get a hot fudge sundae
and celebrate.
Could we just...
go home?
Sure we can, sweetie.
You allergic to any medication?
Use alcohol?
You ever try
any over-the-counter medications?
Yes.
They do any good for the pain?
Who's gonna win the BCS?
TMU, sir.
At least your head's
in the right spot.
- Here you go.
- Thank you very much.
Good luck tonight.
They said I came close,
whatever that means.
And they'll of course
keep the resume close by.
So you never know.
There's no accounting for taste.
That's what my mom always says.
I've heard that a few times myself.
So this is it, huh?
This is it.
It's beautiful.
You know what?
I didn't want that job anyways.
See those trees right there?
That little ridge?
That's where the house is gonna go.
And then I want that deck
that goes all the way around.
A wraparound.
Maybe even a little guest house.
You never know.
You see the tree line right there,
I mean, I've walked this property
a few times,
and it goes way, way beyond that...
It's endless.
I wanted to...
I wanted to thank you...
for helping me with...
the process.
So...
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Welcome, folks, and all the fans
of the East Dillon Lions.
We invite you tonight
to the radio debut of Lions football
on 1040 A.M, El Fuego.
Now over to my partner
and your play-by-play man Willie Gault.
Thank you, Buddy Garrity,
and thank you to all you fans
who tuned in to hear a game
that has been given
a very special billing...
The toilet bowl.
- One, two, three!
- Lions!
There's the snap,
he's looking left...
No place to run.
He cuts up the middle.
It's a little late. Makes a move.
Touchdown!
There we go, there we go!
And the Lions draw first blood.
What an impressive first series
that coach Eric Taylor
has designed here
in East Dillon tonight.
I tell you what, Vince Howard
is gunned up, he is yoked up,
and he is playing like he's been playing
quarterback his whole life.
And this touchdown
was brought to you
by El Amigo restaurant.
Vince Howard comes
back out in the spread.
He's got his a back setup
in the slot.
Rolling right to throw back.
Beautiful pass!
He overthrew him. It's incomplete.
Would you look
at the gun on that kid?
Howard has just thrown the ball.
It looks like 60 yards, Willie.
9 seconds left in the half,
fourth down.
Landry! Field goal.
- But it's on the 25 yard line.
- I know where we are. Just go kick.
Go, Landry, go!
Ladies and gentlemen, Landry Clarke
has hit a very long field goal.
East Dillon Lions go into halftime
with a 17 to 7 lead.
You scared the crap out of me.
What's with the monkey suit?
How much money are we talking about?
I don't want you involved in this.
How much?
You'll make more money in two months
than you could in two years.
Two months?
Two months max.
It's 17-7, East Dillon,
and the way the Lions
have been playing tonight,
I hope coach Taylor
can keep things going.
Go on one. Ready?
Howard over center. There's the snap.
He's looking left.
Under pressure, throws the ball.
It's picked off!
What are you doing?
Timberwolves have it.
Going the other way!
The pack on the move.
Touchdown, Timberwolves.
You know what, a good quarterback
has got a short memory.
Cafferty's looking for a place to go.
There's nowhere to run.
And Cafferty gets swarmed
by the Timberwolf team.
Oh, my, fumble! Campo picks it up.
Looks like reservations for six.
Touchdown, Timberwolves!
Another Timberwolf touchdown.
This cannot be.
The Lions are down now 21-17.
I think I'm gonna be sick, Willie.
You all right?
Time out. Time.
- You all right?
- I'm fine.
- You all right till next series?
- Yeah. Let's go. Yes, sir.
And here we go, folks,
60 seconds left in the game,
the Lions * and Coach taylor
out of time-outs.
You know, sometimes, Willie,
there are other forces at work.
Damn it, coach Taylor
has inspired these boys,
he's worked these boys,
and these boys are a team.
Go, go, go!
East Dillon Lions win!
We won! We won a game!
I'll see you later.