I saw Lyla the other day,
and I wish I could just hate her
and walk away from it
and be done with it.
But I love her, you know?
There's no weakness
in forgiveness.
This is my dad.
This is Coach Taylor.
- This is my Dad, Henry Saracen.
- Coach, how you doing?
You're on leave?
Yeah, he's home for two weeks.
Just some pick-me-ups
I been taking.
It's just gonna give me
a little edge.
You're an amazing woman,
and you are a damn good mother.
But God, you are such a loser
when it comes to men.
Get the hell out!
Get out!
You okay?
But how far am I
supposed to go for love?
I'd would give my heart
and soul to him.
But I'm not sure
I'd do time for him.
Well, of course you'd give
your heart and soul
and of course, you love him.
My question to you is--
- All right, that's enough.
- Don't touch that.
We're listening to that.
You wanna listen to this girl
who's runnin' around town
with her loser boyfriend,
robbin' liquor stores--
- that's what you wanna listen to?
- She's robbing for love.
Dad, it's compelling stuff.
Guilty pleasure, babe.
Why can't we listen
to Sammy Meade?
- What's wrong with Sammy Meade?
- Sammy Meade is no good for you.
Dad, Sammy Meade is just
stress in a bottle.
Stress in a bottle, babe.
Stress in a bottle.
You are in control
of your destiny.
The minute
you truly believe that,
- freedom comes with it.
- That's good advice.
You are in control of your destiny.
Right now, y'all are in control
of your destiny.
You remember that.
Last week, we were waiting to
see if Arnett Mead would lose,
and they lost.
We are in control.
Got a big game come Friday.
We get out there this week,
we take care of business
with this one, babies,
- we go to the playoffs.
- Yes, sir!
Hut!
Catch my Sammy Meade
interview this morning?
Aw, heck, Coach,
I didn't.
Girls made me listen to some damn
psychologist on the radio this morning.
Dr. Q?
You listen to Dr. Q?
I live by her.
Here I am pulling double shifts
trying to make ends meet
and put food on the table.
And this is the thanks I get.
You could at least
make up the bed.
Oh, no.
Come over here.
Mama.
Mom, what are you doing?
What you doing here?
You better get in this office.
Mama, look, whatever it is--
I wanna know what kind
of team you're runnin' here.
- What are you doin' to my son?
- Mama, what is--
Wait a second, now I don't know
what's goin' on here, but--
I'll show you what's goin' on here.
This!
And I thought you were
a Christian man, Coach Taylor.
But you messing
with my son's life--
- Mama, he--
- to win football games-- with his life!
- He didn't--
- You be quiet!
I don't wanna hear one word
out of you right now.
These kids, they're stupid.
They think they're invincible.
I see it every day at the clinic.
But Coach Taylor,
you supposed to know better.
Ms. Williams, I can promise you
I didn't know anything about this.
You have anything
to say for yourself?
No, ma'am.
Friday Night Lights - 1x13
Little Girl, I Wanna to Marry You
Transcript: Raceman
Synch: Tauri41
..:: www.forom.com ::..
You would not believe
who came in the dealership today.
- Who?
- Ed Johnston.
- No!
- I'm not kidding ya.
How's his family?
They're fine.
They're all great.
I mean, he drove all the way in
from Dallas to buy a car.
Hope you gave him
a good deal.
Of course I gave him
a good deal, sweetie.
That's what makes
your old man who he is.
I give everybody a good deal.
They got that son Ty.
You remember Ty, Lyla?
- Oh, nice boy.
- Yeah.
Yeah, he's over at SMU.
He's a freshman.
And he's in
the psychology department.
He's doing some kind of
paper on cheerleaders and football
and boys and girls and...
some kinda weird
psychological deal.
But anyway, he wanted to see
if he could
talk to you, Lyla,
since you're a cheerleader and
you know all about this stuff.
So I told him he could
meet with you Thursday at 1:00
to talk to him
at that new Oriental place.
I've heard it's really good.
Why are we even goin'
over to the Rodells'?
We don't have to go
over there.
I don't know, honey. I didn't talk
to her. You talked to her.
Don't lie down, please.
Please get right back up, honey.
Let's go, come on.
I put your ties out.
I put your clothes out for you.
Come on.
I like this one.
What are you gonna
do about Smash?
You tie that.
If I report him,
and I'm obliged to report him,
that kid's never gonna play
high school football again.
His career's over.
Yeah.
And if I don't report him,
which goes against
everything I stand for...
I can't let the kid
play juiced.
So then he's all, like,
"I'm sorry, Tyra. I miss you."
Whatever.
I'm sure there's a certain
throbbing member of his body
- that misses you.
- Exactly!
Oh, stop it--I think you should
give him another chance.
He's very cute.
Come on,
you can't argue that.
Well, he is.
He's very cute, that kid.
Mother, you are
a barrel of bad advice.
All right, ladies.
Here's one.
Buddy Garrity is looking
for a receptionist.
"Administrative Assistant.
50 words per minute.
Salary commensurate
with experience."
Even Mom can't fake
50 words a minute, dumb ass.
How 'bout you stop criticizing
and start helping out a little, Mindy?
Maybe we should stop
discussing this family dynamic
and accept that I pay
half the rent around here.
I don't see you coughing up
any Applebee's money.
Yeah, well, you don't
make the same kind of tips
when you leave
your clothes on.
That's funny.
But you know this guy?
Yeah, like when I was 12.
You goin' to that
Japanese restaurant?
Yeah, I guess.
Why can't he just come
to the school?
Why are you making
such a big deal out of it?
Because it's annoying
is why I'm making such
a big deal out of it.
It's annoying that your dad
sent you on a date
with some college boy,
and it's annoying that just you do
whatever your dad wants
you to whenever he wants you to do it.
Jason, it's not a date.
If you don't want me to go,
I won't.
Just tell me.
No, it's fine.
It's fine.
You can go.
Okay?
Okay.
Hi, Lyla.
I gotta go--I'm being rude.
You wanna say hi?
I'm good.
- Okay, be right back.
- I can wave from here.
Tell 'em I say hello.
I'll be back.
So...
explain to me
how I'm seein' what I'm seein'.
After what she did to you?
I love her.
- You love her.
- Mm-hmm.
That's all the explanation
you need.
That's just--
that's great.
And you know what--
you can get away with anything
when you're Lyla Garrity, it seems.
Hi, Tyra.
Hi, Lyla.
Can I get my seat back?
Oh, no problem.
So...
this receptionist/secretary job
that's available
at your dad's dealership--
how much typing
is required?
I don't know.
I'm--
What about benefits?
I don't know, Tyra.
I'm really not sure you're
what my dad's looking for.
No, but he might be looking
for my mom.
Barbara comes from a long line
of Georgia democrats.
Serious bleeding hearts.
To this day,
they talk about Jimmy Carter
like he was the Second Coming.
Habitat for Humanity
is, like, every third word
out of their mouths.
That's right.
And when the two families
get together,
- oh, baby, can things heat up.
- Lord.
And Luce and I, well,
we just don't know what to do.
I'm--I'm sure that--
that must be, uh--
That must be awkward.
Oh, yes.
- Tami.
- Yes.
You know I'm running
for reelection.
Yes.
We're starting to put together
my campaign team.
I want you to be
part of it.
Wow.
You're a strong, smart,
charismatic lady.
- Thank you.
- And, um, together...
there's no stopping us.
Well, thank you.
I appreciate that.
That is--that is flattering,
and--and I would love to--
to consider it.
Thank you, Mayor Rodell.
Where you been?
Things ain't bad enough,
you got to keep me up
half the night,
wondering where you are?
- Where you going?
- To my room!
I'm goin' to my room.
You better lower
your voice, boy.
Your sisters are sleepin'!
How could you be so stupid?
You better watch your mouth.
How could you go to Coach?
Do you realize what you did?
If he goes to the Athletic Commission,
I'm gone,
I'm off the team forever.
My scholarships--
oh, yeah, all them letters
they been sending me,
they don't mean nothin' now,
they--worthless, gone.
All gone.
You ruined my life, Mama.
No, son, I'm trying
to save it.
You wanna know why
I went to your coach?
- Please tell me.
- 'Cause I didn't want to think
you were dumb enough to do
something so stupid on your own!
This was all I got,
and you took it away.
You know what?
You need to get
out of my house
till you can learn
some respect for your mama!
You gonna kick--
Fine, I'm leaving.
I don't need this.
I made a mistake.
You tell me something
I don't know.
W-haven't you ever
made a mistake?
Yes, Smash,
I've made mistakes.
I've been late for dinner.
I forgot stuff
at the supermarket.
I've made mistakes out in
the field I've come to regret.
Those are mistakes, Smash.
What you did wasn't
any mistake, though, son.
What you did is
you screwed yourself over,
and you screwed
this team over.
You know what you call that?
You call that a stupid,
dumb-ass, cowardly act
is what you call that,
Smash.
You know what--I wanna
know what you're doing,
I wanna know
how long you do it.
I wanna know who else
knows about it.
I wanna know where you got it.
We'll just start right there.
How's that?
Mom, I'm home.
Did you call about the job?
I don't think I can
make it without Bob.
What the hell
are you talkin' about?
I know you don't like him,
but he was payin'
the bills around here.
Did you call about
the job at Garrity Motors?
Yes, I called about the job,
and I can't even get an interview.
They had about a hundred
people call in, so...
Before we watch the game tape,
I got an announcement.
Smash is not gonna be playing
in the game Friday night.
Quiet! Listen up.
It's a personal issue.
Let me tell you somethin'.
I am not asking you
to respect his privacy.
I am telling you
to respect his privacy--
- you understand me?
- Yes, sir.
We're not gonna worry about
the one player
that's not out there.
We're gonna worry about
the 44 that are.
We're gonna take care
of the job at hand.
Gonna win Friday's game
and gonna get to the playoffs.
Are we good with that?
Yes, sir.
We got Brian "Smash" Williams
benched,
not playin'.
Mysterious circumstances.
Yeah, grandma,
I know.
Well, you know what?
It's too bad we don't
have an insider,
somebody that could shed
some light on some of this.
Please, he doesn't
tell me anything.
I just love your daddy.
Coach Taylor is great.
Does he like cherry pie?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait.
Did you see that?
When the quarterback shifts
the running backs into the slots,
he shifts 'em to a spread
formation out of single backs,
and the safeties, they just sit
there--they don't even move.
So that just leaves, like,
this huge, big gap,
basically an ocean.
I mean, I could just--
I could just fire pops and slants
right into there all night.
Matt, why don't you just
let the coach call the plays?
No, no, this is key,
Dad!
This is how we're gonna win
without Smash!
You're gonna see on Friday night.
You'll be there.
You're gonna see.
And you're gonna say,
"Matt, you were right."
Matt, I been trying to figure
out how to tell you, but, uh...
W-what?
My unit called.
They need me to ship out
on Friday before the game.
All right, that's, um--
Th-that's okay.
I'm sorry.
I really wanted to be there.
It's not a big deal, so...
don't worry about it.
Those soldiers over in Iraq,
they might see that game.
They see the Super Bowl,
don't they?
Have you heard that?
They've got cables and all
kinds of stuff over there.
You know, the highest
technology--that's what I hear.
Every single child
in the independent school
district of Dillon
deserves better.
- She is a smart politician.
- Mm-hmm,
smart politician
with an alternative lifestyle.
Shocking!
This town just gets
weirder and weirder.
And why did she choose us to--
to open up to?
Because she realizes
what a forward-thinking
individual I am,
and she felt comfortable.
I'm sure.
It's different.
I did look at her website
today, though.
This education plan she has
is really good.
You know what, though?
With everything that
you got on your plate--
Julie and me and my needs
and demands--
that's an awful lot,
isn't it?
Well, I know you do have
many needs and demands.
I sure do.
But the schools
need a lot of help.
Does she even know that
you voted against her?
Details.
What--
honey, if that
is Buddy Garrity at the door,
I swear to God
I'm going right now
and gettin' out
your new deer rifle.
- You know it's past 11:00?
- I'm sorry, sir.
What you need?
Look, I'm sorry
for what I did.
Am I off the team?
Look, I know I'm not
playing on Friday,
but am I off the team?
Don't I deserve to know?
I should have reported this
as soon as it happened.
I'm risking my job.
Inside this house,
I've got a wife and a daughter.
They depend on me
to provide for them.
Do you understand that?
Yes, sir.
I don't know what
I'm gonna do.
When I do know,
I'll let you know.
Until then,
why don't you do me a favor
and just try and keep
your mouth shut?
Yes, sir.
You got it.
Good night.
I told you go ready
asit's an internal matter.
I'm not gonna
talk about it anymore.
I appreciate
y'all coming out today.
There's some doughnuts
and coffee back there.
Coach, do you mind staying
for one more question?
- Hey, Buddy.
- Hey, Eric.
What the hell's
goin' on?
You know, I cannot
stand you dodgin' me.
And to tell you the truth,
I'm hurt.
As I said,
it's an internal matter.
Yeah, well, I am internal.
If anybody's internal,
I'm internal.
I'm probably the most
internal son of a bitch
you've ever met in your life--
is that not right?
I'm not gonna
talk about it.
Until when?
Until ever, Buddy.
I can't talk about it until ever.
Ever is a long damn time.
Yes, it is.
- Come in!
- Hang on, Matt.
- I can wait.
- Come on in.
- Are you through, Mr. Garrity?
Okay.
All right.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Hello, Matt.
- Mr. Garrity.
- Say hi to your dad.
- I will.
- Thank you so much.
- Have a great game.
- I'm gonna try.
- Yeah.
Have a good day.
Look, I was checking out
the South Pines game tape,
and I found some holes
in their defense
that I think we can take
advantage of,
so I drew up a few plays.
Now, it's really easy.
We don't need to change any assignments.
We just--
if we audible out
to the spread formation,
out of the single backs--
You know what,
I appreciate this, Matt.
- It's good work.
- Thanks.
Let me tell you something.
Why don't you let me do my job,
and you do your job?
Your job right now
is to go out
and get the team ready
to play for you
All right?
How's that?
And I think this will
get them ready.
Especially since
Smash isn't playing...
- I'll take a look at 'em.
- I think this is what's gonna help us out.
Okay, thanks.
- And I really think the first two plays--
- I'll take a look at 'em!
Okay.
Yes, sir.
- Can you do me a favor?
- What's that?
- Turn right here.
- Where at?
Turn right here!
Here, here, turn right.
Whoa, whoa! You mind telling me
where the hell we're going?
I'm just gonna take
a little peek at something.
Well, easy, Unabomber.
What's goin' on?
- All right, slow down.
- Slow down?
Slow down, real slow.
- Stop. Stop, stop, stop, stop.
- What?
Stop.
Look through that window
over there.
Is that Lyla Garrity?
Whew!
Now is that
a family friend or a date?
Knowin' her track record,
- that's a date.
- Shut up about that.
You don't know anything
about her track record.
You've known her
for two months.
Don't you wanna go in there
and pop him one
like you did Riggins?
Yeah, does that look like--like
she's helping him with a paper?
Stalking is not becoming
- of you, I tell you.
- I'm not stalking.
I'm not stalking.
Just taking a little look.
- Just go ahead and go. Please leave.
- It's the same thing, right?
- Bonehead move.
- You want me to go?
Yes, please.
Hi, Lyla!
- Faster. Move faster.
- Hi, Lyla!
Shut up and drive faster.
- Faster, faster!
Hey.
So I need a favor.
And just for the record,
it's not gonna involve any kind
of thank-you sex
or make-up sex.
In fact, it's gonna involve
absolutely no sex whatsoever.
Tyra, um,
believe it or not,
it's not all about sex for me.
Well, your timing
is terrible, Tim.
Yes, sir.
I get that a lot.
I mean, first of all, I just hired
Matt Saracen's dad to be a salesman,
and I don't mind telling you
that that man
could not sell a life preserver
to a drowning man.
And secondly,
I cannot really believe
that you're comin' in here
asking me for a favor
after that nonsense
that happened with my daughter.
Sir, I know you're
a big man in this town,
and I know you don't owe me
or anyone anything,
for that matter, but Tyra--
all she's trying to do
is help her mom out.
And all I'm asking from you
is to consider
giving them a break.
I respect that.
You're a good man.
You tell her to come by
and see me tomorrow afternoon.
There's no guarantees.
I mean, it's just an interview.
Yeah.
And tell me about Smash.
I have no idea what's goin' on
with him right now, sir.
Really?
Absolutely.
No one does.
Well, okay.
You're a good man, Tim.
- I appreciate your candor.
- Thank you, sir.
Noannie, go upstairs.
I need to talk to Mama.
- Good night, Mama.
- Good night, baby.
I disgraced myself,
and I disgraced this family.
God gave me a way
to support this family,
and I threw it away.
I--I can't even look
at my face in the mirror.
Mama,
you just gotta know that
I'm trying
as hard as I can
to make this happen.
And what if Coach
don't let me back on the team?
Then you let God guide you
in another direction.
Mama, you don't understand--
without football,
I know, I know.
Without football,
there's no--
no scholarship,
no--no pros,
no big house for Mama.
I don't need no big house,
especially if I can't
come by it honest.
Oh, I love watching you
play football, Brian.
Oh, you're so beautiful
out there.
But sometimes, baby,
sometimes I just wish
you didn't have
all this expectation on you,
all this pressure.
Sometimes I wish
you could just be a kid.
I love you, Mama.
Oh, I love you, too, baby.
Hey, Jason.
What the heck are you doin'
sittin' out here in the cold, son?
I think, uh, Lyla's
in her study group--
I know where she is.
All right.
So what are you
doin' out here?
Why'd you set Lyla up
on a date with Ty Johnston?
Why?
Yeah, why?
What, you need me
to answer it for you?
'Cause if I was still the quarterback
and wasn't the town cripple,
you wouldn't be setting your
daughter up on dates
- with college boys.
- Now you just hold on there, son.
You just watch
what you're saying.
Ty Johnston happens to be
a friend of our family's.
She went with him
to help him on his paper
he's doing for SMU.
You know what
I'm talking about, sir.
No, Jason,
I'm afraid I don't, son.
You don't want your little girl
to end up with me,
so you're just trying to show her
that there are other choices out there.
Bigger fish in the sea, huh?
Now, son, you know
that everybody
in this family loves you.
We always have,
and we've supported you
ever since you were
a little bitty boy--
Please, please
do not patronize me,
Mr. Garrity.
You sent your daughter
on a date,
and I asked you why.
Now can we please just speak
honestly about it?
You want me to be
honest with you, son?
- Do ya?
- Please.
I love that little girl
in there.
That's my daughter,
and I want her to have
a great life.
And I'm real uncertain
about the future here.
I mean, how is
she gonna get money?
How you gonna get money?
You gonna go to college?
Is she gonna go to college?
Are you gonna have babies?
Can you have babies?
Can you?
Can you have children, Jason?
We haven't quite
answered that yet.
Well, what if you can't?
And what if you can, Jason?
When that little baby's
crying upstairs in the night,
who's gonna go up
and take care of him?
I don't want Lyla
to be a caregiver
her whole life, son.
I know that's a bitter
pill to swallow,
and I'm sorry
I have to say it to you.
And Lyla Garrity,
she loves you.
She'd follow you
into hell.
Are you sure you want
to lead her there?
I mean, that whole family,
the whole Garrity family,
I'm allergic to them.
I mean,
Pam, I don't know
who she thinks she is.
She doesn't even look at me
in the market.
And Lyla, well, I mean,
what a little you-know-what.
Well, Mom,
you need a job.
I know, but I don't know
what circumstances
I would have to be under to
actually work for Buddy Garrity.
How about to avoid eviction?
I'm just thinking.
You don't have to be--
Damn it!
I can't believe this.
What on earth--
Blowout--perfect.
Oh...well, I just think
that is God's way of tellin' us
he does not want us
to go to Buddy's.
Think you got everything, honey?
I think so.
Hey, I put a surprise in there
for when you get over there.
- You'll find it!
- All right.
I hope so.
And don't forget
to watch the game.
- I won't.
- Ask 'em when you get there,
just ask 'em.
I think they will if you just
tell 'em right away.
That's what
you need to do.
I will do that.
It's been great
having you here, honey.
Okay.
I guess this is me.
Mama, you be good.
'Course I'll be good.
Now, you just go
make us proud.
Don't you worry about us.
We're gonna be fine.
Julie, a pleasure.
Nice meeting you.
Have a safe trip back.
Matt.
Keep those damn feet
movin', all right?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
All right.
Take care of yourself.
We're gonna make it fine.
Come here, sweetie.
Come here.
We're gonna be all right.
All right, we know
we're gonna have 8 in a box
with an 11 package, right?
Got motion left here.
We got three deep.
We got Riggins on a linebacker.
Superior athlete--
Riggins should be able to beat him.
He's gotta beat him.
Hey, guys,
give me a second.
Hi, y'all.
How's it goin'?
Sorry to interrupt y'all.
Be one quick second.
Nice seeing you, McGill.
- Why are you interrupting my meeting?
- I'm sorry, honey.
- I apologize.
- I don't appreciate that.
I'm interrupting
your meeting--
Come on, now, I'm busy.
All right, I wanted
to come down now
and I wanted to tell you
that I have decided
that I think I'm gonna
go ahead and, uh,
join Mayor Rodell's campaign.
Well, that's great.
I--it is great.
Honestly, it's great.
It's a great opportunity.
I'm gonna be able
to help our school.
I'm gonna be able to help all
the schools in the commun--
in the whole county.
I'm sure she realizes
how good you are.
I'm sure she realizes, also
that you're the coach's wife.
That'd help out
with the campaign.
Oh, you think--you think
that's why she asked me,
'cause I'm the coach's wife?
- I didn't say that.
- That's exactly what you just said.
I don't like...
politicians.
The other night,
that little reveal
at the dinner and everything--
just hear me out here.
Something like that
gets out in this town,
that's not gonna do
her any good,
and it is not gonna do
anyone any good
that is close to her--
that's what I'm saying.
Wait--so you don't want me to
do this because she's a lesbian?
I'm not sayin' that.
- That's not what I'm sayin'.
- That's exactly what you said.
- I'm bouncing it back to you, sugar.
- What I'm saying is
I'm uncomfortable with it.
Well, you know what?
You're just gonna have to be
uncomfortable with it then.
Well...
It's never
a dull moment with you.
Well, that's why
you married me, sugar.
I guess so--I don't quite
remember why I married you,
but there's never
a dull moment with you.
Oh, I'm so happy
to have your support.
Hope you have a great game tonight.
Thank you.
I don't understand why you're
goin' over and over with that.
You know what, Mother,
I have it.
It's not even touchin' the top.
. Isn't it supposed to--
- It's all yours.
- Go for it.
- Well, I'm just sayin'--
- Well, do it!
- Oh!
At least try this thing--
at least try to get that
with this thing, you know,
because that thing
obviously doesn't work!
Tyra,
you're makin' me so mad!
I'm not cut out for this!
I don't know
how to change a tire,
and I don't wanna
know how.
We can change this tire!
It's not the end of the world!
You know, I just don't know
what's gotten into you!
I mean,
was life so bad with Bob?
He hit you!
- I told you he was workin' on his anger!
- Oh, my God!
This has to end!
I-if not for you,
then for me.
I love you.
More than anything,
My worst fear...
is to become you.
And call me crazy, but
we don't change this tire
right here,
right now, by ourselves...
we're both doomed.
Give you one drink,
you're good to go.
Cheap date.
I gotta tell you,
I went over to, uh,
Garrity's house
the other night
to confront Mr. Garrity
on sending Lyla on a date.
Oh, I'll bet
that went well.
It did.
Because I went over there
specifically
to have him look me in the eye
and tell me that he did not want me
dating his daughter anymore.
What happened?
He did.
He told me, uh,
he wanted his daughter to have a
"good life."
- Quad quote.
I gotta hand it to him,
though.
He went at it.
Direct, honest
and I started thinking about, uh,
how selfish I've been
since the accident, you know?
Always thinking about me.
Never really thinking about
her, and...
how, little by little, over time,
being with me's
gonna define her.
What are you
gonna do?
I don't know.
I think it's a...
maybe time
that I let her go.
Just...let her go.
You know I'm not
Lyla Garrity's biggest fan,
but, uh...
if you're thinking of
leaving Lyla
'cause of Buddy, you listen to me,
Grasshopper.
There is gonna be a million
Buddy Garritys out there
who will try and tell you
that you aren't worth anything.
And you just gotta look him
right in the eye
and flip him the bird.
Just like that?
I'll work on it.
And the Buddy Garritys
of this world,
they're a cancer
to you and me.
This is another tight one, folks.
No one can seem to get
the ball in the end zone,
and there's only nine minutes
left in this contest.
Now if Dillon does not win,
they will not go
to the playoffs.
But the real headline tonight
is Smash Williams
is ridin' the pine,
and nobody's talkin'.
It's a mystery
wrapped in an enigma
hog-tied and shut up tight.
And everybody wants to know why.
Saracen takes the snap,
he hands off to Baxter
off the left side.
Nice little spin move.
He's got some room.
- Oh, and he has dropped.
- Way to go, Jim!
Go, Matthew.
All right, all right,
let's keep it going,
let's keep it going.
Move your sticks!
It's second and a long 6
for the first down.
Looks like the Panthers
got a little momentum
going here, folks.
But let's see if they can finish
without Smash Williams
in the backfield.
Oh, it's another
9 level run.
He's going down
close to the first down.
That is gonna bring up 3rd
and 1 for the Panthers.
Make something happen!
Come on, let's go!
Red eight!
Hut!
It's a draw to Riggins.
Riggins has nowhere to go,
and it is another big loss
of 7 yards on the play.
There is a time out on the field.
Now hold on, hold on.
Coach Taylor is not gonna send
the punting unit out.
It's 4th and 8
from their own 42 yard line.
This will be a very,
very risky move
if he decides to go for it.
We get the cross
or we get the deep rout.
I been lookin' at those plays
you drew up--
What are you thinking?
If we set the X receiver
in motion,
the linebacker's
gonna follow him.
That's gonna leave a huge gap
between the safeties
and the other receivers.
Then 8 to 10 yards,
- linebackers fill the coverage,
- Yeah, exactly.
fill the gaps, yeah?
So what?
So then I can just
fire pops in there and stuff,
'cause there's, like, an ocean
between the safeties
and the other receivers.
You know why they play
those safeties back so far?
'Cause they're the fastest damn
safeties in Texas, that's why.
They got 21 interceptions
between them,
- do you understand that?
- They want you to throw there,
- Matt, it's a trap.
- You sure you can hit them?
- Yeah.
- You're sure you can hit him.
I'll him him fast, I'll
hit him right in his stride.
If you get picked,
you know what's gonna happen?
We're gonna be watching
the playoffs on our sofas
in our damn houses--
you understand that?
Coach, I got this.
I can do it.
- It's real risky.
- Let me throw it.
Risky.
Take your shot.
Take a shot.
And quarterback Matt Saracen
is coming back onto the field,
and Dillon is going for it.
Fourth and long
in their own territory.
If they don't get this,
this could be a disaster.
Shift 68 high to 11-99.
Niner on one, ready? Go!
Let's go!
That's 4th and 8th.
The crowd on their feet.
And this is a roll of the dice
for Coach Taylor.
If they don't make it,
the momentum shifts heavily
in favor of South Pine.
Go Matt!
Saracen is over the ball.
Red Omaha!
White nine!
Hut!
He's got a man in motion.
Saracen fires-- it's a bullet!
Pow! Wow, it's right on
the numbers!
And Riggins is in the open field!
He could score!
He's breaking tackles.
Ho-ho, he will not be denied!
He is in!
Touchdown!
Touchdown Dillon.
Let's see if the Panthers
can keep their season alive.
How about those Dillon Panthers?
Let's hear it, yeah!
Yeah!
Have a good time!
Thank you very much,
- thank you.
- Coach, I really--
- Hey, buddy.
- I just wanted to say
- thank you for trusting me tonight.
- Huh?
I wanted to say thank you
for trusting me out there tonight,
and letting me help us
to get that win.
It really meant a lot to me.
I just--
I just wanted
to let you know that.
- You did good tonight.
- Thank you.
You had some good ideas.
- Keep your head on straight.
- Thanks...I will.
Then we'll start
congratulatin' each other.
Other than that,
you have a good night.
- Okay, you too.
- All right.
- Hey.
- So I want you to come over,
and we'll have some drinks,
and we'll, um,
well, we'll talk about
some serious social issues.
- Okay.
- Because I know that you and I
are gonna see eye to eye
on lots of things.
- Oh, I'm sure we will.
- Yeah.
and I'm just so lookin'
forward to that.
And that's what I love
about the man.
It's collaborative.
Well, he's a fine coach
because he will take an idea,
and he'll listen.
Pretty sure most of them ideas
been coming from you, Bud.
- Well, I don't know about that.
- I'm pretty sure.
Excuse me, Mr. Garrity.
Hi.
Hang on just a second.
I-I am so sorry.
I'm so sor--
it's all my fault
that my mama missed
her interview.
We were,
we were driving.
I mean, we were
on our way here,
and w-we got a flat tire.
And, so, um, well,
that's why we're late.
Well, that's okay.
I filled that position, but..
Um, I'd even forgotten
all about that,
but it's okay,
don't worry.
Hi, there.
Hi.
I'm Angela,
I'm Tyra's mom.
I am so sorry--
- You're Tyra's mom?
- Yes, I am,
- and I'm so sorry--
- That's--that's okay.
- No, I-I'm Buddy.
- Hi, Buddy.
Well, we had a little
car trouble, so here we are.
- Nice to meet you.
- Thank you.
Um, we could--I mean,
I got a little time
if you want to talk now.
We could talk right now.
- Really?
- Sure.
You are such a gentleman.
- That is so nice of you.
- Sure, sure,
- let's go in my office.
- That'd be great, all right, thank you.
Uh, Reg,
- if you see Pam--yeah.
- I got you.
Hey, Corrina, how you doin'?
I'm good, how are you?
Good, I'm doing fine.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Hey, listen,
can I have him for about an hour?
I'll get him back home.
Yeah, you can do that.
Thank you.
Come on.
Yes, sir.
I'll see you later.
I'll see you at home.
- Good night.
- Take care.
So?
I'm the new receptionist!
That's great!
God, that's so great!
Okay, so, the typing
isn't a problem.
'Cause, you know, the ad
said they wanted typing.
Yeah, it didn't come up.
Okay, so... benefits?
Salary?
I don't know, we didn't
talk about it, honey.
Will you stop?
I just got a job!
That's what you wanted,
and I got it!
Let's go celebrate!
- All right, you're right, you're right.
- Yeah!
Congratulations, Mama!
Thank you!
- Let's get drunk.
- Okay.
When I was a kid,
we used to do all kinds
of craziness after a win.
Now it's come down to
burgers at Lenny's.
What I'm about to say
stays between you and me.
You're gonna get
yourself clean.
You're gonna submit to private,
voluntary drug testing.
Until I decide I can trust you.
Which'll probably be
a damn long time.
- Thank you, sir.
- I don't want you to thank me.
See that kid back there
washing dishes?
He used to be
quarterback over at Westerby
about six years ago.
He was on Grady Hunt's
top 100 list at number six,
if I'm not mistaken.
He never made it
past sophomore at Notre Dame.
You got yourself
into this crap
because you didn't think
you were big enough.
I hope you see
the irony of that.
You don't listen
to the Grady Hunts of the world.
You listen to the people
that love you,
and you listen to the people
that you trust.
Most of all, you listen
to yourself.
I hope...
you realize just how far
I am sticking my neck
out for you.
I do.
And I'll never
let you down again, sir.
You best damn not.
Yes, sir.
See you, Lyla!
Congratulations
on the big win tonight.
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
How are you?
You never, uh,
told me how your
lunch date went.
I think you know how it went.
Busted.
I was jealous.
- Should I be jealous?
- No.
Come here.
You're beautiful.
And you're smart.
And you're talented.
You got your whole future
ahead of you.
Oh, my God, are you
breaking up with me?
My choices are
much more limited
than yours.
Please don't tell me
you're breaking up--
I went out with Herc tonight.
And I basically spent
the whole evening
convincing myself that I was
just a huge thorn in your side.
And after I got done doing that,
I started to think
about Herc.
And why I like him so much.
And I started to realize that
I think I like him so much
'cause he..
he...he took his handicap,
and he didn't settle
for just becoming
as good as he was before,
he tried to become a better man.
And he did.
And I think that,
if I could be more like him,
maybe I wouldn't be
such a bad guy to be around.
And what...
what he would do
if he was in my shoes.
He would dump me
and go after Tyra.
No, he wouldn't.
Yeah, he would,
he told me.
But if it were you
that he loved.
If it were you...
Lyla, I love you
more than life itself.
And I have loved you like that
since the first moment
I laid eyes on you.
Lyla Garrity...
will you marry me?
Baby?