Mornin', sunshine.
Seriously, Tim, I want you gone.
Need a place to crash?
If you take care of Roscoe and Coltrane,
you're welcome.
- Who?
- My ferrets.
- Hey, Glenn, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you too.
- Why are you meeting him in the lounge?
- That is adorable, you're jealous.
Put your hands on my hips, go ahead.
Side to side.
My dad destroyed evidence.
He's a cop.
- I've got him into this thing.
- What do you want me to say?
Watch the pass!
This Panther defense
just can't catch a break.
Weak on the run,
even weaker on the pass.
What are you doing?
Stick him!
37-zip
and with only quarter left to play,
you can call in the dogs,
because this hunt is over.
Somebody's not getting laid tonight.
Oh, will you just stop that!
In front of the baby, good Lord.
- What, trouble in the bedroom?
- Honey, I said, just shup up.
This is why Eric's so grouchy
all the time, great.
You must be real bored if the only thing
you can talk about is our sex life.
Tell me you started up again.
We did it the once.
Like I say,
anything less than three times a week,
Stop it!
I'm tired Shelley.
I know that.
Look.
There's Julie with that cute
english teacher that she has a crush on.
- She tell you that she has a crush on?
- No, she didn't tell me, but I mean,
she told me she thought he was cute
and he was really overminded and smart
- and very cultured.
- I don't like it. I don't trust him...
Come on!
She's a good girl.
And he doesn't seem like the type.
It's embrassing.
It's just embarrassing.
You take it home, you sleep on it,
and then you forget about it.
Because monday,
we will start all over again.
Coaches' meating in 15 minutes.
Thas a good-lookin' man right there.
Wipe it down, wipe it down.
Smash, what the hell
are you so happy about?
- We lost the game.
- I don't got time to talk.
The Smash got other business.
I got appointments and engagements.
- Holler at me later and I'll try to...
- Smash, shut up!
What you doin' next week, Matt?
I'll tell you what you're not doin'.
You're not going on a recruiting trip
to Macnair state
where your cup's never empty,
and the girls never say no.
It's gonna be like Cabo in my pants.
You'll get a real good education
hugging porcelain there this weekend.
My parents are gone.
They won't get back
till tomorrow night.
You could spend the night...
Yeah, I do. But...
My grandma thought
I was gonna be coming home.
She's just kind of freaks out
if I don't say good night to her.
You're so sweet.
Thanks.
Spill some spices there?
- What?
- You know, after we kinda...
Nothing happened!
- Nothing happened.
- I know that.
I know that nothing happened.
I just thought,
you know, maybe we went
to the next level of...
We kinda shared a connection.
We're not going to talk,
or even think about it, okay?
You unrdestand?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Man.
Transcript: www.swsub.com
and Raceman www.forom.com
2x08: SEEING OTHER PEOPLE
Subtitles: Andy, GillesSilb, Ju, Sixe
www.top-series.net (0.90)
Shella's taking me to the bus.
Don't be silly. You know
I'm gonna take you. I'm your mama.
You forgettin' this shirt.
I hate the school
you're getting ready to go to.
It's nothin' but a party school.
You just gonna drink beer
and chase women.
- Mama, we already been through this.
- Let me finish.
You're my son.
When you go there,
you represent this family.
I want you to remember that
and I want you to behave yourself.
- You hear me?
- Yes, ma'am.
I love you.
- You got a second?
- Sure.
I guess I'll just cut to the chase.
I don't know what to do anymore
to get back on the team.
I was hoping if you could say
something to coach for me.
Help me out.
Please.
He doesn't listen to me much
with those things.
But I'll see what I can do.
Appreciate it.
I'll do what I can.
Take care of yourself, okay?
I will.
Thank you.
Okay, books closed, please.
Pop quiz.
Oh, now, now, now.
Let's keep our eyes
on our own papers, please.
You'll all have ten minutes.
Excuse me, Miss Russey.
I need to see Tyra Collette.
Tyra, honey.
They need to see you in the office.
Jeff Coldwell.
He's the brother of the guy
who attacked you.
Wants to talk
to some of his brother's victims.
Make amends on behalf of his family.
Are there other people meeting with him?
Yeah, a few.
I mean, for many victims
of a serious crime like this,
it helps 'em get a sense of closure.
Thank you so much for this.
No problem.
Breast feeding makes me hungry
all the time.
Oh, gross.
I think Gracie threw up on your back.
- I'm serious. I think she...
- Really?
I can't see it.
- Can you get it off?
- I don't know.
I'm eating my lunch.
I can't believe I'm at school.
Is it really bad?
It might be easier to have Gracie
throw up on the other side, you know?
I think I see the virgin mary
in that vomit.
- Oh, hey, hon.
- Why's the door shut?
Because he brought me a burger and fries
And I didn't want everybody
to see me eating like a pig.
- How you doing, Coach?
- You want me to come back later?
Honey, I need to talk to you
about Tim Riggins.
You should think about
bringing him back.
He was like a little lost boy,
this morning.
You know, maybe if Tim
was back on the team
you know,
we wouldn't have lost on friday.
I'm not, like, an expert.
You know what, Glenn,
can I ask you a question?
Can I talk to my wife alone
for a few minutes?
Yeah, absolutely.
Let me just get my stuff.
I'll get right out of your way.
Thank you so much, Glenn.
This is so delicious.
No problem.
Good to see you, Coach.
What?
Let me tell you something about Tim,
that look that you're talking about,
he's had that sily look
his whole life long,
ever since he's a little kid,
he's been using that look.
As far as everything else is concerned,
he didn't just let me down, honey.
He let the team down.
And you just don't...
You just don't get on and off the team
like it's a bus.
Like it's a flaky kind
of real estate class.
- Or like it's a...
- You're making fun of my sister now?
I guess I'm sort of making fun of her.
When Tim Riggins gives me something...
- I need a night out.
- I'll give something back to him.
I need a night out.
- You want a night out?
- I really do. I really do.
You know what I was thinking
we could do?
We could go over to Don Antonio's,
and we'll get couple bottles of wine
and some chocolate.
Then we'll get a room
over at the casa...
I was thinking more like bunco.
Honey, I smell like onions.
Bunco?
Like, with people, the teachers.
They're having a bunco night.
It would be fun. Just, I needome people,
grown-ups to talk to.
You know what I mean?
That'd be fun.
I gotta hide my food
before the kids...
There's Jamell Halloway, wide receiver.
Kid's got hands you wouldn't believe.
I saw that one-handed grab
against Oklahoma Southern.
Hey, what's up?
That was off the chain.
This here is Jordan.
He's our quarterback.
Over here, this is Willis.
He's our all-american fullback.
They know who you are.
Highly recruited too.
Smash Williams.
Coach thinks that you'll be perfect
for our offense.
Well, look, it's an honor
to even be considered
for an offense as explosive
as y'all got here.
Man, how 'bout you shut the hell up
and let me work out!
Oh, I'm sorry, man. We was just...
Hey, I'm smash, man.
All right, man. It's cool, man.
That's Katrelle.
Fool's always in a bad mood, man.
Katrelle Kennedy?
Big, dumb, and ugly.
I never seen 'em eat
out of someone's hand like that.
- Yeah?
- That is awesome.
You must be an old soul, man,
you know that?
You want a smoothie?
- Have a smoothie.
- I'm all right.
Come on, what's bothering you,
my friend?
I guess I miss football.
I guess I miss being around the guys.
That is so sad.
You're like an animal
raised in captivity.
It's like stockholm syndrome.
Yeah.
I just miss all that adrenaline
more than anything else.
you don't know what you want.
You know why?
- Why?
- 'Cause you haven't lived.
A lot more to life than football.
Tell you what. You and me, pretty boy,
we're going hunting tomorrow.
- All right.
You need to kill yourself
some dinner, dude.
I just want to return your book
and thank you.
The world according to Garp...
it was amazing.
- Wow, you're fast.
- Well, I couldn't putt down.
I mean, it was smart
and funny and sad.
And, I don't know, he's a genius.
I don't know how somebody
can write that well. It was amazing.
If you like this, you'll love
A prayer for Owen Meany.
I'll bring it tomorrow.
Okay, um, and then I have
your Jose Gonzalez CD I promised you.
- Excellent. Thank you.
- It's really great.
Especially track number four.
Number four? Okay.
Mental note.
See you tomorrow then.
- Bye.
- See you later.
Mr. Barnett.
Can I ask you a question?
- Why'd you give my daughter that book?
- This?
Because it's really funny.
It's, uh... a pivotal book...
Can we, uh...
Let's see if we can...
- Let's go in here, okay?
- Okay.
It's a pretty adult book,
don't you think?
- It's pretty sexual.
- I'm an english teacher here,
and I can recommend reading
to my students.
Well, I find you inappropriate.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
And I find you condescending.
I don't like you giving salacious
reading material to my daughter.
I don't like you having lunch
with her behind closed doors.
I don't like you touching each other
when you talk to each other.
- Look. This is...
- No, listen to me.
I want you to be clear about something.
I can have you fired.
I can have my husband come over
and beat the crap out of you.
And I can have you thrown into prison.
You hear what I'm saying?
- If you lay one hand on my daughter.
- Is that all?
- Do you have anything to say?
- No, thank you.
I don't understand
why he wants to meet me.
It's creepy.
Don't you think it's creepy?
What if they're twins?
Probably they're not.
They're not twins.
Why don't you tell him
that you're not gonna go?
Because I told him I would,
and I don't want to look suspicious.
What kind of freak wants to meet
their brother's rape victim anyway?
What does he want?
I'm scared, Landry.
I don't think I'll be able
to look him in the eye.
I'll go for you.
I'll tell him that
you changed your mind.
All right?
She's going with me, so...
Hey. Haven't seen you here in a while.
Me and noah were supposed to have lunch
together, but I don't know where he is...
You haven't heard yet?
Your mom got into it with him.
- She accused him of all these things.
- My mom?
She pretty much called him a pedophile.
I can't believe you haven't heard.
- How dare you?
- What?
You had no right whatsoever!
Not everybody out there
is having sex with each other!
What are you talking about?
You accused Noah of pedophilia
in front of the entire school!
Sweetie, lower your voice.
Why would you do
something like that to me?
He's the only person who listens to me
and you just get him out of my life too?
Sweetheart, I'm just your mother
I'm just trying to do what I...
No, you don't!
You don't need to do that as my mother,
or as a guidance counselor.
or even as a human being, mom!
Why would you do that?
Somebody's got to look out for you.
These people think
that meat is something that
magically appears
in their supermarket wrapped in plastic.
But that ain't natural.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah, I got you.
I mean, if you don't have the stomach
to take it down yourself,
you better just be eating chicken.
I agree.
This is awesome, man.
Did I tell you?
You know what? You're right.
It doesn't get any better than this.
Doesn't get any better than this.
This is one on one.
Man versus nature.
I just feel free.
- You were right.
- Lot better than taking a hit, huh?
What's so damn funny, man?
These girls are bangin', son.
You gotta love life, boys.
That right there, that's for you.
Cloudy, I need that Dom.
So you're Smash, huh?
Yes, ma'am, that's right, I am.
Oh this is a treat,
getting my hair done.
I want it to look
- like Angie Dickinson.
- Who's that?
She's very famous actress.
You don't know who that is?
Famous, famous celebrity.
Matt, it's Smash.
I got somebody here
who wants to talk to you.
Is this Matt?
Tell me, are you as cute
as your friend Smash?
Look at these people.
That hairdo's cute.
- That's pretty.
- That's real sweet of you to do this.
- I can do that.
- You could?
- You Jeff Caldwell?
- Yeah.
I'm a friend of Tyra Collette.
She's not coming.
She didn't want to. Didn't see the point
in going back to what happened.
I honestly didn't either.
Is there something you needed to say?
I'd like this to be as brief as you can.
Look, if you could, uh...
If you could just tell her I'm sorry.
I mean, I know that's...
Why exactly are you doing this?
Just trying to understand how my brother
could have done these things.
That's not what he was like.
One, he was a sick,
irredeemable piece of scum.
He was a poor excuse of a man.
I don't know...
I don't know what you don't understand.
He wasn't, though. I mean, yeah,
obviously with what's happened.
yeah, he was, but...
I mean, he stuck up for me.
Fixed food for me
when mom was too drunk.
Don't. Please don't tell me about that.
You ask anyone in Dillon,
they probably got
the same story,
and they're not off becoming rapist.
He was my brother, OK?
He's my brother.
You know? What's the purpose
of your sister even being here
if she can't babysit?
Honey, what part of the fact that she
has class tonight do you not understand?
I have to work tonight,
but I'm babysitting, aren't I?
Well, it's not babysitting
when it's your own child, sweetheart.
Wait. Why are you putting perfume on?
You're going to bunco night.
'Cause I'm trying
to mask the smell of spit-up.
- That dress looks nice.
- Thank you, sweetheart.
Sweetie, there's extra breastmilk
in the freezer in case she gets thirsty,
whatever.
I love you. Have fun, have fun.
She's your baby.
- It's in the freezer?
- Thank you.
I love you. Bye.
Love you. Bye.
All right, well...
All right, I got it.
Roadhouse is the best action movie
of the '80s. Hands down, no doubt.
At least action movie.
Maybe all-time movie.
It's got all the key ingredients.
Town in need...
Man searching for his soul.
Hot sex, fisticuffs.
Two words:
- Patrick...
- Swayze.
- He's freakin' awesome.
- I know.
Need you to go in and grab some beer.
I think we're out.
Go ahead, grab some.
A few boxes of cold medicine too.
Why am I getting cold medicine
at midnight?
I got a cold coming on, man.
Carlotta.
Hello?
I'm coming.
I baked you some cookies.
Great.
- Just throw 'em onhe table the.
- Okay.
I'm Lauren.
- Hello. Carlotta.
- Nice to meet you.
You work here with Matt's grandma?
- Yes.
- Oh, that so great.
So do you want watch TV,
- or a movie or something?
- Yeah, you two go ahead.
She's so nice.
Yeah, she's nice.
She's really nice.
- Hey.
- How did it go?
She cried all night.
Projectile pooped across the room again.
It was hard to clean up.
Oh no, did she really?
I'm sorry, babe.
Did you have a good time tonight?
I did.
Sorry it was hard for you, though.
Those teachers can play some bunco.
And I'll tell you what. Glen won $100,
and we went out a got a beer.
I'm gonna have to pump.
- Glenn had a good time.
- It was fun.
- Give Glenn a great time.
- Yeah, it was fun.
Honey,
you're a little bit jealous of Glenn?
Can I tell you something, seriously?
I don't like you and Glenn yukking it up
in the hallways
like a bunch of little kids.
Honey...
What? Yukking it up?
It's goofy.
It's goofy?
And people are gonna start talking.
I don't like y'all running around behind
closed doors. Like the other day
I walk in there, and he's laying
all over the couch there,
eating his sandwich and stuff.
I have to ask him to leave the room
before he even damn sits up.
I don't appreciate that.
- That's ridiculous.
- No, it's not ridiculous.
- Yes, it is.
- No, you know what it is?
It's disrespectful.
It's disrespectful
to me. It's disrespectful
to this family.
That's what I'm thinking.
What about God?
Is it disrespectful to God?
That's not funny.
- Well, I mean, this is silly.
- It's not funny. You know what it is?
It undermines us. You think about that.
- Just think about it.
- It undermines us?
Yes, it undermines us.
It does not. That is ridiculous.
One last thing
and we can leave it alone, okay?
You need to pay more attention
to your family.
How dare you?
Don't do that.
You know what?
You can go sleep on the couch.
So I can get a good night's sleep
so I pay a lot of attention
to my family tomorrow.
Go on.
I'm sleeping.
Look, she... She went home.
I didn't know that she was coming over.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing to be sorry for.
Go to bed.
Smash, this is the way we roll 24/7!
What do you think of our little paradise
- of a college here?
- Call the dogs off. The search is over.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
- We just found our missing link.
- That's right.
Let's see what you got, young pup.
Look around. See what you like.
Go get 'em.
Take your shirt off.
Let me see your tummy.
Oh, God!
- Open this door!
- Hey, we're kind of busy!
- Open the door!
- Katrel, take your drunk ass home!
Katrell?
Katrell Kennedy, the nose guard?
- Yes.
- Hell, no.
Oh, my God.
The hell you doing, rookie?
I think we got started
on the wrong foot!
It's not that dramatic!
Tell coach you found another school!
Hey!
Don't ever come back!
What the hell
took you so long?
- I'm freezing.
- I got here as fast as I could.
- You grab me some clothes?
- Here, here.
So...
So how was your visit?
I'm not in the mood.
Let's just go.
Seriously,
was it like cabo in your pant?
I never ran so fast in my life.
On the real,
if they was timing me
I'd have ran, like, a 3.8.
Yeah, I think that may be the funniest
story I've ever heard in my life.
Glad somebody finds it funny.
Hey, um...
Can I ask you a question?
Do you know, like, a good way
to break up with somebody.
I don't know what to say,
I've never broken up
with a girl a day in my life.
Now you're just lying.
I'm trying to have a real talk.
On the real.
I mean, I just tell 'em
I want an open relationship.
I let that sentence do the work
and they break up with me.
And I come out smelling out like roses.
Open relationship, Matty.
Magic words.
It's okay, baby.
Just give us one second, okay?
Okay.
Hey, hon.
- Thank you, Shel.
- Of course, baby. Anytime.
See you later, hon.
She's really upset.
I know. I know she really is.
She's embarrassed.
I don't think I need a mediator
to help me with my daughter, Shelly.
I know you think you were right.
And honestly,
most of the time you are right
but in this situation,
do you really think
that reaming that guy a new one
in front of the entire school?
You really think that was
the best way to handle this?
I did not ream that guy...
in front of the entire school.
- That's what Julie said happened
- Well, I'm sure she said that.
But you have no idea
what really happened.
And, you know franckly,
you're not a mother.
So you have no idea
what the situation was that I was in.
My God. Sometime,
we are gonna have a whole conversation
where you don't say that to me.
Seriously, Tami, honestly.
If mom had done that,
how would you have felt?
I probably would have felt mortified.
Exactly.
Thou dost preparest a table before me
in the presence of my enemies.
My cup overflows.
Surely goodness and love kindness
will follow me all the days of my life.
And I will dwell in the house
of the Lord forever and ever.
So what does that mean to us?
What does that mean to you? Me?
That means if we put our trust
in the Lord,
his promises will...
open up to us.
We will see his promises.
Dors everybody understand?
Should we trust God?
Should we believe him?
Should we put God first?
Yes.
His promises are right here.
Dwell in the land.
- Paul, I'll be right back.
- Okay.
And cultivate faithfulness.
Hey, Landry.
You okay?
Yeah.
You look like maybe
you needeed some company.
I mean, you can sit if you want.
Okay.
So are you a good christian
or a bad christian, Lyla Garrity?
I try and be a good christian.
So, uh...
It's not always so easy to tell, though.
I don't think any of us are perfect.
I know I'm not.
Are you?
Not so much.
I've had this secret...
for a while now,
and it's starting to literally
just eat away at me.
Seems so easy to just tell the truth,
to get it all off your chest.
To do the right thing.
Seems so easy to do.
I've got so many people
involved in this.
I just don't know what to do.
I don't think there's anything
wrong in telling the truth.
I think that...
telling the truth is a way
of surrendering to God.
Man, I don't what would happen
if I were to do that.
I mean...
That's why they call it faith.
Just tell the truth, huh?
Just tell the truth.
Go on, Matty.
You can do.
Call you guys later.
Bye.
- How's it going?
- Good, you?
- Good.
- That's good.
Can we maybe talk for a minute?
Yeah, of course.
I was just thinking maybe
we should try and have, like...
an open relationship.
What?
Like, an open relationship.
Like, you wanna be with another girl?
- No, I don't want to.
- What did I do?
You're perfect, you're great.
I told you this
about my ex-boyfriend.
- It's not like that.
- Honestly, don't touch me, okay?
Stay out of my way, Matt.
Okay?
Okay.
See? Problem solved!
What happened to coming out
smelling like roses?
That part don't always work.
Yeah, has it ever worked out?
You ever seen that work out?
Like how I decorated?
Good thing you're a cool dude.
Or I'd have to kill you.
Let's go!
Let's hear it now!
Spread 'em.
Stretch it out good,
gentlemen.
Lean it, lt!
Coach.
To the right.
What the hell are you doing?
What the hell are you doing
in my uniform?
It's still my uniform, coach.
What the hell are you doing
in my uniform and my field, Riggins?
- I'm not getting off the field, Coach.
- You're not?
You're get off my damn field
if I tell you to.
I'm not leaving. I'll do whatever
it takes to stay on this field.
You didn't just let me down,
you let yourself down,
you let the damn team down.
You understand that?
All right, then.
Get off my damn field.
Let's go!
Six! Call it out!
What'd I tell you?
Get out of here.
I can't hear you!
Left over right.
Hang it!
What the hell you think you're going?
What's up, Rig?
We have not playing since pee-wee,
and I let you down.
And I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
Thanks, Rig.
I appreciate it.
4-6.
Hey, look,
I don't ever recall seeing you play
in any of the games.
I don't think you ever will.
But I can tell you,
the effort you put forth
on practice days is undeniable.
Thanks, man.
2-0.
You know, to be honest, I just...
I know you try and sleep
with a lot of girls
that I've previously slept with
so just left town for a bit
to give you a break.
You know?
You lose that virginity yet?
We're good, man.
It's good to have you back.
I, uh...
I apologize to eveyone here.
And if you can find it
within yourselves
to let me make it up to you
in the showers.
I appreciate it.
Listen up.
Your penance isn't paid up yet.
Wipe that stupid smile off you face.
Go take your spot.
Let's go!
Come on!
Call 'em out, let's go.
Get out of my spot, rookie.
Bring it up!
- Hi.
Where's everyone?
Julie and Shelly took baby Grace
to the mall
to buy her some new baby clothes.
Which is very sweet.
That's good.
I can't not have a friend
at school that I, you know,
spend time what, for 20 minutes a day.
It's not about Glen.
Don't give a damn about Glen.
I'm supposed to be the one
that you're yukking it up with
in the hallways.
I'm supposed to be the one
that you're laughing with.
I Miss you.
I Miss you too.
I like you.
- You do?
- Yeah, I like you.
I like you too.
I broke up with Lauren.
I don't know why
you're telling me uhis, Matt.
Because she was really nice
and really hot
and I had absolutely
no reason not to like her.
Except that I can't stop
thinking about you.
Look, I know you work here,
and I'm not trying
to make anything weird,
but I like you,
a lot.
And I just want to spend
every second I can with you
or around you.
I just want you to know that.
- Look, I...
- No.
I need to speak to someone
about the murder of Mike Caldwell.
What is it, son?
I did it.
I killed him.