What do you want to talk about, Tim?
The fact that you're sleeping with
your paralyzed best friend's girlfriend?
Tatom, get over here
We gonna win, we gonna play my way.
Oh, and it's picked off!
Get outta my sight, son!
You are done!
- I don't care!
- You are done here!
Some questions have arisen about
about Ray Tatom's eligibility.
If he is deemed ineligible,
Ray Tatom won't be playing
football here anymore.
And Dillon will be stripped
of last night's victory.
I'm here tonight at the Texas High School
Athletic Administration District meeting.
If it is found that district
regulations were violated,
Ray Tatom no longer be allowed to
participate in any varsity athletics.
More importantly,
last week's Dillon Panther win
over the Arnett Mead Tigers
would be ruled a loss.
- Can we change the channel?
...to see how this turns out for the Panthers...
I don't get what the big deal is.
Kaster, she's just asking you
to turn your volume down.
It's not just me playing loud.
We're all doing it.
No, see, actually, she did
single out the bass player.
Hey, Saracen!
Get over here, man.
I'll be right back.
I'll count the seconds.
Hey, I want you
to meet some people here.
This is Tiff.
Look, I'm telling, Tiff.
This man right here is golden.
You better get him now before
somebody beats you to it.
Hey, that's not--
That's a Joke.
He's totally crossed over, man.
Would you calm down?
No, man.
Look at him.
Like the entire world
revolves around them.
Don't they know they're gonna
end up menial laborers one day anyway?
Virgin territory.
Smash, no. See, now that's--
I'm trying to help you out, man.
What you doing here, Voodoo?
Just getting a burger and fries, man.
You got a problem with that?
Yeah, I got a problem with that.
We all got a problem with that.
Why don't you find another
restaurant, man?
Why don't you go on back
cross that river?
What'd you say to me?
I said you should take
your wetback ass
right on across the river.
- It's not worth it.
- Just chill, just chill. Don't even listen.
- Don't even listen to him. All right, just chill.
- Everybody needs to just chill out.
Last thing you need right now
is to mix up with us, man.
Trust me.
Food sucks here anyway.
Move.
Take your bodyguards with you.
My man Rig.
Making the peace.
Hey, the news!
We're live with Channel 8 Action Update.
We are here at the Texas High School
Athletic Administration District meeting
where board member Lance
Jennings is about to announce
the board's decision
about Dillon quarterback
Ray Voodoo Tatom's eligibility.
I would like to thank everyone
for their patience in this matter,
but I feel we need more time
for deliberations. Therefore,
we will not be issuing a final ruling
until some time later in the week.
Hey, we're heading out.
You need a ride?
Uh, yeah.
Just gimme one minute, okay?
Get over yourself, man.
It's just a stupid football game.
In the large scheme of things,
do you think anyone's gonna give a crap?
Kaster, please, just go wait--
Am I right about that?
- Just go wait outside, all right?
- That's fine.
- Is this your buddy?
- Is he being serious right now?
He's joking.
He's making jokes.
I mean, I like Kaster okay
and everything.
But seriously, he's gotta learn
that he can't just talk to people like that.
I know.
I said that I'll talk to him.
What a dumb-ass thing to say, man.
Look, I'm sorry, man.
Sorry?
Look, man,
I'm sorry, all right?
You don't look sorry.
What's your problem, man?
Dumb football players, huh?
Man, chill. Come on.
You know that's not what I meant.
Is that what you heard?
Do you mean that?
Get off, man! Hey, Kaster!
Get off him! Kaster! Reyes!
Man, what the hell you doin'?
What the hell, man?
Let's turn him.
- Easy!
- No, just stay there. Just stay right there!
- Oh, my God.
- Breathe, man.
Friday Night Lights
s01e06 - El Accident
Blue, 52.
Hut!
Bring it back.
Hustle up, come on!
Coach, the board didn't come
to a decision.
So why am I not getting snaps?
All right, now, hey, coach!
Let's get 'em together. One minute, take a break.
One minute, bring it back
to the 30, let's go.
Hey, Reyes. Reyes.
What happened?
What are you talking about?
Last night with Kaster.
I know that kid.
He dissed us.
You heard him.
What are you talking about,
that stupid thing that he said?
It's done, man.
Get over it.
Let's go, gentlemen!
Let's go! Let's go!
Coach.
Sorry to interrupt your practice, Coach.
We need Bobby Reyes.
I've got a warrant on him.
What do you need Bobby for?
A ssault.
Get him.
Reyes!
Yeah, Coach?
Ron, you don't need
to use handcuffs.
Hell, come on.
Where's he gonna go?
Sorry about your practice.
Let's go. Come on.
Concentrate on the field.
Let that go, come on!
This is your job right here!
- Get under it, Saracen. Let's run this.
- It'll be all right, Reyes!
Tyra...
you're flunking algebra.
Ms. Kincaid hates me.
- She does not. Come on.
- Yes, she does.
Well, if you fail it
with Mrs. Kincaid,
you're gonna have to go do it
next semester with Mr. Wendell.
Well, I'm not gonna be here
next semester.
Where're you gonna go?
California.
What are you gonna do in California
without a high school education?
I'm taking my GED.
Listen, I know.
I was just like you.
I was the pretty girl in school.
I was terrible at math.
I got myself through it.
I don't wanna be you, Mrs. Taylor.
I don't wanna stay here.
Stuck in this small town...
in a job like this...
married to a coach.
Tyra, it's your choice.
If you wanna go off and take the GED, fine.
But you better bring me proof
that you did it.
Otherwise, you're taking algebra
with Mr. Wendell next semester.
Fine.
Mrs. Taylor?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm Kurt Kaster's mother.
Oh, come on in. Come on in.
I'm so sorry to hear about
what happened with your son.
Have a seat.
I was told to see you about
getting his homework
sent over to him at the hospital.
Yes, we've already arranged
that his daily assignments
are gonna be taken over there
every afternoon.
And then everything else that we need to do
academically will be taken care of.
I appreciate that.
Absolutely.
And just--if there's anything
else that I can do...
I raised my boy right,
Mrs. Taylor.
He's a good boy.
- Yes, he is.
- He doesn't get into fights.
A few days from now, that Reyes boy
is gonna be back on the football team
like nothing ever happened.
But I don't need
to tell you this, do I ?
You're the coach's wife.
You know how all this works.
Well, no, I don't actually.
Thank you for helping
about the homework.
You tellin' me the truth
straight up?
That's it.
They just talked.
Y'all are telling me
everything you saw?
That's it.
You have any idea how difficult it is
with these recruitment accusations
flying around right now?
Now I gotta deal with Reyes
and this Kaster kid situation.
It's just as much your fault
as it is his.
From now on, when you're out,
you hear something, you see something
you're gonna stop it.
As leaders of this team, that is gonna be
your job. Are we clear?
Yes, sir.
Good.
That's all I got to say.
You ever get an answer back
on that request we put in
for extra time
in the weight room?
Not yet.
Jason's making world-class progress.
I'll make sure and get you
an answer on that.
Thanks.
What's so funny?
You know what they call you
around here?
- What?
- "Advocado."
I don't get it.
- It's like advocate and avocado.
- I don't find that very amusing.
It is funny.
Come on, think about it.
They pumping you
with nitrous or something?
What is going on with you?
- I don't know.
- What are you doing?
Come here.
- Jason, we can't do this.
- Yeah, we can.
- We're in a public place.
- I knew it.
- I knew it!
- What?
We have a visitor.
Oh, my...
Lyla, I gotta tell you.
I am horny as hell right now.
- Jason!
- What?
I have never heard you talk
like this in my life.
- That's just naughty.
- Naughty.
You are one of a kind,
you know that?
Hey, Lyla.
Hi, Francine.
Is it possible that we could have
about 40 minutes of privacy?
No, Jason.
We don't need it.
Can I talk to him for
a second, Lyla?
Yeah, sure.
I'll just be outside.
You wanna make sure you don't get any dirt
up in this carburetor.
Mess your engine up something fierce.
Looks like we got company.
What's up?
Tim, we have to stop this.
Look at me, Tim.
Please.
Jason is getting out of there soon.
He's changing.
He's getting back to his old self.
So you're done with me?
- Tim, don't.
- Don't what?
Don't react like that.
You knew this had to end.
Look, I take full responsibility for
everything that's happened.
It's all my fault.
Sounds like it was the biggest
mistake of your life, Lyla.
I feel like I have to make
a choice here, Tim,
before things get more messed up
than they already are.
I care about you, Tim.
I do.
I just...
I can't live
with myself anymore.
Bye, Lyla.
So you're telling me
I can't have sex?
No, I said it isn't
medically safe to ejaculate.
You see, that's funny 'cause I always
kinda put the two together.
Jason, look.
Semen can backflow into your bladder
and it can cause a whole bunch of things,
especially a severe
urinary tract infection.
You know, I like you
a lot, Francine, but...
you really know how
to break a guy's heart.
I'll check on you later, okay?
Mrs. Kaster came
and talked to me today.
I don't...oh, yeah.
How's the boy doing?
Well, he's not doing very well.
You know, Reyes really did a number on him.
I know. Listen, he's a good kid.
He just gets a little hot under the collar.
A little hot under the collar?
I mean, he put him
in a hospital, bad.
I understand that.
I guess I'm just a little
curious about what you think--
You know, what you're going to
do about that whole situation.
What do you mean, what am I
gonna do about it?
Well, I mean,
I think you're in a position
- where you might be able to--
- Wait, wait-- Let me ask a question.
Who am I talking to right now?
Am I talking to the guidance counselor,
or am I talking to my wife?
- Oh, come on.
- I'm serious.
What do you mean, I'm either speaking to you
as a guidance counselor,
- as your wife.
- Sometimes I don't really know.
It doesn't make a difference
how I'm speaking to you.
Sometimes it does make--
There's something that I--
Well, I'm just curious about
how you're--
...involved in the situation.
This is a very serious situation.
Hey, honey.
How are you today?
Hey, guys.
You all good?
Gooood.
You have a good day at school?
Yeah, a blast.
Here, I got you something.
I got you something.
I got you an apple.
Oh. Gee whiz.
Apple of your daddy's eye.
- Yeah?
- Hey, it's me.
Hi.
Thanks.
Come on in.
I just, you know,
wanted to stop by to let you know
that Bart Oliver asked me out.
- Bart?
- Hummm...
He's a defensive end.
Yeah, I know who he is.
Well, you know, I just wanted
to give you a heads-up
before anyone else ends up in the
hospital like that Kaster kid.
Don't flatter yourself, Tyra.
You know, I'm trying to be
the mature one here.
- Douche bag.
- That's classy.
Have a good day.
You're such a jerk, Tim.
You know that?
H ello?
I need you to come down here, Timmy.
J?
There's something I gotta talk
to you about.
Where?
The rehab center?
Where do you think?
Come on.
Just get down here, all right?
Yeah, man.
Well, i'm glad you called me on this, Eric.
It's the right thing to do.
I'll make sure this kid
gets a fair shake.
He's a good kid.
And the last thing this team needs
is having our star defensive player
sitting over here in the jail.
Oh, and another thing.
We may have to go back in again in front
of the Athletic Administration.
What?
Well, evidently, when they interviewed
Voodoo's family, somebody mentioned
the "academic council"
we had with Voodoo.
That's what you call that?
Academic council?
Yeah.
The meeting we had.
- Damn, Buddy.
- What?
When did all this take place?
Look, he has to have 30 days
of established residence
- before he even puts a uniform on.
- Damn, Buddy.
The meeting took place in July.
The meeting took place two weeks ago.
- Hey, don't worry about it, okay?
- Oh, don't worry about it.
Every single team
in the district did exactly
- the same thing that we did.
- Don't ask me to lie.
I'm not gonna ask you to lie.
Let's just solve this crisis
right now, okay? One crisis at a time.
Let's take care of Reyes,
and then we'll do the other deal later.
Made a mistake, Coach.
I don't know what to do. I'm scared.
Yeah, well, it sounds like
you made a mistake.
Why don't you tell me exactly
what happened?
We're at the sandwich shop.
Just there, you know, hanging out.
We, uh--we were watching
the hearing on TV.
I guess I was a little pissed.
Then Voodoo comes in... comes right in,
like nothing even happened.
All right, that's all great.
How'd the Kaster kid get involved?
When that guy came on TV and said that
they were coming up with a decision,
you know, we all got upset.
Then that Kaster kid comes in
and he starts mouthing off
about football players
and talking smack about the team.
You know that no matter
what anyone says to you,
that doesn't give you the right
to cause physical harm to them, don't you?
- You understand that?
- Yeah, Coach.
Then why would you be so stupid, son?
Then I...
Kaster kid called me a wetback.
Well, that's not right.
I mean, that's just racist is what that is.
He said I should go back to Mexico.
I'm not even from Mexico, Coach.
Anyway, I went outside afterwards
and asked him to apologize
for what he said.
He didn't want to apologize.
So he goes up
and he tries to hit me.
So we started fighting, Coach.
He's trying to fight me. I fight back.
It just set me off so bad.
I've been trying to control my temper.
You know I have, Coach.
You're telling me the truth?
- Yes, sir.
- You look me right in the eye.
You tell me you're telling me the truth.
Coach, I'm telling you the truth.
Six.
Took you long enough to get here, man.
My truck ain't runnin'.
We're putting in this
four-barrel carb.
I hitched a ride, man.
Sorry.
I'm guessing you know
what this is about.
- I do?
- Yeah, of course you do.
You wanna call yourself
my best friend
and you haven't shown up but once
since I've been in here.
Six weeks, man.
Six weeks.
Let me go ahead and recap my life for you
over the last couple of weeks, huh?
My day starts out with me
laying down on this bed.
Well, pretty much the whole day
takes place with me laying down
on this bed on my sorry
quadriplegic ass.
Every day, people come in here
and poke and prod at me
like I'm a piece of meat.
Go ahead and stick a catheter in me
in places you don't even want to know about.
My big adventure of the day
is going to the commode.
'Cause I gotta go
the same time every day
so I can teach my body
how to crap on cue.
Impressive, huh?
And then Lyla comes running in.
I wanna know if she's as chipper
out there as she is in here.
'Cause I'll tell you what--
I love that girl... I do.
I love her more than life itself.
But I'll tell you what.
If she tells me how great
everything's gonna be when...
I finally get out of here
one more time, I'm gonna lose it.
Point is this, Timmy.
While I'm in here dealing
with all this, by myself,
and my best friend's out there
putting a four-barrel carb
in his damn truck.
Is that what's important
right now?
Answer me this, Timmy...
What happened to Texas forever?
Huh?
What happened to livin' large?
What happened to that eternal bond
that you used to love to throw
around when I was still health
and headed towards the NFL, huh?
I need you here, Tim.
I need you here.
I expect...
I expect you here.
You are my best friend.
Grace period's over.
It's embarrassing for me to admit, but...
before things got physical,
Kurt Kaster called me
and my family racist names.
Said I was a...
A dirty wetback jock who should
go back over the border
with my dirty wetback mom.
I realize that--
that what I did was wrong.
And that I should have responded
in a more mature way.
I've been released on bail,
but the Kaster family
is still pressing charges against me.
I just wanted everyone to hear the truth.
You know, directly from me.
Thank you.
I'm not buying his story.
I'm not buying that.
What do you mean
you're not buying it?
Kurt Kaster is a straight-A student.
He's on the student mentoring program.
And I talked to his mother.
I just--
I don't feel that he
would've said those things.
Look, people--
they say stupid things.
They're--they're teenagers.
She just knew in her heart that
he didn't do it. I believed her.
Look, I've known Reyes for a long time.
I've coached him for a long time.
- Did you know that--
- He's not the kind of kid
- he's got a record?
- That's gonna go and do something like that.
Did you know that he's been arrested twice?
Two burglaries, and one of them,
he resisted arrest.
Well, he is a little bit--
He's had a tough upbringing.
That's not what we're talking about.
I'm not saying it was the right thing
for him to do-- beat the hell out of this kid.
But he was obviously provoked.
I would like for you to really look
at all sides of this thing.
Of course I've looked at all sides of it, honey.
I'm just telling ya...
I looked that kid right in the eye.
He's telling the truth.
All right?
I can tell.
Hey, who you taking to homecoming?
Man, you should take
that, uh, rally girl, Drew.
Uh, no, I got--I got someone
else in mind, so--.
Aw, man, quit stalling!
Come on.
Hey, I bet your granny
still cut an ill two-step.
- Hey, Matt.
- Hey.
Can I talk to you for a second?
- Hey, what's up?
- What's up? What's going on?
Reyes lied.
Look, man, you weren't outside, okay?
Neither of us were.
We don't know that for sure.
Well I mean, we've known Kaster
since the seventh grade.
I mean, he's not a racist.
He's never said one racist thing.
Voodoo's the one who said
all that stuff.
Yeah, but it's over now, okay?
It's done.
It's--It's not over.
I mean, you-- you can do something.
- What am I supposed to do?
- You wanna make a statement?
Call a press conference?
I mean, you're the starting
quarterback, aren't you?
Wait, I'm not--
I'm not Peyton Manning.
I can't call a press conference.
I've played three high school football games.
I haven't even started all of them.
If we need to stop at 12 we can.
- I can do 15.
- Okay.
J. Street.
- Hey, uh, Kristen?
- Yeah?
Could we, uh...
Could we get just a couple minutes?
Sure.
Can you spot him so he
can't--doesn't fall forward?
- Yes, ma'am.
- He just got his brace off.
Put one hand right there.
There you go.
And you do it slow.
Thank you.
Brace off today.
How nice. Congrats.
What say you and me
get out of here later?
Yeah, great idea.
- Where do you think we're gonna go?
- I got some ideas.
Tell you what,
anywhere but here, man.
It smells.
It smells like a hospital, man.
I hate hospitals.
All right, genius, when--
when are we doing this?
I'm thinking tonight.
Let's do it.
I'm not lying.
Hey--
You wanna coach big time
high school football?
'Cause that's what every single
one of these coaches does.
This is part of the deal.
You wanna coach,
you better get ready for this.
This is just the way it is,
and I don't like it any more than you do.
So get it together.
Let's go in there and get this done.
Gentlemen, thank you for coming.
My God, Taylor.
Forrest frickin' Aiken.
- How are you, man?
- Good to see ya.
Good to see you, Buddy.
How's Pam?
She's fine, she's fine.
How about yours?
Doin' well. Keeping me in line.
Yes, sir.
Listen, have a seat, have a seat.
Yeah. I can't believe it's you.
Hey, Coach, this is my old buddy--
- Forrest Aiken.
- Hi, how are you doing?
We played football together at UT.
Played defense.
- Coach, how you doin'?
- Uh, just fine. Everything's going just fine.
You know, Coach, I hate that
you're having to go through all this.
And I'm sure you'd rather be spending
time with your boys right now.
I know you got a big game
this Friday night.
Yes, a big one coming up.
That's for sure.
Well, I've looked through this and, uh,
let's cut through all the hoopla.
- Oh.
- Yeah, let's--
- Let's settle this matter.
- That sounds good to me.
I feel real comfortable with it.
I've looked over it
and I feel real good about it.
- I think everything's gonna be just fine.
- That's good.
Attention please.
Assistant Principal Trucks here
with a little news update.
The ruling just came down from
the Athletic Administration.
Ray Tatom was deemed eligible
to play in last week's game.
This means the Panther victory
over Arnett Mead still stands.
Oh, yeah!
State! State! State!
Just reach behind me and lift.
- Ready?
- Yep.
Why don't you save some of that Jell-O
for the other patients, Street?
You kidding me?
- You good?
- I'm in.
I'm in, I'm in.
Just swing my legs around.
Okay, I got you.
What is going on?
- Field trip.
- Field trip?
Yeah.
Who did you clear this with?
Street.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Yes.
Go easy on him, boss.
- Tim, what are you doing?
- We're going on a little ride.
Going on a little ride?
Yes.
You ready to rock and roll?
Hold on just a second.
Lyla...
Come with us.
No, no. You guys go.
I'll be behind you
with the police brigade.
Come here. Come here.
Let's just for once let
the rules go, all right?
I need this.
You know I need this.
Come on.
You guys are crazy.
Timmy, let her in.
She's coming along.
A man named Gene's
got a beautiful voice
You know how great this is?
Me, you, Riggs, open road, fresh air.
No hospitals.
Man, did I need this.
Just sing me a song
And if it's sad
I'll sing along,
long, long
I told you
I knew every word
- And a straw.
- Don't forget the straw!
Don't forget the straw!
I'm really glad you came, babe.
Me too.
I, uh...
Running a little low on the cash.
What a surprise.
- Be right back.
- Ok.
I don't want this to be awkward.
Well maybe we can start
by you not shoving
your tongue down his throat, Lyla.
I can't take all the blame for this.
Oh, and here I thought you
were taking responsibility.
Oh, shut up, Tim.
Lyla, look--
It's J's night, all right?
Let's just get through this for him.
You ready?
Uh!
You ain't in game shape,
are you, Streeter?
How are you supposed to carry your team?
You can't even carry me.
Maybe I should just
get rid of the chair
and have you carry me around everywhere.
Street!
Here you go.
Two burgers, straight up.
- Hey, picking up for Taylor.
- Sure, one minute.
Thank you.
Hey.
So where's the other one?
Ah.
Trouble in paradise.
It's this whole Reyes thing.
You mean the guy who nearly
killed the other kid
but nobody's gonna do anything about it
because he plays football?
So I guess that puts you
on his side?
No, it...
I just think you should man up
and talk to him.
I mean, you two look pretty
pathetic without each other.
There you go, hon.
Do you need any utensils?
Uh, no, I'm good.
Thanks.
All right, look, I thought about
what you said, all right?
And?
And I think, well, you're not really
recognizing my position in all this.
Look--I'm under a lot of pressure.
I'm supposed to lead this team.
They're depending on me.
I just can't make accusations
about my teammates.
You're Matt Saracen.
QB1, right?
Look, can you just cut me some slack?
You're supposed to be my best friend, okay?
Fine, all right?
Reyes--Reyes is a crazy son of a bitch,
but he's key to our defense.
We're relying on him.
He also assaulted
one of our friends.
Or do you not have time to think about that
with all the pressures and everything?
Lovers spat?
Look, not now, Reyes, all right?
What's wrong?
Where are you going?
Home.
Did I upset you?
- Just leave him alone.
- What's wrong with him?
Just leave him alone, okay?
I mean, do you realize that if you weren't
a Panther you'd be in jail right now?
- Excuse me?
- He didn't say nothing.
You assaulted Kaster.
And you just think that you're gonna
get away with it, don't you?
You better watch what you're saying, man.
Seriously.
I'm not afraid of you.
If that's what you think.
What are you talking about?
Reyes..
You're not worth it, man.
Hey--
Landry!
Get him off me!
Lay off me!
Come on, man!
Go home! You don't need this!
Okay?
Just stop!
Just go home!
You know what?
Kaster was right about you.
You did cross over.
You're one of them. Congratulations.
I could be out here
all night listening to this.
Just nothin'...
Congratulations on the Voodoo decision.
You know it could've gone
the other way, don't you?
Why, exactly?
You go with Buddy Garrity
out to a seedy little motel
to meet a kid named Voodoo.
Along with a manager.
And then ol' Buddy,
he starts promising things.
- What kind of things?
- He starts promising things.
But you didn't do that, sugar?
I think sometimes that for anyone to do
what I do it is damn near impossible
to not to sell your soul just
a little bit down the river.
Think you just keep doing
what you're doing, Coach.
- Taking it one day at a time.
- You know what I really love?
Mm-hmm.
I love football.
- I love football.
- I know.
I love those kids.
Hey, Matt.
- Hi, Julie. H--how's it going?
- Um, not bad.
How was dance rehearsals?
Dance--It's--
It's going really good, you know.
We have, uh, like,
three practices a week now.
Um, the girls are doing
really good, so...
- That's good.
- Yeah.
Uh, is--Is your dad around?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Um... Dad, Saracen's here.
What's going on?
You all right?
Yeah.
What's up?
Kaster didn't say anything racist.
Thought you said you weren't outside.
I wasn't.
I--I was inside, but...
But I know Kaster.
I've known him a long time, and I don't think
he would say anything like that.
And besides, that wasn't really
the way it was going anyway.
Voodoo's the one who called
Reyes a wetback.
Not Kaster.
And I think Reyes was probably just ...
all riled up...after that.
And then Kaster was just
in the wrong place at the wrong time.
I know I should've said something sooner.
I think I might've been confused
between what was right for the team and what...
And what was right.
Anyway...
sorry I bothered you.
Good night, Coach.
Hey, Matt.
Tell your grandmother
I say hello.
I will.
Good night.
Hey, I'm Coach Taylor.
Yeah, I know who you are.
I was wondering if, uh,
if I could talk to Kurt.
Please.
Hey there, son.
I want to apologize for what happened.
When I get back to school,
every football player's gonna have a
piece of me on a daily basis.
Thanks for the apology, Coach.
I can guarantee you no football
player's gonna come near you.
There is no excuse
what Bobby Reyes did to you.
Remember when we were just junior high
schoolers, Street, sneaking down here?
Dreaming about playing varsity?
You know, things have changed, Tim.
We're still getting
that hunting ranch, Street.
Yeah, and how are we gonna do that
without my NFL money and your whopping 1%?
That's just it.
I think I'm gonna go pro.
You think you can do that?
No.
Nope.
But, I mean, that's just
the money part anyways.
We can figure that out.
Best friends, right? Wasn't that
always more important than football?
No.
Not always.
It is now.
Three of us.
We'll rise up.
Together.
Get through anything.
Anything at all.
Have a seat.
What's up, Coach?
I was down there trying to help you,
and you looked me right in the eye and you lied.
I'm not wrong, am I?
Can you even admit the truth?
That boy didn't call you
any names, did he?
No, sir.
You went and you beat the hell
out of that kid
and then you made up a lie
and ditched everything onto him.
That's a hell of a position
you put me in, isn't it?
Come on, Coach. I had to lie, Coach.
You know I had to lie.
I was scared, Coach.
You need to pack up your personals and clear
out your locker. You're off the team.
You can't do that to me, Coach.
Football's all I got.
You screwed yourself real good.
I believe in you,
but I cannot help you here.
You are on your own at this point
and I'm gonna tell you what I suggest.
You go over to the guidance counselor office
and you start working on your anger problems.
There's nothing else
I can do for you.
Go clear it out.
Hold your water, lineman!
Hold your water! Here we go.
Hut!
- Aw, come on, Matt.
- Come on, let's go!
- Nice play, Voodoo.
- Take a break, Matt.
Hey, get in here.
Coach--
Coach, why you got me
playing D?
Get back to practice, son.
All due respect, I got a state ring sitting
in my drawer and it's not for defense.
With all due respect, you can go
sit on that bench if you like.
Hustle up, guys!
Guess who came in for counseling today.
Bobby Reyes.