Why she staring at him like that?
You really want me to tell you why?
I could.
You're not gonna want to hear it.
All I'm saying is she's my girlfriend,
all right?
She probably shouldn't be staring off
at Swedish people like that.
Why don't you go over
and punch him in the face?
Is that what you would do?
In some situations,
you need to ask yourself
WWRD?
What would Riggins do in this situation?
He would walk over to him--
Riggins would not be in this situation,
cause Riggins
is captain of the SS Tatas over there.
He's probably slept
with literally, like,
half of the girls
at Dillon High, not to mention
some of their moms and sisters--
Look. That's the guy that's
gonna give me the ball.
Smile, man, it's gonna be a good year.
- Come on, smile.
- What's up, Smash?
All you got to do is hang
on at my coattails.
When did he turn into such a tool?
This is ridiculous.
It's never gonna happen.
Don't be negative.
You don't know what could happen.
What if I made team, and--
she starts to see me...
- I need to ask you.
- Spark something inside her.
Why are you trying out for the team?
Because you're gonna get hurt.
- Don't be cynical.
- Cynical?
Hi, honey.
You watch my stuff for me, please?
No, no mom.
You need to leave right now.
How many times have we talked
about this? Don't come to the pool.
We've already been through this.
- This is the only place-- Excuse me.
- You can't show up all the time, mom.
- Sweetie, I don't show up all the time.
- Can't you go to a different pool ?
I miss your father,
you never talk to me anymore,
there ain't a room in the house
big enough to contain me.
I'm getting in the water.
You're just here checking up on me--
I am not checking up on you.
That is ridiculous.
- You're just trying to spying on me.
- Honey,
I'm not spying on you at all.
I am curious about your life.
I enjoy being in the pool--
Am I gonna have to help you
out of the pool?
I am curious.
I am curious about "the Swede,"
I'm curious about what Matt
thinks about the Swede,
I'm curious about--
You don't--
You're embarrassing me.
Honey?
I think my water just broke.
Your water can't break, mom.
You have another three weeks.
Either I just peed in the pool
or my water's broke.
I can't do it.
No, I can't do it anymore.
I'm too tired.
Just hang in there, okay?
Where the hell's your father?
- Tami Taylor's room?
- Yeah, in 206.
Hey, baby, hey baby.
Can I stand here?
Oh, honey.
- Oh, I'm so happy to see you.
- How are you, huh?
We need just a little bit more, darling.
I'm gonna get you this baby,
but I can't do it alone.
I hate you. It's coming.
Welcome to the family.
2x01: LAST DAYS OF SUMMER
Transcript: www.swsub.com
Synchro: Andy / Ju
www.top-series.net
This is slammin' Sammy Meade, folks
and welcome back
to another glorious year
of Panther football.
It's summer.
It's 120 damn degrees on the gridiron,
and the Panthers are entering
the fiery gates of hell week,
and I for one could not be happier.
Will our new coach, Bill McGregor,
the Tennessee tyrant
known for winning State titles,
be able to fill the shoes
of the great Eric Taylor?
The art of the last year's
championship offense is back:
QB Matt Saracen, highly ranked
running back "Smash" Williams,
and hard-hitting full back Tim Riggins.
That leaves the most exciting part
of the pre-season,
new talent.
Who knows which fresh face
might impress the new coach,
and win a job
on this great Dillon Panther team
come opening day.
- Get ready.
- Here we come.
Come on, let's go little dancer.
Welcome home, baby Grace.
Here's your new home.
This is where it's all gonna happen.
It's all gonna happen right here.
Jules!
I had asked jules to clean this up.
Look who's home. Say hey.
She's opening up her eyes.
So she can say, "Hey, big sis."
- Why is her head so pointy?
- That's normal, sweetheart.
How come you didn't clean this place up?
Because I didn't have time.
I got to go to work. Sorry.
I thought you were taking today off.
It's your sister's first day at home.
I have to go to work, okay?
I love you guys. I'll be home tonight.
Say hi to the Swede.
Who's the Swede?
Someone she's flirting with at the pool.
I can't believe this mess.
What about the Saracen?
She's dating the Saracen,
and she's flirting with the Swede.
Welcome home, sweetheart.
I think this whole football thing
is a terrible idea.
You've mentioned that a few times.
But does my shoulder
look swollen to you?
You think your daddy's
gonna love you anymore?
I do actually.
- I am burning up.
- Me too.
Would you mind doing my back for me?
- Do what?
- My back.
Yeah. Of course.
Thanks.
It's just...
You got to be sure
to put on several coats
throughout the day.
Got a little bit too much.
Are you ready?
Actually, got a--
I got a show on Thursday.
At the Bend.
Oh, the Bend.
- That's a cool place.
- You've been to the Bend?
- Yeah, a few times.
- Well, you should come by.
- Really?
- Yeah. Yeah, what do you mean?
- Okay.
- Yeah, it starts at eleven.
Yeah, I guess,
- I guess I'll see yo there, then.
- I guess.
- All right.
- Yeah, don't be late.
As you were born the first time
from broken waters,
you will be born again today,
from the broken waters of baptism
and baptism is going to--
Upon the profession of your faith
to the word of God, I baptise you
in the name of the Lord Jesus Christ.
Ladies!
You guys want to make
some memories tonight?
I'm thinking like 7:30.
Where's my flier, Garrity?
No one would be happier
to save your soul than me, Tim.
Christ Teen Messengers.
What was that, like a cult or something?
It's young Christians coming together
to worship and spread the word of Jesus.
You look good. Like, real good.
It's probably because
yesterday I was baptized
and accepted Jesus
as my lord and savior.
What did you do recently?
I had a three-way with
the Stratton sisters.
I wouldn't go around town bragging about
how you spent your entire summer
in a drunken stupor.
So what you're saying is you're jealous.
Yeah, Tim. I'm jealous.
Just so you know...
You're still number one.
You're still the best I've ever had.
- It's true.
- Don't talk to me like that.
Good-bye.
- Enjoy Jesus.
- Enjoy your depraved hedonism.
- Oh, I will.
- So will I.
- I mean Jesus, not Hedonism.
- Of course.
Jerk.
Well, I don't care what the man said,
I'm not gonna take off your uniform.
It's really not that big of a deal,
grandma.
So we don't need any...
any of that meat stuff.
Oh, my Lord.
How are you doing?
How are you?
Coach Eric Taylor.
How are you, son?
Miss you.
How you doin'?
How come you didn't come to see Gracie?
Because I had two two-a-days, so..
- Julie's been telling about it.
- How are you and Julie doing?
Good. Why?
I mean, did she say
anything to you?
She supposed to say something?
Something I'm supposed to know?
- No, I just didn't know--
- Come see the kid.
I was gonna come and see,
you know, a lot of football,
and she's been lifeguarding, so...
I didn't wanna just stop by.
- All right.
Don't just stand by and watch it happen.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
I do. Thanks, coach.
Take care.
Hey, Carl.
This-- this Friday?
Well, I got football practice,
then I might go work out...
After that. I'm serious.
Well, call me if you want to see
a movie or something, okay?
What happened?
Who was that?
I- I think that was him.
Was who?
The guy who attacked me.
- Come here.
- I'm going to bed.
I've been at Lois.
Come here, I want to talk to you.
I just want to go to bed, okay?
I have work in the morning.
How are you doing?
Good.
How are you and Matt doing?
Fine.
Good.
Who is this Swedish guy?
And what does this have to do with you?
What does this have to do with me?
I'm your father, that's what
it has to do with me.
So you decide to come back
after eight months in Austin
and have these deep long conversations?
You are so hypocritical.
I'm done. I'm tired.
I'm going to bed.
Come here.
Come here, come here!
Six!
Blue eight!
Hut!
Outside!
Riggins, you gotta cut it.
Come on, Riggins.
Come on.
- What's Buddy doing here?
- Watching practice.
I run closed practes.
Send him home.
- How are you?
- Hot enough for you?
I've sweat runnin'
off my sweat, bro.
This is awkward, but I'm gonna
have to ask you to leave.
It's not pop warner. Keep your head up
like a man and stick him.
If he wants me to leave, then he needs
to come over here and tell me himself.
Cut him down. Do it again.
Come on, Riggins.
Black nine!
Who does-- who does he think pays
- his bloody damn salary.
- Would you tell him later?
Come on, let's go.
You know what?
You are disgusting.
You are miserable, miserable!
A miserable, god dang
football player. You have no potential.
You're just walking through this..
What did you say to me?
Guys like you, okay?
- With no heart--
- Oh, I got no heart?
Here. This helmet...
For your new full back,
good luck opening day.
Riggins!
You do not walk away from me, number 33!
The point is...
Is that she--
she told me to lotion her up.
Maybe she just didn't want
to get sunburn.
All I'm saying is
I was literally inches away
from, you know, copping a feel.
It's a good picture of him, though.
It's a great picture of the Smash.
He really looks like a captain.
I'm gonna go get some cheetos.
What's going on?
What you doin'?
Nothin'.
Just-- just hanging.
There's this party
at lake Orio Thursday.
I was kind of hoping
maybe you'd come, please.
I was just gonna stay at home,
and take it easy, read a book.
The whole team is gonna be there.
And everyone that's got a girlfriend,
their girlfriend's gonna be there.
And since you're kind
of my girlfriend I was
kind of hoping you'd be there.
Look, it's just, you mean a lot to me,
and I don't want to just...
Lose you.
It sounds great.
I'll try to make it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Thursday.
- Okay.
- You're gonna love this.
- That's it.
It's tofu-- come on, one more.
Tofu and porcini mushroom,
it's got some onions in there,
- some brown rice.
- I'm good.
Got some beans there, we all set?
- There you go.
- Looks delish!
- Enjoy.
- Aren't we forgetting sothing?
No, no.
Of course.
Thank you, Lord, for this food
that we are about to receive
and for your wisdom, Lord.
I pray that you will guide me
and everyone at this table
to help respect you,
and make good choices.
For exemple, to not take
advantage of the vulnerability
of a recently separated,
but not yet divorced woman.
And in turn, to give others
at the table the strength to remember
that a mother of three should not
be wearing skinny jeans.
Amen.
Bon appetit.
- Enjoy.
- Looks good.
Please, sleep.
Little girl.
- Is she down good?
- Could you make some cookies?
Thank you.
You're nice to me.
Carl called.
They need me to come back Friday.
Which Friday?
This Friday?
I thought you had two weeks.
Bottom line, they need me back.
It's not my decision,
*
he passed the buck up on his top.*
And uh...
We've been through this before,
we just have to deal with it.
You know the drill, what happens.
You know, I don't have a choice.
The fact of the matter is,
I don't have a choice.
I mean, it's--
You know it's what I do.
I can't go, and I can't,
I can't do this thing half-assed.
I do it half-assed,
it doesn't help anyone.
And I can't.
No, I can't.
You know?
I really need you to talk.
That's it?
I'll be back in a little while, okay?
Dog thinks he is the boss.
He's not the boss. You are the boss.
You must be dominate him.
*
- Look what the cat *agged in.
- Unlock the door!
You heard that...
Tennessee Hillbilly stonewalled me.
He won't even talk to me.
Locked me out of practice.
Told mike mcGill that I was...
an annoying nuisance.
Can you imagine that?
That is hard to...
There is nothing I love more
than Dillon Panthers,
I always have and you know
that I'm trying to help.
That's all I'm trying to do.
That's all I've ever cared about.
How long have you been sleeping here?
I don't sleep here much.
I work late sometimes.
It's comfortable, you know,
the neon lights.
- Congratulations on the baby.
- Thank you.
Can I speak to you for a minute?
- Out here.
- Yeah.
I'll be righback.
What were you doing
at soccer practice tonight?
- What you're talking about.
- I saw you there, buddy.
I do not understand
how a smart, beautiful,
intelligent woman
could fall
for a little tree-hugger who makes
seven dollars an hour
at health food store.
He owns that store first of all,
were you at my meditation group
the other night too?
I have a right to protect my children,
if I think their mother is becoming
a part of some kind
of cult or something.
You know what,
- do whatever!
- Don't go to soccer
- practice again.
- Do whatever you want.
But he is not gonna turn
my children into communists,
with all these hippie ideas.
Is it-- He here?
That's him? You here?
You brought him here?
He's in my-- You get out of my truck!
Open the damn door.
Get out.
Unlock that door.
- You come out of there.
- You gotta calm down!
Unlock that door.
Get in the car.
Don't make me--
Stop, stop.
It's all right.
Come on, Riggins.
- What you gonna have for dinner?
- I think I'm gonna have a salad.
- I got some chicken.
- I got to get in shape.
I'm gonna learn how to surf.
- That'd be good.
- If not now, when?
Come on.
Pick it up, Riggins!
Come on!
I think he's had enough, coach.
He owes me five more.
- Come on, Riggins.
- Five more, son.
All right, Riggins, you're done.
First off, I would like to say that...
This is your team.
And 100 percent I am in support
of you, and the decisions you make,
and the leadership of the team.
Go on.
I know Tim Riggins really well.
Both on and off the field.
He's one of my closest friends.
Leaning on him like that isn't
gonna get you any results, sir.
Well...
You got a decision to make, Jason.
You can come to the games
Friday nights, and be some kind of...
town symbol
some kind of mascot.
Or you can come to Friday night games,
and you can be
a football coach.
But you can't be both.
They can't be your friends.
- Hey, honey.
- Hey.
I want you home
by eleven o'clock, all right?
Mom said eleven thirty.
I don't care what she said.
I want you home by eleven o'clock.
Your absentee father says
eleven o'clock,
but of course if you'd like to make it
ten thirty, we can make that happen too.
- Whatever.
- And if Lois
should even look at any alcohol
this evening, I want you
to give me a call, you understand?
Where are your shoes?
I'm not wearing shoes, dad.
Ty. Are you okay?
- What took you so long?
- I came just as soon you call...
- Where do you hear the noises from?
- Out here.
- Be careful.
- You stay here, okay.
I'm gonna check the perimeter.
- Near the tree.
- Make sure everything's okay.
I'm sure it's nothing.
All right, your knight
in shining armor has arrived.
Tyra, it's a skunk.
Tyra, that's a skunk.
- Let me in in the front.
- A skunk?
I just don't want to get sprayed.
It's fine. There's none back here.
I've to go home.
My mom gonna beat the hell out of me.
We should've gone to the party.
It's okay. You can go.
- What?
- No, it's okay. I'll find a ride.
I'm not just going to leave you here.
I swear. It's fine, Lois.
Call me later, okay?
Man, I'm in Tyra Collette's
bathroom right now.
Why are you calling me from
- the bathroom?
- You gotta try to keep up me here,
cause I've got like 45 seconds
and I really need to get
your advice on something.
I'm on Tyra's couch.
We're watching Fried Green Tomatoes.
Everything's going great.
And I need to figure out
how to get my arm around her.
No, no. Look,
does she want you to touch her?
I'm not calling you for relationship
advice, I'm calling you
to find just some technique.
Just sit down close to her
and try, I don't know,
rub your arm against hers.
If she doesn't hit you
or doesn't seem weird
then try to put your arm around her.
All right.
Me, once I get my arm around her,
things will just kind
of fall into place,
this has been like a long time coming.
Anyways, I got to go.
How you doing at the party?
- It kinda sucks. Julie never showed up.
- That sounds great, man.
I'll call you later and let you
know how this goes.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Are you hungry?
Are you hungry?
- Yeah. I'm hungry.
- Let's go get some food.
Well, yeah. Come again.
It's good to see you.
What's up? You came.
Did you like it?
It was totally amazing.
I was pretty nervous.
I don't know.
No, you guys looked awesome up there.
Well, come-- Just come again.
Just don't say enything else.
No, I mean, it was emotional
and heartbreaking.
I'm adamant.
You gotta come again.
Babe. I gotta go.
Julie, this is Meg.
Meg, Julie.
Julie. Your friend from the pool.
Your high school bud. It nice
to meet you. Antoine loves you.
We have this party. And if I don't
show up, my sister is going to kill me.
- It was nice to meet you.
- Yeah, you too.
I'm really happy you came.
You gotta be kidding me.
Can we just go?
Can we go?
Yeah.
No, no, we can't go.
We can go as soon as you tell me
what the hell you' doing
at a place like this at 12:30 at night,
and then we can go.
I know I'm grounded and everything.
Can you just really
not yell at me right now?
Can I tell you something?
I'm leaving early.
I have to leave tomorrow night,
all right?
I'm not gonna be back maybe
for a few weeks.
So you being my daughter,
I'd sort of like
to know what the hell is going on.
I came here to chasing some boy.
And got completely humiliated
because guess what, he has a girlfriend.
I misread every stupid signal.
What's going on with you and Matt,
what's wrong with that?
There is nothing wrong,
that's the point, okay?
Matt's perfect, right?
And we're the hit couple.
But I just-- I see him turning into you
and-- and me turning into my mom.
And that just terrified
the crap out of me.
And. I'm 16.
There is just--
There has to be more than this.
And I just...
I feel so guilty for feeling like this.
Listen to me.
You can leave Matt.
No one is gonna love you any less.
You realize that, don't you?
You got that?
The other guy sounds to me, like,
you know, he's...
he's some other guy.
He's just some other guy.
Hell with him.
You're all right.
It's all good.
We really miss having you around.
OK, so we got Kit Kats, Nachos.
- Okay.
- You get the Pringles.
Kit Kats, Nachos, Pringles. Is that it?
yes, and you are on your own,
because I forgot that the
Collette account has a little overdue.
- Pringles, Nachos--
- And don't forget the Ding Dongs.
Are you gonna eat all them?
I'm not gonna help you out.
'Cause I'm tryin' to cut down.
You know I'll eat all at.
Okay, that's true.
My knight in shining armor.
I'm gonna go get some Pringles.
Alright, good luck.
How was the movie?
If I was on leave, that 'cause of you.*
I ain't telling what I would have done.
What the hell are you doing here?
Why are you hanging out with a loser?
We could have us some fun.
Don't touch me.
You get away from me!
Get away from me!
Get off her!
I'm gonna be back for you.
Oh my God.
What are we supposed to do now?
We gotta go to the hospital.
Tyra, what did I do?
He's not--
Tyra, where the hospital?
The hospital's close, I swear.
He stopped breathing, Tyra.
He's dead.
I killed him.
- What are you doing?
- I'm gonna call my dad. He's a cop.
- He'll know how--
- No, just stop it.
Tyra, we're not-- We can't--
I mean, we can't.
What else are we gonna do?
Presenting the 2006 championship ring
to Bradley Colby, Greg Rawlins.
The next championship ring
presented Mathew Saracen.