The MRI shows a damage to the cord
at the C7-T1 juncture.
I just want to know if I'm
gonna be able to walk again.
Jason's paralyzed.
You are Jason Street,
and I am Lyla Garrity.
And everything is
going to work out
just the way we planned it.
He's down on the ground.
He is down.
Who is that, Street?
You think little Matt Saracen
can get it done?
I don't want you thinking
out here.
I want you to throw the ball.
Dolia runs deep,
hit him deep.
He's open on the break,
hit him on the break.
You got four seconds
or a five-step drop!
That's all you got.
You up for this?
Yes, sir.
We are live
from Panther Stadium,
in Dillon, Texas.
And we are ready
to play football.
It was just a week ago
this town was rocked
by the tragic injury to our
quarterback, Jason Street,
a young man who embodied
the hopes and dreams
Jason, are you sure
you want to watch the game?
I can just...
Leave it, please.
Now, the question is,
will Coach Taylor
be able to survive
without his star quarterback?
And can young Matt Saracen
step up to lead this team?
Saracen's only taken
about three snaps
his entire career..
We're going with I right, power.
44 tomahawk, on one.
Ready, break.
Tonight, it's all about
the ground game.
Coach Taylor's
gonna have to hope
Saracen can get the ball
into the hands
of their outstanding
running back Smash Williams,
if the Panthers are gonna
have a shot.
Come on, Matt.
Saracen's into the count.
Defense pushing in.
They're expecting run.
He opens to the left,
hand off to Williams.
Wait, Saracen keeps
on a bootleg.
Oh, and he gets drilled
as he lets that ball go.
He's got Dolia at the 45.
He makes the catch.
To the 40.
What an inspired call
by Coach Taylor.
He could go all the way!
Go.
He's to the 20,
to the 15.
I don't think
they're gonna catch him.
Oh, Dolia gets stripped
at the 10-yard line.
And the Rattlers come up
with the ball.
What a gutsy call
by Coach Taylor,
but, man, did that just
blow up in his face.
Execution!
Where the hell's
the execution out there?!
Huh?!
My God, we oughta be
beating these bums
by 40 points!
Riggins,
you're supposed to be
one of the toughest guys
in the district!
They are handing your ass
to you, son!
You better get your head
in the game.
Hut, hut!
Smash...north, south.
North, south.
If you want to dance
with these boys out there,
you invite them
to the prom!
- They spottin' me every...
- What?!
You got something to say to me?!
Call some play-action
to open me up, Coach.
- They see me coming.
- What?!
I can't hear you.
What?!
Our Dillon Panthers
are runnin' out of time.
Deep into the fourth quarter.
Come on, coach!
Run the football now!
There're only 15 seconds
left in this contest, folks.
And it is third and goal
from the 9.
The Panthers down by six points.
And they have all but
self-destructed here tonight.
Although you've got to
admire the courage
of young Matt Saracen.
This quarterback has really
played hard,
with a lot of heart.
Read your defenses.
Come on, Saracen.
Hut!
Saracen on the fake.
He drops back.
He's in trouble.
He beats 'em
out around the right side.
Oh, he's got legs on him.
The 15, the 10.
The 5.
He's gonna score.
He's down to the 3.
Bringing it hard
to the goal line.
And dropped
right at the goal line.
The Panthers are saying
touchdown,
but we are gonna wait to see
what the referee's call is.
No touchdown.
Damn  it.
They had it.
They had 'em beat.
That is it
for our Dillon Panthers.
They have lost
a heartbreaker here,
in a game that they should have
easily dominated tonight.
And I'll tell you,
Coach Taylor is off
to a disastrous start
this season, folks.
Saracen!
That was a good game.
But not good enough.
Not nearly good enough!
It ain't hard, Tim.
Hell, it's not
rocket science.
You beat the living dog snot
out of those guys.
You win the game,
then you go out and you get yourself
a little piece of tail.
What part of that equation
don't you understand?
You guys just bent over
and grabbed your ankles.
You shamed your good name.
Yeah, I feel really awful
about that.
Speaking of pieces of tail,
Lyla Garrity.
- You're not...
- What?
I can't understand you when
you're not moving your mouth,
Tim... you're not speaking.
Hi, is Tim here?
Uh, no.
Not at the moment.
Well, can you please tell him
that Lyla Garrity stopped by?
and I will be in the hospital
with  his best friend
Jason Street!
Today and tomorrow,
and the next day, and so on.
So whenever he wants
to visit is fine.
But Jason is asking for him,
so sooner is better.
Could you please tell him that
when you see him?
I'll give him
the message, sweetie.
Thanks.
Matt, I've been working
on this theory.
You know what?
Can you just
help me out?
I really don't want
my grandmother to see this.
Funny you should mention that,
because she's at the core
of my theory.
Tell me this.
Dillon hasn't lost to South Milbank
in what, like, 20 years?
- 17.
- 17, right.
So why do they lose now?
No, I know what you're thinking,
and that's not it.
'Cause you know you played
a good game last night.
I mean, that's not what
I'm talking about.
What I'm talking about is
the supernatural.
You're retarded.
In a lot of cultures,
they believe older women
to be very powerful witches.
Oh, you think
my grandma is a witch.
Look, my grandmother
can barely remember
how to work the phone
half the time.
How's she gonna put a spell
on the Dillon Panthers?
Plus, why would she
put a spell...
Matt?
What are y'all doin' out here?
I'm just cleaning up
a little bit, Grandma.
Oh, well, when you get done,
I want you to go out back
and water the children.
Y-You mean the flowers,
Grandma?
Is that what you mean?
Yeah.
Just what I said, wasn't it?
Hey, losers!
Come on, you got it.
Lift it up.
There you go, give it a shot.
Lift, lift, lift, lift, lift.
Unh! All right.
All right.
Relax.
I want to do this again.
I can do it again.
- You don't have to do it.
- I can do it.
Not today.
Let's wait for tomorrow.
All right?
Down you go.
It's all right. Okay?
Thank you.
There you go.
- All right, you good?
- Yes.
Hey, baby.
Hey, Danielle.
Hey, Lyla,
how you doing?
Good. How are you?
All right, Jason,
same time tomorrow?
Yes, ma'am.
- I'll be here.
- All right.
Hi.
Boy, were you missed
last night.
We got spanked.
It's like no one knew
what to do without you.
I'll tell you what,
I would not wanna be
Coach Taylor right now,
that is for sure.
Just give him some time,
all right?
He'll be fine.
So,  we're expecting
a huge turnout
for the pancake supper
tomorrow.
The what?
The pancake supper.
The benefit.
Oh, yeah.
Sorry.
To help with the cost
of the rehab facility.
Yeah.
It's exciting going
to that rehab place.
You know why?
Why is that?
Because that's where you're
gonna get your legs back.
Lyla...
You and me,
we can get through anything.
What's up?
- Oh--
- What?
Um, excuse me.
Nurse?
Lyla.
Something's wet down there.
Dolores,
what's going on?
Excuse me.
- Jason, it's your catheter.
- Oh, God.
We're gonna take care of you.
Can you give us a minute?
Um, I--
Just a minute.
Go ahead.
You're going to be fine, Jason.
Hey.
Tim.
- Hey.
- How you doing, honey?
Hi. I'm okay.
How are--
How are you and Mr. Street doing?
We're, uh--
We're holding out.
Jason's been asking about you.
Yeah.
I've been meaning to go
to see Jay, and--
I know, you're busy
with football and all.
Tim, just 'cause Jason's
in the hospital
doesn't mean
you can't come over
for Tuesday night dinner.
Thank you ma'am.
I'll, uh--
I'll call you.
Get some rest, okay?
Take care of yourself.
Yes,  ma'am.
Am I gonna see you tonight
at the pancake supper?
Yes, ma'am.
Good.
Bye-bye, honey.
I'll tell you what,
if she did let us get a dog,
the kind of dog
we're gonna get
is a brown Labrador.
And if it's not
a brown Labrador,
we're not getting a dog.
Then we can name it,
like, Fluffy, or Spike.
Hey, Jill.
Two burgers, with bacon.
Onion rings, Diet Coke.
- Extra cheese.
- Spicy chicken
sandwich for mom. Get Mom's--
And Dad's.
Don't do it with
the three hamburgers.
- Go sit down.
- Too much dead cow.
She wants onion rings,
diet cola.
Um, we need two burgers.
I need a spicy chicken to go.
And I'll have the biggest
French fries you have.
You're Eric Taylor's girl, right?
Uh, yeah.
I was just wondering if y'all
had started packing yet.
Uh...
Things can get real
unpleasant around here
when you lose.
Can I help you?
I was just telling her
how it works around here
when you lose football games.
If you got a problem,
you can talk to me.
You don't have to talk
to my daughter about it.
I do have a problem.
I have a problem with you
pissing our season away
calling them dumb-ass plays.
I'm here with
my 15-year-old daughter.
You know?
So I'm just gonna
walk away right now.
That's really great
of you, though.
I sure appreciate that.
Come on, let's go.
You got no guts.
See, that's why you ain't gonna
never have one of these.
All right.
Don't listen to him.
Don't listen to that.
You won't even finish out
the year here, Taylor.
You will not last
one year.
These are some big horses
we're running up against.
Their offensive line averages
290 across the board.
Matt, how big's
our biggest guy?
Oh, Pudnick goes about 265.
When you run up against
the biggest boy on the block,
you gotta be faster.
Velocity kills,
gentlemen.
We need to be faster.
We will outlast them.
We will go above and beyond.
Smash, what the hell
you doin', son?
Hey, Coach, look, listen.
Me and the guys
have been talking.
Look, we got a tough game
coming up.
Shouldn't we work on
some hand-offs?
Give our QB some practice?
I mean, seriously,
we gotta get that boy
up to speed.
Maybe we should
get him a tutor.
We all know what the problem is.
Look, the guy's a weak link.
I'll tell you what.
Everybody listen up!
I was gonna let everyone
get out of here early
this morning.
But since you're
in such good shape,
What do you say
we run five more?
- Coach, are you--
- How 'bout ten extra ones?
- I don't see how this--
- 15 more!
I can count real high, Smash.
How high do you think
I can count?
You want to test me?!
Let's go!
Pick it up!
There he is.
You wanted to talk to me,
Mr. Garrity?
Hello, Mr. Deitz,
how you doing?
Well, so there's this
stud quarterback
out of Louisiana.
He's displaced.
Katrina victim.
And he's over here now.
Name's Ray Tatom.
Voodoo Tatom?
You know him?
I know of him.
He's gonna be over
in Marlsboro
Thursday afternoon.
At that old lot over there,
about 2:00.
What I thought was
maybe you and I could
just kind of
ease over there.
You know, drive over there
and check him out.
See if he lives up
to the hype.
Let's go, Smash!
Get on there!
Pick it up!
Yes, sir.
Hey, you get the napkins
and stuff?
Yep, we're all set.
Good.
We better hurry.
All the girls are gonna
be there soon.
If no one's there
to tell 'em what to do,
they'll just fool around.
Slow down.
There's time.
So, your birthday's tomorrow.
What do you want to do?
I'm having dinner with Jason
in the hospital.
- Oh, honey...
- What?
You've been spending
so much time there lately.
I thought we could go out.
No, Mom, it's already
all planned.
Sorry.
Lyla, are you sure this isn't all
just too much?
I mean, you're at the hospital
every day.
You'd do it for Dad,
wouldn't you?
Well, yeah, but he's
my husband.
Well, I'm marrying Jason
someday.
Honey, you need to
accept the reality
of the situation.
I mean, this is a terrible thing
that has happened.
And  maybe you should
talk to someone.
He's coming back
from this, okay?
He just is.
That's all there is to it.
He needs me right now.
*people are saying that time*
*Will take care of people like me*
*Say I'm livin' too fast, boy"*
*And no, I can't last*
*For much longer* *
Yep, Matt, the river
of Rally Girls
- has pretty much run dry.
- Will you shut up?
Look at him go at it.
Ew, gross.
All right, wanna go get
a turkey burger?
Hey, Julie, I got you
some soy sausage.
Hey, Matt.
Thank you, but I'm actually
on my way out.
So you can have my pancakes.
All right, I'll see you later.
- All right.
- Bye.
Damn.
I heard about your new job.
- Mm-hmm. Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Jason Street is probably
never gonna play football again.
You know about as well
as I do.
And Matt Saracen is not
gonna take us to State.
The last school counselor
killed herself.
- That's right.
- I'm sorry?
Yeah, she killed herself
with pills, I think.
I was just thinking
it was about time
for us to move
on the Katrina kid.
Let me just say
one thing about that.
I hope this is
on the up and up,
because I really got
enough headaches going on
right now as it is.
Just let me handle it..
I just need you to
look at the tapes for me,
if you will.
Will you just look
at the tape, Coach?
Just look at it for me.
All right. All right.
Good. Look who it is.
My little ray of sunshine.
Not now, Smash.
Have you seen Tim?
He said he was gonna be here.
No, I haven't seen Rig.
He probably passed out
cold somewhere.
Let's talk about us.
I don't think so.
Hey, dumb-ass.
Just gonna ignore me?
Think I'll go away?
That's what I keep hoping,
but you don't seem to want
to get the message.
You know, you're such
a big tough guy.
You can't even go see Jason
in the hospital.
I mean, damn, it, Tim,
grow a set, why don't you!
'Cause we both know
that's what this is all about.
Hey, Tyra.
How's Smash?
Was he good?
Did you have a nice time?
Nothing happened.
Not really.
Besides, don't pretend like
you haven't slept with
half the Rally Girls.
We sure do have
something special here, Tyra.
You know,
maybe you're right.
Maybe I am wasting my time.
'Cause you are just another
mediocre football player.
who's gonna grow up
to drink himself to death.
Maybe we should just
end this right now.
I'll see you around then.
I am serious, Tim.
Are you listening to me?
If I get in that car
right now,
I'm never coming back.
Do you understand?
I get it.
That's it?
Breaking up for real,
and that's all you have to say.
That was great
All right, Tatom can
throw the ball.
Can he scramble under pressure?
Keep watching.
Kid's team went to the state
championship last year.
Broke three tackles
on a 40-yard touchdown.
You've seen this tape already?
Yeah, I was over
at Buddy's last weekend.
Barbecue.
I didn't know y'all
were such good friends.
Hey, Tim.
Here's that paper on East of Eden.
I misspelled a bunch
of the words
so this time,
it'll look like yours.
And your biology homework
is on the bottom.
Thanks.
So I heard that you
and Tyra broke up.
Is it true?
I suppose it is.
Yeah.
Hey, Tim.
Bye, Lyla.
Tim? Hey.
We're having
a prayer meeting
for Jason this afternoon.
You wanna come?
What are we
praying for, Lyla?
A new spine for Jay?
Tim.
I know you never do anything
you don't want to do,
and I guess that's fine.
But don't insult me.
Excuse me, Mrs. Taylor?
Hey, Matt.
- Hey--oh.
- Come on in.
We'll do--
We'll do the rest later?
Yes, thank you.
Hey, Matt,
how are you?
How's it going?
I need to drop pre-calculus,
so that I can go
to morning practices.
Oh, okay.
When are you gonna take
pre-calculus?
Uh, next semester,
I guess,
when football is done.
All right, as long as
you take it.
Yeah, I'm gonna take it.
You sure?
Yeah.
Okay.
I know I saw drop cards
somewhere.
How have you been doing?
How are you holding up
through all this?
It's been kind of
a crazy time, has--
Drop card!
Here you go.
You can fill that out.
I'll sign it.
Yeah, we're gonna do
a lot better
against Arnett Mead,
so, you know,
don't worry about that.
No, but what I mean is
how are you doing?
I mean, you know.
I know your dad's in Iraq,
and that you're living
with your grandma, right?
Yeah, uh, I'm fine.
I mean, Grandma's
going through
one of her good spells
right now.
So that's--
that's good.
There are bad spells sometimes?
I mean, nothing, really.
Just, like, she gets
a little loopy sometimes.
I mean, she'll
put the ice cream
in the cupboard.
Or forget to take her medication,
that kind of stuff.
It's really not--
It's not a big deal.
Is it your responsibility
to make sure she takes
her medication?
Well, there's really
no one else around, so--
Boy, you got a lot on your plate.
I mean, I think
just football itself
is more than
a full-time job.
Yeah, well, I mean,
I really love playing football.
So I just hope
I get to keep playing.
Well, that shouldn't be
a problem.
You're doing a great job.
Yeah, but I keep hearing
that, like, they're trying
to bring in this Katrina
refugee, or something.
This quarterback
from New Orleans.
I never heard anything
about that.
Keep your head up.
Come on, Riggins, let's go.
Hold on to that ball.
Come on, keep digging your legs.
Come on, son.
What's your problem?
You do it again.
Keep your legs moving.
Keep your head up.
Keep digging.
Come on, son, let's go.
Let's go!
Keep your head up.
Keep digging your legs.
Keep digging.
Get over here.
Come here.
I don't see you preparing
for this game, son.
You go hard or you go home.
Come on, now, you're out here,
you give 110%, like everybody else.
You give 110% all the time.
Not just when you feel like it.
Now, come on, son, do it again.
Let's do it again.
Don't do it, son.
Don't do that.
Don't do what I think
you're about to do.
Don't do that.
You don't want
to do that.
Son, don't--
Let him go, Coach.
Listen, he's been watching
the game film
from when Street got hurt.
I have a feeling he thinks
it's all his fault.
What the hell would he think
it's his fault for?
I don't know,
maybe he thought
he might have made
the tackle, or something.
The kid was 30 yards away.
Hey, hey, Coach, listen.
You can blame yourself
for just about anything,
if you think about it
long enough.
Hey, Coach.
Coach. What was that?
Did I just see Tim Riggins
just walk off practice?
You know, that is one thing
that never,
ever would have happened
in the old days.
Ever, you think?
- No.
- No way.
But you know, times have
changed, I guess, huh?
What can I do for you, Buddy?
Well, I just wanted to see
if you want to go with us
over to, you know,
talk to that kid.
That Ray Tatom kid.
Matt Saracen may be
a wild card.
You know one thing I like
about Matt Saracen?
- What's that?
- I don't have to be worried
about recruiting violations.
Who said anything
about recruiting?
I didn't say
anything about recruiting.
This is about that kid
whose whole family
has lost everything--
devastated by Katrina.
It'll help us out,
And we can help him out.
That's all.
That's all there is to it.
I mean, it's a win-win
situation.
Right, Mac?
Whoa! Hey, Coach.
Buddy.
Coach.
What'd I tell you?
I told you he'd be there.
Here it is.
We're here, Vic.
You and everybody else.
Come on in.
Good to see you.
Hey, Voodoo.
Coach.
Good to see you.
How are you, son?
Look here.
This boy and his family have
been through a terrible time.
They lost everything in Katrina.
And they've been bouncing around
from place to place ever since.
The people of Dillon, Texas,
are here
to open their hearts.
We might be able
to provide housing.
Very fine,
very comfortable housing.
They need a fresh start.
We might be able to
get Mr. Tatom over there
a nice new job.
We could arrange that.
We might also even be able to
arrange a little fund.
You know, from some of
the local businesses.
Might be able to help a family
get back up on its feet.
We could set you up.
The town of Dillon
is a generous town.
It's a fine town.
It's a good place
to call home.
He gets a guarantee to start?
Oh, yeah. That's right.
Right, Coach?
You know what, Buddy?
Actually, I got
a problem with that.
I got a problem with that.
Well, now, you know,
the coach and I can work
on the details later.
The point is, you want to
go all the way, son?
I am going all the way.
You want to play college ball,
go to the pros?
That's the idea.
Then you want to be with
the number one team in Texas.
Your representation can squeeze
all it can out of this.
But it's not about new cars
and start-up money.
This is about your future.
And starting positions aren't
handed out in motel rooms.
They're earned on the field.
You want to play
with Arnett Mead, fine.
They're gonna have a short season.
- It's your choice.
- Ma'am.
It was nice to meet you.
I wish all the luck
to your family.
I am telling you
I need some help here.
Yeah, well, what do you
want me to do?
I want you to talk to her.
You know, I love
how you can find time
to take an 80-mile road trip
if the Dillon Panthers
need something.
But if your own daughter--
Hey, hey, she is gonna be fine.
She's a smart girl.
She's got a good head on her shoulders.
How is she fine?
She's living in
a fantasy land..
She's not thinking
about college.
about her own future.
I mean, what's she gonna do?
She's put all her eggs
in one basket,
and I'm sorry to tell you this,
but you and I let her.
Just give it some time.
'Cause she'll get bored,
and she'll move on.
- Mm-hmm. She will.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey.
-Hey, kids.
Hi, Daddy.
Did you eat any dinner?
Uh, no, I didn't.
But I think I can
find something here.
There's chicken in there.
Hey, you didn't tell me
that y'all are getting
a new quarterback
from New Orleans.
Where did you hear that?
Well, Matt Saracen
came in today.
He's feeling real
stressed out about it.
Really?
Matt Saracen's under
a lot of pressure, huh?
Yeah.
Maybe I should go over
to Matt Saracen's house
and make him some Omaltine,
read him a bedtime story.
I think you might want
to just try
a little compassion with him.
- Bye, Daddy.
- Hey, kiddo.
You don't need to be sarcastic.
You know what I think?
I think everybody
in this town is telling me
how to do my job.
And the one thing I think
those kids don't need
is that they don't need compassion.
That's what I think.
You want to know
what else I think?
What they do need to do
is they need to win.
And something else.
You and I,
we need to win, Tami.
We need to win.
Honey, there's Smash.
Channel 13 Sports here
at Hermann Field,
where the Panthers had
a great season last year.
Hopefully they'll repeat
that success this year.
Been a lot of talk
around Dillon
that Taylor's not
the right guy for the job.
Oh, see, look, man,
I can't even mess with you.
You're already trying
to get me in trouble.
Oh, no.
I just want to know where you stand.
Come on, you must have
an opinion.
Oh, yeah, I got an opinion.
I mean, I would,
if I were you.
You've got a lot to lose,
if the coach mismanages
this team.
Look, off the record,
I just think Coach T
ought to be
winning football games.
That's all I'm saying.
See, I knew you had an opinion
about how things were going.
Let it go.
How do you feel
about Friday night?
He's a stupid kid, honey.
Let it go.
Eric, what are you doing?
Just let it go.
Come on.
Mac, I want--
Yes, I did just see it.
I want you to
get the team together,
and I want you to meet me
at the field house
in a half an hour.
Yes, Mac, I know what time it is.
Mac, meet me at the field house
in half an hour.
Thank you.
Bye.
You guys have a nice night now.
Who's calling so late?
I got--
I got it.
Hello?
Now?
Coach is on the phone for you.
Hey...you better
get dressed.
Somebody gonna get that?
Noannie, get the door!
Hi, sweetie.
You get yourself dressed.
We're going on
a little field trip.
I'll see you in the car
in two minutes.
You tell your mother
I say hello.
What's goin' on?
I have no idea.
Let's go.
Everybody off the bus.
Let'go, gentlemen.
Let's go!
What's he gonna do,
kill us all?
Maybe.
Move 'em out.
Line 'em up!
Wind sprints,
up and down the hill.
Let's go.
Go, move it, come on.
If you think you're champions
because you wear
the Panther uniform,
you're wrong!
If you think you're champions
because they give you
a piece of pie at the diner,
you're wrong!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Champions don't complain!
Champions don't give up!
Let's go, Coach.
Send 'em now!
Champions don't give up!
Champions don't complain!
Champions give 200%!
You're not champions
until you've earned it!
Turn around.
Don't stay in them bushes.
Let's go! Let's go!
There you go. Let's go.
Coach, don't you think
maybe they've had enough?
I'll say when
they've had enough.
Clear eyes...
full hearts...
can't lose!
Clear eyes...
full hearts...
can't lose!
Clear eyes,
full hearts,
can't lose!
Clear eyes,
full hearts,
can't lose!
Clear eyes,
full hearts,
can't lose!
Can't lose!
Go!
Cute movie, right?
It was a pretty
sad birthday, huh?
No, it wasn't.
This was exactly
what I wanted, Jason.
Anyway, we'll go
to dinner next year.
When you're all better.
When I'm better?
Lyla, I don't know if you noticed,
but I'm not getting any better.
Can't you see that?
Come on, Jason,
you gotta have faith.
Lyla, stop.
Jason...listen to me.
This is just
a little hiccup.
That's all.
It's a year.
In one year, you'll be
back on track.
Lyla, stop it.
- You will go to Notre Dame--
- Stop it!
Stop!
My legs are never gonna get better.
Ever.
But there are cases,
lots of cases--
And those cases aren't me.
All right?
I don't even have
full use of my hands.
I'll be lucky
if I get that back.
I can't even put
my own shoes on and off.
How can you not see that?!
What the hell is wrong with you?!
I'm just trying to help.
Yeah, well, you're not helping!
You want to help?
Then stop pretending
that everything's okay!
Why are you getting so mad?
Because every night
when I go to sleep,
I dream that
I can walk again.
And every morning,
I wake up,
and I have to accept it
all over again.
And then you walk in here,
all smiles, and acting
like nothing's wrong.
And it's killing me!
So get this through your head.
All right?
My life as we knew it--
over.
Don't say that, Jason.
Football--over.
Notre Dame, going pro,
all that--gone.
You and me?
We're not getting married.
So I need you to do
something for me, all right?
Get out.
Get out!
Don't just look at me,
go!
I'll be back tomorrow
for when they...
transfer you to the rehab facility.
What happened to Jason Street
was nobody's fault.
This is football.
Things happen.
It was an accident.
You understand me?
I didn't even try, Coach.
I didn't even--
You were on the other side
of the field.
It wouldn't have mattered.
It was an accident.
It was not your fault.
Look at me.
I want you to let yourself
off the hook, son.
off the hook.
Yes, sir.
Be smart.
Now, you ever walk out
of one of my practices again,
and I will kick your ass
off the team.
That's a promise.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
You owe me a practice.
You walk home.
We'll call it even.
Coach.
* If I keep holding out *
* Will the light shine through? *
* Under this broken roof *
* It's only rain...*
What are you doing here?
Do you want a ride?
Isn't it past
your bedtime, Lyla?
* Come back *
* I have been planning on... *
What, are you drunk again?
Soon enough, Lyla.
Soon enough.
You know, I thought
God would do me a favor
because I'm such a good girl.
Isn't that the stupidest
thing you've ever heard?
- It's not stupid--
- Shut up, Tim.
What's wrong with you?
Jason is in the hospital,
and you won't even go to see him.
You can walk!
You can walk on your two feet
to get another glass of beer
if that's what
you want to do.
Why don't you get it?
You make me sick.
Why won't you go see him?
He's your best friend.
He asks about you all the time.
Why don't you help me?
Why don't you got
and see him?
Don't hit me.
He's never gonna walk again.
* And these days *
* They linger on *
* Oh, yeah *
* And every night *
* Been waiting for *
* A real possibility *
* That I may meet you
in my dreams *
* Sometimes you're there *
* And you're talking
back to me *
* Come the morning,
I could swear...*
It's 3:00 in the morning.
Where have you been?
Practice.
* It's okay *
Where's Lyla?
I thought she said
she was gonna be here.
All right, you ready?
You gotta shift
your weight back...
- Hey, sorry, I'm late.
- Oh, there you are.
I was just asking about you.
Hey.
I'm real sorry
about last night.
Can we just pretend
like it didn't happen?
Okay.
You know I didn't
mean any of it.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Oh. Thanks, Pop.
- You okay?
- Uh-huh.
Okay, Jason, we're sure
gonna miss you around here.
I'll miss you, too.
Not the room, though.
I'll come back and visit.
Drive it up the field.
Official.
Downfield. Visual.
Good hands and feet, boys.
Good reaction.
Hut!
Do it again, do it again.
No, no, no, step back here.
That a boy.
Never underestimate the power
of a good spanking, Coach.
Yes, sir.
Looking good out there, guys.
Looking good.
We got ourselves
a quarterback, Coach.
Nice speech, Coach.
Did the job.
Welcome aboard, son.
Jack!
Take care of this boy
for me, would you?
Let's go!
What's everyone doing?
What are you looking at?
Let's go, pick it up!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Keep your head up.
Let's get back in it, boys.
Come on, now!
www.forom.com
Capture: Raceman
Sync: Tauri41