You and Timmy see a lot
of each other other now?
No, not really.
Something's up.
I can smell it.
I kind of think she might
be sleeping with my best friend.
Oh, wow!
You must be feeling
the pressure then.
Grady Hunt in the house.
Who?
Mr. Hunt's been scouting
high school ball
since before we were born.
Don't I got what it takes?
Hard to say yet
on strength and size.
On a night when we all expected
Smash Williams to shine,
it is Tim Riggins
who's stepped up.
Come on, baby.
You got game, Phil.
I'm coming.
Look, Jack--
I'm sorry I misfiled that invoice.
But I can get those--
I can get those drill bits
out to Rusty.
They can't--
My point is that there's no one else
that they can go to by that time.
There's no way that they can get it delivered
by Monday. It's $2.
What do you mean Lawerty already did?
That's impossible.
Back!
No, Sir.
Yes, Sir.
Come on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa--
You're kidding me, right?
No, you gotta start
eating better.
Why?
'Cause you had a hell
of a game this past week. All right?
We need to feed the beast.
Keep it up.
I'm not joking about this.
$96.50.
Uh...
Take that back.
And these and this.
$84.23.
I'll get this though.
No, you're not.
Put that back.
- This too, please.
- I am not paying for that.
We do not have money for that.
Put it back.
Billy, you got peas.
Why can't I get what I want?
We're not taking that.
Boys, boys--
I'll buy the damn magazine
if it comes down to it. Okay?
Billy, you go ahead.
I'm gonna get a ride from, uh...
Tyra.
Feel that?
Yeah.
How about this?
You feel that?
No.
- Feel that?
- Yeah.
I gotta ask you something.
Okay.
Is there something happening
between you and Riggins?
No!
Why would you even say that, Jason?
'Cause I saw you in the parking lot
the other night.
You saw us?
Doing what?
I don't know.
No--
Nothing, I guess.
That's crazy.
I love you.
Okay.
Jason, you know that.
- Don't you?
- I do.
I just had to ask.
I'm sorry.
-  I love you.
- I know. I'm sorry.
I love--
And I'm here.
I'm right here.
Okay.
Friday Night Lights
1.08 - Crossing the line
.: www.forom.com :.
Transcript: Raceman
Sync: Tauri41
Whoever told you
to take Nandro was an idiot.
What you need is Oxymetholone.
And you need to stack it with Boldenone.
Is this gonna show up on a drug test?
And how's it gonna affect
my personal life, I mean--
If you're that concerned
about your love life,
maybe you need to get
your priorities straight.
All right, how much?
- 300.
- A month?
Try a week.
All right, can I pay you
next week?
You're good for it.
$1,200.
You know, you've lost your mind.
Momma, come on.
- I need it for SAT prep course.
- Mm-hmm.
Think about it like this--
If I nail my SATs
and get my college scholarship,
you'll be saving yourself thousands.
I'm gonna say this
as plain as I know how.
I ain't got no $1,200.
How about you try studying for your SATs
the old-fashioned way?
Quit runnin' around
with them fast-tail gals
and get your lazy ass upstairs
and start reading.
- Momma--
How's that for your SAT prep course?
I wouldn't come asking
for something like this
if I didn't need it.
Now, look. They tutor you.
They give you practice tests
and quizzes.
And teach you tips
you can't teach yourself.
I need help, Momma.
Please.
Get in there.
Yeah, that's it!
Nice work, Smash!
Let's group!
Keep drivin' now!
Drive him, drive him!
Attaboy!
Coach Taylor.
Hey,  Billy.
- How you doing?
Good to see you again.
How's everything going?
Good. Team's looking good.
Yeah,  I'm trying to keep 'em honest.
Coach, I was wondering
if I could talk to you
for a minute.
They had a hell of a game
last week, didn't they?
- Yes, they did.
- Hey, Steve!
We were kind of wondering
if we should start looking
into applying for school
applications and such.
We hadn't really considered it
before, but...
Coach...
I know there were scouts there last week.
And I'm not really sure
what we're supposed
to do in this kind of situation.
But if it means a future for him...
Hey, I'll tell you what.
You and Tim come out to dinner.
I'll talk to Tami, get the time.
- All right?
- Thank you, sir.
- Yeah.
- I appreciate it.
- All right.
- All right. Take care
Hey, Mike!
Get off the line.
Come on now!
Well, it looks like you missed
the first PSAT test date.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no, sweetie.
It's okay.
I mean, there's another one
coming up before Christmas.
You can do it then.
Do you have any ideas
what electives
you're interested in doing?
Do you have a sense of how you
want to, kind of, proceed?
No.
Are you okay, April?
My Panther wants me
to do a three-way.
- Yeah, and--
- Hey, you know what?
I'm just gonna close this door.
He says that
all the Rally girls do it.
You know, I know a ton who have.
I just, I--
I haven't.
But I really like him.
And, uh--
And he says that if I do it,
I'll be his girlfriend, so...
Matt, that's the thing--
You're not listening to me.
If you look at a girl
like a geometry proof,
the answer is just right in front of you.
It's your job to find
the missing variable.
You gotta solve for x.
Yeah, um, that's actually algebra.
Well, that's actually
not the point.
All right, y'all.
Do you want to go inside and eat?
- No, no, no-
- It's cool.
You're gonna go get it?
You want me to help you?
No, I'm good.
I'd like my social status
to stay intact.
Oh, hey.
Heads up, Matt.
All right.
I'm just trying to make you look okay.
Fix your hat.
Sharpen your pencil, buddy.
Pop quiz.
Hey!
Um, uh, yeah...
Can I get three burgers,
two fries,
and three chocolate swizzlers?
Sounds like you're pretty hungry.
No, just really, really depressed.
Maybe you should get
some more fries.
Uh, it's gonna be $16.45.
Here you go.
Have you, um...
You haven't maybe
thought about, um...
Maybe what I'd asked you
the other night--
About maybe going out?
Uh-- Yeah, yeah.
Um, I'm considering it.
Considering.
I--I just--
- No, no. That's great.
Um...
You know what happened to me today?
No.
This girl comes into my office.
Tells me she's contemplating
having a three-way
with a Dillon Panther.
She's a Rally girl.
Apparently,  it was suggested to her
that that might be part
of her duties
as a Rally girl.
Girl's a sophomore.
Well, you know what?
Our daughter's a sophomore.
- Oh, come on. Stop that.
- I mean, she's in there--
Stop that.
Our daughter reads Melville.
The only thing
she hates more than football
are football players themselves.
Stop that.
I'm just saying.
What do you need money for,
anyway?
Look, Noannie--
A man needs money.
- Hey, Mattie.
- What's going on?
What's up, baby?
Looking sharp in that hat.
Oh, man. Shut up.
Yeah, pimpin', pimpin'.
Listen, how long you been
workin' here?
I don't know.
About a year or so.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
Brian!
Can we order?
I'm gonna deal with you
in one second.
How much money do you make
working here?
Everybody just starts out
at minimum wage, so...
Okay, okay.
You think you can get
the Smash an application?
For real.
Yeah, I'll just talk to the manager.
Go talk to him.
I'll be right back.
Be serious, Brian.
You walkin' home.
Hi.
He knows.
What?
Tim, he knows.
Jason knows.
Does he know because you told him?
No.
- He asked me.
- Well, I didn't tell him.
He asked me if something happened
and I said no, but--
Then there's nothing else to do.
We're done.
You called it off, so it's off.
As far as I'm concerned,
you're Jay's girl and always have been.
So let's move on.
How?
Hey,  Lyla.
Hi.
How's Jason doing?
He's good.
He's real good.
Um, I just actually came by
to invite Tim.
Jason's doing a scrimmage thing
this Thursday at the center.
That's really sweet.
Yeah.
- Thanks for letting me know.
- Yeah, see ya.
Real nice of you to stop by.
The best one was that
i had this cigarette.
So I slap it out of his hand.
He leans into me.
He gets real close.
Right in his nose.
Blood everywhere, I bet.
Midget, toss you out the window.
Oh!
You tell the boys here
that I'm gonna come scrimmage
on Thursday?
I'm ready.
I told you I'm ready.
Jason, you're not ready.
Phil, come on.
Everyday it's about how great
my progress has been.
And how unusual I am.
What's the worst that could happen, huh?
I fall out of my chair,
break my neck--oh, wait.
That already happened,
didn't it?
You could tear your rotator cuff.
You can get a concussion.
Worst case scenario,
our fusion's still healing.
You don't seem to know
what that means,
so let me spell it out for you.
Those little bits of bone
are all that's protecting
your spinal cord at your injury sight.
You know how you can use your hands?
Screw up your fusion--
No more grip. Then what?
I want you to think
long and hard about this
before you do it.
You're really moving me, Phil.
If you hadn't noticed, we are crippled.
Kicking a boy while he's down.
Captain Bringdown!
I don't know why I do this.
Captain Bringdown,let's show
that super speed you got.
Lyla!
Hey, Lyla.
Hey, sweetie.
How are you?
- I'm good.
- Good. You know, I was wondering,
Would you mind
just telling your mom
I am not even halfway through
"The Secret Life of Bees"--
Sweetheart...
I'm sorry--
Is it over with you and Tim Riggins?
- Yes.
- Is it, really?
Yes, absolutely.
Can I give you a piece of advice?
Yeah, please.
Jason Street has been hurt...
worse than he has been
in his whole life.
I know.
Don't you hurt him more, girl.
But--
You would not be telling him for him.
You would be telling him for you.
You let him heal.
You move on with your life.
What do you want me
to cook for dinner
when the Riggins boys come over?
Should I slaughter a goat?
Mmm, slaughtered goat would be fine.
Hey, kiddo.
What do you got going on this week?
Um, tomorrow is Lois' birthday,
so Katie's gonna make
some red velvet cupcakes
and bring them to school.
Probably go into
a sugar coma at lunch.
And Matt Saracen
asked me out on a date.
Just putting it out there.
What did you say to him?
I told him I was considering.
Oh...
All right.
See, Smash, the key with all this
is really in the swirl.
So that then you can get
all the candy in it
and what not.
Are you getting this?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm putting
my own little spin to it.
No, that's the thing, though.
We're trying to keep product
really consistent
'cause our manager's a real stickler.
Oh, man, I think'm gonna
like this job.
Why?
Hey, look.
Check this out.
Take notes.
Hey, how you doing?
Um, could I get
a scoop of mocha, please?
No.
No, no, no.
You don't want that.
R eally?
Look, what you want is
a chocolate-covered
mocha cup with jimmies.
All right.
If that's what you say I want,
then I'll take that.
All right, well--
He'll get it for you.
Yeah--
How much to I owe you?
It's on me.
Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
See, that's what you do.
No, that's what you do.
You don't ask someone
what they want.
You tell them
You'll learn.
Jules?
Brought you some clean.
How's Faulkner?
Good.
So, uh, can I talk to you for a second.
You're just freaking out
because I got asked on a date.
I'm not freaking out.
I think it's great.
I think it's nice.
I'm just, uh...
- Freaking out.
- No.
I mean, I sit in that
counselor's chair all day,
you know and I kinda get a sense
of what goes on over there
at that school.
And I just want
to make sure that you've--
You know--
Are comfortable.
I haven't even
told him "yes" yet.
Okay, good.
I mean, oh...
Hey, man.
You're worse than the IRS.
hat's what your
football name should be.
"The Accountant."
That's funny.
Dammit.
I'm short.
Oh, yeah? By how much?
-$1.10.
-You gotta be kidding me.
Wait, hold on a second.
Hold on, hold on.
Come on!
You ain't got nothing on me, baby!
I'll get your wallet, boy!
Come on, now!
Ain't you got
some medals or something?
Don't feel bad.
I was all conference last year.
Yeah, that don't mean you're
ready to get on the court yet.
I'm telling you.
Phil's telling you.
Your doctor is telling you.
Even your cute little cheater's
telling you.
She didn't cheat.
Oh, now, pal...
You and me both know that's not true.
- She is messing with you--
- Herc--
And you are letting her!
You're just trying to hold on
to something that don't exist anymore.
You told me what you saw.
Yeah?
Well, I saw wrong, huh?
Oh, you saw wrong.
That's pathetic.
That is pretty pathetic.
Oh, really?
You know what's pathetic?
What's that?
You're little obsession with trying to get me
to break up with my girlfriend.
You got a little crush on me?
You think as long as you
hold on to that girlfriend--
The girlfriend you had
when you could walk--
You could avoid the reality
of being one of us.
That's got nothing to do with it.
Oh, so you admit it?
She's cheating, huh?
Where you going?
You running away, all star?
- Leave it.
- Leave it?
- Leave it!
- Ugh! Ow!
- Dammit, Herc! Argh!
She's all I got, man.
So quit busting my balls.
Just 'cause we're crippled...
Don't mean we have
to take the crumbs.
You got some secret way
we get back up on our chairs now?
Uh, yeah, I do.
Call Phil.
Phil!
Phiiiiiilll!
Phi-il!
Phil!
Jack.
No, that's not fair.
I shored those orders up.
Well-- Ask Ailene.
She filed the paperwork.
Come on, Jack.
I am telling you right--
Yeah?
Well, if that's the way you feel,
you know what you can do?
You can just go to hell,
you son of a bitch.
Let me guess--
Fired again, huh?
Jack Gordon wouldn't know
a good salesman
if one walked up
and smacked him in the mouth.
Why don't you just try
selling weed again?
Look, that was a short-term thing, all right.
What the hell are you doing eating that?
We got dinner in fifteen minutes.
I'm so tired of being
the damn man of the house.
Yeah, you really are
a good role model.
You're go into your room.
Comb your hair,
wash your hands,
put on a clean shirt!
And run a comb through your hair
for once in your life!
Will do, bro.
- Hey.
Smells good.
Thank you.
I hope you got that ice cream
because this
is all I had time to prepare.
Of course I got ice cream.
It's what you just sent me out to get.
How could I forget to--
Hey, come here.
Hey, what's wrong? What's wrong?
I think she's on the phone
with Matt Saracen.
Look, you gotta stop
with this Matt Saracen thing.
He's a good kid.
Don't worry about it.
Just relax, would you?
You know what, honey?
He's a good kid now,
but he's about to become
the star quarterback
of your football team,
where we know they like
to just use these girls
- and throw them away.
- Wait a sec.
Wait a second there.
First of all,
she's my daughter too.
Second of all,
I'm not the enemy.
Don't start lumping all of us
- into this culture you've created.
- I'm not saying--
What are you talking--
I'm not creating some kind of culture.
All I'm saying is you can't
do anything about them.
But you could talk to you daughter.
It would make me feel really good
if you could just talk to her.
- Is that what you want me to do?
- From your point of view as a--
I'll talk to her.
I will talk to her.
If you'll relax, I will talk to her.
I'll have a talk with her tonight.
- Wait--
- I gotta get the door.
You look beautiful.
Now, go answer the door.
Thank you.
Julie, get off the phone
Now!
How's that?
Oh, that's very good.
- Hey!
- Hi, how are you doing?
Good to see you again, Tami.
Come on in.
Brought you a little, um,
dinner present there.
Thank you, that's great.
Come on in, get something to drink.
Oh, fantastic.
Thank you all.
You been on break all day,
it seems like.
Yeah, well, I'll tell you
when I'm done breaking.
All right, you let me know.
Oh...
What?
This is it.
This is the one.
- Uh, no--
- You do this--
- One more time.
- Dude, it's all on you.
Come on.
All right.
Hi, how's it--
What can I do for you?
Can I have an Alamo burger
and a root beer?
Uh, no--
I don't think--
I don't think you really want that.
I don't?
What do you want me to have?
I don't know.
Um...
Well, you wanted root beer,
so you like root beer.
And I make a--
I make a mean root beer float.
Is that so?
Mm-hmm.
- Make you wanna cry.
- Yeah, it's real mean.
Hmm, well...
Or a sundae...
With jimmies.
Hmm, tempting.
All right.
But I think I'll stick
with the Alamo burger
and just a plain root beer.
Okay, well...
Maybe next time.
Oh, here.
The drinks are just
right over there.
Thanks.
All right.
What do you think?
Think that went all right?
Hey, it's a start.
Now, it wasn't the best.
But, you know,
no shame in the game.
Yeah, all right, cool. Thanks.
Look on the bright side.
At least it's pay day.
Speaking of which, um...
Can I sign my check over to cash?
Actually, you're not gonna get
a paycheck today.
Man, stop playing with me, man.
This ain't no volunteer work.
No, no, but seriously.
We only get paid every two weeks.
And because of processing
and everything
they're always a week behind.
So, you're probably
not going to get a check
'til the end of the month.
- Maybe.
- What?
Sorry, man.
Oh, no--
This ain't right, man.
But you get free ice cream.
That's good.
That's a perk.
No?
So I grab that ball
and I just start running.
And I am running and running.
I am chugging down that field
and the whole entire crowd
is going nuts.
People were standing up and screaming.
I couldn't even hear anything.
I get all the way into the end zone.
After I throw the ball down
I realize--
I went the wrong damn way.
Oh, no!
That's an awful story.
Mmm, that's really nice.
Truth is I was never
much of a player.
Not like my little brother here.
He's got the gift.
He's good, he's good.
So, Coach, uh...
You think he's got a shot
at college ball?
Keeps playing the way he does, yeah.
I like to hear that.
Right, Tim?
You bet.
Do both parents live here
in Dillon?
Dad is down in Corpus Christi
He's working on a driving range..
Doesn't get home
a whole heck of a lot.
- He's a real hard worker, the old man.
- Yeah...
Shagging golf balls for a living--
It's real important work.
What I meant was...
He sends checks pretty often, so...
That'd be twice.
Two checks in six years.
So, what are you looking to do now?
Whattaya got going on, Bill?
You know what I've been looking into
is, um, real estate.
Real estate, yeah?
I've been in sales for years,
so I figured once I get
my real estate license,
I'll be selling the biggest things--
Dammit, Tim!
Um, sorry.
You know, the Riggins boys
came over for dinner last night.
You and Tim, you're still best friends,
aren't you?
I guess so.
You guess so?
Parents did a number
on those kids, that's for sure.
Yeah, well...
Everyone's got a sad story.
Doesn't excuse anything.
He played a hell of a game Friday.
I'll tell you that.
He'll make something of himself
If he doesn't become his own worst enemy.
So, uh...
See these two cones behind me?
That's the goal line.
Why don't you try and get across it?
All right.
Try it again.
Everyone says
I'm not ready for this game.
Everyone says I shouldn't be
at the scrimmage tonight.
Doctors, parents...
Why, what--
What do you say?
I say I am ready.
I don't know, it's just--
My whole life I've been
thinking about football.
Football, football, football--
That's all.
Nothing else.
Think about what it
used to feel like.
Be able to compete,
be able to be a part
of something, you know?
I feel like...
Like that whole part of me
is just empty now.
It's just gone.
Maybe they're right.
Maybe it's too soon.
16 years ago,
I wasn't ready to be a father,
I can tell you that.
I wasn't ready
for the responsibility.
You cannot be prepared
for something like that.
Believe me.
But you grab the bull
by the horns and you move on.
You...
No 17-year-old kid
should have to go through
what you're going through right now.
No, stop!
You're dealing with it.
You're doing what
you're supposed to do.
You're being a man about it.
Go with your heart.
Hey...
Smash...
It's all there.
You're good to go.
Hey, what's going on?
Hey, chill, Mattie.
No, no, no-
I vouched for you, okay?
Then I see you
messing with the drawer.
What's your problem?
Look, there ain't no problem.
But if you want to find a problem--
No, seriously--
If you lose this job,
I lose my job
because I vouched for you...
'Cause I thought I was
vouching for my friend.
Hey, look--
I had a bad game.
- So?
- I had a bad week.
Did you know that there was
a scout there last Friday?
Yeah.
Well, can you think
of one thing I did
to distinguish myself on the field?
Yeah.
But that was just one game.
Yeah, well I can't have
another one like it.
All right,
I can't afford it.
What do you need
all that money for?
I don't need it!
I thought I did,
but I don't, okay?
I see things
a little more clearly today.
How's your dating situation going?
Good.
I take it,
by that limited response...
You don't think
it's any of my business.
All right, listen up.
I'm supposed to give you
some fatherly and wise advice
at this time in your life.
Listen up.
If you're wondering
if a boy's thinking about you,
he's not.
He's thinking about sex
or he's hungry.
Those are the only two options.
Are you trying to be funny?
No, I'm not finished.
Listen to me.
Boys think about sex
every single minute of the day.
That's what they do.
That's why they lie.
They're gonna leave you
waiting around for them to call.
And they won't call.
They're gonna be cruel
and they're gonna be misleading.
And your mother wanted me
to add this:
That, by and large,
football players
are the worst offenders.
However, I think that it
pretty much crosses all lines.
Are you done?
You are beautiful.
You are sensitive.
You are sweet, and I don't want
to see you get hurt.
I love you too, Dad.
You're a lousy ping pong player
though.
You mind?
I just cleaned up.
Least you could do
is put your crap in your own room
and let it fester there.
Maybe you should just
get a job as a maid.
Yeah, maybe.
Least I'd have a marketable skill,
unlike you.
I mean, when you graduate--
If you graduate,
you'll be lucky if you can get
a job pumping gas.
Then again,
maybe Tyra will support you.
She's a real go-getter.
That don't bother you none, huh?
Trying to get second helpings
from my girl?
That's pretty sick,
to be honest with you.
Yeah?
I'm a real loser, aren't I, Tim?
Let me ask you a question.
Which one of us is banging
his crippled best friend's
girl friend right now?
That would be you, wouldn't it?
How's that real estate license coming?
You sell any condos today?
What's gonna happen to you, Tim?
You know what I see?
Another 40 pounds
and delinquent child support.
Remind you of anyone?
Maybe Dad?
What's your problem with Dad, now?
What's my problem with Dad?
Yeah.
What is your problem with Dad?
What's my problem with Dad?
You want to know what my problem
with Dad is, Tim?
You want to know
what my problem with Dad is!
God, Nick, I admire the guy.
Couple postcards every year,
and he gets off scott-free.
Not me, though.
No, I get stuck with you
because nobody else wants you!
When's the last time
you heard from Mom or Dad?
Been a while, hasn't it?
Don't you forget, you little bastard--
I'm the one paying the bills
around here.
Buying the groceries.
Going out there and watching
your damn football games.
Not them!
Ow, you're pulling my hair!
Get off of me!
Get up!
You were never a real football player
and you know it.
Yeah, you're right.
You got more talent than I ever had.
And I got to sit here every day
and watch you throw it away.
And it makes me sick!
You're not my father.
You're worse than no father.
I'd be better off alone.
Go ahead and walk away.
Just like Dad!
You ready, Sparky?
You better be.
Get that ball!
Get it! Yeah!
That's what a QB does, huh?
Go, Street.
What you got!
You ain't got nothing!
How's that ground taste?
Feel pretty good?
Let's go!
Come on, baby!
Yeah, Baby!
Yeah!
Did you talk to her?
- Yeah.
- And?
And, contrary to popular opinion,
I'm very good at communicating
with women folk.
Sweetheart, that is ridiculous.
Now, tell me what happened.
I'm telling you.
You can rest easy.
She has now received
fatherly advice.
Are you sure--
Okay.
So, it's pretty obvious
that both of you
have a sudden, weird
curiosity in my social life.
So, in interest of full disclosure,
I would like to tell both of you
that I'm going on a date
with Matt Saracen.
Time and place to be announced.
Good night.
Good night, hon.
Good night, sweetheart.
* What a friend we have in Jesus *
* All our sins and griefs to bear *
* What a privilege to carry *
* Everything to God in prayer *
Come on, let's give God
a handclap and pray.
Give him a hand.
Before we begin our Bible study,
there are some special prayer
requests that we have.
And I want us all to be praying
for these particular people.
Brother Moses London
is suffering with shingles.
And we pray that God
will give him a speedy recovery.
Amen.
We also have
another prayer request
for a young leader
in our community.
He's a young man who shows determination
to be a scholar athlete.
Because he's so determined
to finish his education,
he's gonna need
a low financial assistance
because of exams
that he's gonna have to take.
And so what I want us to do
is to show this young man
that if you will humble yourself,
make your request known,
that God will provide
your every need.
Yes, yes!
I believe in this young man,
so I'm gonna ask you
to do me a favor
and sow a generous seed
into this young man's life.
When you sow into him,
you're sowing into your life.
- That's right!
- Come on, let's be a blessing to this young man.
Let's show him how much we love him.
And how much we're rooting for him.
And we want him
to go all the way
and make us all proud.
Amen.
Good game, Sparky.
See you back at the ranch.
Hey, rookie.
You didn't suck, man.
That is the six I know.
Man, I tell you, those hits--
I gotta take some notes.
Great game, man.
Tell you what--
Get up, Riggins!
Get up and fight me, huh?
Come on, you coward.
Come on, hit me!
You steal my girl but
you're not ready to fight me!
Jason!
Don't you dare, Lyla.
Don't you dare.
Come on, look me in the face.
Come back here. Come back here!
- Jason!
- You gonna steal a cripple's girl,
but you won't fight a cripple?
You coward!
You're a coward, Riggins!
Always will be.
Jason...
Go!
Go, go!
What happened to your eye?
Tim, who did that to you?
Jay.
Yeah.