Previously on "Grey's Anatomy"...
You're watching me sleep again?
It's just that, .. you snore a little ..
Harold O’Malley, 63 .. Scheduled for ..
a transhiatal esophagectomy
tomorrow morning at 9.
I want that you take the tumor out.
As things progress with my dad ..
It will help me if you were straight
with me
Okay
so, that's it ?
we're closing him and back up?
- No.
- but, i thought ..
the patient asked us .. to proceed
You would have watch his kidneys.
Because if the kidneys fail, ...
that's a sign that
everything else is starting to go
130cc of shiny yellow urine!
That is fantastic!
Heather Douglas, 17.
Past medical history of VATER syndrome.
i think i could significantly
help with this spinal curvature.
I get to scrub in.
No, until I say so
I deposited the damm check
Insurance bastards.
the surgery's too experimental.
Looks like there won't be a surgery
to scrub in on.
Sorry, Stevens.
You don't get the high-horse
this week, Addison.
Not this week.
Dr Burke's hand ..
has he had any tremors?
Talk to him.
No, because then he wins.
My father's here.
The one i don't talk to and barely know.
He's here.
If you want to go back to plastics ..
Nahh ....
Oh! Just ..
shut it off, please!
Could you not snap at me?
I didn't sleep much.
Maybe it's because you were too busy
shoving me every five minutes.
I wasn't shoving you.
I was nudging you to stop the very ..
loud sawing of wood.
I wore the nose strip.
Oh, it's cute, but it doesn't work
- Aouhh!
- What?
- You need to shave.
- Uhm
Izzie, uh, the, the-the, the,
the check ..
the, it's not, uh, it's--it's not--
Did you--did you drop it?
Here, Move,move,ve.
No, Did you-- not--it--it's not here!
Izzie, it's not here!
I depositied it. Okay?
You didn't deposit it in the garbage disposal
or something like that, did you?
It's at the bank. Ok, George?
Now, you shut up about it already.
It's at, it's at the bank?
It's, it's earning interest?
Did I not just say,
"shut up about it already"?
Izzie! It's really now... I mean..
That money, it could .. Money could travel.
It could, it could buy things.
It could buy many, many things.. That's ..
It's a lot of money, Izzie!
Shut out about it, George!
I'm just sayin'... I'm just sayin'...
Life is short, You know, it's .. cancer happens,
and surgery happens, and, eh ..
I-- you know, it's-it's
"gather ye rosebuds"...
You know,
you have 8.7 million rosebuds, Izzie.
You gotta spend some rosebuds.
That's what i'm saying.
You made me burn my french toast.
You can buy new french toast!
- Oh!
- Hey. Uh, I was, uh ...
Yeah, I was just, uh, just  ...
- The baby's doing ..?
- Good! Yeah, she's good.
- Good! That's, That's good!
- Yeah ...
Doctors?
- Yes?
- What?
I was wondering ...
The baby looks ...?
- Good! Yeah, she's good!
- Good! Yes, she's good!
Good! She looks good.
- Yes, she's She's, uh...
- She's good?
She, She's out of the woonds?
She is. She is, uh ...
She's good.
She is out of the woods.
Her vitals are strong.
Uh, she made it through the night,
and she's, uh ... she's a fighter!
So-So, I can tell my wife and my daughter?
You can.
And, you should.
Oh! Thank you.
Thank you both .. so much.
Yeah!,
No, she's out of the woods.
How am I related to that man?
What yu mean?
Look at him. He's a mess.
Yeah!
I mean he's a disaster. He's a
stammering, mumbling, clumsy disaster
with whom I have absolutely nothing in common.
Not one thing.
I hate to break this to you..
What?
Well, you know, you do your own share
of stammering yourself.
- Yeah, that nervous talking thing you do?
It's actually a lot like him.
- Mmhmm. Mmhmm.
No, it's not.
- Plus, that messy thing.
- Oh, totally.
You're the messy one.
No, my apartment's messy,
my locker's messy, ..
but, I am not messy....
Sometimes, you know, you have
like food and stuff in your hair.
Yeah, food.
Band-aids on your face.
I can still kinda see the indentation from
the nose strip you were wearing last night.
You, .. are in a relationship with no words.
And you are a millionaire
in twenty dollar shoes. Whatever!
- Oh , my god!
- She's just like him.
Right!!
- Dr Bailey, you paged me?
- Yes,i did.
We're going to proceed with
heather's surgery, as scheduled.
The insurance company changed their mind?
No. Better.
It seems an anonymous donor has offered
to foot heather's entire bill.
Well! That is incredible.
You're a very lucky girl.
Hey, that's the first time anyone's
ever said that sentence to me in my entire life.
I like it.
You spent 300 grands,
so you could scrub in on this surgery?
No.
No?
I spent the three  ..
Have you seen that girl?
Her life is miserable.
She's deseparate, she's, she's ..
she'll, she'll never have a date,
she'll never wear high heels
she'll never feel normal,
I-I spent 300 grand because ..
It-It's a good thing.
I was hoping you tell me
you spent the money..
so you could scrub in.
But, I ..
You need to decide, whether or not,
you are a surgeon, because .. th ..
thing you did, this is lovely and generous, and,
i'm not trying to away from any of that, but ..
You are, once again, overly involved,
Once again, ..
you are personally involved, so..
No, I'm sorry, you cannot scrub in.
Grey's Anatomy  312 - Six Days, Part 2
George kissed me. Yesterday.
One minute, he's holding a urine bag,
the next minute, he's kissing me.
You think he's just freaking out about his dad?
Oh, you're right, you're right.
He's probably just freaking out.
I shouldn't hold him to it.
- Oh, man!
- What?
Did you not just hear a word I said?
I'm pouring my heart out here.
Jeez, it's all about you. Isn't it?
It's all about
.. everything's about Addison.
I aborted Mark's baby.
It is all about you. Floor is all yours.
About eight months ago,
I ... peed on a stick,...
and I wasn't even, uh, ..
gonna tell him but then I did...
tell him. And, uh, he went out and bought this
insane Yankee's onesie ..
and a calendar, and marked the due date,
which I should mention, was today.
You didn't want a baby?
I wanted Derek.
I wanted to have a baby with Derek.
I never thought I'd end up alone.
You have not "ended up" anywhere.
Yeah, yu're right, I know,
it's just that, um,
sometimes it feels that way, you know?
This is one of those weeks it feels that way.
Drill.
Another screw, please.
Hey, how's your old man?
His urine output's holding steady.
Mostly it's steady today, which is good.
Have you seen Burke, today?
Even if I did, like you,
I still wouldn't tell you that.
How can you be okay with burke,
but not Cristina?
Her career wasn't on the line when she lied to me.
Why don't you just ask Burke about the hand yourself?
But, I-I am not talking to him.
He owes me.
What?
Oh, I don't know.
So, you're together
but you don't talk to each other.
Uh huh.
I wish I could find that in a woman.
Hey, how's it going with Addison?
What? What, wha-what y do? what do y,
what do y, what do y-you mean by that?
Laura Grey, tiny baby.
Laura. the baby, right,
She's, she's um, doing fine.
She's doing well.
I gotta get, yo know..
I gotta get back to Sloan.
What are you plotting?
and can I get in on it?
- Shut up.
- Oh!! - God!!
Ahh... this is my surgery,
I should be down, here.
- No!
- Escuse me.
Mr O’Malley...
- 9.1.1 ?
- Yeah.
It sucks.
Yeah...
Could you give me the retractor?
Um, Dr. Shepperd,
can you proceed without me?
Are you kidding me? This is your surgery,
Torres. This is your find, you want to leave?
I-I'm, I don't, but, eh, yes, I'm sorry
But if it's all right, I need to leave.
Give me some sponges.
Okay, i called the family in,
because, i need to ..
perform a procedure, um, on your father,
to help him breathe.
Uhm, So, so you're saying,
he can't breathe?
Uh, With the, extensive surgery,
uh, your father,
is not breathing on his own.
Which is why we still have him intubated.
Intubated?
The tube in dad's mouth.
It's breathing for him.
And right now, that tube has a kink,
in it, which is straining his breathing.
How did it get a kink in it?
It just happens, mam,
We don't always know why.
But, but he's doing good, today..
I mean, he made--he made plenty of pee, so...
Still, we need to replace the tube.
So, why don't you just do it?
I mean, what are we waiting for?
Ok. With the damage to your father's oesophagus
and the swelling in his throat ...
from being intubated all this time ,...
You might no be able to get it in ..
the new tube?
Under this circustumcies,
it can be a complicate procedure
if i am not succesfull...
I am saying, uh, you need, ..
to prepare yourselves.
What is that?
It's Jerry.
I'm sorry, I'm nervous
Oh, God!
- My God!
- Stop it, Jerry!
I'm nervous!
For God, sick!
take some charcoal or something, son.
- Tyler!
- Yeah?
Could you let dr.Burke know that
Mr. O'malley is having some kind...
of medical crisis right now,
and I thought he would like to know.
He is awake, you know?
Yeah, I know.
You want to handle this, chief?
Dr. Bailey, you have a lot more
hands on hours these days than i do
I'll be standing by to help,
but this is all yours.
All right, Grey, let me have 8.0 E.T, tube?
Dr. Bailey, this is a patient,
like any other patient,
There is no room for error, which means,
there's no room for nerves
so shake it off.
All right,
let's do this.
- great
- 8-0.
- I can't, uh ...
- is it too tight?
I can't get past the vocal chords.
Damn it.
- Pulse ox down 88...
- Damn it!
86 Come on!
Lets go! ,Lets go!, Lets go!
Let me have a 7 1/2.
Hurry!
Oh! Come on, come on, come on!
Good!
- let me get a !
- okay,I got it.
Beautiful job.
Beautiful job....
Oh, can I go tell george?
Dr. Bailey, you're all right?
My son .. he's named after his son.
I just need a minute.
There is a surgery, you know?
It's a minor laser thing.
Supposed to really help.
We could look into it.
Sure, and while we're at it,
let's look at halitosis cures for you.
Not to mention stubble cures,
Because, it's now become physically
impossible for me to kiss your face.
I am too tired to shave!
Sloan! Dr. Sloan!
Bone dry Capuccino
And I watched 'em make it this time so no mistakes.
Hey, I-I noticed you had a reconstructive rhinoplasty
on the board today,
and I'd--I'd really like to scrub in if at all possible.
You been working with addison this week?
Yes, sir, working.
Working ...a lot.
Working hard.
Just ...working
- Is she miserable?
- I'm sorry?
It's just ... I need to know if she's...
at least miserable this week.
Did she seem... is she miserable?
Oh, dude, she's awful.
She's torturing me.
I seriously have to get away from that woman.
I mean, she is completely
and utterly, 100% miserable.
Good.
- So can I scrub in?
- No!
Are you sleeping?
I should be.
I haven't slept in days.
me neither. I can't sleep alone anymore.
I used to sleep just fine, and then he...
God, he gets me all strung
out on him, and then he disappears?
He didn't disappear.
He's in an hospital.
- I just want to know how he's doing.
- You could just ask him.
Uh, he could just tell me.
Georgie's dad is going into renal failure.
I heard.
My dad's here, everywhere, every day.
He's perfectly healthy,
and I have nothing to say to him.
- If george's dad dies...
- I know.
If thatcher died,
my life wouldn't be any different.
Is it weird that I'm a little jealous of George?
Yes.
Bailey re-intubated him, but um, he was
without ox-oxygen for, I don't know, a few minutes.
- O'Malley... there's no blame here.
- No ..
Your father's body is diseased
and has undergone tremendous trauma.
Now, his organs are shutting down.
There's no blame here.
Do people come back from this?
His B.U.N. and creatinine are high.
I get that.
I was just wondering, in--in your experience,
can people come back from this?
I don't have any statistics....
I don't have any more medicine for you.
- Now, it's about faith.
- We're men of science.
In my experience,
science is not enough, OMalley...
But if you want me, to hope with you...
if you'd like me to send up a prayer,
that is a thing I'll be happy to do.
- You have family here?
- Yeah, a daughter.. She's 17...
oh, I'm so sorry...
She had surgery on her spine.
And they said it went well.
But then she has trouble with her kidneys and...
well, she hasn't woken up.
- My husband either.
- It was a dangerous surgery.
- They told us that.
- My husband's, too.
He has...cancer, so...
I was surprised when they went through with it.
I thought I'd be taking him home.
Excuse me, mrs.Douglas?
Heather is asking for you.
- She woke up?
- She did.... And she looks great.
Congratulations!
It's wonderful!
- Good luck. I'll... good luck.
- Thanks!
- What did you do it?
- Dr. O'Malley!
What did you do the surgery
once you saw the cancer had spread?
- George...
- He asked you? Right?
He asked you to do it no matter what?
We have to honour our patient's wishes.
You said that you will be straight with me ...
He-he could've live for .. weeks, .. or months!
We could've months with him.
My Mom!
She could've months with him!
- He wanted to fight the cancer, George, It was his choice...
- He didn't know any better!
You knew better!
You shouldn't done it!
You shouldn't done it.
- Oh, my God! Look at you!
- I'm miserable.
it's the rain... the constant dampnes in the air.
- It takes the body a while to adjust.
- I don't want to adjust.
Then go home.
If you'd had the baby,
we'd be together in New York right now;
it wouldn't be raining and even if it was,
we wouldn't care because we'd be together.
We'd be together.
And I'd have a family ..
instead of walking pneumonia,
and an ex-best friend who hates me.
You didn't want to raise a child, Mark.
You just wanted to trump Derek,
You wanted to win.
Don't make this my fault.
- You didn't want a baby.
- No, I did .. want a baby, Mark!
That last woman you slept with before I left New York
Charlene, the peds nurse? I--did you think
that she was the only one I knew about?
You're rewriting history, Mark.
We wouldn't still be together.
We weren't a great couple.
And you would've made...
a terrible father ..
Mark, .. I did want a baby. It did. I just...
I just didn't want one with you.
What? Is that his lunch?
I've been looking everywhere for that.
- Oh,no. He can't have that.
- What?
- He's, uh, restricted from food.
- No, he's not...
- No,I'm his doctor.
- You are not!
I just want to know how he is.
And withholding food gets her that how?
- Fine. Feed him... Whatever!
- You want me to call security?
- Hey!
Haven't seen you the last couple of days.
Yeah, I was covering the pit, and, uh,
I got pulled into an emergency appy and a ruptured spleen.
It's been pretty chaotic.
Look, Karev, I'm your attending.
I'm sorry about what happened.
It's been a ...
a weird week, for me.
so, normally, ..
anyway, I apologize.
The baby's, uh, bowels functioning yet?
Uh, yeah, actually, um...
she had her first diaper change today, so...
- that's good!
- Yeah, it is.
That neighbor kid, Mike Wildon,
I did hit him in the face with a stick.
Um..
when his dad came over and was yelling and ..
and, you asked me if it was true ...
I lied.
And you thought I never lied.
So you took my side, ..
and you and his dad got in that big fight.
And then his kids egged our house, and then
Ronny and Jerry went over
and blew up his lawn mower.
Anyway. I did it. He was teasing me,
and he was bigger than me.
So, I needed a stick to reach his face.
And I lied to you dad.
So, ..
I'm saying I'm sorry.
Dad ...
If you have any more fight in you,
if you could fight this thing just...
just a little harder, that would be good.
That'd be good right now.
- Where is Derek?
- He slept at his place
Do i really snore?
Well, I grew up next to a freeway,
so it doesn't really bother me,
but, yeah, you do.
Did you get any sleep last night?
No...
No, I stayed up last night baking
and cleaning the bathroom floor, ..
in case George wants to lay down on it.
It's weird.
I have all this money. I..
I have all this money,
and i would spend every penny of it
to save george from what he's
about to go through, but I.. I can't.
It's useless.
So, I made cobbler.
- Well, cobbler's good.
- Yeah!
She told you.
Hum...
Yeah.
- You think I'd be a terrible father?
- Oh, I don't.. I don't know .. are you?
Okay, do you like kids?
I don't know.
It depends on how loud they are.
Okay, .. do you like your family?
I mean, are you a family kind of guy?
I don't really have a family.
Derek ...  was my family.
Okay, well, what about birthdays and
anniversaries. Do you remember
those sorts of things?
No. I don't know.
Sometimes.
- Hum...
- Isn't it the same with all men?
No. Some men just like kids.
To uh, to some men, family is everything.
Right...
And you know these men?
I do. .. I know one.
I would've made a terrible father.
You're saying ..
you're saying it's not getting better.
You're saying he's not gonna wake up?
Mrs O'Malley... All of his organs ar shutting down.
His liver and his kidneys are no longer supporting him
And, he his entirely dependant upon his life support machines
We are saying he is not going to wake up.
You can keep him on .. life support
and wait for nature to take its course
That could take .. days .. or weeks ..
Or, you can ... take him off, life support.
- Unplug him?
- Yes, Ma'am.
- Georgie!
- Yeah.
What do you think?
Dad is in pain.
His organs were shutting down.
He can't breath with his own.
It's painful.
And he's on medication, but ..
medication can't only do so much
You think ...
You're saying you think it's time ...
.. to let him go?
We can't tell you what to do, here, Georges.
He is not Dad like this.
and he's not gonna wake up, mom...
No!!
Is there a drawer of
unopened cards, somewhere?
I'm sorry. What?
I just wanted to know... I've only ever heard
my mother's version of the story
of why you left and ...
And I was just wondering,
if maybe you have a side, that I hadven't heard.
Your mother moved to Boston.
And uh, .. I wanted to..
but she told me not .. to call
or come around and ... uh, she-she was.. um
eventually, I re-married
and I...
I'm-I'm sorry.
- Do you snore?
- What?
It appears that, I snore.
My mother never did, so I was just...
- Forget it.
- I snore!
I snore like a trucker.
You get that from me.
The wax earplugs work pretty good.
Thanks.
Hey.
Derek... I was waiting on an update
on Mr. O'Malley.
I didn't want to intrude, but, uh...
Did you have an update?
They're letting him go.
- Hum.
- Hum!
I haven't had any more tremors.
Not one all week.
- How about that?
- Yeah. How about that?
- I'm both.
- What?
I'm both ... I'm a surgeon and I am a person
who becomes emotionally involved.
I will never again,
cross the line like I did with Denny.
I have learned my lesson.
But I'm still both,
and I'm not gonna give up either part of me.
And I am not gonna to apologize for it.
There's a club...
The Dead Dads Club,
And you can't be in it until you're in it.
You can try to understand, you can sympathize.
But until you feel that loss...
My dad died when I was nine.
George.
I'm really sorry you had to join the club.
I...
I... I don't know how to .. exist in a world
where my dad doesn't.
Yeah, that never really changes.
Beer, Joe, please.
How is Georgie's Dad?
Hey.
You got a dad?
Not really, not anymore.
Sources - 1000fr & Dupontt