Previously on
"Grey's Anatomy"...
You're shot?
Christina?
You're throwing me out?
Got no choice.
What's with the suitcase?
Yes. My answer is yes.
An hour ago,
he was proposing.
I thought l was a surgeon,
but l am not.
I stopped teaching when you
needed a teacher the most.
Our marriage is over.
There's this thing that allows
for the considering of options.
In the olden days,
they called it dating.
You bowing out?
No. You?
I don't think so.
Surgeons usually fantasize about
wild and improbable surgeries--
someone collapses
in a restaurant,
we slice them open
with a butter knife,
replace a valve with a
hollowed-out stick of carrot.
But every now and then,
some other kind of
fantasy slips in.
Good morning.
It is a good morning.
Hi.
Did you get any
sleep last night?
Not really.
You want to get some now?
Ow !
Most of our fantasies
dissolve when we wake,
banished to the
back of our mind.
But sometimes,
we're sure...
if we try hard enough...
we can live the dream.
Damn it! Stupid -- ow!
I was having a
really good dream,
and you ruined it.
Sorry. It's, uh, the, uh,
these boxes.
All these boxes.
Callie said she was
bringing her stuff over,
and, uh... it's all here.
It's okay, George.
I don't mind.
I don't mind either. No.
Don't mind a bit.
Kick her out.
What? I can't kick her out.
You were the one who told
her she could move in.
I said she could stay
for a couple of days--
a couple of days.
It's been over a week.
Now there are boxes,
and she's using my computer.
And she's here all the time.
Would you kick her out?
And kick her out now.
Hey, you guys might want
to wait a little while.
There's no more hot water.
Do it.
Why do you hate me?
Just do it.
Hey.
Can l get a ride with
you guys to the hospital?
You're going to the hospital?
Yeah, l'm--l'm gonna go in,
talk to the chief,
see about coming back.
Anyway, just let me know
when you're leaving.
that's great.
Izzie is coming back.
That's... great, right?
Mm-hmm.
That's my towel.
Oh.
Sorry.
Boy, he is really
moody in the mornings.
Yeah.
He's, uh... yeah.
You know l don't
have to leave today.
I could change my flight.
No. No, you can't.
Because l'm... sober now,
and, uh,
there's work to get to and--and planes
to be caught and real lives to be led.
Thank you, truly, Mark,
for all of the...
sex.
I-l really, l feel much better now.
I do.
And l'm--l'm--
well, now l have to go,
and so do you.
So,  uh, do you, uh,
want me to call you...
a cab to the airport?
Oh!
Why don't you try
your bad hand?
That's what the
ball's for, right,
fixing your bad hand?
Works.
There's  coffee on the floor.
Fine. I'll--you know what?
I'll clean it up.
Whatever. Leave it.
It doesn't matter.
So l was thinking,
since your shift
ends after mine,
and l don't want to
have to wait around,
maybe l should get a
copy of the house key.
No. I like leaving together.
You don't need a key.
Izzie?
I'll see you guys in there.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Bailey is on your side.
And the chief is...
he is gonna put on his angry face,
but he's on your side, too.
Everybody wants you
back in that building.
I know. I know.
You guys go ahead.
I'll be fine.
I'm just gonna take a minute,
practice my speech.
Okay.
I didn't ask you to
convince her to come in.
But l did.
I did convince her.
There is a whole series of disciplinary
and rehabilitative steps that Izzie
Stevens will have to take before we can--
- You can explain them to her.
I never agreed to that.
She didn't commit a crime.
She's an intern--
my intern.
You--you want to blame someone,
blame me.
Look, but that girl is
coming in hertoday,
and--and--and you are
going to talk to her.
And you're gonna remember all the
other surgeons you've known who've ever
had a lapse in judgment that led to
someone dying or someone's arm
falling off.
Most importantly,
you're gonna remember all the mistakes
that you made when you were young
and stupid.
And you're gonna be filled
with patience and compassion.
That's what l'm gonna do?
Yes!
Because l'm the boss.
I'm...
Look, l didn't mean
any disrespect, sir.
I apologize.
This is really important
to you personally.
Very personally, sir, yes.
Being the boss isn't as
gratifying as it used to be.
No, sir.
Get outta here.
I'm on my knees in
a puddle of coffee,
and he's lying on the
couch playing with himself.
You know,
and not in a good way.
He's recovering from surgery,
and you've read the studies on recovery
and depression in surgical patients.
Well, he's not a patient.
He's Preston Burke.
He's just milking it.
You know, he's got me fetching his food
and the paper and his slippers like l'm
a dog.
Hey.
Hi.
I had a dream about
you last night.
You did?
Mm-hmm.
What was l doing,
bringing you coffee?
You were definitely
not bringing me coffee.
But coffee's good.
I'm told dating starts with a casual
invitation over a cup of coffee.
Does it?
So,  meredith,
would you like to go out
to dinner with me tonight?
How was that?
Was that casual enough?
That was good, right?
Mm.
No? Mm.
So we're dating.
We're dating.
Pick you up at 8:00.
Hey.
I was in the neighborhood.
Actually, l wasn't.
But l decided you
were worth a detour.
I had a dream about
you last night.
Was it a good dream?
It was.
And what was l doing?
Yes, Mer,
what was he doing?
What's that?
It's for you.
It's coffee cake--
best in the northwest.
Figure l better soften you up so that
when l ask you to dinner tonight,
you have to say yes.
Uh, dinner tonight?
How about that?
Are you free tonight,
Meredith?
Actually, uh,
I'm not free tonight.
Well, how about lunch?
I could come here.
You're volunteering
to eat hospital food?
I love crappy food.
1:00?
I'll  be here.
Okay.
You had a dream about
the both of them?
A threesome?
Nice.
Just when l think you're boring,
you rise.
I'm dating.
And... it comes with snacks.
Hey, Iz.
Hey. I'm going in
to see the chief.
Excellent. Back in the game,
stepping up to the plate.
Look, l'm--l'm running late.
Um, l'll catch you later?
Yeah, later.
Izzie's back. That's good.
Ooh, coffee cake.
I'm dating.
Touch that piece,
Iose a hand.
Morning, people.
Grey, we're clearing the decks.
I need you writing
discharge forms.
Yang, you're with Dr. Shepherd.
Karev, as usual, you're with Dr.
Montgomery-Shepherd in O.B.-G.Y.N.
O'Malley, Dr.
Torres has requested you today in ortho.
Was she smiling?
Izzie's back.
"Dr. Torres has requested you."
- Just tell her, George.
Tell her you're not ready
to move in together.
And then try dating.
Dating is fun.
Karev, we ready?
Isn't this getting old for you?
nope. Makes my whole day,
actually.
Hello. Hello.
Are you okay?
No. Uh, ye--
n-no, l can'T.
I gotta--
five minutes.
Go find something
to do in the pit.
Personal problem?
Go.
Fourth visit in three months.
I'm Dr. Karev.
And you are...
Megan Clover.
And it's not as bad as it looks.
She fell on the playground,
and there was a lot of blood,
and it looked deep.
We know how this looks.
Just so you know,
we know how this looks,
and it's not that.
She just... plays rough.
You know?
This is her file, allright?
And it goes back since
way before we got her.
Before you got her?
We're her foster parents.
She's such a great kid,
but she plays really--
she plays rough.
Yeah. Yeah.
Right. Uh...
Why don't you guys go up to the nurses'
station and let them make a copy of
her file for you?
And, uh,
l'll take a look at Megan's leg.
Okay.  We'll be
right back, honey.
You all right?
- Yeah.
- OK.
You got some mean looking bruises,
you know that?
What, did you hurt
your arm, too?
Nothing big.
I fell off my bike.
Are those staples?
What the hell?
Did they do this to you?
No! No!
Who did this to you?
I did.
I didn't want to go to the doctor again,
so l just stapled it.
It's no biggie.
You stapled your own arm?
Can you please just stitch up my
leg so we can get out of here?
You're not going anywhere
with those people, Megan.
They're never gonna lay
a hand on you again.
They didn't do anything.
Please. They're my best
parents l've ever had.
Megan.
They don't hurt me.
I can't be hurt.
You don't believe me?
Punch  me in the
stomach right now.
The staples are in
there pretty deep.
I'm gonna have to give you
a shot to numb the pain.
I don't need a shot.
Trust me.
You want a shot.
It's swollen.
It's gonna hurt like a...
there. Can l go now?
That didn't even hurt?
I have superpowers, okay?
Mr. Tresselt's having
a corpus callosotomy.
What's that gonna look like?
We'll be severing some of the fibers
that connect the right and left
hemisphere of his brain...
To prevent the spread of
seizure activity from one half
of his brain to the other.
Good. Right.
Daddy's letting them chop his brain
in half because daddy's a big dummy.
Yes, he is.
They're not chopping my
brain in half, Leanne.
Chop! Right down the middle.
Taylor should function much
like he does right now.
- Really?
- I'm having five seizures a day, Leanne.
I know that.
You don't leave me in a
room alone with the baby.
You think l don't notice?
You ask your mother to come by every
time you need to take a shower.
That's not the reason.
It's because you think
l'm a danger to the baby.
And l am.
Look, if you're not sure,
for any reason,
we can wait.
I want to be able to
take care of our baby.
Please, Leanne,
we already agreed.
Please.
I got this kid in the pit.
She's psycho and her foster parents
are beating the crap out of her.
She tell you that or you
figure it out yourself?
Well, she's covered in bruises.
She's got a 10-centimeter lace on
her arm with three staples in it,
Iike from a staple
gun in your garage.
Her parents did that?
Well, she says she
did it herself.
She's got this whole bit about being a
superhero and how she can take the pain.
You call social services?
They're on their way down.
Okay,
well have them speak to the parents
while you run a cold pressure test on
the girl.
A what?
Ice water.
Test her response to pain.
At the very least,
it'll keep her distracted while
the parents are questioned.
You requested me?
Yeah, l did.
You were weird this morning.
I wasn't weird...
any more than l normally
am in the morning.
It's a weird time of
day for a lot of people.
It's bright...
and crowded at our house in the morning.
There's just a lot of
people running around.
Good. We have a
radical case today.
You're gonna be glad
you're with me.
Thanks.
Mr. Jasper Hobie.
- Dr. T.
- Hey!
You missed me.
More than words can say.
This is Dr. O'malley.
He's gonna be helping out.
Hi.
How you doin'?
June 12th, baby.
Mm-hmm.
2.4-mile swim,
112 miles on the bike
and then a marathon.
Mm. That is rockin'.
Am l gonna be ready?
You bet your sculpted
ass you are.
l love this woman.
You had three
surgeries last year.
Yeah, two rotator
cuffs and an A.C.L.
All with dr. T.
And now you're having
an ankle replacement?
We waited over a
year for a match.
We're gonna replace his ankle with
an ankle joint from a cadaver.
Who's my guy?
Your donor?
Well, he hasn't been
dead long, right?
Um, about a week.
And he's downstairs.
No way.
Can l meet him,
pay my respects?
I don't think you two are
gonna have much to talk about.
Dr. O'malley's gonna
handle your labs.
have you met my guy?
Hey, superkid.
Where are my parents?
They're talking to
some grown-ups.
I'm not a moron.
They're talking to
a social worker.
Megan...
these bruises,
these cuts all over you,
this isn't normal.
I get in fights a lot, okay?
Because l'm stronger than
some of the other kids,
so l end up defending the ones who
are wimpy or small or whatever.
You know you're scrawny, right?
I mean,
you're not one of the big kids.
Yeah, but l can take
them in a fight.
All right.
Put your hands in here.
Why?
Because... we're gonna
test your superpowers.
You don't believe me?
Punch me in the stomach right here.
Come on.
Punch me in the stomach.
Let's just stick to the water.
Just put your hand in here.
And l'll--l'll race you.
You can race me. What? Come on.
What are you afraid of, uh,
you afraid of a little ice?
You afraid l'm gonna beat you?
Come on. On the count of three.
One, two, three.
Pull your hand out when it
starts to hurt, please.
What are you, deaf?
It won't start to hurt.
Just think about it, okay?
Superheroes are all kids
with dead parents, like me.
And they all figured out when they were
around my age they could do things
that nobody else could,
like me.
You missed your plane?
- Grounded on account
of bad weather.
It's a cloudless sky.
That happens like,
twice a year in Seattle.
Yeah, but there's a
typhoon in New York.
Sit down.
Have a drink with me.
No, l'm not having a drink with you.
I am working.
At work, not here.
So coffee, right?
Mark--
Joe, can we get the
doctor a coffee?
And they think it's weird that
they can do all this stuff,
but they don't tell anybody because
people would freak out like you did.
What's wrong with you?
Son of a--ow!
Ah! Ah!
Take your hand outta
there before it falls off.
You need to relax.
You didn't feel anything?
Nothing?
No. Nobody ever believes me.
Like yesterday in school,
this kid said l was full of it.
I had to letim punch me in the stomach
25 times before he believed me,
and once with a baseball bat.
What?
We'll have cardiology
check this,
and then you'll be good to go.
All done. There's my guy.
Jake... we're almost all
done with this whole thing.
We're not almost done.
You still have brain surgery and God
knows how many weeks of recovery is
ahead of you.
She's right.
It's good to know what you're
getting yourself into.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
Yeah. Recovery's
hell on the spouse.
It's gonna be harder
for you than on him.
My mom's staying
with us for a week.
Maybe she should stay longer.
You know,
it's--it's brutal being the caretaker.
You'll be fetching the paper,
- and then cleaning the carpet...
- Honey.
And oh--oh,
he wants ice in a cup, not a mug.
It's like--it never stops.
It's the caretakers that
are the silent victims.
You know,
and when do you ever hear about them?
Honey, take the baby.
Never. I never hear
anything about them.
It's always, you know,
"the patient this,
the patient that."
Silent victims.
Honey, take the baby.
Oh!
Taylor!
Can someone help here,
please?!
Taylor, please.
Annette, come on!
His seizure lasted
about a minute,
and he was post-ictal for five.
Is the baby okay?
He's fine.
It shouldn't interfere
with his surgery,
assuming we're
still going forward.
Honey?
Yeah. I guess we don't
have any other choice.
All right, Leanne,
I'm gonna do everything
l can, okay?
It's not gonna be
a walk in the park,
but l'm gonna take care of him.
Okay.
Hey, Izzie.
You done with the chief?
Not yet.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
What are you guys doing?
Uh, she's dating
everyone with a pulse,
and, uh, l'm trying to get
Burke out of the beljar.
Crap. I'm late for Finn.
Gotta go.
You're sure you're okay?
Yeah.
She's playing the field,
and l've got a wife.
Point to the justice.
Uh... okay.
Here's the thing--
we've both really
enjoyed each other,
b-before and now again,
and--and l think that's
a healthy release.
I mean,
l-l think it's--it's healthy,
for everybody involved.
And, um,
but l do think that
just because l made
what can only be considered
a transcontinental...
booty call...
doesn't mean that we should be
trying to make
something out of this.
Stop doing that!
Why?
Because l can't think.
We're good together.
We aren't.
You have to go home.
Come back with me.
You're insane.
I'm not going back--
I'm not going back to New York.
'Cause it was just about sex?
Ooh!
Oh.
Okay. Uh, well...
good-bye.
Good-bye.
Stevens was supposed to
be in my office at 9:30.
Didn't show.
Did you two change your minds?
No, she said she was coming in.
I'm sure she'll track you down.
We need to run a C.T.
On this kid's abdomen.
This superhero stuff's
way out of hand.
It's all right if she
thinks she's a superhero.
I believed in Santa
Claus till l was 11.
Really?
Did Santa ever hit you in
the gut with a basebalbat?
Hey, lab's good?
Yeah, they're all clear.
So why does a guy have four
ortho surgeries in one year?
Because he's a serious athlete.
His body takes a beating.
Maybe his body can't handle it.
Do you know how many
triathlons the guy's done?
Right, he's 55.
Do you think an ankle replacement and
26 miles a day is still a good idea?
Um, what, do you think we
should fit him for a walker?
He's pounding the crap
out of his joints,
and he's asking
you to clean it up.
Do you know how many hips l replace
because people can't be bothered to
walk around the
block once a month?
Sometimes, we can make
dreams come true.
It's not all the often.
When we can, we should.
Don't you think?
Yeah, yeah.
George,
don't worry about it.
Hey, l was gonna
go home for lunch.
You wanna come?
Callie just called my house
"home." Where does she get that?
Shh.
It is not her home.
What are you doing?
Meredith and Finn.
50 dn on whether Shepherd shows
up to challenge Finn to a duel.
Oh, can l be, uh,
with 5?
That's not a bet.
That's milk money, dude.
Oh and she's laughing because he made
a joke which probably wasn't funny.
- "Oh, you funny vet."
- l left the rest of my cash at home,
which l can call it
because l live there.
I'm not a visitor.
Hey, you're a loser.
You like comic books, right?
- No.
- l got this kid, this patient.
She thinks she's a superhero.
What's up with that?
Superhero?
Well, superheroes look like anyone,
like you or me.
Maybe they're not someone that people
necessarily notice as extraordinary,
maybe in their daily life,
they get walked on,
but then there's a moment--
they get hit by a cosmic ray or
bitten by a radioactive spider,
and then suddenly,
something that has been
inside them all this time,
Iying dormant,
comes raging out--
Dude, forget l asked.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go. Okay. Ahem.
Come on, come on, come on.
takes it like a man...
and walks away.
Thank you. 43...
He's comin' back.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yes, he is.
Mnh-mnh.
Give me my money, Mary Jane.
Let it go.
Oh, god.
I'm so sorry about this.
What?
Hi.
You're having lunch?
In fact, we are.
Oh, it looks good.
You know,
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but l'm doing a
corpus callosotomy.
Thought you might
like to scrub in.
Are you serious? When?
Mm-hmm.I'm gonna guess now.
Look, if you're busy,
don't bother, but, you know,
it's not something that happens every day.
- He's cutting a man's brain in half.
I'm sorry.
I'm an intern and...
I have a lot to learn.
Apparent so do l.
It's okay.
Oh, shoot.
I'll call you tonight.
Oh, you're busy tonight.
She has a date.
I'm sorry, Finn.
It's okay. Go.
Take care.
- l think l owe you another 50.
- Yeah, l think you do.
Coming or going?
I don't know.
Me neither.
That was brilliant, really.
I thought so, yes.
It wasn't because now l
owe Finn another date.
That's okay.
He needs all the help he can get.
This isn't gonna
be easy for him.
Oh, you think he
can't take the heat?
I think he's out of his league.
But you gotta hand it
to the guy for trying.
This is Mr. Tresselt.
Prep him.
I thought you said
we were operating.
We orate at 4:00.
I'm not just gon slide
you into the O.R.
You gotta work a little,
too, right?
How much is this
gonna cost my parents?
That's not something you
need to be worrying about.
But this is so stupid.
I'm fine.
Hey, punch me in the stomach,
right here.
Stop telling people to
punch you in the stomach.
You need to lie
down and not move.
Which of the superfriends
can do that?
Hi, Miranda.
You needed a consult?
Yeah. Just waiting
for a picture.
Haven't seen you since you were
sucking down martinis at Joe's.
Oh, yeah. That was just--
well, l'm--l'm over that.
Good.
We talked about, uh--
a lot of things.
And l remember--none of them.
Is that for the best?
I think so.
She came in for sutures,
but she's a walking accident and has
got an off-the-charts pain threshold.
I'm thinking--
chronic insensitivity
to pain, yeah.
I've seen it in babies.
It's usually diagnosed young.
But... if she's been bounced
around in the foster care system--
Dr. Bailey,
what the hell is that?
Dr. Burke.
Oh, o'malley, how are you?
Good. How's your arm?
Good, good. Slow.
P.T., You know.
Yeah.
Well, uh,
we all miss you around here.
You're missed.
Hey, o'malley.
Stevens is standing
outside the hospital.
I am retracting the
right hemisphere.
What do we want to avoid?
Grey?
We want to avoid retractors
on the sagittal sinus.
That's right. Why?
To prevent sinus thrombosis.
Excellent.
Saw Dr. Burke today.
He looked good.
Yeah, he looks great.
He was meeting with the chief.
Working out the leave?
The what?
His leave of absence.
His what?
You've been standing
out here for a while.
For a while, I stood over there
Maybe you should sit down.
I don't want to sit down.
Maybe you should
sit down anyway.
Go inside, George.
Izzie, seriously this is--
I hate the bride thing.
I hate the pictures in the magazines
of the girl with the veil and the
flowers that she's sniffing like it
never occurred to her to stick her nose
in there until there was
a camera pointed at her.
I hate the idea of
bridesmaids and the colors
and "does the bustle make my
ass look bigger or smaller?"
l hate the whole thing,
and i never wanted to be that girl.
That girl is stupid
and shallow.
Why the hell is that girl's
thoughts running through my head?
Izzie...
I'm going to do it, George
I'm going to walk
through those doors.
I just need to make sure that when l'm
standing in front of the chief
of surgery
I am not thinking
about my wedding dress.
And that's gonna
take another minute.
And with surgeof this kind,
there's always risk of an infection
if the bone is compromised--
blah, blah, blah,
I could die on the table.
Where do l sign?
I think we should talk through the
rest of this consent form first.
Fourth surgery in a year--
I know the routine.
When l come back in for my hip,
you can give me the
speech in french.
You're having hip surgery?
In the fall,
after Patagonia.
Do you still want
to meet your guy?
Megan's bleeding internally.
What?
It appears there's some
severe trauma to her abdomen.
If you're trying to
ask us if we hit her,
we've said ten times and
in ten different ways--
Social services cleared you,
and l'm sorry that we suggested
you were mistreating her.
But she's hurt pretty badly,
so we're gonna need to operate.
Oh, my god.
Megan may have a chromosomal
condition that causes her to not
feel any pain when
she's injured.
It would explain why
she gets hurt so often.
We need to do some genetic
testing before we can be sure,
but let's assume she'll need to be
monitored very closely from now on.
We got O.R. Three.
So surgery is the only option?
I think it is.
I-l know you've been put through
the wringer already today,
but l need to ask you to
trust me on this one.
Where is she?
Where's Megan?
She's over...
Hey, a leave of absence?
Yeah, l'm on my way home.
I was just making some notes for the
chief so he careassign my open cases.
Because you're taking
a leave of absence?
Okay, that's, like,
what, a week?
As long as it takes.
Well, it's not gonna
take that long.
You're already three weeks into P.T.
already, so--
Come on, recovery from brachial plexus
surgery is measured in
months, Christina,
years, not weeks.
The surgery's considered a success
when the patient can flex the elbow.
Some patients never move
their shoulder again.
Some don't recover sensation,
they don't recover dexterity,
they simply don't recover.
Yes, but you are
not one of those.
Really?
Says who?
Thanks, Carl.
That's my guy?
No, that's not him.
That's someone else
we lost last night.
He came in for lipo.
He died on the table.
Complications.
Didn't know they did
liposuction on men.
People do a lot of
stuff they don't need.
And, uh, the older you get,
Here he is.
That's your guy.
That can't be my guy.
He's really old.
His bones are probably brittle.
What are they doing using
a guy that old as my donor?
He's two years
younger than you are.
What the hell happened
to my ankle allograft?
I had O.R. 2 at 3:00.
Anybody wanna tell
me where it went?
It was canceled.
The guy went home.
Why the hell would he do that?
Hey!
O'malley!
We've lost supergirl,
and she's bleeding
into her abdomen.
Start looking in corners.
Do you think you cut enough of the
fibers out or are you gonna have to go
back in?
We'll see if the seizures
are under control.
If not,
we'll go back in for the last third.
Well, do l get to
scrub in on that, too,
or only if l'm in the middle
of a date with somebody else?
I wouldn't consider a meal
in the cafeteria a date.
Don't denigrate
the competition.
I have nothing but
respect for Dr. Dandridge.
It shows courage to woo a
woman with a tuna salad.
Keep an eye on Taylor.
If there's a problem, page me.
I'll see you in
the lobby at 8:00.
Hey, grey, l lost a kid.
Help me look for her before she
bleeds out in one of our bathrooms.
What's her name?
Megan!
It's not easy.
If you think you're a superhero,
you're not gonna let someone
come at you with a knife.
There's no way to tell what
it can do to your powers.
I mean,
if you take away Green Lantern's ring,
Hal Jordan is still a hero,
but it creates a crisis
of confidence...
- Come on, Megan.
- When you've worked hard
to hone your strength.
Hey, just look at,
uh, Batman.
Robin just marches
into the batcave,
and he says, you know,
"Here l am.
I'm gonna live here, too.
Give me some tights,
and l'm taking your towel."
I mean, Batman,
he fought for his powers, you know?
He honed his strength !
- Dude,
if you don't stop this,
I'm gonna punch
you in the face.
O'Malley.
Good luck with that.
I arrange for you to see an
incredibly cool surgery,
and you talk my patient out of it?
- No, l didn't--
You asked me what l thought,
you didn't like what l said,
so you went behind my back.
Jasper's gone.
He canceled the surgery.
- I expressed an opinion.
I suggested that, you know,
not everything has
to go at warp speed.
It is all warp speed with you.
It is all, "oh, your ankle hurts? Let's cut if off."
- You intimidated my patient.
You got a problem,
you bring it to me.
I'm not ready for us
to move in together.
And if you weren't toddler,
if you could use your words,
then maybe you could've said that
the first four times l asked you.
And then l would've said,
"oh, that's funny, me neither.
I'm looking for a place.
I'll be out in a week."
Really? Because remember, you--
George, save it. I'll be--
I'll be out in an hour.
Megan.
Megan. Oh.
Hi.
Weren't you just up on three?
I was. We lost a patient,
a little girl, and l was just--
Look, why don't you pick
a floor and stay on it,
and l'll pick a floor
on stay on that?
Because l really need a
moment or two without you.
Your face shs up in my head,
your... panties show up
in my husband's pocket--
really, you're everywhere--
and l need a moment
or two without you.
I get that.
Thanks.
megan.
Come on. Enough already.
We got half the hospital
looking for you.
Your powers of invisibility
are well intact. Get up.
You're a hosebag,
you know that?
And you have a potty mouth.
Nobody's cutting me open.
Hey, it's surgery.
We do it all the time.
In fact, it's all we do.
You can't keep telling my
foster parents l'm defective.
They can't afford surgery.
It's too expensive.
They can handle it.
They'll send me back.
Dude, that's stupid.
They got their own
personal superhero.
Nobody sends back a superhero.
I thought you said l
didn't have superpowers?
Yeah, well, you don't.
But take away Green
Lantern's ring,
the guy's still a hero, right?
Okay. Close your eyes.
Squeeze 'em tight.
Good. Okay.
Can you squeeze my fingers?
Fantastic.
Let's wiggle your
toes for me, please.
Very good, vy good.
Flying colors.
He's always tested well.
I kicked ass on the, uh...
what--what's it called?
The S.A.T.S.
Now can you tell me,
what is this?
Honey?
Take your time.
Honey, what's that called?
It's right in front of you.
Can you see this here?
I can see it.
I-l just can't think of the...
That's all right.
t's okay. Take your time.
See, sometimes the names
of things are tough.
So try again.
What's my name?
I can't...
Wh-what's his name?
I-l know what it is.
I-l-l just...
what's his name?
Leanne, let's just
give him a moment.
It...
what's his name?
I...
He named the baby.
He named him after his father.
How do you not know the
name of your own baby?
Well, he knows who the baby is.
See, the right side of the brain senses
emotional connection to the baby.
It just can't communicate with the
left brain where the words are formed.
The pathway to the two
sides has been compromised.
He needs to make new pathways.
How long is that gonna take?
Well, he'll get there.
Recovery is hardork.
It's a learning process.
You need to be patient.
You need to help him.
He can't do this
without your support.
Man, she wasn't kidding
about the baseball bat.
I need more lap pads.
Just keep 'em coming.
Are you gonna resect the liver?
I need to try and
do a debridement.
Look at this.
Everybody wants a
life without pain,
And what does it get you?
She needs to be on
a poster somewhere,
to remind people pain's
there for a reason.
Megan's stable.
I ordered a repeat
h&h in two hours.
She been outhere all day?
Dinner was good.
Dinner was excellent.
Are you coming in?
I don't know. Am l?
Well, you could come in
for a drink or a-a coffee.
I owe you one from
this morning.
Yeah, you do.
- Hi.
Finn.
I didn't think you
guys would be here.
I just wantedto drop this off.
It's strawberry ice cream.
A patient made it for me.
Patient's owner.
It's made from scratch.
Real strawberries.
I love strawberry ice cream.
And he remembered.
I did.
I just thought l'd
leave it by the door.
Oh, you didn't
think it would melt?
No, you take your chances.
Worked out for you.
What exactly is going on here?
He's crashing our date.
Where do you think
l got that idea?
I didn't crash your date.
It was professional.
You can't operate without her?
I certainly operate
well with her.
Enough.
This is not dating.
I want moonlight and flowers and
candy and people trying to feel me up.
Nobody is trying to feel me up.
Nobody is even looking at me.
l'm an intern.
Do the two of you have any idea how
much effort it takes to do all this?
I'm waxed and plucked,
and l have a clean top on.
And the two of you are looking at each other.
- Meredith, it's--
No! My fantasy is not two men looking at each other.
- We didn't--
No talking until one of you
figures out how to put on a date.
I want heat, l want romance.
Damn it,
l wanna feel like a freakin' lady!
The fantasy is simple...
Pleasure is good...
Ahem. I'm in
room 22-something--2214.
If anyone calls,
I'm not here.
Yes, ma'am.
And twice as much
pleasure is better...
Hi. Checking in, please.
Certainly. Room for...
one.
That pain is bad...
Room 1817. Any messages?
And no pain is better.
Checking in, please.
Room for one.
Something on the 22nd
floor if you've got it.
I'll take a look.
Dr. Sloan?
Dr. Webber.
What are you doing in seattle?
I don't know.
I have a thing for ferry boats.
But the reality
is different.
Are you cooking for me?
I am not.
You can take a leave of
absence if you want to,
but you're not gonna
sit on your ass all day.
You're gonna work hard
and you're gonna get
every bit of your strength
and dexterity back.
Really? How?
Put it back together.
The reality is that pain is
there to tell us something.
Iz.
I'll do it.
Izzie.
I can do it, Alex.
I know l can.
Does it hurt?
Yeah.
Where does it hurt?
Everywhere.
Maybe it hurts for a reason.
Come on.
Let's go.
And there's only so much pleasure we
can take without getting
a stomachache.
And maybe that's okay.
Hey.
I didn't go in today.
Maybe tomorrow.
Hey, George.
Callie moved out,
which is a relief.
Oh, l am so relieved.
Strawberry.
This is good.
You left spare(?)
on this spoon.
No l didn't
You did a little...
Maybe some fantasies
are only supposed
to live in our dreams.
Brought to you by :
Raceman and Bemused
www.forom.com