Who's Mark?
Derek found us in bed together.
You are in love with me.
I'm well off, but I'm not into money,
and I'm hot.
I'm a catch. You know, if you can wrap
your head around the enlarged, failing heart
and the dependency to I.V. Meds.
- I'm not ready for us to move in together.
- I'll be out in an hour.
An hour ago, he was proposing.
- Are you gonna tell Shepherd about...
- Not yet.
If I haven't made a decision by the
end of the day, I'm flipping a coin.
A girl can only hold out for so long.
Grey's Anatomy - Episode 304
"What I Am"
At some point during surgical residency,
most interns get a sense of
who they are as doctors
and the kinds of surgeons
they're going to become.
If you ask them, they'll tell you--
they're going to be general surgeons...
orthopedic surgeons...
neurosurgeons...
distinctions which do more than
describe their areas of expertise.
They help define who they are.
Because outside the operating room,
not only do most surgeons
have no idea who they are,
they're afraid to find out.
Time me.
I've been timing you.
My last time was off by six seconds.
Well, it's not about speed,
it's about accuracy.
I mean, your sutures are fine.
My sutures are textbook.
The edges are perfectly aligned.
Mm-hmm. You're ready.
- I need more chickens.
- No more chickens, okay?
It's bad enough that Meredith is dating
a vet. I'm not dating a chicken surgeon.
Stop second-guessing.
It's not like you.
Your hand is fine, and Shepherd
will clear you for surgery.
- Cristina.
- Yeah, baby?
- Nothing.
So Izzie left the house this morning.
That's a good sign.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. I'm just not feeling like myself.
O'malley seems to have that
effect on women. Ask Dr. Torres.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Dude... You threw her out on her ass.
I did not.
Who told you that?
Torres.
- Oh...
- Don't worry. I get it.
She's hot, but she's not for you.
Why is that?
- Because she's hot.
- Mm.
- Callie.
- Mnh-mnh.
Hey, come on. Wait.
Before you start yelling, you were right.
I should have told you how
I felt about you moving in,
not that you were moving in. It's just,
I'm not good at the whole...
"talking about feelings" thing.
I bet you told Meredith how
you felt, though, didn't you?
And Izzie--
you don't seem to have any trouble
talking to them, George, but me--
Let's go, people. I've been in surgery
since 2:00 A.M. I'm in no mood.
George.
I miss you.
No cutting. No cutting.
- Yang, you're late!
Hey, I got here before George.
- I'm here. I was here.
Nice of you to join us, Yang.
Yeah, what are you smiling about?
Aren't you supposed to be on the gynie brigade?
Yeah, whatever.
Woman troubles?
Oh. Men troubles.
I think this dating two guys
thing is getting to me,
the stress of it.
Finn, Derek, Derek, Finn.
I think I'm getting an ulcer.
McDreamy and The Vet are making you sick?
- I just need to make a choice
and get it over with.
Shawn Sullivan, 62,
had minimally invasive bypass surgery two
days ago to remove a blockage from his L.A.D.--
But  I'm all better now.
Thank you, George.
So what do you think, Miranda? Can I stop being
a burden to you good people and go on home?
You need to stop interrupting the doctors, Shawny.
You just need to listen to what they say.
I need to get back to the dealership.
They're gonna can me if I'm out too long.
They can't can you, sweetie. You're the best salesman they got. Come on.
What do you sell?
- Cars.
My shawny could sell... anything.
Yeah, I believe he can.
What he can't sell me on is going back to
work before he gets his oxygen levels up.
So you put that oxygen
back on, Mr. Sullivan,
before I even think about
letting you out of here.
You know, and if I do, I want your word--
nothing fried, no alcohol
and no cigarettes.
- Boy, you're tough, Miranda.
- I need your word, Mr. Sullivan,
or I'm not gonna sign
those discharge papers.
I give you my word.
Hmm. All right, then.
Mrs. Sullivan, you need to go to the
front desk to fill out some paperwork,
and then you can take
your husband home.
How are we doing, guys?
She's at 8 centimeters, but the
baby's still at minus 3 station.
So what do we do, uh,
patterned breathing, squatting?
Dude, squatting?
Dr. Karev, how do we normally
proceed in a situation like this?
We monitor the baby's progress.
If the descent stops entirely
during active labor,
we perform a c-section.
Not on me, you don't.
I'm sorry, Dr. Karev, but...
Jeff and I have a natural birth plan,
and Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd promised us that...
-I promised that we would do what we can,
but if your labor intensifies and the baby doesn't descend--
Well, then we'll wait until he does, right?
I'm not having a c-section.
A c-section is actually the safest way...
- To what, avoid a lawsuit?
We don't have to decide right now.
I'm not gonna miss out on an experience
that my body was made for
just because it's more
convenient for you.
You all right, Dr. Grey?
Yeah, Dr. Bailey. I just...
Need to make a choice is all.
Karev. Dr. Grey, I am clipping a
basilar tip aneurysm. Any interest?
Dr. Bailey, can I get...
Oh, my God.
Oh... my... God. - Oh, my God.
Is that... McSteamy.
No, Mr. Sullivan,
don't light that!
Somebody get a fire extinguisher!
Call a code red.
Make sure he has an airway.
Sir, can you hear me? Sir?
No, he's out. Hit his head.
Small hematoma in the occipital region.
Get him to the burn unit till he's
stabilized, and then get a C.T.
- Go.
- Right away, doctor. Come on.
- You're burning up.
- I'm fine.
You don't look fine. You look
beautiful, but you don't look fine.
-  Now I'm gonna throw up.
- Go, you have aneurysms to clip
and surgeons to confront.
- You're gonna be all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Will you look after her, please?
- Mm-hmm.
You think I'd miss this?
- What kind of idiot lights a cigarette in a hospital?
- Apparently people do idiotic things all the time.
Chief. Chief.
I thought you were going back to New York.
I thought it was time for a change.
You can't do this. You can't be here.
Sure I can. It was easy.
Sublet the apartment,
sold the practice.
He is a liar and a cheat.
The man is one of the finest
plastic surgeons in this country.
His department will generate twice
the revenue neurosurgery does.
Money, that's why he's here?
Why do you think I'm here?
- This? This is why I left you.
I thought you left me for Derek.
I left New York because of him.
He was your best friend for years.
Right up until the point where
he had sex with my wife.
We all make mistakes.
Holy crap! Are you pregnant?
Oh, this is just perfect...
- An adulterous love child.
- Goes along with an adulterous sociopath.
Meredith.
Unh-unh. You've done
enough already.
Meredith.
Oh, uh, doctor, I-I finished
filling out the paperwork.
When do you think I can
take Shawny home?
Um...
So who's the father?
I'm not pregnant.
I didn't think I was pregnant
when I was pregnant, either.
But the abdominal pain, fever
and the nonstop vomiting--
I'm not pregnant.
You don't know who
the father is, do you?
It would have to be Derek's.
There's no way it could be Finn's.
You haven't had sex
with the vet yet?
Well, you gotta get outta
that relationship, immediately.
Oh, I can't be pregnant, can I?
- With McBaby.
- Oh!
Was I this mean to you
when you were pregnant?
Oh, I thought you said
you weren't pregnant.
She's not. We'll have
to run more tests.
In that case, can I have
some morphine?
I want you checking the
fetal monitor every 30 minutes.
What's the point?
The baby's nowhere near
where it needs to be,
and you know you're
gonna have to cut her open,
so why not get it over with?
Because it's not what the patient wants.
And it's our job as doctors
to balance the desires of the patient
against the risk of complications.
So if the patient wants to have a natural birth--
so if the patient wants a
natural birth, it's not surgical.
So why not just cut me loose
and let me in on a surgery?
I might actually learn something.
- Like Sloan's burn case.
- I'm going into plastics anyway.
Do  you think that Mark Sloan
has anything to teach you?
He is just like you. He is only
looking out for himself.
So what? Your patient's
looking out for herself,
you're looking out for yourself
- No, I'm not, actually.
Well, maybe you should be.
Go. Go find Sloan.
Do whatever you want.
Just get out of my face, Karev.
Go!
- You know, I'm not saying he's a bad doctor.
- Of course not. Listen--
I'm--I'm saying that he's,
like, a bad person.
The man has no morality, no ethics.
Yeah. But there's no pain,
there's no numbness,
but, um...
- I mean,
The question is do we really want our
interns learning from somebody like that?
Derek, my arm.
Yeah. Oh, it's good. It's great.
You have great
range of motion.
I  can clear you for surgery.
- Really? You're sure?
- Yeah, absolutely.
Complete recovery.
You're not having any problems, right?
- No. Uh...
I-I've been doing his physical
therapy with him every night, so...
He's perfect. He's Burke.
Good. Glad to hear it.
Welcome back, Dr. Burke.
Yeah.
Uh, Dr. Bailey wanted to know
if you still needed an intern?
No, I'm fine.
How's, uh, Dr. Grey?
Oh, she's not pregnant
with anyone's baby, so..
Izzie... Good to see you.
You want some lunch?
I'm meeting somebody.
Anybody I know?
Actually, I don't even know him.
You never met?
Know what he looks like?
So for all you know, he could be an older,
rugged, ex-marine-looking dude?
Dr. Stevens?
Mr. Duquette.
Please... Call me Denny.
Pretty girl.
Not Denny's type at all.
Really?
What was his type?
Um...
Dark-haired girls, smart.
Uh... well, not that you're not smart.
You're a doctor. Obviously--
I was. I was a doctor.
I'm not anymore.
Oh, that's right.
Dr. Webber said you'd quit.
You... talked to Dr. Webber?
Uh, yes,
and he said that, well,
if I wanted to hear the whole
story, I should talk to you.
So if you don't mind, Dr. Stevens...
- Izzie.
Izzie... If you don't mind,
I need to hear the whole story.
Dr. Sloan.
You my intern?
Yeah. Uh, I'm your intern.
My face... oh.
No need to talk, Mr. Sullivan.
That's gonna be painful for a while.
My face.
He wants to know that you can fix his face.
He needs to know that you can fix it.
I'm going to remove the burned tissue
and then bandage your face
with a dressing of live cells.
And that'll do it? His face
will be back like it was?
Because his face was-- it's a nice face.
He's a salesman.
I'm gonna do absolutely
everything I can, Mrs. Sullivan.
We'll need a neuro consult
before we operate.
Anything  else? I mean, uh,
I could do debridement or, uh--
Actually, there is one more thing.
Bone dry cappuccino.
Make it a double.
You're a good friend.
- You are so high right now.
Actually, you're my best friend
in the whole entire world.
Now I just feel sorry for you.
Why? Because I could die today?
This is why I hate being
around stoned people.
And if I did die today,
I'd only be remembered as the
slutty intern who dated two doctors.
No, one doctor, one vet.
Derek, Finn.
Derek or Finn?
I'd die as the girl who couldn't
make a choice, right?
Probably. But none of that matters,
because you'll be dead.
Dr. Grey... You've got a
fever, high white count
and tenderness over
McBurney's point, which suggests--
appendicitis.
Dr. O'malley, prep Dr. Grey for
surgery. You're scrubbing in.
I am, in Meredith's appendectomy?
I, uh...
Am I the only one who remembers the last time
George scrubbed in on an appendectomy?
He almost killed the guy. Sorry, George.
I don't have to scrub in, Dr. Bailey. I could just, uh...
uh... unless you want me to, which...
no. It's not gonna happen again.
That good enough for you, Dr. Grey?
You're pretty.
George! Ice chips.
- Hey.
- I, uh, heard Meredith's having an appy.
It wasn't my idea to scrub in.
- I tried to get out of it.
- George... I was just...
I just thought maybe we could have
a late supper at the Archfield.
Why would we have dinner at a hotel?
Because they bring it right to your room.
You're staying at the Archfield.
How--how are you affording that?
I still have some secrets, O'Malley.
And if you come see me tonight,
I just might show you one or two.
I was just checking on the Sullivans,
and how is he doing because he...
- You are?
Dr. Bailey. We met this morning.
I was the resident on
Mr. Sullivan's bypass.
Well, I don't need a resident on this case, so...
Excuse me. I wasn't asking
to be your resident.
I was asking how my patient was doing.
He's not your patient anymore.
Hey, so congratulations. I told you.
- Yeah.
- What? What?
Shepherd shouldn't have cleared me.
Burke, you're back.
You're back and you're fine.
- Burke.
- What?
What?
He just... shouldn't have cleared me.
Another contraction,
Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd.
You're fully dilated. But the
baby's only at minus 2 station.
- He just needs more time.
- We don't have it, Rebecca.
His heart rate's slowing
with each contraction.
If he starts having late decels, I...
- Is he having late decels?
- Not yet, but...
Then stop trying to scare me into
an operation I told you I don't want.
I have a birth plan.
Look, I'm not-- I'm not gonna be
one of those weak-ass women
who give all that up the minute
things start to get scary. I...
- Rebecca... your birth plan is just that, it's a plan.
- Jeff, get her out of here.
- Honey, I think she's just trying to be cautious...
Just get out! Just get out!
Get out! Aah!! Get out!
Since when do you "get out"?
Clearly, I am not myself today.
Never would've figured
Mark Sloan to be your type.
He's  not. He's not.
What is he doing here?
He's not supposed to be here.
I can't have him here. I can't.
He's supposed to be
in New York. I can't--
I can't function with him here.
I'm a professional here.
People respect me here.
But when he's here, I'm just--I'm--
A woman who gets the hots for
man-candy and cheats on her husband.
That is rude... and unkind...
And completely true.
Oh, my god. What am I gonna do?
For starters, you can keep your
knees closed in his presence.
- Miranda.
- You asked.
And also, you can remember that no man--
not Derek, not Mark-- defines who you are.
Well, let's see-- your complexion is flushed...
abdominal wall is tender.
Are you happy you have a boyfriend
who works in a hospital?
You... are just one of many men that I
happen to be dating at the moment.
Really?
- Mm-hmm.
How many of us are there?
Uh... well, there's, uh, you...
- Hm-hmm.
And Finn and...
well, forgive me for
pointing out the obvious,
but I don't see any practitioners of
veterinarian medicine at your bedside.
You would if you turned around.
Ah, Finn.
Derek.
Oh, can I just say how much it helps
that I am on drugs right now?
- So.
So how's life in the animal kingdom?
What about you, Derek?
Slow day?
If you need to take off, that's...
- No, it's fine. I can stay.
- Great.
- Okay, let's get you prepped and ready for...
- Dr. Shepherd. Dr. Finn.
- Now all my boys are here.
You're all so handsome...
and such good kissers.
Oh, God.
Excuse me?
She's on drugs.
He's an excellent kisser.
- You two... dated?
- You didn't know?
It wasn't a date so much as a
disastrously uncomfortable sexual experience.
Oh... I-I-- I can't be here.
None of you can be here.
This woman is being prepped for surgery,
which means you all need to leave.
- Gladly.
- Now! Not you, O'Malley.
Dr. Bailey, all my boyfriends are here.
Not for long. Say good-bye, Dr. Grey.
- I'll be here when you wake up.
- So will I.
- Now!
What are you doing?
What does it look like I'm doing?
You're not in med school. You don't need
to practice procedures on a corpse.
Better than on a patient.
- Burke, your hand is fine.
- Right.
Are you... mad at me?
Hey, hey, you're mad at me?
Forget it.
Just... don't worry about it.
You have patients.
I'm on call for the pit.
- Cristina--
- I-I am not leaving.
Time me.
The transplant went better than
anyone expected, and he was better.
He was... so much better.
But Denny, um...
before the surgery, he was hooked
up to a machine called--
you're not answering my question.
I'm trying. I-I'm getting there.
It--it was complicated,
and his heart was--
I don't give a damn about the medicine.
I know what killed my son.
He had a bad heart. He had a bad
heart for a long time. I get that.
What I don't get... is how a girl like you
goes from being my son's doctor to-
to his fiancée on the very day he's
supposed to get a new heart.
What I don't get is how you got him to
propose to you hours before he died.
Mr. Sullivan,
I'm gonna recommend a night
of observation in the I.C.U.
Before Dr. Sloan proceeds with your surgery. - Oh.
Is that really necessary, Dr. Shepherd?
The longer we wait, the higher the risk of infection.
I think it's important that we attend to
potential life-threatening injuries
before moving on to cosmetic, Dr. Sloan.
He's not here for a face-lift, Derek.
He's a burn victim.
Why did you ask for a consult if you've
already established a course of action?
Because I thought you were good enough at your job
to put aside the personal and do
what's best for the patient.
My job? You're telling me how to do my job?
Now you're telling me how to do my--
Please, I'm sure it's complicated. And I know
Shawny's sorry for lighting that smoke.
He was trying to keep his
word to Dr. Bailey.
He told her he wasn't gonna smoke
when he got home, and he was...
Just trying to keep his word.
He knows he did wrong.
But he'd... he's a salesman. That's who he is.
So could you please just fix his face?
Could you do that for us, please?
If what happened between me and
Addison is so unforgivable,
how do you justify what happened
between you and Meredith?
What the hell are you talking about?
You need me to be the bad guy? Fine.
But I'm not the only bad guy here, Derek.
You and me, we're the same.
Addison. Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd.
You bellowed, Dr. Grey.
- Hi.
- You certainly are, aren't you?
But you're not pregnant.
No.
Are you okay?
Fine.
How are you?
I'm trying to choose between two men.
Okay, well, good luck with that.
How did you know
Derek was the one?
Excuse me?
I know you hate me and all,
and you don't owe me anything.
Nothing. No... thing.
What was I saying?
Derek.
Right.
I want him to be the one.
But I would know if he was the
one, right? You knew, right?
You don't...
I didn't... know. I just...
Derek's the kind of guy...
I just knew he wouldn't hurt me.
I mean, not on purpose, anyway,
not the way I hurt him.
He hurt me...
when he chose you.
I should've let him go.
I should've stepped aside,
been a better person.
I... should've...
a lot of things.
Me, too.
A lot of things.
I don't hate you.
How come we never talked
like this before?
The only reason we are
talking like this right now
is because I know you won't
remember a single word of this
once the drugs wear off.
Dr. Karev, you need to see this.
I'm off the case.
Page Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd.
We did, but...
oh, man.
Were you just
talking to Meredith?
Yeah.
What?
Don't, um...
Don't hurt her again.
- You planning on killing a woman today?
- What?
The c-section you should've performed
on Rebecca Bloom this morning?
At this point, it may be too
late for her and the baby.
Nice work, doc.
Get an O.R. and an anesthesiologist.
We're doing a crash
c-section right away.
Oh! What is happening?
Rebecca, your baby is having late decels.
He's in distress.
We have to get you into the delivery
room and get him out right now.
- Oh, no, please.
- This is no longer a conversation.
I am your doctor, and I am responsible
for your life and your baby's life,
and I'm not about to lose either
one of you, are we clear?
You just gonna stand there,
Karev, or are we doing this?
Mr. Duquette, Denny and I--
he--he was my patient for months.
And the minute he died, you quit your job.
- Because I couldn't..
- Four years of medical school,
now that's a whole lot of debt.
How were you planning on
paying that back, huh?
Did you think that Denny
would pay for everything?
Why are you... what--
what are you talking about?
I'm talking about protecting my son.
Oh, where were you
when he needed you?
Because I was there the
whole time. I was there.
I was working 80-hour weeks,
and I was still always there.
He had so many surgeries,
so many procedures.
He was so scared.
Where were you then?
Where were you?
You may not get me,
but you don't have to because
I don't get you either.
- I don't get how a father abandons his dying son.
- Wait. Wait.
Is that what he told you, that I--
that his mother and I abandoned him?
Well... he didn't tell you the truth.
What? What?
Oh, Burke. I thought you-- you told me--
- I can't hold it still long enough to attach the graft.
- You told me your hand was fine.
- I can't--
- you told me your hand was fine.
It's not fine!
You wanted to believe I was fine.
You wanted me to be fine.
You wanted-- I wanted-- damn it.
My hands... are the only things that
I have that are of any value to me, to you.
- Not to me--
- Oh, yes, to you. You want Preston Burke.
My hands... these are who I am.
If I can't do this, if I can't
finish this surgery, then...
what if I hold the vessel?
Come on.
Burke...
if I hold the vessel...
- I can attach the graft.
- Okay, so...
I--okay, I put my hand...
Nobody has to know.
Derek. Look, I know
you're mad at me,
but Mark Sloan is
the best in his field.
Any surgical unit in this country
would be lucky to have him.
You did what you thought was best for this hospital.
- I did.
Uh... are you all right?
Can I ask you a... personal question?
Why did you leave Meredith's mother?
I could've left Adele.
I could've gone away with Ellis.
But I would've had so much
baggage, so much guilt.
Ellis couldn't see it, but I wasn't...
I never would've made her happy,
not like she deserved to be happy.
I was a better man for walking away.
I loved her enough to walk away.
Oh, oh, on the table,
keep me draped.
Too many people have
seen me naked already.
I'd like to keep whatever dignity I have left.
McSteamy.
Meredith--
- McSteamy! Whoo-hoo!
Is that what you're calling me now-- McSteamy?
Yeah, but I don't think you
were supposed to know that.
How's my favorite dirty mistress?
Haven't you heard? Now
I'm an adulterous whore.
He's so beautiful.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
The appendix is out. Now
what do I do, O'Malley?
You invert the stump into the cecum
and pull up on the purse strings.
Show me.
Okay.
Where's my coffe Karev?
I got pulled into an
emergency c-section. Sorry.
That's too bad. I was gonna let
you scrub in on a real surgery.
Oh, well. Maybe next time...
if O.B. can spare you.
See ya.
Finn.
Derek.
She's still in surgery.
Yeah. Yeah, I figured
I'd wait for her here.
Meredith, uh, tells me that you fish.
She does?
She tells me a lot of things.
Have you been up to Cornet Bay?
It's mostly chinook, some rockfish.
- You fish?
- Yeah, as much as I can.
My wife hated it.
you had a wife?
Yeah. She died.
I'm sorry. I-I didn't know.
Meredith doesn't tell you a lot of things. Only me.
Yeah. Funny. Very funny.
You know, when I heard that she was sick, I...
People come through
appendectomies all the time.
I mean, she'll be fine, right?
- Mm-hmm.
You really like her, don't you?
- Yeah.
You're a good guy.
Uh, yeah, I think so. I-I hope so.
Okay.
- See you later.
- I'll see you.
It was doctor after doctor.
Everybody had a--
had a different opinion.
Everybody had a worse opinion.
Before that, Denny had never
been sick a day in his life.
Before that, he had been...
You know, the...
The thought of having to bury your own son...
His mother and I, we didn't--
we didn't handle it very well.
One day, we came home and
found a note saying, uh,
he didn't want us to have to
watch him die, that he left.
We thought... we thought he
was dead all this time.
I had no idea.
Believe me, if I had known, I would...
Never have let him get away with that.
I believe it.
I worked my way through med school.
- You--
I paid off my debt.
- Look, I'm, uh, sorry about before.
You--you don't have to explain--
I do. I do.
You're his dad and you're
trying to protect him.
And I want you to know that
I've paid off all my debt.
And when I met Denny,
I was gonna be a surgeon,
so I didn't need his money.
I had everything I needed.
I had everything I needed un-until, um...
We miss him.
My god, we miss him.
Yeah.
I, um...
yeah.
What is this?
It's for you.
It's from Denny.
Hey. You ready to go?
I'm sorry I have to do this,
but I have to go home.
It's Izzie.
It's always Izzie or Meredith.
It's... it's never me.
Oh, come on. That is not true.
Who am I to you, George?
Am I your girlfriend? Am I somebody
you mess around with?
Do you even know?
well, guess what.
Now you don't have to
bother figuring it out.
How's he doing, Mrs. Sullivan?
We're just getting an
update now, Dr. Bailey.
The surgery went well.
We removed the necrotic tissue,
applied the live cells,
and if his body responds, in three or four weeks--
He'll have his face back?
Mr. And Mrs. Sullivan,
Your face may never be exactly what it was.
Even if everything goes perfectly well,
there will be scarring.
But he's a salesman.
He has such a nice face.
You have an incredible wife, Mr. Sullivan,
And half a dozen car salesmen in
the lobby waiting to visit you.
Your face may be different,
but you know as well as I do,
it's not about what you look like
Or your job or how successful you are.
It's about having people in your life
that you love and who love you.
That--that's all that matters.
How you feeling?
Oh, mortified.
I was just explaining the "Meredith
on morphine" experience.
Ahh. You don't remember?
Was it memorable?
I'll let Finn tell you. I'll come back.
No, a-actually, I've--
I've just been sent on a
mission to get the, uh,
patient's ice chips. Be right back.
How badly did I embarrass myself?
What?
You deserve to be with somebody
who makes you happy,
somebody who's not gonna
complicate your life,
somebody who won't hurt you.
He's a better guy, Meredith.
Finn's the better guy.
Derek...
I'm walking away.
He left a message.
Denny left a message for
his parents the night...
His father gave me the number
and the code, but, um...
I just couldn't do it alone.
Addison... Can we talk?
- I don't want you here, Mark.
I think I've made that abundantly clear. So...
If you insist on staying, just...
Know that we're coworkers,
and nothing more.
Karev.
As of right now, you are
officially off my service.
But for what it's worth,
I think you're gonna miss me.
Hello, you've reached the Duquettes.
DENNY : Dad, Mom, it's me.
DENNY : I'm calling from Seattle Grace hospital,
DENNY : where the beautiful, talented and
incredibly stubborn Dr. Isobel Stevens
DENNY : has just given me a brand-new
heart and promised to marry me.
DENNY : I know we've had our differences,
and I'm sorry we've been out of touch.
More chicken surgery?
I'm making you dinner.
DENNY : Believe it or not, I was trying to make everything better.
DENNY : I know you're angry.
I hope you'll forgive me.
DENNY : Turns out, sometimes you have
to do the wrong thing...
McSteamy, right?
You must be a friend of Meredith's.
Not really. Dr. Torres. Callie.
Mark Sloan.
Bad day?
You could say that.
- You?
- Oh, yeah.
So what have you heard
about me, exactly?
Mostly things that involve
the words "dirty" and "bad."
Right.
I guess there, uh, really is no
starting over, is there?
Can I buy you a drink, Callie?
Only if you have it delivered to
my hotel room, because I'm off to bed.
DENNY :Sometimes you have to make a big mistake...
You comin'?
DENNY : To figure out how to make things right.
So what time do they let us visitors
start visiting in the morning?
You shouldn't do that.
I don't mind.
No, Finn. Really, you shouldn't do that.
So it's Derek.
I'm sorry.
Can I ask why?
You are a great guy...
you're a wonderful guy,
and you may even be the better guy.
But...
- He's the one.
- And I wish he wasn't.
He's gonna hurt you again...
And when he does,
I won't be here.
DENNY : Mistakes are painful...
Take care of
yourself, Meredith.
DENNY : But they're the only way to
find out who you really are.
DENNY : I know who I am now.
I know what I want.
DENNY : I've got the love of my life...
a new heart...
DENNY : and I want you guys to get on the
next plane out here, and meet my girl.
DENNY : Everything's gonna be different now.
DENNY : I promise, from here on now,
DENNY : nothing's ever gonna be the same.
DENNY : I love you. Bye.
Brought to you by Raceman & Bemused.
www.forom.com