PREVIOUSUSLY ON
"GREY'S ANATOMY"...
GOT ADMITTED LAST NIGHT.
(Izzie) GEORGE'S DAD
I MET A SISTER
I NEVER KNEW I HAD.
(Izzie) CAN YOU IMAGINE--Y WHOLE
FAMILY YOU KNOW NOTHING ABOUT?
I'M JUST ASKING
ABOUT YOUR DAD.
WHY DO YOU CARE?
YOU BROKE UP WITH ME,
REMEMBER?
MR. O'MALLEY HAS ELECTED
TO HAVE DR. HAHN
PERFORM HIS VALVE REPLACEMENT.
I CAN CLEAR YOU FOR SURGERY.
YOU'RE SURE?
YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
I NEED YOU TO TELL ME
WHY YOU DIDN'T WANT ME IN
ON YOUR SURGERY.
I'M AFRAID
I JUST CLDLDN'T USE YOU.
I CAN'T SEE YOUR MOTHER
ANYMORE.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO RETIRE, RICHARD.
(Preston) I'M GOING TO BE CHIEF.
I HAD A TREMOR AND I DIDN'T
SAY ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
WE CROSD D THE LINE.
YOU DRAGGED ME
ACROSS THE LINE.
www.1000fr.com Present
Capture:FRM@FadeOut
Sync:FRM@Navel
HE'S WITH HER.
HE'S WITH THAT WOMAN--
HIS WIFE.
@@
I DON'T THINK HE IS,
NOT ANYMORE.
HE IS. I MEAN,
WHY WOULD HE DO THAT?
HE LOVES ME. (scoffs) I MEAN,
WHY WOULD HE GO BACK TO HER?
I GAVE UP EVERYTHING
FOR HIM.
MOM.
MOM, LOOK AT ME.
THIS HAPPENED...
A VERY LONG TIME AGO.
THIS IS NOT HAPPENING NOW.
IT'S BECAUSE I HAVE
A DAUGHTER, ISN'T IT?
HE ALWAYS SAID
DIDN'T WANT KIDS.
I SHOULD NEVER
HAVE HAD A KID.
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN
TO THEM?
WHAT?
DR. BURKE AND DR. YANG--
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
TOTO THEM,
THEIR PUNISHMENT?
DR. BAILEY--
THERE'S A NEED
FOR JUSTICE HERE.
JUSTICE?
JUSTICE HAS NO DEFINITION
WITHIN THE FOUR WALLS
OF A HOSPITAL, DR. BAILEY.
THIS ISN'T A COURT OF LAW.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW
WHAT'S GONNA BE DONE.
LEGALLY AND TECHNICALLY,
THEY'VE DONE NOTHING WRONG.
NOBODY DIED,
THERE WAS NO MALPRACTICE.
I HAVEN'T MADE A DECISION.
EXCUSE ME. HE--
HE WHAT?
NOTHIN'.
DR. YANG,
YOU'LL GO BACK ON THE FLOOR
WITH DR. BAILEY.
SIR--
DR. BAILEY, AM I NOT
UNDERSTANDING THIS?
DOES THIS SITUATION DIRECTLY
HARM YOU IN SOME WAY?
NO, SIR.
IAM FINE.
THEN GET BACK TO WORK.
BURKE, YOU AND SHEPHERD
NEED TO COME TOGETHER
ON THIS TREMOR
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
HE DOESN'T WANT MY HELP.
DEREK--
I DON'T WANT HIS HELP.
THAT HAND
IS WORTH $2 MILLION.
I WANT IT FIXED,
AND I WANT IT FIXED YESTERDAY.
FIGURE IT OUT.
LISTEN, YOUR BROTHERS
ARE GOOD BOYS,
BUT THEY'RE NOT
THAT RESPONSIBLE.
IT'S A STANDARD PROCEDURE.
IT'S JUST THAT,
IF THINGS GO WRONG--
DAD--
IF THINGS GO WRONG,
THE LIFE INSURANCE PAPERS
ARE IN THE SECOND DRAWER
IN MY NIGHTSTAND...
AND MY... MAGAZINES
ARE IN THE GARAGE
WITH THE TRUCK MANUALS.
YOUR MAGAZINES?
GET 'EM OUTTA THERE
SO YOUR MA DOESN'T SEE THEM.
YOUR MAGAZINES?
(clears throat)
GOOD MORNING, MR. O'MALLEY.
JUST WANTED TO STOP BY
BEFORE THE SURGERY
AND SEE HOW THAT COLLARBONE
WAS HEALING.
GEORGE... YOU'RE NOT GONNA SAY
HELLO TO DR. TORRES?
I'M GONNA SEE YOU
FOR ROUNDS, DAD.
HAD YOU TOLD ME THAT YOU WERE
DEVELOPING A TREMOR,
I COULD'VE RUN SOME TESTS.
THE LIKELIHOOD IS THAT
THERE'S JUST SOME COMPRESSION
OF THE STRUCTURES
AROUND THE INJURY.
I CAN GO IN THERE--
I DON'T WANT ANOTHER SURGERY.
IT COULD BE A SMALL CLOT.
I JUST GO IN--
SHEPHERD, I DON'T WANT
ANOTHER SURGERY.
THE FIRST ONE
CAUSED ENOUGH DAMAGE.
I CAN DO THIS.
THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID
THE LAST TIME.
NOW I HAVE A TREMOR.
MAYBE SHE'LL BE ON "LOOK
BUT DON'T TOUCH" PATROL, TOO.
AT LEAST I'D HAVE
SOME COMPANY.
WHATEVER SHE GETS,
I HOPE IT'S BAD,
REALLY BAD.
SHE MADE A MISTAKE.
A MISTAKE?
WE ALL--
SHE WAS GONNA LET BURKE--
BURKE WITH THE SHAKY HAND--
OPERATE ON MY FATHER.
COULD YOU STOP LKING
AT ME LIKE THAT?
IT'S CREEPY, AND IT MAKES ME
FEEL LIKE YOU HAVEN'T BEEN FED.
HOW'S IT GOING?
HOW'S WHAT GOING?
YOU AND BURKE,
ARE YOU OKAY?
(exhales) WE'RE EXISTING
IN TOTAL SILENCE.
HE'S NOT TALKING TO YOU?
I'M NOT TALKING
TO HIM EITHER.
I'M SORRY.
ARE YOU OKAY?
STOP ASKING ME THAT.
I'M MAKING AN EFFORT HERE.
PLEASE DON'T.
ROUNDS STARTED 30 SECONDS AGO.
THE CHIEF MAY BE CONFUSED
ABOUT PUNISHMENT FOR YOU,
YOU'RE LATE AGAIN,
YOU WILL FIND
ANOTHER RESIDENT.
DR. BAILEY,
CAN I HAVE GREY?
YOU CAN HAVE 'EM ALL.
SOMETHING YOU NEEDED,
DR. MONTGOMERY?
THIS IS NONE OF MY BUSINESS,
BUT I JUST THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
WANT TO BE WARNED.
I'M SORRY. I DON'T KNOW--
YOUR SISTER MOLLY'S
JUST BEEN ADMITTED
FOR AN EMERGENCY C-SECTION.
MOLLY'S NOT MY SISTER.
OKAY, BUT TECHNICALLY,
SHE IS,
YOU HAVE THE SAME FATHER.
AND, UH, SUSAN--
SUSAN GREY
IS DEFINITELY NOT MY MOTHER.
I APPRECIATE YOUE TRYING
TO BE NICE AND EVERYTHING,
BUT I REALLY DON'T EVEN
NEED TO KNOW THIS, SO--
ACTUALLY YOU DO.
(clears throat)
HELLO, MEREDITH.
HI, MOM.
HONEY. OH.
I PUT OUT SOME BREAKFAST
IN CASE YOU KIDS
HAVEN'T EATEN YET.
SCORE.
KAREV.
HEY, READY FOR
THE BIG DAY, POPS?
MM, FOOD.
OH.
L RIGHT,
LET'S MAKE THIS FAST, PEOPLE.
I HAVE A DAY. WHICH ONE
OF THE INTERNS IS MINE?
IT'S MINE.
HE'S FAMILY,
AND SHE'S A CANDY STRIPER.
I'M READY.
WHAT IF YOU DID PICK ME?
WHAT IF YOU PICKED ME?
(Ronny and Jerry) PICK ME!
GUYS, THIS IS SERIOUS.
YANG.
WHAT?
(Alex, Izzie and Cristina)
DR. HAHN, CRISTINA IS
VERY GOOD WITH CARDIO.
I'M SURE YOU CAN USE HER
FOR THE DAY.
UH...
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR,
YANG? PRESENT THE CASE.
HAROLD O'MALLEY, 63, DIAGNOSED
WITH ESOPHAGEAL CANCER
AND SEVERE AORTIC REGURGE,
IS SCHEDULED FOR AORTIC VALVE
REPLACEMENT THIS AFTERNOON.
DUDE, I WANTED THAT SURGERY,
AND SHE HANDS IT TO YANG.
I HAVEN'T HAD
A CARDIAC CASE IN AGES.
IT'S MY FATHER.
IT'S NOT A CASE.
I GUESS THERE'S
A DOUBLE STANDARD NOW.
(Izzie)
YANG DOES SOMETHING WRONG,
AND SHE GETS REWARDED.
THAT'S FAIR.
YEAH.
IF YOU THUMB SUCKERS
DON'T STOP WHINING,
I SWEAR I WON'T SHOW YOU
WHAT'S BEHIND THIS DOOR,
AND TRUST ME, YOU WANT TO SEE
WHAT'S BEHIND THIS DOOR.
EXCUSE ME, DOCTORS, YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO WAIT A FEW MINUTES.
HE'S GOTTA PEE. EVERY FIVE
MINUTES, HE'S GOTTA PEE.
A SMALL BLADDER.
I'VE ALWAYS HAD
I CAN'T LIVE LIKE THIS
ANY LONGER.
YOU? I'M THE ONE WHO HAS TO
PUT UP WITH YOUR WHINING.
LIKE THE WHINING
YOU'RE DOING RIGHT NOW?
NOW WHICH ONE OF YOU THINKS
THAT YANG GOT THE BETTER CASE?
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
JAKE AND PETER WEITZMAN,
35-YEAR-OLD PYGOPAGUS
CONJOINED TWINS
ATTACHED AT
THE LUMBOSACRAL JUNCTION.
BUT NOT FOR LONG,
RIGHT, DR. WEBBER?
THE WEITZMANS CAME
ABOUT SIX MONTHS AGO
FOR A SEPARATION PROCEDURE.
THEY OPTED OUT
BECAUSE OF THE RISK.
PETE CHICKENED OUT.
WELL, FORGIVE ME FOR WANTING
TO LIVE LONGER,
EVEN IF IT MEANT
LIVING WITH YOU.
YEAH? WELL, YOU WASTED
SIX MONTHS OF OUR LIVES...
OH, COME ON.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
STOP IT.
YOU GUYS CAME BACK
AT THE RIGHT TIME.
WE JUST SCORED NEW YORK'S
TOP PLASTIC SURGEON.
(Richard) MARK SLOAN, PLASTICS,
AND YOU REMEMBER DR. SHEPHERD,
YOUR NEUROSURGEON.
(Derek) JAKE.
WE, UH, WE USED TO WORK
AS A TEAM, ACTUALLY.
PETE, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
WE WORKED TOGETHER. WE WERE
NEVER ACTUALLY A TEAM.
(Jake) I HEAR YA.
MR. WEITZMAN?
CALL ME JAKE.
CALL ME PETE.
JAKE, PETE, UM, WHY--
DO YOU MIND ME ASKING WHY NOW
WHEN YOU THOUGHT THE PROCEDURE
WAS TOO RISKY SIX MONTHS AGO?
WELL--
GUYS.
WHOA.
THAT'S A LOT OF DOCTORS.
I'M--I'M JUST GONNA
COME BACK LATER.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
ELENA, COME IN, COME IN.
YOU WANTED TO KNOW WHY NOW.
THIS IS WHY--
THE LOVE OF MY LIFE--
ELENA.
JAKE, DON'T--I-I TOLD HIM
NOT TO DO THIS,
NOT FOR ME ANYWAY,
'CAUSE THAT'S JUST CRAZY.
'CAUSE PETE SAID THAT
THEY COULD END UP PARALYZED.
THEY COULD END UP DEAD.
WHAT DO YOU TELL HER
THINGS LIKE THAT FOR?
I WASN'T TELLING HER.
I WAS TELLING YOU.
SHE JUST HAPPENS TO BE
THE ONLY ONE WHO LISTENS TO ME.
SHE HAPPENS TO BE RIGHT.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO HAVE TO BE STUCK
TO THE SAME PERSON--
HERE WE GO.
EVERY--THAT'S RIGHT.
HERE WE--
DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE TO
HAVE TO BE WITH THE SAME PERSON
EVERY MINUTE OF EVERY DAY,
TO NOT HAVE ANYTHING
THAT'S JUST YOURS,
NOT BE ABLE TO DO ANYTHING
ON YOUR OWN?
WELL, NOBODY SHOULD HAVE TO
LIVE LIKE THAT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, PETE?
I THINK, WHY WOULD I WANT TO BE
ATTACHED TO SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T WANT TO BE
ATTACHED TO ME?
(Alex) I'M CALLING IT.
IT'S MINE.
I HAVE TWO BROTHERS.
I FEEL THEIR PAIN.
I WOULD BE GREAT
AT WATCHING THIS.
ZIP IT, ALL OF YOU.
WE'RE ON THE CASE, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
YES!
AWESOME.
STEVENS, YOU ARE TO--
LOOK AND NOT TOUCH OR SPEAK
OR BREATHE. I GOT IT.
SO THIS IS
THE CRACK TEAM, HUH?
FEEL FREE TO TAKE ONE.
HOW ABOUT I TAKE THE ONE
THAT DOESN'T TOUCH
OR SPEAK OR BREATHE?
(whispers) RIGHT.
DAMN IT.
THANK YOU...
FOR PICKING ME.
EVEN JUST OBSERVING
WOULD BE--
THOUGHT YOU MIGHT BE FUN
TO LOOK AT WHILE I WORK.
WILL YOU BE WORKING ON
BOTH THE NERVE GRAFT
AND THE SKIN RECONSTRUCTION?
YES, AND I THINK I'LL
HANDLE THEM A WHOLE LOT BETTER
WITH A LITTLE CAFFEINE
IN MY SYSTEM.
GET ME A BLUEBERRY SCONE,
A BONE DRY CAPPUCCINO
AND A LITTLE SOMETHING
FOR YOURSELF.
THERE'S A CAFETERIA
ON THE SECOND FLOOR
AND A COFFEE CART
IN THE LOBBY.
FEISTY.
CAPPUCCINO.
YOU CAN KICK ME BACK TO BAILEY
IF YOU WANT. I DON'T DO COFFEE.
SO HOW WILL YOU BE HANDLING
THE NERVE GRAFT
AND THE SKIN RECONSTRUCTION?
CONJOINED TWINS, DEREK.
(Derek) I KNOW, CHIEF.
CONJOINED ADULT TWINS.
MM-HMM.
I MEAN, IT'S RARE ENOUGH
TO SEPARATE CONJOINED INFANTS.
BUT CONJOINED ADULTS?
MM-HMM.
CAN YOU IMAGINE THE PRESS,
WHAT A SURGERY LIKE THIS
COULD DO FOR THIS HOSPITAL?
I KNOW, WHICH IS WHY
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD DO IT.
THEIR SPINES ARE FUSED TOGETHER
FROM THE L4 DOWN.
THEIR BLOOD FLOW
IS INTRICATELY CONNECTED.
THEY COULD END UP PARALYZED,
OR EVEN DEAD.
YOUR PATIENTS WANT
THIS OPERATION, DEREK.
WHY ARE YOU BACKING OUT?
THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU.
UNLESS THERE'S
INCONTROVERTIBLE EVIDENCE
THAT THIS SURGERY CAN'T BE DONE,
WE'RE MOVING FORWARD.
YOUR FATHER'S NOT HERE.
THATCHER'S AT HARVARD MED
VISITING LEXIE.
WE THOUGHT WE HAD
A LOT OF TIME.
I MEAN, MOLLY'S ONLY
36 WEEKS,
AND DR. MONTGOMERY'S BEEN
TRYING TO STOP THE CONTRACTIONS,
BUT I GUESS THE BABY
IS READY TO COME OUT.
WELL, DO YOU NEED
ANYTHING ELSE OR...
YEAH, ACTUALLY, I COULD USE
AN INTERN FOR THIS.
CAN YOU ASK DR. BAILEY
FOR SOMEONE?
UH... I'LL DO IT.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH, I'M FINE.
OKAY.
IT'LL BE SO NICE TO HAVE
A FAMILIAR FACE
IN THE OPERATING ROOM.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
IT'S MY JOB TO BE HERE, SO...
UH, DOES MOLLY KNOW
WHO I AM?
SHE DOESN'T.
I WANTED TO TELL HER,
BUT YOUR FATHER...
HE JUST--HE--
NO, IT'S--IT'S BETTER.
IT'S BETTER THAT SHE
NOT KNOW. IT'S GOOD.
SO I THINK, UH, MOLLY SHOULD
BE READY IN THE O.R.
SUSAN, YOU'LL NEED SCRUBS
AND A CAP.
I'M ABOUT TO BE
A GRANDMOTHER.
YES, IN ABOUT A HALF AN HOUR,
YOU WILL BE A GRANDMOTHER.
OH, MY. OKAY.
HERE WE GO.
WE'RE GOING TO BE REPLACING
YOUR AORTIC VALVE
WITH A PORCINE VALVE.
WELL, GEORGIE SAYS
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
HE SAYS THEY KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
BESIDES, IF YOU DIE,
I'LL KILL YOU.
WELL, IT'S A GOOD THING
WE'RE DOING THIS TODAY.
WE NOTICED YOU HAD A LOT
OF IRREGULAR HEART RHYTHMS
THIS MORNING.
DID YOU CHECK HIS DIG LEVEL?
EXCUSE ME.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THIS MORNING HIS POTASSIUM
WAS A BORDERLINE LOW.
ALL RIGHT, WE'VE GOT A HANDLE
ON THINGS HERE.
OH, I'M SURE YOU DO.
UH, GEORGE, I THINK MAYBE
YOU SHOULD STEP OUTSIDE.
LIKE THAT.
YOU DON'T TALK TO ME
OH, SHE'S WAKING UP
THE BABY.
RONNY, SHUT UP.
BE CAREFUL, DR. HAHN,
HE MIGHT START CRYING.
I SAID SHUT UP.
ALL RIGHT,
YOU ARE OUT OF HERE.
NO, I'M NOT.
GEORGIE.
NO, UH, SHE CAN'T
KICK ME OUT.
SHE HAS NO RIGHT.
I HIREHEHER.
I'M STAYING.
(Addison)
HOW YOU DOING THERE, MOLLY?
OKAY. I'M JUST EXCITED
TO SEE MY GIRL.
WELL, YOU'RE GONNA GET
TO TAKE A LOOK AT HER
IN JUST A COUPLE OF MINUTES.
A LITTLE MORE TRACTION, PLEASE?
DR. GREY, CAN YOU GIVE ME
(woman) VITALS ARE
HOLDING STEADY.
CAN YOU SEE HER YET?
(chuckles) NO.
I'M NOT GONNA LOOK
UNTIL THE BLOOD'S ALL GONE.
OKAY. YOU WANT TO CUT
THE CORD, DR. GREY?
@@
(woman) THE WARMER IS READY
WHEN YOU NEED IT,
DR. MONTGOMERY.
DR. GREY,
WILL YOU FOLLOW ME?
DR. KNOX, WILL YOU
CLOSE FOR ME, PLEASE?
BAG VALVE MASK.
WE HAVE TO STABILIZE THIS BABY
AND GET IT INTO SURGERY.
(woman) GET HER ON THE MONITOR.
THE PULSE IS WEAK.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HER?
SUSAN, I NEED YOU TO STAND BACK
AND STAY WITH MOLLY, PLEASE.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HER?
(woman) NO RESPONSE TO
STIMULATION. LET'S TRY SUCTION.
(Addison) GREY, YOU WANT TO
TALK HER THROUGH THIS?
GR, I NEED YOUR HELP HERE.
THE BABY IS NOT BREATHING.
(Molly) WHAT?
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
YOU LEFT ME HANGING
IN THERE, GREY.
I'M SORRY. I WAS...
I'M SORRY.
DO YOU NEED ME
TO SCRUB IN ON THE BABY?
NO. I WANT YOU TO KEEP
MOLLY AND HER MOTHER
APPRISED OF THE BABY'S CONDITION
WHILE I OPERATE.
I'M SURE
THEY'D RATHER TALK TO YOU.
THE BABY'S GOT JEJUNAL ATRESIA.
SHE MAY DIE.
I GOT CONSENT, BUT I DON'T
HAVE TIME FOR UPDATES.
I THINK I WOULD
REALLY LEARN A LOT
FROM OBSERVING
THIS PROCEDURE.
NO, IT WAS A MISTAKE
TO LET YOU IN THE O.R. WITH
YOUR FILY IN THE FIRST PLACE.
IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN AGAIN.
CHECK IN WITH ME EVERY HOUR.
HOW MANY VALVE REPLACEMENTS
HAVE YOU PERFORMED
@@
IN YOUR LIFE, DR. O'MALLEY?
NONE.
NONE. AND HOW MANY
VALVE REPLACEMENTS DO YOU THINK
DR. HAHN HAS PERFORMED?
THAT IS MY FATHER!
AND YOU ARE IN THAT ROOM
AS HIS SON.
YOU INTERNS THINK YOU CAN DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO DO.
WELL, NOT ANYMORE,
NOT WITH ME,
WHICH IS WHY YOU
ARE GOING TO STAY AWAY,
50 FEET AWAY
TO BE PRECISE.
YOU ARE GOING TO REMAIN
50 FEET AWAY FROM YOUR FATHER
AT ALL TIMES TODAY,
AND, DR. O'MALLEY,
DO NOT MAKE ME
TELL YOU AGAIN.
EVERYTHING OKAY
WITH THE O'MALLEYS?
THE KID'S A PAIN
IN THE ASS.
BUT DR. YANG HERE
IS PROVING TO BE
AN EXTREMELY CAPABLE ASSET.
I HEAR SHE STUDIED UNDER YOU.
YOU TRAINED HER WELL.
YES.
WELL, SHE'S VERY...
PROFESSIONAL.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT DR. LEVINE?
PRETTY GOOD.
BETTER OR WORSE
THAN DR. KORSIKOV?
ITIT...
WHY ARE YOU
RESEARCHING NEUROSURGEONS
WHEN YOU AND I BOTH KNOW
THAT DEREK'S BETTER
THAN ANYBODY?
I DON'T WANT SHEPHERD.
YOU BLAMING THIS
ON HIM?
YOU KNOW,  UNTIL NOW,
I HAVE NOT YELLED.
I HAVE NOT YELLED
BECAUSE YOU WERE A GUY
IN TROUBLE,
AND I WAS SUPPORTING YOU.
BUT NOW...
I AM YELLING!
CHIEF.
I AM YELLING
VERY LOUDLY!
I WANT TO RETIRE, BURKE!
I WANT MY WIFE BACK!
AND I PASSED
THE TORCH TO YOU!
I PASSED THE TORCH TO YOU,
AND YOU BLEW IT OUT!
LOOK, I KNOW
I LET YOU DOWN.
I'M TIRED.
I'M TIRED OF YOU MEN
ACTING LIKE BOYS.
YOU LET ME DOWN.
AND IF YOU DON'T LET DEREK
FIX THAT HAND,
YOU'RE LETTING YOURSELF DOWN.
22 SURGEONS--
IT TAKES 22 SURGEONS
TO DO THIS.
SO WHERE ARE WE?
I'VE GOTTEN TO
THE CAUDA EQUINA.
I'LL BE WORKING
ON THE MUSCULATURE
OF THE PERINEAL FLOOR.
I'LL BE HARVESTING
THE SURAL NERVE FOR TRANSFER.
NOW ONCE
I RESECT THIS ARTERY,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
LESS THAN TWO MINUTES
BEFORE ALL SENSATION
TO THESE NERVES ARE GONE.
I'I'M PRETTY SURE
WE'LL HAVE ENOUGH NERVE TO
TRANSFER AND COVER THE DEFICITS.
WE CAN DEFINITELY DO THIS.
OH, DAMN IT.
IT'S GONNA BE A LOT MORE
FRAGILE IN THE BODY.
IT'S ONE THING IF THIS IS
A LIFE-OR-DEH SITUATION
AND THIS IS ALL WE CAN DO
TO SAVE THEM.
BUT THESE GUYS ARE FINE.
THIS ISN'T WORTH THE RISK.
HOW IS OUR BABY?
SHE HAS
AN INTESTINAL OBSTRUCTION,
WHICH IS WHY
SHE COULDN'T BREATHE.
DR. MONTGOMERY IS OPERATING
ON HER RIGHT NOW.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
I CAN'T DO IT.
YES, YOU CAN.
I AM RIGHT HERE, BABY,
AND DAD'S ON THE WAY.
I HAVE TO CALL ERIC.
OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO TELL HIM.
THAT'S HER HUSBAND.
HE'S IN IRAQ.
I CAN'T TELL HIM THIS.
HE'S GONNA WANT TO NAME HER,
AND I DON'T WANNA NAME HER
'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG
SHE'S GONNA BE OURS.
OH, NOW--SHH.
WE'LL CALL HIM TOGETHER.
OKAY.
@@
HE'S JUST GONNA BE HAPPY
TO HEAR YOUR VOICE.
THE BABY'S GONNA BE OKAY.
YOU HEAR ME?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
SLOAN'S RIGHT HAND.
YEAH, WELL, SLOAN
CAN KISS MY--
OW
I HAVEN'T EVEN PUT
THE NEEDLE IN YET.
SORRY. I'M JUST NOT
A BIG FAN OF PAIN.
WELL, YOU'RE ABOUT TO HAVE
A FAIRLY EXTENSIVE
AND PAINFUL SURGERY.
YOU THINK THIS IS
AN ELECTIVE PROCEDURE?
(laughs) THAT WE'RE JUST
COMING IN HERE
BECAUSE WE'RE GETTING
ON EACH OTHER'S NERVES?
PLEASE, YOU WANT TO KNOW
THE REAL REASON?
COME ON, JAKE.
SHE DOESN'T WANT--
IT'S BECAUSE--
YOU DON'T WANT TO HEAR--
IT'S BECAUSE WE HAVE RULES.
RULES?
YEAH, LIKE SAY ONE OF US
IS ON A DINNER DATE,
ACCORDING TO THE RULES,
THE OTHER ONE'S
SUPPOSED TO SIT THERE QUIETLY,
EAT HIS FALAFE
AND SHUT THE HELL UP.
I TRY. IT'S JUST THE WAY
YOU TALK TO HER SOMETIMES--
'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
HOW IS IT
NONE OF MY BUSINS?
HE STICKS UP FOR ME, AND I
THINK THAT THAT'S KINDA NICE.
OKAY, YOU DON'T
TALK TO HIM ANYMORE.
WHAT?
OH, WE CAN'T EVEN
BE FRIENDS NOW?
WE HAVE OTHER RULES, TOO.
OH.
LIKE FOR WHEN WE'RE
WITH SOMEONE.
GOT IT. SORT OF.
NO LOOKING, NO TALKING,
NO TOUCHING.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
BADLY.
OH, THIS IS GONNA END
(Jake and Pete
arguing indistinctly)
I TOLD YOU,
I'M COMPLETELY FINE WITH IT.
HOW ARE YOU OKAY WITH THE FACT
THAT HE'S TOUCHING YOU
WHILE YOU'RE NAKED?
UH...
BE... CAUSE IT WASN'T
A BIG DEAL.
AND IT WAS KINDA SWEET
AND...
IT JUST--
IT WASN'T A BIG DEAL.
WAIT, YOU...
YOU LIKED IT.
YOU ENJOYED IT.
I'M... COMPLETELY
IN LOVE WITH YOU.
THAT'SOT EVEN--THAT--
YOU'RE--YOU'RE A GREAT GUY.
AND, YOU KNOW,
WHEN WE MAKE LOVE,
THE--IT'S--IT'S GREAT.
IT'S--IT'S REALLY GREAT.
AND I'VE NEVER
HAD THAT BEFORE AND--
IT'S JUST THAT
WHEN YOU FALL ASLEEP,
THAT, UH, PETE AND I JUST--
WE TALK.
AND, UM...
I REALLY LOVE THAT, TOO.
ELENA.
NO, NO.
NO, YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE.
WHAT?
HIM OR ME?
WE'RE GONNA HAVE THIS SURGERY,
AND YOU CAN'T HAVE US BOTH.
SO CHOOSE--HIM OR ME?
SEE, THIS IS THE PART
WHERE YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO SAY,
"YOU, JAKE. I CHOOSE YOU."
I'M SO SORRY, JAKE.
I'M SO SORRY.
ELENA--
OH, GOD!
(Alex) NO, NO, NO!
I SWEAR TO GOD...
JAKE, IT'S--
I AM GONNA KILL YOU!
OW! GET HIM OFF!
I THINK IT'S ROMANTIC--
TWO BROTHERS FIGHTING...
OVER THE SAME WOMAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S FREAKY?
THE WHOLE CONJOINED TWIN
HAVING SEX IN FRONT OF
THE OTHER ONE THING.
HOW DO YOU DO THAT?
FAMILY IS COMPLICATED.
YOU'RE HERE. YOU HAVEN'T BEEN
KICKED OUT OF THE PROGRAM YET.
(Meredh)h) ALEX.
NO, NOT YET.
I'M STILL HERE.
HOW'D YOU DO IT?
I MEAN, DID YOU HAVE SOME KIND
OF SIGNAL IN SURGERY
SO THAT THE NURSES
WOULDN'T KNOW, OR DID YOU--
ALEX--
WHAT? I MEAN, I'M JUST WONDERING
HOW TO GET AHEAD AROUND HERE.
ME? I GET COFFEE FOR SLOAN.
YANG--SHE GETS SURGERIES
NONE OF US WOULD GET.
GOT A HEAD COUNT
ON HOW MANY PATIENTS YOU TWO
LIED TO THE PAST MONTH?
(Meredith) GEORGE.
LEAVE HER ALONE.
HER PATIENTS LIVED
SO SHE GETS TO SCRUB IN.
IZZIE.
MEREDITH, PLEASE, CAN YOU
JUST STOP DEFENDING ME?
AH.
AH. NO, NO, NO, NO.
I'LL, UH, I'LL GO.
NO, WAIT, WAIT.
GEORGIE, YOU SHOULD
MAKE NICE WITH HER.
LOOK, DAD...
NO, REALLY, MR. O'MALLEY,
IT'S FINE.
IT'S NOT FINE.
GEORGE, YOU'RE SO ANGRY.
NO, I'M NOT.
YOU'VE BEEN PICKING FIGHTS
EVERY CHANCE YOU GET,
AND THAT'S NOT LIKE YOU.
DAD... YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON.
OKAY, THEN TELL ME.
WHY ARE YOU SO MAD
AT DR. TORRES?
I SHOULD GO.
I HAVE PATIENTS TO SEE.
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GONNA GO.
NO! EVERYBODY STAYS.
YOU'RE ANGRY, GEORGIE...
AT CALLIE, AT YOUR BROTHERS,
AT DR. HAHN,
AT DR. BAILEY, AT DR. YANG,
AT DR. BURKE.
THAT'S A LONG LIST
OF PEOPLE TO BE ANGRY AT.
ESPECIALLY WHEN THE PERSON
YOU'RE REALLY ANGRY AT...
IS ME.
DAD?
I-I DRINK AND I SMOKE
AND I DON'T EXERCISE
AND I EAT
ALL THE WRONG THINGS,
AND NOW I HAVE CANCER.
AND YOU HAVE TO TAKE CARE
OF EVERYTHING.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE CARE
OF ME.
I DON'T MIND.
YOU DO.
YOU'RE MAD AT ME,
AND THAT'S OKAY
BECAUSE I'M MAD AT ME, TOO.
YOU THINK I WANT TO DIE
AND LEAVE MY BOY IN CHARGE?
YOU ARE NOT GONNA DIE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE
IN HERE, GEORGIE.
YEAH, YOU'RE GONNA GET
IN TROUB, GEORGIE.
GEORGIE DOESN'T WORK HERE!
IN THIS HOSPITAL,
MY NAME IS DR. O'MALLEY!
DR. O'MALLEY...
(struggles for breath)
DAD.
(monitor beeping erratically)
HONEY!
DAD.
I-I CAN'T...
DAD, DAD,
DON'T TRY TO TALK.
(Louise) HE'S HAVING
A HEART ATTACK, GEORGIE!
WHY DON'T YOPUMP HIS CHEST?
THEY ALWAYS USE THE PADDLES!
GET THE PADDLES!
HE'S NOT HAVING
A HEART ATTACK.
DAD. DAD, STOP!
I'M TRYING TO HELP.
YOUR HEART'S GOI TOO FAST.
RECYCLE HIS B.P.
UH, PULL, UH, VERAPAMIL,
5 MILLIGRAMS.
DAD. DAD!
STOP FIGHTING THE MASK.
O'MALLEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU SHOULD'VE PAGED HAHN.
I PAGED ANYONE
FROM CARDIOTHORACICS.
HE'S GOT A-FIB
WITH RAPID VENTRICLE RESPONSE.
I'VE ORDERED VERAPAMIL.
HE'S IN V-TACH.
THE VERAPAMIL IS GONNA CAUSE
MORE PROBLEMS THAN IT SOLVES.
100 LIDOCAINE.
UH, PUT ON HIS 0-2 MASK.
(Erica) ALL RIGHT,
WHAT HAPPENED?
HE WENT INTO V-TACH. O'MALLEY
IS GIVING HIM LIDOCAINE.
IT'S ALREADY PUT HIM
BACK IN, UH, NORMAL SINUS.
ALL RIGHT,
I NEED EVERYONE OUT OF HERE.
I GOT YOUR PAGE.
I NEED ANOTHER CAPPUCCINO.
DID YOU THINK
I WAS KIDDING BEFORE?
I AM YOUR ATTENDING,
AND IF YOU WANT IN
ON MY SURGERIES,
YOU'RE GONNA LEARN
HOW TO FETCH AND STAY
AND HEEL.
FINE.
DON'T FETCH ANGRY.
IF YOU THINK THIS MEANS
I RESPECT YOU,
IF YOU WANT ME
TO RESPECT YOU,
YOU HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
WORTH RESPECTING.
(Derek) ALL OF THESE CABLES
OF NERVES...
AH...
I CAN'T DO THIS SURGERY,
MIRANDA. IT'S--MNH-MNH.
I STARTED TO THINK
I SHOULDN'T BE OPERATING
ALL THE WHISPERS
AND THE TALK...
I LET THAT IN.
MM.
I STARTED
TO QUESTION MYSELF.
I BELIEVED IT
WHEN I WAS TOLD, UH,
I WAS NO LONGER OF USE
IN THE O.R.
OH, SO WHEN YOU SAID
YOU WANTED JUSTICE,
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT--
I'M A SURGEON.
UH-HUH.
THERE ARE LIVES IN MY HANDS.
TO MAKE ME QUESTION THAT...
NO, THAT'S TO PUT
A LIFE AT STAKE
EVERY TIME I HOLD A SCALPEL.
WELL, I TOLD BURKE
I COULD FIX HIS HAND,
AND THEN...
WELL, YOU DID.
YEAH.
HE IS NOT PARALYZED
OR--OR DISABLED
IN ANY WAY.
HE HAS A TREMOR.
AND IF HE HAD BEEN HONEST
ABOUT THAT,
WELL, THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT YOU COULD HAVE DONE
TO PREVENT IT.
MM-HMM.
WE CAN DO THIS.
HOLD ON TO MY WEDDING RING,
HONEY.
HOSPITAL RULES.
GEORGIE, ARE YOU GONNA
BE THERE IN THE OPERATION?
THEY DON'T ALLOW FAMILY IN,
BUT YOU'LL BE FINE.
I'LL BE FINE.
WE'LL TAKE GOOD CARE
OF YOU.
(Louise)
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
(sobs) WHAT AM I GONNA DO
IF HE DIES?
I CHANGED MY  MIND.
OH, NO, YOU DIDN'T.
DR. BAILEY, I'D LIKE TO BE
EXCUSED FROM THE TWINS
IF THAT'S ALL RIGHT
WITH YOU.
I'D LIKE TO BE
WITH MY MOM.
THAT'S THE RIGHT CALL,
O'MALLEY. GO.
PROMISE ME SOMETHING--
WHEN YOU SEPARATE US,
CAN YOU MAKE SURE HIS ASS
IS BIGGER THAN MINE?
I CAN HEAR YOU.
YOU'RE STILL HERE.
I WENT TO N.I.C.U.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE DONE.
I'M HAVING TROUBLE
WITH THIS ANASTOMOSIS,
AND I STILL HAVE TO TAKE
A LOOK AT THE DISTAL BOWEL.
WHAT SHOULD I TELL MOLLY?
I DON'T KNOW.
TELL HER I'M DOING
THE BEST I CAN.
I DON'T KNOW.
(Mark) DR. BAILEY,
I'D LIKE MY INTERN TO OBSERVE
FROM A BETTER VANTAGE POINT.
DR. STEVENS?
YES.
SHE'S MY INTERN TODAY,
AND I'D LIKE HER NEARBY
DURING SURGERY,
NOT UP IN THE GALLERY,
IF THAT'S OKAY WITH YOU.
NO PROBLEM.
DR. BAILEY, STEVENS IS
WITHOUT PRIVILEGES.
OH, 'CAUSE SHE MESSED UP?
DR. YANG MESSED UP, AND SHE'S
OVER IN O.R. TWO RIGHT NOW.
WILL YOU HIT THAT FOR ME?
STEVENS, I TAKE IT
YOU REMEMBER HOW TO SCRUB IN.
COME ON.
(Derek) THIS VESSEL'S
EVEN MORE FRAGILE
THAN IN THE BIOMODEL.
(Richard) HMM.
LET'S DO A MICROVASCULAR
BYPASS GRAFT.
I COULD HARVEST THE SAPHENOUS
VEIN WHILE I'M DOWN HERE.
I DON'T KNOW. I DON'T KNOW
IF THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
GENTLEMEN, WE NEED
TO MAKE A DECISION,
AND WE NEED TO MAKE IT NOW.
DEREK, IT'S YOUR CALL.
DO YOU OR DON'T YOU
WANT TO PROCEED?
ALL RIGHT,
GIVE ME A 10-BLADE.
(Richard) LET'S GET SOME
SUCTION IN HERE, PLEASE.
I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
ME EITHER.
HOW'S IT GOING?
THEY JUST STARTED.
(Erica) THE SKIN INCISION
IS DONE.
LET'S GO.
SHE'S...
THROUGH THE STERNUM.
THERE'S A BIT
OF BLEEDING.
SHE'S STOPPING IT
WITH BONE WAX.
INSERTING THE RETRACTOR...
SHE'S OPENING
THE PERICARDIAL SAC.
TAKING A LOOK
AT THE ECHO,
SHE'S NODDING.
LOOKS GOOD.
THEY'RE LOOKING AT
YOUR DAD'S HEART NOW.
SHE'S PREPARING TO PUT IN
THE STAY SUTURES.
IS THE SAPHENOUS VEIN
GRAFT IN PLACE?
(Mark) YEAH.
YEAH, I'M READY.
DR. BAILEY?
I'M GOOD.
CHIEF?
READY WHEN YOU ARE.
ALL RIGHT,
THE MOMENT OF TRUTH.
REMOVING THE CLAMPS.
CHECK THE NERVE STIMULATOR.
S.S.E.P.ARE FALLING.
ALL RIGHT,
PUMP UP THE BLOOD PRESSURE.
WE NEED AS MUCBLOOD THROUGH
THE AREA AS POSSIBLE.
(Miranda)
I'M GOING UP TO 2 MILLIAMPS.
UP TO 3.
(Richard) WAIT A MINUTE.
UH, I SEE SOMETHING.
A FLICKER ON THE HAMSTRING
OF TWIN "A."
(Mark) ANYTHING ON TWIN "B"?
PUMP IT UP SOME MORE.
OKAY, UP TO 4.
A TWITCH. I GOT A TWITCH
ON TWIN B's GASTROC.
YEAH, IT'S SMALL,
BUT IT'S THERE.
WE HAVE A SIGNAL.
CONGRATULATIONS,
LADIES AND GENTLEM.
WE HAVE FOUR FUNCTIONING LEGS.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
ON THREE.
ONE...
TWO...
THREE.
IT'D BE NICE
IF EVERY LOVE TRIANGLE
COULD BE FIXED WITH A SCALPEL.
IF THEY COULD, YOU'D HAVE
STABBED ME WITH A 10-BLADE
A LONG TIME AGO. (ughs)
(laughs)
BYE. HOW IS SHE?
PLEASE TELL ME GOOD NEWS
BECAUSE I HAVE TO GO IN
AND TELL MOLLY,
AND I DON'T WANT TO TELL HER
ANYTHING BAD.
DR. MONTMERY IS ON HER WAY,
AND SHE WILL EXPLAIN EVERYTHING.
BUT THE BABY--
LAURA.
MOLLY NAMED HER LAURA.
OH, LAURA--WILL NEED
SOME RECOVERY TIME,
BUT SHE SHOULD BE
JUST FINE.
OH, THANK YOU.
OH, I WAS SO SCARED.
(laughs)
OH, THANK YOU. OH, GOD.
SHE'S GONNA BE SO HAPPY
TO HEAR THIS.
HEY, THIS IS YOUR NIEC
YOU KNOW?
I'M SORRY.
YOU'RE VERY NICE.
YOU BOTH SEEM...
SO NICE.
BUT I DON'T KNOW YOU.
AND YOU ARE NOT MY FAMILY.
I'M CLOSING THE AORTOTOMY.
WHAT'S NEXT?
PLACE THE NEEDLE
IN THE ASCENDING AORTA
TO REMOVE AIR AND THEN RELEASE
THE AORTIC VALVE CLAMP.
YOU REMIND ME OF MYSELF
WHEN I WAS AN INTERN.
I DO?
FOCUSED, INTENSE...
COLD--AND I DON'T MEAN THAT
AS A BAD THING.
COLD IS GOOD.
THE DATING, THE FRIENDS,
THE FAMILY--
IF YOU ASK ME,
IT'S ALL OVERRATED.
(Erica)
ALL RIGHT, TUBES ARE OUT.
OH, THE ASCENDING AORTA
IS LOOKING DILATED.
(Erica)
THERE'S TOO MUCH BLEEDING
AROUND THE AORTIC SUTURE LINE.
B.P. IS 68 OVER 42.
GOD...
(woman) HE'S BRADYING DOWN.
GET ME ANOTHER T.E.E.
AND AN ECHOCARDIOGRAM, STAT.
LET'S MOVE IT, PEOPLE.
THIS DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
WE GOTTA GET CONTROL
OF THIS BLEEDING.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET HIM
BACK ON BYPASS.
I COULD PUT THE AORTIC CANNULA
INTO HIS RIGHT ATRIUM.
BY YOURSELF?
YES.
ALL RIGHT, DO IT.
REPLACE IT WITH A 2-STAGE
VENOUS CANNULA.
WHY IS SHE DOING THAT?
WH-WHY IS HAHN
LETTING HER DO THAT?
NO, IT'S OKAY. SHE'S DOING
A RUNNING WHIP STITCH.
SHE'S DONE IT BEFORE.
THAT'S BEAUTIFUL WORK,
DR. YANG.
DR. HAHN'S WORK
WAS IMPECCABLE, O'MALLEY.
I WOULDN'T HAVE DONE
ANYTHING DIFFERENT MYSELF.
IT'S JUST, UH...
YOU CAN NEVER TELL
HOW THE BODY
IS GOING TO RESPOND.
EVERY SURGERY...
EVERY BODY IS DIFFERENT.
YOU JUST...
NEVER KNOW.
BUT IT'S OKAY NOW.
THEY'RE IN THE HOME STRETCH.
THANK YOU, DR. BURKE.
(Miranda)
IT UNDERMINES EVERYTHING
FOR MY INTERNS TO SEE YANG
GO WITHOUT PUNISHMENT,
FOR ME TO SEE BURKE
GO WITHOUT PUNISHMENT.
TAKE A STEP BACK.
TRY AND GET
SOME PERSPECTIVE.
SO THERE WILL BE
NO CONSEQUENCES,
FOR EITHER OF THEM.
WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE ME DO,
FIRE THE BOTH OF THEM,
END THEIR CAREERS?
THEY MADE
A TERRIBLE JUDGMENT CALL.
WHICH IS WHAT HAPPENED
WITH DENNY DUQUETTE.
AND THEY DIDN'T KILL
ANYBODY.
AND I DID.
YOU DIDN'T KILL DUQUETTE,
AND I WON'T HAVE YOU
SAYING YOU DID.
I WAS RESPONSIBLEFOR IZZIE STEVENS.
I WAS RESPONSIBLE.
AND I'M RESPONSIBLE
FOR CRISTINA YANG.
I...
AM THE COMMON THREAD HERE.
I... LOST THEM.
CRISTINA, IZZIE--
ARE NOT THE SAME.
MIRANDA...
YOU RAISE THEM...
YOU RAISE THEM LIKE...
LIKE CHILDREN...
AND SOME OF THEM
MAKE MISTAKES
DISAPPOINT YOU.
SOME OF THEM...
DO YOU KNOW WHAT KIND
OF STRENGTH
IT MUST HAVE TAKEN YANG
TO COME TO ME,
TO REPORT ON AN ATTENDING,
ON HER BOYFRIEND?
DO YOU SEE
HOW MUCH SHE'S GROWN?
YOU RAISE THEM...
LIKE CHILDREN...
AND SOME OF THEM TURN OUT
EXACTLY LIKE YOU, DR. BAILEY.
WE'RE FINALLY ALONE.
(chuckles) YEAH.
PETE?
IT'S BEEN A LONG DAY.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, YOU GET
A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP,
AND, UH, I'LL, UM,
COME BACK IN THE MORNING.
(Meredith) AT THE END
OF THE DAY,
WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT,
ALL WE REALLY WANT
IS TO BE CLOSE TO SOMEBODY...
COULDN'T STAY AWAY?
SO THIS THING WHERE WE ALL
KEEP OUR DISTANCE
AND PRETEND NOT TO CARE
ABOUT EACH OTHER--
IT'S USUALLY A LOT OF BULL.
DID YOU WANT TO COME IN?
NO. UH, I JUST, UH...
SHE'S AY?
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
GOOD.
WE COULD BE YOUR FAMILY
IF YOU WANT US.
YOU HAVE A MOTHER, I KNOW.
I'M NOT SAYING...
I'M JUST SAYING THAT
WE COULD BE YOUR FAMILY, TOO.
SO WE PICK AND CHOOSE
WHO WE WANT TO REMAIN CLOSE TO.
I CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE.
(Izzie) WHAT?
LET HER OFF THE HOOK.
LET CRISTINA OFF
THE FREAKIN' HOOK.
MEREDITH...
IZZIE,
YOU CUT THE LVAD WIRE.
SHE STUCK BY YOU
AND DID DENNY'S ECHO.
YOU CHEATED ON IZZIE
WITH SYPH NURSE,
AND SHE HELPED YOU STUDY
FOR YOUR BOARDS.
AND, GEORGE, WHEN EVERYBODY
WAS CALLING YOU 007--
SHE WAS CALLING ME 007.
JUST LET HER OFF THE HOOK.
IT'S OKAY.
SORRY.
WHY CAN'T YOU MIND
YOUR OWN BUSINESS?
YOU KNOW,
WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU'RE MY SISTER.
YOU'RE MY FAMILY.
YOU'RE ALL I'VE GOT.
AND ONCE WE'VE CHOSEN
THOSE PEOPLE...
I'M SO TIRED.
I KNOW. ME, TOO.
WE TEND TO STICK CLOSE BY...
UH, I WAS--I JUST--
I WANTED TO CHECK ON YOUR DAD
AND SEE HOW HE WAS DOING.
GOOD. HE'S RESTING,
BUT HE'S GOOD.
OKAY.
NO MATTER HOW MUCH
WE HURT THEM.
HEY.
(Derek) HI THERE.
I'M GONNA GO BACK UPSTAIRS
WITH DR. BURKE.
HE WANTS ME TO TAKE
A LOOK AT HIS SHOULDER.
I'M GONNA BE A WHILE.
DON'T WAIT UP, OKAY?
OKAY.
THE PEOPLE THAT ARE
STILL WITH YOU
AT THE END OF THE DAY...
THOSE ARE THE ONES
WORTH KEEPING.
AND SURE, SOMETIMES CLOSE
CAN BE TOO CLOSE...
I COULDN'T STAY
WITH THAT MAN.
I DON'T CARE THAT HE--
THAT HE'S MEREDITH'S FATHER,
I-I JUST COULDN'T TAKE IT,
AND THEN RICHARD--AND HE--
AND HE... (sobbing)
NO... (gasps)
???
mami
but sometimes...???
???????
Welcome to www.1000fr.com