Previously on Grey's Anatomy...
You and the red make
a pretty good team.
- Don't tell Sloan...
- Oh...
She and Sloan aren't happening.
- I'm not what you're looking for.
- What are you talking about?
Once a man-whore,
always a man-whore, right?
I keep telling her there's more
to life than surgery and career.
- Mother.
- It has to be small.
Make an appointment at city hall,
and that'll be that.
I don't know if I wanna keep
trying to breathe for you.
- I'll go.
- He said he spent the day in the clinic
when he spent it doing
god knows what with Izzie Stevens.
You're gonna transfer to Mercy West?
I mean, no offense.
Today was awesome.
It's just you're not my girlfriend.
Okay?
The dream is this:
that we'll finally be happy
when we reach our goals.
Find the guy,
finish our internship...
That's the dream.
Then we get there.
And if we're human,
we immediately start dreaming
of something else.
It's 3:00 in the morning.
What are you doing up?
I can't sleep.
What are we watching?
- Why can't you sleep?
- No reason.
Because if this is the dream...
then we'd like to wake up...
Now, please.
Cristina, stop lurking.
Come and say good morning
to your guests.
Good morning, mother.
Uh, good morning, Missus...
Mama.
What...
What's every... everyone...
doing here so early?
Early? Darling,
by the look of the calendar,
we should've been here
6 months ago.
She doesn't understand
what goes into planning a wedding.
Breathe.
Sip... and breathe.
The police haven't found
anything on our Jane Doe.
Well, I believe
she calls herself Ava now.
Yes, well, she doesn't seem
to be getting her memory back.
Now that the rest
of her medical problems
are taken care of,
I'll see what I can do.
- That'd be great. Thanks.
- Has anybody seen Addison?
- Oh, she's gone.
- Gone?
- She took a leave of absence.
- Why?
- I mean, did she tell you why?
- What'd you do to her, Mark?
She didn't give a reason.
Did she tell you
where she was going?
All she said was
she need some time,
"To be happy and free",
if I recall correctly.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's just...
Where I come from...
elevators tend to be this
kind of aphrodisiac.
You know? People get on 'em,
and they just get all horny.
No, no. Not that I'm, uh,
not that I'm talking about
you and I. No.
I'm... I'm just saying,
it... it's a relief.
You know, to be
on a not horny elevator.
You know? Just get on...
And ride... without the sex.
Right?
Oh, my god. I'm becoming
a crazy freak...
A crazy, inappropriately chatting freak.
Becoming?
Seems like you're already there.
Hello.
Someone have bones
that need resetting or...
- Bridesmaid.
- Excuse me?
Bridesmaid.
My mother and...
Burke's mother
have been talking on the phone,
and now they are here...
with me.
To plan the wedding.
Cristina led us to believe
that you were friends.
Okay. I guess.
Good. It's settled.
Wait. Um... what are you...
are you... are you...
You actually asking me to be--
To be one of my bridesmaids? Yeah.
Did you get any sleep?
I did, actually,
after I evicted a raccoon
who chewed his way
into the luggage compartment.
Mm. The trailer.
Yes.
So while you were sleeping...
When I drowned,
it was different for you
than it was for me.
Something happened to me.
And I really don't know
how to explain it
without sounding like...
I just... I feel different.
I wanna be better at everything,
and I wanna let you in.
I swear.
Did you practice that?
With hand gestures,
but I dropped those.
Just, now is not the time
to give up on me, okay?
That's what I'm saying.
Oceanside Wellness Group.
Uh, yes. You're confirmed
for tuesday at 4:00.
Oh, no. No, Ma'am.
No, I'm not a doctor.
I don't know
what you should do
about the itchiness "Down there."
Okay. Okay, bye.
Hi. I, uh, I think
I'm in the right place.
I'm looking for, uh...
Maya, is that you?
- Addison!
- Oh, my god. You got so big.
What are you, like, 45 now?
Maya, you're gonna be late for school--
Addison.
Naomi.
Surprise!
Oh, I got lost like eight times,
I smell like someone who's been
driving in car a for two days,
and I think I just had
some kind of psychotic break
in your elevator, but, um...
Surprise!
Maya, go get your backpack.
So...
What do you want, Addison?
- I miss you.
- Really?
'Cause I haven't heard from you
in over a year.
Unless you count the christmas card,
which was nice.
I know. I'm sorry about... I'm--
I left you messages on your pager.
I e-mailed you.
I had some really
special conversations
- with your voice mail.
- Can we let this go?
I've been having
some rough times lately, okay?
- I got divorced.
- So did I.
Oh, my god.
You and Sam?
- Bye, daddy.
- Bye, baby.
Sam, I'd say good to see you, but...
- Yeah.
- Your face is everywhere.
"Body language"?
Uh, yeah, I just...
I had a few thoughts,
so I wrote 'em down,
and that's...
And now you're
the common man's medical guru.
Hey, Dell, can you push
my appointments back an hour?
I have to rescue Cooper.
This is Addison.
Addison, this is our shrink.
Violet. Hi. Bye.
- What did Cooper do this time?
- What is Cooper always do?
- A woman.
- Can't believe this.
I'm his colleague,
not his chauffeur.
So this is, uh...
co-op medicine, huh?
Yeah, doctors working together.
It's me, Naomi,
we have a pediatrician, a shrink,
an alternative medicine practioner...
- Could you excuse us for just a minute?
- Sure, I can.
- Good morning, Naomi.
- Oh, shut up.
So you two still work together?
Hey, Pete.
Who is that redhead
with your ex-wife?
She's hot.
Possibly insane, but hot.
Don't even think about it.
You work with your ex-husband
in a shrine
for your ex-husband.
It's actually a good book.
And we're friends.
We stayed friends
even after we got divorced.
It's very healthy.
We're healthy.
What happened between you and Sam?
Addison, you and I were close
in med school.
- It was a long time ago.
- Oh, Naomi.
Come on. You can't stay
mad at me forever.
I know you.
- You got fat.
- I did not.
Your hair looks hideous.
- It does not.
- And you're getting really really ugly.
I've missed you, too.
So... why are you really here?
You're a fertility specialist,
one of the best.
You want to have a baby?
I want to have a baby.
Susan Grey.
You sure you're in the right place?
I have reflux...
acid reflux.
And the, uh, hiccups come and go...
when it gets really bad.
They've stopped a few times,
but lately it's been getting...
worse.
Have you had chlorpromazine?
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Isn't that the crazy person's drug?
It's used as an anti-psychotic,
but it's also,
helpful with hiccups.
And if we don't stop these soon,
you will be a crazy person.
Hey, how is Meredith doing?
I know they have
that big intern exam coming up,
and she's been really busy.
I tried to call, but...
Hey, no hiccups.
Chlorpromazine.
I'm not getting any younger, you know?
And I always planned
to have one, it's just...
Well, now clearly,
a man is not in the cards for me.
I mean, this is Addison
post Mcdreamy, post Mcsteamy.
You know, I just have to...
- Mcwhat?
- Forget it.
You know what?
Let's never "Mc" anything.
A baby, that is...
my answer.
Find a sperm donor,
have a baby.
My new dream... a baby.
A baby's not really an answer.
It's more of a crying,
puking, non-answer.
- But you did it.
- With a husband.
Yeah, but you did it.
You got married,
you had a baby.
You're my example.
Okay, we should check your F.S.H.
And your estradiol levels,
and we should probably do
and antral follicle count.
Holy crap.
I'm gonna have a baby.
The treadmill, huh?
Okay, what's going on?
I tried to take it up to ten
and do the hilly terrain mode,
which you can do,
but only if you're an olympian,
so I paused and I went flying off.
No. I mean, what's going on with
you pushing yourself this hard?
This is your fourth
sports injury in three months.
I am a sexual person.
I'm a normal sexual person.
I like sex.
I need sex.
And he won't do it.
He won't have sex with me.
He just... won't.
I'm hoping you're talking
about your husband.
I'm not hoping
because of the no-sex part...
It's been 18 months.
18 months! Do you have
any idea what that is like?
My husband won't do it.
- So you know what Ido?
- Uh, you run.
I run. I run
so I won't sleep with someone else.
I run so I have someplace
to channel my energies.
I run so I won't pick up
a tire iron
and beat my husband to death.
I need sex!
You'd do it with me, right?
I think you need to spend
me time with our therapist.
Thanks for the ride.
- Have you been crying?
- Where's your car?
- Were you crying?
- You wanna walk?
I met a girl at a bar...
on the Internet...
And she borrowed my car.
- Did you file a police report?
- She might bring the car back.
- She was gorgeous and hot and s...
- Okay Cooper, Cooper.
All right, so you meet a strange
woman on the Internet again.
You bring her back
to your apartment
to have sex with you again,
and she steals from you again.
What does that suggest
to you about you?
That I'm an optimist.
That I believe in magic.
That there is a soul mate
out there waiting for me.
Oh, Violet...
Allan's not wort it.
You deserve better.
I know that. I do.
I'm not...
I'm not crying about him.
I'm not.
Don't look at me.
Look over there.
I switched my hours at the clinic
so I can go to the bridal shop. Yay!
Did she cheer?
She just cheered.
Someone's not being very bride-y.
I am not a bride.
I am a surgeon.
Don't tease the caged animal.
You're not excited?
I'm excited. I love weddings.
Weddings are
all about hope and the future.
Okay. I rescheduled an A.C.L. repair,
but I wanna be clear.
I will not be wearing pink
or baby blue.
I do not do flowers in my hair.
And I will never be seen
with a bow on my ass, okay?
See? She's got the right attitude.
Thank you very much.
Hi. I... I'm here with Susan.
She's down in the clinic.
The clinic?
Is everything okay?
Callie's a bridesmaid?
Yeah, Ca... Yes, of course.
Callie's a bridesmaid.
- Fun.
- Yeah.
You gotta do it.
That kid of yours
is gonna need you on your feet.
She's cute, huh?
She's a cute shriveled kid.
She's cute. Come on.
Let's keep walking.
So... where is she?
Red... I thought that was on.
- Walk.
- Gossip.
You called it.
She was too serious
about the whole thing.
And Alex is a rolling stone.
I was being thoughtful.
Yeah, right. And dumping red
after one night is sensitive?
Come on.
You need to buff up.
So did she just take off?
What'd you say to her?
Did she cry?
Idiot. You divorced Naomi?
Look, just mind your own business.
Moron.
She is my best... friend.
Stop hitting me
on top of my head.
Did you cheat?
Two things I learned
way back in kindergarten...
One, keep your hands to yourself,
two, he who smelt it dealt it.
- That makes no sense.
- Yeah. Well...
You cheated.
You cheated on your husband
with his best friend.
There. Smelt it, dealt it...
It works.
You're using fart logic.
Hey, if you want details,
go see Naomi.
- She won't talk about it.
- Then you get no details.
- I'm on her side. You know that.
- That's why you get no details.
- Oh, details!
- Woman, be quiet.
I've missed you.
Well, you know,
Naomi's known you longer,
so she gets custody of you
in the divorce.
So, uh, other than project baby,
this is strictly a vacation.
I am here to read trashy novels
and go to the beach.
Okay, nobody over 30
goes to the beach.
You should stay here
at the practice, hang out,
see how we work.
It's more fun
than a stuffy hospital.
And we have an empty office.
Are you trying to lure me?
Look, maybe.
We do have sunshine
and cute boys.
Speaking of which,
cute boy behind the desk
- is tracking you with his eyes.
- No, he's not.
Oh, cute boy wants Naomi.
Okay, maybe you should shut up...
And go get some coffee
or something...
Please.
- You have to stop that.
- Stop what?
You cannot watch me like that.
It's... not something you can do.
I won't allow it.
Yeah, you can't make
rules about my eyes.
- That's enough!
- No, all of you.
Did you hear that?
- What was that?
- Did I just hear...
I'm the father of that child!
- No, I'm the father!
- If it's anybody's baby, it's mine!
Calm down everybody!
A little help here. A little help.
Dr. Freedman!
Oh, that's great.
- Really great.
- You gotta be kidding me.
You could've called.
Oh, it's such a silly problem.
Hiccups?
We didn't want to bother you.
Well, it's not silly
if you can't sleep.
Chlorpromazine is good,
but it doesn't always work long-term.
We've had some good result
with endoscopic gastroplication.
We put a tube down your throat
and sew together
the bottom of your esophagus
to protect it from
the acid in your stomach.
- It would be an outpatient procedure.
- I'm sold.
- Ready when you are.
- You're sure that that's not...
Just think of it like
breathing into a very expensive
brown paper bag.
Okay, let me see
if I can explain this to everyone.
So Carol was married to Rick.
Carol is now married to Doug.
Keith is Lisa's husband.
- Uh, I'm Rick's husband.
- Life partner.
- You're just mad I left you for a man.
- I'm Lisa's husband.
- And Lisa is the...
- Surrogate carrying my child.
- Our child.
- You are not the father!
- You don't know that, Rick!
- I am so sick of you!
- Hey, hey!
- O-Okay, okay.
Let's all try to remember that
we are in a place of healing.
Uh, Lisa...
H-How are you feeling?
Guilty.
Guilty is how she is feeling.
Wh-why is that, Lisa?
Because the same week that
I brought her here to be inseminated,
she had sex with him...
and him... and him.
And we have no idea
who the father is.
Yeah, she, um, really gets around.
Okay, how does this happen?
How do you pick a super freak
- for a surrogate?
- I screened her.
There was nothing there
to indicate she was...
Sex crazed?
Insatiable?
- Cooper-like?
- Oh. Okay.
The point is, everybody's
flipping out over nothing.
Medically,
it has to be Rick's baby.
We implanted Lisa
with a fertilized embryo
from Carol's egg
and Rick's sperm.
Then Rick implanted some more
of his own for good measure.
Before he decided he was gay.
I've treated Doug.
I have him on valerian root
for anxiety and stress.
And I knew
he was fooling around,
but with his new wife's surrogate?
Can I just, uh...
I think the more pressing issue,
uh, here, is that, uh,
Lisa's had no prenatal care.
She took off
- right after her, uh...
- Sex-a-thon?
Hi. We haven't officially met.
Cooper. Pediatrics.
Hi. Uh, yeah, she... left town,
and, uh, she and the baby
need a complete workup.
Um, who's your usual G.Y.N.?
Uh, she left the practice
rather suddenly.
I didn't do anything.
Well, look,
I would be happy to examine her.
Trashy novels can wait.
Have you ever thought of...
plying your trade
in sunnier climes, Addison?
"sunnier climes"?
Now we see why he has to type
to pick up women.
Hey!
Besides, we have a very strict
no consorting rule here now.
I didn't do anything.
I can't wait to tell Meredith
her stepmom hiccupped
through the whole thing.
She should be here for this.
Susan asked her
to be with her father.
She said he's having
a lot of anxiety.
And... Meredith is supposed
to help with that?
You know there's nothing
to worry about.
What I...
What I worry about is,
Molly living in a new city
alone with a baby
most of the day.
That's hard. And Lexie, who's...
about to start her residency.
She's a really good student,
but it's grueling.
I know.
You know. Right. And...
I worry about you....
Too. How you're getting on,
your mom...
None of that was... simple.
Susan's really on you
to talk to me, huh?
I got to admit, I'm envious...
that she's getting to know you,
and I'm not yet.
I think she may be faking
these hiccups.
To get... us in the same place?
I guess I'm just not very sexual.
He's having an affair.
He's not in love with me anymore.
That's not true, honey.
I love you. I love you so much.
I-I want to do it.
I just want to want to do it.
Okay, Paul, I'm gonna give you
some homework for next session.
- Homework?
- Have sex with your wife.
- Well, but...
- No matter what.
Whether you're in the mood or not,
have sex.
Do it in the bed,
do it on the kitchen floor.
- Do you have a pool?
- Yes.
Okay, do it in the pool.
Have sex.
No pressure, no judgment,
no expectations.
Have sex. Just... do it.
We do need a new G.Y.N.
- Right.
- And Addison seems...
Oh, no, huh-huh, absolutely not.
- What?
- Addison is a nice person.
She is a decent person.
She is a person.
I'm lookin' for a person.
Man, you're just looking.
At least I'm trying.
Dr. Feelgood.
- Hey.
- I love you.
Hi. Thank you.
Okay, Dr. Feelgood,
this is what I'm saying.
Your career is taking off,
girls like that are
throwing themselves at you.
You should be celebrating.
Celebrating?
I just got a divorce.
You got a little tiny dog,
and you cook it chicken,
and you talk to it.
- That's not normal.
- Hey, easy. All right?
I'm alone because I choose to be.
It's... It's a choice.
So you're saying
that you're not interested in Addison,
but I can't have her.
See, Addison isn't
the type of woman you have.
She's a marriage woman.
All right?
She's gonna want a commitment,
and you--
Hey, I do not sleep around.
No. You are a serial monogamist,
all right?
You... You date a girl,
you romance a girl,
and when it's time to commit,
you cut and you run.
- I do not.
- Linda,
Karen, uh, Julie.
Then there was Tricia,
Amy, Carrie, the other Linda...
- Fine. I won't ask her out.
- Good boy.
That's a good boy.
And the week before
I implanted the embryo,
you slept with how many, three?
Three men.
We're almost done here, Lisa,
and then we'll do the amniocentesis.
You're on Carol's side.
I'm Carol's doctor.
You came to us.
You applied to be a surrogate.
- It was your choice.
- I know. I just...
I was about to hand my body over
to a baby that's not mine
for nine month
which is a big responsibility.
That... hit me...
The responsibility... and I just...
They all wanted me.
Me.
And f-for once,
I just stopped thinking and I just...
I did something wild.
Dr. Montgomery, is something wrong?
I'm gonna run
some more tests.
You promise me
you'll take it easy.
I have a stack of dvd's to watch,
and I expect your father
to feed me by hand.
So just call
if you have any questions.
It was nice t-talking with you.
Any news about Mercy West?
Uh, there's a spot.
There's a lot of takers,
but they said it looks good.
So after the intern exam...
I'm not an unfaithful guy.
I'm not a cheater.
You think it'll happen again
if you stay here...
- With me?
- No, I don't know.
George.
I have to go.
- Sam.
- Yeah.
So Paul and Kathy,
I gave them an assignment.
I told 'em to do it.
He didn't rise to the occasion.
Nothing?
No wood.
Not even a twig.
There's gotta be something
physical going on, right?
Because the only other option...
That he just
doesn't love her anymore...
I mean, that's just...
Not the only option.
I mean, did they meet
in the drama department in college?
Could be a thyroid thing, anemia.
- Could be a bunch of stuff.
- Have you checked for extreme ugliness?
Okay, not funny.
Will you get back to me...
- Yes, I will.
- With what you find soon?
And, Cooper, you know what?
Ugly people have sex, Cooper.
Ugly people are people, too.
Hello?
You fill out this E.E.G. request on Ava?
Yeah, you asked for it.
I asked you to run labs
on her every other day.
- What the hell is this?
- Shepherd's doing a full neuro workup.
- Just get the hell of my...
- Go ahead.
I would love to have
an excuse to lay you out.
I didn't do anything.
Whatever you didn't do,
sent Addison running for the hills.
Okay, this guy is 6'2",
dark hair, green eyes,
totally healthy.
He plays the violin,
and he's a physicist.
That is good sperm.
Geeky, but, uh, good.
Lisa has extra donors
if you want to borrow one.
Her tests come in yet?
No, tomorrow.
I don't want to ring
any alarm bells till we're sure.
Ooh. What about this guy?
He's a marine biologist.
Good hair.
Are you sure you want to do this?
Your life is really gonna change.
That's why I'm doing this.
I want my life to change.
I need... my life to change.
I mean, look, you have Maya.
You have a family.
You did everything
the way you were supposed to.
You didn't wait.
Maybe I should have.
Waited.
What do you mean?
Addison, I did everything
exactly the way
I was supposed to.
After college, I never dated anybody
but Sam, because he was the one.
I never had sex with anybody
but Sam because...
cheating is wrong.
I had a baby because...
That's what you do
when you get married.
I never made a single mistake.
I did everything right.
And then Sam comes home
and says he wants a divorce.
So all those photos you're...
busy admiring,
all they are are reminders
of all the stuff I didn't do.
I'm 38 years old,
and I don't know
how to have fun.
That's not lucky.
That's sad.
So just...
shut up about lucky!
Poor...
sad... dried up Naomi.
Shut up.
Poor little, special
talented doctor girl.
Let's make a made-for-tv movie...
about the poor little, dried up
special girl who has no fun.
I could put you out.
You'd have to sleep in the car.
I just...
I just wish I'd been
a little more like you.
What, an adulterous bitch
who forgot to have kids?
Violet?
- Allan.
- Hey!
- Great to see you.
- How you doing?
I'm great. Really.
I'm really wonderful.
Well, I saw you and I...
I didn't want to be rude.
So I hope it's okay.
You know, it's just...
It's really wonderful to see you.
You look, uh...
You look really wonderful.
They didn't have
the gouda you like,
but they had a camembert... Hi.
Hi.
This is Violet.
Violet... Oh, Violet.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
I-I'm Cami.
Allan's wife.
God, I still can't get used
to that word... Wife.
Uh, wife?
- How long have you been married?
- Newlyweds...
eight weeks.
Congratulations.
We'll see you.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, Addison, uh, latte?
Or ac... more of a cappuccino.
Lisa's baby has something
- called lacenta accreta.
- Is that bad?
The placenta abnormally
attaches to the uterine wall.
It makes delivering dangerous
for both mom and baby.
- But there was something else.
- That's not enough?
The baby has some genetic markers
that don't match Carol,
just Lisa.
What? The embryo...
- Did not implant.
- This is Lisa's baby?
Which also means
that the paternity is once again
up for grabs.
Good luck.
I'm off to the beach.
Uh, you can't leave.
Someone has to tell the patient.
Honestly, I ha... I have...
low people skills
with anybody over 12.
It's true. An Internet
hooker just stole his car...
Violet! Privacy. She was not...
She just...
She borrowed my car.
She... She borrowed.
Borrowed.
911 turbo, hand-sewn leather seats.
911 turbo with hand-sewn
leather seats.
Who does that,
to a 911?
A chick. A crazy chick.
- But she was so hot.
- A crazy hot chick.
I loved that car.
That was a single man's car.
That's the point.
I mean, I...
I thought maybe
I was done being single.
I thought she was gonna be
the mother of my children.
What was her name again?
Sexyboobs316.
Are you...
Dude, are you crying?
You better be crying
about that car
and not over sexyboobs315.
316.
I can't. I can't.
I'm gonna hurt him.
Let's just say he's crying
over the car and the woman.
All right? There we go.
Let it out.
Uh, Cristina?
That's a pretty one.
Moves very well in it.
Looks quite natural.
- You paged?
- I need you over here.
Should I be seeing you in
the dress before the wedding?
You think I'm wearing this?
- Well, it is very femine.
- Exactly.
Do you know your mother booked
a chapel that sits 200 people?
Okay, how did I get bridesmaids, huh?
Freakin' stupid cotton-candy
colored bridesmaids?
No offense.
What happened to our small ceremony?
What happened to you
and me at city hall?
I didn't...
I didn't think you were serious.
I am not wearing this.
Oh, I gotta get to the hospital.
You know, we should, uh,
give 'em some privacy.
What?
Oh, you want me to go
over there with you...
- By myself.
- Yeah.
You want a big wedding?
You want the chapel,
you want the guests
and me in a white dress?
Well...
Yes.
I'm a traditional man, Cristina.
- Are you kidding me?
- No.
The saleslady has another batch
of dresses for you to see, Cristina.
Oh, thank you... Mama.
Cristina has certainly
made quite an effort.
Tried on, I would say,
over a hundred dresses,
and that certainly could not
have been easy for her.
Yeah, Mama, I know she seems
disinterested in wedding planning.
But Cristina...
she's not cold.
- I know she seems cold...
- Preston...
If you think Cristina
is right for you,
I trust you.
I trust your instincts.
And the baby, the, um...
the baby isn't even mine?
- Honey, calm down.
- Calm down?
You mean I can keep this baby
if I want to?
Uh, legally, yes.
So who's the father?
We won't know the paternity
of the baby till after Lisa delivers.
More urgent at the moment
is the lacenta accreta.
The fact is, Lisa is at risk
of having
a life-threatening hemorrhage
and the baby could deliver preterm.
So you're saying they could die?
There is a risk of death, yes.
Lisa,
I know you're scared.
If you do go into preterm labor,
you'll have a c-section.
And they'll monitor it
and control it so that they have
a better chance
of saving your uterus
and your life.
And you'll save us,
me and the baby?
Well, I have...
I have to get back to Seattle.
I have a practice.
But I can refer you to someone local...
No, I want you.
You be there.
I thought Kathy was coming
to the appointment today.
Just...
Kathy didn't come home last night.
And, you know,
I don't blame her, but it's just...
What... What if
she's with some guy right now?
Some guy... some... some guy...
who can... who can bring it?
Let's not get ahead
of ourselves.
It's okay. All right?
There are plenty of medical
reasons for low sex drive.
All right?
Sorry. Sorry.
Honey... where were you?
I was out.
All night?
And I had a chance to cheat,
believe me.
But I passed. Okay?
I passed up being with someone
who actually wants to be with me
because I am stuck with you.
You're crying?
Okay, let's...
let's all just calm down here.
I'll be in the waiting room.
Oh! She's starting to hate me.
Oh. What am I gonna do if
little Paul can't perform?
Don't talk about your penis
while you hug another man.
- I'm sorry, man.
- It's okay.
- I'm sorry.
- Let's draw some blood.
Let's draw some blood.
What's in L.A.?
What?
For Addison.
Any idea...
what she might be doing there?
Uh... Naomi and Sam are
down there, I guess. I don't know.
You all right?
We were gonna try.
We were gonna make a go of it...
as a couple.
She bet me I couldn't go
60 days without having sex.
Oh. Let me guess.
You couldn't do it.
No, she couldn't.
She didn't want to be with me.
I thought she did.
I thought she might.
But she didn't.
And I caught her.
You know...
Sleeping with somebody else?
That must have been
so hard for you.
Not that I can't relate.
So I told her I did it.
You told her you did it?
I told her I lost the bet.
I told her I slept with someone.
I figured if she didn't want
to be with me,
she shouldn't have to
feel guilty about it.
Selfless. That's...
- out of character.
- Yeah.
Anyway, uh...
I was just wondering
if you knew what was in L.A.
No.
Okay,
now I am going to the beach.
Wait, Addie.
- Your test results came back in.
- Oh, good.
Because, um, I picked a donor.
I think I'm gonna go
with physicist guy.
Your F.S.H. level is high.
Well, they're high this month.
We can do, uh,
ovarian stimulation.
And your antral follicle count
is only two.
That could be due to stress.
Addison, I'm sorry.
I did all the tests.
There's no fertility potential here.
This is good. This is, um...
Oh, this is just... perfect.
- Addison...
- I have the great guy.
I don't have a baby because
I'm focusing on my career.
Then I have the other guy.
I don't have his baby
because he's not the great guy.
And now I don't have
the great guy or the other guy,
and I'm finally ready
to have a baby, and I can't.
That is so...
exactly what my life is.
Addie, there are other options.
Yeah,
I know about the options.
I'm so sorry.
I know how much you wanted this.
It's okay.
I just, um...
I just didn't realize
I was out of time, that's all.
Addie, please stay so we can...
No, it's okay. I'm fine.
Thank you... for telling me.
Thank you.
I will see you at home.
Looks like you had a bad day.
Okay...
enough.
Okay? Not today.
This is not a good day all right?
So why don't you just... shut up?
Shut up! Shut up!
All right, then.
Transcript: swsub.com - Sync: Benj!
~ seriessub.com ~