Previously on "Grey's Anatomy"...
She cut his LVAD wire.
Denny Duquette died at 7:42 this evening.
I had a baby and I went soft.
Your hand is fine,
and Shepherd will clear you for surgery.
- Our marriage is over.
- Yeah, I guess it is.
Who am I to you, George?
Am I your girlfriend?
Am I somebody you mess around with?
Can I buy you a drink, Callie?
Only if you have it delivered to
my hotel room, because I'm off to bed.
You are a great guy.
So it's Derek.
He's gonna hurt you again.
I'm walkin' away.
It's for you.
It's from Denny.
First, do no harm.
As doctors, we pledge to live by this oath.
But harm happens...
and then guilt happens.
And there's no oath for how to deal with that.
Morning.
I thought we were done
with the whole muffin thing.
This isn't muffins.
This is breakfast.
Mer needs a good, solid breakfast.
First day back after the big surgery.
Are you okay?
Of course I'm okay.
I'm a millionaire.
Fruit?
What do you guys think about B&Bs?
I'm thinking about opening a B&B in Vermont
where the foliage is, you know?
- Maybe you should go back to bed.
- Can't.
I'm going to the hospital.
- Are you gonna go talk to the chief?
- Nope.
Going to clean out my locker.
I could buy a hotel.
How much do you think a hotel costs?
- Ooh.
- Ooh. Izzie!
Is that...
That is $8 million.
$8 million does not like
to have juice spilled on it.
You have to take that to the bank today.
It's making me nervous in the house.
I will, as soon as I clean out my locker.
I am fine.
Really, I am fine.
Denny loved me.
He wanted me to have this money.
He wants me to be happy.
So I'm happy.
Juice?
She's losing it.
She almost battered and deep-fried
an $8½-million check this morning.
That kind of money, I'd buy my own hospital
and stock it full of sick people.
Valvuloplasties and ruptured aneurysms...
You're a psycho. You know that, right?
I'm not the one with an $8½-million
check I won't cash.
Stop talking about me.
I'm fine.
I am cleaning out my locker
and I am going home.
Mer is the one with the problems.
What's wrong with me?
Well, now you haven't told McDreamy
that you dumped McVet.
Oh, you haven't done that yet?
- Dude, tell him already.
- She's scared.
I am not scared.
Derek walked away.
He walked away.
And maybe that's a good thing.
I mean, maybe he's happier.
Maybe he's moved on.
He's got Addison here.
He's got Mark here.
He's got a lot to deal with.
And I'm not gonna make him feel guilty.
I mean, I am being an adult here.
And I am not going to drag him into our whole...
Izzie is the one with the big check.
I'm fine.
Guilt never goes anywhere on its own.
It brings its friends doubt and insecurity.
Is that your boyfriend again?
I do not have a boyfriend.
Then why the guilty face?
You were sexier when you weren't talking.
Am I keeping you, O'Malley?
M&M in 15 minutes, people.
Wait, wait, wait.
We get to go to M&M?
- Even if we haven't finished our rounds?
- Even if.
- I want all of you at the M&M today.
- Yes!
People die in this hospital on our watch.
Once a month, we meet to discuss how our actions
as physicians contributed to the deaths.
This is a serious exercise.
Dr. Bailey.
George, Alex, you guys get good seats.
- Mer and I will get snacks.
- Yeah.
Uh, Mr. and Mrs. Niles.
We kinda got turned around
on our way to admitting.
Oh, oh, not a problem.
Dr. Karev,
uh, Mrs. Niles is scheduled
for a mastectomy tomorrow.
Uh, why don't you show her
and her husband up to the fifth floor?
Is this the little man?
He is adorable.
He's not so adorable at 4:00 in the morning
when he's screaming and won't take a bottle.
Can we just get to the room?
It's been kind of a rough week.
She had to stop nursing.
- Gus here just won't eat.
- Here.
Why don't I take you up?
- There you go.
- Yeah.
You know, you can try a little sugar water
on the bottle, just until he gets used to it.
Does that woman have breast cancer?
What is she, 30 years old?
It's a new baby.
Probably thought the lump was a milk duct.
Hmm?
You learn things on the vagina squad.
Okay, yeah, focus, people.
M&M.
Insults flying, residents covering their asses,
our bosses getting kicked in the teeth instead of us.
- Seats. Snacks.
- Yeah.
Hey.
I didn't know you were coming to the M&M.
You brought snacks?
Well... yeah?
- You okay?
- Fine.
Hey, no surgeries today, right?
- I mean, I'm ready if you need me.
- No.
No surgeries.
Callie.
Hey.
Hi.
Did you get my message...
my messages?
Yeah. I gotta get a seat.
Alex is saving us a bunch
if you want to sit with us.
No.
She's trying to make me feel guilty
about the other night, about the Izzie thing.
- I thought you said you apologized already?
- I did.
I have.
I'm done.
I am not apologizing anymore.
I'm enjoying life.
I'm loving the M&M.
Okay, people, let's begin.
Patient 34986 died last month from
complications following a heart transplant.
Dr. Burke will present.
Guys...
- Isn't patient 34986...
- Denny.
$8 million...
$8 million could get us on a plane
to somewhere far, far away.
Cause of death at autopsy was an embolus that
dislodged from the suture line of the transplant
and caused a CVA with brain stem herniation.
So the company line is that he died of a CVA?
There's no company line.
That's what he died of.
Uh, yes, let's get back to this, uh,
patient's need for an emergent transplant.
You're saying that his left ventricle
had been weakened by the LVAD malfunction?
His left ventricle was weakened by the fact
that he suffered from congestive heart failure.
Oh, come on, Dr. Burke.
We all know the LVAD was cut by an intern.
Oh, I'm going to my happy place.
The exact chain of events remain unclear.
It remains unclear to you because
you were in the ER with a gunshot wound.
Why aren't we hearing from Dr. Bailey?
She was the senior physician on the case.
I am the attending on record.
Yes,
I was the resident in charge.
Dr. Burke has summarized
the medical facts of this case.
Are there any questions for me?
3x05:
Oh, The Guilt
You recently had a baby, Dr. Bailey?
I don't see what that has to do with...
- Sleep deprivation coupled with
wild swings in hormone levels
are factors that could cloud
anyone's judgment.
I sleep just fine, Dr. Savoy.
Really?
'Cause if a patient died
due to my poor decision making,
I'd probably lose
at least a little sleep over it.
Let me remind everyone that our
purpose here is not to place blame.
This is a forum to discuss mistakes
in patient care and learn from them.
Well, so far, I haven't heard
Dr. Bailey admit to a mistake.
Why don't they just put a bullet
in the back of her head?
It would be more humane.
So, for a period of several hours,
your interns were running amok in the hospital,
totally unsupervised.
I'm waiting for a question.
The question is, where were you?
There was the shooting,
and the ER was chaotic.
ER is always chaotic.
Did you page them during this time?
Yes, I paged them multiple times.
Well, apparently, they thought
it was okay to ignore your pages.
Doctor, why do you think your interns
have such contempt for your authority?
You don't know what the hell
you're talking about!
Dr. Karev, sit down.
Izzie.
Next question.
Derek says that neither of you brought
any assets into the marriage.
Well, I had my trust fund
and a sparkling personality.
And the futon couch.
Yes, Addison had a very ugly,
very heavy futon couch.
What ever happened to that couch?
I gave it to Mark.
- She can have him.
- I don't want him.
Okay, well, that's settled.
What else?
So, aside from Addison's trust fund,
which remains in her name,
you'll split everything, stocks,
bonds, 401Ks, down the middle.
The only that gets a little
complicated is the real estate.
Let me make this, uh, simple.
I'd like to keep my trailer
and the land in Seattle.
Addison can have the rest.
Hold on.
That's the house in the Hamptons and
the brownstone overlooking Central Park?
- That's very generous, Dr. Shepherd.
- Thank you.
Hold on.
- He's up to something.
- No, I'm not.
I came here to fight over CDs and books,
go to war over a crystal vase.
What are you up to, Derek?
The divorce is my fault.
Let me take responsibility.
We both had affairs.
You had a one-night stand with Mark.
Derek, actually...
- Well, it was...
- Okay, it was two nights.
You made a mistake.
Meredith and I, we had a relationship.
Make these changes, and I'll sign it today.
You weren't supposed to be in here, Izzie.
You shouldn't have had to see that.
No, it's fine.
I'm fine.
Clearly the doctor thing
was not working for me.
So go about your business.
Run labs, cure cancer.
I'm fine.
You're not going home.
Either you hang out with us
or we'll call your mother.
She's just a few hours away, and I'm sure she
wouldn't mind coming and staying with you all day.
You wouldn't.
- Dialing.
- Whoa, hey, hey! Okay.
I'll just...
go hang out in the locker room.
What is she doing here?
She has no business in this room.
What are you looking at me for?
I didn't have anything to do with this.
I didn't have anything to do
with any of this.
I'll stay with her today, if that's okay.
I'll update charts and I'll run labs
and just keep an eye on her, if that's okay.
She shouldn't be alone.
Fine.
Dr. Bailey...
We just wanna say,
we're really sorry about the M&M.
No, you do not get
to apologize to me for this.
You do not get to feel better.
Neither do I.
Get to work.
O'Malley, just keep an eye on her.
Yes, Dr. Bailey.
Dr. Bailey, you understand,
it's nothing personal.
People talking about your hormone levels
starts feeling pretty personal.
Hey, Dr. Bailey.
Look, you're the baby whisperer.
Gus here drank the whole bottle.
Here, you want to hold him?
Uh, actually now isn't a good time.
I'm about to go and get your wife's labs.
Oh, yeah.
Do you, uh, think you could talk to her?
She's kind of freaking out.
She's not too sure about the mastectomy.
She's thinking maybe a lumpectomy.
I know she likes you.
- Maybe you could talk her into...
- Oh, no, no.
It's not my job to talk her into anything.
Maybe if she knew more about
her reconstructive options...
Um, I'll send our plastic surgeon up.
Hey, chief.
- You got a minute?
- Sure.
- Quite a morning, huh?
- It was.
It's always good to be reminded how
important it is to be at the top of your game.
That's actually what I wanted
to talk to you about.
I am so glad you are back in this building.
I need your help focusing the staff.
They respond to you as an authority figure.
I mean, you're an example
of what they should be:
a leader.
I'm glad to have you back, Preston.
Thank you, chief.
You're back.
I am.
You look, uh, good without an appendix.
It suits you.
How are you?
Fine.
I'm great.
Feeling well? No pain?
No pain.
That's your wife.
I'm on her service.
Oh. Okay, then.
I won't stand in your way.
Okay.
Hi. I was paged by Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd.
Dr. Grey.
- Welcome back.
- Thank you.
And, uh, it's just Montgomery now.
- What?
- My name.
The divorce was finalized this morning.
So...
Montgomery.
To add to our fun,
we've been asked to consult on a case
where a woman has a foreign object
stuck inside of her.
It hurts whenever you move.
Well, then keep your weight off my bad knee.
I'm sorry.
I thought it was on the left side.
19 years of marriage,
you'd think you'd have that one down.
It appears that her husband is the foreign object.
- Ex-husband.
You had to go and get a piercing.
- Sonja.
- What?
It's not like they're not going to find out.
This is so embarrassing.
No. Embarrassing is meeting your husband
for lunch with your ex-husband still attached.
How long is this gonna take?
Because I really don't want
my husband finding out.
Please, could you work out
some small miracle?
Well, first of all, we have to figure out
what the piercing is caught on.
Okay.
Do you have any piercings?
Me? No!
I'm sorry.
I sell real estate.
What is that supposed to mean?
I sell real estate, too.
We've been divorced for five years.
But we keep running into each other.
You know, work stuff.
We get together sometimes.
It's stupid and weak,
and it is never happening again.
Okay, well, Dr. Grey is going to
check on the X-rays, and then...
then we'll take it from there, okay?
But, um, you...
you might want to cancel your lunch plans.
Hey.
- That M&M was...
- Yeah.
I went to tell the chief...
about my hand.
Burke, how...
But I couldn't.
I...
I don't know what I'm going to do.
Well, I-I can be there
if you need me in surgery.
I'm not going to do any surgeries.
I'm gonna catch up on paperwork.
Wait, so...
so what does that mean?
I don't know.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
I need time to think.
I have...
paperwork.
I need to do paperwork.
I know how the rumor mill
works around here, George, okay?
I'm the crazy intern, and now I'm the crazy
intern whose friends have to babysit her.
You know, what we should talk about is
what you're gonna do with all
that money once you deposit the check
after we don't let you destroy it.
Don't move, Adam.
I'm not moving.
- Are those people having sex?
- Just lay still.
They were having sex.
Now they're just fighting.
Good to have you back, Stevens.
I'm not back.
I'm fine, just not back.
Hey, you're Addison Forbes
Montgomery-Shepherd.
That's a lot of names,
a lot of rich sounding names.
You're rich, right?
Oh, that's rude.
That's a rude question. I'm sorry.
It's just that I'm rich now, too.
You're not rich until you deposit the check.
- Do you ever feel guilty?
- I'm sorry?
Being rich.
'Cause I have all this money now,
and I don't really feel like
I did anything to deserve it,
and I can't really talk to my friends
about it 'cause they're all so poor.
Standing right here, Izzie.
Deposit the check, Stevens.
Just start there, okay?
And, um, the guilt will work itself out.
Hey.
You're everywhere.
Well, I'm sorry.
For once, it was actually not on purpose.
Do these look blurry to you?
What exactly am I looking at?
A divorced couple
who got stuck together during...
Oh, wow.
That's gotta be pretty awkward.
Yeah. Divorced five years,
and still going at it like teens at the prom.
So to speak.
Speaking of divorce...
I heard because I'm working with your wife.
Ex-wife.
It was time.
Good.
How's Finn?
Finn is...
fine.
Good.
You're right. They're blurry.
You should get some new ones.
If you go ahead with the mastectomy,
there are several reconstructive options.
Saline implants are used most often,
but silicone has a more natural look and feel.
I can't deal with this right now.
Diana, come on.
It'll take two seconds, huh?
You're the one who has to feel them,
so you decide.
I don't care.
- Dude, believe me, you care.
- Dr. Karev.
Dude, he's right.
You care.
Dr. Bailey?
What's wrong with my wife?
I'm... sorry.
Uh, as you know,
she has stage IIb breast cancer.
I know that.
Will you please tell me what's wrong with her?
- Mr. Niles...
- 'Cause she won't.
She won't talk to me.
I've tried, and I'm trying.
And I know this sucks,
and it's scary, but we can do this.
We can fight this.
But she won't.
She won't even look at Gus.
She won't hold him,
and all he wants is his mom.
It's just...
She's such a good mom.
I know it doesn't seem like that,
but she is.
Okay, I can schedule a psych consult.
I don't want a psych consult.
I just want my wife back.
Please.
Now she's talking crazy, how she might
not have the surgery at all.
Mr. Niles...
Can you please tell her
that she has to have the surgery?
Please.
Somebody has to tell her.
I did this for you, you know?
You know, you have got to stop
doing things for me.
I'm with Tom now.
I love Tom.
I still can't believe you left me for that guy.
Wh-what does Tom have that I don't?
- Well, he doesn't have a pierced...
- You two need to stay completely still
so that we can get a clear picture.
We fought through 19 years of marriage.
The only time we didn't fight
was when we were having sex.
That's not true.
- I still love you.
- Okay, I-I'm in hell.
Mom?
Dad?!
Scratch that.
Now I'm in hell.
Jennifer, maybe you want to go wait in the...
You guys are so paying for
my therapy and my rent...
and a new car.
- Of course, sweetie.
- Oh, go ahead.
Coddle her.
You are old enough to know that your parents
are sexual beings
and that they make mistakes.
Oh, is that what you call this, mom,
a mistake?
Because I call this
you, once again, being a slut.
Hey!
You don't talk to me like that.
I am your mother!
Yeah, and what a great role model
you've turned out to be.
Look at you...
cheating on your husband
with your ex-husband. God!
And, daddy, what are you doing?
I thought...
I thought you had finally moved on.
You said you were gonna start dating.
It's complicated, honey.
Well, it seems that your IUD
has dislodged from your uterus, hooked on
to your husband's piercing and
is embedded in your vaginal wall.
Did she say "piercing"?
Daughter.
Perfect.
- Hey.
- So, who got the brownstone?
- You heard?
People talk around here.
I listen.
- Who got the brownstone?
- It's none of your business.
I left my bike in the basement.
I just want to know
who to talk to to get it back.
Buy a new bike.
You know, this angry divorcée thing
really turns me on.
I got the brownstone.
And you'll get your bike back when you
come to your senses and go back home.
Derek took the Hamptons?
Derek hates the Hamptons.
Derek gave you the Hamptons, too?
He still doesn't know
the whole story, does he?
No.
And as long as you don't tell him,
you get to be the good guy,
and I'm just the chump who seduced
his wife for the hell of it.
Real fair.
I think I'm gonna buy something
for Bailey and for Burke.
What do you think Burke would want?
- Nothing you can get with money.
- He likes jazz.
I'm not buying him a CD, George.
I'm a multimillionaire.
I need to buy him something...
big.
A house...
in the Bahamas.
I'd buy the Bahamas, or at least a Bahama.
An island.
You know, for $8 million, I'd buy an island.
Oh, you're an intern.
When would you have time
to go to your Bahama?
- I'd quit.
- Oh, no, you wouldn't.
You're a surgeon. You operate.
That's what you do.
Sorry.
What?
It's fine.
I'm fine.
I am not a surgeon.
My patient? 30 year old
with advanced breast cancer.
I say live your life
while you can in the Bahamas.
Have you told Derek yet
that you broke up with Finn?
- I'm giving him time.
- That's stupid.
You know, what's stupid
is carrying around a check for $8 million.
I'm fine.
The check is fine.
We're all fine, okay?
I slept with another guy.
Do I tell George?
I, um...
broke up with Finn.
Do I tell Derek?
I can't tell Derek.
I have to tell George.
Honey, please, at least hold Gus.
- No, don't...
- Stop it.
- Will you at least talk to me?
- I want you to leave me alone.
You took a lot of hits today at that M&M.
Some of 'em justified, some of 'em not.
Compassion and empathy
are a big part of the job.
Look, I don't care what Savoy said,
and I know I haven't always been supportive,
but being a parent makes you a better doctor.
Hi.
I just...
wanted to say hi.
Denny left me $8 million.
$8.7 million to be exact.
Did you know that he had money?
'Cause I didn't know.
No, I didn't know.
I'm thinking about using it to travel,
maybe go to Italy.
I've never been there before.
- I hear Venice is amazing.
- Izzie...
I'm fine.
Really, I am. I'm fine.
Everyone thinks I'm not.
Everyone thinks I'm...
But I'm fine.
You're fine.
I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
- So...
- I got shot.
I got shot because I was coming back to the
hospital to check on Denny.
Because you told me to.
I'm not fine.
Denny asked you to marry him,
and now he is dead.
You're not fine.
Don't come in here and...
Just...
We're not fine.
I'm sorry.
We were friends.
You were my boss, but...
I think we were friends, too.
And-and I never meant...
for anyone to get hurt.
And I know there is nothing
I can do to take it back.
No.
Preston, please...
You quit.
You quit being a surgeon.
You have two good hands...
and you aren't using them.
Feel guilty about that.
Sonja, quit grabbing my leg.
I am not grabbing you anywhere.
She is.
Mr. Morris, we need to position you
correctly in order to get a clear image.
Dr. Yang, move him a little to the left.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Oh, I heard about it.
I had to see it.
And I've seen enough.
Dr. Yang, I need you to lift him
a little as you pull him.
Trying.
Now lift his right leg 20 degrees.
Oww! Pain!
Freeze!
Hold that position.
Okay, now, Dr. Grey, can you kind of slowly
swirl Mrs. Kellman in a
counterclockwise direction?
Swirl?
- Swirl?
- Swirl.
Swirl.
Oh, my God, Sonja.
Oh, God, Adam.
Not now!
Careful. Careful!
Oh, my God.
Grey, Yang, on the count of three,
I want you to slowly,
gently pull them apart.
One, two, three.
- Oh, okay, he's having a...
- Sonja!
- Heart attack!
- He's having a heart attack!
Oh, thank God.
I mean, code blue!
He's tearing through his aorta.
We need to get him to an OR now.
He's going to die.
- Who's the cardiothoracic surgeon on call?
- Dr. Harrison, but he's in the middle of surgery.
- Where's Burke?
He's in the conference room,
but he's not on the board yet.
Well, he is now.
Notify the OR.
Let's move, people.
Come on, go, go, go!
How do we do this?
- You stand on my right side.
- On your right side.
- And if at any time during the procedure...
- If you tremor...
I'll look at you.
You'll know to slide in to do
the sutures we've practiced.
What if one of the scrub nurses notices?
What if they say something?
Cristina, I can't walk away
from this surgery.
If I do, that man in there will die.
So tremor or no tremor, I have to try.
- But you...
- I'm your intern.
I will be there on your right side.
10 blade.
As soon as we hear something
about your ex-husband,
we'll let you know.
Since I removed your IUD,
you may want to use a backup method.
Oh, I doubt I'll be having sex
anytime soon once I tell Tom.
You're...
you're gonna tell your husband?
You know, the first time it happened,
I felt so guilty, and I wasn't gonna tell Tom
because it was never gonna happen again.
And then it happened again...
and again.
And then somewhere along the way,
I just stopped feeling guilty.
Yeah...
I'm gonna tell my husband.
I think the truth just has
to come out, you know?
Dr. Burke, I know it's a lot to ask,
but I would really appreciate if you'd
let me try my running whip stitch.
All right, take a good bite.
You want to make sure it holds.
Good.
Don't put too much pressure.
There.
Keep going.
Oh, my God.
Cristina's doing a running whip stitch on a heart.
I guess sleeping with your boss has its perks.
This sucks.
Cristina gets sex and perks.
Maybe you should just apologize again, George.
Yeah, 'cause you're in a great position
to give relationship advice.
Cristina's doing a running whip stitch on a heart.
I don't feel like talking.
When I'm driving home at night
after a long day at work,
all I can think about is getting to my baby.
If this is where you tell me
to fight the cancer
so I don't miss out
on the joys of motherhood...
- Then I get home,...
the baby's crying,...
the exhaustion hits,
and I resent that tiny baby's
presence in my house,
my previously very quiet house.
Why are you telling me this?
So you know what I do?
First, I pick a fight
with my husband, you know,
blame him for not settling the baby down,
then I bitch about
the neighbors' loud music.
And if I'm really tired and pissed off...
I blame the baby.
I mean, if you hadn't been breast-feeding,
you never would've thought
the lump was a clogged milk duct.
You would've gone to the doctor
as soon as you felt it,
the cancer wouldn't have gotten this far,
and you wouldn't be here
making this decision.
Am I close?
What kind of mother
blames her own baby for her cancer?
A mother who's human.
A mother who's overwhelmed.
But if this is gonna kill me eventually,
wouldn't it be easier
if it happened when Gus was little?
Wouldn't it be easier for him
if I just never existed?
Okay. Shh.
Now this is the part
when I tell you to fight the cancer
so that you don't miss out
on the joys of motherhood.
- Derek.
- Yeah.
Hey, you know what I like?
I like that we're civilized.
We're these adult, grown-up people
who can be divorced and friendly.
We deserve a medal.
- It wasn't a one-night stand.
- What?
Mark and I...
it wasn't a one-night stand.
I was in love with him.
Or...
at least, I thought I was.
After you left,
we lived together for two months.
I wanted to believe
that we could make it work,
that I hadn't thrown my marriage away,
that I hadn't thrown
my life away on a fling.
But he's Mark, and, well...
I caught him with someone else, and...
and then Richard called...
We both had relationships with other people.
We're both equally liable for everything,
so please take the brownstone.
All I want is Seattle.
I want Seattle,
and I want never to see you again.
You're here.
You're everywhere, and I can't not tell you.
You know, I've been...
not telling you all day
because I thought it was kind,
and I thought I was giving you space.
But I can't not tell you
because you're here and you're you and...
I broke up with Finn.
Okay.
Okay...
then.
Okay.
I told you.
Yeah.
The operation was successful.
- The next 24 to 48 hours are really critical, but...
- We expect your father to make a full recovery.
Thank you so much, Dr. Burke.
First, do no harm.
Easier said than done.
We can take all the oaths in the world,
but the fact is...
most of us do harm all the time.
I have $8 million.
So I've heard.
I can...
- do anything I want.
- Just about.
And all I really want to do
is a running whip stitch.
My first year as an intern,
I had a stable cardiac patient
who blew out his lung
while I was transporting him to CT.
I called in the code.
By the time everyone got there, he was dead.
If I had put a chest tube in right away...
You made a mistake.
But I stayed.
I worked.
I learned.
I never made that mistake again.
If I had quit,
all I would have had was that life...
that I lost.
Instead, I get to save lives.
Every day, I get to save lives.
Sometimes even when we're trying to help...
we do more harm than good.
She told you.
I've known you my whole life.
I grew up with you,
so I know what you're thinking.
That there is a year of your life wasted,...
trying to make it work with Addison
when you could've been with Meredith,
that you could be happy right now,
that all this...
everything...
That you and Meredith could've had a real chance.
Still...
I thought you should know the truth.
I thought I owed you that...
as a friend.
You're not my friend.
And then the guilt rears its ugly head.
What you do with that guilt is up to you.
Babysitting, Dr. Bailey?
That's right.
I'm babysitting.
I'm being all unprofessional
and emotionally involved while
my patient and her husband
are having a moment together.
Oh, you might want to leave now.
I'm feeling a rush of hormones coming on.
There's no telling what I might do.
How's it going in there?
I think they're leaning
towards a mastectomy.
Well, that's good.
Uh, about Izzie...
- I didn't do anything.
- I know, Karev.
You didn't do anything.
You weren't even here.
No, listen...
I knew.
Izzie told me what she was gonna do,
but I didn't want to get involved.
I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything to stop her.
You weren't the only one.
Alex.
Thank you.
We're left with a choice.
I got fried chicken, extra crispy,...
coleslaw, peach cobbler,
"Beetle Jump", and...
"Samurai Ambush."
The other night, when I told you
I was done trying to compete?
That was me breaking up with you.
No.
No, I think I would've noticed that.
Except you didn't.
Which is why I broke up with you.
At least now you don't have
to feel guilty anymore.
Shut up.
Either let the guilt throw you back
into the behavior
that got you into trouble in the first place...
...or...
...learn from the guilt
and do your best to move on.
Are you seriously not going to deposit that check?
Some good needs to come from this money.
And until I know what that good is,
no, I'm not depositing the check.