The following story is fictional and does
not depict any actual person or event
- Are we going to that party tonight?
- Yeah
Man, forget about that party,
just keep driving right out of Philly
What's wrong with Philly?
May's got her big plans
Singing, huh?
She's gonna cut some place of her own
in New York City
Why do you wanna go to New York?
You don't know anyone there
I know everyone here
I bet she makes it
We won't hear from her ever again
except for on the radio
My Daddy says if you plan big
you'll just disappoint yourself
- Yeah, well I got plans that involve you
- You do?
Oh, crap, get a room
8 Years Later
So this chick went AWAL
after a highway shooting in '88?
Yeah, the guy she was with was killed
She got winged, skipped out of the hospital
before the cops could interview her
Now someone dropped a dime?
Old classmate saw her
on the boardwalk last week
Man, what is that?
- Rice cake
- All right
- May Pierson
- Yeah
Philadelphia Homicide
I don't have anything to do with anything
That's a pretty broad claim
I've been up all night,
I can't be doing this
Doing what, May?
You don't even know what it's about
- Or do you?
- Clem Garris
Shot on the expressway in '88,
you were there
'Till you fled
No
That was another girl
So you're not May Pierson?
That works at this fine establishment
and drives this vehicle?
I'm sayin' that was a lifetime ago
Yeah, we gotta talk about it
- Forget it, I'm goin' home
- This ain't a debate, May,
we got a warrant
We do this here or do it in Philly
You can't take me there, on what basis?
Obstructing a police investigation '88,
New York bench warrant '94
And irritating two homicide guys, 2006
Get in the car
Philadelphia Police Department
Central Division
Were you in court this morning?
Cat emergency,
Olivia got chomped by a neighbor dog
You get the ???
That's not funny
Rita
Hi, John
I almost came by,
I didn't wanna bother you
Lilly Rush, Rita Hart
Formerly Stillman
Oh, hi Um I'll see you later, boss
So, what brings you here?
- House got robbed last night
- No kiddin'?
Yeah, I just reported it
Was Joel with you?
Joel moved out
Few months ago
- The drinking?
- Yeah
- Sorry
- It's better
I'll talk to major crimes,
have them fast track it / OK
- Give you a call
- Thanks
Clem Garris shot and killed January '88,
found on the shoulder of I-76
But not alone
No, that's the scandelous part,
he was found with a woman not his wife
May Pierson
Was shot in the arm,
slipped out of the ER
before the cops could get a play by play
But Vera and Valens
picked her up this morning
Got her upstairs
Leaves the scene
and doesn't turn up for 18 years?
- That's a person of interest
- At least
Clem told his wife Sally, he'd be
at a local bar that night with the guys
So why is he out on the highway
with this gal?
Rough way to find out
what your husband's up to
Unless Sally already knew
Decided she'd had enough
Making her a person of
interest number two
Between New York and Jersey,
there's a lot of ink on you May
That's from way back
A DUI, arrest for loitering, solicitation?
I know what I did
Now you know why I ditched
the cops that night
You didn't wanna get jammed up
Never mind helping find
who killed your boyfriend Clem
He wasn't my boyfriend
Sayin' you weren't screwin' around?
I hadn't seen him in years
Well then how the heck do you end up
on that highway with him, May?
I ran into Clem at Atlantic City that night
Told his wife he was at a Philly bar
I can't account for that
So, you run into him
We're talking about old times,
we're both headin' back to Philly,
he offers me a ride
- And?
- And we're almost there
Get bumped from behind
He pulls over
Gets out
Gets shot
Just like that
Clem talk about bein' in trouble?
Anything like that?
I don't know what his life was like
We'd said our goodbyes years earlier
when we were just kids
May Pierson shows up
What's one last shift
You're really goin', huh?
Leavin' for New York, 8 am
Not gonna wait for Petie
to come get you?
Petie's a big college football star
He's never comin' back
You gonna marry Sally?
That's the plan
What if you came with me instead?
Come with you?
Remember that day we drove around
playing 'Born To Run' until the tape broke?
Yeah, we ran out of gas
We could spend every day like that
I'm not like you, May
I'm not a big dream kind of person
But you are
I gotta stay
Well She sure is pretty
Bye, Mayflower
Just Married
That's how I like to remember Clem
'Cause when I saw him that night
at Atlantic City,
he'd turned into just another
disappointed working guy
It happens
That's what I know
Now can I get back to Jersey?
So May Pierson gave us new details
about your husband's murder
Like? / He was in Atlantic City that night
Not in Philly, like he told you
Look, I know everyone thought
Clem must have been seein' her
behind my back, but he wasn't
How do you know?
Clem wasn't perfect,
but he was more good than bad
And when he was in something,
he was in
When I was 19,
I took off with a guy
2 weeks into knowin' him
The heart wants what it wants
Yeah He was a biker, drinker
But I thought this is it
Roll out the carpet,
we're goin' down the aisle
You didn't go through with it?
We came close
We were road trippin'
Went to a courthouse in Knoxville
and we just sat out there on his bike
Neither one of us could get off
Well Clem and I never had
any doubts / No?
Getting married was
the happiest day of our lives
Anyone unhappy that day?
One person
- Are you sorry?
- No, come on
I didn't want it to be this way
We were gonna have babies anyway
We're doin' the right thing, Sal
I'm gonna make you happy every day
What a frickin' joke
Petie, we didn't think you were coming
You two aren't foolin' anyone
Are you drinkin' this early?
You're just marrying here because she's
knocked up OK, and everyone knows it
- Keep it down
- Pete you're acting really embarassing
Whoa, I'm embarassing?
I know who you really wanna be with
It's my girl May
What the hell happened to you?
What would happen?
I got my ass kicked out
and I'm washed up
and my girl's gone so you get everything
and I get nothing
Hey start up my car
Me and my bride are pullin' outta here
Just Married
Petie had some kind of wall?
Somethin' went real wrong
at Penn State
He dropped out,
came home damaged good
Brought some strong feelings home
If it's true, that Clem was
in Atlantic City that night? / Yeah?
Petie spent a lot of time there
So he could've run into Clem and May,
and reacted badly?
I can't put it past him
He's in jail now
I hear you made a spectacle of yourself
at that wedding, Petie
Yeah, what a jerk
Pretty bitter about things
going so good for Clem?
I was in a real bad way then
I just lost my free ride to Penn State
- I played ball, too
- Yeah?
What went wrong?
First game, I choked
Froze up on the field, did it all year
Got cut
Couldn't've been easy
comin' home after that / It wasn't
- People look at you like you're crap
- Including Clem?
No He was cool
I apologized for the wedding thing
We moved on
Started hangin' out again
Were you surprised to hear that he was
with May the night he died? / Yeah
- Everyone was
- Bother you at all?
- How do you mean?
- She was your girl, right?
I went with her in high school
So maybe you wanted to
get back to that time
When you were a football star,
and had your girl May
Not denying those were better times
but 8 years later I wasn't thinkin' about May
- No?
- I was thinkin' about someone else
*  Glory Days
by Bruce Springsteen *
9 seconds left and crazy Rick
tosses me that screen pass
Yeah, I remember,
me and Sal were on the field
gettin' ready to do the homecoming thing
Caught that baby,
turned on the jets
- That was something
- Crazy times, crazy times
Never been a prettier
homecoming queen, Sal
You in that white dress
You remember that, huh?
Are you kidding me?
Everybody noticed
Someone got the best catch in school
I sure did
Who's that?
A guy I do favors for,
make some cash
- I'd better get back to the baby
- I'll be home soon
Why is she so down?
Things have been kind of yippy at home
You know truthfully, man,
I don't know if me and Sal were
ready for all this
So young
- It's probably just tough times, right?
- Yeah
No, man
- It's more than that
- You think she's sorry?
I think she wishes
she didn't cry every night
So Clem and Sally were on the outs
Win or lose
I'll lay it out for you
Things between me and Sally kind of grew
So Sally and Petie started up
??? Clem their marriage was so great
That gives her motive
if she wanted out for good
What about these favors
that Petie was doing for money?
Breakin' legs, stealing cars
Thug stuff
Clem ever get in on it?
Petie says he offered
but Clem wouldn't go for it
The guy walked the line
Uh, anyway guys, good night
What's he nervous about?
Her
So they found who did the robberies?
Bobby Greene
Lived up the street
He used to throw mudballs at our windows
- That little kid?
- He's grown up
- Criminal now
- Oh, God
He hit two other houses on the block
but he got picked up this morning
That's sad
So, why didn't you come to me
about this in the first place?
I knew you'd be busy
A long time to be less busy
You are who you are
I would like to think I've
learned some things
- Anyway I
- Would you
you wanna have dinner?
- Go to Irena's?
- Really?
- Yeah I'm free Friday
- Me, too
- 7?
- OK
OK
- All right, I'll see you
- OK
- 7
- Yeah
Clem made you happy every day
- Right Sally?
- Right
- Don't wanna revise that statement?
- Why would I?
How about because you were bangin' Petie
- That was wrong
- But it happened
And you not tellin' that,
get's the wheels turnin'
Maybe you felt trapped
Things between you and Clem
died out but he wouldn't give up
'Cause when he was in somethin'
he was in / Look
I never had that kind of love again
So maybe I wanna remember things
a certain way
But we don't live in that land, Sal
We got a real life murder to solve
That's true
Things faded
And? / And it's true Clem
wasn't one to give up
But he did
Finally
- Oh, man it's
- Valentine's Day
Baby, I'm sorry
- I was gonna get flowers and candy
- It doesn't matter
Let's go to bed, huh?
No
We ain't makin' it, are we Sal?
- Why can't we fix it?
- I don't know
It's just gone
But it was right
It was fun and easy and right
Yeah, it was
I don't wanna be a divorced person
Yeah, but do you wanna be
this married person?
That's when Petie came into the picture?
It wasn't love
But he wanted to be with me
And Clem wanted to be somewhere else
By the time May came back to town,
he knew he could go see her
May came back?
When her mother died
Clem went to the funeral
I told you I hadn't seen Clem
since high school
Oh, I know what you told me
His wife said he was at the funeral
Look, I didn't kill him
Then why lie to my face?
What are you hiding?
Me and Clem did a stupid desperate thing
Tried to get back something
we'd never have again
I need to hear about that
I saw him at the funeral
And?
Everything rushed back
Clem Garris shows up
Hey, Mayflower
I should get to the reception
Let me drive you
How'd New York go?
Not too good
How is that possible?
You're the best singer I've ever heard
Turns out a lot of people can sing
You going to that reception?
No
Just keep drivin'
You got a guy there? New York?
No Mostly just got debts
How you been gettin' by?
I don't wanna talk about it
OK
I just haven't been livin' right
What if we started over?
You and me
How? / Get out of here
Just drive away
Like we should've done years ago
I loved you so much
Maybe it's still in you someplace
I know it's in me
I owe this guy
There's a job I can do
In Atlantic City, get you money
- And then clear out of here?
- Yeah, you and me Finally
We thought we could pick up
where we left things all those years ago
But you can't go back
Learned that the hard way
So then you met in Atlantic City
He did this job and we went
Then the shooting happened
- What kind of job?
- Just said it was a favor for a guy
Looked into the dude Petie
was doing favors for,
he's a lowlife named Henry Mack
Probably who Clem got mixed up with
What's this Mack's line of work?
Had a ring of guys stealing cars,
at airports, casinos,
bringin' then back to
his chop shop in Philly
So maybe Clem's doin'
some runs for him that night
Maybe Petie knows more about
that night than he's lettin' on
- You find this Mack?
- 6 feet under in Trenton
- Tough interview
- But there's a story to that
Guy was murdered,
shot on a casino parkin' lot
That connected to Clem somehow?
I'm guessin' because Mack was killed
the very same night Clem was
I know Clem usually walked the line
Didn't get mixed up in
the kind of favors you did
He kept his nose clean
Is that maybe just one time
when he really needed the money?
- For May?
- Maybe
But that one time you two worked for Mack
Clem gets shot
So does Mack / Uh-huh
It's kind of hard to miss
what those murders have in common
- You
- I was a theif not a killer
You and Clem were stealin' those cars,
maybe get ambitious?
- Decide to double cross Mack?
- No
But Clem was desperate
Maybe havin' a runnin' buddy
made you bold and Henry Mack
- probably deserved the pop in the head
- I don't know how Mack died
And after you two waste him, you panic
Word Clem's gonna fold 'cause he don't
got a criminal nature, he walks the line
Clem was the one guy who was nice to me
when I came home a mess!
Everyone else kept away
He stayed my friend
So be a friend to him, Petie
Say what happened that night
He didn't wanna be dirty
But it was his only ticket out
* Stolen Car
by Bruce Springsteen *
* I found me a little girl
and I settled down *
* in a pretty little house
in a pretty little town *
* We got married,
and promised never to part *
* then little by little
we drifted from each other's heart *
* Now I'm driving a stolen car *
* down on a pitch black night *
* And I'm doing my best to make it through *
* Well I'm just sittin' down here
at a Stanton light *
* I wanna get caught but I never do *
* At first I thought
it was just restlessness *
* that would fade as time went by *
* and our love grew deep *
* But in the end it was
something more I guess *
* that tore us apart and made us weep *
* And I'm driving a stolen car *
* waitin' on that little red light *
* I keep tellin' myself
everything's gonna be alright *
* But I ride by night and I travel in fear *
* That in this darkness
I might just disappear *
* She asked if I remembered
the letters I wrote *
* When our love was young
and we were bold *
* She said last night
she read those letters *
* And they made her feel
one hundred years old *
* As the river runs by the little town *
* down into the sea *
* it was there in the shade
I let my body down*
I'm out, Petie
No if you wanna get paid,
we gotta go to Philly
I'm takin' the car
- What?
- Forget the money
No, it's no good, Clem
Mack won't go fot that
Mack's not gonna find me
Be good to her
He went off to get May
That's it
The '69 Chevy, huh?
It was a beauty
Yeah I've seen it
You're still driving the same car
you and Clem took out of Atlantic City
And the only person who knew
where Clem was going that night?
- Petie
- It wasn't Petie
- Who then?
- A guy Clem called him Mack
There had to be two people, May
Someone drove that second car away
And somehow the Chevy
ended up back with you
You would'nt've given us Mack right off
Unless it was someone
you wanted to protect
Maybe you and Petie need to talk
Hey, Mayflower!
Hi, Petie boy
May IDed Henry Mack
from a photo spread as the shooter
So we know he was one of our guys
at the scene
But we still got the matter
of who was with him
And who killed him later that night
You ever make it with singin'?
I'm just a cocktail waitress
So May says you two made a promise
Back when Clem died
Yeah
I'll keep it Petie
I'm not scared
It's over for me
But you can still have a good life
What happens?
After Clem takes off in that Chevy?
He finds trouble
All because of me
We both had our part in it
- You think you can steal from me?
- Mack
Take their car
Meet me back there
You gave him up?
He was gonna kill me
- Get in the car and drive!
- OK, OK
* One Step Up
Bruce Springsteen *
* Woke up this morning my house was cold *
* checked the furnace, she wasn't burning *
* Went out and hopped in my old Ford *
* hit the engine but she ain't turning *
* Giving each other some
hard lessons lately *
* but we ain't learning *
* The same sad story, that's a fact *
* one step up and two steps back *
* Bird on a wire outside my motel room *
* but he ain't singing *
* Girl in white outside a church in June *
* but the church bells, they ain't ringing *
* I'm sitting here in this bar tonight
but all I'm thinking is *
* I'm the same old story, same old act *
* one step up and two steps back *
* It's the same thing night on night *
* who's wrong, baby, who's right? *
* Another fight and I slam the door on *
* another battle in our dirty little war *
* When I look at myself I don't see
the man I wanted to be *
* Somewhere along the line
I slipped off track *
* One step up and two steps back *
* There's a girl across the bar *
* I get the message she's sending *
* Mmm, she ain't looking too married *
* me,well, honey, I'm pretending *
* Last night I dreamed
I held you in my arms *
* the music was never-ending *
* We danced as the evening
sky faded to black *
* One step up and two steps back *