When I first started the show,
I knew two years.
Then we knew four, then we knew five.
The sixth year happened,
and then "That's it."
Then suddenly seven happened, and
we went "This is really it. We're done."
Eight. And so it's just been a crazy ride.
Honestly, who knew it would go this long?
Who knew it would be this successful?
Part of the success of Stargate too
is not something that we see,
except that we keep getting renewed.
I'm not always really aware of what's
going on out there in the real world
in terms of our ratings or fan response.
I know the fan base
for the show is phenomenal
but, until you go overseas,
you don't really know.
Suddenly, you're in Europe
and people are going "Sam! Sam!"
Australia - everywhere I went,
people recognise you.
So then you go
"Wow, it is a success." Who knew?
Sci-fi was not a genre
that I was hugely into.
I've said this before and I'll say it again:
I was a Little House on the Prairie girl.
But I wanted to do this show
because of the character.
Because I loved the character
and I saw so much potential for her.
In the pilot, I saw her flaws,
but I also saw great potential
and I saw all her strengths.
It's not a character that
you come across very often, as a woman.
So I was really thrilled
by the opportunity to play her.
That's what jazzed me.
OK, I'm Stargate Barbie and we're dead!
It wasn't that I thought "Sci-fi",
and I still don't.
We're not in a ship all day long.
We're present-day, fallible human beings.
We're goofy and irreverent at times.
There's a definite sense of humour to
the show, and a definite human element.
And I think it's very accessible.
Even though I am probably
the most sci-fi character in it
because of the techno-babble I speak.
I used to do Shakespeare.
Now I do techno-babble.
I don't think of it as a sci-fi show.
I hope that doesn't upset sci-fi fans.
Cos it is a sci-fi show,
but it's so much more.
- What? What?
- We got trouble.
- W-What kind of trouble?
- Think Bolivia.
Oh, Jaffa?
They made our position.
Keep working.
What a dream job. We get to do
what we love to do for a living.
Everyone loves being here - crew, cast.
It's so hokey but we really like each other.
We love each other.
Just last night, I'm talking to
Chris Judge for an hour and a half.
I talked to Michael before he went
to Australia, and to Don the other day.
And getting together with
our craft-service guy and hair stylist.
We really dig each other.
We're very, very lucky, and I don't know
that it's the same on every show.
It's just like a family.
Michael, Chris and Rick
are just like my three brothers.
So we have our sibling rivalries
but, when push comes to shove,
we'd go to the wall for any one of us.
We'd all look out for each other,
and that's rare, I think.
So what happens beyond the gate?
I have a very boring life
during the shooting of Stargate
because I have to stick
to a pretty regimented routine
in order to say all the words
that I have to say.
This is my favourite thing.
But on weekends, for me, it's about
getting out into the woods with my dog,
just breathing fresh air and hiking.
I'm still renovating my house.
I play guitar.
Not in public. Ever.
But it's really quiet, sedentary,
just chilling. Chilling, chilling.
I'm not a big party girl.
I don't go to the club scene...
unless I go out with Christopher Judge.
Which happens once a year -
cos that's all you can handle.
It's very quiet.
I'm nature girl on weekends.
I bought an Ocean Kayak,
and now I'm kayaking, which I love.
So I'm just outdoors-y girl.
Shooting in Vancouver is brilliant.
In the summertime, and even up until
a couple of weeks ago, I was kayaking.
Wintertime, you go skiing.
The guys play hockey,
so you go to the hockey games.
My husband plays with the Stargate guys.
It's a perfect lifestyle out here,
especially if you're into the outdoors.
Directing was, and is, and has been
something I've wanted to do
since before I got on Stargate
and I was directing theatre.
For me, it was really six years of proving
to the powers that be that I could do it.
In the negotiations for season seven,
I laid it on the table
and said "This is a deal breaker.
I have to be able to direct."
And they let me.
That's the scene. We're doing one crane
shot which'll end up in a wide master,
a two-shot of Daniel and Carter,
and simultaneously shoot a medium
close-up of Barrett with his radio.
Nice!
"Resurrection" - initially I was gonna
direct it early in the season.
Then I was gonna direct the episode
right after the summer hiatus.
Then I was gonna direct
the second-last episode.
Suddenly it was the last episode and it
was Michael's episode, which was great
because I could talk to Michael
about what his vision was
when he wrote the script.
I've never seen
such a complete bastardisation
of what was once a very lyrical
and musical piece of work.
It all worked out.
Initially I was freaked out.
"Oh, my God! How am I gonna do this?"
It turned out to be the most phenomenal
experience of my career so far. I loved it.
The one thing I kept forgetting
to do was say "Action."
- Action!
- That's brilliant.
Daniel/ You OK?
Where is she? She won't get far.
All units. This is Agent Barrett.
The female prisoner is unaccounted for.
Secure all exits.
Without exception, every single member
of this crew gave 110% for me.
And they all said they would,
from our locations manager, Lynn Smith,
to Bridget McGuire to James Robbins.
All of the elements
that happen prior to shooting.
And then on set, everyone.
It will take a really long time,
but... that's what cool shots take.
I was able to design a show
and design a style for the show
based on the knowledge that I knew
I could push the camera department
because I knew that our crew could
handle what I was throwing at them,
the two-and-a-half-page crane shot that
I designed for the opening of the show.
And I knew that it would work,
and they all added.
I also had the privilege and the safety net
of Michael Greenburg on set every day.
He just let me do my thing.
I designed every shot.
I drew it out on paper.
I'd say "Michael, this is the next scene.
These are my camera angles."
"This is why I want
the camera to move here."
A great director.
I can't believe she's a first-time director.
She's got all the right moves,
all the right stuff. And she looks good.
She used to be really ugly, then she got
punched in the face and became pretty.
Then, of course, I had a great cast.
Rick wasn't in it, sadly.
But Michael and Christopher...
I just love them. They were so on board.
That goes back to that whole...
why we love each other so much.
Brad Rines was my editor,
and he's an amazing editor.
So I came in with his mix and his first edit
and went "This is great!
I barely have to change anything."
Will Waring said to me
"When you go into the first-day edit,
you'll pretty much sit there and go 'Cool."'
This is really cool!
There was just a few things
that we changed,
a couple of takes we used differently.
But it took less than a day for me to do
my director's cut. It was that easy.
Mind you, I designed the show in such a
way that there was little room for editing,
which the producers may
or may not have liked.
But it was like "You kinda
have to do this. This is the way."
I did a lot of what we call "oners"
where it was an entire scene in one move
so you can't cut into it.
All part of my design.
It was great.
Directing is a career path.
I will always want to be an actor.
There's always a charge to that creative
juice, but to open up other elements.
Especially after seven years on a show,
you don't wanna become stagnant.
I would love to direct episodes of
the spin-off, but certainly other things.
This is the final shot of season seven.
And it's bloody
brilliant, if I do say so myself.
Cut. Project the gate!
That's a wrap till season eight.
Whoo!
Thank you to the fans, to all of you.
Hope you're enjoying season seven.
Hope you're enjoying the DVDs.
I've said this before and I'll say it again:
There but for the grace of you go... we.
If it weren't for your support, we wouldn't
be doing the show, or season eight.
Oh, my God, it's fantastic!
For your letters and your love
and... just for sticking by us.
From the moment
the show was announced,
we had a fan base,
before we even hit the airwaves.
You stuck by us and so thank you
from the bottom of our hearts.
If it weren't for you,
we wouldn't be here. Thanks.
I'm Amanda Tapping.
Thanks for watching "Beyond the Gate".
Or something like that.
D'oh! D'oh! D'oh!
How was that?
ENHOH