Season 3 Episode 9
The Three-Card Monte Job
I think he understands.
This is a bomb?
It's a phone.
Now you have two choices...
Either you do
what we're asking you to do,
or I have to pay visit
to Natalia and little Sasha.
They go to school same way
every morning. Did you know this?
Is not safe.
Anything.
- I'll do anything.
- What I'm asking for you to do is...
Answer this phone.
What are you supposed to do
when they call you?
I do whatever they ask.
Then destroy the phone,
and tell no one,
or they'll kill my children.
You install and repair
telephone lines for a living?
For 10 years.
I have three major contracts
right now.
If I'm arrested,
it all goes away.
And you have no idea
why they specifically targeted you?
I'm not perfect,
but I try to be a good man.
My parents came to Boston
to get away from this kind of thing...
Russians hurting Russians.
And if you contacted the police?
The Russians will know.
They say they're watching.
This bar, I've been here before.
It's probably safe.
And you...
- You're no cop.
- No. I'm no cop.
Cloned.
This phone rings,
I want you to answer it.
- We'll contact you.
- Thank you, Mr. Ford.
We're not gonna let anything bad
happen to your family.
Thank you.
Okay, now, I put a tap on the phone,
So if that thing rings, we'll know it.
Good. What else?
There's one incoming call.
These guys were thorough.
They wanted to make sure if they called,
Andrei would answer.
- Yeah, they call it once to test it.
- Exactly.
So if we just call them back...
You going to get that?
This is Pieter.
Hello?
Marco.
Polo.
- You sure this is the place?
- I'm sorry,
am I sure?
Eliot, what is that Russian carrying?
It's called a smartphone.
Smartphones read e-mails,
they have GPS maps,
They link to an atomic clock on
this little thing called the Internet.
You ever heard of it?
A smartphone has an operating system.
If it has an operating system,
you know I can hack it.
Think I may have just ID'd
our bad guy.
His name is Pieter Volokh.
Him and his crew,
they used to belong to the M-45s,
ex-military hitters
turned mafia boys.
Now, they took a big hit
in a bust last month.
They lost $20 million
in merchandise to the police.
That's gotta hurt.
We know what they're after.
They're looking for a big-payout job,
so that they can
get back on their feet.
Now, I've ID'd the perp,
I know what they want,
and I know why.
What did you do with your afternoon?
I'll tell you what I'm gonna do
when I get back there.
Think he's involved?
It's Russian mafia.
They wear their tattoos
like a résumé.
See that cathedral on his neck?
Three spires, three tours in prison.
The stars on his arm
means he's a Captain.
- So he's the boss?
- I don't know. Probably.
I ran into some of these cats
in Petrozavodsk.
They blackmail
innocent people like Andrei
into committing crimes
and dropping off money.
Then those guys get picked up
by the cops or they end up dead.
It's brutal.
Want me to taser him?
No tasering, Parker.
Not yet, anyway.
- Are they still in sight?
- I hate this kind of criminal.
What were you doing
when I chased you?
I stole art from rich people
who could afford it.
These guys?
They terrorize their victims,
they harm families,
and the worst part?
They make innocent people
commit crimes.
That's the worst part?
You blackmail an innocent man
into breaking the law,
the rest of his life he's gonna feel
shame over how you made him helpless,
or guilt over what you made him do.
We chose crime.
Andrei didn't.
Hurry up!
I hurried! Then I hurried again!
I checked it three times. It's clean.
Check it again.
What are you doing?
- You don't throw crowbars at people!
- Sorry!
"You don't throw crowbars at people!"
Could have just tasered him.
Promise me we're gonna
take these guys down hard.
I promise. Where are they going?
I want this to be exciting
and dramatic.
It's already exciting. Look.
They reversed the phone tap. We're blown.
They're gonna kill Hardison.
They're gonna kill who?
No, they ain't!
I bet you they ain't!
Nate, you better stall!
Come on.
Wait a minute.
My only way out is the front door.
Are they coming through there?
- I don't know.
- What you mean you don't know?
You better say something.
I swear on my mama,
I will blow a hole through your bedroom.
Tell me something.
We'll tell you something
in a second, Hardison.
We're coming through the back door.
What?
- You're not gonna like this.
- What?
Somebody's been eating our porridge.
You don't have to be
so rough with him...
Hold on, Hardison.
They're not here for you.
Yeah, I knew it.
Nobody can reverse my phone taps.
Come on, man.
I don't see why y'all
were getting all excited.
All right, I'll do whatever you say.
I still have the phone!
- What else do you want from me?
- The red phone again.
Nate, this guy's not our boss.
- He's another blackmail victim.
- Yes, I know.
I'm about to meet their boss.
Go on.
Hello, dad.
Give me a moment.
I want a word with my son.
Go on.
I got out a while ago.
Yeah, I know.
I knew you were out.
I didn't see you at the prison gates
waiting to pick me up.
Yeah, I was visiting mom's grave.
So, what's a washed-up bookie
like yourself
doing with a Russian
blackmailing crew?
I went to prison
'cause I took the fall...
for the three families.
I did my time for them
like a stand-up guy.
- You heard what happened.
- It was on the news.
- Artie Van, he turned state's evidence.
- Turned state's evidence...
Gave up his ledger.
20 years of payoffs...
The McTeagues, the O'Hares,
the Donnellys...
All the big families
are going down by law.
Now, once upon a time,
they would take care of someone
who's gone inside for them.
I went to jail for nothing.
I want to get my piece.
With these guys?
These guys that threaten children?
- What?
- You thought you were smarter than me,
brighter, better than me.
Everybody in the neighborhood
always treated me with respect,
- but my own son...
- What did you do to respect, exactly?
My son, my altar-boy son.
Listen to you.
Never broke the law,
you never broke a rule.
Look at you now. You're a thief.
You've done time.
If you know where I've been,
then you know
that this is my town now.
And I don't want
you running game in it.
All your life you thought
you were better than me.
Now you're trying to be me?
You can't be me.
You don't have the stones for that.
You're not tough enough.
You're not ruthless enough.
You don't have what it takes.
You remember the first time
I brought you into my office?
Queen and her court.
Got that? Watching?
Keep your eye on this.
It's the lady.
Now, pay attention.
Which one?
You still don't get it, do you?
You got to think this through, kid.
You're just never gonna get it.
You weren't good enough
to know what I was doing then
and you ain't good enough
to know what I'm doing now.
By the way, I'm setting up
in my old workshop in the back there.
I'll be out by this weekend,
so don't worry about it.
Okay. Run it.
Go ahead. Run it.
You know what?
Maybe we should just discuss first.
- They feel weird going after your dad.
- Well, I don't.
Come on. Run it.
Jimmy Ford.
Hardison, tell us about Jimmy Ford.
All right.
Jimmy Ford.
Jimmy... your pop.
He wore a lot of criminal hats, man.
But he was well-known
in the neighborhood.
I think people liked him.
- He helped some people get some money.
- Forget it.
Come on, you can't sugarcoat it.
You got to tell it like it is, all right?
Jimmy Ford, he started off as a bookie
who worked for the McTeagues.
He ran every bet
this side of Atlantic city.
Once he had a fair amount
of honest citizens in his debt,
he made the transition
into being a loan shark.
Now, he used those contacts
to become a fixer.
So what he'd do is he'd take
a bad guy that needed a job
and a boss who needed a henchman,
match them together.
That...
That's Jimmy Ford at his peak.
King of the neighborhood.
I don't know how this ties in with
the whole cellphone/blackmail thing.
We've got multiple victims.
Andrei, the telephone repair guy.
- Eliot's friend Simakov.
- What does he do?
Shipping. Industrial clothing, uniforms.
Nothing remarkable.
Then, following Pieter's phone,
- we found a third red phone.
- That's a dead end.
We don't know who this guy is
or why the Russians want him.
He's not gonna talk to us 'cause Pieter's
boys already put the fear of God in him.
What is Jimmy's game?
I would imagine he has a chess board
set up in the back room.
Looks a lot like yours.
No, dad doesn't like chess.
No, his game is three-card Monte.
Just keep the cards moving.
Don't show you the queen
until he wants you to see the queen.
All right, so,
we don't have enough information
to run a con on this guy.
Not yet, anyway.
So, why don't we just sit this one out?
No, we're gonna keep at this.
We're gonna gather information.
Let me be a bit clearer...
Why don't you sit this one out?
You want us to go after the bad guys,
we're gonna go after the bad guys!
And we're gonna go after them hard!
Yeah, right.
I said:
"Let's go after the bad guys."
But not Jimmy Ford.
You honestly think that you can put
your own father behind bars?
You got to stop looking at him
as my father.
He's a mark like any other mark.
He's hurting people.
We can do this. It's what we do.
It's our job to go after the bad guys.
It's not your job
to take down your own father.
No. It's my pleasure.
Hey, guys,
Andrei, our first victim...
- He just got a call.
- Okay. Let's go.
Andrei's scared, but he's told us
what they've asked him to do.
He's been tapped
because of his access.
He's supposed
to get into the precinct
on one of his routine maintenance calls
and install a black box.
With that,
the Russians can spoof phone calls
off the hardwired phone trunk.
- Can you turn it off remotely?
- Too antiquated for a digital hack.
So Jimmy can control which alarms
reach the precinct and which don't.
Like silent alarms? From banks?
Or any building
with a high security system.
So if we can't hack it,
how do we stop him, then?
We mustn't stop him.
If Andrei doesn't do what they say,
then they're gonna go after his family.
All right, so we don't stop him.
We help him.
What?
Hey, bartender!
Get me a drink!
Quiet down.
Detective Moffat. Detective Davies.
We're with district eight.
What do you got?
Who the hell are you, cupcake?
You want to know who I am?
I'm Viola.
- Viola Dagostino of...
- Of the Dagostinos.
We got her husband, we got a brother,
and both uncles up at eight.
Got her on a drunk and disorderly,
that's not gonna keep her away for long,
we got to store her somewhere
away from the press.
Yeah, I got you.
Let me call it in.
Incoming.
Eighth district here.
She's a handful.
One little drink.
You're good. Just take her downstairs
to the drunk tank. It's empty.
Gotcha.
Come on!
Make it snappy!
Being handcuffed in a police station is
a recurring bloody nightmare of mine.
How do we look?
This baby's a lot more sensitive
than what Andrei has access to.
See, we can block alarms,
we can trigger alarms,
but most importantly,
we can track alarms.
It should be synchronized.
Nate?
All right, we're good.
Let's get the hell out of here, then.
Sophie?
My exit is with Parker.
See you on the outside, cupcakes.
Where's he at?
- He's gone!
- Lucille! Lucille 2.0!
- He's off comms.
- He's off the reservation.
I know what he's up to.
You interfered.
How unlike you.
Where I come from,
this is not tolerated.
We're nowhere near
where you come from, so just shut up.
Let me tell you what I did.
I know what you did.
You let our repairman loose.
This repairman was a liability.
He could've panicked,
or he could've tipped off
any of those cops at the precinct.
I mean, he's not like us.
Us?
Us. Yeah.
You know, using a civilian
was a brute-force move,
but let me show you
a more elegant way of doing...
No, that's all right. I'm just...
I'm getting a remote-control device
out of my pocket, fellas.
All right?
I want to show you a more elegant way
of doing business with this remote.
You have much finer control
over your phone lines
than you could ever hope for.
Now, this is an unexpected gift
from you, my son.
Thank you very much.
Now you can go.
Only I control the box.
You try to take this from me,
I will destroy the black box. I will.
All right?
I'll do it remotely.
- Didn't see this coming.
- Like I said, this is my town now.
You want to pull a job this big
in my town...
I want in.
- He's setting us up for the cops.
- I just got out of prison.
You escaped.
And yet, you do not run. Why is this?
Because you are,
how do you say, a narc.
If you'd done your homework,
you'd know that I set up a warden,
brought him down, and got myself
a free pass at the same time.
Nobody could do this.
I did from inside a prison.
Now, if I can do that,
think what I could do for you.
Or to you.
Carrot in one hand, stick in the other.
That's a hard way to come at them.
I learned from the best.
He's in.
What's the plan?
All right.
Pay attention.
I don't like you.
Gee, does that mean I can't come to
your birthday party and ride the pony?
First Boston independent,
state street branch of the Boston bank,
Commonwealth loan and securities.
Now...
First independents got
a Glenn-reeder alarm system,
series f-900.
Two guards in the front,
ne guard in the back.
Cameras record...
not monitored.
Daily turnover... $2 million.
State street,
mostly commercial papers and loans,
but they do have bearer bonds
in a basement lock down room.
Just takes a key and a retina scanner.
Commonwealth...
Their alarm system's a holdover
from the '70s, but...
But it's...
What?
What do you do on your weekends?
There's something wrong with you.
So, which one's he gonna hit?
- None of them?
- None of them.
But, see, since we control
the precinct alarm system,
the cops are gonna think
they're being robbed.
Think of this, Nathan.
Three banks being robbed
at the same time.
They're gonna think it's Armageddon.
Every cop in town Is gonna be
heading towards those three banks.
And away from...?
- Away from what?
- I don't know.
He won't tell me.
He won't tell me yet.
You realize how many banks
there are South of the precinct?
67.
You keep your eye on the queen.
You learn this, you'll be in good stead.
Pay attention.
Are you watching at all?
That's the best you can do?
It's not the best you can do.
What, are you being a wise guy?
Okay, guys,
it's three-card Monte, see?
We got to find the red queen.
We got too many cards in play.
- There's still the third phone.
- That's for you and Eliot.
You're gonna find the guy,
get his story.
Sophie, downstairs, that equipment
in the back is used for the job.
Go get a look.
I'll take Parker.
What you gonna do?
I'm gonna go get my father
to trust me enough
to tell me the whole plan.
I'm gonna go help him plan
a bank robbery.
That's George Pimsleur.
Works at Hancock alarm security,
And in that briefcase is a binder,
with all the schematics and codes
of all the alarm systems
they installed,
Including the alarm system
on our real target.
Which is what?
My boys kick his teeth in,
they take his wallet,
his briefcase, watch, maybe...
And over in five minutes.
Well, we could.
Or we could take what we want,
and the mark never knows he's been hit.
- How many men?
- Two. You and me.
What are we doing?
You got to limp.
- Which leg?
- Your left leg.
We're gonna do the pill scam.
There you go.
Excuse me, sir?
I'm sorry to bother you.
Do you have change for a $20?
The machine's broke over here.
I got to get my car out.
Got to get my dad to dialysis.
- Sure. Hang on.
- Thank you so much.
Those are so expensive.
I appreciate your...
My mom's got heart trouble.
These damn pills cost a fortune, I know.
There's one over there, too.
I sure appreciate that.
You all right there, dad?
- Yeah, feel just fine.
- We're almost...
Your mother...
Would be very proud of you.
No problem, sir.
- You both take care now.
- Nice of the guy.
- That's not bad.
- Thank you.
- It worked out, didn't it?
- My little boy.
Hardison got background on Pieter.
Ex-soviet army,
three counts armed robbery.
I want the good stuff.
Give it to me.
He's from Lipetsk.
That is close to Penza.
And his mother's name is Rada.
So what are we thinking?
The Berlin shuffle?
- Little orphan Annie.
- Excuse me.
- Need this?
- Thanks, Parker.
- You cannot come in here!
- Sorry.
You're Russian?
That was something
my father used to say. Is it bad?
No, it's not so bad.
Your parents are Russian?
Yeah, from...
Penzo?
Penza!
I'm from Lipetsk.
- What is your name?
- Rada.
This is my mother's name... Rada.
Shut up!
I wish I did speak some Russian.
My mom and dad died
when I was just a kid,
she didn't want me speaking it, so...
And for you to say "my name's Rada,"
Menya zovut rada.
No, you got to go slower.
Mañana... no!
That's Spanish!
Next red phone is right ahead.
We just got to figure out who has it.
- How you doing?
- What are you doing back here?
I think you are holding a gun
that was tagged in a case we caught.
Let me get you one here.
This is the best coffee.
You want to get in there before
the shift changes. 'cause that evidence.
That ships out to Holyoke
first thing tomorrow.
- This a drive you do not want to make.
- I don't want to make that drive.
Thank you so much.
Good to see you.
Thank you so much for this.
You sure that's the same red phone?
Is it me or does this make less sense
every time we find something out?
Pretty much.
It sure is.
You were supposed to call us!
To hit the alarm man.
Well, Nathan here... He took care of it
with a little soft touch.
- You can go.
- I'm not going anywhere.
He says I'm in, I'm in.
I am so sick
of this idea about you...
Stop waving that gun in my face.
You're so tough, prove it.
Go on in there.
Come on. I got your back.
Thanks, dad.
We don't have to do this.
It's all right.
"Stop waving a gun in my face
and prove it."
I had to have it out with the guy.
I'd rather he punch me in the face
than shoot me in the back.
No.
You really went at it back there.
What was it you used say to me?
"You're too much of a thinker, Nathan.
You need to be more
of a scrapper to survive."
Well, I'm never wrong.
That, too, you used to always say.
I gotta tell you,
I doubted your intentions
when you came to join this lot.
Join this lot? No.
Joining you.
You.
These guys,
they're a dime a dozen, pop.
But that dime a dozen are getting
tougher every year, ain't it?
What do you hope to get out
of this plan you're cooking up?
Without giving you any particulars,
I plan to make
a small fortune out of this.
Wait. So one last job?
If there's enough money in it, yeah.
- And then?
- Get on a boat.
Go back to where
your grandfather came from.
Used to got some pretty cousins
back there.
All right, so...
This big last score,
and the great Jimmy Ford, what,
goes to Ireland to retire?
That's quite a picture.
You ever wish ma was joining you?
She didn't really understand me.
But she loved me.
That's more important.
You were up late.
I was out trying to get information
from my dad.
Good. So you know
what bank he's gonna hit, then.
- Today's the day.
- I know.
This would be really hard on anyone.
You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do.
I'm the only one who can.
All right, dear old dad,
you're now gonna tell me everything,
because I...
All right, go on in there.
I got your back.
Thanks, dad.
There you go.
Nate, what's the deal?
He cleared out. They're on the job,
and we have no idea what the job is.
- We got the two guys...
- We have no idea what he's doing.
Look what I found in the alley.
Great.
A map that we've seen before.
This is not her fault. You're the one
who let your dad walk out of here.
- We got our room back.
- Nate, the plans you got
were from the Hancock alarm company.
We just need Hardison
to figure out How many banks
in this radius have got Hancock alarms.
23.
Assuming it is a bank.
I don't know what you would be doing
with one of these in a bank.
It's the same one that Parker saw
in Pieter's bag. A bar-code scanner.
It scans a bar-code label
and compares it to a remote database.
But what are they doing with it?
We still got the coffee guy in play.
What's he up to?
It's a lot of cops, man.
Maybe he's drugging them.
- Slows down response time.
- That's a good idea.
You think he'd drug
the whole precinct? Come on!
You're not paying attention.
Pay attention.
Are you watching at all?
We got the lady here.
Which one?
We got to start all over again?
Pay attention.
Think about it.
You're never gonna get this, are you?
You're just never gonna get it.
These are not queens! You understand me?
Don't get me pissed off!
Does it look like there's a queen
in there?
You're never gonna get this, are you?
You can't figure that out for yourself?
I want an answer.
I know where he's going.
What's the trick to three-card Monte?
The queen's never even on the table.
It's not a bank.
Hardison,
where do the police keep evidence,
the really valuable stuff?
that ships out to Holyoke
first thing tomorrow.
In the district,
then they transfer it out.
Russians.
The Russians.
Remember that big bust last month?
They lost $20 million in merchandise
to the police.
That's gotta hurt.
They got to get drugs, guns,
and $20 million.
It's on the move.
Today.
That's correct.
Ready to get out of here, boys?
- Come on, guys. Let's go.
- All right.
We got a silent alarm call
at First Boston Independent.
We got another alarm call.
This one is at Boston bank at state.
We got a third one!
It's Commonwealth.
Dispatch,
this is district nine duty.
We have got multiple code ones
at the following sites...
- Get some backup to the cruisers.
- Who do I bring?
- Get everybody out there!
- Come on, let's go!
I need every available unit rolling now.
First Boston,
Boston bank state street,
Commonwealth Loan and securities.
- You okay?
- I can't seem to keep my eyes open.
I can't get any confirmation.
I told you, Boston bank,
First Boston independent,
and Commonwealth.
- Evidence transfer?
- Yeah, you're good.
I just need bodies out there.
Get the 2nd, the 4th,
the 10th districts over there.
If they wake up...
Kill them.
You know the plan.
Run and hack at the same time...
sure.
Wait a second.
Let's go over this, all right? Stop.
Why don't you tell
the cops everything?
- The Russians could start shooting.
- There's enough cops to handle.
We stick to the plan,
the Russians will go down.
And your father.
I've got him. I want to look him
in the eye when I put him down.
- You're expecting us.
- Where's your transfer order?
- That's it.
- Let me see that.
All right.
Start your timer.
Five-minute grace,
then the system resets.
All the evidence is bar-coded.
You'll find your stuff
in here someplace...
All your guns, all your drugs.
Okay, it's good.
Look at that! That's him!
He's the one!
My name is I'm Jimmy Popodokolos,
and I represent miss Dagostino here.
We're a little busy. Every cop
is hitting the streets right now.
I am gonna Sue you...
- And I am gonna sue the city.
- Here's the thing,
We need to do is I want to see
the department's legal counsel now.
Fine. Just wait over there.
I'll have somebody escort you.
You better listen to him, wise guy.
Artie Van's Ledger.
It's gonna end right here, dad.
You ready?
How'd you know?
You'd never take the money and run.
$5 million's a lot of money, Nathan.
For you, it's never about the money.
I knew that growing up,
watching you.
It was about respect for you.
- Artie van's ledger.
- Yeah, they made copies.
You know that won't hold up.
The original disappears,
the case against
the big families goes away,
and who do they owe?
Jimmy Ford,
the biggest fixer in town.
Let's join up.
Together, we can run this town.
It's too late.
- What do you mean?
- My people are gonna take down
the Russians, and any minute now,
the cops are gonna come.
I'm not going back to prison.
All right.
Right here.
You can't do this.
I could, but...
You're your mother's son.
Go.
Get out.
Open up!
Move, move!
Napkins?
This cannot be right! Time!
Is this the right time? I keep scanning.
More boxes! More boxes!
You let him go.
I had to.
I know.
It's not time!
Stupid thing!
Age of the gig, baby.
Stay strong.
- Don't move!
- Hands in the air!
Look at this.
You guys did everything
but cuff yourselves.
Help 'em out, boys.
Aidan McTeague.
Yeah, this is Jimmy Ford.
Damn straight.
Say, I got some good news for you.
Yeah, I got the ledger right here.
What's that?
What would you want to do that for?
Jimmy Ford for Bridgette O'Hare.
It's a gift.
Ronin Donnelly, I worked for your father
for 30 years. I wouldn't...
Mr. Donnelly, it's not true.
Geez.
Nathan, what the hell have you done?
Yeah, I called each of the families.
I told them that you were the one
who stole the evidence against them.
They were grateful.
Until I laid out the deal.
He wants $500,000 to destroy it.
Otherwise,
it goes right back to the evidence room.
Not a Penny less, Mr. Mcteague.
You blackmailed them?
You blackmailed them.
- They almost killed me.
- Of course they did.
You've got a price on your head
bigger than most of my team's scores.
- Who wouldn't want that kind of scratch?
- You want me killed, then?
See that boat behind you?
You're running me out of town?
My own son?
Cheap passage booked
under "Jimmy Logue".
You'll be in Galway in two weeks.
Logue.
Your mother's maiden name.
How sweet of you.
You better hurry up.
A man with no suitcase
is likely to look suspicious,
so try to act natural.
You betrayed your own father.
You're more ruthless than me.
Crueler than me.
Maybe you are better than me.
I'm proud of you, son.
Enjoy your retirement.
That was...
Kind, what you did.
So, is Nate gonna be nice now?
Don't count on it.