Somebody, please, help!
Hey! Open the door! Please!
- She can't breathe!
- Can't you see the sign, pal?
CLINIC PERMANANTLY CLOSED
- Over here!
- Hey! Unlock the damn door!
- Asthma?
- Yeah, her inhaler's not working.
- Get out of my way. Call for an ambulance.
- What do I do?
Set her on the ground, but keep her upright.
This inhaler's gonna relax her muscles...
Okay.
...while the epinephrine
opens the airway.
There you go.
- Oh, thank God. Thank you.
- Yeah.
She could've died.
I mean, she would've died.
Well, she- she was very lucky
you were there.
No, luck shouldn't have
anything to do with it.
You know, the clinic
never should have closed.
- And it's all my fault.
- Hey, it's- it's not your fault.
There's no way
you could've seen this coming.
No, I was the one that recommended
Mr. Fowler to our board of directors.
You know, he told me that the fund
would double our clinic's money in a year.
- I believed him.
- It's okay.
We all do stupid things sometimes.
No, uh, she...
Um-- How did you meet Daniel Fowler?
I only volunteer at the clinic on weekends.
My day job is at Dalton Academy.
It's that private school up near Brighton.
And I'm the on-site nurse there.
And Fowler's stepson is a student there.
He's a sweet kid. Allergic to strawberries.
That's ironic.
- Why?
- Because he's sweet.
Yeah, uh...
A lot of the parents had money
invested with him. And I figured...
you know, if they could trust him,
then we could, too.
Okay, well, here's the thing.
The government has frozen Fowler's assets.
- So you'll get the money back eventually.
- No, the clinic is out of time.
The board has put the property
up for sale next week.
That's not gonna happen.
I promise.
Sorry. Um...
It's just really hard to trust
people right now, you know?
That's okay. We don't
trust you either. So...
No, she didn't...
Thank you for your time.
That went super.
Oh, God...
Where is Sophie?
The rich and powerful,
they take what they want.
We steal it back for you.
-= www.subcentral.de presents =-
-= Leverage - The Fairy Godparents Job =-
And sometimes, bad guys
make the best good guys.
We provide...
Leverage.
Thanks for meeting me this morning.
Sweetheart, listen-- I know you're crazy busy.
It's final-exam time and everything...
but I was thinking this weekend
we should definitely...
- definitely check out the venetian exhibit--
- I don't think so.
I don't think that
this is working out.
Wait.
Listen, I know that...
You know, I travel a lot with...
my job.
It's not that. Um, listen...
We talk all the time...
but it never feels like you're
actually sharing anything.
As great as you are...
there's always a mask.
I just don't know
who you really are, Catherine.
I got a class.
Sophie.
Pardon?
Or Alice...
Karen, Michelle...
Elizabeth...
Hey. This looks like
an ordinary cellphone, right?
It's not, man.
It's a metal detector.
See, it uses
pulse-induction technology...
that sends out a current
that generates a magnetic field...
and then--
Are you even listening?
- Yeah.
- Well, what did I say?
You were explaining
how you're still a virgin.
...isn't a kind of skill. Talking to clients.
You're supposed to sympathize.
I told you not to take her.
- Well, you were right. Where's Sophie?
- I don't know.
Well, we're not waiting.
Let's go. Let's start.
Daniel Fowler, 61,
C.E.O. of FTP Fidelity.
Now, this is the largest private-investment firm
in the state-- Up until about three weeks ago.
This whole thing was blown as a big Ponzi scheme.
And I'm not talking crooked investments.
I mean stone-cold con.
There was never any fund,
no trades, no real accounts.
The clinic lost everything.
10 years, this guy wore all the right suits
and filed all the right papers...
with the S.E.C. Nobody looked twice.
Well, as soon as the FBI figured it out,
they slapped a little house arrest on him...
and they froze all his assets--
I'm talking corporate accounts...
personal accounts,
real-estate holdings.
Anything on planet earth
with this dude's name on it is on ice.
- The FBI's very thorough, huh?
- Extremely.
- So what'd they miss?
- Oh.
$20 million. They moved it off the books
right before the warrants came down.
Yeah, well, he knew the end was near,
and he was getting ready to bolt.
Tell me something--
Where was Fowler arrested?
In his apartment, packing for his
"business trip" to the Maldives.
You see, he'd need it light,
portable, close at hand.
That $20 million is in his apartment.
Yeah, but this guy's on house arrest, man.
I mean, he's practically living with the FBI.
The problem is not getting into
the apartment, but getting them out.
Where were you?
Oh. I- I was running an errand.
Weren't you with the boyfriend?
So, um, what are the terms
of his house arrest?
Fowler's confined to his $6 million
penthouse overlooking the Charles River.
Yeah, that's a rough punishment, huh?
The whole place is outfitted with 24/7
surveillance so the feds can keep an eye on him.
Now...
We can, too.
I piggybacked on their wireless feed.
Still, for us to get in and search the place,
we've got to get rid of Fowler.
Now, there are three general
exceptions for house arrest.
There's personal safety,
death of a relative, and family events.
Personal safety.
We could burn the apartment down.
- Ooh! Ooh!
- Or...
death of a relative.
Uh, w- who's that?
Oh. Oh, the kid.
Kid's from her first marriage.
Widmark.
Oh, I'm sorry.
"Widmark"?
- Rich people, man.
- Geez...
Oh, can you, uh,
punch in on that, please?
Do you have any respect
for your personal property?
Do you have any respect for me?
I bought you that cellphone.
Dan.
He said he was sorry.
Yeah.
He's sorry, all right.
I'd ground you, but you don't have
any friends to go out with anyway.
I'm gonna talk to him.
I'll be right back.
Wow. Okay.
What do we got on the kid?
Widmark Fowler, age 10.
No arrests. No outstanding warrants.
Hardison...
He's a fifth-grade student
at Dalton Academy.
Academically unexceptional.
No extracurriculars.
He's allergic to strawberries.
Strawberries...
Judges give out day passes
for family events.
It's one of the three things, right?
So Fowler...
is going to ask for one
so he doesn't miss his kid's big debut.
Okay, I'll bite.
What's he debuting as?
Yeah, I don't know. But we're gonna
go steal his school and find out.
- A mister Ando Buhari is here.
- I don't have any appointments.
- I know. Do you want--
- Oh, Dr. Jerrod.
Dr. Jerrod, come.
It's-- ahhh.
It's a pleasure.
I am Anando Buhari,
Botswana special envoy.
I work for president Khama.
He is most impressed when he read
your paper you wrote as a student.
How do you say, your, um...
- The--
- That-- These--
The president of Botswana
read my grad-school thesis?
Yes!
All 600 glorious pages...
from which insight drips like honey
upon which bees of wisdom feast.
The president is rebuilding
the educational system from the ground up.
Would you consider
going to Botswana to meet him?
All expenses paid, of course.
I...
Yes.
Everyone, settle down!
I assure you everything is under control!
Mr. Jerrod just took a leave of absence.
In the middle of the school year?
The school board has already
sent over an interim headmaster.
Would you be quiet?!
And after reading his file...
I can assure you
we are in excellent hands!
Dr. Melcher?
Guten Tag.
My name is Dr. Melcher.
And I presume
that you are all familiar...
with the pre-eminent literature
on the children's education--
My book,
"The Melcher Method"--
Ja?
In which case any further
introduction would be redundant.
I'd like to begin
by speaking about the changes
we're going to be making
in the curriculum.
Excuse me.
- Shh! Shh! Shh!
- Ja, ja?
Mark Sanford. I'm head of the
concerned parents association.
That must be very exciting for you.
Yes, I'm sure. Why do we need
any changes at all?
I mean, this is the best
private school in Boston.
- Ja, ja.
- Let him talk!
The Melcher method involves
the education of the whole child--
Mind and body.
Ja, when a child fails,
is it just the brain that fails?
Nein. No, the body contains
the failing brain...
and both are cast into a cruel
world of darkness and despair...
and even worse--
Public school.
- Oh, oh, right.
- Public school?
Dante's inferno of mediocrity.
Which is why I bring with me
two of my most valued associates.
We have mind and body.
Ja. Ja.
Miss Donovan
will hone your children's minds.
And Mr. Brewer, he will craft
your children's bodies...
into the proper mind-vessels
through exercise and nutrition.
And any questions?
Open floor plan.
3,200 square feet.
Uh, panoramic views of the park
and the Charles.
Uh, there's a fitness center,
a rooftop pool...
uh, concierge service.
It's the perfect newlywed apartment.
Oh, it's-- the place,
it's fantastical.
- What do you think, Binky?
- It's a little small.
The- the apartment, Binky.
What do you think of the apartment?
We'll take it.
She-- She loves air.
Hardison and Parker are all set.
Now all we got to do is, uh...
give Widmark a triumph
worthy of a day pass.
A triumph?
In what?
I mean, in five years, this kid hasn't joined
a club, he hasn't played a sport.
I've got to be honest with you. I don't know
how I feel about using a kid to get to a Mark.
We're not using him. I mean,
every kid is good at something.
You know, we just got to draw Widmark out.
Give him his moment to shine.
Oh, so, we'd be like
his fairy godparents.
Exactly. And, I mean, come on.
Look at this. Cushy private school.
No gunrunners, mob bosses, Interpol.
This is a breeze.
We've got one week before
the clinic closes for good.
Athletics. Academics. Let's go get
Widmark the win. All right?
All right, Widmark.
Get on the line. You're up.
Yeah, you're up. Get on the line.
Show them what you got, man.
I got this...
Hey. You.
Take your helmet off.
- What's your name?
- Skyler Sanford.
- Sky... Skyler?
- Yeah.
Is that a boy's name?
Don't do that again.
Put your hat on.
You're up against Wid--
I said get out there, man.
Get out here.
All right.
What are you doing, man?
What are you doing?
Don't laugh!
There's girls here.
You're better than that.
Turn your hat around.
All right.
Here we go.
En garde.
Fence!
Next week is the state spelling bee,
and we're going to be sending...
a representative
from right here in Dalton.
Now, I've chosen the best spellers
from every class to compete in the tryouts.
The winners will compete in
a school-wide competition next Friday.
Your parents are gonna be there--
It is gonna be huge. Let's get started!
Widmark-- food.
Food.
F-O-O-D.
Pseudosyllogism.
- That's not fair. He got "food"!
- Uh-uh-uh. Skyler...
I can assure you that the order
of these cards is entirely random.
Pseudosyllogism.
Um...
Pseudosyllogism. S-
Whatever.
Chylocaulous.
C-H-Y-L-O...
C-A-U-L-O-U-S.
Chylocaulous.
That's impressive.
Sunset.
- S-U-N...
- Ribonucleic.
Ribonucleic.
R-I-B-O-N-U-C-L...
- E-I-C.
- Wildfire.
W-I-L...
- D...
- Flibbertigibbet.
F-L-I-B-B-E-R...
T-I-G-I-B-B-E-T.
- Bicycle.
- B-I...
S-I...
C-L-E.
Bicycle?
- Antidisestablishmentarianism.
- A-N-T-I...
D-I-S-E-S-T-A-B-L-I-S-H...
M-E-N-T-A-R-I-A-N-I-S-M.
Antidisestablishmentarianism.
Congratulations, Ms. Kim.
Class dismissed.
Hey, Widmark.
Good job.
- I just got lucky with the words you gave me.
- Mnh-mnh. Be proud of yourself.
The important thing is you tried.
I try hard.
All the time, but...
no matter how much I want
something, it never happens.
Oh, sweetie.
What-- what do you want?
I don't know.
I just...
I want someone to like me.
Does that get easier
when you're a grown-up?
Um... no.
I don't think it does.
You're nice.
But weird.
All right, go on.
You're late for class.
Stop moving!
Look-- it don't have to be exact.
Woman, it's a motion detector.
Just point it that way.
Watch out...
What the hell do you guys want?
Well, we're having a problem
with the signal from camera two again.
Hey! FBI!
Drop the gun!
Special Agent Hagen?
It's me. McSweeten.
Todd, from the Moscone
mob case last year?
Oh.
Yeah!
- I lost--
- You dropped this.
Yeah.
I- I didn't even realize.
Yes, I dropped it.
- Agent Thomas, good to see you again.
- Right back at you. Um...
- Taggert from the Moscone case.
- R- right.
Right. Right. So, uh,
what you all been up to?
Well, actually, we've had
a pretty good run of it lately.
- Closed some big cases.
- Big.
- Moscone, for one.
- Moscone, no more-ne.
We also shut down
a huge meth ring in California...
during a bank robbery.
What are you guys doing here?
I mean, we--
We're undercover, man.
Yeah, yeah. More manpower
on the Fowler case.
- Oh, well, we never have been notified--
- They never said anything about--
We're your secret backup.
- Well... that's great!
- Hey! That's good.
Shh! Secret!
So, me and you--
You, I-- us--
We should resume surveillance.
Fellas.
Can you imagine having
her for a partner?
What?
- You want to see other partners?
- I didn't say that.
- Yeah. Fine. Whatever.
- That's not what I meant!
Let me just g- get this straight,
okay. All right, you two--
You couldn't rig a gym class
or a spelling bee?
And you two-- you run into the only FBI
agents on the planet that recognize you?
I got to be honest with you.
I think we broke the kid even more.
We are the worst
fairy godparents in the world.
Uh, listen, we still got to get Fowler
out of the apartment so we can get in.
Yeah, except now when he leaves,
there will be somebody waiting to kill him.
One of his victims wants payback
more than he wants to be paid...
Back.
One of you two can identify
the gunman, right?
Oh, yeah, sure. He stopped and let me take
a picture of him as I was chasing him.
Hey, you know what, man? I've been around little
kids all day. I don't need to come home...
- and do all this crap.
- Hey, man, with all that?
I've been in this pink shirt and these
tight plaid pants, these old webster loafers...
This girl is walking on my back.
I don't need this, man.
Is this the guy?
See?
Wow. I didn't know you could do that.
I thought everybody could do that.
Okay. All right, all right.
We'll keep an eye on him.
In the meantime, if they think
you're real FBI, be real FBI.
I mean, use it to case the apartment.
All right, so I'm out of this, and I'm
on FBI detail with Parker and Hardison.
Actually, no.
I need you to be coach Brewer, so...
There's an armed gunman out there. You want me
in the gym with kids named Skyler and Indigo?
Where did coach Brewer go?
- I mean we are... there
- Shh! Shut up! Shut up!
"The play is the thing where in
I'll catch the conscience of a king."
* ...times I'm up *
* Sometimes I'm down *
* Ohh, Lord *
* Sometimes I'm almost to the ground *
Sophie, how long would it take
you to stage a musical?
Six weeks.
You have two days.
* There can be no confusion
that fusion powers the star *
D- did...
- Did you just make that up on the spot?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Huh. You really are quite relentless.
- Thank you, ma'am.
M- Miss Donovan?
Why are we singing
at a science fair?
Ah. Good point, yes.
Science. Knowledge.
What is knowledge
without emotional context?
- Facts.
- Uh-uh. Empty. Meaningless.
We're taking left brain--
Science--
And combing it with right brain--
creativity--
To engage the audience's entire brain.
Now, just- just present your projects,
and we'll just set it to a little melody.
Who's next?
* I can make a battery out of a potato *
Thank you.
- But I can turn on a light bulb.
- Mnh-mnh. That won't be necessary.
Mr. Fowler?
* You might find this distasteful *
* Or call it just plain gross *
* To sing in praise
of bread mold or wonder *
* How it grows *
* It even makes you crazy *
* That mold devours your food *
I don't know what to say, Widmark.
- I- I'm sorry.
- No, no, no. That was...
That was--
Yes, that was impressive.
It was-- It was understated.
It was-- It was potentially wonderful.
Yes!
You, Widmark, are gonna sing
in the grand finale.
Security system installed,
5- camera set-up.
Two in the living room,
entryway, hallway, kitchen.
Could I take a look at your logs
for Fowler's phone calls?
I- I mean, if I put in a request
to home office-- It takes forever.
Pencil pushers don't understand
what it's like for us out in the field...
- face-to-face with crime.
- Yeah, nose-to-nose with evil.
I can hear that.
The files are in here.
- Who the hell are you?
- FBI.
There are cameras everywhere.
You people don't need to be in here.
Out of every kid in the entire school,
she picks him for the showcase performance?
- D- does she even know who he is?
- A student who--
Whose father ripped off
everyone in this school.
I'm a money manager. I put millions
of my client's accounts with him.
We lost everything. And there isn't a parent
in this school who doesn't have the same story.
Ja, it's not our philosophy
to punish the kinder...
for the sins of their parents,
Mr. Sanford.
And Ms. Donovan, she assures me
that Widmark's starring role in the, uh...
The science-sical.
Ja, science-sical--
Is, uh, based solely on merit.
Now, if you excuse me, I have
a lot of work to do, please.
Good afternoon.
Nice to see you again.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
Goodbye, goodbye.
Could you just please try to
maybe not make this so difficult?
I can't take you seriously
with that dead cat on your head.
Eliot had trouble adjusting, all right?
But he found a way to make his style
work in this setting, so...
Hai! Pain! Honor! Strength!
All right.
Come at me!
It was the best I could manage
under such short notice.
The props are made, the kids have
memorized their presentations.
- I'm just setting it to a bit of music.
- Listen. We-- I mean...
let's not forget why we're here.
Let's not lose focus.
I mean, the object is to get Fowler
out of the apartment, not--
What? Not-- not Widmark.
Right, yeah, I get it.
- He's just the bait.
- Come on. That's not fair.
What's not fair is the way people see him.
His father sees him as a loser...
his mother sees him
as this fragile little baby...
his schoolmates see him as the boy
whose father stole Christmas.
I just think he--
He-- he...
Ohh.
I just want people to see him
as he really is.
He deserves that.
Everybody does.
This is why we can't have nice things.
Rich guys and their crazy
security systems.
Door alarm's got a Takashita 500
with redundant infrared.
- Window's easier.
- The window?
- The window that's 20 stories up?
- Like I said-- easier.
I've done this a million times. All I need
is a pneumatic drill, some diamond bits--
Go, go, go.
Hey.
- Oh, uh, thanks.
- What's up?
Oh, that one's actually mine.
Uh, I just had my lips on that.
If.. uh...
It's like I gave you
a little coffee kiss.
I think your partner is sweet
on McSweeten.
- What? No.
- I dont really talk about this kind of stuff.
No? Well anyway.
Uh, the judge approved
Fowler's day pass...
so he can go see some play
his kid is doing at school.
Final-freaking-ly, man!
I- I love the theater.
It's-- "Cats".
R- reow!
All right, well, see you downstairs
in a couple of minutes.
- Um, what?
- You're our backup.
- You're coming along with, right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- You got our back, right?
- We, we, we-- Jo, yeah.
- We got your back.
- Okay. Good.
Nate, we got a problem...
- Straight in that way.
- Well, so do we.
It's final rehearsal, and so far
Widmark hasn't sung a note.
* You *
- Shh!
- Hey!
The camera's charged, right?
I don't want to miss a second.
Sir, I'm gonna have to check that bag.
Oh, uh, hey, guys,
can we get a minute?
Look, uh, quick update.
One of us is gonna have to stay upstairs
with the surveillance equipment.
Lucky me.
Okay.
Well, we only really need
two agents on Fowler...
so why don't we switch up?
Yeah. Yeah, that's a good idea.
You know, I could just...
- stay here with Agent Hagen.
- Yeah.
Uh...
You know what?
Hagen, you go with the guys.
More manpower for the suspect.
I'll babysit the equipment.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Look, Agent McSweetheart
is gonna go wherever you go...
so you got to go to the school,
and I'm just...
just talk me through the break-in.
Talk me-- just...
After you.
All that personal space.
Good luck.
Uh, Sophie, are we good to go?
Uh, uh...
No, everything's gonna be fine
as soon as I...
find Widmark.
Hardison, what is going on?
What's your status?
I just looped the FBI video feed, so...
nobody will see me in the apartment.
Assuming I get in the apartment.
Please take a seat now.
Hurry, hurry along.
All right, our man has arrived.
The curtain goes up in five minutes--
One way or the other.
Don't wait for Sophie.
Widmark?
Please take a seat now.
Hurry, hurry along.
Take your seat.
You sure you can handle this?
Oh, yeah. What's the worst
that can happen?
- Well, you could tangle the lines--
- Hey!
Can you believe they have
a smoothie shop in this place?
- What were you saying?
- Oh...
I was just worried about the play,
and the actors, they cross their lines...
they could really fall on their face.
I'm good! I'm good!
Widmark.
Y- you-- you can't let them win.
Y- you can't show them
that they're getting to you.
Sophie, no. No.
- What?
- Just- just talk to him.
Don't tell him what to do
or who to be. Just talk.
Widmark, I'm sorry.
For what?
For trying to con you
into being brave, and...
that's what I do.
I'm a bloody con artist.
Look, I'm not very good at being honest.
Not even with my friends.
- Do you have a lot of friends?
- No.
No, I--
I never used to have any.
But, um,
now, yes, I- I do.
A few.
I used to have friends.
They don't talk to me anymore.
Because of what my stepdad did.
That's got nothing to do with you.
You know that, don't you?
- Then why did they make fun of me?
- Because when they look at you, they see him.
They're not seeing you
for who you really are.
How much time do I have left, Parker?
Do you believe in love at first sight?
I believe that when you meet someone,
you have 30 seconds...
before the bells and whistles go off.
Don't be afraid to override
your feelings.
Don't be blue.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Okay. I got you.
On 30 seconds,
"Don't be blue", override--
Wait, uh-- does that mean
cut the blue wire
or don't cut the blue wire, Parker?
That is-- That is so true.
I think you need to be honest--
20 seconds.
It took-- I can't count in 20 seconds
how many blue wires there are.
- Parker, help me out.
- Not following.
You just have to cut loose.
Output your feelings.
- Snip that blue mood--
- The out-- output?
Output? Okay, I got it.
Gotcha.
Come here, you blue.
Got it.
Daddy's home.
- Did you know I was an actress?
- No.
Are you good?
Well, others don't seem to think so.
Maybe they just can't see you
for who you are.
Do you know what they say about acting?
They say it's about telling the truth, about--
about sharing a little part of yourself
that people don't normally see.
But if you don't-- if you don't
really know yourself...
then they think you're lying.
And...
I think that's my problem.
I've been lying for so long,
that, um...
I don't even know
what the truth is anymore.
I don't want to lie to anybody.
No.
No, you don't have to, Widmark.
What you need to do is you just
have to go out there and be Widmark.
Just tell the truth.
Be-- be who you really are.
If you can do that,
then I promise you...
people will believe in you.
Sure is taking them a long time
to get everybody in there.
Yes, a lot longer than I thought.
Excuse me for interrupting prom night
with my annoying felony burglary.
She's ungrateful.
Just ungrateful.
Aha!
Come to pa.
- Widmark okay?
- Guess we're about to find out.
Yeah!
Hacking, rappelling--
Whatever, put me in a dress.
I can do all y'all's jobs.
- It's empty.
- What do you mean it's empty?
I mean it's empty,
like somebody cleaned it out.
I hate to tell you this, but that ain't
our biggest problem right now.
We've got company.
* There are many types of clouds *
* Like stratus, cumulus, and nimbus *
* Nimbus said to a glum-looking cloud *
* Please don't be so cirrus *
* Clouds are high up in the sky *
Yeah, but how'd he know
Fowler was gonna be here?
Only ones that knew
were us and the FBI.
Uh, yeah, and Fowler himself.
Maybe we were wrong.
- Maybe Fowler isn't the target.
- Then who?
- What?
- Thank you.
- For this delicious smoothie, Agent.
- Oh.
Um...
His FBI handlers.
Fowler's arranged to have them killed.
- He's about to run.
- No, there's no way...
he could arrange that, man.
He's under house arrest--
No phone calls, no internet.
They're even reading his mail.
- How could he arrange a hit man?
- Let's ask him.
- What do you mean you lost it?
- I thought it was in my room.
You thought? Do you have any respect
for your personal property?
Do you have any respect for me?
I bought you that cellphone.
Feds confiscated his cellphone.
They didn't take Widmark's.
* You will see in the... *
Fowler's getaway explains the empty safe.
Whatever cash he had on him...
he took with him.
And, uh...
I think I know where to look.
Wait. Didn't you search
Fowler before he left?
Of course. Nothing on him except
for that camera and some tapes.
Yeah, well,
there's something in that bag.
Where are those tapes?
Thank you...
- Sophie, can you swipe it?
- Mm-hmm. Yes, I'm a little bit busy here.
...Juilliard, for that
wonderful rendition...
of "How Clouds Are Formed".
And now we have Milan
with a ballad about photosynthesis.
Enjoy.
- Has anybody seen Widmark?
- Sophie, the job's over.
What happens from here on is not
our concern. We have other priorities.
No way. No, no. The- the clinic
isn't the only victim here, Nate.
No, I- I didn't prop up this boy
just to see him fail. No way.
I'm not letting that happen.
Yo, what's up?
Uh, Nate--
This phone has sent a bunch of
text messages in the last 48 hours...
to some guy named "Skyler".
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Skyler's a kid at the school.
Why would Fowler be texting
a middle-schooler?
* Photosynthesis is the cause *
* Of this process
that makes things bigger *
He wasn't texting Skyler.
He was texting Skyler's dad.
Uh... sorry.
Mark Sanford's an accomplice.
He set up the gunman.
He just traded bags with Fowler.
No, man, why would Sanford help Fowler?
Isn't he one of the guys who invested with him?
* Really a gas *
- Sorry I'm late.
- No, no, no.
You're right on time.
And now with
"Growth Factors In Bread Mold"...
it's Widmark Fowler!
* You might find this distasteful *
* Or call it just plain gross *
* To sing in praise of bread mold *
* Or wonder how it grows *
* It even makes you crazy *
* That mold devours your food *
* Until you find I've changed your mind *
* And you see that mold is good *
Shh!
* It's the mushrooms on your pizza *
* It's the yeast
that makes your crust rise *
Well, keep it off the stage!
You're gonna ruin his big finale.
* ...this fun guy *
* That get eaten--
Don't look surprised *
* And while we're on the subject
Who among us *
* Would want the nasty job
that fungus has *
* Scarfing down toxic waste *
* Molds go where they're needed *
* So they find our stuff to feed in *
* Molds just want to grow *
* So they pop out spores, you know *
* That a mold wants to thrive *
* Needs much more than to survive *
* Because mold's like us *
* Just loving our li-fe *
He is competitive.
Uh, Hardison,
are you at your computer?
I need you to check a name for me.
Go ahead.
Doug Fineman.
And first place goes to
Mr. Widmark Fowler!
Sanford is providing Fowler
with a new identity...
and a new life waiting for him in...
Bogot.
Oh! Coach Brewer!
- Shut up!
- I'll take that.
Yes.
I'm just saying you can't make
the returns too consistent.
10% growth every year,
no matter what the market does?
- The S.E.C. Is going to ask questions.
- Let me worry about the S.E.C., Mark.
But we have to be careful.
My job is to buy off the regulators.
Your job is to bring in new money.
Now, this whole thing goes off
the rails when you stop doing your job.
Where the heck
do you think you're going?
Ja, ja, he, um,
he dropped this.
What is this?
I thought his name was Fowler.
- I don't know.
- Thanks.
- Ja, ja.
- Come on!
No! Stop it!
You can't play that!
Now, that...
Is no way to treat a lady.
Come on.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Got something for you.
Wow, that is far more than we lost.
Well, you know the $20 million
the feds couldn't find?
Fowler had it in an overseas account
using one of his aliases.
Yeah, he struck a deal with Sanford.
He traded the tapes for a new passport...
- and two dead FBI guys.
- And our friend Hardison--
Well, he liberated some of the cash
so you could use it for your clinic.
Wow.
- Hey, Kay!
- Hi, Claudine.
She, um, needed a job
after Fowler went to jail.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Well, you know, this is interesting.
This must be a- a first.
I mean, it's the only time
I can remember...
that the con depended solely
on you telling the truth.
- How'd it feel?
- Eh, good.
- Don't get used to it.
- Oh, no. No.
I start
telling the truth all day...
I stop being Sophie Devereaux.
Maybe that's, uh...
A good thing.
-= Timecodes by gius =-
www.tvsubtitles.net