He's telling me something.
I don't know what this means.
What is it?
I'm getting a "B"-sounding name.
Bruce maybe?
Brute?
Oh, my god.
Brutus.
That's our dog.
Whenever we would come home,
Brutus would always run to me first
and Mike would say, "Et tu, Brute?"
We're getting very close now.
Seven months.
Actually, that's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
Do you think...
Could we...
Could you ask Mike
what we should name him?
I don't have to ask him.
Jodie, he hears you.
He always hears you.
His energy's gone.
I've lost the connection.
No, wait. Just ask him...
Perhaps we can try again next week?
He's always with you, you know.
I want you to know that.
Thank you.
Good job on the dog.
She had her photos up on facebook.
It wasn't hard to find.
Her most recent bank statement...
According to this, she's got about 8000$
left in her joint savings account.
Well, it's formerly joint.
So we can squeeze another five sessions
out of her tops, before she balks.
She's still got the house?
She can sell that.
Never leave money
on the table, Wilson.
All right, who's next?
It's been five months
since the accident.
I don't know how to describe it.
It's like she's a zombie.
Everyone grieves in their own way.
But she's not dealing with it, Mr. Ford.
He's not letting her.
She thinks he's channeling Mike and all
guy's doing is taking her for a ride.
He ran a credit check on her.
Who does that?
People who want your money.
I assume you've shown this to her.
I've tried.
She won't listen to me anymore.
It's like she's been brainwashed
or something.
Belief perseverance. People cling
even tighter to their beliefs
after they've been shown
evidence contradicting them.
What am I supposed to do?
This guy's taken every penny
from Mike's life-insurance policy.
And now Jodie's talking about putting
her house up on the market next week.
Her house.
And the baby's due in two months.
- If this keeps up...
- All right, don't worry.
This guy Rand is gonna pay.
We're gonna make sure of that.
I'm not here asking for money,
Mr. Ford.
I just want my sister back.
The rich and powerful,
they take what they want.
We steal it back for you.
And sometimes, bad guys
make the best good guys.
We provide...
leverage!
Welcome to the show.
Okay, go right ahead.
This is where he shoots his show.
Surrounded by warehouses
and storage lockers?
Well, it's local cable access.
He's self-financing...
Probably trying to score
a bigger payday...
network or something, probably.
You're right about that.
I've hacked Rand's website,
stole his passwords,
and accessed his e-mail.
You know, this man has his computer
hooked up to the city's free wi-fi?
My nana could hack this thing.
It looks like there's gonna be
a network scout from wmn
in the audience today.
Sounds like he's trying
to go prime time.
TV show means a control room.
I'll see what I can find.
- Who are you hoping comes through?
- Nothing.
Nobody.
I don't want to talk to anybody.
What's wrong?
I just don't like psychics, okay?
They freak me out.
Okay, just relax.
We're just here to see
what tricks Rand has up his sleeve.
That's all. Just...
Thank you all for coming.
I'd like to just jump right in here,
because I'm feeling an energy.
It's coming from someone over here.
An "M".
I'm Monica.
I'm getting an "L" name
that connects with you.
Lucky. Lucy.
Lucille?
It's maternal energy.
Your grandmother, is that right?
You should know
she's very proud of you.
This is not the bathroom, is it?
What's going on, man?
- You're not authorized to be in here.
- You're like the wizard.
- Sir, you got to go. What is this?
- Like, the guy behind the... All right.
- I said get out.
- All right, man.
Go play with your computer.
I got it wrong. Sorry.
And we're in.
Now we see what they see.
What is that smell?
What smell? I just washed this thing.
You could eat off the floor.
No, there's definitely a smell.
There's someone else
coming through right now.
Is it Fred?
- Or Frank?
- I got a gecko named Frank.
He's still alive, though, yeah.
At least he was this morning
when I left.
Are you trying to tell me
something about...
It's not a gecko.
You shut yourself off to the energies
that are around us.
But your friend here,
she's a little more receptive.
In fact,
I think I'm getting an energy
right now.
It's definitely family.
Is it your father?
No.
No, it's a sibling.
A brother.
You were both very young.
It was an accident.
I see a road.
I see a car.
But your brother's not in the car.
He's in the street.
Wheels.
I see wheels.
A skateboard.
A bicycle.
Was he riding a bicycle
when he was struck?
He's been gone a long time
from you now.
He's sorry that he had to leave you.
He knows...
that you feel responsible.
But he wants you to know
it was an accident.
You taught him to ride that bike,
didn't you?
That's all right.
Sometimes people just aren't ready
to hear what the spirits have to say.
Damn.
He is good.
He should be shot.
There's no way
he could known that stuff.
I've never told anyone.
No one.
Ever.
- Parker, he didn't know anything.
- No, Nate.
You said we'd find a trick
up his sleeve.
You said we'd find a trick.
We didn't find a trick, did we?
He knew things.
He's really psychic.
He's not a psychic, Parker.
He's just a con man.
He just did a cold read on you.
That's all.
He just asked questions and used
your answers to guide him.
- But I didn't say anything.
- You didn't have to.
Can I show you something?
Right there.
Do you remember when he asked you,
"Is this energy that I'm getting does it
have anything to do with your father?"
Do you remember?
Well, you furrowed your eyebrow.
You might as well have told him,
"No."
And then, when he keyed
in on your brother...
Right here...
Your eyes widened just slightly,
so he knew he was on the right track.
And then he just guessed, Parker.
He got a hit when he said
that you were both very young,
and he just went with the odds...
An accident of some kind.
But he knew about the bicycle.
No, he didn't.
'cause what happened was,
he said "wheels."
And then he moved on,
and he said "skateboard."
You told him about the bicycle.
- No, I didn't say anything.
- You had a certain tell, Parker.
Your mouth opened
just a little bit...
Enough for him
to register your surprise.
Then, well, he just guessed.
He used all of these things
during the reading...
How your breathing changed,
if your shoulders were raised
or slouched,
how you were holding your hands,
if your lips were pursed.
But what about the other people?
He knew names and relationships.
Yeah, the hot read.
What he does is
he researches before the show,
gets himself armed with all information
possible to help him with the readings.
It's not really that much
different than what we do.
But he doesn't know who's gonna be
in the audience ahead of time.
Well, no. No, he doesn't.
He doesn't know...
until they're there.
He's got cameras all over the place
hoping to pick up something,
hear something
that's gonna help him in the reading.
He also has a plant.
He's got an assistant
who stands in line and pretends
to be part of the audience.
I can't explain it, but sometimes
it feels like he's still around.
I know what you mean.
My mom died a few months ago.
Heart attack.
I'm just hoping Mr. Rand
can make contact with her,
- Find out if she hears me.
- And that person
feeds him the information
about the readings in his ear
using earbuds just like we do.
First one up is Monica.
She's here to speak
to her grandmother Lucille.
She's sitting on your left.
Your other left.
Guys, there's like...
a dozen hidden cameras
and the bug Eliot planted
in the control room.
I got audio feeds off
of 20 hidden microphones
that were taped to the chairs
in the audience.
I got names, people they wanted
to contact, dates.
And that is what Rand
has hidden up his sleeve.
So, what do we do now?
Cut off his arms.
And his head.
I want to kill him.
Can we make that happen?
I can...
I mean, I could...
Or we could give him
exactly what he wants.
And then make the world think that he's
the greatest psychic that ever lived.
And then, in front of the network
and his audience,
we destroy him.
How do we do that?
We go and steal the future.
Even move to LA if you want.
Mr. Rand, I don't doubt your gift,
but it's nothing we haven't seen before
on television.
And I got an e-mail
from the network this morning.
The audience for psychic shows
is leveling off.
I can't justify picking you up unless
I see something truly unbelievable.
Let me set up a special taping
to show you exactly
what I'm capable of.
Although going deeper into the void
is a little dangerous,
I'm willing to do it if you are.
Mr. Rand, I got to talk to you.
About what? That show?
It was a disaster.
I need more,
more things on more people.
Real facts...
things that only the dead would know!
I've already replaced all the equipment.
upgraded all of our microphones.
I could put more plants,
but if the questions get more explicit,
they could give us away.
I had to cold-read half
that audience in there.
You're always saying how you never
get to practice cold reads.
Not live! Not in front
of the network suits, you idiot.
But, sir, you were amazing.
The way you used that rainbow ruse
and the russian doll.
You had them eating out of your hand.
I've never seen anything like it.
You want to know what the trick is?
It's confidence.
You believe what you're saying,
and they'll believe it, too.
It doesn't matter how many misses,
'cause it's the hits
that they'll remember.
Yes, sir.
All right.
So, what do we have scheduled
for the rest of the day?
That's what I wanted to talk
to you about. We've actually...
had some cancellations.
Cancellations?
- Did they give a reason?
- The same reason, actually.
Here he comes.
Just incredible.
Here, let me give you something
for all you've given me.
Please, you know
I can't accept that.
You know, I always thought
you guys were fakes.
- I saw this one guy the other night...
- That's not why I do this.
You sure?
How may the spirits serve you today?
Maybe they can explain why you keep...
poaching my clients.
I must apologize, Mr. Rand.
It's true I've had more visitors lately,
but I had no idea it was
at your expense.
I'm Bethany. Bethany Noble.
The outfit is a little on the nose,
but other than that, I got to say,
I find your shtick amusing.
I'm sorry?
Working out of a coffee shop?
No neon lights.
No tarot cards or ouija boards.
So, what's your story?
You got me curious.
Two years ago, I was diagnosed
with a brain tumor.
The doctors removed it,
but ever since...
I guess you could say
I was twice blessed...
with renewed life
and with this gift.
You're serious.
Do you feel the scar?
All right, then.
Tell me something
that only the spirits would know.
Tell me about my father...
How he died.
Don't worry. I got you, girl.
We didn't give her that scar,
did we?
No, we did not.
I could channel your father,
Mr. Rand,
but that might be difficult,
seeing how he's still alive.
Indiana, isn't it?
Do you still have the prayer book
he gave you?
What's wrong?
I felt something.
Nate had me rig the table
with a mild electrical current.
- You electrocuted him?
- Yes, I did. It helps sell the bit.
- I approve.
- Thanks, Parker.
No. Her agreeing with you
is not a good thing.
- That's...
- Thanks.
You saw through a trick question.
Doesn't mean anything.
I'm a known commodity in this city.
You could've looked me up.
The spirits are all around us,
watching us, guiding us.
I don't need to look people up.
The spirits tell me all I need to know.
You're clairvoyant.
They're clairvoyant. I just listen.
What do they say about me?
You want to know your future.
They're calling you
by a different name.
Do you know the way, José?
What?
They're saying José doesn't pay
his tickets and it will burn him.
Don't ask the officer for help.
He has his own problems.
But don't worry, you're the life
of the party, so celebrate.
And bring extra cash
because you won't have enough.
A day late, a dollar short,
and if you don't look both ways,
you'll never live to see tomorrow.
Listen, I think I've heard enough.
Lady, I love your act,
I really do, and I wish you
all the best with it.
This is my turf.
Stay off it.
I got a misto here for José.
They're calling you by a different name.
Do you know the way, José?
I think that's supposed to be mine.
I paid all my tickets!
They're saying José
doesn't pay his tickets.
Mr. Rand, your 12:00's here.
It's a new client. I think he's...
I'll handle it.
- How can I help you today?
- Actually, this is...
This is kind of embarrassing.
The guys would kill me
if they knew I was here.
Don't ask the officer for help.
He has his own problems.
Officer.
You're a police officer.
How did you know that?
Right. Because you're...
You're the life of the party,
so celebrate,
and bring extra cash
because you won't have enough.
And if you don't look both ways,
you'll never live to see tomorrow.
Have you been here all night?
Bethany.
It happened. All of it happened
just like you said it would.
How do you do it?
I'm just a conduit. I don't do anything.
I simply speak what's on their minds.
You got to come to work for me.
My gift is just that...
It's a gift.
It's meant to be shared,
not bought and sold.
And you're a charlatan, Mr. Rand.
I can't be a part of that.
No, no. See, I did my homework.
You need me...
Just as much as I need you.
You're in debt up to your ears.
You got no steady stream of income.
You will never pay off
those hospital bills.
How did you get my credit report?
It doesn't matter. What matters
is you and I we can help people.
You want to use my gift to make you
famous. How is that helping people?
Come on!
It's just for a little while,
till you get back on your feet.
- It would only be temporary.
- Absolutely
Only...
You got to tell me something.
How do you do it?
Honestly.
I paid all my tickets!
I paid 'em!
The truth is,
I have a lot of help.
Mr. Rand.
I thought you said no one
else was allowed in here.
Change of plans, Wilson.
You're out.
Ms. Noble will be taking over from here.
- I don't understand.
- I need you outside.
Go work the line.
- This doesn't feel right. I should go.
- Because of Wilson?
Bethany, the Wilsons of the world...
They serve their purpose,
but you and I... we are special.
We're gonna do something great.
Here.
What do you want me to do?
Okay,
this microphone
connects to my earpiece.
Now, you
look in the audience,
tell me who to talk to.
Use your gift.
When I connect with their loved ones,
you want me to tell you what they say?
You tell me, I communicate it to them.
See, that's my gift.
Relax.
It's just a trial run.
If we do well,
in a little while,
we'll perform live for the network.
Okay, you ready?
You do realize what you're asking
me to do is impossible, right?
There you go.
And my gummy frogs.
I need my gummy frogs.
You serious?
Yeah.
Okay, Parker, how's the harvest?
Excuse me.
Hi. There's no food or drink
in the auditorium, miss.
- Sorry.
- Thanks.
I can only get one wallet at a time
Because someone is
making me return them.
I still don't get why we're
not just making this guy dead.
Yeah, well,
that's why you're on wallet detail.
Okay, guys, show's about to begin.
Tara,
it's on you.
Got it.
The people that we've lost...
They are not gone to us.
They're on the other side,
and they're trying to
make contact with us,
to guide us, to console us.
And all of us here have,
atne point or another,
Wanted to talk to
them one more time.
Tonight,
we're gonna do just that.
I feel a presence.
Third row, aisle, yellow dress.
Third row on the aisle.
Woman in the yellow dress.
- Got her.
- Right there.
Sandra Kimmel, hairdresser.
Credit score is really low... 580.
Last posted statement paint store,
truck rental.
I got a 17-year-old cutlass.
There's a breast-cancer ribbon
on the rearview mirror...
Bunch of financial
magazines in the back.
This presence...
Is someone that you loved very much.
- It's...
- Her mother.
... Your mother.
Yes.
Breast cancer.
She died last year.
She was taken from you
just last year.
Breast cancer.
Yes, that's right.
Tell her her mother doesn't blame
her for the salon going under.
Your mother...
she knows how much you wanted
your business to succeed.
It was a salon, wasn't it?
Yes.
Her mother also knows How hard she worked
on the painting, the construction.
Your mother says that your whole life,
you never asked for help.
Never.
She knows that you built
that salon with your own two hands,
and she's proud of you,
no matter what happens.
I'm feeling another presence.
It's...
It's a man this time.
I got a truck...
Michigan plates, covered in mud.
Two suitcases in the back.
He drove all night to get here.
He didn't even check into his hotel.
Ight, big floral arrangement posted
to his credit card a week ago.
He canceled a trip the same day.
Do you know what you're touching?
His father died last week.
He got a call from the national
transportation safety board.
It was a private plane.
It went down.
Your father died in
a plane crash last week.
That's right.
- How'd you know?
- He knows...
That you two had your differences,
and he loves you.
But he wants you to be safe.
Driving 10 straight hours
from michigan to get here...
At's not safe.
That's my dad.
Margaret Kusen parents both deceased
over 20 years ago. She hired
a private inveigator last month.
She's not here to talk to anyone.
She wants answers about her husband.
The spirits are telling
me one thing...
Your husband is hiding something.
I'm sorry. That's all I'm getting.
It's okay.
That's what I wanted to know.
And we'll be right back.
She's amazing.
- Is she for real?
- Who cares?
Look at these people.
They're eating it up!
She isonna make me a star.
- I'm sorry I couldn't give you more.
- More? Are you kidding me?
Save it for the pay-per-view event.
I'm telling you... I'm starting
to rethink this network deal.
They'll still come
for the show, right?
Yes, they will come. Are you kidding?
After what you did in there...
Tara, you got company.
... But they are gonna back up the money
truck for you. I can just see it.
Come on.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Any theories?
Maybe somebody didn't like their psychic
reading.
- Or maybe someone liked it too much.
- What do you mean?
Rand told me it was
the best show he ever did.
Everyone was there at
the show to talk to
to the dead except that woman
at the end why was she there?
Her husband.
She thinks he's cheating on her.
How'd you know that? All I said was
she hired a private investigator.
Married woman in her 40s? She's
not looking for the maltese falcon.
What do we know about this husband?
Here's the guy she came in with.
Let's see what the facial
recognition says about...
Hello. Nickolas Kusen,
age 44. He did time in riverview
a few years back for armed robbery.
One of the thugs who tried to
grab her had a prison tattoo.
What... Kusen has a secret,
And he's gonna kill rand
so he doesn't reveal it?
That'd be good.
You want to kill someone, you don't
get out and throw 'em in a van.
- You don't get out of your seat.
- All right, Kusen needs
rand for his psychic abilities.
That's why he was being so secretive
around his wife.
Let me get this straight... We did such
a good job of convincing people Rand
was really a psychic
that we got him kidnapped?
Which means we have to find him, rescue
him, and then, you know, take him down.
Let's go to work.
It looks like
they're headed east.
Give me some good news
on the financials.
They're all over the place. It's hard to
get a clear picture.
Must be a cash-heavy operation,
probably import/export.
You know that body shop
Kusen pays property taxes on?
- Let me guess... not a body shop?
- It's a parking lot.
I managed to track them as far
as tremont before I lost them,
but they're definitely
somewhere in the north end.
If I had to guess,
I would say they're being...
Union wharf?
And I can do you one better.
I've got an address.
All right.
I'm gonna be right outside. I can
be there in seconds if you need me.
Let's hope I don't.
Excuse me.
Are you...
Gonna keep him long?
Because we have a show later.
Who are you?
She's... With me.
M-ms. Noble.
She and I, we work together.
- How'd you find me?
- The spirits told me.
They said you needed my help.
You're psychic, too.
Join us, join us.
Get the lady a chair.
As I was, just explaining to Mr.
Rand...
... I have a bit of a problem.
Several years ago, I was involved
in a short-term business venture
with a very high rate of return.
An associate
and I had gone
into this endeavor together,
but before we could split the
profits
from our enterprise,
an unfortunate misunderstanding
forced me to spend a few
years in upstate new york.
- Have you ever been there?
- It's beautiful this time of year.
Yeah, it's... it is beautiful.
Beautiful. Gorgeous.
Anyway, when I returned to claim
what was mine, Mr. Brancato wasn't
particularly forthcoming
With the information.
He passed away without revealing...
Its location.
And now you see my dilemma.
You robbed a bank,
and you want us to help you find
Where your partner hid the money.
My wife is such
a big fan of yours, Mr. Rand.
She seems to think you have a
knack for this sort of thing,
so I hope that's true,
Because this is only
gonna go down two ways.
You don't find the money
and I kill you...
Or you find the money,
and I consider not killing you.
So, what do you say?
At least he's not
cheating on his wife.
Okay, I found his ex-partner,
cesar brancato.
His name was on the lease
for that body shop that
kusen supposedly owned.
This guy wants a bag of money? Let's get
him a bag of money. Everybody listen up.
There was a problem...
before the robbery.
You had issues with him.
You didn't trust him.
I don't need to be psychoanalyzed,
Mr. Rand. I can get that at home.
Where the hell's my money?!
I'm seeing something.
It's a car, an old car.
I'm walking around it now.
The license plate's missing.
It's a chevrolet...
a chevrolet malibu.
That's what he drove a '78 malibu.
If we follow the car,
it'll lead us to the money.
What do you say we go for a ride?
It's in this direction...
Over here.
Buy me 10 seconds.
- Are you all right?
- I'm sorry.
Sometimes the visions are...
A little overwhelming.
Good to go.
It's this way.
I'll be damned.
Search it.
May I hold it?
You see anything?
What does it open?
I see a storage unit.
Someone's making a deposit on it.
He has a beard... And glasses.
That's him. That's brancato.
I only need the unit for a week.
Are you attached to
those overalls, Phil?
Come on!
- I know this place. We're...
- I need to concentrate.
Which unit does this open?
Guys, we're not ready.
We got to stall. We got to stall.
No, I'm sorry. I've lost my connection
to the spirit world.
It's like a car battery.
I just need to recharge.
I've waited long enough.
Come on. Try this one right here.
Take those, get it. Go get it.
What's going on?!
What the heck you doing over here?
I need to see your records.
- Just few more minutes, keep them busy.
- Are you guys cops?
Yeah. We're the k-9 unit.
The dog ate my badge.
Now, which unit does this key open?
Right.
Let's see. I'm gonna have
to check my records.
- Let's look at your records.
- Okay, we're gonna check the records.
- We need more boxes.
- And a lot of luck.
Yeah, I think we used all
our luck on finding this place.
Wait. Man, you know what?
It ain't luck, okay? Finding the perfect
place to end the treasure hunt
Is a testimony to my
intellectual prowess.
What?
It's baby clothes.
It says "books," man!
Does it?
Not that.
You got to line up the right...
Hey. We're all clear.
... Code with the thing there,
And, I think there... yeah!
There we go. It's...
That'd be unit number, 398.
Go! Come on!
You better hope they find the money.
Come on, come on, what's in there?
Keep going. Open that box.
What's your crystal ball say now?
I don't know.
You better go into
a trance or something,
Whatever it is you do,
Because I'm fresh out of patience!
I'm not psychic.
I can't... I can't
communicate with the dead.
- It's all fake!
- I think you're holding out on me.
I think you know where the money is...
You just want it for yourself!
No. No! It's not...
listen to me.
My studio is wired up with
microphones and cameras.
And I make it look like
I'm a psychic, but I'm not.
You know, I cold-read people.
Yeah, I ask them questions.
I look at their reactions.
It's all I do!
It's a scam okay?
I've been running it for years!
Have to say, guys,
I totally saw this one coming.
How'd you know I was hiding
something from my wife?
I didn't. She did.
I cold-read people.
Yeah, I ask them questions,
I look at their reactions.
It's all I do.
It's a scam okay?
I've been running it for years!
I'm not done piggybacking the signal from
the unit cameras to the live studio feed.
Guys, we're not ready yet.
You got to stall. You got to stall.
It's all fake!
You know what I think?
I think you're holding out on me.
I think you know where the money is.
You just want it for yourself!
No! It's not listen to me.
My studio is wired up with microphones
and cameras.
And I make it look like I'm
a psychic, but I'm not.
You know, I cold-read people.
Yeah, I ask them questions.
I look at their reactions.
It's all I do! It's a scam okay?
All right, there he is.
You're under arrest.
Hey, you know what?
He's the bad guy here.
When we were in there, he had a
gun on me, and he robbed a bank.
Like I'm gonna believe
anything you say.
- Get them out of here!
- Wait, no! Come on! Aw. Not jail.
... Microphones and cameras.
And I make it look like I'm
a psychic, but I'm not.
Okay, you know, I'm getting
a bad feeling about this.
Now, really.
Watch your head.
"He who sells miracles will have
the devil knocking at his door."
- What is that, a proverb?
- Fortune cookie.
What?
What? It started with "he who."
They do make a cute pair,
don't they?
Let's see, we got assault,
Kidnapping, and burglary
for our iend kusen,
Garden-variety fraud for our
psychic friend, dalton rand.
Any way we can get them
in the same prison?
- That could be arranged.
- Hey, let's go, man. Let's go.
All the people who thought he could talk
to their loved ones on the other side.
What's to stop them from falling
for the next dalton rand?
Not a thing.
Then why do it?
It's okay, jodie.
I'm sorry. I'm just so embarrassed.
No, no. Don't be.
Dalton rand is a con artist.
He took advantage of hundreds
of people, maybe thousands.
But now that he's heading to jail,
he can't do it to anyone else.
There was a part of me that knew
it wasn't real, but I didn't care.
I just missed mike so much.
I wanted to see him again so bad.
You will see him again.
Maybe it'll be a look.
Maybe it'll be a gesture.
Maybe it'll be the way
He spreads peanut butter
on a slice of bread.
But when you see it, you'll know,
And you'll say "That's Mike."
And you know what? That's a miracle
that no one could ever sell you.
Thank you, Mr. Ford.
And now I see why you do it.
Before you go, this is for your sister
and the baby.
What is this?
It's the money rand
took from your sister...
All of it.
I don't know what to say.
Wait a second.
I thought you said all of rand's money
Went into paying for his show.
- I thought you said he was broke.
- It did. He was.
Where'd the money come from?
- Did you guys find the stolen money?
- Did you find kusen's loot?
Without...
Unbelievable.
He who looks for hidden
money shall find it...
If he is also a thief.
BorderLine Crew on www.U-Sub.net