I checked
Airport charters in 15 minutes
I'm sorry, Mr. Ford, sorry
I know who you are
I've.. Excuse me.
I've read all about you
I know, for example that
When you found that stolen ...
in Florence
You probably saved your insurance company
What.. 40-45 million dollars
Then there was that identity theft thing..
You see.
Your insurance company. How do you
even know how many millions of dollars..
I.. I just know that
when you needed them..
What happened to your family,
it's a kind of thing..
You know, that's part of the conversation
When I punch you in the neck
nine or ten times
And we coming up on that pretty quick
I just want to offer you a job
What do you got?
Do you know anything about airplane design?
You can give it a shot, you know,
give me a pencil,
and one of that little rulers..
Somebody stolen my airplane designs.
Aah, I see..
And you'd like me to find them, right?
No. I know where they are.
I want you to steal them back.
Are you sure Pirson stole your designs?
My engineer goes missing.
It desappears with all my values.
And one week later Pirson starts
an identical project? Come on!
I don't know. Stealing them back,
it's like a stupid risk.
Listen to me. At the end of this month
I have a shareholders meeting, it's important.
I've spend five years and hundred million dollars.
And I go for that meeting with nothing to show for?
Then I am dead.
Look, I'm serious, look.
Look at the people I've already hired.
Do you recognize any of this names?
Year, I've chased all of them one time or anoth..
Parker, you have Parker.
Is he somebody bad?
No, but Parker is insane.
Which is why I need you.
No. I'm not a thief.
Thieves.. I got. But I need this
one honest man to watch them.
Are you in?
It's not gonna work,
these people you hired..
They are at the same rep.
They work alone, they always work alone.
There's no exceptions.
There's no way they'll work for you.
Yes, I know, I know. For $300'000 each they will.
And for you, for running it, it's double that.
And it's off the books.
Look at me, who's desperate here.
That's just the salary. There is a bonus.
Pirson is insured by IYS, your bosses.
It's a $50 mil. intellectual property.
Mr. Ford, how badly do you want to
screw your insurance company
That let your son die?
OK, clear comms.
No, no-no-no, no! Hell, no!
This equipment is total VH-1, bro.
It's busted in 80's.
I got something nicer.
Allright, no surprises now.
I've been doing this since high school, bro.
I'm can't be disciplined.
It came straight from the airport and up to that room.
So you didn't actually saw any of them.
But they credit card numbers checked out.
Brake it down!
Does that look like Mick Jagger to you?
This is not the room you looking for.
This mike works out of vibrations in your jaw.
You can hear everything.
You not as useless as you look.
I don't even know what you do.
I'm here to collect the merchandise.
Can I have one?
You can have the whole box.
What're you gonna do if the finds out
you lives with your mom?
Age of the geek, baby.
We run the world.
You keep telling yourself that.
You thought I wouldn't find this?
You don't get bunny
until you do what I say.
So be a good girl.
Or, I don't know.
A better thief.
Last time i used this rig -
Paris, 2003.
Is this thing safe?
Terma de Carvaggio? You stole that?
Yes, it's completely safe, it just
you may experience
nausea, weakness in your right side,
stroke, strokiness..
You - preciselly why I work alone.
Guys, listen up, you're gonna go on my count,
not a second sooner.
Parker, no freelancing.
Hey, relax. We know what we're doing.
And on the count of five.. four.. three..
- She's gone.
- Son of a ...
Yeeehaaa!
It's twenty pounds of crazy in five pound bag.
Vibration detectors are on.
No cutting, Parker, use the binary.
You know, Parker
any time you...
Whoa!
Boys are on they way.
Will you get me security?
Do you see security?
They don't see a thing.
Door is open.
Allright, guys, it's showtime.
Here we go.
- Here.
- Got it.
OK. You got any chatter on their frequencies?
No. Why?
There's eight listed on a duty roster,
and there's only four at the guardpost.
I can't even tell how many guys is in the room,
how can you tell who is who?
Haircuts, Parker, count their haircuts.
???
What?
Nothing.
Problem?
Aah.. Maybe.
Run the cameras.
Send digitals forward. I salute you, sir.
Got 'em!
They doing a walkthrough an hour early. Why?
Because it's the playoffs.
Yeah. They doing the rounds an hour early
so they can watch the playoffs.
- Allright, where are they?
- They at the stairwell!
OK
Hey! We've got a security breach!
Get 'em on the radio up there. Go, go!
OK, guys. Here's what we got to do.
We got to squelch 'em.
Elliot? What I want you to do
is clear the zone and use Hardison as bait.
Bait? Hold up, wait a minute!
What're you talking about, man,
I ain't nobody's bait.
Hardison, they're on stair.
Come on, baby, come on, just come on, man!
Forget it!
Hold it right there!
That's what I do.
Guys, guys, you got to talk to me, OK?
'Cause I don't know what's going on!
It's all good, I'm stripping the drives right now.
Come on, baby.
Got all the designs, got all the backup.
Drop the spike.
Did you give'em a virus?
Dude, I gave 'em more than one virus.
Problem.
That guards again. They resetted all the alarms on the roof and the floor above us.
We can't go up.
Every man for himself, dude.
Go ahead, but I'm the one with the merchandise.
Yeah, and I'm the one with the exit!
And I'm the one with a plan.
Now I know you children don't play with others,
but I need you to hold it together for exactly seven more minutes.
Now, get to the elevator and hit "down".
We're going to the burned scam.
Going to plan B?
Technically, that'd be plan G.
How many plans do we have, is there like a plan M?
Yeah. Hardison dies in plan M.
I like plan M.
I thought we locked down those elevators.
Hey, hey, stand still, don't move.
- Nice! Would you stare a little more?
- Sorry.
You gotta be kidding me!
No, Tom, it's OK.
No, it's not.
- Sorry.
- I understand.
Come on, come on, it's gonna take all night..
I got a couple of wi-fi networks with some crappy bandwidth.
OK, there you go.
The designs are sent.
Allright, the money will be on all your accounts later today.
Anybody else noticed how we rocked last night?
Yeah, well, one show only, no anchors
I've already forgot your names.
It was kinda cool being on the same side.
No, we a not on the same side, I'm not a thief
You are now.
Come on, Nathan, tell the truth
You have a little bit of fun doing a bit of black king, instead of white knight
Just this once
Yeah?
You screwed me!
The designs never got to me.
No, I watched them go out.
I don't know what you saw,
but I received nothing!
Look, I told you you couldn't trust 'em.
It's not my job to trust anybody
that's you were here for.
I'm freezing the payments.
I'm freezing all the payments!
All right, look, look, look, uh ...
I'll come over there right now...
- No, no, no, no!
Do not come here. My company...
Has an old facility outside the city ...
I'll text you the address and you be there in one hour!
You wanna say what happened to the designs?
What makes you think I know what happened?
Stupid.
Yeah, forget it, you did it.
When we were coming down in an elevator.
Yeah, that makes sense, doesn't it.
Were the files ever sacked?
Hey, wait, Cujo, I did my part.
- I transferred the files. What did you do?
- What if I take the gun and...
Hey!
Did you do it?
You are the one who has played on both sides.
Yeah, you seem pretty relaxed with a guy with a gun pointed at you.
- Its safety is on.
- Like I'm a fall for that.
No, actually he's right, safety is on.
Are you armed?
I don't like guns.
My money isn't on my account.
That makes me cry inside.
In my special angry voice.
OK, Parker ...
Now had you came here to get paid?
Hell, no. Transferring funds, man.
Global economy.
It supposed to be a walkaway, I'm never supposed to see you again
The only reason we guys are here
it is because we didn't get paid.
And you are pissed off!
As a matter of fact, the only way to get us all
in the same place at the same time ...
is to tell us that we're not getting
paid.
Come on, get up, get up!
Go, Hardison, go! Go!
You don't like hospitals.
Not much.
It's about time!
What the...
Cops and firemen got there just as they were waiting it.
Where are we?
At the county hospital
Local cops are responded to the explosion
We've been processed?
They faxed our prints to the state police.
If the states run us, man, we're screwed.
- How long?
- 30, 35 minutes, depending on the software.
They printed us 20 minutes ago
Unless we get out of here in next 10 minutes ...
- We all go to jail.
- Hey, yeah, yeah, allright.
I can take this cops.
Don't you dare! You kill anyone, you screwed my getaway.
Hello, I'm still handcuffed here, I can't even go to the bathroom,
and I got to go.
- Parker!
Get me a phone!
What we're going to do is we get out of here together.
This was a one-time deal.
OK, guys, here is your problem:
You all know what you can do, and I know what all you can do
So it gives me the edge, it gives me the plan.
I don't trust these guys.
Do you trust me?
Of course.
You're the honest man.
Parker, phone.
This is kinda suck.
Oh, hell!
The nausea could men a concussion.
If you feel any more effects, or blurred vision
tell the policeman right away.
Hey.
Nate!
I got it.
So the trick is to give them what they want.
They expecting a phone call,  right?
Here's an outside call for you, line 2.
OK.
This is deputy Brians.
Yeah, this is Detective Lt. Carlton, we dealing with a state police.
We got those prints that you've send to us.
The problem I have that there's all kinds of red flags,
I have somebody on the phone for you, from the FBI
down there in Washington. Can you hold on, son?
Yes, sir.
There it goes.
Yeah, deputy Brians, this is deputy director McCumber, FBI.
Yes, is our man allright?
- I'm sorry, I don't follow...
- Deputy, listen to me.
The man you have inside there, he is ours actually.
He has been in deep cover for 3 years.
Seriously?
That's correct. You should be receiving a fax any moment now
confirming what I'm telling you.
Most of what I've told you is classified, I need to know that I can trust you.
Can I?
Yes, sir.
Walk it off, walk.
Get inside.
Fills my heart with tears of joy,
what you guys do.
It does.
There's a call for you, state police.
4 first-class tickets to anywhere but here coming up.
Who's place is this?
It's mine.
I'm going to beat Dubenich so bad, even from one look at him you're going to bleed.
You won't get within a 100 yards.
He knows your face, he knows all our faces.
He tried to kill us.
And more important, he didn't pay us.
How is that more important?
I take it personally.
There is something wrong with you ...
Hey, hey, heads up, look.
Dubenich history is 90% truth.
He is in Bering Aerospace, big rival of Pirson's.
But check out what my little web crawler has caught up.
We've lost research ...
that we've been working on for 5 years.
Our servers have been sabotaged.
Now we are going to pursue these perpetraitors with a full extent of the law,
and with all the resources we have at our disposal.
Could be a cover story.
Here's a logs from last night, it has a time stamps of the projects from
2003, 2004, and way, way down ago.
- There's no reason to fake those, man.
- So we didn't steal those plans back?
No, we were just stealing them.
And why would Dubenich lie to us?
Because you are thieves.
If he hired to you for a straight up crime,
You'll know he's bad guy like you, you'd be suspicious.
This way you saw just another citizen, in over his head
and that's why you didn't see the double cross coming.
- Why didn't you see it coming?
- Because I am not a thief.
-  You know? Maybe that was the problem.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Our 4 tickets to London,
Rome, Paris and Sao Paulo
all matching the ID's that you gave me.
You running?
- Yes. You  got a better idea?
- No, no.
You're running.
That was a high-risk play.
You got your balls tied to the stock price like a senior block
with shareholders meeting coming up.
We can't let this guy have any time to cool down.
You want to run a game on this guy
You?
Yeah, I mean, how do you think I got most of my stolen merchandise back?
This guy is greedy, he thinks he's smart, is the best kind of mark.
He thinks he got rid of us.
An element of surprise.
What's in it for me?
Payback.
And if it goes right, a lot of money.
And what's in it for me?
A lot of money.
And if it goes right...
payback.
Hardison?
I was going to send thousands of porn magazines to his office, but ...
Hell, yeah, man, let's kick him up!
What's in it for you?
He used my son.
Allright, let's go get Sophie.
Who the hell is this Sophie?
Hail you spirits
that tend on mortal thoughts!
Unsex me here
and fill me from the crown to the toes.
at the foot ...
Full of darkness ...
Make my blood
stop all the all access ...
and passage to remorse,
that no...
- That no ...
- She's very awful.
Is she injured?
In the head?
Seriously, man, this is the worst actress I've ever seen.
This is not her stage.
No.
No! I vote no!
Parker's right.
Dubenich knows us.
And we need fresh face.
I thought you were great.
My only fan.
Freeze!
You wanco...
I'm a citizen now.
Honest.
I'm not.
You play on my side?
I always thought you had it in you.
Are you in?
I wouldn't miss this.
All right, let's go break the law, just one more time
Victor Dubenich, executive vice president in charge of new tecnologies
and development of Bering Aerospace.
Rich daddy, trust fund, Yale MBA,
blah blah blah ...
Victor. Now when was the last time you met a Victor?
Vietnam. Tinh Cao Bang Na Ziai.
Chinese border
That's an odd thing for you to know.
That's an odd place for you to be.
Bering is in charge of all that big fat government contracts.
Some Department of Defense things very classified stuff.
Can we use that?
No, I do not think so.
Dubenich is in charge of the commercial airline business.
I know that when you sent Dubenich's designs,
you weren't supposed to make any copies..
No, I promise.
That wouldn't be very well.
Show me your copies.
It's an airplain.
This is short range domestic airliner.
Usually, one hour flights
It's a fastest growing segment of the industry
Very fuel efficient, hi tech
Very nice carbon nose
It's got a titanium rap, 3 to 1
You know, you pick up thing here and there
You pick up a lot of stuff.
Now check this out.
Dubenich and Pearson,
they were head to head for 5 years,
trying to grab the lead in the industry,
it's profit like an 11 billion dollars.
So, Pirson got there first,
Dubenich sticks at the back.
So they got a rival.
It's kind of rival that hurted him so much
has hired us to steal his designs. This is good.
- What are you thinking, Nate?
- I'm thinking Nigerians.
Yeah, Nigerians will do nicely.
Well, he hasn't changed a bit.
Your 9 o'clock is here.
But ...
Mr. Dubenich.
Anna Gunstott,
African Commercial Transport and Trade Initiative.
Faking amount is suck.
- You're government?
- No, no.
Private business consultant.
We looking to incourage infrastructure development
and economic renewal.
I don't know what's that means in English.
What does it mean?
We create jobs in trade in Africa.
Keeping graft and stealing managable.
But she's not awful.
This is her stage.
Sophie Devereaux is the finest actress you've ever seen
when she's breaking the law.
Keeping graft and stealing managable in Africa?
Good luck. I do not think I can help.
I don't think that any human being on Earth can help you with that, sorry.
Come on.
Let's go and talk somewhere less formal, eh?
No, no, no, I ...
Uh, look, uh ...
Miss, uh ...
OK, and...
Now.
What? No, no. No.
No, no, no, no.
No. No, no, please.
Hello, IT?
Yeah, this is Victor Dubenich's office,
my computer just completely crashed.
Oh, ma'am, I'm sorry to hear about that.
You tried to turn it on and off again?
- It does not work..
- Thats the computer thing.
They ought to say that.
Well done.
We got someone on your floor already
Thank you.
Somebody called IT?
I represent a group of investors ...
who looking to start an airline.
for short-range flights in Africa.
From Johannesburg?
Ok, he's testing you, you want Bloemfontein.
Keep away from the hubs,
revitalize the original airports. In South Africa,
Bloemfontein, for example.
Machili,
It's Nigeria we focused on.
- Yeah, perfect.
- Lakes ??? a mess!
I beleive new airplanes will make people so comfortable
while renewing the tracks.
Aha.
I do not recall having said anything about new planes.
Victor.
But you and your chief engineer are planning
speak in their shareholders meetings.
I think you know more about my business than I do.
I've done my homework.
You find you fascinating.
It's good to have a passion.
It is. Let me show you how to
reconnect with the network.
Should I be playing a computer guy?
No, I want you to actually be the computer guy.
All right. Uh, no.
And... reboot.
Voila.
You strong for a computer guy.
Thank you.
I like to work out, try to stay big ...
I love dressing up for a Klingon,
go to all the conventions, you know..
Baklag!
Sorry.
- Baklag!
- Don't you tease me!
Oh, hold up, man, that is not cool.
We'll have a strong talk when you'll get back.
But with blue eyes...
Thank you.
... blue ...
Sorry, is it Gunshot?
Sorry.
- Gunstott.
- Gunstott!
- Sorry about that.
- Anna.
Anna. Thank you.
How is this?
If we announced a new product ...
then you can order as many as your little heart desires.
OKl, you know what to do.
Hit him.
We select to build the plains. More jobs.
Built'em in Africa, fly'em in Africa,
and sell the rest around the world.
- Now, that's very ambitious.
You have manufacturing facilities to do all that?
Ach!
We can easily rise the money to build the facilities.
If ...
we know for sertain that we will get the contracts.
Attah girl.
Anna ...
I'm really sorry, but I can't help you.
Yeah, that was a nice try, man.
Wait for it.
- And I really..
- I understand.
I really do have...
I'll take it to Pirson.
Pirson?
No! Pirson is a great company.
Sure, go ahead, I do not think that can help you, but ...
Well, they have a reputation for long-term investment.
You don't. They are innovators.
Yeah.
It's probably a better fit.
I know, I'm aware
that you manipulating me, Anna.
I should hope so.
Hundreds of millions of dollars in new contracts.
A lot of good press.
All at your door.
Okay, I give up, I'll take the meeting.
I'll have my office call you.
-  What? Yeah.
-Day after tomorrow?
Yeah, sure. Look forward..
doing business with you...
Yo, Nate!
I've got all their financial records, all passwords
The five ... No thanks.
The five to the corner.
You look better.
- Then when we started.
- Yeah.
What's that bothers you, huh?
- I... Well, this isn't suppose to feel..
-  Good?
It's not too hard to figure out.
Dubenich screwed you.
He cheated you by stealing from another company
and in your good guy brain sees him as the bad guy.
Your conscience is clear.
You want to take your shot?
Listen, I'm sorry about your kid.
You don't know anything about that.
Everybody knows it.
Guy like you goes of the street, then a lot of people notice.
And it was a bad story too.
How they even justified that, the insurance company?
Just not paying for his treatment?
They claimed it was experimental.
You should've kept on of those Monets you found.
- If you'd sold ...
- Elliot, you and I are not friends.
Right.
Because you have so many of'em.
Ann coming.
Hey.
- Help me with this headset.
- Why don't you ask Hardison?
Nate, come on.
Thanks
So...
this time you really are inside my head.
Sophie, he's on site.
What?
No, Im not ready!
If you don't meet him right down in the lobby
his going to the building directory looking for the office number.
Guys, we're not in the building directory!
And why aren't we in the directory?
I don't know, maybe because of fake offices?
What's with the elevator?
Allright, I'll distract him.
Parker, you got 10 seconds to get Sophie to lobby.
Sophie!
- What's going on?
- Put this on!
What's it for?
Speed.
Our offices on the 10th floor.
Oh, you're...
You have a glow.
Just ... excited.
One thing.
The gentlemen bringing this opportunity ...
to work with their government, they're ...
expect some ... compensation.
Not a bribe, of course.
- A finder's fee.
- Exactly.
I thought your job was to eliminate graft and stealing?
No. My job is to keep it managable.
- Good afternoon.
- Hello.
- Mr. Dubenich.
- Yes.
- We're honored by your presence.
- No, no, the honor is entirely mine.
Getting it at the ground floor, something like this is a ...
wonderful opportunity, sir.
Nice job with the zipline.
Totally thought she was going to break a leg.
Not bad for the first time.
So, what do you think?
She's closing it up.
Yes, absolutely.
We can definitely recompose those factories.
Great.
I beleive we'll be able to do a lot of business together, sir.
About ...
the other matter.
Of course.
Is that agreeable?
Oh, I think we can work something out.
Excellent.
We got him?
We own him.
Ok, gang, let's go, we got a busy day tomorrow.
- This is going to work, right?
- I guarantee it.
- This is insane, you're risking everything!
- Adam.
We took a chance ... stealing those plans now ...
What is that?
It is a transmitter, and they've been listening to everything that we've been saying.
- Who 'they'?
-  Who do you think?
Also, I checked, there's no office
fo the African Commercial Trade Initiative anywhere in the city.
They're runnig a scam on me and i know exactly what they're doing.
Tomorrow it stops.
- Get the FBI on the phone.
- Yes, sir.
-  Sure you know what you're doing?
- Yeah, they're pissed, I get that.
They want to make me pay.
I mean, an opportunity like this the same week
with the shareholders meeting, the bug, the fake offices
cash bribes, Nigerians, for god's sake!
Nigerians, I mean, its like, those e-mail scams
with Nigerian bank fraud letters.
Who the hell do they think I am?
Some dog they could just lead around.
They're going to find exactly how wrong they are.
Fly anywhere, anywhere in the world.
I want to introduce to you...
It's more than just nuts, bolts, and scrap metal...
- What I noticed - it's good for you.
- It's a good day for all of us.
The stoks got 15 points up since the announcement.
Really?
- You didn't know ?
- No. I'll pass it around.
Aren't you the cat that take the canary?
- It is a joke?
- ???
Gulity.
Why don't we get this done?
-  Now?
- Yeah.
- You have the whole payment?
- Yeah, absolutely, I think we should make the deal
I'm going to make the announcement, get'em bigger headlines.
I'll take'em into the conference room, away from all this
Come, come, let's do it.
- I'll be right back.
- OK!
Gentleman.
Now everybody come in, sit down, relax, make yourselves comfortable.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
I assume we all understand the tirms of this agreement.
Well, I'll tel you.
The exact turms of the agreement ...
are these.
FBI, don't move! Are you allright, sir?
- Oh, Im fine.
- Yes, of course.
Thanks for asking, everything's perfect.
What?..
What're you?.. Wait a minute, wait a minute!
Let go of me!
Please.
Why are you looking at me, for the criminals just sitting right over there, look at them.
Listen, I spoke..
I spoke with special agent Higgins,
- If you'll call him on the phone...
- I'm special agent Higgins.
Victor Dubenich, you're under arrest for soliciting a bribe ...
from these Nigerian government officials.
I do not ... I do not ... This aren't even Nigerians!
Of course we are!
- No, no. No, no, no.
- Your woman knew that when she contacted us last week.
My ... woman?
Ann ...  Anna?
Anna!
Special Agent Higgins ...
Anna Gunstott works for them.
Ridiculous!
She contacted us on your behalf.
She told us she were directly under you now.
Anna Gunstott, from Bering Aerospace.
Directly under Victor Dubenich.
But ...
She took me ...
She took me to their office!
No, we do not have an office in this city.
Exactly.
We met her at your other office.
Anna Gunstott, from Bering Aerospace.
Shareholders.
The shareholders!
In god's name...
It's a private party, you can't...
No, no, no.
Everybody, can I have your attention?
It's a ??? problem!
- They have sent the wrong people..
- Victor, what's going on?!
I can explain, Tom, it's just a mistake.
Anybody else here involved in the bribe?
Bribe? There's no bribe!
I handed this man an envelope containing a cashed check
- for 200 thousand dollars!
- No, no. Nobody...
I wasn't handed in...
I didn't...
Nobody handed ...
This'll look better for you if you did not deposited that check.
- No, no.
- Do you still have it?
I didn't get a check!
Sir, we got people searching the lab,
- ceasing the files and computers.
- Good job, Walter.
Victor, we screwed if they find out..
Higgins. Higgins,
You can't do that!
You can't take my computer!
This company has a government offense contracts.
There are very serious rules concerning contact with foreign nations.
The Patriot Act applies here, my friend!
Sir, I can take your underpants.
- Look, look, it's getting a little agressive.
- Yeah.
Sorry, Robert Ntunde, this is Tom Bailey, this gentleman is from Nigeria.
Everybody just take it easy, relax
- I'll be back to explain everything to you..
- Victor, where are you going?
Guys, we got to get rid of this stuff!
Keep srhedding, keep shredding!
Help me!
FBI!
I came alone.
Yes, I know. Thank you, mr. Pirson.
Now, I understand your research was completely wiped out.
I have complete copies right on these hard drives,
along with absolute proof that they were at Bering Aerospace computers
that should be good for a couple of law suits, right?
I drop the investigation
against all parties involved with the original theft.
It seems fair, you get your property back.
Agreed.
No charges.
Nothing on you, or your people.
Don't you want money?
This particular project has a different revenue stream.
In a massive sell-offs, followed by a federal investigation Bering Aerospace,
the stock dropped 33%
before trade was withholded.
Yeah?
Yeah, you should've just paid us.
I found the transmitter.
You found the transmitter with the blinking light.
Yeah, we wanted you to figure some of that out.
Now we just gave you what you expected.
I am Victor Dubenich.
I am gonna beat this.
Aren't you forgetting about the bribe?
Who cares? Can't prove anything, I didn't get any money!
- Bingo!
- Yeah, no, it doesn't account for all of us, Sophie kept a little
to buy a truly impressive number of shoes.
What is it with women and shoes?
There's something wrong with you.
That's what I said.
You see, if the company stock price falls 10 - 15% one day
and you see it coming, you sell short and you can make a lot of money.
If it's gonna fall 30%
you can make shattering amounts of money.
We didn't need the FBI to take you to jail,
we just needed them to show, to take boxes out of your office.
All day long.
In front of TV cameras, scaring your investors
You going to jail is just a bonus.
So if you telling anything about us to the feds
next time we won't be so nice.
Who was that?
Nobody.
I am ...
Job well...
Wow.
It was an overlap in the London stock market
variation carried over to the NASDAQ, and...
I'm just very good at what I do.
This is the score. THE score.
Age of the geek, baby.
Somebody kiss this man, so I don't have to.
So ... we out?
I mean, we out, this is retirement money.
"Go to jet and buy an island" money.
Yeah.
Yeah. A pleasure working with you.
One show only. No anchors.
I've already forgot your names.
You know, I've never had that cool time on a job.
It's a walkaway.
And I got focused on it, bro, it kept me right on.
- I'm really good at one thing.
- Parker ...
Only one thing, that's it, but you, you know other things, and then...
- I can't stop doing my one thing, I can't retire...
- Want to know what I think?
Not really.
How long before you fall apart again?
Oh, I'm touched.
A guy like you can't be out of the game.
Thats why you need the chase.
Yeah, I'll manage.
Yeah.
You pick the jobs.
My job is helping people.
- I find bad guys.
- Well, go find some bad guys.
Bad guys have money.
Black king.
White Knight.
I'm sorry.
No, no.
Please.
Take your time.
She ...
She was 17...
I know.
They ... They killed her.
They said it was an accident.
But the company killed her.
I want them hurt!
We can't pay you.
We work on a ...
alternative revenue sream.
I don't understand.
The judge said we couldn't appel on them.
What are you gonna do?
People like them...
corporations like that,
they have all the money, they have all the power.
And they use it to make people like you ...
go away.
Right now
you suffering under an enormous weight.
We provide ...
leverage.
SLY@Moon Base Alpha
www.tvsubtitles.net