LILLIAN FOODS INTERNATIONAL
LEVERAGE
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@∑ÎŒµ
Sync:FRS@Jingshan ”Í‰Ï
Dr. Jameson.
Mr. Casten.
You scared me.
Only the i.T. Department
is allowed in the server room.
Oh, i...didn't want to
bother them.
I was just trying to copy
some old research...documents.
What are you doing here?
Over the last month, our head
of security, mr. Markland,
Has been tracking illegal
activity in our databases.
Now, you haven't seen anything
suspicious up here, have you?
No, that's --
I just lost some documents.
- Flash drive.
- Mm.
Dr. Jameson, you're gonna
need to come with --
Find her.
Yeah. Come on.
Going down.
This is markland.
I need ground-Level security.
Hello?
Is this leigh jameson?
Yes, it is.
Who is this?
This is forrent alarm systems.
Ma'am, your home alarm
has been activated.
What?!
Which may indicate a break-In
or a home invasion.
Female -- Blond, wearing a white lab coat,
Exiting elevator bank "a."
Hey, you -- With the blond ponytail.
Stop right there!
You're coming with me!
Come on!
The rich and powerful,
they take what they want.
We steal it back for you.
And sometimes, bad guys
make the best good guys.
We provide...
So, when i got back home yesterday,
My place was trashed.
But the only thing stolen
was my hard drive.
I'm -- I'm gonna stay
with friends for now.
Just...in case.
What is it that you have
on lillian foods?
About a month ago,
One of our quality-Control inspectors
Found salmonella bacteria
On a shipment of frozen dinners.
- Here you are, ma'am.
- Thank you.
It's been a rough week.
Bartender.
Thanks.
- One more.
- You got it.
Turns out the entire frozen-Food
division was contaminated.
Our V.P., erik casten,
Did a cost-Benefit analysis
of the problem.
The study found
that it would be cheaper
To pay off any lawsuit
Than to pull the bad products
off the shelves.
- Here you are.
- Thanks.
Oh, do you --
Do you want a --
No, thanks.
Um...
Mnh-Mnh.
I'm so nervous.
Casten's report estimated
how many people will die.
He looked at the data and decided
it was an acceptable number of deaths.
"An acceptable number
of deaths" -- Over food?
So supermarkets are selling
lillian products that will kill people.
Dr. Jameson, we won't let
that happen. I promise you.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
You've made me feel much better,
mr. Ford.
Oh. Um...you --
Uh, not "mr. Ford."
You -- You --
You should call him nate.
I appreciate it, nate.
Well, i-It's what we...
This, uh, casten, the V.P.,
uh, he's just a VS.P., right?
What -- What about
the c.E.O.?
I mean...
Uh, mr. Price.
He doesn't know anything about it.
That's why i was trying
to get the report --
To give it to him...
or the fda -- Anyone.
Well, okay,
what i'm gonna do --
I'm gonna go brief the team
about all of this.
Oh, um, no.
I've -- I've got a better idea.
I think i should go
and -- And --
- Oh, no, no, no. Don't be silly.
- Yeah. No, don't worry about it.
Because i-I think that you
should actually stay here,
Because dr. Jameson, she still
looks a little bit rattled.
That's a hell of a story.
So...
Yeah.
I'm gonna go brief the team.
Then i'll give you a call.
Oh. Okay.
How you doing over here?
Okay?
One more.
Thank you.
You got it.
Her name is katie.
Likes -- Wild horses.
Dislikes --
Vanilla tootaste.
Please stop talking.
- Hey.
- Well, i can certainly check.
How you doing?
Oh, i'm so in.
Hey, uh, eliot, what is that
blocking your button cam?
yeah, it's your ego.
Parker?
First 10 floors are free-Climbing heaven,
But after that, it's a slip and slide.
You have pretty hair.
You don't.
I just don't know
what you're doing up here.
You know,
you should be downstairs.
Why would i be downstairs
with her? I-I --
- Look, she's beautiful...
- we have a meeting, and i --
...she's available, and she's
into you -- I can tell.
How could you possibly tell?
Look, i appreciate what --
- And you've got things in common.
- ??? But i don't ???
You definitely have things
in common with her.
- Like what?
- Well, um, she's a scientist.
And, well, um...
You're --
You're a bit nerdy. Aren't you?
I'm -- I'm a --
I'm a bit nerdy?
And food --
She works with food.
Well, you eat, don't you?
I don't understand how she
could make this -- Look, i --
- Just -- Just think about it.
- No, i don't --
Just go with it.
Come on.
- Take a leap of faith.
- Nerdy? Seriously?
Trust me. I just wish you had someone
in your life. That's all i'm saying.
Yeah, but, sophie,
she's a client.
- Mm, that's an excuse.
- Oh...
When was the last time you had
a date, huh -- A real date?
- Stop.
- And with whom?
Hardison!
Mnh-Mnh.
I don't think that counts.
Are you, uh, you running recon
on lillian foods?
Uh, yeah?
Don't you think you should
consult with me first?
Did you -- Did he ju--
We do this all the time,
nate.
Hey, look, man, where do you
think my intel comes from?
For the last time,
there is no blueprint fairy.
Yeah, well, i want you to
pull them out. Do it now.
Look, we know what we're doing,
man. It's a food company.
No, no, you don't, no.
Not with a place like this.
You don't know
what you're doing.
I can try to transfer you
to the department again.
- Come with us, please.
- Sure.
Don't you go anywhere.
I'd give it exactly, uh --
Uh, two seconds
Before this becomes
a train wreck.
Hardison,
we got a problem.
What kind of problem?
They're mri'ing my pizza,
and their stance says "ex-Cia."
You can tell somebody work
for the cia just from how they stand?
It's a very distinctive
stance!
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
You are getting query spiked
all over the grid.
Nsa. Cia. Oss.
I-I don't even know what that --
You know what?
You want to play rough?
We gonna play rough.
Oh, we gonna play.
How...do you like me...
- Now?
- Yeah.
Oh.
Uh, eliot, you need
to get out of there...
...right now.
Working on it!
Parker, i'm coming out hot.
Okay. All clear out here.
Just me and...
Copy that.
I think i goone out here, too.
Hey, big boy.
What are you -- 240, 250?
I'll call you.
You know when i said
you had pretty hair?
I was lying.
Yeah, well, so was i
when i said you didn't.
Wait. Damn it!
What?
Haison!
Wait for it.
See?
See? It wasn't no problem.
I mean, i-I had it
under control.
You like the, uh,
the new clear image on the...
Button cams?
I-I upgraded. Yeah.
So, pizza-Delivery guy
was your big plan?
You know what, man?
It was recon. Okay?
Information gathering has historically
been a very safe and peaceful business.
And -- And it was
a food company!
It wasn't like
they was making weapons.
Listen, i-I've worked insurance
for companies like this.
Anyone gets their hands
on the company's food patents,
It could cost them billions.
And, by the way, they guard that stuff
better than defense contractors.
- Does that hurt?
- Yeah.
Well, that explains all the ex-Spooks
hanging around the lobby, then.
You know what?
You live and you learn.
No, i lived.
All right?
You sat behind a computer
and acted like kool moe dee.
What you call me?
Kool moe dee?
Like you even know anything
about kool moe dee.
I was gathering
very crucial information.
- Does that hurt?
- Yeah.
How about now?
How about you share that crucial
information with the rest of us?
Okay.
You -- You know what?
You ain't said nothing
but a word.
Stop.
Eliot. Guys. Eliot.
What are you doing?
She was poking me.
Don't. Man --
Lillian foods is the third-Largest
food company in the world.
Last year, made $12 billion.
This is the vice psident of the
frozen-Foods division -- Erik casten.
Erik with a "k,"
casten with a "c."
How is that relevant?
Oh. Eric with a "c" --
Nice and friendly,
Erik with a "k" -- Evil.
I didn't know that.
Everybody knows that.
According to dr. Jameson,
Erik with a "k" is trying to cover up
Salmonella found in the frozen dinners
So his division doesn't have to
pay out for that recall.
That's why i grow
my own food.
How do you find the time?
You make time.
I only sleep
90 minutes a day.
All right, so what we have to do is
we have to get ahold of casten's report
And make it public. It's on the servers.
How do we get into the building?
I'm so far ahead of you, man,
it's scary.
Look, i can't hack their system
from the outside,
So i sent a trojan phone.
It's hacker 101.
What i did was messenger
a smartphone with an extended battery
To an employee
that's on vacation.
Package sits
in the mail room,
It scans for wireless
and bluetooth access points.
Unfortunately, even their internal servers
are locked down like the cia,
So all i was able to get
was employee e-Mails.
Well, anything useful there?
Oh, yeah.
You know what?
Marie from payroll has a crush
on steve from accounts receivable.
Look, that's steve right there
on his vacation in florida from a month ago.
She likes him?
Really?
Oh, yeah. That man is a sexy
man-Beast right there.
Now, shannon and chris
from marketing,
They got a little fight going on
with lauren from ads.
Office politics.
God, it's lucky we don't --
We don't have that.
Everybody up in there is complaining about
this "state of the company" thing tomorrow.
And brian from i.T. --
That's it. That's it right
there. That's our way in.
Brian from i.T.?
No, he is not a team player.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's our -- That's our way in.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
That's it. That's it.
Yeah, the "state of the company"
meeting. Here we go.
- What is that?
- I don't know what that is.
- Me neither.
It's like state of the union --
- What is that?
- ???
Oh, right, right. No, you guys
never had real jobs. Yeah.
- Never.
- Of course not, man. Come on.
Right.
All right, so when i used to
work for iys,
We would do this
all the time.
The company --
Big companies,
They make their employees sit
for the entire day
And listen to these
boring speeches,
Lame entertainment,
bad food -- It's --
Ugh. I'm so glad i don't live
in the real world.
Yeah, and it's mandatory.
It's the only time that all the employees
Are away from their desk at the same time.
All right, so, we go in as caterers,
We download the report
While everyone's chucking back
the mini quiches -- Easy.
No. No, see,
it's a food company.
All the catering
is in-House.
The only outsiders involved in this whole big
operation are the entertainment.
And who would that be?
Oh, you're gonna love this.
Chronos the magnificent.
More like
chronos the jackass.
Look.
Multiple sexual-Harassment charges.
Even his assistant hates him.
That's kind of sad.
For my next trick,
i will need a volunteer.
Go ahead.
Put your hand up.
- I don't want to do it.
- Woman.
- I really don't want to go.
Don't make me go.
- Girl!
- Take one for the team.
- Okay! Me! Me!
Me! Me! Pick me!
You.
Come on up here.
The box is an sasj-6412.
This is how it works, all right?
Well...
- What's your name?
- Kara!
Yeah, kara!
Love you! Love you!
Silence!
Love you, too.
Sorry.
Well, kara...
Are you ready to step
into the box...
Of mystery?
Uh.I don't know.
I assure you,
it's perfectly safe.
I love you.
That's my girl.
That's my baby.
Sexy.
She been doing pilates.
Give kara a round
of applause.
Sexy stuff! Go ahead, girl.
Do what you do.
Ow!
- Hey! Ow!!
- Oh!
Let go!
She --
She's perfectly all right.
- Let go! Ow!
- Hey, kara! ???
Damn all that "she's all right."
Baby?
Um, baby?
Baby? Ma'am?
If you don't --
Just kidding.
Ha! Isn't she great?
Isn't -- Come on.
Snoodles.
Oh. Love you.
And thank you and you
and you and you!
Interlocking rings.
Hey, man, you --
You forgot one over here.
Just...
Thank you!
That's dope, man.
I like that.
Get off my stage!
Oh, look, y'all,
this --
It -- It ain't real.
That ain't even all that, man.
That's --
Get -- Get off --
Oh, my god!
Baby, i'm here!
I'm, like, totally here for you right now!
Somebody get on your cellphone!
-  I love you!
- Get a dentist! You.
I love you!
Oh, that's great.
Here you go.
He did what?
Yeah it's not as bad
as it sounds,
But, um, chronos is gonna be
held in custody for the next 24 hours.
Our event is in two hours.
We do have a replacement, though,
And he'll be with you any second.
I just need you to put his team
on the security list.
Pick a card.
Harry turner.
"Magician."
I know.
"Illusionist."
Magicians do kids' parties.
I do fortune 500 companies.
Uh, right this way, gang.
Whoa!
And who are these people?
Oh, this is my team.
I believe you spoke
to my manager.
This is nell carver.
All right?
And my illusions designer,
frank brunner.
And my lovely assistant, clea.
Hey, man.
I hope you have a doctor
in the house,
Because this man right here
is gonna blow your mind.
All right. Come on.
We're on a very tight schedule.
Nothing gets in or out of
this building without getting scanned.
These crates contain
my illusions, my life.
I'm not gonna reveal my secrets.
Come on.
That's not my problem!
Is it?
Could you please --
Yeah, i'll take care of this, harry.
Mr. Markland, um, i'm sure
we can figure something out.
- It's not gonna be possible --
- Yeah, let's pull up the van, frank,
And let's get out of here.
- Harry...
- yeah, i think so.
This is ridiculous!
What the hell is going on here?
- Mr. Price. Sir...
- this is --
Harry turner,
illusionist extraordinaire.
You are mr. Price,
C.E.O. Of this company?
I am.
What's going on here?
I would like very much, sir,
To give your people
a wonderful show,
But your, uh, your doorman here would like
to look at our boxes of illusions and --
And destroy the illusion.
Markland, just lighten up,
will you?
- Just lighten up, would you?
- It's a magic show,
- for pete's sake.
- For pete's sake.
Okay, we're clear.
Let him out.
It's a good job you're not
claustrophobic, eliot.
- I was when i was a kid.
Take this damn thing.
- Oh, all right.
- Really? How'd you get over it?
- Here, parker.
I locked myself in a woodshed
Behind my house for a couple nights.
After that, i was fine.
That is so funny. I was scared of the dark
and did exactly the same thing.
You ready?
That's not the same thing.
What's wrong with you?
So, you -- You --
You're actually enjoying this.
Oh, you know, being a magician,
It's the next best thing to being a con artist.
You know, it's all about
misdirection and control.
So, uh, no one actually told you
that you can't control life?
You see, this is why
you're not in a relationship.
No, sophie, i'm just very focused on
my work right now, you know?
I was out of control before.
Now i'm in control.
It's a good thing.
So, what you're doing is trading
one addiction for another.
Hey, man, do you know
how to do this magic stuff?
Oh, no, absolutely.
Positively.
Yeah. No, it's all about...
the rabbit.
You know, having --
By the way, where's --
Where did the rabbit,
uh...
Uh, okay. Uh...
well, okay, okay.
Hardison,
let's go over the plan.
Okay, the show opens
with our friend erik casten...
Delivering the
"state of the company" speech.
The speech is scheduled
to last an hour,
Giving myself, eliot,
and parker enough time
To go down to the server room,
hack the servers,
Download the report,
and get back downstairs.
So, massively,
there will be no magic show.
Oh, no, there
might be a magic show.
No, absolutely. We might want
to treat these people
To the illusionist
extraordinaire, right?
Yeah, you, um, you really do
need a girlfriend.
No, all i need is the...
is the rabbit.
Where's...
- Yeah.
- H-Hardison.
- Hmm?
Have the rabbit?
It's a real magic hat, man.
Where's the rabbit?
- I thought you had it.
- Come on, fan out. N out.
Let's find the rabbit.
Damn it, hardison!
I never had it.
Sophie, you're on.
Molly, i just want to say thanks
for all you do. It means a lot.
- Mr. Price. Nell carver.
- Hi, nell.
Yeah, i-I -- We met earlier,
actually. I work with harry.
- Oh, the -- The magician.
- Yeah, that's right.
So, listen,
um, there's this little thing.
When harry does these
-- These corporate gigs,
You know, he likes to work
in a few little tidbits
About the employees, you know,
just funny little things. Mm.
I knew you'd want to help.
I wondered if i could just
scribble down a couple of things.
Oh, boy.
- Let's see. Um, well, one is dave bickle.
- Bickle.
Dave bickle loves his coffee.
- Loves his coffee.
- Takes it very seriously.
Yeah. And, uh, who else we got?
- Oh.
- I --
He...just loves his coffee?
Yeah. Oh, i mean, he pours
down... oh, i see.That's it
I thought you said you had to have a
corporate i.D. Badge to get in the elevator.
We do. We actually need
one from a top executive.
Where are we gonna get that?
Sophie's sending one
to me right now --
By magic.
And then there's, uh, sam weston,
Except we call him "spam" weston,
Because this guy forwards e-Mail
all over the company.
-Unbelievable.
- "Spam" weston. I get it. That's great.
Now, harry is gonna
work wonders with that.
That's -- That is
fabulous. Thank you so much.
See, sophie's smartphone is picking up
the rfid signal from the big boss's i.D.
All she had to do was
cozy up next to him and...
go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Go.
You picked his pockets without
actually stealing anything? Cool.
It's what i do. A man.
A phone. No limits.
How about "a man. A phone. No action"?
Come on, man, you left that out
there like a hanging curveball.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
To deliver this year's "state
of the company" address,
I've chosen a rising star.
This is a man whose work
ethic, whose creativity...
...and utter disregard for human life...
...and whose dedication to our mission
Make him uniquely qualified, really,
To talk with us about how far we've come
And also how far we still have to go.
I am honored to introduce
vice president erik casten.
Erik, come on up.
Give him a little moment
before, uh, he sinks himself.
You know, i wrote a
speech about this company,
Which i have been proud to
call my home for five years.
But then i thought,
Doesn't our record-Breaking
third quarter speak for itself?
So, with that -- And
the open bar -- In mind,
I'd just like to say...
thanks, everybody.
And let's give a warm welcome to...
- harry turner, illusionist extraordinaire!
Parker, i need my assistant now!
Yeah. Yeah, speaking of that -- How
come parker gets to be the assistant?
How come nate gets to be the magician?
I do card tricks, too. I do great card tricks.
Yeah, exactly. That's
what i was just saying!
Does anybody want to do my job?
Huh? I get punched and kicked.
I just think that if it was me, we'd
be better off -- - I gotta go. Go!
hello, lillian foods!
It's such an honor to be here with you.
it's, um...
lillian foods. When
i think of lillian foods, i think of...
i think of frozen pizza.
What am i supposed to do with that?
- Hook it to something.
- Ain't nothing to hook it to.
We're gonna do a lot
of magic here today.
- You hear that?
- Yeah.
Ah! My wonderful assistant,
The spectacular, unpredictable clea!
Wow.
Wave. Say hi. Something.
Isn't she magnificent?
Oh, look at that.
I could've just hooked it to the rail.
My bad.
How am i supposed to get down?
Go change!
Really, man... you
didn't see that coming?
Not funny.
Mr. Casten. What
happened to your speech?
While everyone's busy with the show,
I've got some things to
take care of upstairs.
Alone.
All clear.
Well, if you wanted to make coffee
disappear, what would you do? Hmm?
Well, you
know, da--
Bickle.
David bickle knows about
disappearing coffee,
Don't you, dave? Hmm?
Right?
How long is this gonna take?
As long as it has to take.
You know, i was just pulled up to the
ceiling of an elevator by my pants,
So do not take that tone with me.
Go. Go!
It's casten. What the hell's
he doing in the server room?
Let's find out.
What are you doing?
All the employee phones in this building
are hooked up to the internal wi-Fi.
You remember the trojan
phone? It works both ways.
See, i can use the server
to access his phone.
And once i'm in, i can see
through his phone's camera.
You can do that?
Oh, you'd be surprised at what i can do.
He's deleting the files.
Guys.
You remember that bright idea we had about accessing
the server room while everyone was at the show?
Parker, where are you?
We're not the only ones.
He's gonna wipe
everything from the system.
People are gonna die.
So, do you like working
at lillian foods? Yes?
stall, nate. Stall. Yes.
Ah, here she is now.
Uhthe lovely clea!
Yes! Clea! Very nice!
Ho! Thank you veryuch, clea.
I'll just put that right here.
I have something for you, clea.
Something you might like very much.
Mm. It's right here --
Somewhere. Ah. Here it is.
It's not working.
Have to have another way
to access the servers, guys.
Already on it.
Leigh, i need secondary
acss to the servers.
Try the junction room. It has
one i.O. Station. And be careful.
- Bartender?
yeah.
- Can i have another?
- Okay.
Can you get to the servers from here?
Oh, yeah. If anything, the computer
systems are more vulnerable up here.
- The only catch is, security is way gnarlier.
- What about casten?
It'll take him some time.
See, he has to find and
delete all the copies.
We just need one.
Uh, guys, i-I can't
bypass the biometrics.
I need a fingerprint.
And it has to be somebody
with pretty highlearance.
Shh.
I'm on it.
...supernatural forces.
But here at lillian foods...
- mr. Price, mr. Price!
- What?
We're ready for you.
It's time for your
bit of the magic show.
- No, i didn't -- - We did
clear it with your assistant.
She said that you wanted to
show a more fun side this year.
So, let's go.
Um...okay.
But -- But is it
gonna take much time?
No, no, no, no. It's
gonna be over in a...
...flash.
thank you!
And now, to help me
with my next illusion,
A man you know all too well,
A man the h.R. Department
likes to call a "hire" power...
mr. William taylor
price, ladies and gentlemen!
Mr. Price, mr. Price, if you could just
come and stand next to me right here.
Right here, sir.
That's fantastic.
Now, there's something
i'd like you to hold on to.
Okay? Just come stand over here.
That's right. Just keep
that in your hand like this.
- Okay, now, i want you to concentrate.
- Why -- Why am i holding --
No questions.
i mean,
believe in the magic.
Yes, believe in the magic.
Abracadabra.
All right, are you believing?
I...yeah.
Yes, what are you thinking
of? A number between 1 and 7.
That's good. Don't tell me.
Okay, now i want you to hold
out your arm like this. Okay?
And on my count, you're
gonna open your hand.
- Look here.
- What --
Ready and open!
Thank you very much, mr. Price.
It was 6.
It was 6. Sure, it was.
Certainly. It was 6.
Who would like this?
What?
It's not optical.
They're using active capacitance.
See, what happens is, it measures the change
in voltage across the microridges of the --
Can you get in or not?
You...
gummy frogs?
Gummy frogs have the same
resistance as human skin --
What'd i say?
That's a low-Tech hack right there.
It's just a piece
of ca--
There may also be a retinal scanner.
Retinas? How am i gonna get his retinas?
Well, a proper assistant
would know the answer to that.
Okay, hold tight.
And now, uh...
how many of you would like
to see your boss disappear?
Hmm? Show of hands.
Uh, now, if we could bring mr. Price
back up here, that would be great.
Mr. Price. Mr. Price...
mr. Price, how are you doing today, sir?
i --
We did this.
See, you're supposed to do it like this.
Next time, you jump
down the elevator shaft.
Oh, stop it. Everybody
knows you love that.
right this way, mr. Price.
Now say goodbye to mr. Price,
because you may never see him again.
This illusion is very, very difficult,
Especially for someone who
has never performed it before,
Such as myself.
Mr. Price?
y-Yeah?
Okay.
Say goodbye!
Goodbye!Goodbye! Goodbye!Goodbye!
So, that's how they do that trick.
- All right. I'll go check it out.
- Right behind you.
Hello? Hello? Hello?!
- Hello!
- Shh! Shh! Shh!
- No, mr. Price.
- Am i moving?
Don't make a peep.
The audience, they're lapping it up.
- You're doing great!
- Yeah
This is --
This is good.
I...think.
Oh! Terrible, i know.
Now are you ready to
see dear old mr. Price?
Yes?
Clea, we must do this.
One, two, three!
Voil?!
Okay!
Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you very much!
I don't see why i wasn't the assistant.
well, why wasn't i?
"Abracadabra." I could do that.
stop.
It's all yours.
hello?Hello?
Thank you!
I can hear you breathing out there!
Hello?
Please take care of this bird.
You said take care of it!
hello?
Would you move the -- Move
the box. Move -- Move the box.
Oh, thank god.
I was really beginning to think
this whole thing was gonna be
Bickle getting back at me
for all the coffee j-- Hey!
Doing a hell of a job, man.
You're killin' 'em out there!
It's really dark in here.
Bickle? "Spam" weston?
Are you guys in on this together?
Who else is out there? Come on!
Now, uh, ca, if you'll
pull the end of this rope.
And the other one. Blow on this.
Now blow on this.
There we go.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
we're too
late. They're all gone.
Casten deleted all copies of the report.
Markland, i'm on the way down.
Dr. Jameson can cry all she wants.
She's got nothing on me now.
Markland.
Besides the server room,
Where else cou someone
access protected files?
Uh, the junction room. Why?
We may have a breach.
There it is. We have
movement in the elevator!
Lock it all down.
Done.
Go to the
elevator -- Now!
Uh-Oh.
"Uh-Oh"? What do
you mean, "uh-Oh"?
this isn't funny any
longer! Step out of the elevator.
Oh, that "uh-Oh."
Help!
- Step out of the elevator.
- No.
Hello?!
Heo?!
Stop! Help!
I can hear you.
Just stop it!
Hey, nate.
You know that trick where you make
the guy disappear from a locked room?
I could really use that right now.
What's wng, clea?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, the --
Is there a doctor in the house?!
Echo team, report.
team is down. Magician's
assistant took them out.
Repeat that last. Did
you say "magician"?
This is no longer a joke! Come on!
Oh, my goodness, stop!
If you can hear my voice out there,
I'm telling you, you're fired!
Stop it!
hello?
Hello?
Show's over. We're blown.
Hello
Nate, bring down the curtain now.
Hello?
Hello?!
And now -- Now it's time
for our grand finale!
Clea? Grand finale.
Thank god.
This, it turns out,
is not the men's room.
But y'all should really have
signs up and down the hallways,
'Cause i been stuck up in
here for about an hour, man.
Ironic, i know, because
of the whole magic,
But see, i build the magic
trick. My man does them.
The drive.
The -- I'm s-- The,
uh -- I don't drive.
That drive. Oh, okay.
I see what you --
Ah, yes!
Now, i'd like you to
count with us, please.
Are you sure this is gonna work?
50-50 chance.
One...
one!One! One!One!
Where is the rest of your team?
I don't even know what
you're talking about, man.
Two...
two!Two! Two!Two!
Three!
Three!Three! Three!Three!
go through the
wing! Check the exit door!
Magic tricks?
hey,
man, you --
You lookin' at all my stu--
That's all my business.
You know what? You, sir,
Should expect a very strongly worded
letter from the magicians local 77.
The labels on frozen dinners
say "heat to 161 degrees."
That kills the bacteria.
It's on the package.
The world is a very dangerous place
For people who can't
follow simple instructions.
I'm sorry.
They're outside in the gray van.
Good man.
Was all that necessary, man?
I got asthmatic tendencies.
I don't see a van.
You have five seconds to tell
me what's really going on here.
Do i? Really? Okay.
You're a little strong-Arm, ain't you?
I blogged your website about that.
- The lillian foods website.
- Did you pocket-Dial me?
What?
Give me that!
Who the hell is this?
The secret of magic is
misdirection, mr. Casten.
The magician?
What are you doing on my phone?
Misdirection.
So you went after the
incriminating report.
And i deleted it.
Every copy.
Absolutely.
But you know, i don't
think all that security
Is in place just to
protect those reports.
Do you? I mean, uh...
what's really valuable
on those servers? Hmm.
We're too late. They're all gone.
Casten deleted all copies of the report.
do you have access to
the company's food patents?
Yes.
Yes, i do.
yes, i had my
assistant download them.
Magician, thief, whatever.
We have your man and his hard drive.
You never got the patents
out of the building.
No, no, no.
You got those patents
out of the building.
All we had to do was pick up your phone.
Now, these patents represent
hundreds of millions of dollars
Of your company's present
and future earnings.
They're on your
cellphone --
Downloaded the day you were
alone in the server room.
See, i can use the server
to access his phone.
You can do that?
Oh, you'd be surprised what i can do.
I wodn't want to be caught
in that act. Would you?
Huh, mr. Casten?
What do you want?
Well, first, i'd like
you to let my friend go.
Next, you'll pull the entire
frozen-Foods line from the market.
You have to be kidding me!
Do you understand how much
that'll cost the company?
Yes, well, we're sending a
specialist to help with the recall.
You'll also issue a formal apology.
along with your
letter of resignation.
You know what? They had me in a box!
Get him upstairs! Clear
out his office right now!
Now, why don't we give the
lady a nice round of applause?
And your queen should be...
this right here.
Stole it.
You -- You
can't do that.
I'm finishing off the kung pao.
Okay, yeah, i got three
possible clients to research!
Just want to finish.
I've got an idea. Listen, why
don't you give dr. Jameson a ring?
I'm working. Working over here.
put it in. All right.
I'm not even looking.
What?
He's fine.
We practically had to beg
him to come back, all right?
He's not drinking. He's
at the top of his game.
I got to be honest with you. I can't
even believe we pulled this one off.
Well, that's the
problem. He keeps winning.
And every time he wins, he believes a
little bit more that he can control...
life.
It's what gets him through the day.
What happens when he loses?
The first time he lost, it broke him.
He breaks again,
I don't think even we
could pick up the pieces.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net