the first priority for new England
is to get their defense healthy.
Their defense is fine, you morons.
They allowed an average
of 10 points per game last year.
...throw for, you know --
He was, what,
I think he was 7 of...
everybody down! Down!
Hell!
Oh, no!
Get away from the vehicle!
ugh!
Davai! Davai!
Davai! Davai! Davai!
I've been a cop with the Boston
P.D. For over 20 years.
My wife got laid off
a couple months ago,
So I picked up some shifts with
a security company to make ends meet.
Mr. Cospito, you were doing
a side job for Kerrity Diamonds?
Please, call me Joey.
I'm feeling like an old man
these days as it is.
I was hauling about $10
million in diamonds that day.
I'd done the same route five,
maybe six times before --
No problem.
Armored-Car drivers are supposed
to stay with the vehicle, right?
I'm a cop first.
My instinct was stop
a robbery in progress.
Hell of a job I did, huh?
One guard for a delivery that size?
Ah, these days, with companies
pinching anywhere they can,
Happens all the time.
It sounds to me
like an inside job.
Except they thought
the inside man was me.
Hey, I know --First
guy you look at
Is the blue-Collar guy
who's got money trouble.
Until this investigation's
closed and my name is cleared,
I'm suspended from the
force without pay.
Yeah, although, not
much of an investigation.
No witnesses, no prints.
Trace elements of
the explosive they used,
Fast-Burning det cord.
Medical bills are piling up,
And there's no work for a guy with
a bum shoulder and an open investigation.
All right, listen, Joey,
we're gonna do everything we
can to help you with that, all right?
Never thought it would be so tough
Just to try and keep a roof
over my family's head, you know?
Yeah.
Who's the other drink for?
Oh, that -- She's, uh...
Nobody.
Leverage s02e08
The rich and powerful,
they take what they want.
We steal it back for you.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@CC
Sync:FRS@–°∏£ ”Í‰Ï
And sometimes, bad guys
make the best good guys.
We provide...
Leverage
Jim Kerrity III --
He took over Kerrity diamonds
four years ago after his old man retired.
And in that small amount of time,
He managed to drive the business
straight into the ground
By living way beyond his means.
I'm talking drugs, booze, women.
According to his credit cards,
same as -- What? What? What?
-Why? What?
-What?
-What are you doing? What?
-It's distracting.
Well, the couch is just
feeling a little empty.
Eliot, will you please
sit next to parker?
No. Iím sitting here now.
Guys, guys, all right,
we all miss Sophie.
We just have to adapt.
-I got this. Move.
-Please.
-Go. Bye.
-Go.
You happy?
Now, Kerrity's finances
are a mess --
Maxed out,
maxed out, overdrawn.
Now, according to the insurance claim,
He stands to gain $9 million
from the armored-Car robbery.
You know, a guy like this,
You know, he gets in over his head,
And his insurance policy starts
to look pretty attractive.
Hires a couple of thugs,
knocks off his own truck.
It's a sweet payout, too.
He gets the insurance claim,
plus he still has the diamonds.
Mm-Hmm, and honest people
like Joey take the heat.
You know, the thing about this
That most people don't
understand is insurance fraud --
It's a lot of red tape.
I mean, a big claim like this --
It'll take about a year before
Kerrity sees any of the money.
And the bill collectors --
They're not gonna wait around.
-He's got to fence the diamonds.
-He can't.
What do you mean?
His diamonds are GIA-Certified,
VVS clarity, all about two carats.
That's my clicker.
Who stole the polar star?
Who stole the gem of Gibraltar?
Damiani raid? Me.
I know diamonds.
And our bad guy can't fence those diamonds
Because stones that size have an
I.D. Number laser-Inscribed on them.
Oh, so, itís like a stolen car.
You got to clean the vin
before you can sell them.
How do you get
that I.D. Number off?
With a special laser,
but only three guys can do it --
Antwerp, Dubai, Tel Aviv.
And as of right now,
Boston, right?
I mean, Kerrity
has to move his diamonds,
So we convince him
that we're the only people
Who can make them clean enough to move.
Get them to bring the diamonds to us.
And when he shows up --
Oh, Hardison, can you put
the crime-Scene photos...
Can -- Can...
State police guy,
lieutenant Bonanno.
Yeah. So, we drop Kerrity on his
lap with the stolen diamonds.
Lieutenant Bonanno
drops the hammer.
Our guy gets cleared,
gets his job back.
Pardon me, but I don't mean
to stop the fun train --
We're out a grifter here.
I know who we can call.
No, we're not gonna call Sophie.
No, she has asked for space,
and we're gonna honor that.
No.
Hardison, you're gonna be our grifter.
-I'm listening.
-What? No, no, no.
-Parker, youíll be the roper.
-What?
Cute dress, heels --
You'll be fine.
Sure. Iíll be fine.
Eliot, you be the muscle.
-Hi.
-Hello.
Buy me a drink?
You got it.
So...
Aah!
Ugh!
parker? Parker?
Aah!
Yeah, Iíll be fine.
I will not be fine.
I stabbed that guy with a fork!
Parker, parker, relax.
It's fine.
Listen, go to Nateís
storage cupboard,
And you're gonna find
a sexy little mini dress
And my emergency jimmy choose.
Jimmy who?
You have a body
in Nateís closet?
Shoes, parker!
Didn't I teach you any--
All right, listen,
okay, this is the important bit.
Do you still have the Rosalind
diamond you stole in Perth?
Yes.
Wear it.
The diamond will speak for you.
You won't have to say a word.
This is the key to the grift.
You just trust the character.
Say nothing. Trust the diamond.
I can do that.
Don't tell Nate I called.
I won't.
Where's the mark?
Kerrity's at the bar --
Gold Rolex, purple tie.
Say nothing. Trust the diamond.
Say nothing and trust the diamond.
Parker, what are you saying?
Nothing and trusting the diamond.
I'll have an Appletini.
-They make them strong here.
-Oh, do they?
Is that an Australian pink diamond?
Is that the Rosalind?
That's an impressive,
uh, replica.
It's the original.
I'll have to take
your word for it.
I have people who certify
these things for me.
"do you want to take a closer..."
You want a closer look?
No stabbing, parker.
This is a very famous diamond.
How did you get it?
It was a gift
from my boyfriend.
Ah.
He works in diamonds.
So do I, and I would love
to talk shop with the man
who managed to get his
hands on the, uh...
The Rosalind diamond.
-no.
-N--
Come here.
What have I said?
What have I said
about new people? Huh?
What have I said?
Hey, it's okay.
This guy works in diamonds.
He wants to talk
business or something.
All right.
Lay the arms down, brother.
He's cool.
You'll have to
excuse my bodyguard.
He's touchy.
It's because he's a
mute, all right?
Yeah, well, my bodyguards
don't talk much, either.
Well, looks like we found
our armored-Car robbers.
Gonna shoot through
your own mate, then?
To be honest with you,
I never liked him.
Legit. Goon
squad and all, innit?
Stand down.
Jim Kerrity.
You're Jim Kerrity --
Kerrity diamonds?
oh, no.
Brother, you got
hit hard last week.
The heist, yes.
That was me.
So, did you use the Romanovs
back there or just hire out?
I'm in the business, jimmy boy.
I can smell an inside job.
So, what do you do
in the business, mister...
I'm a thief.
They call me "the ice man."
"ice man"?
No, Hardison, you have to have
a light touch. Undersell.
What kind of a thief
calls himself a thief?
An uncatchable one
with a brilliant reputation.
You've seen my work in Perth.
The polar star?
Nicked it.
The gem of Gibraltar?
The Damiani raid?
Distraction while I nicked
everything in the vault next door.
Big stones, trust me.
Yeah, well, then, I shouldn't
be seen talking to you.
Right, right, right,
'cause two criminals can't
talk business while shooting pool.
Bitch of it is,
nicking them's butter --
Moving them's the pain.
Yes, especially with
those inscribed I.D. Numbers.
No, no, no, no.
I got this laser, see?
Only one in this
country, mind you.
This thing I had to bring over Piece
by sodding piece from Turkmenistan.
It can scrub an I.D.
Clean off any diamond --
Re-virginized.
And what kind of fee do you charge
for such a specialized service?
30%.
-5%.
-30%.
No way in hell.
See, that's the
discounted rate, brother,
'Cause anything lower than
that is an insulted rate,
'Cause it's an insult
to me, savvy?
You, uh...you ring me
when you wisen up, yeah?
Thanks...
But no thanks, brother.
ice man?
-hey, I put a lot of work into that character.
-Seriously?
No, no, no, no.
I bought new clothes --
Ugly as hell, too.
-This always happens when you go on the grift, Hardison, okay?
-I-I put stories on the website.
You go way too big.
Yeah, Sophie told me to say
as little as possible.
Let the character do the work.
When did, uh,
Sophie say that?
A long time ago.
Maybe last Christmas.
I don't even think
it was Sophie.
I'm gonna go put
more pressure on Kerrity.
I want you guys to
be on the clear-Out.
Ice man, play it cool.
That's just
an awful, awful name.
-Genius.
-See?
It's genius.
When you get in
too deep on this,
I ain't bailing
your ass out.
I don't need you
to bail me out.
Iím the ice man.
Not...gonna...help.
We did our job,
and you haven't paid.
I told you --
You do the job,
The insurance pays out,
and then you get your 10%.
Sell the diamonds while you wait
for the insurance money, hmm?
Use the Englishman
to launder them.
Yeah, Iíll do that when his 30%
comes out of your 10%.
You know that is a mathematical
impossibility, hmm?
There's a Mr. Sterling here
from the insurance company.
What did I tell you?
He's probably here
to drop off a check, okay?
Get out of here.
I'll call you.
Come on. Come on.
Yes!
Mr. Sterling, Iím, uh, Iím Jim Kerrity.
So glad you could stop by.
I just wanted
to introduce myself.
Your claim has raised
a lot of red flags,
And Iím in the
red-Flag department.
My company has asked me
to review your entire policy,
Just to make sure
no mistakes were made.
I can assure you that nobody
takes security more seriously than I do.
In fact, that's the reason
I hired what I was told
Was the best armored-Car
service in town.
My vault has
a seismic sensor.
No other company
in Boston has that.
Yeah, well, Iím sure all that will be taken
into consideration, Mr. Kerrity, yes, mm-Hmm.
Good. So, uh, how long
do you think this is gonna take?
'Cause Iíve got a
business to run here.
Assuming no problems arise,
You should expect to
see a check in, uh...
Oh, seven to nine...
Days?
months.
Mm. Yeah.
Wow.
Well...
I'll be in touch.
Mm-Hmm. Mm-Hmm.
I know.
He's driving me crazy.
How, huh? I'm backup.
They can't rely on me.
All right.
Hey...
Thanks.
Don't tell Nate I called.
Who was that?
Cable company.
Whoa! Whoa!
What are you people doing here?
We work here.
Who are you?
We're with Osha.
We issued a class-1 evacuation notice
for this facility, effective 24 hours ago.
This place is on lockdown
for chemical exposure.
Did nobody read the memo?
Did nobody read the memo?!
You, cough!
what chemicals?
Given the setup
for this place,
It could be a matrix of
solid-Phase sulfates, nitrates --
That's inside me?
Honey, your lungs are
a parking lot, sweetheart.
And in that parking lot,
The diagonal lines
are painted with poison.
People, move towards the door.
All right?
Do not inhale unless you are
at least 50 feet from the entrance!
This should all be taken care of
by tomorrow, so nothing...
okay, Iíve got a visual.
Where is Mr. Ice?
He's late.
He's always late.
Oh.
Hmm. Subtle.
The ice man cometh.
Let me introduce you
to my laser, Glinda.
You see, Iíve found that laser fluences
below the diamond graphitization
threshold are most effective.
Wouldn't you say?
Yeah.
Did you bring the diamond?
Two carats, very few flaws --
My salesman said.
She's a beaut.
Sheila, get us a pop.
Because this would be classified I.F.,
An internally flawless,
two-Carat round cut diamond,
It should be easier to oblate.
you got that, parker?
How is this gonna fool him?
He's not looking
at the diamond.
He's looking
at the I.D. Number.
I.D. Numbers are etched at a
depth Between 5 and 7 microns.
Using nanoblation, The U.V.
Laser pulses irradiate the etching.
Thank you, sweets.
Should be about done.
It's like it was never there.
I could do the rest in a day,
But Iím only here
for another week.
I've got a thing in Antwerp.
All right, well, let's --
Let's do it tomorrow?
-Done.
-Excellent.
Mr. Ice.
All right, nice work, guys.
Tomorrow, when he shows up
with the diamonds,
The state police will be there.
Why? So they can
arrest Harrisonís ego?
be cool, baby -- Ice cool.
Hey, who wants to go for a spin?
I can't believe
you rented a Ferrari.
Rented? Iíll get
a ride home with Eliot.
Y'all are just jealous.
Oh, they're just jealous, baby.
Don't worry about that.
Look at you --
Looking better than green...
You, my friend, are the
answer to all my problems.
what exactly are we celebrating?
We are...stealing
Kerrityís diamonds...
...again!
You guys are gonna
scrump his jewels?
No, not you guys --
Us guys.
We know where the diamonds
are kept in the vault.
We need someone to bust
the diamonds out of the vault.
That's ??
??
We're going tonight.
You clean the stones
with your laser.
We sell them
and make a ton of money.
Diamond Jim is dropping
the stones by my lab tomorrow.
Why don't you just
pick it up in transit?
Is that what the ice man would do, huh?
It's not really
my style, but --
Too many variables. We have
a way in and out of a vault.
We take diamonds in a
controlled situation.
We'll be a long way gone
Before Kerrity notices he's been robbed.
What?
Is there a problem?
No.
To our success.
Nostrovya.
Yeah, um, cheers, mate.
I need -- I need to
make a quick call,
Bug the old lady, let her know Iím not
making it in tonight. You know birds.
Of course.
Yeah, yeah.
Sheila, not making it in tonight.
Yeah, work thing. Bugger all.
Hardison?
Are you calling me in character?
I told you, butternut, it's work.
I can't get out of it.
What accent is that?
Ooh, you --
You've been nabbed.
- Afraid so.
- Is it the mark?
No. No, muffin, no.
Oh, it's the goons.
You oversold the part.
You fell into the trap of
the overzealous henchmen.
Look, don't worry about
it. It happens all the time.
Just -- Well, as long
as they're not Russians.
It's gonna be a bit of a problem.
Is it the Russians? I'm
gonna have to phone Nate.
Leave it off, crumpet.
No, no, no, no, no, listen, Hardison,
You -- You cannot talk
your way out of Russians.
I mean, you -- You can
stall them, maybe, for a bit.
But whatever you do, do not tell
them you can do anything else.
Smooches.
Love her.
So, do these other
blokes talk, or just you?
No.
Let me show you the plan.
Hey, Hardison, I just got
an interesting phone call.
Sophie tells me you've been
recruited by the Russians.
I had courtside seats, man.
Tell Hardison if he makes it out alive,
I'm gonna snap him in half.
Uh, Eliot says "hi."
So, what's the plan there, ice man?
Just so Iím clear,
you want me to help you
Break into Kerrityís vault
and steal his diamonds.
Oh, beautiful.
We blow the floor of the
vault and climb through.
So, what you're saying is
We're gonna explode through the
ceiling of the tunnel using det cord
And climb into the
vault through the floor.
Yes.
This is what I just say.
Det cord -- That's how
they blew the armored truck.
Exploding through the floor
will set the seismic sensor off.
The tunnel's a terrible way in.
Hardison, you're gonna have to
tell them their plan won't work.
The tunnel is a horrible way in.
I heard you, parker.
Yeah, you know, Iím -- I'm -- I'm
-- I'm sor-- I'm sorry, comrades,
But your plan is ronk.
See, the explosion will
trip the seismic sensor.
We'll have the feds on
our arses in no time.
Well, then, the world's greatest thief
Have to take us another way, hmm?
Yeah.
I'll get you into Kerrityís vault.
No need to be pissy, mate.
Oh, yes, of course you will.
Now, listen, Hardison, you're
gonna have to figure out a way
To buy some time so we
can get you out of this.
Yeah, get busy.
Guys, guys, I can't make any
sense of Hardison's files.
You can't track him, man. He's
usually the one that does the tracking.
Yeah, well, maybe he left it on, huh?
- What if we just tell him to make a run for it?
- Well, they'll kill him.
Well, if he goes along with their
plan now, they'll get arrested.
Look, we got to find another
way for Hardison to break in.
- We need a closer look at the vault.
- Yeah, Iím working on it. I-I...
here -- Hair spray.
You're gonna need this.
Let me ask you a question, man. If Hardison
helps these Russians steal the evidence,
How are we gonna prove that
Kerrity set up the robbery?
I'm working on it. I-I...
do not call Sophie.
Mr. Sterling...
good news, I hope.
Well, it's too early to tell.
The claim is on your jeweler's
block coverage policy.
In order to verify the
eligibility of your coverage,
I'm gonna need to see your vault.
I'm sure you understand,
if there's any discrepancy
Between what you say your security is
And what your security actually is,
Well, that would invalidate the claim.
I can assure you my vault
is as good as I claim.
All right, all right.
I'll show it to you myself. Come on.
13-Ton
steel door --
Can withstand 12 hours of drilling.
Now, the door can withstand
up to 12 hours' drilling.
You can't use force.
The lock has a million
possible combinations,
And Iím the only one
who knows the combo.
The magnetic sensors are deactivated
By punching a color
code into the RGB keypad.
If he has an RGB keypad, we're buggered.
They're unhackable.
RGB keypad? Let me see.
Move the camera left. No, vault left.
All right. Then you
have to do this my way.
Remove the sensor while keeping
the magnetic field intact.
You're going to need a 4-Inch...
...a 4-Inch by 4-Inch
aluminum plate,
Double-Sided tape, and a
Philips-Head screwdriver.
Come on.
Got it.
Pressure-Sensitive tiles,
Disabled with the keypad right here.
Two cameras. Who monitors the feeds?
The guard upstairs
-- 24 hours a day.
I also have a monitor in my office.
Hmm. Heat sensors, motion sensors?
Yes, but to minimize false alarms,
The alarm only goes off if both
heat and motion are detected.
The keypad over there disables them.
Please?
Hardison's not gonna be able to do
anything if the heat sensors are on.
Nate, use the hair spray.
It creates a film that blocks the heat.
Heat sensor over here, and
this is the seismic sensor.
Any sound louder than my
voice, and it triggers.
The alarm will sound.
You know, I noticed your
box-Numbering system is off.
It goes from 82 to 84.
It's -- Yes, it's
very, uh, strange.
It's, um...
ah, it's right here.
Oh, there it is. 83.
Sorry. My mistake.
Of course. What's that?
Security fog.
If the alarm triggers,
that door locks down,
And the vault fills with a
glycol-Based, nontransparent fog.
Visibility is zero.
You can't steal what you can't see.
And the fog is triggered by the floor?
Triple-Wired. It'll go off
at the touch of the tiles,
The motion sensor,
and the seismic sensor.
Lockdown, full fog, cops on the way.
You are very proud of your security
system, aren't you, Mr. Kerrity?
I spare no expense, Mr. Sterling.
How bad is it?
There's no way Hardisonís gonna
be able to break into that vault.
What is Hardison gonna do?
No, Hardison is gonna pretend
to break into the vault.
Yeah, well, hopefully, the Russians
will only pretend to kill him.
No one's getting killed.
We're gonna break in for him.
All right, we're gonna
do this quick and dirty.
You guys break into the
vault before Hardison does
So the Russians think he's doing it.
Why not? He's been taking credit
for my work all day anyway.
And then Hardison will lead the Russians
into the vault a few paces behind you.
Hey, I got something.
Hardison must have hacked into
the security feed before he left.
Well, well.
I'm just gonna have keep
Kerrity out of his own vault.
So...brilliant plan to get us inside?
Oh, believe it.
So, uh...what deposit box
are the stolen diamonds in?
You get us in...
we'll tell you.
Wow, that looks beautiful.
$300,000 on your neck.
Oh, Amy, Iím gonna meet you
at the bar, sweetie, okay?
You'll earn that later. Let's go.
Excellent. This had better be important.
Yeah. Can we talk somewhere private?
When did he get here?
Yo, yo. Late night, man.
Is there a register
Iím supposed to look at?
Sorry, buddy.
Okay, parker, you're
clear. Come on down.
The, uh, inspection of your
vault did reveal a few issues.
The magnetic sensor is an s-2000.
That's right. It's the latest one.
Sorry, but, uh, your policy indicates
That it is an s-950 model,
And that, my friend, is a discrepancy.
It's a better version.
Yeah, well, no, I mean,
Mr. Kerrity, you know,
Given this new -- Uh,
this new information,
I'm sure that my company will most
certainly deny your, uh, your claim.
Look, I could be drinking champagne with a
tall brunette sitting in my lap right now.
Why'd you have to come here
and tell me this tonight?
Well, I came down here tonight to
present to you a-A different option --
You know, one that, uh, you know,
I have to tell you about in person.
This will hold them together.
Electric's faster.
The vibrations will set
off the seismic sensor.
Eliot, approaching the building.
Approaching the building.
Wait here, right?
I've got to handle the
initial break-In myself.
Too many cooks and all.
Oi, delivery.
Next time, Iím playing the thief.
I'd like to hear you do an accent.
???
I went to second city in Chicago.
When did you find time between
that and karate at the y?
You know what? Shut up.
Just -- Just shut up. Just --
Shut up, guys.
A private arrangement
could be made, you know,
To, uh, perhaps ease some
of the -- The paperwork.
Are you talking about a bribe?
No, no, no, listen,
I prefer to look at
it as a processing fee.
Yeah, an agreement between two
gentlemen who understand each other.
Lay down. Stop moving. Stop moving.
How about that?
Idiot.
Stuck it.
This little baby will
deactivate the magnetic sensors.
Smells like...patchouli.
Does it?
Parker wrote the combination in
invisible ink on the door next to you.
She's in there, but she hasn't
deactivated the floor yet.
Take your time with the tumblers.
You are really everything you claimed.
Sorry?
I said, "you're really
everything you claimed."
If Iím lying, Iím dying.
Yes, you are. Yes, you are.
I'm sorry. Just to say
in English -- Very tricky.
Hardison, slow down.
You're breezing through
that combo lock way too fast.
Parker, what's your E.T.A.?
Not ready yet. Floor's still hot.
Nate, our timing's not gonna work out.
Look, Kerrity, you know, you could have
the insurance company process your claim
And, you know, go through it
by the book and everything,
And I guarantee you
you'll see your money,
Just as soon as hell freezes over.
Or...
or you accept my alternative terms,
And, you know, we, uh, we both win.
Who do you think you are, huh?
They let you out of your little
insurance cubicle once a year
To hustle honest customers?
Look, Kerrity, you know,
you and I both know --
You come in here way after hours,
Thinking you can extort me for a bribe?!
Get the hell out of here!
Parker, you've got to get a move on.
Nate and Hardison are way ahead of you.
Okay, the floor is clear.
Nate, parker's still in the vault.
Get the hell out of my office!
No, Iím -- I'm
not going anywhere.
Are you gonna finish this up, Mr. Ice?
Right, right. Yeah, sure. Just...
there it goes. Got it. I found it.
I found it.
I need 60 seconds.
Well, can you turn
invisible in 60 seconds?
'Cause they're busting in there.
Parker, you're out of time.
I'm not ready.
???
Box 72.
I'm on it.
- She didn't crack those.
- What?
She didn't have time.
You moved too fast.
You're gonna have to improvise.
"What?" What?
Do you mind? Personal space.
What part of "get the hell out
of my office" don't you get?
Mr. Kerrity, Iím in insurance.
Now, if you think that Iíve never
been threatened by a firearm before,
- You're quite mistaken.
- Oh, yeah?
Well, why don't you consider this
gun your little security escort?
What the hell?
Is this a setup?
Guys, uh, Kerrityís on his way down.
Oh, what? What? Shh! Shh! Shh! Shh! Shh!
Did you hear that?
Diamond Jimís coming down here.
You -- You go and stop him
while I nick the diamonds.
Hey, what the -- What
the hell's going on here?!
What are you doing here?
We're taking matters into our own hands.
Instead of 10%, 100%,
minus, uh, his cut.
Where is he?!
What the hell's going on?!
What is this?
The security system.
What the hell was that?
Shh! Did you hear that?
Diamond Jimís coming down here.
You -- You go and stop him
while I nick the diamonds.
Thank you. And I mean thank you.
But how are we getting out of here?
What is that? Shh.
Pull your arms in.
Det cord.
Against the wall!
What is that --
A gun? Drop it.
Mr. Kerrity, it's a hell of
a month you're having, huh?
I mean, first, a $9
million armored-Car heist,
And now this?
What are you doing here?
Well, your alarm was activated.
See, and that notifies the
local police, which notifies me.
Right, but you don't have to
worry about anything, lieutenant.
It was a -- It
was a false alarm.
Yeah, we've taken care of it.
You guys -- You guys don't have to
stick around anymore. You can go.
Uh, we tried to stop a robbery.
Box 72.
It's empty.
Now, you said in your report
That your last shipment of loose
diamonds was stolen en route.
And what do you know?
That's the same logo as
the armored-Car company.
But Iím sure when we
check these diamonds out,
I mean, they're not gonna have the
same I.D. Numbers as the missing ice.
I'm sure of that.
Are you sure of that, Mr. Kerrity?
Thought we couldn't use this tunnel.
The tunnel's a horrible way in...
...but it's a great way out.
Your name's been totally cleared.
I'm back on the force as of Monday.
Shoulder's pretty much healed up, too.
Excellent. Kerrity
and his goons --
They went down for
insurance fraud and theft.
Business has basically collapsed.
And, uh, we, uh, we managed to
retrieve something from the wreckage
For, uh, you know, help
with your medical costs.
Where'd this come from?
Should be about done.
It's like it wasn't even there.
What are you smiling at?
You still screwed it up.
I'm smiling 'cause you said if I
got in trouble, you wouldn't help me.
- Parker made me.
- No, I didn't.
Come on, man. Let's hug it out.
I'm not hugging it out, ice man.
Just hug it -- Just
a little man hug.
I'm not hugging it out with you.
No, it's
not --
Man, just sit down on your stool.
- Just don't make this --
- What are you doing, man?
- This is uncomfortable
now. - Just don't -- Dude.
- Get in the pits, man. Get in the pits.
- I'm gonna break your frickin' arm.
Not you, too, huh?
Sorry. What -- What
do you mean me, too?
Well, you've been captured by Russians?
Oh, yeah, that.
That could have gone
better, no question.
It worked out, though.
Oh, it worked out
just fine without me --
Is that what you're saying?
No, no, no, Iím
not -- I'm not --
I'm not saying that at all, no.
No, I just want to say, uh...
to say what?
I just wanted to say Iím sorry...
for bugging you, um...
and for them calling
-- For them calling.
I-I won't let that happen again. I...
listen, call whenever you want.
You know...
bye.
welcome to www.1000fr.com