Previously...
I want the real you.
And I want the real you.
Sometimes I think you're the most real
person I've ever met.
Echo's not a blank slate.
She's a person.
Everything you've imprinted her with
for the last six months is still there.
What does that make her?
Miss Lonely Hearts.
Everyone likes to take something home
from the office once in a while,
but he's the least
of your indiscretions.
I think they're trying to build
a portable device
that will be able to imprint anyone.
- They're grouping, aren't they?
- I sorry to say yeah.
Split them up in separate houses.
This has the potential
to change everything.
I suspected as much.
You did the right thing.
Hurry, Sergeant! Orders!
- Shall we celebrate?
- There's no smoking in my office.
When did you die?
Catherine, wait.
Darling, darling...
we need to talk.
I don't want to talk.
You want Roger.
I want to roger Roger.
Stop!
It would be dishonorable for me
to let this go on any farther.
There's someone else.
What do you mean?
I've fallen in love
with another woman.
Don't tease me.
That's patently impossible.
I'm afraid,
I'm afraid I'm quite serious.
So where did you meet
this other woman?
On one of your international
jet-setting trips?
The flat in London.
The condo in Rome.
Who do you think designs your life
when you're not with me?
I'm having a hard time
figuring it out for myself.
It's as if I met this woman
in a previous life,
as though our love transcends
our very being.
Come on.
You're not real.
You're a Doll.
One whose contract is up, and I was just
getting in one last go-round
before they release
your body into the wild.
And if anyone should be
getting upset, Roger,
it's you,
'cause this time tomorrow,
you're not going to exist anymore.
Catherine, I'm sorry,
I know you're upset,
but don't make up stories.
I don't believe for a second
you'd ever stoop to the level
of those pathetic souls who have to hire
your programmable love dolls
to get what they need.
Do you see what I see?
- I don't see anything.
- Exactly.
There's nothing left
in Ballard's head.
Alpha scrubbed him clean.
Even if I could make the chair
work on someone
without Active architecture,
I'd be lucky if I could make
him walk in a straight line.
But he's stable, physically?
As a zucchini,
which is what he's gonna be
for the rest of his life.
Now my brain is starting
to feel like his.
Get some rest.
I'll deliver the news to Echo.
Another woman, Mr. Brink?
What?
- You're the only one here.
- Who else is in on this practical joke?
Boyd, Ivy?
If it was funny,
I want to take credit for it.
I don't think this was funny.
Miss Lonely Hearts was dumped
by Roger this evening.
Are you sure the dementia
hasn't got into her?
Stop being cute!
How long have you known
the identity of Miss Lonely Hearts?
You?
Oh, my God!
What have I said to you about her?
Octogenarian, walker jokes,
the thing
about the early bird special?
I didn't know.
If you didn't alter the imprint,
I want to know who did.
Roger came back early.
He didn't say why it ended,
but my money's on a broken hip.
What?
She definitely didn't do it.
It wasn't on our end.
Roger's parameters
were exactly as you, she...
She requested.
So where did the mystery woman
come from?
Has anyone seen Sierra?
Look on the bright side.
Roger didn't reject you.
No, Victor did.
It's just grouping,
which won't be a problem
after we set him free tomorrow.
Just make sure this doesn't happen
with any other Actives.
Clients can't being rejected by Dolls
who are programmed to love them.
Yeah, we're lucky
this happened to you.
If anyone finds out about this,
you won't be so lucky.
I don't think that's a smart idea.
DeWitt's watching you.
If you upset her,
you're gonna end up in isolation again.
Or worse.
I haven't seen Paul
since they stabilized him.
- What if I don't get to see him again?
- That's not gonna happen.
Topher's working every angle.
Say good-bye to Victor.
His contract ends first
thing in the morning.
I thought you'd be glad.
I was gonna
use him to help me get everyone out.
He's already been used for five years.
You'll manage without him.
Everything's slipping away from me.
Before, it was memories,
but I figured out how to hold onto them.
And now that I have
something real...
people I care about...
they're slipping away from me, too.
I'll talk to DeWitt about Paul.
Maybe she'll change her mind.
Absolutely not.
Paul Ballard is brain-dead
because of Echo.
Funny, I thought he had Alpha
to thank for that.
It's all of a piece.
Echo brought Alpha to the house.
She made him jealous.
It all starts with Echo.
- You got it all figured out.
- Hardly.
I still want to know what's going on
in that very special brain of hers.
She's not a blank slate anymore.
She's a person
like you or me.
And keeping her away from Ballard
is killing her.
- Perfect.
- You want her to suffer.
Pain reveals who you really are.
Let's see who this girl really is.
Are all the arrangements
for Victor's release finalized?
Everything's set.
Would you mind handling
the final paperwork for me?
Usually, you handle Active releases.
I thought it gave you
a sense of satisfaction
- seeing them through.
- When I've recruited them.
Victor was assigned to this house.
He wouldn't know me from you.
I saved my strawberries for you.
They're my favorite.
Victor, it's time
for your treatment.
Will you sit with me at dinner?
That would be nice.
You're not coming back.
When you get out of that chair,
you'll have your original personality.
You need to say good-bye to her.
If you don't get a chance
to say goobye, you'll regret it.
- Good-bye.
- Good-bye. I'll see you at dinner.
Afghanistan war vet, severe PTSD,
which we cured.
This one actually makes
me feel good about myself.
The last thing
he remembers is reclining in that chair
five years ago as I explained
to him the last thing
he would remember
is reclining in the chair.
I was probably standing
right... here.
Did it not work?
Did something go wrong?
You were not just standing there.
And you were wearing
different clothes.
Well, not that different.
- What did I just tell you?
- That five years would seem like...
five seconds.
Welcome to the future
where cars fly, robots
serve our every whim
and genetically engineered
dinosaurs rule the Earth.
It's pretty much the same
as when you left.
And the war?
- Is it...?
- It's still going on.
So that's it.
Five years just like that.
It wasn't just like that.
Right. Five years
I don't even remember.
I don't know.
It almost seems too easy.
We've set up a trust fund
in your name.
Reserved a suite at the Hyperion
until you find something more permanent.
Found several employment opportunities
should you choose to work.
If people ask,
you spent the last five years
at a VA hospital
as part of an experimental program
that treats veterans
for post-traumatic stress.
We've created a paper trail
to verify your story.
For the first 3 months,
you'll come into the Dollhouse
on a bi-weekly basis for a diagnostic.
For a year following that,
we'll send a representative
into the field to check on you.
If you have any problems,
you can call us 24 hours a day.
But I don't expect any trouble.
This entire process was designed
so you can slip into your old life
without realizing you were gone.
Congratulations, Mr. Ceccoli,
you're a free man.
Episode 209: Stop-Loss
www.subbercafe.fr
With an increase in troop numbers,
U.S. military forces begin
a new offensive against insurgents
in the southern regions
of Afghanistan.
Reports coming out of Kandahar
indicate that two more regions
had been secured.
- How long he you been sitting here?
- I'm waiting for Victor.
We're going to have dinner together.
Victor's not coming back.
But he always comes back
from his treatments.
This time he isn't.
He left. For good.
He wouldn't leave me.
He's free.
They gave his life back to him.
But you're not happy for him.
I needed him.
I thought he could help me
get everyone out.
I'm sad, too...
but not for us, for him.
He's not ready to be by himself.
Excuse me.
Have we met before?
- Where's Paul?
- He's not dead...
- if that's what you're thinking.
- What did you do to him?
Mr. Ballard...
has been moved
to a more secure location,
one where your illicit key card
will be of no use.
No need to fret.
He's receiving top-notch care.
Do you think that anything goes on
in my house without my knowledge?
I don't know, it seems like
a lot went down without you knowing.
Well, I'm not surprised that Paul...
and Boyd managed to keep
your secret from me,
but Topher?
He can barely keep
a belch to himself.
Come on, don't be rude...
it's just a friendly chat.
You really want to do this?
Pretend that we're equals?
- Go toe to toe?
- Why?
You having trouble keeping up?
You think I'm scared of you?
I have a serial killer in my head.
Yes, if memory serves me,
one that's petrified of women.
All those people in your head,
I know their deepest, darkest secrets.
You're forgetting who put them there
in the first place.
So now you're trying to take credit
for making me?
You didn't make me.
I made me.
You may think all these people
knocking around in my head are useless,
but that's 40 more brains
than you have.
So I think we can agree
that I'm smarter, tougher,
and a whole lot scarier
than you could ever hope to be.
If you're so powerful,
why are you still in my house
sneaking around,
trying to find
your comatose boyfriend?
Lady, if I wanted to be
somewhere else, I would be.
But there's work to do here.
Now, you can be on my side
or you can be on Rossum's,
but the time
for playing both is over.
Protocol says
I maintain a Doll's biolinks
for 90 days
after they leave the house
to monitor the reintegration
of their original neural topography.
- That's Victor's readout?
- Was Victor's readout.
At 1:53 AM last night,
his biolinks went kaput,
as in no signal.
I can't even raise his GPS.
I'll send a van to bring him in.
Those aren't "I'll send a van to bring
him in for a diagnostic" squigglies.
They're "fight for your life"
squigglies.
I'm on my way.
I need your help.
- All clear.
- Same here.
Ready to process the room?
You want FBI, private investigator,
or should I surprise you?
So, how exactly does this work,
you accessing other personalities?
I used to have to make an effort
to switch between imprints,
but now I can slip back and forth
without even thinking.
Who am I talking to now?
You're always talking to Echo.
But Roma Klar and Eleanor Penn
are duking it out in the background
over who gets to help me
figure this one out.
I'll take all the help I can get.
They came through the front door.
No sign of a struggle.
And they left the place pretty clean.
Whoever did this, they're professionals.
It was an inside job.
You see a clue I don't?
Victor's been out of the house,
what, less than 24 hours.
Which isn't enough time
to be on anyone's radar.
And they knew enough about our tech
to deactivate his biolinks and GPS.
Looks like
you're working on a theory.
Who the hell are you, huh?
Somebody better say something!
Anthony Ceccoli, sergeant,
Third Battalion, 75th Ranger Regiment...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's me.
Who are you?
What do you want?
We apologize for our methods,
but they were necessary.
Hagan?
- You got transferred to the 160th.
- We all got transferred.
The military called us
broken soldiers,
didn't know what to do with us,
so they packed us away for five years.
- If you tell your commanding officer...
- We don't follow traditional structure.
Officially, we're not a part
of the United States armed forces.
No kidding.
- Why'd you bring me here?
- Military was supposed to fix us.
They took away the pain,
the fear, the shame,
but they left us empty.
Do you know why?
'Cause we're soldiers.
We need something to fight for.
We can give you something
to fight for.
You want me to be a soldier.
Where do I sign up?
Victor's file was accessed
three months ago,
with continued break-ins
leading up to his release.
Someone was making sure
he was still on schedule.
Can you run a back-trace?
It's a Rossum server.
Defense-grade firewall.
Can you hack into it?
Someone in here can.
That's just for immunizations,
right?
It'll be easier for us to explain
after we put this in.
You'll never be alone again.
Have you ever heard of Scytheon?
It's Rossum's military contracting wing,
their answer to Blackwater.
They're the ones
who kidnapped Victor.
They've got a dossier on him.
Personal history, military records,
Dollhouse engagements.
They've got it all.
He's been placed
in a classified program,
code named: Mind Whisper.
It's being operated out of a bunker
on the California/Nevada border.
According to this,
Mind Whisper has recruited
dozens of ex-Actives.
The Active architecture allows
their minds to blinked via neural radio.
They hear what everyone thinks,
see what everyone sees.
Rossum's building an army.
They kidnapped Victor.
Rossum's building an army?
Remember what happened last time
we poked our noses
where they didn't belong.
We failed and I nearly lost control
of the House or something like that.
I'm giving you a chance
to help Victor.
They've turned him
into some kind of soldier.
That's what he wants.
And isn't that why
we're in business?
To give people what they want?
Neural radios?
That's the short-bus version
of this tech.
What's the endgame?
Groupthink.
And not the bad kind
that gave us the Bay of Pigs;
this would be
the much badder kind.
Multiple minds thinking as one.
Imagine war minus the individual.
He's thinking
about one single thing: the objective.
Soldiers who won't stop fighting
until they've accomplished the mission.
Once you're absorbed in the group mind,
the individual ceases to exist.
If we don't rescue Victor
before he's fully integrated
into the group mind,
we lose him for good.
This wasn't on the schedule.
Load me up.
We're going to war.
I got what I need.
Keep them coming.
Field medic, advanced triage,
and it comes with a Texas twang.
Have anything else
that might be useful?
- Why didn't you let me in on this?
- You were on a need-to-know basis.
Need-to-know or need-to-fetch?
The Flying Cardona Brothers?
She's breaking into
an underground bunker, not the Big Top.
No, acrobatics makes sense.
You want Enrique or Ernesto?
Ernesto.
My choice, too.
DeWitt's out cold.
We got at least half the day.
After we're done here,
can I go to her office with a Sharpie?
You've been downloaded with
everything from basic G.I. Jane
to nuclear physicist weapons maker
who secretly yearns
for nuclear disarmament.
Did everything take?
Locked and loaded.
But I need one more thing
to pull this off.
All I have left
is naughty pirate wench.
You promised me
I wouldn't remember that day!
You told me I could skip it!
- Calm down.
- Why? I don't want to remember Nolan!
I don't want to remember any of it.
Get her a beer.
I couldn't delete that day,
because then you wouldn't remember him.
I don't want to remember Nolan.
Not Nolan.
I couldn't delete that day
because you wouldn't remember Victor.
Before I wiped you,
you told me you knew.
You saw Victor
and you told me you knew.
That I loved him?
Exactly.
Why?
What's going on?
His name's Anthony now.
If he's started to lose his identity,
you're our best shot at pulling him out.
Has Victor...
I mean, Anthony, ever met me?
As Priya?
He's met Sierra.
Think Priya with all the complications
stripped away.
So why not just send me as her?
Because you'd still be figuring out
how to buckle your seatbelt.
How do we get in?
We get caught.
I just lost Echo's GPS.
They're inside the bunker.
You really think we'll be able
to pull this off
without Cruella DeWitt finding out?
Don't piss off a blind girl.
Now we just need to make sure
Anthony sees me.
He's already seen you.
One of them sees us,
they all see us.
Come on.
So he'll come to us?
Eventually.
Stay right there.
I'm so glad it's you.
Anthony's gone.
Anthony's gone, but what about Victor?
I know he's in there.
You're trying to confuse us.
You're not gonna confuse us.
Victor remembers me.
He couldn't forget; I didn't forget.
Anthony, lower your weapon.
They don't want me to remember.
Eliminate target.
They want me to kill you.
Eliminate hostile target.
I remember.
Are you in control?
If she's here,
it helps me to remember.
It helps me to stay focused.
They're not happy.
What's the fastest way out of here?
If we follow
the electrical conduits,
it'll lead to a service tunnel.
There's a utility hatch at the end.
Then that's where we're going.
You take the lead.
I'll bring up the rear. Got it?
- You hit him. Why'd you hit him?
- He's still connected.
Anything we tell him, they hear.
Now half the squad's headed
for that service tunnel.
In five minutes, they'll realize
they went the wrong direction.
What is the right direction?
I'm gonna figure out a way
to change the group mind's orders.
You're gonna hold down the hallway.
You know how to fire a gun?
My grandfather took me hunting
in Gippsland once.
So you know how this works?
Why, I shot at rabbits.
I didn't hit anything.
Same idea, just bigger targets.
Judith!
Judith, can you get that?
What is it?
Yes, Mr. Harding.
Of course I am aware
that two of my Actives
are on an engagement.
What sort of House
do you think I run?
No, I wasn't aware
that it is a Rossum training facility.
Of course.
I will have them recalled immediately.
They're not in control.
I'm in control.
But they can hear you.
And I can hear them.
It's a tactical advantage.
I know every move they're gonna make.
Target's acquired.
There's two soldiers,
A-team formation.
XM8 assault rifles,
MK23s and flash grenades.
They're about to make
an offensive move.
I'm Anthony, by the way.
You can call me Tony.
Nice to meet you.
So you're from Australia?
Maybe we should save the small talk
till after the gunfight.
No, it's good.
The more I can remember
about me... us,
the easier it is for me
to keep them out.
You sent Echo and Sierra
to retrieve Victor.
- Someone had to make the call.
- I ordered you to leave it alone!
I was hoping you wouldn't
remember that conversation.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying that you're a drunk.
You're obsesd with keeping Echo
under your thumb.
And you'll do anything you can
to keep Harding smiling.
We may not have agreed,
but at least we put this house
and the Actives first.
What happened to that woman?
She's standing in front of you.
No, she's not.
If you don't find her soon,
you're gonna lose control of this House,
and I'll be the one
knocking down your door.
I hope it doesn't
come to that, Mr. Langton.
Your elevation's off.
You keep going high right.
I'm not hitting anything,
if that's what you mean.
And I don't plan to.
Okay, come on. We got to go.
You don't want to shoot!
Remember five years ago?
Outside Qalat?
It wasn't that much different
than this.
We fought side by side.
Not against each other.
Think about it!
I will shoot you if I have to.
Hurry.
Group mind disengaged.
Eliminate.
Keep it together.
For me.
We just got company.
A whole lot.
Where? I don't see any others.
She's inside.
I knew you were going to do that.
And you knew I was going to do that.
Only four? I'm hurt.
Disengage targets.
Eliminate target.
Disengage target. Stand down.
Eliminate target. Fire.
Echo's down.
We're alone.
We're on our own.
What happened?
They missed.
Echo changed their marching orders.
What did she tell them to do?
Go home.
Favorite breakfast food?
Pancakes with strawberries.
We really have lived another life
with each other.
Or just had breakfast.
I can feel the rest of it
just beneath the surface.
I wonder if we'll ever
remember everything.
I mean, really remember.
It doesn't matter.
I wouldn't mind discovering
all these little things about you again.
Do you think
that was our first kiss?
Out.
We're in the middle of the desert.
Out of the car.
I don't have to explain it to you.
Take her and go.
Guys, we don't all have radios
in our head.
I can't take you back
to the Dollhouse.
You have your original personalities.
You found each other.
You should leave.
Start your life together now.
There's no reason to wait
until I free everyone else.
There are GPS chips
implanted in your bodies.
Find them. Cut them out.
- You need our help.
- She's not going to change her mind.
There's enough traffic on the main road.
Someone will pick you up.
I don't need thanks.
I don't need good-byes.
Do us a favor and look us up
after you get everyone out.
If I get everyone out,
you'll have to look me up.
Caroline F...
You can't do this to her!
Really, Mr. Langton,
I think you were bonded to Echo,
not the other way around.
This is going to blow up
in all our faces.
All of Rossum is chattering
about how you single-handedly
defeated an entire army.
Harding was so impressed
by your performance,
he's devising ways
to turn you into a weapon.
- We know whose side you came down on.
- I told him you're far too dangerous.
There's no way to control you.
But you're still going
to hand me over to him?
You've disrupted
countless engagements.
Brought Alpha into my House.
Deceived me
with the help of Paul Ballard.
Dragged Topher and Boyd
into the fun.
And now Victor and Sierra.
You leave a wake of destruction
wherever you go.
There is only one place for a Doll
as irreparably damaged as you.
The Attic.
They say it's
whatever hell you imagine,
but I think it's
something far worse.
She shouldn't be able to do that.
Welcome to the conspiracy.
Can I go back
to getting you juice boxes?
What's the holdup?
Neuromods set
for chemical saturation.
LTP depotentiated.
Transmag primed.
We're ready.
There has to be another
way to deal with this.
If you don't want to do this, I
can find someone else who does.
Even if it means imprinting someone else
with your personality.
I'm sorry.
Send her body to the Attic.
Then do the same
to Victor and Sierra.