Previously...
Sorry, sister.
- I stay, we both get nabbed.
- Don't leave me.
I was her best friend.
This is what I got for it.
This is my gift from Caroline.
And he took
all of Caroline's imprints?
Where's her original self?
- You have a backup?
- This was the backup.
Alpha mapped his entire brain.
I'll try and piece it back together.
You made me a doll?
Then why do I feel like myself?
You are, but it's an imprint.
There's only one place for a doll
- that's irreparably damaged.
- The Attic.
They say it's whatever hell
you imagine.
This is your worst nightmare?
This is the shape of things to come.
We got it... the information
we were looking for.
I know how to get
at the heart of Rossum.
- We're ready.
- It's time for me to meet Caroline.
Not this one.
Come on.
You said you'd give me the tour.
Here it is, all right?
It's just like any other office.
Can I have my key card?
I want to take you to the roof.
Why are you so nervous?
Whose office is it anyway?
It's nobody's.
Look, nobody's got a bar!
Come on, you want to get me fired?
I want to get you fired up.
- We really shouldn't be doing this.
- Come on.
But I mean, just in here.
You said you dummied up
the security feed.
No, I know,
it's just that I, you know,
I just don't want to leave any DNA.
Then don't make me bleed you.
What are you doing?
What I came here to do.
God, you're a thief?
I let a thief into the building?
Relax. I'm not a thief.
I'm a terrorist.
I am so screwed.
The woman who works here...
What do you know about her?
Nothing. I don't know anything.
I work for a security company.
I'm practically a temp.
Rossum's not gonna give a temp
full access to their buildings.
Hello, Carrie-at-the-prom.
Off-the-chart smart.
Bet you could kill me with your brain.
What makes you a priority?
Full scholarship.
- What's in Tucson?
- I don't know.
Please, just put
all this stuff back.
What the hell is this?
I have no idea.
But that can't be in this building.
Then let's bring down the building.
See what's underneath.
Who are you?
Caroline?
We need to know what she knows.
Clyde said there was one person
who had seen his partner face-to-face,
and that was Caroline.
She can I.D. the man in charge.
- Or the woman.
- Or hermaphrodite.
Say, can we get back to the part
where the chair-less imprinting
tech that I designed,
which you handed over to Harding
in order to get the swank office back...
how that leads to the apocalypse?
'Cause I thought that was
kind of an interesting detail.
It doesn't matter
where the tech comes from.
We have to do more
than disrupt production.
As long as Clyde's partner
is still out there,
Rossum will go on.
We have to cut
the head off the snake.
And Caroline's the only one
who's ever met that snake.
She's been behind the curtain.
Now we need for her to take us there.
What if she won't?
You're impressive, you are.
You're carrying multiple constructs.
And something in you has allowed you
to fuse them into a kind of super ego.
Caroline isn't just one more personality
build you'd be adding to the mix...
she's real.
- Echo is real.
- You're damn right she is.
Ivy's right.
We actually don't know
what dumping Caroline
into Echo's brain will do.
Your original self
comes home to find
the house party that's
going on inside your head...
she might fight back.
- She'd lose.
- All right.
Pull Caroline from the vault.
Put Echo in the chair.
Is that really necessary?
- It's just a precaution.
- And not an unwise one.
Unlike the rest of you,
I've actually met Caroline.
You okay?
I'm good.
We haven't really talked
since you... died.
I guess we've both died since then.
Weird week.
Are you finally ready to meet the girl
who started the trouble in your life?
What? Janice Charles
from my fourth grade math class is here?
We're all set.
All we need now is...
Caroline.
Where's the wedge?
Gone.
What?
Caroline's missing.
Episode 211: Getting Closer
www.subbercafe.fr
Obviously clueless.
She is clueless.
She's at my party.
The be-atch comes up
to my boyfriend...
And you looked so hot. I mean...
- I looked so good.
- Amazing.
- You looked really good, too.
- Thank you.
Excuse me.
Are you finished?
You can take those.
So I was like, "You've got to be
kidding me," and she was like,
"No, I'm not. " Okay, be-atch.
I am not a waitress.
I'm not a waitress.
I'm just another person
standing here with a tray.
So, I was like,
- "You go anywhere near him..."
- It's very crowded,
and you ladies
are taking up four spaces.
- Also, you appear to be finished.
- We're not finished.
Does it look like we're finished?
- I just said that.
- God, was that the bisque?
Did you have the bisque?
I had the bisque...
It's coming up again!
Oh, God. Love your bag.
Take the table.
Care to join me?
You're not ill?
See, the mistake you made
was trying to reason with them.
But I find that even rude people
don't like to barfed on.
I imagine that's true.
- Caroline Farrell.
- Bennett Halverson.
So I'm just going to guess.
Neuroscience major.
How did you know that?
Fish. Brain food.
Also brain books.
Of course.
I'm an idiot.
And a genius, probably.
Technically.
And you?
Not a huge genius.
What are you studying?
I'm still trying to pin it down.
I see all the things
they have to offer, and I figure
once I settle on one thing,
I've excluded everything else.
And there are a lot of things
I'd like to be.
Get that thing out of my face.
It's for the video yearbook.
Okay, hi, Mom.
Are we done?
Is there someone
you'd like to say good-bye to?
Dieter and Meg.
And the girls of Sigma Tau.
Sister's forever.
Let's hope those venereal
diseases make you...
She seems so innocent
in a way, doesn't she?
Unspoiled.
She wasn't, you know.
Caroline Farrell left quite a trail
of unhappiness in her wake
and not a few bodies.
Are you saying she's evil?
Worse.
An idealist.
- And I want to travel.
- I shouldn't be at all surprised
if it turned out her wedge had got up
and walked out of here on its own.
I was glad
when I heard it was missing.
It's only natural.
But I didn't take it.
I only considered it briefly.
What can I say?
I want to do everything.
Is that too much to ask?
Why would Echo
steal her own imprint?
Because she's become a real girl.
And if Caroline were to come back,
she might cease to exist
or wind up nuts or very confused.
Okay, but it doesn't track.
Echo went to the Attic
for the cause.
Whatever that does to your brain
is worse than getting a roomie.
Now, this is just Rossum
being five steps ahead of us again.
We're there.
Harding runned this place for months.
His people were everywhere.
Rossum could have had them
grab the wedge at any time.
We have ignition.
Ghost chair's just been engaged.
Let's do this.
After Apollo's accomplished
bring Cassandra down
for a full diagnostic.
She's been complaining about...
That's wrong.
Something's happening.
Something unintended.
Not unintended...
intentional.
Cancel this imprint.
This imprint's been corrupted.
Corrupted from the outside.
School pranks.
This reeks of Topher Brink.
We're in.
She's here. We got her.
Is she okay?
Is she still cute?
Don't you hurt her.
Gingersnap.
- What is this? What are you doing?
- I'm taking you to see an old friend.
We're not leaving yet.
And the flight...
not too exhausting, I trust?
You used the company jet to abduct
the programmer of a rival House.
I'm certain I'll be kicking myself
come holiday bonus time.
I'm sure you'll be dead by then.
It's a very open space.
Quite a lot of beige.
You let them roam.
They roam like free-range chickens.
We keep ours more like veal.
Hi.
Welcome.
You routed through an I-09
to seize control of my chair.
Impressive.
Topher here is going to explain
why we've gone to such lengths
to procure your services.
You won't be getting my services.
But you don't even know
what we need yet.
I don't care.
This man assaulted me.
Struck me in my own lab.
I'd like to file a formal complaint.
Ms. Halverson, as you correctly noted,
you have been abducted.
Now, you could be treated
as a prisoner or as a guest.
It's entire...
Can I get you anything?
- A diet soda.
- I have some!
I mean,
in my fridge.
Come on.
Well, lab's in here.
You showed me yours.
Let me...
show you mine.
I can...
I'm all right.
How long do you think
before they track her back here?
Sooner than I'd hoped, I'm afraid.
Damn romantic fools.
I'm surrounded by them.
He couldn't just leave her there.
No, I suppose not.
But I had hoped
for an outward appearance of normalcy
while we marshaled our forces.
However, any good battle plan
must be fluid.
We'll be going
into full lockdown mode.
You did a good thing.
Did I?
She walked away from me,
and I let her.
I never looked to see
if she was okay.
She was a person, and now she's...
nothing again.
We'll fix it.
We'll make her right.
Once they've done this to you...
can you ever be right again?
Imprint wedge.
It's an original personality.
- What happened to it?
- It...
got damaged last year.
I only kept this around
to see if, as an exercise,
I could restore it.
You know?
Like you did
with the Hamilton wedge.
- You heard about that?
- That was legend.
Thing is, I still have no idea
which decompression algorithms
you used to recover the imprint.
The Hamilton wedge
was only missing half its data.
That's a one to two
compression ratio.
This is only one to four.
An exponential increase.
Failed test pins...
microcracks
in the spindle,
mag comp corruption...
Why do you need this one restored?
Would it sound OTT
if I said this could help prevent
the end of civilization
as we know it?
I would need
to understand the context.
You could use perceptual coding
to reassemble
the autonomic functions, I suppose.
How much data loss would we suffer?
One generation.
No loss.
Every memory will be intact.
Awesome.
Then maybe
we could work on the one memory
I'd like to erase.
I'm so sorry I hit you.
I didn't want to.
God, how I didn't want to.
I was trying to kill
your Active at the time.
You had your reasons.
Still...
that face.
Slugging it.
Not my first instinct.
I didn't think it was.
Some form of contact, but not...
Who's on that wedge?
Who are you trying to resurrect?
This person.
It's stupid.
Does it... does it matter?
It might.
It's not like
it's Stalin or somebody.
I didn't suppose that it
would be a historical figure.
Who is it?
Ready for your treatment?
I think I changed my mind.
No mind changing.
Come on. Back in the chair.
Is it so bad right now?
It's not bad.
It's just... dull.
We're going to make you pop.
I'm not sure I wish to pop.
You're gonna pop. And like it.
In the chair. Lay back.
All right. You're starting
a big new job tomorrow.
You want to turn heads.
I'll mostly be studying them,
and there'll be rat heads.
Well, you want to look nice
for your vermin.
They're largely color blind,
though they can detect
some ultraviolet.
Then they'll love this.
The purple's really going
to bring out your eyes.
Close them. I'm kidding.
This is your color.
What your color should be.
You'll still be you; just more you.
I've often thought
I'd like to be less me.
More like...
You, actually.
Me? I'm still undeclared.
You know who you are.
You're so fearless.
I'd love to get a look
at your amygdala.
You'd have to buy me dinner first.
No one's ever done this
for me before.
Washed your hair?
Taken an interest.
It's me.
I'd have called. I don't trust
the land lines right now.
DeWitt's ordered the House
into full lockdown.
I think it's time we brought you in.
Do we get to have one drink first?
Are you scared?
Not anymore.
What did you do?
Her left arm may be dead,
but she's got
a terrific right cross.
If anyone asks.
Actually, if anyone asks, don't say
I got beat up by a one-armed girl.
What did you do to him?
Him? Him who?
I gave him his life back.
You made him a Doll.
I had to reconstruct
his neural landscape
based on the brain scans Alpha made
when he damaged it, but he's still Paul.
Same taciturn, self-regarding guy.
No, he's not the same.
He's different.
Half his brain tissue was scarred.
I had to do major rewiring,
which required healthy brain tissue.
There were two pieces of real
estate big enough for the job.
The motor cortex
or the cingulate gyrus.
So either he could live his life
trapped in a paralyzed body,
or I could take away something else.
Me, wasn't it?
Not his memories of you.
He's still got those.
Our connection.
I think so.
The freshest, brightest paths...
Those are the ones I needed.
I think that was you.
You're still bleeding.
Why don't you let me do that?
Dr. Saunders?
Hop up.
Tilt your head back.
How did you...
You mean...
You two?
Wait.
Less talking would
mean less bleeding.
And I mean that in so many ways.
So you're the reason Boyd's been
all tardy and sleepy
the last two months.
Glad you're back.
You might not be.
That troublesome
one-armed creature, where is she?
I had to lock her up. Couldn't leave her
in the Lab unattended.
And your charm offensive?
Mostly just offensive.
When Dr. Saunders is finished with you,
come and see me, please.
Right-o.
- I try to be my best.
- Of course you do, my dear.
Try and have her back on rotation
as soon as is practicably possible.
- She is, after all, our Number One.
- Ma'am, a word?
Three months ago, someone
deleted a substantial portion
of security footage from the system.
Three months ago?
Not our system. The main building.
I only learned of it recently.
And?
I spoke to the security
officer on duty that night.
He admitted to it.
Freely?
Loudly. There was some pleading.
Turns out he let a young
woman into the building.
Your office, to be exact.
I'll ask Judith
to inventory my files.
I already did.
Two were missing.
One of them was Caroline Farrell's.
The security officer identified her
as the woman he let in.
Thorn in my side, that girl.
I thought we'd finished with her.
She'd dropped off the radar.
You said there were
two files missing?
The other one was
Bennett Halverson's.
Damn.
Halverson is one
of Rossum's rising stars.
Rumor has it, the man at the top
selected her himself.
Guess who's rooming with Bennett
Halverson at Tucson Tech?
- Who else knows about this?
- Just us.
Keep it that way.
We need to get to Tucson.
Benster.
You're home early.
They were doing routine
maintenance at the lab.
You broke out the Tasty Couture.
Good choice.
You said it was okay
for me to borrow it.
Yeah, totally. Rock on.
I kind of got it for you.
Is something wrong?
I wasn't snooping.
I just...
went into your closet
to find the outfit.
- Who are you?
- Bennie.
Who are you?!
I'm Caroline.
You know me.
I don't think I do.
Where did that file come from?
L.A.
The Rossum office in L.A.
Why do you have it?
Because I took it.
And it led you to me?
I saw you were valuable to them,
which means you're valuable to me.
You wanted to get close to them?
To hurt them?
A lot.
Bennett, Rossum is out of control.
They're doing things,
experiments not just on animals.
- If you'd seen what I'd seen...
- I thought you were my friend.
I am.
Then why won't you let me help you?
You're not... pissed
because I used you?
I'm hurt that you won't.
Do you want to blow up a building?
Hey, stud.
Mother always wanted me
to date a doctor.
I wonder what mine wanted.
- Guess we'll find out.
- It's scary, isn't it?
We need Caroline.
We need you.
I keep thinking there is a me,
that I'm real,
but every time I talk to someone,
they act like I'm doing tricks.
Paul never believed Echo was a person
even when he cared.
Now he's just waiting
for Caroline to kick me out.
That's never gonna happen.
Look,
I never met Caroline Farrell.
I know she drives DeWitt
about as crazy as you do,
so I figure she can't be all bad.
But I know you.
I've watched you grow.
I've watched you build yourself
from scratch against all odds.
Against us.
You're stronger than everyone here,
Echo, even Caroline.
If she gets in there,
I think she'll be proud to know you.
I have to put the House on lockdown.
- You gotta do that now?
- Yeah. Orders.
Give me three minutes.
I'm glad you have found
something for us.
We were feeling
like a couple of fifth wheels.
What do you need us to do?
I need you
to get the hell out of here.
There's time.
Probably not much but some.
- Don't spend it here.
- I don't understand.
Look at her.
Understand?
We're about to go to war.
You never know
what you'll lose in a war.
what you'll lose anyway.
Go, be with each other,
even if it's just for the night.
Thank you.
Guys...
If you somehow forget the way back here,
that's okay, too.
Clyde's dead.
Rossum's on to you.
They're coming.
He said they're on to us.
Probably headed this way.
This could alter our plans
considerably.
Okay, am I the only one thinking
we're getting maybe a little too much
of our intel from The Matrix,
or possibly Tron, given the outfits?
We'll assume
the information is good.
We'll begin
evacuation procedures at once.
Every Active
to be brought to imprint,
their personality restored and released.
We can dispense with the niceties.
I'm not leaving behind
a House full of helpless creatures.
Behind?
Where are we going?
Tucson, obviously.
{\ROSSUM HEADQUARTERS
Tucson, Arizona}
These are the labs
with restricted access.
Then those are the targets.
You sure you're up for this?
We're in it together, right?
Till the end.
Go.
I'll do my work from here.
You should be above
the first lab by now.
Copy.
The charge is in place.
Ten minutes on the clock?
First charge is hot.
No backing down now.
I'm above a lab
just past the L junction.
It's not in the schematic.
Set the last charge and move on.
The only reason you build a room that's
not in the plans is to hide something.
- I'm going in.
- You don't have time!
When you get curious, you get dead.
Do you read?
- Bennett, we have to abort!
- What?
- There are people in here!
- You can't! The timers are set!
I'll try and pull the detonator caps!
You have to run!
Help me!
- Run!
- I won't!
Run! Run!
He was in there too long.
He's going into shock.
- He needs to go to a hospital.
- Impossible.
My entire support staff
are engaged in the evacuation.
Evacuate him. He risked everything
to get his message to us.
Put him back in the Attic.
It's his best hope.
No, you bitch.
I'd rather die.
Well, I'd rather you didn't.
See that it's done.
- Let me take him.
- It's done, Mr. Ballard!
She's right.
His best chance
is back in the Attic.
And we could use someone on the inside
when we hit the mainframe.
I don't know you anymore.
I know.
Do you recall
your former neighbor Mellie?
You insisted she come along.
I insist she be someone
who trusts you entirely.
We shan't have time
for any senate subcommittees.
What's happening?
Is this place what I think it is?
Are you taking it down?
We're taking it down.
And you found her?
You're Caroline.
He never gave up, you know.
He never stopped looking.
I know.
Mr. Ambrose!
What a lovely late night surprise.
Are you surprised, Adelle?
Surprised and delighted.
He doesn't look surprised.
He's paid not to look surprised.
What can I do for you?
You can go with these gentlemen.
They'll escort you
to your debriefing.
As of this moment, I'm taking over
the House and liquidating the inventory.
I beg your pardon?
Let's not play games.
Nobody comes out of the Attic.
There've been multiple breaches.
You're done.
- Take her.
- I don't think so.
Well, I guess we can agree
this carpet's done for.
Mr. Langton!
Bennett?
- Bennie?
- I can't move...
Move this stone!
What are you doing?
You were working late.
The building was attacked.
- They'll find you. You'll be fine.
- No, you can't leave me, I'm with you!
No, you're not.
Don't leave me!
Sorry, sister.
I stay, we both get nabbed.
I'm gonna make sure it's just me.
Don't leave me!
You're gonna bring her back.
- I don't think so.
- No, you're going to.
Or what, you'll hit me?
I considered that.
I also considered letting you go.
I don't want her back
any more than you do.
But the fact is, I need her.
I need what's in her head,
and I need you to get it.
I'll make you an offer.
You resurrect Caroline Farrell
long enough for me to save my friends,
and I'll let you do
anything you want to her.
I will hold the bitch down.
Deal?
Are you out of your mind?
But Ambrose is.
You think a ranking
Rossum board member
would confine his consciousness
to a single body?
When he finds out you've killed him,
you'll be a target.
- How's he gonna find out?
- I'm going to tell him.
Which is why you're going to run.
To draw their fire.
It is a war.
Yes, it is.
She should stay with the group.
She'll be marginally safer.
Thank you.
Thank me later.
Gary Walden.
Hey, Gare!
What do you know?
Term's up!
You're done!
Has it been five years?
Sure, sure.
Sanderson here is going to see
you make it back
into the real world okay.
Five years, huh?
So fast.
Seems like I just got here yesterday.
You got a cigarette?
Last Tuesday, actually.
That all of them?
One more.
You change your mind?
Turns out Echo and I
share some common interests.
Give me a hand?
I'll give you both.
That wasn't a reference.
I'm going for a walk.
Thanks for grabbing these.
Where will you go?
I don't know yet.
I'll have to figure that out
on the move.
Somewhere they can't pinpoint me.
- Where is that?
- I don't know.
And I wouldn't tell you if I did.
Echo's already in danger.
I don't want you to be.
It's an understatement to say
they have ways of making you talk.
Maybe I'll just keep moving.
I'll be okay.
You won't be able to go
to the hospital if you need it.
Some extra bandages.
I'm feeling fine.
You need these to fight off infection.
Fever is the first sign...
It's a through and through.
I'll be okay.
I wish we had more time.
I know.
I'll come back for you.
You understand?
We are now officially evacuated.
I'm going to go in the back
and deal with the burn racks.
Take a message.
You're using nonlinear transformation
for all the cognitive controllers.
Yes, I am.
If you had a Dewey pin,
this might go a little faster.
Sure.
I'm sorry.
More of that if we prevent
the end of the world?
You know,
I always had a crush on you.
Even when I thought you were a dude.
This is better.
He's in love with you.
I'm sorry?
I was the House doctor.
I used to be Number One.
I see.
Topher mentioned there had been...
It's nice to meet you.
Is that Caroline?
Do you really think you're going
to be able to get her back?
I'm confident of it.
Do you really think he likes me?
I didn't say "likes."
He's remarkable.
I honestly didn't think
he was capable
of admitting the existence
of another human being,
let alone loving one.
I think you're the remarkable one.
I couldn't find one, but...
Do not move.
You have much to answer for,
young woman.
I do?
You forced me to come to Arizona.
I loathe Arizona.
We taking her back to the House?
I don't think she's left us
with much alternative, Mr. Dominic.
Of course, sir.
I wouldn't dream
of keeping her from you.
Someone upstairs wants to meet you.
- Who?
- The head of the company.
You weren't invited?
No hard feelings.
A trip to see our director
is generally one-way.
Enjoy the ride.
Topher, I need you to focus.
Saunders did this.
Rossum got to her.
Probably months ago,
right after she left this place.
A sleeper?
Boyd loves her.
He'll have to adjust.
I'm going after her.
Or not.
We can bring her back.
We can bring Bennett back.
We can map...
There's nothing left to map.
The person who we need
to bring back now is Caroline.
Can you do it?
Good.
I can do this.
I got it.
You get your chance, you slip out.
In the real world, you can write
your ticket anyplace you land.
I really do want to help you.
Then live.
You have a remarkable brain.
I think it should stay in your head.
Don't become me.
We're breached.
That's one word for it.
This won't do it.
I was loading the weapons reserve cache
up in the handlers' quarters.
Go!
How long?
This is going to take
just as long as it's...
Done.
Where is security?
Assume they're dead.
Let's do this.
Damn. I just had that replaced.
You should go.
Server room service tunnels.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're our general.
We can't lose you.
Good luck, all of you.
Stay back!
I've imprinted myself
with many useful skills.
You don't want to know.
Hang in there.
Thanks for coming up.
It's terrific.
Can I get you something? Tea?
I hate tea.
So, not tea, then.
I mean... Look at you.
Caroline Farrell.
So, you're Rossum?
Rossum is just a name, actually.
From a play.
Although, technically,
you're not robots, it seemed to fit.
Sorry. Clyde.
Clyde Randolph.
The second.
Well, like the fifth, actually.
I use a lot of bodies.
I'll explain that later.
My partner and I have been
quite eager to meet you.
Why me?
Because you're very special.
You're going to help us
in ways you can't understand.
Not likely.
You don't have a lot of options.
So I'm going to be
one of your zombies?
Open up my brain
like the rest of them?
You'll never be like the rest of them.
You won't be harmed in any way.
You're far too valuable.
And I'm just gonna trust you?
With your life.