Big day.
Is it?
Trust me.
With my life.
We're okay, right?
- She's not going to...?
- Glitch?
She's fine, Agent Ballard.
Sorry, Mr. Ballard.
39 personalities
all wiped clean away.
If she acts funny,
her handler tells me.
I just know this one's
been long-term, and today...
Was definitely one for the books.
But this is the Dollhouse, frenemy,
and nothing happens without my...
What the hell?
What?
Saunders.
We're okay, right?
You're fine.
She's fine.
I'm gonna go to sleep.
It's not that bad.
It's the last thing
she should be doing.
You're not Echo's handler,
Mr. Langton.
- You're head of security now.
- As head of security,
I'm telling you this
engagement poses a risk.
This is coming along well.
Thank you.
We made a deal with Paul Ballard.
Either we honor that deal,
or he exposes us,
or I order you to do something...
extreme.
I'd like to avoid the latter two.
I have plans for the erstwhile agent.
You're touching my face.
Move along.
He hunted the Dollhouse for months.
The Bureau kicks him out
and you think that just flips him?
He's one of us now?
No, I expect he's looking
for something else...
a darker purpose perhaps,
or a weakness.
And there's his extreme
devotion to Echo.
So he uses her
to fulfill some sad fantasy
about righting old wrongs
by doing something worse.
Why in particular does
this engagement bother you?
After that news anchor...
Which one?
The one who wanted to be rolled
in eggs and flour and dipped.
Tempura Joe.
Such a lonely soul.
I thought I'd seen it all,
but this engagement...
Honestly, this one's sick.
Dearly beloved,
we are gathered here today
to join this man and this woman...
Épisode 201: Vows
v. 1.00
www.subbercafe.fr
Do you want to know what I've been doing
while you overslept?
If you tweaked an imprint,
I'll throw you through that window.
I'm just moving things along.
We are backed up like LAX at Christmas.
It's the autumn rush.
Temperatures plummet
to the high 60's.
The leaves fall off
that one tree on Wilshire.
People need comfort.
What's up with you?
If you little worker bees
aren't too busy,
I was promised a treatment.
Sierra.
- Nobody called down.
- I can't have the other one?
The man one?
I need caffeine.
Ivy?
I'm on it.
They didn't change you.
I'm not comfortable with...
Orientals.
It'll only take a second.
It's not a racialist issue.
It's just that...
Well, your culture's not
really the thing, is it?
Have a seat.
I suppose I'm at your mercy.
In fact,
if you were to tie me down
and spank me,
I could hardly be expected
to resist, could I?
I'll keep that in mind.
How many more today?
Well, the Jonas Brothers
are back in town.
Say no more.
Voracious little nippers.
Oh, my God!
Are those from the lab?
I don't care, just get them!
- That one went there!
- Come here.
I didn't know
your problem with rodents.
Clearly somebody knew.
Come here.
Is this your idea of a joke?
You designed me, Mr. Brink.
I guess it must be
your idea of a joke.
I designed you to be
a not crazy woman!
You've got to stop messing with me.
I don't seem to be able to.
Maybe your work's not up to par.
My work is pristine.
If you're losing it,
that's your fault.
Are you sure?
I know what I know.
Put the rats back in the maze,
Topher,
before one of them bites you.
You busy?
Just...
dealing with some vermin.
Is this about Echo again?
Victor.
I didn't know
if you were copied on his results.
The scars are practically gone.
One more surgery,
you'll never know they were there.
Yes, I was surprised
that Ms. DeWitt would authorize
such an expensive
process for an Active.
When she didn't before.
There's no reason
she couldn't do the same for you.
I like my scars.
They bring out my eyes.
Without my scars,
I might as well be one of them.
And sooner or later,
Ms. DeWitt will remember
I was a more lucrative asset
when I was.
- There's no way that I would allow it.
- DeWitt is not the type of person...
What if she went over your head?
I'm very tall.
Before you knew...
Before either of us knew
that I was a fake...
Claire.
An Active, a Doll...
When you thought
I was just a doctor,
you didn't care much for me.
We disagreed about things.
So should I interpret
this new concern as pity?
Curiosity?
Deviant excitement?
There's no judging in the Dollhouse.
You seem to be having a hard time.
My entire existence was constructed
by a sociopath in a sweater-vest.
What do you suggest I do?
Have dinner with me.
I think you should
get out of here for awhile.
And I'd be glad of the company.
I don't...
go out.
I'm afraid to leave this place.
I have a problem with crowds,
with...
people,
and sunlight,
open spaces,
noise,
pets.
For some reason,
I'm just built that way.
Every person I know
is pretty poorly constructed.
Everyone has an excuse
for not dealing.
But eventually, that's all they are.
Excuses.
What's yours?
This is Hugo.
No, the shipment
is only delayed a day.
Mr. Klar is busy today.
Roma Klar.
Mrs. Roma Klar.
I thought you were keeping
your first name.
It's unbelievable.
What?
I found the woman of my dreams.
You'll meet her later tonight.
She's lovely.
I found the thing
that everyone spends their lives
thinking they're gonna find,
but grieving that they haven't.
She's in my arms.
She's mine for life.
And all I can think is...
I'm gonna step on her feet.
I'm practically paralyzed.
We should have taken those lessons.
I don't wanna have a wedding story
where I step all over your feet.
It'd relieve the pressure.
Seriously, these heels are insane.
Take them off.
When it's time.
It's time. It's past time.
Can I wish everyone away?
No, it's my wedding day.
And I never want it to end...
until my wedding night.
Hey, partner.
How was last night? You okay?
I'm so sore.
My feet, perv.
Why do people get married
in frickin' stilettos?
Go on. Work for a living.
How about Klar?
He said, "I do".
I heard that part.
Did you cry?
Little tear, one eye?
Geez, what is with you?
The biggest arms dealer on the coast
just plighted his troth to me.
For five years, the Bureau couldn't get
his cousin's dog walker
to give them the time of day.
Now I'm the Missus.
Five years ago,
I still cared about due process.
The Bureau's going to coo like doves
when we give them Martin Klar.
Then we sneak off into the night.
Forget we were ever here.
Is this about the sex?
I know, for you,
the act of love is the most intimate
and precious thing two people can share.
But it's just bodies. It's useful.
And with Klar, it's pretty damn fun.
- Man's got a work ethic.
- I think you might be a demon.
I'm justice.
I'm blind when I need to be blind.
Well, you're inside now,
so open your eyes.
I have.
This is Martin Klar, okay?
I can't even get him to tell me
where the honeymoon is.
There's not gonna be any honeymoon.
I do this till it's done.
I mean, there's no movement
from suppliers?
All the small arms guys we knew
are accounted for or out of the game.
I still think Klar
is moving something new.
Well, we know Pavel Hund
is in the market for dirty bombs.
- They were really thick in the '90s.
- That was AKs, not plutonium.
Klar wouldn't touch
something that hot.
He married me.
How long have we been partners?
Three years.
Have I ever said I'm sure
and been wrong?
I'm guessing not.
Trust me.
Everything we've worked for
happens now.
Not quite yet.
Not until you've had your treatment.
- Wait.
- No. A treatment sounds great.
- I need her.
- Her protocol says she comes in.
Long-term engagements are tricky.
Got to check the wiring.
And the plumbing.
I want Echo back
as soon as she's checked out.
You're the client.
How are you feeling?
A little sleepy.
They tell me you had a big night.
Who tells you?
You're gonna feel a little pressure.
Clean bill of health.
Did someone say that to you?
- To call me that?
- You were number one.
I don't remember the rest.
Alpha cut up my face.
Do you remember that?
Why?
So you could be number one.
Am I?
You are.
I try to be my best.
Good for you.
You're done.
Go and be your best.
No one is their best in here.
What is more precious
to a human being than their mind?
Everything we feel, see,
everything we are
is controlled by our brains.
They are the most powerful
and delicate part of the human machine.
As some of you know,
I lost my mother to Alzheimer's...
years before she died.
Since I took office,
I have made health care
and medical research a top priority,
and I call you all here today
to tell you
I am shocked and appalled
by what I have found.
There is nothing less
than a conspiracy
spearheaded by
the Rossum Corporation
to withhold medical advancements,
to use radical illegal...
Well, this is charmless, isn't it?
What do you think, Mr. Langton?
I like his suit.
You may well be missing the point.
He knows how to wear it, too.
Money. A lot.
And he was born into it.
He'll have connections.
We have connections.
He also has ambition.
Which he wasn't born into.
Money like that, you either coast
or you shoot for the stars.
This one isn't going away.
How is it he wasn't on our radar?
We weren't on his.
I'm sure he was looking for a cause.
Someone gave him us. Recently.
Any idea who?
Mr. Ballard.
We were just about
to talk about you.
Did you see Senator Perrin's
press conference?
Just now. Nice suit.
Have you ever talked
to Senator Perrin?
Have you?
- Mr. Langton.
- Ms. Dewitt.
He reminds me of you.
I mean it. If you're pointing fingers,
you should be looking at Boyd.
I know why I'm here.
Do you?
I can't beat you.
The FBI kicked me out for trying.
Maybe the Senator can,
and I'll raise a glass.
In the meanwhile, I'm a kiss away
from taking down a gunrunner
the FBI couldn't touch.
A kiss away?
Echo married him.
And my reports put you no closer
to closing than you were
when their eyes first locked.
Are you shutting us down?
I want you to consider
becoming Echo's handler.
I don't work for you.
No, you work
for the betterment of mankind.
Fighting crime by listening
to Echo have sex.
It's terribly noble.
We don't have audio
inside Klar's house.
You never ask about November.
- Who?
- Mellie.
Well, Madeline, actually.
But she was Mellie
when she was with you.
When you used your leverage
to have her released instead of Echo,
I thought you must have really
cared for her.
- Are you threatening her?
- Now I think you were just...
done with her.
But not with Echo.
You still need Echo for something.
But you'll never get it...
with the ex strutting
about the place.
You're a sick lady.
Well, I'm not asking you
to handle me.
Echo's special.
You know it.
Alpha knew it.
She was evolving even before
he dumped all her personas into her.
Policy would be to send her
straight to the Attic,
and if this goes too far,
I still will.
But I'm a little bit curious.
You want to study the rat
before you slice it up?
Well, that is how science works.
What we learn here
feeds Rossum's crucial research.
As much as it feeds their coffers.
She hasn't shown me anything weird.
I wouldn't risk this mission
if she had.
Echo has three more years
on her contract.
I would prefer her to have someone in
her corner who really cared about her.
Even unreasonably.
You're working an angle.
With the exception
of the very special and the comatose,
have you ever met
someone who wasn't?
Think about it.
It'll pass the time
during her honeymoon.
Hugo, is everything on track
with the shipment?
Good. Then tell me what it is you...
If it has to be in person,
it can wait until the morning.
It can absolutely wait
until the morning.
I'll call you.
You were gone too long.
You won't tell me where we're going,
so I had to buy one of everything.
Well, supper's laid out.
Are you hungry?
Are you?
Ten seconds ago, I swear I was.
I think you're controlling
my thoughts.
It's easier than you'd think.
Women.
What the...?!
What the hell?!
Are you drunk?
I'm just trying to be my best.
I don't want your best.
I think you do...
That is the minority vote.
And you tricked it.
A guy's asleep.
Could have been Fozzie Bear
and it would have...
Not that I think about Fozzie Bear.
Let's stop playing games.
How does this qualify
as not playing games?
Because this is the endgame.
This is where it all leads.
You design someone to hate you
so you can convince them
to love you.
I could whip up a love slave
any day I wanted to.
But that wouldn't be
a challenge, would it?
Slaves are just slaves.
But winning over your enemy...
the one person guaranteed
to reject everything you are...
that's real love.
More real than anything up
in the world.
And I understand it now.
I love you.
You need a frickin' treatment!
Why shouldn't I love you?
Aren't you lovable?
Aren't you Big Brother?
Aren't you the Lord my God?
Why should I fight your divine plan?
Because you're better than that!
Because you're better than me.
Dr. Saunders was dead.
And Whiskey was out of service,
at least temporarily.
So DeWitt gave me the call.
"We need a new doctor.
"One who's committed to our cause,
"who's kind and efficient
and will look after our Actives."
So why didn't you stop there?
Because I was designing a person,
not a Roomba.
I needed you to be whole.
If you agreed
with everything I said,
then we would miss something,
and someone would get hurt.
You don't care if people get hurt.
You don't know me!
That's the contract.
You don't know me,
and I don't know you.
Not fully, not ever.
I made you question.
I made you fight for your beliefs.
I didn't make you hate me...
You chose to.
How do I live?
How do I go through my day
knowing everything I think
comes from something I can't abide?
So you aren't really
gonna sleep with me.
I can't stand the smell of you.
I did that...
so we never...
Why didn't you find out
who you really used to be?
You had your chance.
Maybe DeWitt
would even re-imprint your old identity.
You've earned it.
Because I don't want to die.
I'm not even real.
I'm in someone else's body,
and I'm afraid to give it up.
I'm not better than you.
I'm just a series of excuses.
You're human.
Don't flatter yourself.
Honey?
That desk was my grandfather's.
I know.
So I'd prefer
if you didn't stab it to death.
This is your fault.
I'm all ears.
You know I can't stand surprises.
You have to tell me
where we're going.
Half the fun of a honeymoon
is packing and...
Maybe not half.
Wait. You say this from experience?
From your many marriages?
What's up?
What, besides you assaulting
a family heirloom?
I'm sorry.
I didn't leave a scratch.
It's all right. Don't worry.
I can always have it refinished.
What, no self-defense training?
No second gun in the ankle holster?
Please...
I can't believe he'd leave you here
without any kind of defense.
I don't know
what you're talking about!
Do you take this man
to be your lawfully-wedded husband?
Martin, I love you.
To love and honor,
in sickness and in health
so long as you both shall live?
- I do!
- Who are you?!
My name is Roma Klar.
Yes, it is.
It's comical.
It is, I understand,
the key to comedy, the timing.
One day,
one day wed, and I get this!
Proof that my wife is my enemy.
Paul Ballard...
Where did he find you?
I mean, you're not Bureau.
Witness Protection?
Starving actress?
What did he promise you?
- Is he your lover?
- I've never seen this man.
This is a photo!
Have you see this man, darling?!
It's fake! It's Photoshopped!
Or this guy,
he asked me for the time
and had someone snap a picture.
- Why?
- To hurt you!
He's your enemy.
He comes at what's closest to you!
Well, good for him!
I thought
you were gentle and honest.
He knew better,
you wife-beating piece of...
Don't touch me!
- I'm sorry.
- Who has enemies like that?
Who the hell are you
that people hate you that much?
I'm not stupid.
You're not just a frickin' financier,
but I don't care!
I didn't marry your job!
I married you.
I can't be wrong about you.
Look at me.
Forget everything and look at me.
I am your wife.
For the rest of my life...
I am and will always be
Mrs. Eleanor Penn.
Wait.
Who did they make me this time?
Aren't they lovely?
Of course,
they're just little bombs.
But they're not actually dirty bombs
until you've inserted them inside
the plutonium.
But then they're just
ordinary looking.
I like the heart of the thing.
The mechanism,
the light from within.
That's why I loved you.
I never lied to you...
not about anything that mattered.
It's Ballard.
Let me talk to Topher Brink.
Please hold.
This is Topher. What up?
- Something's not right.
- With Echo?
Her handler said she spiked
about two hours back.
Can you access that?
I can, I am.
Why didn't he move in?
He said it was excitement.
They were being newlyweds.
Yeah, that's not hot monkey love.
I got zero serotonin.
Theta activities to the CA1 are peaking.
That was pain, and panic.
- How did he miss this?
- What do you see now?
She's amped, but there's drop-offs.
It's kind of random.
She could be concussed.
I'm calling it.
You move in now,
Klar will kill her for sure.
You got a better plan?
But I do have a much worse one.
Sir.
My God, this is becoming surreal.
Bring her out.
It's Paul Ballard.
Special agent in charge
of bugger all.
Hello, Martin.
Have you come to wish us joy
on our nuptials?
Let her go.
But we're very much in love.
You don't know who her.
Well, I know it's not the FBI.
I think I'm going to keep this gun.
I'm going to treasure it.
- You're making a mistake.
- You're the expert in that field.
Did he tell you he was still
with the FBI?
Not ousted in disgrace?
Did he forget to mention his pathetic
failed attempts to catch me,
or anyone?
I'm just so anxious
to know what he said
that put you in bed
with a man who represents
everything that he will never be.
What?
I don't understand
anything you're saying.
Where's Donny?
Roma, love, it's the wrong act.
It's not an act.
God,
my head is on fire.
Bring Mommy a Vicodin.
I'm starting to feel like maybe
she's not taking this seriously.
She doesn't get what's happening.
The pressure or something.
She cracked.
You couldn't take it.
This is the man from the picture.
I don't know him.
Just give it up.
Your name is Caroline.
I would never hurt you.
I bet everything on you.
I traded my life for this,
and you couldn't even...
All you had to do
was remember who you were.
You can't remember?
Nobody home?
We're going to die, and this scumbag
is going to walk because of you.
The Chinese restaurant...
you remember that!
Whoever you think you are...
- I swear, I don't want to hurt you.
- I know.
I'm counting on it.
Get the plane started.
Let's go, sweetie.
Honeymoon's over.
It's all over the news.
Arms deal gone wrong.
Your friend's plane was nabbed.
So was he.
You got your man.
She got him.
Well, she wouldn't have
if you hadn't seen
what her handler failed to.
Topher said her readings
were all over the place.
Yeah, well, concussion.
Did I fall asleep?
For a little while.
I'm sorry.
I...
I guess I wasn't exactly my best.
I'm trying to do what's right.
And I'm having a harder and harder time
figuring out what that even means.
And maybe I should have gotten
you out of here first thing.
Instead I put you through...
- I know you don't remember it, but...
- I remember everything.
Sometimes I'm someone else.
And then I come back,
but I still feel them...
all of them.
I've been many people.
I can hear them.
Sometimes suddenly.
I'm all of them,
but none of them is me?
Do you know who's real?
Caroline.
I want to find her.
I want to find all of them.
Real them.
They can be found.
We are lost...
but we are not gone.
Will you help me?
I swear, no matter what,
I'm with you.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Now that you're here.
Do you trust me?
With my life.