Previously on Dollhouse...
I can't beat you.
The FBI kicked me out for trying.
I want you to consider
becoming Echo's handler.
Everything's going to be all right.
Now that you're here.
- She's not going to...?
- Glitch?
She's fine, Agent Ballard.
My head is on fire.
All you had to do was remember
who you were.
I remember everything.
I've been many people.
Do you know who's real?
Caroline.
Will you help me?
Goodness gracious, but it is
good to be out of doors.
It certainly is.
And aren't Little Sister and
Aunt Sheila having a time, though.
What a healthsome
and robust young lady you are, too.
You better watch out, Aunt Sheila.
Little Sister's playing to win!
No use in moaning about it.
What?
Me?
Well, I'd love to join.
All right.
Don't think I'll be much
match for Little Sister!
Now watch this drive.
Aunt Sheila!
That's not very sportsmanlike
to just walk off
because you don't like the way
the game is going, is it?
Right when it's my turn to play,
everyone wants to quit.
Well, not this time.
Damn it!
Aunt Sheila!
This... is not...
how we play the game!
Guess we have to find
a new Aunt Sheila.
La BrainScan Team
Dark_Chii
Gaetan753
Gernevie
Grishnak
MiniBen314
Seb
WoLF971
vous présente
2x03 - Belle Chose
I'm Echo.
I was looking for you.
I'm glad.
Would you like...
a towel?
Yes, thank you.
I'm wet.
Good day.
A treatment.
Would you like a treatment?
Yes, please.
I enjoy my treatments.
Shall I dress?
Yes, dress would be good.
And Mr. Ballard has been
given his engagement?
He has.
And any progress on locating
our troubled missing employee?
She's not really missing, is she?
She left.
Well, I call that missing.
I call that leaving.
- One doesn't just leave this place.
- Claire did.
- Claire now, is it?
- Dr. Saunders.
Where is Dr. Saunders, please?
She's not here, Victor.
There is a man... he's not his best.
Dr. Saunders can help him.
Thank you, Victor.
We'll help him.
And we can also keep looking
for Dr. Saunders, yes?
How's the patient?
Not complaining.
Considering he was hit by a car.
Have we determined yet
if the condition is reversible?
I have to finish mapping his neural
landscape but if I can figure out a way
to sneak up behind his reticular
activating system, give it a goose,
that might do it.
It could also give him
a man reaction.
I choose not to hear that.
Do we really want
to wake this guy up?
Mr. Langton, have you no charity?
We are working to reunite
a desperate family with their
wayward loved one.
By wayward, do you mean that
they've been looking for him
ever since he skipped
his last bail hearing?
A bail hearing over a minor matter
which has since been resolved.
And by resolved, do you mean...
A judge was bought off.
There is no need
to continue to translate me.
In any event, Bradley Karrens
is not only a valued client,
he happens to be a major shareholder
in our parent organization.
If we can apply our resources
to resolving his nephew's
slight medical condition,
we do it.
Report any progress.
See? We're doing good.
So your client is an Edmond Gossen.
He's a liberal arts professor
at Clairfield College.
Echo is being imprinted
as one of his students.
- What's the "R" stand for?
- That's the engagement designation.
"R" means romance.
As in R-rated?
Great.
So she's the sex fantasy
for some egghead academic
who can't get one of his real
students to sleep with him.
- Don't you just feel like dancing?
- Not overly.
You know what it is? Normally
at this time,
I'm at yoga disco. So my body's just
sort programmed to do this.
- She's not wrong.
- What is it, Thursday?
Tell me I didn't miss Gossen's lecture.
He's hard enough to understand
- even when you're there.
- You're fine.
Paul here is going to see to it
that you get there on time.
Thanks, Paul.
I'm KiKi.
First, Paul is going to
take you on a little spree.
Shopping or killing?
Joke.
Good news on the coma front?
Good news is that he's in a coma.
- I beg your pardon?
- Just show her what you showed me.
This is a brain...
a healthy brain.
Frankly, an overly smart brain.
It's my brain.
And this is Terry Karrens' brain.
See these dark areas?
How they extend all the way out
to here? You know why
that looks like that? That's because
Terry Karrens doesn't use
that part of his brain.
And that'd be where you find stored
such things as empathy, compassion,
an aversion
to disemboweling puppies.
Basically, this is what
some of your more famous
serial killers' brains look like.
You're quite certain of this?
Certain enough that I have serious
ethical problems trying to wake him up.
Topher has ethical problems.
Way to land it.
Judith, get me Bradley Karrens.
Hello.
You're new.
And of course,
you're always new.
And who are we today?
She's KiKi.
Of course she is.
Excuse me. Work order Echo.
Who's doing that?
I am.
Right, okay.
So not exactly a rocket scientist.
Normally that would be irony,
but here, one never knows.
Why don't you take Ms. KiKi here
on back and stick her in the works.
Who's going to pay for this?
Isn't that cute.
On the casa.
- Free?
- Oui, oui.
- Did I win a prize?
- You are a prize.
How long is this going to take?
Changing their insides is nothing.
The outsides... that's art.
Art takes time.
Magazine?
I won't even do this for my wife.
I was trained at Quantico.
Adelle, tell me
there's been a breakthrough.
Of a kind.
Can your people bring him back?
Convince me why they should.
What?
Bradley, when you came to me
with your request,
you assured me that
conventional medical science
would fail to revive your nephew.
That news of his condition
would be a crushing blow
- to your brother, Terry's father.
- All true.
Yet somewhat incomplete, yes?
I encourage candor.
I have a team standing by
to return him to Mercy.
A return to Mercy.
That has a poetry.
All right, all right.
All right, when I told you
the doctors said
he couldn't be revived,
that was true.
"Revived in time,"
is what I neglected to add.
In time for what?
Well, you are no doubt
aware of Terry's past,
- his troubles with the law?
- Minor offenses.
What you know about
is only what the family
hasn't been able to scrub.
There have been other...
indiscretions.
Women,
"survivors" I should call them.
And when you have a survivor, you have
a person that might be persuaded
monetarily or by other means,
to stay quiet.
But when all you have are bodies...
I see.
We can't be certain, o course,
but recent reports of abductions,
- missing persons, might suggest...
- Survivors?
Terry and I have always been close.
If there are women
out there, he'd tell me.
And I just know
that if I can talk to him...
If he is to be questioned,
we do it on my terms.
My terms.
That's all.
I'll take her.
What?
I'll cover your engagement.
You're staying here.
Why?
Turns out we have a sudden need
for an FBI profiler.
I suggested you.
For what?
To interrogate
a possible serial killer.
"Serial killer"?
Thank God.
Car!
Goodness gracious.
Hello, Terry.
Hello?
I'd like to know if I'm being
charged with something.
Do you know you have to charge me
with something eventually?
I know my rights.
How much does he know
about who he is? Where he is?
Straight brain dump.
He is Terry Karrens.
Right up to the moment
he got hit by that car.
I don't understand why you won't
just let me speak with him.
Mr. Ballard received
his training from the FBI.
He's very experience
in these matters.
We defer to him.
These missing persons reports...
Why do you think he's connected?
Just a hunch.
That's not a hunch.
A 42-year-old woman from Covina,
a 16-year-old girl from El Monte,
a 20-year-old from Whittier
and a 38-year-old from Alhambra.
I don't see a pattern here,
for some reason you do.
Who are these women?
Who are they to him?
They were in a real sense nobody.
The authors of some of the most
important medieval literature
had no concept of self identity
as we might understand it.
We think of them as anonymous.
They didn't think
of themselves at all.
And I can see many of you would rather
not be thinking of them, either.
Okay, your essays on the economics
of love in Chaucer's The Wife of Bath
are being returned to you.
If you have questions or quibbles,
my office is open.
Professor, this can't be right.
- Ms. Turner.
- KiKi.
Okay, so I probably never should've
taken this course to begin with.
But I figured it was Mid-Evil lit,
not Advanced Evil.
How hard could it be?
So I skipped
Intro to Evil or whatever,
but how is it I get an "F" when this
guy that we're reading,
Chauncy, can't even spell?
It's Chaucer.
It's Middle English.
Right like Hobbits or something.
As I said, my office is open
if you'd care to discuss it.
I'd care to discuss it. I'm like the
Scarlet Lady with the "F" on her chest.
- "A."
- If only.
The detail is exquisite.
Chaucer's detail.
Alisoun is his most
fully realized character.
Well, then he sucks,
because I don't get her.
Really?
Because I think I can detect
a little Alisoun in you.
These cuffs are digging
into my wrists.
I have no circulation!
Hello?!
Well, about time.
"Terry Marion Karrens"?
- Any part of that a boy's name?
- What?
So...
I gotta ask and I think
you know I gotta ask.
Have you been practicing
dentistry on large cats?
Leopards? Pumas?
What?
I'm just wondering
why it is you have traces
of a veterinary grade paralytic
in your system?
I demand my phone call!
I want my attorney present.
No attorneys, no phone calls.
- I know my rights.
- And no rights.
You are in big trouble.
When my family finds
out what you're doing,
you and this entire department...
- This isn't a department.
- What?
And I'm not a cop.
What do you mean?
Who are you then?
What is this place?
This is the place you're not in.
And I'm the guy
you're not talking to.
And these?
These are the women
you're going to tell me how to find.
I've never seen any
of these women before.
Take another look, Terry.
Squint if you have to.
I told you I've never seen
these women before.
I don't know them.
Let me help you out.
Mother.
Big Sis.
Little Sis.
And Aunt Sheila.
At least that's how you know them.
This is exactly the wrong
approach to take with Terry.
- He needs to know you're on his side.
- But we're not on his side.
Adelle, I know my nephew.
And you should visit your nephew.
Escort Mr. Karrens downstairs
where he can see for himself
he care being provided.
I'm sure you'll be impressed.
He's got his own private room
and we've kept him very...
clean.
You know, Terry, when I was
first told that this is what you did,
abducted women who looked like
the women you grew up with.
Who told you that?
I figured, "Hell, the sick, little twist
must've killed his family."
It's a whole Norman Bates thing.
But no. Your real mother
and sisters and your aunt
are all still living in the family home.
You know what that makes you.
Very weird.
- I'm not weird.
- No.
No, you're weird, Terry.
But what you're not is special.
It doesn't take a criminal
profiler to figure you out.
Maybe just a pimp.
It's ordinary.
You're ordinary.
Maybe you got bottle-fed,
maybe you got dumped.
It doesn't matter. At some point, you
decided real people weren't worth it.
You pushed them away.
Alienated everyone in your life
so you could surround yourself
with the fakes, the copies.
It made you feel like
you had some control.
You're not in control.
Does this look like
a guy who's in control?
Goodness gracious.
No, it's impossible. It can't be me.
It's you, Terry.
- What is this?
- You remember that car, don't you?
You think you walked away
from that without a scratch.
Is that what you think?
This is a trick.
Is it?
You need too tell me
where to find those women.
They're the reason
you're in that bed.
your Uncle Brad looks so worried
and they're your only hope
of ever getting up again.
They did this to me.
You did this to yourself.
It's her.
That one.
It's all her fault.
What about her?
She made me. I didn't mean to.
I didn't want to.
She meant for this to happen.
You bitch! You bitch!
What did she make you do, Terry?
You just want to have a nice time.
You want to have a nice day,
but they won't let you.
Because they're not nice.
They are never nice.
They care more about their dates
and their boyfriends
and they don't pay attention
to Terry.
They never let Terry play.
No time for Terry.
They are...
whores.
No, she's not a whore.
You're saying she uses sex
to get what she wants.
I'm saying she's a lusty,
bawdy, self-aware woman.
She doesn't allow men to define her.
She knows she's the one
with the real power.
What power?
The same power that all women have.
You make a nice day.
You make shade.
You put plastic
umbrellas in the drinks.
It doesn't matter.
It never matters.
But I thought women back then
had to do whatever a man said?
Alisoun knows better.
Alisoun knows it's all up to her.
She can have what she wants.
She knows how to get it.
"Meself have been the whippe."
She is the whip.
She's the one in control.
They never do what Terry wants.
They always do what they want.
She made me.
It's not my fault.
So if she were here,
and you were Chauncy...
Chaucer, and he's the author.
Doesn't matter.
She'd know how to get the "F"
on her chest turned into an "A."
You're learning.
Not literature.
But still...
But I can fix this.
I can make this right.
They'll let me play again.
We just need a new Aunt Sheila.
We know he's killed at least one.
The unfortunate,
ubiquitous Aunt Sheila.
I wasn't expecting that.
I didn't think he'd cross that line,
but it makes sense.
She probably fought back.
That's why he was wandering around
with traces of that paralytic
in his system.
He'd lost a piece and was out looking to
replace it when the accident happened.
You gleaned quite a bit in there,
all things considered.
But not enough.
By the way, smart move sending
the uncle down there.
I knew what you had planned.
It might add a touch of pathos.
He was really getting
on your nerves, huh?
Couldn't stand another moment.
- What happened?
- I don't know. His uncle was visiting
and then he went into
cardiac arrest or something.
- Where is Bradley?
- He was right here.
False alarm, it was nothing.
How was that cacophony nothing?
Somebody tampered
with the main lead.
This is entirely unacceptable.
We tried it your way.
It didn't work.
Terry's going to have a little
chat with his unc.
Everything will be fine.
Now, Terry...
He's refusing to pick up.
I would say this is
a very positive turn of events.
You think?
I do,
assuming your profile is correct.
You still believe Terry Karrens
will return to his victims?
I think he's in the market
for a new Aunt Sheila. But yeah.
All our Actives are tagged
with a GPS strip.
We can find them
anywhere at any time. So...
if there are survivors,
Victor will lead us to them.
What do you mean
he wasn't tagged? Why not?
They took his GPS strip out
before they started all that
complicated facial reconstruction.
The scar removal.
- The surgery's complete.
- Right, but Dr. Saunders
is the one who signed off
on having it taken out.
And she kind of left before
telling anybody to put it back.
Lovely, so you're saying
that we've imprinted an Active
as a serial killer and then blindly
let him loose upon the streets?
I wasn't saying that.
Victor might not have
a working GPS in his body
but maybe Bradley Karrens
has one in his car.
Funny how my mind would
never think to go there.
- What's happening?
- The stuff, it's wearing off.
Where is he?
- I don't know.
- He killed her.
- I know.
- He's going to kill us, too.
- No, he isn't.
We won't let him.
What's your name?
Megan. I'm Robin.
We have names.
Remember that.
We're human.
Not his toys.
We're getting out of here.
Find a weakness.
He's on foot.
Damn.
- Or maybe not on foot.
- What do you see?
Metrolink station.
If he got on it, he could be anywhere
from the Valley, downtown, Hollywood...
The accident.
- The hit and run, where did it happen?
- Just outside Beverly Hills.
That has to be close
to where he's keeping the women.
You think he's headed back there?
Probably with a stop along the way
to pick up a new Aunt Sheila.
The Hollywood line would put him
straight towards Beverly Hills.
I'm going to see
if I can pick up his trail.
Your one man manhunt's using
public transportation now?
Which is why you're going
to provide assurance.
Beg pardon?
We cannot allow Victor to be
used as Terry Karrens'
vehicle for abduction and murder.
I'm personally against it.
You need to free Victor of him.
Love to. He's not here.
I do know this.
A remote wipe?
It can't be done.
- Alpha did it with Echo.
- But he used a tonal interface.
Serial killer Victor would need
to have a phone. I need to have a tone.
I'd have to get him
answer the phone.
- Do you have his number?
- Obviously not.
Well...?
Think another way.
Think of it fast.
"Upon an ambler easily she sat.
"Well wimpled, aye, and over all
"a hat.
"As broad as is
a buckler or a targe."
A "targe" is a shield.
Still not following.
"A rug was tucked around
her buttocks large."
I guess a fat ass was
a good thing in the 1300's.
"And on her feet,
a pair of spurs quite sharp."
Nasty.
"The remedies of love
she knew perchance
"For of that art she'd learned
the old, old dance."
Liking that.
Where's your tune-age?
Don't you just feel like dancing?
Are you feeling my Bathy girl power?
'Cause I'm pretty sure
I'm feeling your boy power.
Now, let's talk about this "F."
Must be love. Or something.
This is Boyd.
Boyd, it's Topher.
We're trying something in here
and so we're calling
all the handlers in the field
to let them know that I'm going
to be taking the biolink grid
off-line for a few seconds. So...
When, your screen goes dead,
there's nothing to worry about.
What are you trying?
A remote wipe.
Why?
Victor's loose, doesn't have GPS
and apparently, he's a serial killer.
So, what I'm going to attempt to do
is go into his biolink feed,
which doesn't tell me
where he is, but it does give me
a way into his head.
I'm going to reverse the signal,
send a purgation tone
and blow his mind.
Literally.
Then what? Just leave him
out there in his Doll-state?
Totally wiped?
He'll be an empty-headed robot
wandering around Hollywood.
He'll be fine. We'll find him.
How will we know
if we're successful?
See this?
Right now, his vitals
are doing the mamba.
He's excited about something.
If the wipe takes,
they should flatten out.
Go.
You do have power over me.
You are an incredible woman.
What did you call me?
I am an incredible woman.
Hello, Mr. Langton,
how's your evening out?
A lot like my evenings in.
I'm afraid there's been a little bit
of a situation here.
I spoke to Topher.
- Did the remote wipe take?
- It remains to be seen.
The attempt seems to have thrown
the entire system off-line.
We'll know all
once Topher has rebuilt it.
Until then, we're blind. We need
to bring in all our field Actives.
Get them in pocket till
the situation is resolved.
- I agree.
- You'll take point on this?
Will do. I'll start sending
out the word.
- Then grab Echo and come home.
- Very good.
I thought I would make a nice day,
but they just won't let me.
You know what?
Now they don't even get
a new Aunt Sheila.
Full recall.
Everybody's coming home.
Hang on. That's my other line.
This is Boyd.
Cooper, did you end the engagement?
What?
Get back to the house.
It's fine.
Everything's going to be fine.
This is Boyd.
I need an ambulance.
So how did it happen?
- Do we even know what happened?
- My best guess?
I had to access the biolink
grid for the remote wipe.
I thought I isolated Victor, but
everything must have gotten scrambled.
So we assume Terry Karrens imprint
somehow got transferred to Echo?
Either that, or my attempt
to make her hot for teacher
really didn't come off.
If Terry is in Echo,
where did KiKi go?
I'm KiKi.
I don't know how I got here.
I sort of don't care.
Am I drunk?
Hang on just a minute.
I noticed you watching me.
I think we both know why.
"As help me God,
"I laugh when I think,
how piteously a-nyght
I made them swynke!"
You know what that means?
I have no idea,
but it's wicked filthy.
How about...
buying a girl a drink
before you swynke?
You think he might be what?
You suck!
Trying to hit a girl?!
Why did you ever leave me?
You got a problem?
I got it, I got it!
Let's go.
Thank God.
We thought that you were him.
I am him.
Hello, ladies.
Ready to finish our game?
She's really hurt.
She's really hurt?
How do you think I feel?
You tried to kill me with a car.
- What?!
Don't play stupid. You think
I don't know what's going on here?
What you've been up to?
We need to get her to a hospital.
Please, Mother, always
protecting your little princess.
I am not your mother.
Then I guess I'm not your son.
You always said, "Be a man."
You do make it a little difficult.
You think...
you can make me dirty like you.
I am not...
They are... whores.
You did this to me.
Please, we just want to leave.
I'll just bet you do.
Everybody always wants
to leave Terry.
How about you, Aunt Sheila?
Huh? You still feel like leaving?
Aunt Sheila?
Aunt Sheila doesn't want to leave.
I say we all take a tip from her.
You're staying.
Did I fall asleep?
Don't engage until we know
the worm is dead.
You have to kill it in the g-line.
- The wave is hiding.
- Why is it moving?
Because it's designed to go
where it's not supposed to.
It's the whole point.
The system's still down?
Evidently.
I see you've made a friend.
I'm KiKi.
Okay, I think we're good.
All right, where is she?
Beverly Hills.
I think she's gone shopping.
Maybe they're both KiKi.
He was here.
He's still here.
He wants to kill you.
You have to kill him first.
He's coming back.
He's coming back!
Get away from the door.
- He won't let me.
- What are you talking about?
Get away from the door!
You have to kill him.
- What do you mean?
- We have to kill her.
Yes.
No problem.
He'll find you.
He won't stop.
He'll never stop, he can't.
What you're saying
doesn't make sense.
It doesn't have to make sense...
it just is.
He took you from a shopping mall.
He followed you from your house.
He'd been watching you for days.
Your little house, the yellow house.
He watched you from the street.
He sat in his car
and he watched you.
He could see your kitchen
from the street.
He saw the boy,
the redheaded boy.
He liked the way the boy looked at you.
That's why he took you.
He'll do it again.
You need to stop him
for that little boy.
You won't get another chance.
Are you okay?
I don't think so.
Would you like a treatment?
I rather like him this way.
Even though you asked me
to get into his head,
I never really could.
His uncle's having him transported
back to the hospital this afternoon.
Think he'll ever wake up?
Wouldn't it be nice if he didn't.
- Good day.
I think he dreams.
Not anymore.
Goodness gracious.