Previously on Dollhouse...
I have a message for you
from inside the Dollhouse.
Who? Who sent you?
My name is November.
Mellie. Your name is Mellie.
They've been using this body
to spy on you for months.
Don't do this.
The Dollhouse knows you know.
They will kill you.
Tell me who.
You warned the NSA Sierra was coming
so that they could plant this file
for her to find.
Get what you can out of him
about the NSA and have Topher
prep him for the Attic.
Do it.
Jack!
I'm taking him around the park.
He needs to stretch his legs.
All right.
I'll see you later.
We won't be long.
Be good.
Hey, am I ever?
Come on. Ha. Come on.
So, someone said
there was gonna be tennis...?
Is that what I said?
Because I was pretty sure
I said Long Island iced tea.
Wait, wait, there's tea in this?
We're not playing tennis?
Because I got this damn
hypercarbon racket,
or whatever the hell
this thing is.
Hey, uh, Jack...
Where's Margaret?
Addy.
Adelle?
What's wrong?
You look terrible.
Margaret, I'm sorry
to be the one to tell you.
You're dead.
Boyd.
Hey.
How's the promotion treating you?
You must be thrilled.
I mean,
you were no fun
as Echo's handler
and now you get to be
twice as no fun
as head of security.
Yeah, well.
So far, not a lot to do.
Miss DeWitt's keeping
the Dollhouse idle
for the most part,
after Dominic...
After Dominic.
Yeah.
Most of the Actives are on rest.
Echo's out, though?
Uh, yep.
What is she, uh...
Having trouble letting go,
Papa Bear?
Aw.
We put a dead lady in her.
That's what I heard,
but I didn't believe it.
A dead client?
I guess she's special friends
with Adelle, or something.
I mean, not special friends.
Although, late night,
too much wine...
So we can give you
life after death.
Only if we really like you.
Hey, uh, Boyd...
I need an Active.
What?
Why?
I'm doing my annual anterior
insular
cortex diagnostic,
and though it may sound simple,
it's actually a very complicated
super-specific imprint
and I need head of security
to sign off on a subject.
Is there risk?
Not if I know
what I'm doing.
Um...
Sierra's been idle the longest.
Look at you
with the big decisions,
big boss-man.
Life after death.
Where does that end?
Same place it begins.
Death.
This is so... stunning.
Really.
Last thing I remember
is coming here a month ago
for that dreadful
process of yours.
Well, if we'd spoken
in the meantime,
I'd have been able to tell you
about the last three weeks
of your life, but...
Well,
this way I don't have
to remember dying.
Undoubtedly a plus.
God, it's all a plus.
I mean, more life!
Can you imagine?
And this body...
Nice work, Addy.
I'm pointing
to the sky.
Shame it's only
a loaner.
That was always
the deal.
I swear I've never felt
this good.
Did being young
feel this good?
I seem to recall
it was rather nice.
I wonder why we gave it up.
Please.
You're, what, ten
years younger than me?
And, oddly,
15 years older.
Just remember,
it's temporary.
Just a chance to
indulge my curiosity.
See my own funeral.
Who wouldn't want that?
To hear what the world
really thought of us?
To count up the number
who love us?
Addy?
Are you all right?
Well, let's see.
My friend just died.
Come on.
We've got a funeral to go to.
Then maybe you can
help me wrap this up.
Wrap this up?
Your life?
Well, I thought maybe
I'd solve my murder.
massive heart attack.
I was perfectly healthy
and ridiculously wealthy.
And wealth can be a
dangerous thing to have.
You suspected
this might happen.
When I was three,
my nanny put ground glass
in my nap time snack.
She wasn't going
to let me eat it.
She was going to be the hero
who caught it just in time.
I snuck a cookie and spent
two weeks in the hospital.
Forgive me if I'm
the suspicious type.
You had the scans
so you could come back
and solve your own murder?
I like a puzzle.
Are you certain
you're ready for this?
Of course.
Come on, let's go in.
I used to say I'd be late
for my own funeral,
but I didn't mean it.
Not a bad turnout.
I'd like to hear more
weeping, of course.
You know, you don't have
to do that for my benefit.
Be all chipper.
Oh, come on, my dear.
I'm doing exactly
what you would.
Stiff back,
stiff lip.
You know that's
how you'd play it.
Margaret.
Not Margaret.
I'm Julia now.
You've really thought
this through.
I started mentioning
Julia now and then
to my family before
we started the scans.
I wrote myself
into my own will,
instructed the family
to expect me...
While you spy on the servants
and the family friends
and the business associates.
A spy?
No, no, Addy.
I'm a ghost.
Welcome.
We are here to remember
a very special woman.
Margaret Bashford
wasn't the first of that name.
She was a formidable
woman.
Let me introduce
you to the family.
Shh.
I want to hear
how great you were.
Over there...
Nicolas and Jocelyn.
My God.
Your children.
Watching them go
through this.
One buries one's parents.
Unpleasant, but natural.
Do let's focus.
...like her namesake, strong...
Oh, my brother William came.
I haven't seen him
in a dog's age.
Seems somewhat
the worse
for being
stupefyingly drunk.
So, no change there.
And lined up along the walls,
the loyal household staff.
The grooms from the stables.
Well, who are
all the others?
Oh, you know.
All my closest friends.
I should probably
remember their names.
Every one of
them a suspect.
Ooh, someone's tardy.
Oh...
Jack.
You never met my
husband, did you?
He is young.
Mmm.
When I met him, I stopped
becoming such a regular customer
at the Dollhouse.
I can see why.
I was a lucky woman.
Until recently.
Almost there.
Almost...
Yes.
Tell me you got Speed Force 3.
And downloaded the bonus maps.
Pizza?
On its way.
Beer in the fridge.
Dude!
Oh, I've also got this new kind
of Battleship game I invented
with real explosions.
What, like you can
really get hurt?
Yeah.
My man.
Appetizers.
Word.
Get ready to have
your ass kicked
and possibly
lose an eye.
You're a better cook
than you think.
Hmm.
I don't think pasta
should be that, um...
...snappy.
It's al dente.
That's Italian
for "Ow, my teeth."
Um...
I know the quickest way
to kill a relationship
is to take
its temperature, but...
are you okay?
I'm just tired.
Okay.
So, there's nothing new?
Nothing with work?
You don't talk about
the Dollhouse much anymore.
No. I don't.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm being...
I'll be fine.
I'm fine and you're adorable.
You're beyond
adorable, you're...
If you say "adorabubble,"
I'm leaving.
I wasn't going to,
but I love the fact
you thought it was
the next logical word.
I'll clear.
No, no, no.
Wow. What a gentleman.
Well, it could also be
I made a mess in the kitchen
and I don't want you to see.
You don't seem like
an old friend.
I was backpacking,
like the kids do.
She sort of took me
under her wing and
showed me Morocco.
Hmm. And you
stayed in touch.
She'd call and
we'd talk for hours.
We were very close.
Hmm.
I think she liked
having an outsider
to sort of share
her little insights with.
Huh.
Always gushing
about her loved ones.
You know how she was.
What?
We're talking about
the same woman, right?
Tall, blonde hair.
Margaret Merriam
Bashford.
Stern look
stuck on her face?
Mid-50s, liked horses?
Yes. Margaret.
I knew her very well.
Mom wasn't exactly
a bundle of warmth.
She tended to
push people off.
Like a bulldozer.
She did like to befriend
complete strangers
for short outbursts,
and have them stay
for the weekend
wearing all of my clothes.
Bulldozer? That wasn't a stranger.
that was Camille Beauvais,
the tennis player.
Well, she was a stranger
to me, and she was rude.
She just looked better
in your clothes than you did.
Oh, my God,
you slept with her, didn't you?
Technically, no,
we didn't sleep...
Ah, Nicky, just like me when I was your age.
Wooing all the women
and sort of
worthless.
He is not worthless.
Nicolas has loads of potential.
Margaret told me.
It's funny how you
not doing anything
was called potential,
and me working my ass off
was called a pipe dream.
This isn't a funeral for
your photography career.
Oh! What do you know, Uncle Bill?
We haven't seen you
since Mother banned you
after the boat fiasco.
I was, like, 12.
Yes, Margaret could be awful,
but so can I.
And from what I can gauge,
the two of you are hideous.
So, come on.
You should have seen our mother.
Of course, you would
have turned to stone.
Margaret was nothing
like Mother!
Your... mother.
You knew Nana?
Right now we should
be drinking...
I wasn't aware you'd stopped...
To Margaret.
To the woman she was, and to all
she left behind.
Split three ways.
I know Margaret was guarded,
but she did have
a soft side.
She fell in love with Jack.
Mm-hmm.
Well, she did like him better
than she liked us, I suppose.
She loved you.
I haven't seen much of Prince Charming.
Deep in grief, I suppose.
Well, after she slapped him down
at long last,
he's sulking.
Slapped him down?
She left him the horses.
She knew he didn't know
anything about them,
didn't care about them, but he
got them instead of money.
Don't you think... No.
That's because she treasured
the horses and she trusted him.
Well, I'm glad
that she's not around to see
how he's taking that.
Oh, what did he expect?
They were in love.
Julia, I know
we're being terribly shocking,
and you're being
charmingly loyal,
but you may want
to brace yourself.
You may be here to
mourn Margaret Bashford,
but the rest of us,
we just live here.
Hey.
Oh, Nicolas.
I needed some air.
I think I need to explain
something about tonight.
Mother thought sentiment
made you... cloudy.
I know we sound harsh,
but she never
would've wanted
a bunch of flowery tributes
that people didn't mean.
She was that hard?
Well, a lot of it was fear.
Huh. She was terrified
that we'd have no ambition,
so she made us work
for everything.
I like numbers, percentages.
So, she decided I'd
work on Wall Street.
Rode me about it every day.
She wouldn't let it lie.
That's not so...
I was 12.
She wanted the best for you!
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm not trying to lecture you.
I'm trying to...
comfort you.
You are?
Inside, she...
She told me that she cried
over all your pains,
and she thought...
she thought all the time
about what it was like
when you were small
and she could hold you and...
and how proud she was
when you grew into this
handsome, confident man.
Whoa!
Are you, uh, gonna...
Ugh! I don't, uh...
Yeah?
I don't think so.
You okay? Want
some water? No?
No. I'm okay.
Okay?
Well, I mean, it seemed
like you wanted to...
No.
Subconsciously?
No!
You said
you wanted to comfort me.
Not with my tongue.
You also checked out my body.
I saw that.
God! Oh!
Okay, well,
this is a new personal
worst for me.
I'm so sorry.
I had too much wine.
Look, I...
gotta go.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh, hey.
Wrong room, my mistake.
No, wait.
You must be Julia.
Margaret told me
about you.
I don't know
how I got so turned around.
Well, it's a big place.
Jack...
what Margaret did--
I hope you know
it was a gesture of trust.
What-what... what she did?
Leaving you the horses.
It was her way of saying
she knew you weren't in this
for the money.
Right.
So you get it?
The, uh... horses...
her real loves...
my reward.
Her real...? No.
That's...
You were with them
tonight, weren't you?
They call me a killer
or just a gold digger?
Killer?
Why would they say that?
Search me.
Inheritance like I got?
Not exactly worth
killing for, is it?
Addy, it's just so...
ugly.
I love these people,
but I don't like them.
What if one of them...?
Oh, God.
Killed you?
Am I being paranoid?
You spent a year and a half
having regular painful
brain scans
because you thought
someone was going to murder you.
So, paranoid
is still a contender.
I thought it would be a maid.
Margaret...
Someone who resented my money.
A distant friend, maybe.
God, Adelle,
there's just so much anger.
At least the first time I died
thinking people loved me.
All just a worthless illusion.
Illusions aren't worthless.
They're at the heart
of most relationships.
I suppose you'd be out of a job
if they weren't.
We'll figure this out.
Of course.
I should've stayed dead.
Yes?
Eternal life.
Nice adjective.
Excellent noun.
Is there more?
Is that something
we offer now?
Because...
...if it is, that's...
You realize that's the beginning
of the end.
Life everlasting--
it's...
it's the ultimate quest.
Christianity,
most religion, morality
doesn't exist
without the fear of death.
I'm not planning on presiding
over the end
of Western civilization.
This is a one-time situation.
You know that you're asking her
to voluntarily die
when the time comes.
Well, if she resists,
I have a new head of security
who handles that kind of thing.
Hmm.
Yes, ma'am.
You can still help
Echo, you know.
Tell me your take on this.
First instinct.
Follow the money.
That's not easy.
It is when the money runs.
I've looked into the horses.
One of them, King's Ransom, was
a derby contender not long ago.
So the husband stands
to make a bundle.
So does the buyer.
I thought I'd send someone to
take a look around the stables.
A breeder with a naturally
curious streak.
Drew Chilton?
Glad to meet you.
Thanks for coming
all the way out here.
Well, you've got
some fine incentives.
Yes, I do.
One in particular.
Right this way.
Hope you've been
treating him right,
a fine horse like that.
Oh, fresh water,
fresh oats,
and barbecue
on the weekends.
Who among us could
ask for more?
So, this place been
in your family long?
Hey.
Go away.
Sure.
Wait. I'm... I'm sor... sorry.
Um... I'm just...
God, I'm so emo.
Are you?
Uh...
I have to say,
there's a part of me
that's not sad
to see someone
mourning my friend.
Is that what this is?
You lost your mother.
It's only natural
you'd be so elmo.
Emo.
That's not a word, sweetie.
God, you sound just like her.
She didn't even know me.
She didn't know me
any more than you do.
She didn't want to.
I'm sure that's not true.
I take pictures.
I'm good.
She never came to a single one
of my exhibitions.
You were serious about that?
I mean, obviously
you were serious about that.
You're right.
That was very bad of her.
I don't... I don't know
what to say.
All of her lectures
about being practical,
and then she throws herself
at some little tropical cookie
she picked up in Manila.
He is my age!
Some tropical...
Jocelyn!
He played her like a fool.
He spent her money,
and he probably slept
with every woman
who set foot in this place.
Did he...
Tell me, did he ever try...
With me?
God, no.
Although I wouldn't
put it past him.
If you don't believe me,
go talk to him.
When your ass hits the sheets,
you'll know.
I spent my whole life,
watching her being...
you know, tough,
and it was okay
that she didn't let me in
because she didn't
let anyone in.
Right?
And then, uh...
two years ago, she meets Jack,
and she's all fluttering
and whispering secrets,
and then...
now there's you.
Whatever.
Holy...! Oh.
Sorry.
You can't be here.
I need you to run some prints.
They're entered,
all keyed up.
Just need authorization.
Comfy?
I... I shouldn't do this.
I got prints
on someone
who might be a missing person.
You got prints on someone
who might be a Doll, you mean?
They are missing people,
you know.
They just... don't know it.
My God, it's her.
How do we access the file?
Polly Keller?
Oh, my God.
What...?
They're gone.
What just happened?
I just started to believe you.
Earth-identical gravity and
atmosphere on other planets.
Is that two?
I'll give you one.
That's fair.
One ecosystem
for a whole planet.
Good.
Human-alien cross-breeding
without scientific intervention.
Nice.
Flame-y explosions
and sound in a vacuum.
Yes!
Good job.
Oh, but there's
so much more.
Light speed travel, space storms
and a sexy sexy alien.
Uh-uh, I said
classic sci-fi errors.
Now you're just attacking
good storytelling.
Speaking of sci-fi,
can we play with the sleepies?
No.
Come on, Topher.
We could have them
battle one another
and bet on them
like gladiators.
We can't play with the sleepies.
Or we could have them
act out skits we write,
film it and see who gets
more hits on YouTube.
That's...
not a bad idea, but no.
You want to play chess?
A variant? Flying chess.
Excellent.
But how about
every time you lose a piece
you drink?
Sounds good.
Advantage, me.
Hey.
I couldn't
help, but...
Are you going somewhere?
Yep.
I got the first ticket
to Not Here.
Margaret belonged here.
I didn't.
I just belonged to her.
She seemed very devoted to you.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Was it hard?
Was what what?
Being married to someone older?
A man like you
would have options.
Hand me that tie?
Maybe you didn't
exercise those options.
Maybe...
maybe you waited
very patiently
till you were free.
I know who you are.
I don't know
which of them hired you,
but I know a spy
when I see one.
What are you trying
to find out?
If I killed her,
or if I'm onto
the person who did?
Either way, what
Wearing her perfume,.
trying this
summer stock seduction.
You working for Nicolas?
Jocelyn?
Tell them they're looking
in the wrong place.
Tell them I'm
selling the horses
because I can't stand
the constant reminder
of the woman I loved.
Oh.
They want a
real bad guy--
tell them to look at
dear old Uncle Bill.
He just came
for the funeral.
Oh, no.
Didn't he mention that?
He came the day
before she died.
He did?
That was after
the last...
the last time I spoke
to Margaret.
He showed up
out of nowhere.
Needed to talk to her.
About what?
She said she'd
tell me later.
If I had to guess,
I'd say he wanted
to borrow money.
And I guess she said no.
William?
h, there, there you go, boy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, okay.
Not short on spirit.
Oh, gorgeous.
I worked with his sire
a few years back.
This one's got better hooves.
What about EIPH?
No history of
hemorrhaging.
His lungs are fine.
Who the hell are you?
I'm gonna buy this here horse,
if everything works out.
He barely waited for her body
to be in the ground.
What was that?
This was my mother's horse.
It was her favorite... thing.
I can't believe
the bastard's selling it.
He should.
This horse has got another
year of racing in him.
You think so?
At least.
Won't fetch this price
forever, though.
You know what, I don't want
to hear about it.
Whatever you're
doing, stop.
Stop thinking, stop testing.
He's not for sale.
Do you believe in ghosts?
Uh, sort of.
Just recently.
Margaret and I moved into
this house when we were kids.
We were convinced
it was haunted.
Slept in the same bed
the first night.
Anyway--
I'm getting the same
creepy feeling again, now.
Like Margaret is lingering here.
And she's angry.
Why would she be angry?
'Cause she wanted more time.
You know, we hadn't said
one word to each other
in 13 years.
She wouldn't pick
up the phone.
'Cause she was
too damn stubborn.
And you?
Why wouldn't you call?
'Cause I was too
damn stubborn.
But fate grabbed an old fool
by the scruff of his neck
and brought me here.
Just in time.
The day before she died.
I just knocked
on the door.
Can't say she was thrilled
to see me at first,
but I expected as much.
The important thing--
we reconciled.
Can you...
can you tell me what she said?
"Hey, remember the time...?"
"Yeah, yeah."
No, it wasn't
the words that mattered.
It was...
she just looked in my face
and I looked
in hers.
And we just both knew there
was no reason to stay mad.
Here's to you, Margaret.
Mm.
Well, I guess I was
the lucky one.
Nicolas would be coping
with this better
if he'd talk to her
about his debts and all that.
Addiction--
not for the faint of heart.
In a world where all men
are guilty until proven dead,
one man stand as our only hope
in the fight against...
Aw!
I told you I've
got your back.
Nice.
Or "I told you
you'd get it in the end."
"The quickest way to a man's
heart is through his back."
"I'm sending you back
to the future... of being dead."
This one's going nowhere.
What are we at?
Tied up. Best of seven?
Eleven.
Hey, you.
How was your day?
Uh, you know,
fine I guess.
I let myself in
a little while ago.
Hope you don't mind.
You have a key.
I know, but it's just...
your apartment
and with everything lately,
I don't know, I don't
want you thinking
I'm in here nuzzling your
shirts while you're gone.
Anything weird like that.
Good to know.
I mean, they smell really good.
Some of them not so much,
but overall your shirts
are nuzzle-worthy.
Joke.
Geez,
so grumpy.
That looks nice.
It's Cabernet.
I bought it.
I should have gotten
white, though.
Red wine makes
my teeth purple.
Paul, we have to talk.
Okay.
Well, you don't have to talk,
but you have to let
me talk at you.
Because I've been
thinking a lot, and...
Just let me do this, okay?
Good.
Paul...
Mellie.
I like being with you.
I love it, actually.
And you say
everything's fine,
so I'm going to stop
asking if it is.
If that means lying next to you
while everything's not fine,
then that's
what I'll do.
I will give you
what you need and let you
take it from me.
And if you want to give back,
give back.
But it doesn't have
to mean anything.
It doesn't have
I've still got it,
don't I, handsome?
I know. I miss you more.
Strange-- he doesn't like most people.
Who's there?
I have a better question.
Did you think I wouldn't
recognize my own mother...
Mother?
Honestly, it's a relief.
I couldn't tell a soul
what was going on,
Mm-hmm.
and it was
proving difficult.
How did you know?
Well, little things,
you know,
like the way you moved.
And I watched you through
your window the other night
when you were trying to go
to bed in your old room.
Same routine as always.
You checked the shutters,
flipped the light switch
down the hall
that's impossible to find.
Nobody knows where
it is but you.
But I didn't really know
until I saw you
with King's Ransom.
Oh.
It was definitely after
I tried to kiss you.
Oh...
Well, I should
hope so.
But, I mean, how would you
ever even think it was possible?
The Dollhouse.
In Manhattan, right?
I am a customer.
Nicolas.
What? So are you.
We're all adults here, sort of.
I didn't use it
for anything like this.
I mean, life after death?
I never even
considered that.
I don't get to keep it.
I didn't think so.
Although,
the possibilities...
Living forever,
moving from body to body.
Brilliant.
People should know that
you are to be feared, Mother.
Even after death.
Feared?
Nicky,
I only ever wanted
you to be happy.
I'm your mother.
I'm supposed to
bear your burdens,
even if you
lost everything.
I couldn't stop.
Gambling is all
about ups and downs,
and when it seems like
you have all these...
all these resources,
you can just wait around
for another upswing,
so I-I kept
chasing losses...
And then you
hit bottom.
And I went below it.
Nicolas.
That's millions.
I knew that you would
be ashamed of me
and that you wouldn't
let it lie,
so I-I couldn't tell you.
I couldn't tell you.
Okay, okay.
We'll...
It'll be all right.
After you died,
part of me was relieved
because you never knew.
But now, I just want you back.
You were taken
from me too soon.
Smart boy.
You suspect that, too.
Look, he's supposed to be worth
over $4 million.
Go, go, go!
You think you can hustle me?
Oh, what the hell
do you mean?
King's Ransom
has been juiced.
Anabolic steroids,
stimulants.
Enough to make
his heart pop.
You really think you
could hide this
with a little
clomiphene citrate?
I mean, masking agents can't
hide themselves, you know.
If I wasn't looking for it,
I might have been fooled,
but I ain't a baby
in this freaking business.
You were going
for a money grab.
Trying to pass
that horse off
as race ready,
raise his value.
He looks that way now,
but a couple weeks
without that stuff,
he'll be put to pasture.
I know you're
new to this,
but in layman's terms,
you just made yourself
a $4 million pet.
He killed me.
Oh, God.
Whatever he gave
to King's Ransom,
that's what he used on me.
Okay, okay.
Calm down.
We have to think.
Why? Why don't I
just walk out there
and let him kill me twice?
I'm dead anyway.
Because you can prove
that he did it.
You can get him the
punishment that he des...
Run!
Sorry to disturb
you, ma'am.
Not at all.
Victor tested the horse
and I just got
the results.
My hunch was correct.
They were tied together.
Your friend was
killed with a drug
that was being
given to the horse.
The killer masked it, so
the coroner didn't find it.
Any idea who?
No.
If I went in...
She has a new handler.
You're going to have
to get used to it.
Yes, I guess I am.
One other thing,
Ms. DeWitt.
Are you aware of this
Topher situation?
Yes.
There's no need to address
the issue with him.
I allow him one of
these diagnostic tests
every now and again.
So, I guess Topher
can make friends.
Loneliness leads to nothing good.
Only detachment.
And sometimes the people
who most need to reach out
are the people
least capable of it.
In any case...
...it only happens once a year.
Come on, come on, come on.
He's coming.
What's your plan?
You got a gun stashed somewhere?
No. You know how
I feel about guns.
Though I'm warming up
to them right now.
Evidence.
There-There is evidence
that he killed you.
Just the drug,
but we can't prove...
No, not that.
A letter from Margaret Bashford
in her own handwriting,
written a week ago
and hidden somewhere
in this room.
Nicky, that's brilliant.
Great letter. Says that
he'd do it, when he'd do it,
and how he'd do it.
Okay.
to eat this up.
What was the date,
the day I died?
The 19th.
It's all here.
How he'll use
the same masking agent
he's been doping
the horses with to...
Jack didn't know
much about them.
Uh, we have to hurry.
Let's find a place to hide it.
How would he learn
how to drug a racehorse?
Well, he must
have had help.
It's not that hard to find
someone with that type
of knowledge, you know?
He must have, uh...
Oh, Mother.
You could never let things lie.
Nicolas.
What are you doing?
What in the hell do I have to do
to get you off my damn back,
Mother?
This was difficult the first time.
But being around you more,
it's getting easier.
Nicky, I love you.
I can even see why
you drugged King's Ransom.
You thought you could sell him,
get out of a hole.
I had to make him
worth something.
In case all you only left me
was the damn horses.
But Jack got
stuck with them.
Even better.
So, you were going to kill me,
no matter what.
It was the only way to
get out of the hole, Mom.
I didn't expect
you to come back.
Or Jack to figure out
you did it.
Jack gets into
everything, doesn't he?
My business.
My mother's bed.
I really am sorry, Mom.
No!
This is going
to sting a little.
I knew it was you.
Darling!
Are you all right?
He killed my wife.
Jack, are you all right?!
He murdered Margaret.
He killed my wife.
What the hell is going on?
Call an ambulance.
And the police.
Okay.
Margaret.
Yes?
I hope she didn't know...
didn't know the truth
about her son.
It would have killed her.
It did.
"...most likely
with clomiphene citrate
or any other drug used
to mask the doping of horses..."
My God. She knew?
"...on or around the 19th.
"You will also find
"enclosed a last will
and testament,
"adjusted in light of these
recent discoveries.
"As you may imagine,
"Nicolas now gets nothing,
"but he will be spending
his life behind bars no doubt,
"so what use would it be to him?
"In any case, that means
"more for everybody else.
Yay."
Mother wrote this?
"Jocelyn,
"I know that the tone
of this document
"may seem out of character,
"but in these final days,
I am feeling different,
"wise and full of warmth,
"and I would love to say
a few things to each of you
before I go."
That was pretty crazy last night.
I don't know if I can handle
that all the time, but...
I kind of liked it.
Not all the time, though.
So, you going to do
more hunting today?
For Dollhouse clients?
I've found one.
I don't know when
I'll have the chance
to see something
like this again.
I wish Margaret was here.
You could, um...
pretend she
could hear you.
No, I... I don't believe
in that stuff.
I just hope I did what
I could when she was here.
You know?
I tried to show her
as best I could that she was...
...he was my favorite person.
Plain and simple.
But I'll never know
if she believed me.
I have a feeling she did.
Tell me you weren't tempted,
even a little
not to come back
here today,
just to disappear
in this body.
Maybe a little.
But I've had my turn,
and the people I love
are moving on.
Besides...
Besides?
I know you, Adelle.
You're too much like me.
I wouldn't have gotten as far as the airport.
Addy?
Yes?
Will I see my whole life flash before my eyes?
Every single moment.
www.tvsubtitles.net