Previously, on The Tudors.
The king of Scotland is not coming.
But worse,
His army has ridden over the border
and is harrying our people
and killing all those
who oppose them.
Sir Thomas, you'll order our troops
to retaliate with burnings and killings.
3 hurts to every one of ours.
Those men that are made
by the king of vile birth
have been the distraction
of all the nobility of this realm.
And if God calls away the King,
they will suffer for it.
The Emperor and the King of France
are on the brink of war.
You will convey to your master it'd be
foolish to contemplate an invasion.
On the contrary, he regards England
as his natural ally against the Emperor.
I mean to show these French that I won't
shy away from battle if I am provoked.
Until recently, nothing but war
had been talked of.
Something inside me is disappointed.
It hungers for a war.
I actually thought the French
might oblige me this time?
The letter accuses Queen Katherine
of dissolute living
before she was married
and that her way of life isn't a secret.
Do not desist until you've reached
the bottom of the pot.
You are confined to your apartments
for as long as it please the King.
Why? Why must I stay here?
- Francis Dereham, you are under arrest.
- Under arrest? For what?
I don't believe that you didn't have
carnal knowledge of the Queen.
Someone else has succeeded me
in her affections!
- Who?
- Thomas Culpepper.
But it was Katherine who led me on.
She wanted it, not me.
"Katherine Howard, you led the King
by word and gesture to love you,
"concealing your contract
with Francis Dereham,
"and after marriage, you showed
the same Dereham notable favour
"while inciting Thomas Culpepper
to carnal knowledge,
"telling him you love him
above the King."
What has happened is your fault.
You solicited me to marry her.
How misfortunate I am
to have so many ill-conditioned wives.
No! Henry!
Henry's Team
www.sous-titres.eu
www.seriessub.com
Tr.: YYets.
Are you dressed?
Not quite, I was reading.
Come and sit. I have some news.
- What is it?
- I just heard!
By Act of Parliament,
you and I are both
restored to the succession.
After Edward and his heirs,
of course.
The King himself
must have commanded this.
Are you not pleased, Elizabeth?
Think what this means.
Yes, Mary. If you are pleased
then so am I.
It means that the King
loves both of us.
And that you may be Queen some day.
And you,
Queen Elizabeth.
What's wrong?
Because of what happened
to Queen Katherine,
I have made my mind up.
In what?
As God is my witness,
I shall never marry!
Never!
Your Majesty, His Excellency
the Imperial Ambassador.
- Excellency.
- Your Majesty.
Your Majesty is most gracious.
I am sure Your Majesty is aware.
My master, the Emperor
is once more at war
with King Francis.
The French King's despicable
alliance with the Turk
threatens not only the borders
of the Emperor's domains,
but also the security
of the whole of Europe.
For that reason alone,
his Imperial Majesty has asked me
to offer the hand of friendship
to Your Majesty once more,
in joint alliance
against the perfidious French.
What would I gain?
All your lost territories.
The whole of Aquitaine.
Excellency.
Risley!
His Excellency,
the French Ambassador.
- Monsieur Marillac.
- Your Majesty.
I hear your country is at war,
with the Emperor.
Indeed.
The Emperor has broken all his promises
and treaty obligations,
both to my master King Francis,
and to you.
Monsieur Marillac,
when you signed a treaty,
your master agreed to pay
an annual pension to this country,
which he has defaulted on
for the past two years.
As a consequence, he now owes
arrears of a million crowns.
- Majesty, if that is true...
- You doubt my word, Monsieur Marillac?
Then...
His Majesty will be informed.
And redress will surely follow.
The alliance between our countries
has kept the balance of power
in Europe for over ten years.
Surely Your Majesty would not care
to compromise that arrangement now,
in the face of Imperial aggression?
I want you to write a letter
to the King of the Scots.
Tell him that we invite him
to sign a treaty
acknowledging our suzerainty
over his country.
Also to tell him to stop
his French and Papal alliances,
or suffer the consequences for it.
I want you to prepare
to go to Scotland
in case my cousin refuses
to concede to our demands.
And take Surrey with you.
You play very well, Mr. Leigh.
Always the sign of a wasted life.
You know,
you and I have
more in common
than you might imagine, my Lord.
What?
Our families
both come from St. Mary's parish
in Stockwell
and our chapels were
founded in the same year.
That hardly makes us equal,
Mr. Leigh.
There is another thing.
Like you,
my family... was related
to the late Queen.
Do not you think it unseemly
to raise her ghost at court?
I think it unseemly
that you Howards turned a blind eye
to her despicable wantonness,
which tarnished the reputations
of all of us associated with her!
"You Howards!"
Is that what you just said?
"You Howards"?!
Guards!
I'll cut your tongue out,
so help me God!
I'll cut your fucking tongue out!
Get off me!
Lord Latimer,
Sir Thomas Seymour.
How good of you to come.
Please...
Please forgive my infirmities.
As you can see, I am not a well man.
I trust your Lordship
will soon recover.
I am afraid my health
is too far broken to be mended.
Allow me to present my wife,
Catherine Parr.
Catherine, Sir Thomas Seymour.
Please. Sit down, Sir Thomas.
I do not know if you are aware
of my personal history?
The Latimers are
an old northern family.
And, unfortunately, we were caught up in
the late Rebellion against His Majesty.
I myself,
was taken hostage by Robert Aske
and sore constrained by him.
His Majesty demanded that
I reject Aske which I did,
and came to London to submit to him.
Still I think the shadow of treason
hangs over me and my family.
I know you have the ear of the King.
I would like you to make submission
on my behalf to His Majesty,
of my utter loyalty...
There, my darling.
Close your eyes and rest now.
Do you think he suspects anything?
No, nothing. I'm sure of it.
He cannot be long for this world.
Hush! Don't say such things.
I only meant that I cannot wait until
we can be together, and married.
As truly as God is God,
I desire to marry you
above all others.
The Earl of Surrey has written
a letter to Your Majesty's Council.
The Earl is presently
detained at the Fleet Prison.
Prison? What for?
It seems he was in an affray
with one John Leigh
within the verge of the court
and was arrested by
the Sergeant-at-Arms.
The cause of the quarrel?
I believe it touched upon...
his Lordship's pride.
- What does he write?
- He demands his immediate release.
- Have you replied?
- We informed his Lordship
that his lack of humility would only
impair his prospects of liberty.
And why does he say
he should be released?
He infers that the Earl of Surrey
has no business being
so treated in the first place.
He also speaks
of his readiness to serve
Your Majesty on active duty.
I think he is the most foolish
proud man in all of England.
Set a high surety on his future
behaviour, but release him.
I want him in Scotland.
Go on with your Scottish pride!
My Lord Surrey, here are three
of their nobles captured in battle.
Lord Cassilis, Lord Glencairn,
and Lord Maxwell.
My Lords,
you will be treated
with the honor and respect
due to your rank and station.
In the name of His Majesty,
King Henry VIII,
I invite you to return
with us to London,
where you will be most
comfortably housed.
However, I must ask you
to surrender your swords.
Aye.
Come with those horses
and bring the rope!
My Lords, a great victory
was had by us at Solway Moss.
Thanks to my Lord Hertford
and to my Lord Surrey,
several Scottish nobles were captured
and are held here at our pleasure.
But that, my lords,
is not the end to our good news.
Distracted by his grievous defeat,
the King of the Scots took to his bed,
and died just two days ago.
And on that day, his wife
gave birth to their only child.
And it was not the son and heir
that they had hoped for,
but a girl.
Your Majesty,
I think we should see it
as an act of divine intervention,
this passing of the Scottish crown
to a very young female...
Thanks be to God.
Thanks be to God, indeed.
It shall be a very happy Christmas.
In the absence of a Queen, I've asked
Mary to preside over the festivities.
Also, my son will be performing
his first public duties.
- My Lords.
- Your Majesty.
I was told you considered my treatment
of the Earl of Surrey far too lenient.
You said he deserved
a greater punishment.
- I simply thought...
- What business do you have to think?
If I were you I would not think,
if thinking makes me come
to the wrong conclusion.
Get out, Tom.
- You look beautiful.
- My Lord.
May I wish you
a very happy Christmas.
- Lady Mary.
- Catherine.
How is Lord Latimer?
No better.
He did not feel strong enough
to come to court.
I am so sad for him and for you.
I pray for both of you.
I thank you for that.
I will give him your good wishes,
and Happy Christmas.
Happy Christmas.
His Excellency,
the French Ambassador.
Excellence.
Enchanté!
Prince Edward and Lady Elizabeth.
Edward.
Don't be so impatient.
The Earl and Lady Hertford.
Prince Edward.
My Lords, may I present His Grace,
- Prince Edward.
- My Lords.
Your Grace.
You are most welcome to His Majesty's
court at this Christmas time.
Your Grace is very kind
to speak to us in person.
I have been practicing.
Well done. Now come.
Lady Scofield and Lady Davit.
My Lords,
the King has a proposal
to put to you.
There should be a peace
treaty between our countries
and a formal betrothal
between Prince Edward
and the newly born
Princess Mary of Scots.
The King is not unaware
of possible difficulties.
Which is why,
if you support the cause,
you will be rewarded
with a handsome pension
and will be released at once
to return to Scotland.
I am sure your families are missing
you greatly at this time of year.
I know how I should feel, if I were
separated from my own dear wife.
Your Grace.
Welcome back to court.
- Is the Duchess not with you?
- No.
She's...
the Duchess does as she pleases.
We live mostly separate lives.
I'm very sorry.
I will pray for your reconciliation.
How is the King?
He has been melancholy
as you might have supposed.
I think he despairs of finding
any happiness in this life.
But in the last few weeks
his mood has altogether changed.
Why, I cannot explain.
Triumph in Scotland, perhaps?
- Your Grace.
- His Majesty the King!
- Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas Your Majesty!
Bravo!
- Your Majesty.
- What is it?
The Lady Latimer is come
to petition Your Majesty
to lift the suspicion of treason
from her husband, Lord Latimer.
Where is she?
What does any of this
have to do with you, Tom?
Nothing, Your Majesty.
Except that I'm a friend
of the family.
I believe in Lord Latimer's
complete loyalty to Your Majesty.
I think your mind works another way
and to another purpose.
No, no. Don't deny it!
Nor can I blame you.
She is still a very handsome woman,
and soon to be a very rich widow.
Bring her to me.
- Your Majesty.
- Tom.
- Lady Mary.
- My Lord.
My apologies, I have recently been away
from court. I am not privy to the King.
Ambassador, excuse me.
You've been a long time
absent from court, Your Grace!
Only to tend to my estates,
Your Majesty.
I rather thought you'd been
careful of me.
You imagine
I'm still angry with you.
You can be too careful, Your Grace.
It's very remiss of you
to neglect your sovereign for so long.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Anyway, I want you
to do something for me.
- Your Grace!
- I need to speak to your master.
Alas, Your Grace, my master is in bed
with gout and in the greatest agony.
No, no. Show His Grace in,
by all means.
Your Grace must forgive me.
Of course.
I have brought something for you.
May I ask its import?
It contains the outlines
for a secret treaty between our masters.
The recent seizures of English
merchant ships in the French ports,
and the French King's
new amity with the Turks
are the final straw.
King Henry promises
to support the Emperor
whenever he is called upon to do so.
He also pledges to invade France in
conjunction with the Emperor's armies.
Your Grace
could not have made me happier
if you had brought me
a cure for gout!
I will make sure this is delivered
to the Emperor immediately
you can be sure that he will receive it
with the very greatest pleasure.
Your Majesty,
Lady Latimer is here.
I wanted to assure you
there is no suspicion
of treason against your husband,
still less against
you and your family.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I know very well the cause
of the distress to Lord Latimer
during the late rebellion.
I also know that you
and your stepchildren
were very roughly handled
by the traitor Robert Aske.
You must have been very frightened,
My Lady.
Well, at the time, Sir,
I was more frightened
for my husband,
for his safety and his sanity.
I hear that Lord Latimer is unwell.
He is very ill indeed, Your Majesty
and not likely to live long.
You have no children by him?
No, Your Majesty.
Nor by your first husband?
No.
I was married at seventeen
to Edward Borough,
the son of Lord Borough.
But he died three years later.
I was told he was insane.
Is it true?
It was not a happy marriage,
Your Majesty.
Do you think such a thing exists?
Yes!
I believe so
with all my heart and soul.
Ah... please forgive me.
No, no.
You are to be congratulated,
Lady Latimer,
for your...
eternal optimism.
Your Grace,
His Majesty has sent
these papers for your attention.
Thank you, Mr. Risley.
Mr. Risley,
you know I'm sure
that the King has made a
secret treaty with the Emperor,
the great champion of Catholicism!
Well, as a result, I see no reason
why we should not start
hunting down all the Lutherans
and Evangelicals
in His Majesty's Kingdom.
Do you think there are many such?
I know it!
They breed like rats.
They spread the vile disease
of their heresy everywhere!
Some of them, even now,
are very close to the King.
And...
we should flush them out?
Exactly.
And set them
on the pyres at Smithfield.
Don't you agree, Mr. Risley?
Parcels, sweetheart?
Who from?
From the King.
The King?
Parcels from the King?
Are you not going to open them?
- Yes.
- Open them then.
What are they?
Pleats... and sleeves.
For dresses.
Let me look.
- Are they fashionable?
- Yes.
Why should the King
send you presents?
I don't know. I think
that I should return them.
You cannot return
presents to the King.
You must acknowledge them.
I don't know why he has sent them.
Yes you do, my love.
Yes you do.
I feel as though I am dead already.
I call upon His Gracious Majesty,
King Henry VIII,
to pledge before God
and these witnesses
to honor this new Treaty
between His Majesty
and King Charles V,
the Holy Roman Emperor.
This treaty of mutual assurance
contains within it an obligation
to undertake a war against France
within two years of this date,
to which His Majesty
agrees to send 40,000 men-at-arms
for that purpose.
Your Majesty,
do you pledge to honor
all the terms of this new treaty?
I do, so help me God.
- Will you sign the Treaty?
- I will.
Finally.
Your men shall see France.
So Excellency,
is it true that a treaty
has been signed
between His Majesty and the Emperor?
I don't understand.
What, but the design
of subjugating Christendom,
could make a revengeful prince
like the Emperor forget the insult
done to him by the King of England,
in the person of his aunt?
Those insults are long forgotten,
Monsieur Marillac.
You don't deny then,
that your master plan is
to subjugate
the whole of Christendom?
I do deny it.
I believe those ambitions
are held by the Turks,
with whom your own master
is in alliance!
- Excellency!
- Your Grace.
May I present you with a formal
intimation of war against your country.
Lady Latimer is here, Sir Thomas.
My God, look at you!
You look so very beautiful.
What is it?
This dress was a gift.
A gift?
- From whom?
- From the King.
When did the King start
sending you presents?
Recently.
I gave him no cause!
No. Of course not.
How could you?
You do believe me, don't you?
Please say that you believe me.
Thomas, I love you.
I never sought these advances
from the King,
do not welcome them.
You would not...
- like to be Queen of England?
- No!
For heaven's sake! You know
what happens to his Queens!
Everyone knows what happens.
I'm afraid.
Well, don't be.
He's just a lonely man
that has set his cap at you.
I hope so.
Your Majesty should know
that the Regent Queen of Scotland
has given permission
for negotiations to begin
regarding a marriage contract
between her daughter Mary,
soon to be Queen of Scots,
and your son, Prince Edward.
After the negotiations are complete,
a treaty will be signed,
uniting through marriage
the English and Scottish thrones
as Your Majesty so desires.
It seems our Noble Scottish lords
did as we bid them.
Majesty, with an infant Queen,
a quarrelsome nobility,
and a lack of French support,
- what choice do the Scots have?
- I agree.
I ask you to expedite negotiations
and not let this opportunity pass.
I don't always trust the Scots.
Your Grace, you tabled an item?
Your Majesty,
I regret to have to inform you
that we have discovered
a nest of heretics
at the very heart
of Your Majesty's household.
Of whom do you speak?
The musicians of the Royal Chapel.
All of them?
The Master of Choristers,
John Marbeck,
stands accused of being
a secret Calvinist.
Also, the Organist,
Robert Testwood and Edmund Harman,
a singing man.
Do we have permission
to arrest and examine these men?
Your Grace, I give you license.
I will have no Evangelicals
or traitors in this household.
And for those who wish
to alter or push my Reformation
to the extremes, I say this:
there will be no alteration
to the Church of England
as long as I live!
John Marbeck. Robert Testwood!
Edmund Harman! You are all
under arrest.
Seize him!
You should not have come here,
Mr. Testwood.
My Lord, where else could I go?
Please help me.
I beg of you.
There is nothing I can do,
without condemning myself,
and that I will not do.
You are only to be examined
by Gardiner.
If you answer him as he desires,
- then what have you to fear?
- I fear, my Lady,
that His Grace will then resort
to other means of persuasion,
since that is the way now.
Then you must be strong in
your faith, Mr. Testwood.
We all know the day may come
when we have to walk
in the path of Christ.
But if we are afraid,
if we turn away,
then we have no right to call
ourselves true Christians.
If you so much as mention
my husband's name,
I assure you that things will
go very badly with your family.
Your sweet wife
and those two lovely children.
People tell me that you
have been unwell, Lady Mary.
I trust not too unwell.
I thank you.
The surgeons have bled me
once or twice, I think to be better.
God willing.
- Yes, God willing.
- My Lady.
Tell me what is happening in court.
Is the King thinking
of marrying again?
There is a new law enacted.
It requires that any lady
the King may marry must,
on pain of death,
disclose any charge
of sexual misconduct
that might be brought against her.
Frankly, my Lady,
this rather narrows the field.
The ladies at court are...
how to say
not exactly known for their virtue.
I still think the King
will want to remarry.
It is true he has a son,
but he will need another son
to feel secure,
- in case the first should die.
- You are right.
And yet, what woman on earth
would want to marry a King
who either puts his wives away
or kills them?
Master Testwood.
Enough heretical material
was discovered
in your house to have you condemned
as a secret Calvinist.
However, I would fain save you,
but you must help me first.
Just think.
The pain you suffer now
will be as nothing
compared to the pains of the fire.
And all because you...
falsely, mistakenly, treacherously
shelter those above you.
If you will just confess to me
their names.
There is an usher of the King's,
Sir Philip Holby.
Is he one of your heretic circle?
No.
Dr. Simon Heynes,
the Dean of Exeter?
You sang for him once, I think?
Is he another
of your secret heretics?
And what of the Earl of Hertford?
You give me the Earl of Hertford,
and I will give you back your life.
An excellent plan, Your Majesty.
Of all the hook stories,
this is my favorite.
- Do you agree?
- Indeed.
How is your husband, Lady Latimer?
I'm afraid he has taken to his bed,
Your Majesty,
and lately made his will.
I am very sorry to hear that.
I must thank Your Majesty
for this beautiful dress,
and your other generous gifts,
of which
I have done nothing to deserve.
You looked very sad, my Lady.
I am sure your recent life has
been difficult for you.
I wanted to give you something
to give you good cheer.
I wanted to see you smile.
There.
We will soon be at war with France.
How is it, My Lord Suffolk?
- It cannot come soon enough for me.
- I agree.
The war will be a chance for us
to exceed
even the glories of Henry V
at Azincourt.
- And you, My Lord Surrey?
- Majesty, my kind always
desires the honor of the field.
And what better field than France?
Aye.
Do you play cards, Lady Latimer?
Yes, Your Majesty. I do.
Good.
The King seems quite taken
with Lady Latimer.
It's true.
And we know that when he takes
a fancy to a person or a thing,
he usually goes the whole way.
Perhaps that is why he's so happy.
My Lord,
what happened to those musicians
who were arrested?
Gardiner examined them.
He was not satisfied
with their answers,
all three have been transferred
to the Tower.
May I ask why Your Grace is curious?
Yes. You may ask.
Excuse me, brother.
Your hand, my Lady.
Your prize.
- No, Your Majesty.
- Please.
Your Majesty, I couldn't.
Look inside.
Majesty,
although I am so touched,
and flattered,
I cannot accept this ring.
Please...
accept this for me.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I have news for you.
- Majesty?
- I'm sending you to Brussels,
on embassy to the court
of the Regent of the Netherlands.
Does it please you, Sir Thomas?
I'm...
I'm very grateful to Your Majesty.
Good.
Is Your Majesty considering
another marriage?
Perhaps.
- And a war in France?
- For certain.
- Do you really want to fight again?
- Yes.
Don't you?
I thought you did.
- ... take another wife?
- Yes.
Am I not still able?
To have a wife?
To have more children?
To be myself?
Requiem aeternum dona es Domine,
et Lux perpetua Au luceat.
John, I need to say
something to you.
Go to hell...
In nomine Patris et Filii et
Spiritus Sancti. Amen.
Catherine Parr,
we are sent here
by the King's Majesty to offer you,
after your days of mourning
for your late husband are complete,
his Majesty's hand in marriage.
His Majesty esteems you
above all other women in his kingdom
and hopes to find you well disposed
towards his offer,
in which case he will be
the happiest man in England,
and you the happiest woman.