The Tudors 302
Synchro : Flolo Transcript : yyets.net
Sir Thomas.
- What's the news?
- This matter hangs like a fever
one day good, another bad.
With the promise of a pardon,
and the threat of an advancing
royal army, the rebels in
Lincolnshire have dispersed
- and gone home.
- And in Yorkshire?
In Yorkshire and the
whole North we are facing
the most dangerous insurrection
that has ever been seen.
The rebels entered the
town of York three days ago
and celebrated mass in the
cathedral; some say they intend
to march South.
- "Your Majesty, I write
to you on an urgent matter.
"We've had word that a
pilgrim army is marching
"on to Pontefract Castle,
which is under my command.
"I am compelled to tell you
that I can't defend this castle
"without more soldiers and arms.
"As the warden of the East
Marches and a loyal member
"of Your Majesty's council
"I beg Your Majesty to consider
negotiating with these pilgrims.
I remain your humble and
obedient servant. Darcy."
What is it? What have you found?
A splinter of bone, Your Majesty.
You told me before it was an
ulcer. That it was easily cured!
A wound like this, Your Majesty...
Jesus Christ! You don't know
what it is, do you? Do you?
Your Majesty must not be
alarmed. We shall apply
a poultice to draw any more
splinters to the surface.
Then we shall look to other remedies
to heal permanently
Your Majesty's wound.
You treat me like a fool.
Everyone here treats me like a fool.
Get out.
Get out!
- Majesty...
You're quacks and charlatans.
I will find my own remedies.
- Your Grace.
- My Lord,
I was promised artillery
when I arrived here.
But I don't see any guns.
Your Grace, we have guns but
we have not been unable to find
any horses or drays to transport them.
Perhaps you don't understand.
I am about the King's
most urgent business.
And if you cannot commandeer
some horses for his Majesty's
use then how can you call
yourself Mayor of London?
Your Grace, I did not want to
produce panic by forcing people
to part with their horses or drays.
IDIOT!
I charge you
personally to find enough
horses within two days and bring
the guns on after our army
- or God help me I will hold you
to account. With any luck, Mr.
Mayor, I will afterwards get
the chance to see you
disemboweled at Tyburn!
- Lady Rochford?
- Madam,
the King is still confined to his
chambers by his physicians' orders,
but sends his regrets
and hopes you are well.
I worry for him so much.
Especially at such a time.
Your Majesty is right to do so.
These rebels are nothing but villains;
they are totally alienated
from true religion.
They want to take us
back to the dark days
of ignorance and
superstition. And by force!
I hope to God they
will soon be overcome.
- Yes. Lady Rochford,
I have something I wish
you to arrange for me.
I'm sure it will give the
King a great deal of pleasure.
My God, Lord Darcy.
What a sight is there!
Arrant rebels against the King's Majesty
brazenly bearing their badges of shame!
Indeed so, Your Grace.
I never thought in all my
long days to see such a sight.
What are you going to do? Fire on them?
You know very well I have
almost no useful guns.
You could resist them all the
same, and close your gates.
After all those are the King's orders.
As to that, I think it
better to talk to them first,
as fellow Englishmen
and fellow Christians.
I'll meet their leaders
outside the castle walls.
Guards!
- My Lord Darcy, Your Grace, we come here in peace.
- Mr. Aske.
As the King's representative
I have the means here
to hinder you and to do
some injury to your cause.
My Lord, we have embarked
upon this Pilgrimage of Grace
for the common good, for the
love we bear to God's faith,
our Holy Church and
the maintenance of it,
for the preservation
of our sovereign King
and the expulsion of villain's
blood and evil councilors.
We mean to petition the King's highness
to stop the woeful destruction
of our monasteries and abbeys.
Master Aske, you claim
to be loyal to the King
but your very actions defy
and deny the King's supremacy!
Lord Archbishop, there is
no man now alive in England
more loyal to the King than I
am. I trust in time to prove it.
Our quarrel lies not with him, but only
with those close to him.
- It's very well for you
to sound so high and
mighty, but you and your kind
are also to blame for not
advising the King honestly
about the spread of heresy and
abuse throughout his kingdom.
For what are Cromwell
and Cranmer but heretics
and manifest abusers
of this commonwealth?
Lord Darcy, as I told you
we mean no displeasure to any person.
We ask for shelter and free passage.
All our pilgrims have taken an oath
not to slay or murder out
of envy, but to put away fear
for the commonwealth and
march with the cross of Christ
and their heart's faith before them.
But we will fight and die
if you seek to stop us.
I am putting you in charge
of the defenses here the city.
We shall need to organize new
levies. Send word to every lords
and gentlemen to be ready with
his power. Take all the weapons,
harness and ordnance
you need from the Tower.
Buy more if you need to from
the merchants in the city.
Then it's true. We are in trouble.
Mr. Cromwell, His Majesty
will receive you now.
I've just received a
letter from Lord Darcy.
He says that he is in
great danger from the rebels
and cannot maintain his resistance.
And yet he holds a
castle. A great stronghold.
Does he not mean to stand
firm against these traitors?
Your Majesty, I've just been told
that the rebels have already
entered the town of Pontefract
with overwhelming numbers.
Mr. Cromwell...
Pontefract is the gateway to the South.
It has great strategic importance.
You will write a letter
to Lord Darcy at once.
You will tell him that I expect him
to hold that castle at all costs!
Yes, Your Majesty.
And what of the royal army?
What are they doing to
crush this rebellion?
Where is his Grace the Duke of Suffolk?
And that bastard
Shrewsbury! I told him too!
What in God's name are these men doing?
Lord Darcy.
My Lord!
Darcy and York have betrayed me?
Well, we shall see
what end they come to!
And why haven't Shrewsbury
and Suffolk attacked yet?
All I hear are their
complaints and their excuses!
You know what I think?
I think they have become
afraid of their own shadows!
I have a mind to go North myself.
I'll lead the army! I'll
teach these bastard ingrates
and rebels a fearful
bloody lesson in slaughter!
I wish Your Majesty would
not consider doing so.
Why? Do you suppose I'm too feeble?
I meant that Your Majesty's
life is far too precious
to be put at risk against
such a common rabble.
Of course if you chose to go, you
would be like a lion among wolves.
Sir Francis, I don't
require you to flatter me.
No, Your Majesty.
Send a plain message to Suffolk.
Ask him why he refuses
to obey my commands
and ask him if he is a coward.
- Majesty.
- And Mr. Cromwell!
If things go badly, I know
well enough who to blame.
Can I get Your Majesty
anything for your pain?
Yes, I believe you can.
- Your Grace, the Earl
of Shrewsbury is here.
- My Lord.
- Your Grace.
Men dismissed.
We meet at a desperate moment, my Lord.
Not only are the rebel forces
overwhelmingly strong against us,
but those men I do have I cannot
altogether trust. Many of them
I swear think the rebels'
quarrels to be good and godly.
Still, the King has urged us
to attack as soon as possible.
His Majesty would not do
so if he saw our plight
with his own eyes. I
have almost no horsemen,
and those I do have are
rather the flower of the North.
It is not possible your lordship
to give battle knowing
defeat to be a certainty.
- Do you have some other plan?
- I intend to parley with them.
- Parley?
- My Lord,
it's our first duty to stop
them escaping and marching South.
If they are talking
they are not marching.
Then you must tell the King.
Shrewsbury's forces are here...
Suffolk's here, not far from Newark.
It seems likely that they
had originally planned
to hold a line here,
along the River Trent,
to block our advance southwards.
How strong are they?
- We think that Shrewsbury's men
are 6000; Suffolk's a lot less.
They also lack horse and cannon.
- And how many are we?
- By my reckoning,
- somewhere over thirty thousand.
- Thirty Thousand?
We have kept large forces here
at Doncaster, at Jervaux Abbey
and we are presently laying siege
to the Earl of Cumberland's
castle at Skipton.
North of the River Don
we have almost complete
control of the country.
Let them come on to us!
With God on our side, Mr.
Aske, we shall prevail.
Poor you, Your Majesty.
Pour the ointment over it.
I smell sorrel and... linseed?
Meadowplant, crushed pearls,
herb of grace, other things.
I concocted it myself. I
don't trust my physicians.
Hold still!
You're very brave, Lady Misseldon.
Braver, I think, than my Captains.
And much more beautiful.
There, it's done. I trust Your
Majesty is more comfortable.
Does Your Majesty wish me to stay?
It seems we were wrong to
suppose that the King of England
would realize his mistakes
and the dangers to his soul.
Instead he continues
to encourage Cromwel
to vandalize and defile
the houses of God and steal
their treasures, all for
his own use and pleasure.
And yet, even in the
darkness there is a light.
I mean, this great
uprising of the faithful.
This Pilgrimage of Grace.
- I have heard of it too.
The pilgrims who marched
beneath the banner of Christ.
The Holy Father asks you to
write a pamphlet in English
denouncing the King and
his advisors as heretics.
Of course. I will start
work on it straight away.
No, No. Wait, wait.
His Holiness needs more from
you than just your signature.
With my encouragement, he
has decided to appoint you
an official legate.
You will travel to France and
to the Low Countries and meet
representatives of the
King and the Emperor.
- Eminence...?
- You will persuade them
to provide monies, arms and mercenaries
to support this most
Holy Crusade in England.
If that is what His Holiness
asks me to do, then of course
I will do it, like an
obedient son to a father.
His Holiness has agreed
to make you a Cardinal.
And here is your biretta.
- I cannot accept.
- Why not?
- I'm not worthy.
In other words, you
prefer your own judgment
to that of the Pope, your Holy Father.
No doubt you suppose that
makes you seem humble.
But actually it is the
sin of pride for the Pope.
His Grace informs Your Majesty
he has no choice in the matter
but to treat with them...
- In so doing, he hopes to bring
the nobles and the gentry to treachery
and for their own sakes
and their own interests
they will disown the
commons, if promised a pardon
as in fact happened in Lincolnshire.
They are not all to be pardoned.
Not the leaders. Never the leaders.
But what terms does
my Lord Suffolk intend
to offer the commons
to make them go home?
Huh... His Grace does not
go into details, but...
to allay Your Majesty's fears,
he writes, in his own hand:
"I beseech Your Majesty to take
in good part whatever promises
"I shall make to these rebels,
for surely I shall
never keep any of them."
Alas, you unhappy men.
What fancy, what folly
has led and seduced you
to make this most shameful
rebellion against our most noble
and righteous king and sovereign?
Are you not ashamed?
How can you do this,
not only giving offence to
your natural sovereign Lord
but giving us occasion
to fight with you,
that have loved you more than
any other part of the realm,
and have always taken
you for our best friends?
Your Grace, we mean no
offence to His Majesty.
But we have a petition which we
desire humbly to submit to him,
for the restoration of many things
which have gone amiss in this realm.
We demand the restoration of our abbeys
and our ancient rights.
- And a new Parliament
be summoned to address the
people's sincere grievances.
I can decide nothing here.
But I propose a truce, during
which time two of your captains
can take your petition and
present it to His Majesty.
The truce to be maintained
until they return.
My Lord Darcy, can we talk a moment?
My Lord Darcy, you more
than anyone here has cause
to be grateful to the
King for his bounty,
for the trust he reposes in you
and would like to repose in you still.
And yet here I find you
consorting with rebels and traitors.
For my part I have been and
always will be true to the King
our sovereign Lord, as I
was to his father before him.
If you are as true and loyal as you say,
then you can prove it
to us by giving over
your Captain Mr. Aske into our hands.
Sir, that I cannot and will
not do. For a man who promises
to be true to someone then
betrays him may truly be called
a traitor.
His Majesty, the King!
- Your Majesty.
Madam.
Your Majesty.
It makes me happy to
see you so much improved.
I have a good physician.
Nevertheless, I intend
we shall visit the shrine
of Sir Thomas Becket
and give our thanks.
I have arranged for
something else which I hope,
with all my heart, will
make you very happy.
Your Majesty, the Lady Mary Tudor.
I ask Your Majesty for His blessing.
My own daughter.
May I present you to
Her Majesty Queen Jane?
I remember, some of you were desirous
that I should put this jewel to death!
I've got you, your safe.
Be of good cheer, Mary.
For I swear nothing
now will go against you.
Continue!
- Are you happy?
- Yes, Your Majesty.
His Majesty has agreed to give
you lodgings at Hampton Court
and others at Greenwich Palace.
I've seen them both; they're beautiful.
I am very grateful to
His Majesty and to you.
Everyone says my daughter is
innocent, that she doesn't know
any unclean or foul speech.
Do you believe that? Do you believe
that anybody could be that innocent?
Go and find out.
Lady Mary.
I wanted to apologize for my behavior.
I hope you can find it in
your heart to forgive me.
I will try, Sir Francis.
Jesus asks us to forgive everyone.
- Do you like games, Lady Mary?
- Yes.
There is a new game at
court that you might enjoy.
What is it?
It's called cunnilingus.
It's an old country practice.
How do you play it?
Well you...
You...
I think you're making
fun of me, Sir Francis.
No! No le me tangere...
you can't touch me.
For Caesar's I am.
Your Majesty, Sir Ralph
Ellerker and Mr. John Constable.
Gentlemen, I ask you this:
what King has kept his subjects
so long in wealth and peace?
So ministered justice
equally to high and low,
and protected you from
all outward enemies?
I have read your submission.
Your first pretence is that
you seek to maintain the faith.
But I tell you now gentlemen,
that nothing is more
contrary to God's commandment
than rebellion. Rising like
madmen against your prince,
leaving lands untilled and
corn unsown is not the behavior
of the proper commonwealth you claim to be!
- Your Majesty I feel compelled.
Hush! You are before the King's Majesty.
You make false claims about our
intentions towards the church.
We have done nothing but
what the clergy in York
and Canterbury agreed was in
accordance with God's holy word.
God's holy word, gentlemen!
So how can the simple
people say the contrary?
What presumption and madness
is it of them to claim
the knowledge of God's
law when they are ignorant
and less knowledgeable and
should rather know their duty?
You have seen before, in
Lincolnshire and elsewhere,
how temperate and forgiving
is our inclination.
Though rebellion is against God's will,
I declare my intention through the pity
and compassion of our
princely heart to pardon
all of you who have transgressed,
on condition that you
now lay down your arms.
His Grace the Duke of Suffolk
will come North again to Yorkshire
to moderate with you and make peace
and see you disbanded.
Good day, gentlemen.
Your Grace?
Your Grace should know
our army of pilgrims
will not disperse just for
the promise of a pardon.
Our pilgrimage is not over.
- I do know.
And I have told the King.
That is why he has given me
permission to negotiate with
you further in good faith.
- On the basis of our petition?
- Yes.
Does Your Grace have some
token of this "good faith"?
You don't trust my word?
Not for me, for our Captain
Mr. Aske. He's a lawyer.
Here is a promise.
in his Majesty's own hand,
to deal with you openly,
fairly and reasonably,
as his loving subjects.
We are grateful and
bounden to His Majesty.
Good night, gentlemen.
This is for the Lancashire Herald.
See that it is dispatched immediately.
Mr. Constable... I beg
you, do not put your trust
in Mr. Cromwell.
I thank God and Your Majesty
for your great mercy today.
I think you are the kindest of rulers,
and I wish with all my
heart the world knew it.
The world chooses what
it wants to know, Jane.
But you can change its mind!
I beg you to restore
- and keep the abbeys.
- Jane...
Think what the world will think.
That you listened to your
people and to your heart.
- Jane...
- I've told you once before:
don't to meddle with my affairs.
Do you remember what
happened to the late Queen?
Yes...
- I love you more than her.
More even than Catherine.
Don't spoil it.
Cardinal Pole.
My name is Diego Hurtado de Mendoza
and these gentlemen are all advisers
to His Imperial Majesty, King Charles V.
Sirs, I carry this letter
of legatine authority from
his Holiness Pope Paul.
Shall we be seated?
We were aware, Eminence, that
you were on your way here.
But, forgive me, we remain
a little unsure as to the
exact nature of your mission.
I am sure you are aware
of the risings which have
taken place across England
against the King, that heretic
Cromwell and all his sect.
We have heard
some information, certainly.
And naturally we are intrigued.
These popular risings
are the greatest chance
that we may ever have to restore
the true religion to England,
but the faithful people
of my country need support.
Each of us, senor Mendoza,
in our own way must encourage
the risings to continue
and to grow in strength.
Even if that means the
overthrow of the King himself,
not just his wicked council?
Yes.
We can imagine such
an outcome without fear
for there is another,
close to the throne,
with a legitimate
claim and a true faith:
the Lady Mary.
If not her,
there is still another Catholic
with a legitimate claim.
A scion of the Plantagenets,
who ruled before the Tudors,
and would gladly rule after them.
Of whom do you speak, Your Eminence?
I speak of myself, senor Mendoza.
Ralph...
John! We have waited and
prayed for your safe return.
Thank God! Thank God!
- The King in his mercy
has offered us a general
pardon! He is also sending
the Duke of Suffolk to
negotiate and treat with us,
without preconditions and
on the basis of our demands.
- Is it true?
- I trust the King's good faith
and mercy and here's the proof of it.
We are to meet again here.
You have not said anything yet, John.
Is it because you do
not agree with Sir Ralph?
No, I cannot agree with him.
How should I agree when I think
that devil Cromwell has
such a hold over the King
that I account these promises
to be utterly worthless!
You don't think we
should meet with them?
No, I don't. We should
expose their lies.
Call a general muster,
take over all of the North
and only then condescend to a meeting.
Why are you so sure that their
word is not to be trusted?
- Because of this.
- What's that?
A copy of a letter from Cromwell
to the Yorkshire gentry.
I'll read some of it to you.
"There is hope they
may disperse peacefully,
"but if these rebels continue
with their illegal assemblies
"and their defiance then
their rebellion will be crushed
"so forcibly that their example
shall be fearful to all subjects
so long as the world does endure."
"So long as the world
does endure", gentlemen.
But the truth is they cannot crush us.
And that is why the Duke
is forced to negotiate.
This sure sign of their deviousness
does not impress you then?
I say we do not stop our vigilance.
But prepare for our meeting,
clarify our positions
and strengthen our arguments and have
our Church leaders endorse them.
Why should we fear, John,
when we are about God's work?
I know we are but...
I only hope that none of
us - nor our grandchildren -
ever live to regret this moment.
I wanted to wish you every
success for your journey
and conference with the rebels.
- I am grateful to Your Majesty.
You know I desire more than
anything else a peaceful remedy.
You have my permission to
prolong the truce for as long
as necessary. You may also
affirm my general pardon
to all the rebels. Except their leaders.
I want them brought to you still,
with halters around their necks!
Your Majesty knows the rebels,
no doubt unjustly, blame
Master Cromwell for
many of their actions.
Repeatedly they ask for
his removal and punishment.
What should I tell them?
You know what this is, Charles?
Fruit from the New
World. New things come in.
Everything changes. I have
a great appetite for novelty.
Tell them what you like.
Gentlemen, I have
read your new petition.
Among other articles,
you ask for the setting up
of a special convocation or Parliament
to debate without fear
or his Majesty's displeasure
questions of heresy,
the royal supremacy, and
maintenance of the faith.
I can tell you now that the King has
graciously conceded to your request.
A special parliament
will be summoned to be held
not far away at Westminster
but here in York, to debate and
decide on all these questions.
Thank you. We have asked for the
heresies of Luther, Wycliffe and Tyndale
to be annulled and destroyed.
We have asked that the heretics,
bishops and temporal, be punished.
That Cromwell, Audley, Sir Richard Rich
be punished as subverters of
the good laws of this realm
and maintainers of false sects.
That is not for me to decide
whatever my true feelings.
But such questions are exactly
what the special Parliament
will be constituted to decide.
Is it possible that this
Parliament can also debate
the question of papal obedience,
touching the cure of souls,
and the legitimacy of the Lady Mary?
Yes, Mr. Aske.
I can guarantee that all
these great matters can be put
before the Parliament
without fear or favor.
And the King is still willing
to offer a general pardon?
Yes. I say that with hesitation.
The more His Majesty understands
the causes of this uprising,
and the loyalty of the
pilgrims to his person and rule,
the more is he persuaded
to show clemency.
- There is one other great
matter. Your Grace knows
that we demand that the suppressed
abbeys should stand or be restored.
This is our sticking point.
We were always determined
to fight and die
for the maintenance of
our religious houses.
What I can say about that is that
all further destruction
of the abbeys will cease
until Parliament meets.
It will then be up to
Parliament to decide if and when
the others will be restored.
Go home and put aside your arms.
By standing together
and by standing strong,
I believe we have achieved as
much as we could have gained
when we first took up this
great pilgrimage of ours.
It is almost Christmas. Go
home and celebrate the birth
of our Lord Jesus Christ
We thank God as we
thank the King's Majesty
that all this has been
achieved without bloodshed.
Please listen to the King's herald.
"His Gracious Majesty King Henry VIII
"hereby pardons by royal
command all those subjects
who have transgressed and
risen in unlawful rebellion."
I therefore ask everyone of you
to disperse, go home
and put aside your arms.
Firm in the knowledge that
our faith is to be maintained
and not destroyed!
- What is it, husband?
- I believe it's from the King.
What does it say?
Father?!
"My trusty and well-beloved
Aske. I am informed that,
"notwithstanding your
offences committed against us
"in the late rebellion
attempted in those parts,
"you are now at heart repentant.
"And since you are determined
to be a faithful subject,
we have conceived a great
desire to speak with you..."
- Father!
- Hush, children, hush! Listen to your father..
"... and to hear from your mouth the whole
circumstance and beginning of that matter."
The King wants to speak
with me. Can you believe it?
"I therefore order you, as
our true and faithful subject,
"as we now repute you, to come
to court for Christmastide.
"You are not to let anyone know,
but you will use such plainness
"and frankness in all things
we shall demand of you,
that we may have cause to
reward you even further."
There is a credence attached saying
that "You shall safe come
and safe go from court,
returning before the
twelfth day of Christmas."
Just make sure that he
means to honor the promises
Lord Suffolk made on
his behalf at Doncaster.
Is it not obvious that the
King has taken this matter
to his heart? This is a
letter written in his own hand.
- You are still too trusting.
- I would not go now.
But there is a promise of safe return.
- Promises can be broken.
- Mr. Constable, the promises
of a King are worth a great
deal more than the promises
- of ordinary folk.
- Here's what we shall do:
I will arrange to lay post
horses all the way between here
and London, so that if
God forbid, Mr. Aske,
you were imprisoned or
otherwise badly treated,
I will hear about it straight away,
and raise the people
again for your deliverance.
Thank you Lord, that's it.