Previously...
In this realm,
there should be perfect love.
But instead, there is discord
and dissention in every place.
It doesn't seem to matter
who I talk to at court.
All about me now is guile,
hypocrisy, and dishonesty.
I fear more than ever, the plots
about the court and the King.
Men conspire to secure their future
by controlling the Prince.
My poor brother is being brought up
a Protestant and a heretic.
And the King does
nothing to stop it.
- I have written a book.
- You call the Pope's clergy riff-Raff.
Bishop Gardiner
has arrested my sister
and two of my ladies
on suspicion of heresy.
We have discovered certain books.
In the closets
of the Queen's ladies.
Your Majesty has begun a great work,
banishing
the monstrous idol of Rome.
You can finish that work
by purging the Church of England
of its dregs.
Majesty, many of the greatest
subjects in the land
defending those same arguments
have deserved death.
I cannot believe that you would accuse
the Queen of heresy.
I have the proof.
Henry's Team
www.sous-titres.eu
www.seriessub.com
Tr: addic7ed.com
When we compare
the present life of man on earth
with that time
of which we have no knowledge,
it seems to me like the swift flight
of a single sparrow
through a banqueting hall
on a winter's day.
After a few moments of comfort,
he vanishes from sight
into the wintry world
from which he came.
Even so, man appears on earth
for a little while;
but of what went before this life
or what will follow,
we know nothing.
In these last days
I have been thinking
a great deal about loss.
What loss, Your Grace,
is to man the most irrecoverable?
- His virtue.
- No.
For by his actions,
he may redeem his virtue.
- Then his honor.
- No.
For again, he may find
the means to recover it,
even as a man recovers
some fortune he has lost.
Then I cannot say, Your Majesty.
Time, Your Grace.
Of all losses,
time is the most irrecoverable,
for it can never be redeemed.
Walter!
Take this...
very carefully and give it...
to My Lord Risley.
Yes, Your Grace.
The Lord High Admiral of France.
Salutationes Domine,.
Praefectus Magnus Galliae.
Salvete Regis Enrici
octavi maiestatis.
Thank you, Your Highness.
It is my great privilege
and honor to be here.
My Lord Admiral.
May I present his Majesty's daughters,
the Lady Mary
and the Lady Elizabeth.
I never thought to be welcomed
by His Majesty's family.
You are a special and honored guest,
Admiral D'Annibault.
And your visit most timely.
I am sure His Majesty
will be here presently.
My Lord Hertford seems
to be in the King's good graces.
I fear it seems to be so.
The Earl grows more powerful daily
because of the King's infirmity
and his control of the boy.
God help us then
if the King should die.
But I have heard many say
that the people would rather
see you anointed as Queen
than...
leave the country
at the mercy of a mere child
and an overweening uncle.
And what of the Queen?
You shall hear more
on that subject...
very soon.
The King!
Admiral.
We are very pleased
to make a new treaty with France.
I will have no further business
with the Emperor...
who has betrayed me at every turn.
You will find us good
and faithful friends...
unlike the Emperor.
As you know,
in my Kingdom I have made
many changes to religious life.
I have reformed a corrupt church.
I have swept aside hundreds of years
of lies and superstitions.
I have revealed to all mankind
that the Pope
is but a fallible prince,
and not the voice of God.
All this, no doubt,
you'll have heard.
I am certainly aware
that Your Majesty has wrought
many changes in your own Kingdom.
Well, if we are going
to be allies, Monsieur,
then I propose a further change.
I propose that Mass be abolished
in both our realms
and replaced
with a simple communion service.
Now, how would you feel about that?
I have no authority to renegotiate
the terms of our treaty,
especially, as Your Majesty knows,
my King is dying.
Of syphilis, I know.
I am very sorry to hear it.
I have known Francis a long time,
and I beg you to send him my love.
But you may also tell him
that his disease is a reminder
of his own mortality!
Which, in times past,
he has forgotten!
I have something for you
to show the Queen.
I'm supposed to take it
to Lord Risley.
When the Queen's read it,
give it back to me.
... so handsome.
Oh, hush, sister.
What is it?
Oh my God.
What is that?
Who is it?
It's the Queen's Majesty,
Your Majesty.
Why is she screaming like that?
I'll go and see her.
What is it?
I...
I fear...
you have grown displeased with me.
Why so?
Because...
I fear that you have
utterly forsaken me.
I don't understand.
What has caused you to think so?
Why would I have reason
to be displeased with you?
Are you not
displeased with me?
I will ask you one more time:
is there any reason I should be?
There is none, Your Majesty.
Good day, My Lady.
Sister!
Ladies!
Now, you must do as I ask.
Clear your coffers of all books
whether you suppose them
to be forbidden or not!
From now on we shall talk
no more, amongst ourselves,
of any matters, whether religious
or controversial,
and I shall try, in all things,
to conform myself
to the King's mind.
Now go.
Hurry!
Good day.
May I be presented to His Grace?
Alas, my Lord,
His Grace is indisposed.
He caught a chill and is still abed.
I am very sorry to hear it.
I will return some other time,
when the Duke is well.
No, no, my Lord.
I am...
well enough to see you.
I think your faction is engaged
in a fight to the death
with Bishop Gardiner and his.
I will not hide the truth from you.
The King's infirmity
and the youth of my nephew
make the question
of succession urgent.
The stakes could not possibly
be higher.
And you desire to know, I assume,
on which side of the argument
I belong?
Your Grace,
whether you will it or not,
you carry a great weight of confidence
and influence with the King.
And everyone knows that.
But fewer people know
that your wife, the Duchess,
and my wife Anne,
together with the Queen,
are as close on matters of religion
as it is possible to be.
And this close affinity has
emboldened me, now,
to approach Your Grace.
Surely your wife has told you
that the Duchess
and I are estranged!
Thus her affinities
are not necessarily my own
and you do me a disservice
to assume they are.
Your Grace, forgive me...
I do forgive you.
I forgive you
even for hounding poor,
proud Surrey to his death...
for it was his fault.
But as to religion.
I have never read the Gospels,
and never shall.
I am sure they enlighten you,
but I prefer them to remain mysterious.
And, as for the promise
of a better world,
I can only say that England
was merry before,
and all things considered,
I would all things
were as they used to be
in times past.
Your Grace, if I do not have
your support,
may I ask if you will act
against me?
I'm not sure if this is any answer,
My Lord Hertford.
I have always been drawn to a phrase
used by the French peasants:
"Praise the God of all,
"drink the wine,
and let the world be the world."
My Lady Hertford.
I was summoned here
but I have no idea why.
I wonder how I may help you?
You may help me, My Lady,
by telling me the truth.
You were a friend, I believe,
of the heretic Anne Askew,
recently burned?
I was acquainted with her.
You were more than acquainted,
I think.
While she was a prisoner,
one of your servant,
a man wearing a blue coat...
gave her money.
I desired to make her
circumstances more tolerable.
I was only acting
out of Christian charity.
I had been informed
that those who tortured her,
illegally, had stretched
her on the rack
until the strings of her arms
and legs were perished.
But you admit
she was a self-confessed heretic?
You are therefore guilty
by association.
You have a warrant for my arrest?
You will never serve that warrant.
Why not?
Because I know your secret.
What secret, My Lady Hertford?
You are not such a saint
as you appear are you, Your Grace?
You have not exactly
renounced worldly goods...
have you?
There are two monasteries
in Cornwall.
They were stripped and closed,
on His Majesty's orders, and burnt.
Except...
that they were neither stripped
nor burnt,
but their titles and contents
were transferred to Your Grace.
Thus, you are a rich man indeed...
but only by embezzling
from the King.
I advise you
to tear up your warrant,
Her Majesty the Queen.
Come in here.
I am glad you have come.
You can resolve
me of certain doubts.
I wonder, Kate,
how much you think you can learn
from reading the Gospels
and other religious books?
Since God has appointed you
as Supreme Head of us all,
it is from you
that I will ever learn.
But that surely is not so!
You have become a doctor, Kate,
to instruct us, as we have seen
many times before...
but not to be instructed
or directed by us!
Majesty, I think my meaning
has been mistaken
for I have always
held it preposterous
- for a woman to instruct her Lord.
- And yet,
you seem sometimes
to have a different view
of religion than we do.
Only so that you could correct me!
Forgive me, Your Majesty,
but I thought that talking
and discussing
helped to ease the pain and weariness
of your present infirmity.
And it encouraged me in my boldness,
in the hope of profiting
from your learned discourse.
I am,
I am but a woman,
with all the imperfections natural
to the weakness of my sex,
and therefore,
in all matters of doubt and difficulty
I must refer myself
to Your Majesty's better judgment,
as my Lord and head.
Is that so, sweetheart?
And you made your argument
for no worse ends?
Then we are perfect friends again.
I thank Your Majesty.
I promise
that I will never doubt you again.
Sweet Kate.
Shall I rescind Your Majesty's order
to arrest the Queen tomorrow?
Why?
Music.
What is it, sweetheart?
Nothing.
I was dreaming.
We were back in Boulogne...
but I let you go.
I'm here.
- Has the dawn come yet?
- Not yet. Not yet.
I hate the nights.
- I think of perpetual night.
- Hush, darling.
The dawn will be here soon,
and you well again.
Yes, my darling?
I'm so happy.
What is this?
Lord Chancellor!
Why have you come?
I have come to execute
the warrant for the Queen's arrest
and to escort her,
and her Ladies, to the Tower.
You knave!
You arrant knave!
Get out! Get out of my sight!
- Majesty...
- Get out!
And take your bastards with you.
I am so...
sorry that...
the Lord Chancellor should
make such a mistake.
You don't how little
he deserves your sympathy.
He was not your friend, Kate.
- Lord Hertford!
- My Lord Hertford!
Your Grace,
I have already explained,
he called me a knave!
All manner of things.
But for whose ears?
Supposing he still wants the Queen
to feel falsely secure?
If it was feigned anger,
it seemed very real to me!
My Lords, in the King's absence,
Council is called upon
to declare its content
with the terms of the peace treaty
with France.
All in favour say "aye"
Aye.
Council is also called upon
to discuss all arrangements made
for the security and safety
of His Highness Prince Edward,
heir to the throne,
and all provisions made
for his temporal
and spiritual welfare.
My Lords, pray,
what induces you to discuss
such things now,
when all provisions are already made
and the Prince is secure at Windsor,
by His Majesty's orders?
Aye.
My Lord Hertford,
Council is still constituted
to examine such matters,
especially since
the King's infirmities
give us all cause
to think of the future.
And it is treason,
my Lord Chancellor,
to envisage the King's death!
My Lord, all our concern
is for the Prince.
Your concern?!
Are you forgetting
that he is of my blood?
He is also of the King's blood,
which gives us cause enough
to examine those put in charge of him.
And among them, some of whom
we find, like his tutors,
to be suspected heretics!
You talk of heresy! You!
And what are you but a puffed-up
porkling of the Pope's?
My Lord!
I still say, my Lord Hertford...
that the real truth behind
your intentions
towards the Prince and the Crown
must be placed before the King.
- What are you doing?
- Take your hands off!
Bishop Gardiner desires
an audience with your Majesty.
Refused.
His Grace has a troublesome nature
and I don't want to see him here
ever again.
I desire him to leave my Court.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Grace, His Majesty
instructs you to leave Court.
- My Lord Hertford.
- Lord Hertford.
Lord Chancellor.
What may I do for you?
You may forgive me,
if you find it possible to do so,
from some past associations,
which I now regret.
I have no hesitation in pledging my
utter loyalty to Your Lordship's House,
and I trust in future
I can serve you
as faithfully as I have
always served His Majesty.
I am most grateful to you,
my Lord Chancellor.
Mr. Holbein.
- Mr. Holbein.
- Majesty.
I have a commission for you.
I am most grateful to Your Majesty.
I assume Your Majesty
means a portrait?
You once painted my father.
Now you will paint me.
I am deeply honored.
Sweetheart,
sweetheart,
here is a messenger
from His Majesty.
Your Grace,
His Majesty has heard
of your indisposition
and has asked to see you.
No!
That is impossible,
ask the physicians.
What shall I tell His Majesty?
Tell him...
I shall come.
But you can't!
How can I lie in bed, my love,
when the King of England
has summoned me?
Just get them to help me.
What are you doing here?
I have come to see my daughter.
Why should that surprise you, Henry?
You have not always
been kind to her.
I have wept so often
to see her alone,
abandoned by her father.
Is that why you've come back,
to chide me
for all that I am not?
She ought to be a long time
married by now.
She ought to have her own children.
Go away,
shade.
Go away, Katherine.
You sent me away before...
though I loved you.
But I was still your wife
in God's eyes.
And still am.
His Grace the Duke of Suffolk.
Charles.
Majesty.
They told me you were ill.
So I had to see you.
I have a slight fever.
Perhaps Your Majesty should
not come so close.
We've known each other a long time,
a very long time.
And I remember everything.
In fact,
I remember things from long ago
better than I remember yesterday.
I remember Your Majesty's
sister so well.
And the Battle of the Spurs!
And when Your Majesty
made me a Duke...
God knows why!
You were my general,
in York and in France,
because I could trust no one else.
And I beg you now Charles,
to trust me.
I have the power
to make you well again,
you know that.
They told me you were like to die...
but you won't die.
I forbid it!
Kneel.
By the grace of God,
I, the Eighth Henry,
King of England,
Ireland, and France,
Defender of the Faith
and of the Church of England
command you to be healed!
My Lady Suffolk.
Your Grace.
May I say, on behalf of all
His Grace's loyal servants and staff,
that we are as heart-broken
and wretched
as Your Grace must be
on this unhappy day.
For we all loved His Grace
as much as you, his wife,
and son, loved him.
Thank you.
Your sympathy and loyalty
touch my son and I most deeply.
Madame.
Requiescant in pace Domini.
Et Lux perpetua luceat eis.
Requiescant in pace.
He is to be buried
at St George's Chapel at Windsor.
At my expense.
I tell you this, my Lord Hertford:
as long as Charles Brandon
served me,
he never betrayed a friend,
nor ever took unfair advantage
of an enemy.
Which is more than I can say
for anyone else at my Court!
I never thought he would die.
We should talk, my Lord Hertford,
about the arrangements
for the Prince's minority
after I am dead!
Mr. Holbein is here.
Mr. Holbein.
With your permission, I came
to show you my work in progress.
Master Holbein.
When you painted my father,
you made his likeness
when he was old, sickly, and ill.
He looked nothing
like a King of England,
more like a poor wretch!
A feeble, plain, and dying man.
And now you have done
the same for me!
Mr. Holbein, this portrait is a lie!
Do it again!
And get out.
Why are you here?
To see my daughter.
She was the only pure
thing in my life.
And in my life I neglected her,
since she was only a girl,
and I wanted so much to give you a son.
But now I am so proud of her.
Fiercely proud!
She is so clever.
And though she is like me
in so many ways,
she is not intemperate as I was.
You must be proud of her too, Henry.
I am.
I am very proud of her.
And I know how clever she is.
And I wish
that I could love her more.
But from time to time
she reminds me of you...
and of what you did to me.
I did nothing to you.
I was innocent.
All the accusations
against me were false.
I thought you knew.
Poor Katherine Howard.
She lies in the cold
ground next to me.
Poor child.
It was not her fault either.
But we were like two moths,
drawn to the flame...
and burned.
Anne, please don't!
His Majesty, the King.
Lady Mary...
Lady Elizabeth...
Kate...
Come here!
I have decided
to send you away to Greenwich.
I will not spend Christmastide
with you this year,
or thereafter.
- Why, Your Majesty?
- Kate,
do not question my command.
It is as it is.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Mary.
You must be a kind
and loving mother to your brother,
who I leave in this world
a helpless little child.
Please, father, I beg you,
do not leave me an orphan so soon!
Mary,
Mary.
Elizabeth.
You are so very young,
but you, too
can look after your brother.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I promise.
Bless you, child.
Bless you.
The time has come
for us to bid farewell.
It is God's will.
When I die,
I order these gentlemen to treat you
as if I were living still.
And if it is your pleasure
to remarry,
I order that you shall
have 7,000 pounds a year
as long as you live
for your service,
as well as your jewels
and ornaments.
Now go.
How is my son?
Jane!
He is well.
I have taken all care of him...
sweet Jane.
And soon, he will be King.
My poor boy.
My poor child.
No!
He is the most beloved.
He is my special boy.
He will die young.
No! No!
Poor child,
you expected too much of him!
He was only a boy!
Kings, too, are made of clay!
And God forbid you locked him away
from the world,
like your father did with you.
No!
Don't you understand?
You have killed him!
No!
Herewith, my Lords, is my testament.
When I am dead,
my Lord Hertford
will act as Lord Protector
during Prince Edward's minority.
He will be supported
by my Lord Chancellor Risley
and Archbishop Cranmer.
It is my desire
to be buried next to the body
of my true and loving wife,
Queen Jane Seymour, at Windsor.
You shall raise an honorable tomb,
upon which will be our effigies,
fashioned as if we are
sweetly sleeping.
Mr. Holbein awaits you
in the Chapel.
Master Holbein,
it is well done.
Merci d'avoir suivi "The Tudors"
avec la Henry's Team.