Previously on The Tudors...
- Do you really want to fight?
- Yes.
- Take another wife?
Am I not still able to have a wife,
to have more children?
To be myself?
I mean to show these French that I won't
shy away from battle if I am provoked.
The Emperor is once more at war.
A joint attack on France would
restore to the English crown
all your lost territories,
the whole of Aquitaine.
I still think the King
will want to remarry.
And yet what woman on earth
would want to marry a King
who either puts his wives away
or kills them?
Lady Latimer has come
to petition Your Majesty
to lift a suspicion of treason
from her husband.
The King seems quite taken
with Lady Latimer.
You have no children
and none by your first husband?
It was not a happy marriage.
- Do you think such a thing exists?
- I believe so with all my heart.
We should start hunting down all
the Lutherans in His Majesty's kingdom.
We should flush them out?
Some of them are very close
to the King.
You would not like
to be Queen of England?
You know what happens to his queens!
Everyone knows what happens.
Let it be known to all
present that this treaty
contains an obligation to undertake
a war against France.
His Majesty agrees to send
40,000 men-at-arms.
I do, so help me God.
What could make a revengeful prince
like the Emperor?
Forget the insult done to him
by the King of England?
Those insults are long forgotten,
Monsieur Marillac.
Catherine Parr, we are sent here
by the King's Majesty to offer you
His Majesty's hand in marriage.
He will be the happiest man
now alive in England,
and you the happiest woman.
Henry's Team
kiry, Olaola.
::: The Tudors 4x07 VO :::
www.sous-titres.eu
www.seriessub.com
Tr.: YYets.
My Lords,
we will now proceed with our plans
for an invasion of France.
We will start by the capture
of the strategic town of Boulogne.
Your Grace,
I shall appoint you
commander of our armies,
if you have the will
and the stomach for the fight.
I can only thank God for the chance
to win honour and glory in the field.
What man wouldn't prefer to die
with a sword in his hand
and a cry in his throat,
rather than abed in England?
Aye!
My Lords,
I must tell you that a special envoy
from the court of the Emperor,
the Duke of Najera,
will pay us an unofficial visit,
in honour of our alliance.
The Duke is one of the Emperor's
most successful generals.
He should be first received
here by the Earl of Surrey
and then brought to court.
I'm sure your Lordships will see fit
to welcome him as he deserves.
I have vowed to bring King Francis
into submission,
and I will fulfil this promise.
I have been all my life
a prince of virtue and honour,
as you can all attest,
and I have never
contravened my word.
I'm too old to begin now.
"I, Catherine
"take thee, Henry,
"to be my wedded husband,
"to have and to hold
from this day forward,
"for better, for worse,
"for richer, for poorer,
"in sickness and in health,
"to be bonnier and buxom
in bed and at board,
"till death us do part,
"and thereto
I plight thee my troth."
The ring.
"Benedicat, hic anulum,
"Dominus,
qui fecit caelum et terram."
"With this ring, I thee wed."
"With my body,
"I thee worship."
"In nomine Patris,
"et Filii,
"et Spiritus Sancti."
I now pronounce thee man and wife.
Thank you, Lady Herbert.
Sister.
Your Majesty, if I may?
I am determined to be a loving
stepmother to your children.
Of course, I have known Mary
for years,
but it would now be
my pleasure rather than my duty
to make friends with the Prince Edward
and the Princess Elizabeth.
So with Your Majesty's permission
I would like to invite
them more often to court,
not only for my sake
but so they might more often
see their father.
You have my permission.
Thank you.
And perhaps Your Majesty
might also agree
to the Lady Elizabeth having permanent
lodgings at court, like the Lady Mary?
Perhaps.
But I would not like my son Edward
to come to court too often,
for fear of infection.
I have arranged for some gifts
to be delivered to you.
I hope you like them.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Try this one, Your Grace.
- Your Grace.
- My Lords.
I am pleased to convey to you
His Majesty's commissions.
Sir Thomas, you are recalled
from Brussels
and are to be appointed
Admiral of the Fleet.
My Lord Surrey, the King has seen fit
to make you Marshal of the Field,
a singular honour.
Your Grace.
- When do we sail?
- As soon as the King commands.
Sir Thomas...
Is it true that your brother,
Lord Hertford
- is against this war?
- It is true, Your Grace.
He worries for the King's health,
in body and in mind.
He fears that if His Majesty
should die in France,
he would leave the kingdom
in great confusion.
How is the King?
There are rumours that he is unwell.
That he may be unable
to lead the army.
No, my Lord. The King will lead
his soldiers. Make no mistake of that.
For here is the truth,
the King does not
just want France back,
but all of his honour
and his youth as well.
And, in that, he is like me.
May I present His Highness
Don Juan Estaban Manrique de Lara,
Duke of Najera.
- Your Highness.
- Your Majesty.
I am very happy to receive you
at my court.
I trust you have been
well entertained so far?
Indeed. I have visited
the famous Tower
and also the River Thames.
It is not possible that a more beautiful
river should exist in the world.
And with so many...
- cisnes?
- Swans, your Highness.
Yes. Swans.
My Lord Surrey also took
His Highness to the Paris Gardens,
to see bears fighting with dogs.
And then, in the same place,
they brought a pony
with an ape on his back.
And to see the animal kicking among
the dogs, with the screams of the ape
was very laughable.
Well, Your Highness,
I trust this evening you will also
be well entertained
by my beautiful wife the Queen
and my first daughter, the Lady Mary.
His Highness only desires
Your Majesty to confirm
if your armies are ready
for the invasion of France.
I have already given my word.
What more does Your Highness
expect of me?
His Highness, the Duke of Najera.
The Lady Mary.
So, is it a coincidence
that there is talk of war
and then General Najera
turns up here at court?
Absolutely.
This is a private visit.
His Highness came to London
to see the Tower
and row on the river
and see the swans.
Do you take me for a fool?
No, Excellency.
You are what you are.
And so am I.
Kat! May I not dance, please!
Of course you can.
Of course you can dance, my Lady.
Mr. Risley,
may I ask, what have you heard
of the Queen's religious beliefs?
They are the same, surely,
as His Majesty's.
I think not.
Indeed, I suspect Her Majesty
of being a secret Protestant
and I intend one day to prove it.
And in so doing...
risk the anger of the King?
Mr. Risley,
for the sake of our faith,
and the future of our country
I am prepared to risk a great deal.
Dr. Butts! What is it?
It's the King's leg, Your Majesty. His
ulcer has burst, he is in great pain.
Come.
Catherine!
Dearest,
- let me see!
- Please, don't.
I have seen worse things.
Give me a poultice, quickly now.
If Your Majesty could move your leg,
and place it across my lap?
There, dearest.
Quickly!
As long as the King is sick,
I will move my bed to his chamber,
the better to look after him.
Madam.
Next!
Steady!
Forward.
Come on, lads.
I went to war once, a long time ago.
We broke lances against the French.
The knights did in the old days.
This...
this is a different war,
a war of guns.
- Good shot.
- Again.
Good shooting.
Well done. What's your name?
Richard, Your Grace, Richard Leland.
You are soon to war, Richard Leland.
That was well done, Richard.
Harry. Harry Hurst.
- Are you coming to France?
- I don't know.
- I can't shoot like that.
- What can you do?
I'm a farm labourer, me.
I can herd cows, shovel shit,
and build fences.
Christ!
I wish I'd half your talent, Harry!
Thank you.
Next.
Your Majesty,
Prince Edward is here.
Madam.
Your Grace, how lovely to see you.
Madam, I came to thank you
for the outfits
of crimson velvet and white satin
you sent me.
I am very glad that you liked them.
I would also like to thank
my noble and illustrious father
for the jewels he sent me.
But they told me he was sick.
I am pleased to tell Your Grace
that His Majesty is now much better.
He must love me,
for if he did not love me,
he would not give me
these fine gifts.
He loves you very much.
You are very special to him
and I know that he would like
to see you more often if he could.
Thank you.
I wish you a good day, Madam.
Poor child.
My Lords.
How go our preparations?
I think they have gone slackly!
I'm beginning to suppose
your Lordships are not so keen
to go to war after all.
Sit.
Majesty, the gun carriages,
carts, wagons,
the ovens, horses,
artillery, and ordnance
are all made ready
and dispatched for shipping.
And a further 300 ships have been
requisitioned for Your Majesty's use
and will be in port
within the month.
Within the month!
They should be already in port
if you had not been so remiss
and neglectful in your duties!
What about our maps of Boulogne?
Your Majesty,
we do not have any maps,
so we will have to rely
on the advice of a French spy,
De Buren.
So we are to blunder
about in the dark
and trust to the honesty
of French spies!
God help us, Your Grace,
for it seems you have not!
We will not wait for more ships!
This army will embark
for France in 10 days time,
land in Calais and straight away
march to Boulogne.
We have three weeks to take this town
before we proceed on to Paris.
Now, while I am in France,
the Queen's Highness, Queen Catherine
will act as Regent
and rule in my stead.
Lord Hertford, who I begin
to suspect is against this war,
will stay as Lieutenant
to the Realm.
Need I remind your Lordships
that we go to France not solely
for honour and glory,
but to recover our just rights
and inheritances
taken from us by violence
and withheld from us for too long.
He has made the Queen Regent!
Why?
She has no knowledge
of matters of state!
I do not know.
But from what I hear of her,
I do not think it right.
I think the King should be aware
how perilous a matter it is
to cherish a serpent
in one's own bosom.
I have to tell you that I've left
all things here in order,
in case do not come back
from France.
Shortly, Parliament will
pass a new Act of Succession,
naming my son Edward as my heir.
If he has no issue,
then it passes to the Lady Mary
and then to the Lady Elizabeth.
Those are my wishes.
Understood.
Do not cry, Mary,
for I do not intend to die.
Promise you will write to me often!
Tell me all that happens
in my kingdom
and whatever you see fit to write.
I leave my children in your care,
knowing that there are not
more loving hands in this world.
Farewell.
It makes you happy to be alive,
doesn't it, Majesty?
Your Grace.
Majesty.
Well met!
How do we prosper?
Majesty, the port is blockaded
and the town is partially invested.
Its gates are shut
and its defenders shut inside.
The French consider
that their ramparts and double walls
make them invulnerable
to our artillery!
We shall see about that!
We have brought enough
cannon here to conquer hell!
Forward!
I can't believe my eyes
Look, Richard!
It's the King of England himself!
What do you think?
I reckon if I were the French
I'd be fucking scared.
Englishmen, today you have
every reason to be proud!
Today, we begin
our campaign of Boulogne.
We have offered terms of peace
in return for our just rights
and inheritances.
But our enemy has refused
to render what they owe us.
They should know that we do not
lack the courage to fight
to the death for justice.
These lands were taken from us
by violence
and I mean to have them back.
For King Henry,
for England,
and for St. George!
Long live the King!
For England!
Prepare your fire!
Solders, to your stations!
Section One Commander!
Prepare your guns!
Section One, prepare your guns!
Section Two Commander!
Prepare your guns!
Load your cannon!
- Prepare your guns!
- Ready, guns.
Section Three Commander!
Prepare your guns!
Ram barrel!
- Soldiers, into the trenches!
- Quick march!
Section Two Commander,
take both your men!
- Section Three, report when ready.
- Yes, sir!
- Section Three ready.
- That's ready, sir.
All guns take aim
for the gates and castle.
Section One, take aim!
- Section Commanders!
- Confirm you have your target!
Section Three, take aim.
Section One, target ready.
Section Two, confirm target.
Section Two has target, sir.
- Section Three, confirm.
- Section Three ready.
Hold sections!
Hold fire until I give the order!
Let's go, men.
Hold fire!
Move!
Hold your fire!
Easy for the time!
Now we'll see how invulnerable
it really is!
In position!
Ready, captain!
Section one, fire!
For the King!
- Ready!
All sections!
Fire!
Section One, fire!
Ready!
Charge the gun!
- England!
Back into position!
Reload all guns!
If you could see that this is
delivered to My Lord Hertford.
Thank you.
Madam,
here is Mr. Latimer.
Alas, Madam, I am no longer
entitled to such an address.
I was deprived of my bishopric
by Bishop Gardiner.
I know.
And I know the circumstances of it.
Still, I have a mind
to appoint you
chaplain to my household.
Are you absolutely sure, My Lady?
You must know my reputation.
Your reputation, Mr. Latimer,
is of a man of the Gospels
and a true Christian.
For example, do you suppose
that it is a bad thing
that everyone should be able
to read the Bible for themselves?
On the contrary, I believe it
to be a vital thing.
For without God's direct word
we that be unlettered
remain confused and without grace.
Even though some would say
that the reading of the Bible
leads to heresy?
If they say so,
then they are wickedly charging
the holy sanctified word of God
- with the offences of man.
- You are right.
Do people deny themselves food,
because they see others overeat?
Or avoid using fire because they have
seen a neighbour's house burn down?
Blind ignorance, Mr. Latimer,
to slander God for man's offences.
If you are still of a mind
to have me,
I will most joyfully
be your chaplain.
I thank you.
I have one favour,
which is that you conceal
the true workings
of your mind from the Lady Mary.
For nothing in this world
will change her allegiance
to the faith of her mother,
and I respect her for that.
Madam, believe me,
I shall be the soul of discretion
in my dealings
with all His Majesty's children,
and with the world.
Thank you.
My Lady.
Sister,
are you sure you can really trust
Mr. Latimer's discretion?
I know I should not say so
to Your Majesty,
but I fear his appointment.
Should I play the coward?
You know that I never wanted
to marry the King.
But since I had to,
I may at least use
what influence I now possess
to further the cause
that I believe in with all my heart.
The cause of the Reformation!
Then at least I can address my God
with a clear conscience
and an honest soul.
Please say
that you understand, Anne!
Please.
Forward! Come on! Left, right.
There we are!
Shit!
It can't last forever.
Lads, come here!
Come on!
Move on, men!
This way, My Lord.
Your Majesty, signor Treviso.
Girolamo.
Come, show me where you intend
to dig these mines.
I intend to dig three tunnels.
Two will be a diversion,
to confuse the enemy.
The main one will be here,
which will lead under the castle.
How long?
That depends on the type of ground,
danger of flooding and so on.
Also, how far into the earth
they have built the walls.
But I say we could
be under the castle
and able to detonate
a huge explosion in three weeks.
Two weeks, signor Treviso!
Two weeks!
Take the troops you need.
Put your backs into it, men.
We are making excellent progress.
But I want to know how the Emperor
is doing since we are in this war.
The Emperor's forces
are at present besieging
the fortresses of Luxembourg
and St. Didier.
With God's help, we will break
our siege first and advance on Paris.
With the damage our guns
are inflicting,
I swear Boulogne will
not hold out for long.
I think that the French were foolish to
think that their walls were invincible.
They had not seen our guns.
Paris by September! Good!
There are a lot of Frenchmen
in Paris I would like to kill,
so I can sleep with their wives
with a clear conscience!
Gentlemen
- Salut!
- Majesty.
- What is it?
The French! They've broken out
beyond the southern gate, sir.
- I'll go!
- Your Grace!
Cover the gates with a massive force,
in case this is a diversion.
- Go!
- Majesty.
Where are they?
There, there! Get him!
Stop in the name of the King!
- Where is he?
- He's down in the ditch!
Keep your wits about you.
Take cover!
Stay down!
- Do you see him?
- Two on the ground!
Ready!
Let's go!
Your Grace,
I didn't need your help
but thank you all the same.
Shall I leave them to you then?
Here we come!
For England!
Mademoiselle?
Load cannon!
- General.
- Keep the lines straight.
Dig in there.
I've brought you some food.
Your father is still alive.
Is that true?
He was wounded
but we're taking care of him.
- Can I see him?
- Soon.
I promise.
Put your backs into it.
Roll that barrel!
What's your name?
Brigitte,
Brigitte Rousselot.
You should eat.
Why are you here?
In France?
This isn't your country.
It used to be.
We all used to live in Eden.
It doesn't mean we can go back again!
- Why won't you release me?
- So you'll fight against us?
Yes! So I can go on killing you.
No, Mademoiselle.
You're my prisoner now.
Perhaps I'll even get
a ransom for you!
How things are in the town?
Do people have enough food?
They have plenty!
You shouldn't worry about them.
They'll never surrender.
Not to that sacred monster,
your King.
Monster?
You know
we call him the English Nero!
Didn't you know that?
Graci plena. Dominus tecum.
Benedicta tu in mulieribus,
et benedictus fructus ventris tui.
Mr. Risley.
Your Grace,
I have some news I thought
you might be interested in.
It seems
Queen Catherine has appointed
Hugh Latimer as her private Chaplain.
Are you sure?
And I thought someone said
she was an intelligent woman!
How's the tunnelling?
We've dug about 50 paces.
It's bloody hard work,
and there's a lot of clay.
I prefer the clay.
It's not like sand.
Always afraid it's gonna collapse
and bury you.
How've you been?
There's a French officer
comes out sometimes.
He stands for a few moments
on the castle rampart,
looking at us.
Then he goes back inside.
I just need one good shot.
One good shot.
Have you heard?
There are meant to be
a few women around camp.
Not many, mind. Just a few.
That's what I heard.
If you fancy the pox!
Perhaps you're right.
In any case, I have a wife back home
and she is with child.
What do you want, a boy or girl?
A boy.
I hope to God
we're not here too long.
"Although Your Majesty's absence
has not been long,
"yet the want of your presence
"means that I cannot
take pleasure in anything
"until I hear from Your Majesty."
"Time hangs heavily."
"I have a great desire to know
"how Your Majesty has done
since you left."
"For your prosperity and health,
"I prefer and desire
more than my own."
"And although I know Your Majesty's
absence is never without great need
"still, love and affection compel me
"to desire your presence."
"Thus love makes me set aside
my own convenience
"and pleasure for you,
"at whose hands I have received
so much love and goodness
"that words cannot express it."
"We hear word of ill weather
"and delays besetting you."
"And though we thank God
for your good health,
"we anxiously await the joyous news
"of the success
of your great venture
"and for your safe
and triumphant return,
"for which all England
offers daily prayers."
More supports in the space!
"I fear I am but a poor substitute
for Your Majesty
"in the matter of the guidance
of your kingdom."
"I long for your return."
"I commit you to God's care
and governance."
"By Your Majesty's humble,
obedient wife
"and servant, Catherine the Queen."
But, Majesty, I beg you
to give us a little more time.
The men are working
all day and all night.
But sometimes we must stop
digging to support the roof
or else everything collapses.
Master Surgeon!
Signor Treviso.
- What is it?
- Majesty,
I regret to inform you of the deaths
of ten of your soldiers.
- Soldier die of their wounds.
- No, Your Majesty.
The men all died of the bloody flux.
Dysentery?
I am afraid there is an outbreak
of the disease throughout your army.
God alone knows
how many it will take away.
Master Surgeon.
Mr. Treviso.
Let me ask you something.
What do you think of our Italian
gentleman, signor Girolamo Treviso?
The builder of tunnels.
- What do you mean?
- I mean do you trust him?
Why should I not trust him?
It's only that I happen to know
that, some time ago,
he said he could build a mirror
large enough
that if set upon the cliffs of Dover
His Majesty would be able to see,
reflected in it,
the movement of French ships
in and out of the port of Boulogne.
Do you see what I mean, Your Grace?
Do you think he's mad?
It's only a suggestion.
But then,
he's not the only one!
Change the watch!
Section ready!
Pull me up!
Ready captain!