Previously on Blade
Where are you
shipping the bodies ?
Detroit.
Who is taking possession ?
Marcus Van Sciver.
You've been picking through
a lot of keyholes, Zack.
It's my brother.
Your brother got caught up
and somebody shot him, okay ?
Got in over his head, he pissed off
the wrong people just like every
single one of these guys.
The ash. It's found its
way onto the streets now.
With the rest of the drugs.
There's a whole other world
underneath this one, Krista.
Do yourself a favor.
Get out of the city !
You know who killed my brother.
If we have a little patience,
we can find out what they're up to,
what their operations are.
You look familiar.
Like someone I once knew.
It's ok to fight.
It's only natural.
You turned her ?
It's my turn, my...
He's here.
Let me serve you.
It's been fun.
Fritz. That's enough.
You're my new favorite.
What did you do to me ?
I injected you with a serum,
to get you thinking straight.
I can work with you.
Just like I worked
with your brother.
I got to get back.
What do you think ?
Could go either away.
No !!!
You better do it !
Wouldn't want any vampire running
around the countryside, now would we ?
- Please, god!
- God's off playing with himself.
Just you and me now, lunch meat.
Blade The Series - 102 - Death Goes On
If they figured out how to neutralize
garlic and silver, we are chit ???
Any sign of Krista ?
Nothing.
Good morning, sweetheart.
You must be hungry.
Mom ?
You can't be here.
I know, it's all so confusing.
But it will come down.
You just need to eat.
Get out !
Krista !
No !
No !!!
Oh god...
Help ! Help ! Help !
Bloody newborns!
You had night terrors for ten years.
She won't last that long.
But she's gone
the first chance I get.
What's different ?
In this world.
What's new ?
Besides, you deciding to work with a
revenge-crazed vampire chick.
Ash.
Vampire ash.
Now you think Marcus is
juicing his own troups ?
I'll have to have Fritz
when I'll catch him.
You mean kill him.
Catch him.
Dissectr him.
Then kill him.
Does the silver burn?
No. It tickles.
I'm going to think
you like this.
Marcus.
- Pleasant flight?
- No complaints.
Heard you raised a few eyebrows.
It's a new girl ?
An essential addition to the fold.
And how is Prague ?
Missing you.
I'll never understand what
you see in this despicable city.
It has a special
place in my heart.
Hello, Winston.
Chase.
Fritz.
Trenched in blood as always.
And how are you ?
Feeling like a rock star ?
I'm feeling like a rematch.
Blade.
I see.
Is that wise?
No, not yet.
The  vaccine works. We should
take advantage of it.
Fritz.
Blade's interference must
make things difficult.
We're moving RND
to the West Coast.
Trucks carrying test subjects
should be arriving now.
Well, that will be welcomed
news for the board.
You're sure the
vaccine is stable ?
Yes, it's stable.
Then perhaps a new
day has dawned.
I haven't done ash in two days.
It's so hard.
Ok.
You spend this on aspirine,
antiseptic and food for your baby.
Cherry ? Cherry ?
You're listening to me ?
Yes, sir.
Next meeting
tomorrow on noon,
you stay out of
the ash until there.
And keep your fingers
out of your mouth.
Thank you, Reverend.
Sorry for the interruption.
The  church let you back in ?
They call me Reverend
out of respect.
You don't have to be
ordained to have a calling.
As you already know.
Having much success?
Some.
Vampire  ash ain't like
the usual junk.
best stuff hooks you bone deep.
I was wondering
if you'd ever return.
And now I can start worrying that
my recovering ashes are gonna get
caught up in your crossfire.
Your ashes ?
All they need is a little help and
I offer 'em empathy, support, love.
You should try it sometimes.
Back to the question.
There's some vampire
moving in on the ash trade.
Wouldn't surprise me.
Feeding off our own.
But you've heard
nothing concrete ?
Experiments.
On vampires, might be
ash related, might not.
How will I find out ?
You know an ash dealer named Cain ?
Not yet.
So maybe Cain will give
you some answers.
How do I find Cain ?
Try to ask one of
his customers.
But watch yourself.
If they're amped up on vampires dope,
you might find yourself in some serious shit.
Where's Cain ?
How much ash did you do?
All of it.
Like I've got
time for this.
I hear you're having
a difficult time.
Yeah, death's a bitch.
You're not dead, Krista.
My life is over.
What I was,
where I was going.
All that's gone.
Your life is
just beginning.
My life is what ?
Some sort of
a prisonner ?
My door's locked.
It's just a precaution.
Newborns sometimes snap.
It's only until your mind and body
reconcile with the metabolic changes.
Here I was thinking it was
because nobody trusted me.
Perhaps I haven't given
you the proper respect.
Yeah, throwing me off the
building was a little rude.
Yeah, you were trying to
kill me, let's not forget.
I haven't.
You will.
We should talk.
Aren't we ?
I mean over dinner.
I'll collect you
in one hour.
And what's
on the menu ?
Leftovers.
Courtesy of
Detective Boone.
We're not all monsters, Krista.
This will get easier.
I promise.
- Yes.
- This complicates things ?
Immeasurably.
Is Chase in on the joke ?
No.
Only the doctor.
And he's more surprised then I am.
It's all I can do to
keep on track.
Maybe this is fate trying
to tell you something.
Well, there is a bigger
picture Winston, much bigger.
Yes.
Let's hope the board never sees it.
I'll leave that up to you.
Safe journey.
And to you, my friend.
We're making a detour.
Take me to Meanus.
Yes, sir.
Who's this ?
Asher.
Is he high ?
Oh, yeah.
Son of a bitch.
One more time,
where's Cain ?
Go to hell !
Who is Cain ?
A lead that Carlyle gave me.
What about Fritz ?
Fine.
Then I won't tell you that Marcus
made reservation for two at Lotus.
How did you find out ?
Hey, it's what you
don't pay me for.
Is he with Krista ?
That, I can't tell you.
But it is his usual table.
From what I hear, a nice one.
Keep your fingers
away from him.
Anything here
tempt your palate ?
What are they tranqued with ?
You won't taste it.
It's a new herbal recipe.
Too many complaints with
the other stuff.
Mmh,  good.
But I was hoping for something
a little more cornfed.
It's not everyday I get to
sample American cuisine.
You're in luck.
I've just took possession of an honor
student from Illinois out on vacation.
Plucked from a Cancun beach.
Blonde, big boned.
Carpet matches drapes?
Hardwood floor.
Kids!
Don't be so surprised.
- I just... wasn't expecting...
- Food ?
Thank you.
Nutrionally, its effect are negligeable.
But it is pleasurable nonetheless.
You have noticed
your senses are hightened.
Is that what we're
living for now ?
Pleasure ?
Some of us.
As in most families, there are the
breadwinners and the freeloaders.
What are we ?
If I'm successful,
the House of Chthon is going to be
something different entirely.
What's that ?
Eternal.
You were thinking we are already ?
Apart from silver and
garlic we'll live forever ?
No.
Granted our years on this earth
are generous. But like most lives.
We're subjects to nature
occasional calling.
And your experiments
in the slaughterhouse ?
I'm assuring we are not
subject to anything.
Least of all nature.
- What about...
- Blade ?
Ashers ?
You know about them.
I know that there's a drug
trade based on dead vampires.
I'd imagine that's
a problem for you.
Increasingly.
Well, maybe one day
they'll take out Blade.
Blade isn't a vampire.
He's a Daywalker.
half human. And he is the bane
of the Twelve Houses.
Twelve Houses ?
Ah yes.
Your new family
is quite extended.
Is everyone here ?
No.
Just us.
You alright ?
- I don't think so.
- Krista !
It's the serum.
Food will make you sick.
That's nice to know.
- Marcus is up there.
- I know.
I need information
on Fritz.
Like what ?
He is not your average vampire.
Find out what you can.
How he did it.
Hurry.
Krista ?
Feeling better ?
Next stop ?
Hell !
Yo Cain.
Product's in the back.
He just fed so step
on it a few times.
How many times ?
23.
Just make it last.
Dipshit.
You're keeping the car ?
Crash it.
Is there a problem ?
Winston missed
his flight.
We can't trace the driver.
GPS ?
The signal was
terminated.
But we did get
a final fix.
Where ?
M eanus.
You're driving.
You are staying here.
I don't think that's
a good idea.
You said what?
If Blade took Winston...
In all likelyhood, you're
Blade number one target.
If you cross paths,
either you'll kill him,
he'll kill you
or quite possibly he'll take
you down and carve you up
thereby discovering and ruining
all of our considerable efforts.
I'm not going
to risk that.
Neither should you.
Is that quiet clear ?
Yeah.
Can I get something to drink now ?
You haven't told
where Cain is.
I don't know anything.
Swear to god !
You know.
Please, can I
get some blood ?
It'll chew off my gut.
How about an
appetizer ?
What happens now ?
He wakes up in a ditch and
leads me to Cain.
That's positive
thinking ?
He's an addict.
I'm a threat.
He needs to protect
his source.
Something I know
a little about.
We found him maybe 30
minutes after Winston left.
Look, Blade's in town, right ?
Maybe Blade got him.
Blade got Winston.
The man is a scurge.
You really should do
something about it.
This wasn't Blade.
Blade wouldn't have just
stopped Winston.
He would have come in here, slaughtered
you and then freed the poor soldiers
celled to people like us.
Where can Chase find a towel?
There's a closet
in there.
So,
how was your
asher problem ?
It's not so bad.
Ok.
Ok, so we've had some
little trouble lately.
Please, Marcus,
don't shut me down.
Look, I'm upgrading security.
I've a vested interest in keeping
my clientele as safe as possible.
And how many of your clients
have you lost so far ?
This month, 4...
5 if you want to count Winston.
If I must ?
What's with the towel ?
He's shuting you down.
That's a private party ?
Yeah.
Get out !
I thought you were
Marcus' right hand man.
Seems strange him
not letting you...
do what you do.
He has his reasons.
Which you don't
agree with.
Not sure I do either.
Things change.
Take you.
One day you're
home from Iraq.
The next thing you're
the boss' new plaything.
You're walking around,
asking questions.
I'm asking you.
What happened ?
I don't get why Blade
would wanna carve you up.
What's he gonna learn ?
Nothing.
He'll be dead.
And I'll be the
one to kill him.
In broad daylight.
But that's not possible.
Like I said, things change.
One day you're scared
shitless of a pizza topping.
And the silver fillings
of some old man's teeth.
Of the dawn's early
goddamn light.
The sun doesn't
matter anymore.
Because you're different.
Because you believed
in something.
You helped make some
things happen.
What happened ?
Project Aurora.
Five years and
millions of dollars.
And a thousand dead
vampires later.
You get me...
The vaccines were a success,
and where am I ?
In the basement,
beating meat.
Sorry.
Honey, it's okay.
It will be over soon,
I promise.
Just need to
talk about this.
I'm sorry I don't know. I swear to
god, I don't know anything.
We know you use it.
That you use us.
That your blood smells so bad that
it makes me want to drown you in it.
I'll quit snorting ash,
I will I promise.
I've got a baby.
I've  got a little
boy please.
Does his blood reak too ?
No, no, no, no,
please, no !
You tell me you took my friend
Winston and your boy grows
safe and sound.
Cross my barely
beating hearts.
Give me a name or I'll eat
him in front of you.
I think we must assume
that Winston is gone.
Yes, Charlotte, yes.
I'm taking care
of that problem.
Yes, but as I outlined in the proposal,
Blade's involvement is inevitable.
I'm just surprised
you're taking this...
Yes, Charlotte, absolutely.
Everything will be handled.
All assets will be secured.
They want proof of
Aurora's success.
I'm right here.
But there're not willing to
send another evaluator.
They want you in Prague.
And you want me as far
away from Blade as possible.
I know you're eager to
finish what you started.
But Blade must wait.
I'm beholden from those above me,
and they demand caution.
We have done an amazing thing but
no one must know how we did it.
Fritz ?
Fritz tells me you caught
him in a weak moment.
Aurora ?
I want it.
You want ?
We should all have it.
If it's everything that
Fritz said it is.
Fritz has no idea what it is.
And neither do you.
And you will not discuss it
anymore especially with Fritz.
What did you do to him ?
He's going away tonight.
Some place safe.
Marcus.
The girl,
she knew who took Winston.
- Are you certain ?
Dead. His name is Cain.
He deals in ash.
We hit him.
We hit the largest
ash lab in Detroit.
I can have a red
team ready in one hour.
Good.
Let's take the war hero.
I'm sure you'll find it
invigorating.
That's a splendid idea.
Krista.
Keep your head down.
Where are you going?
A warehouse in West Mile.
Where you ate the raver ?
Stop with me.
You best get packed.
See you in a few days.
Kill everything.
Burn it to the ground.
Hey !
Let me in.
Hey, let me in !
I got to see Cain,
I got to warn him.
Shit's coming down.
Blade.
I didn't tell him anything.
You didn't have to.
Stupid son a bitch !
Man, I did you a favor.
Thanks for that.
Give me the belt.
Guys, down there.
Stay with me.
This way !
We got movement on
the north side.
Say again.
Repeat, movement inbound.
Get a fix and pin it down.
We'll do. I'll investigate
and report back.
Let's get going.
Sorry, sir.
Just listening to
the assault feed.
- Seems like Chase's got her hands full.
- What's happening ?
- Not sure, something inbound.
- Really?
Go !
They're gone.
Something over here !
Where's Cain ?
Chase ?
Shut up.
God, don't !
I can't move my leg.
So much for the frying pan.
Welcome to the fire.
Fritz !
Stop, Fritz !
Let's finish this !
Krista, don't let
him take Fritz !
Krista, kill him !
Do it now !
You think she's gone native?
No.
She killed the golden goose.
Fritz was the key.
She did what
she had to do.
She's the key.
She's the way in.
And what about Cain ?
Another day.
Hey ?
Wake up !
Dispatcher, I need a
coroner on county 319,
2 miles east of the Boxton overpass
overpassed and a tow truck.
Better tell the crime lab to.
What you got ?
Body under a blanket
in a silver Dodge.
South Dakota plate 3 6 Adam 4 7 9 current.
Body appears male.
No obvious signs of foul play.
Hardware's rolling.
ETA in 15 minutes.
Thanks, Dany.
Somebody in there ?
I'm a state trooper. I'm armed.
Come out hands first.
Dispatch, I need
an ambulance ASAP.
Did you say an ambulance ?
Come back.
Too late for that, sweetheart.
Next time on Blade.
I think we waked up
the neighboors.
Ready to answer
my question ?
I need you to
make a delivery.
Do I need to know
what it's in the bag ?
Do you ?
You killing vampires ?
Scum from the House of Armaya.
You ???
Jesus Christ !
Transcript : Rijad