Previously on Blade
From the dying ashes of one world,
we will emerge into better one.
You make it sound like apocalpyse.
Destruction is always required
before rebirth.
Doctor Vonner? No!!!
People loved this guy.
After him we knew.
- Well, she's cute.
- She's pregnant.
The question is...
with what?
Boone gets to Domic, tells him
we've been experimenting on his people.
Just the sort of thing, the House of
Armaya might need to turn this into
full scale war.
And if there is a war,
we will lose,
- unless Aurora works.
- It will work.
It'd damn well better.
- What is your business in Germany?
- Pleasure.
And to aid you in your travels.
I'm asking you for help.
And this must remain a secret.
Or the Pure Bloods will kill us all.
- There's something wrong with my baby?
- Everything's fine.
You stay away from me!
What is that?
Dinner.
Please, let me go.
When it's time.
I'll scream.
I'll stop you.
What was all that back there?
Hello, I have a right to know
what's happening to me, damn it!
Let's discuss Doctor Vonner first.
Come on, what does he have to
do with any of this?
Did you kill him?
Is this about my baby?
Is my baby ok?
Vonner, what did he do to you?
I'm not telling you anything,
you freak.
That's it.
Blade The Series - 106 - Delivery
Let's get some to my wife.
Powerful isn't it?
Those bombs even sort of sounded
like that, if that makes any sense.
Yeah.
Who painted this?
There's no signature.
Our specialist Pete Allison.
We were in the 123rd bataillon
together near Doah.
After the bomb went off, when
everybody was yelling and screaming,
at home, it must
has been his lucky day.
A week after he painted this,
he hung himself.
He'd uh, he'd only
been home a month.
I think holding on this community
landmark is essential.
This building, before it became
a glass plant for early 20th century
automobiles was a blacksmith foundry.
Turning it into a public art house
instead of tearing it down
it's not only good for people,
it's good for the soul.
Sorry.
Hello?
Excuse me.
Where's the girl?
Track her down!
Let me talk to Chase.
Is she alive?
When?
Have a full medical team ready.
- Uncle Pat!
- Buddy of mine thought
he saw you here.
- I can't talk to you right now.
- Fine, I'll talk, you'll listen.
Do you have any idea what
you're doing to your mother?
She's got a son who's dead and
a daughter who's vanished.
- God I'm not vanished!
- God knows what you're doing!
Showing up in the middle of the night,
telling her that you're avenging
- Zach's death or some kind of bullshit.
- No.
No, you got to get her help.
I've seen this before. You get back,
you think you're fine but you're not.
I know what you're going through.
You have absolutely no idea what
I'm going through.
Well, I know a couple of things.
That you're abandonning your family
- and your mother needs
you now more than ever!
- Mom is fine!
No she's not, she's not fine Krista,
she's sick!
What?
She collapsed this morning.
I took her to the hospital.
- What's wrong with her?
- We don't know yet.
- Which hospital?
- Heaven View.
Krista! Gotta go.
Hold on, buddy, I'm talking to
my niece here.
Your niece?
Pleased to meet you,
Marcus Van Sciver.
Now we would love to stay and chat,
but we just don't have the time.
Krista?
Chase?
You are home now.
You are home.
Blade.
Blade?
Yes I know.
There'll be time for him.
I want you in Berlin tonight.
What's in Berlin?
A young woman.
My property was stolen.
I want you to find her
and bring her back to me.
- Marcus...
- There is no discussion!
Go!
You know with
that baby coming...
Adams said I could get
a few extra shift.
You know what,
you get that Joe's shift
because I'm telling you, the man just
drives the paychecks away.
Sassy!
So how long until dinner?
20 minutes!
Why don't you go watch
Mannix or something?
Ok.
Just gonna go finish up outside.
Ma?
Hello, sweetie.
Now, you take those shoes off before
you track blood all over my floor.
You know, if I'd had known
what a murderer son of a bitch
you'd grow up to be.
I would have killed you in my room.
Eric, you know what you got to do!
Gut the bitch!
Let me show you how!
You always look at people like that?
Like what?
Like you want to kill them.
If I wanted you dead.
You'd be.
Small mercies.
Don't count 'em just yet.
Just excuse me
for a second.
H ey!
How is she doing?
She's asleep.
- They know what's wrong with her?
- Yeah.
Leuchimia.
Is she dying?
Doctor Westler says with a bone marrow
transplant she's got a good chance.
Of course, it's gotta come from
the family. I was no match.
You're the only family left.
I can't do it.
- What do you mean?
- I mean I can't!
What's the problem?
Hepathitis?
Something worse?
Some goddamn junk?
You smoking it?
Shooting it?
What's that Van Sciver punk
doing to you?
The Army will pay for a program,
Krista, you can get clean!
- You don't get it.
- What's not to get it, you'd rather be
an addict than help your mom!
We're family Krista.
- I'll be back.
- Krista!
What do you think it is?
My baby.
A girl or a boy?
No idea.
And I don't care.
Look, I need to go.
You're staying right here.
Then I'm pissing right here.
Hold it.
Uh, yeah.
Well, how about you punch the pregnant
lady again and see what happens?
I think we need
a new route to Paris.
- Any report from the hunters?
- They're working through Europe
city by city.
There's no sign of Blade though.
And Jakob?
Heading to Paris. He thinks that
Blade has a friend there.
Krista's on road to Berlin, send her
to Paris, tell Jakob to expect her.
Sir?
How many?
Just her.
You're borrowing or returning?
Sit please.
There.
What's on my mind, Marcus?
- I'm sure I've no idea.
- Guess!
Berlin I assume.
And I can bet what's on yours.
Chase.
Roasted and marinating in blood
from what I hear.
She's recovering quite well.
And tell me why
she was in Berlin.
What she was doing at the Malinger
Institute and why Blade showed up.
Let me add...
do... not... lie!
Inspired by my previous
assessment in Project Aurora,
Doctor Vonner's death
has ended us somewh...
Go on!
Chase was in Berlin protecting
an asset that was supposed
to further our progress.
The asset got taken.
By Blade?
You have other assets?
18, in various locations.
Blade has only compromised this one,
the others are safe.
Where are they?
I'd rather not say.
- That information is limited
to keep the assets...
- Safe.
Yes.
So many secrets.
I trust you of all people
who'd want it no other way.
You may have to share
those secrets.
With who?
The House of Armaya.
Domic.
He's requested a meeting.
He has certain informations
he would like to discuss.
To be more specific,
what he'd like to discuss
are terms.
Terms?
Could it be that Boone somehow
managed to spill the beans about our
slaughtering of Armayans for science?
Boone is dead.
- Domic learnt nothing from him.
- He knows!
Is this really the best way?
Streets aren't safe.
You know I saved your ass from
those undead freaks back there.
The least you can do is to
answer some questions!
You first.
Start with Vonner.
I met him at a free clinic
that I go to for check-ups.
He said that I was
a prime candidate,
young, healthy,
good genetic history.
He told me there were
this couple he knew.
Couldn't have kids.
I needed the money.
Screw you.
Look, I'm helping a couple that
can't have children become parents.
Think that was the idea.
Look I don't have anyone okay?
It's just, it always has been,
doing what I have to do.
I saw a way to pay some bills,
lose some debt.
What? What? Maybe I should
have been a stripper?
Doctor Vonner gave me
a better option. You know.
One that make people happy.
He lied.
Those undead freaks,
he worked for them.
They want what you have.
What?
My baby? Why?
That's what I'm going
to find out.
How? Where are we going?
To see a doctor,
someone I trust.
- To make sure everything's ok?
- That's the idea.
Donne-moi 9 mois!
Donnez 9 mois!
Allez-y!
Don't hit the pregnant lady.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
Is something wrong
with my baby?
No, no, no, no dear,
everything is fine.
Yeah, just as I thought.
Perfectly healthy.
How is it?
Allow me to consult
with my associate.
Movement.
We're going in.
Is it Blade and the girl?
If it isn't, we'll wait for him.
Just so everyone understands.
The girl is secondary.
That's what she is carrying
that we are after.
That comes with us.
Dead or alive.
Weapon check.
Marcus tells me you're a vet.
Recent?
Very.
You?
I've served my country.
Several countries over
the past few years.
Where was your first battle?
Gettysburg.
No kidding?
Blue or gray?
Both.
I found the food on both sides
of the line aqually tempting.
Whatt's your ammo?
Hallow point, silver-tipped.
Silver has no effect on Blade.
I know.
I don't know how to say this.
- Vampire?
- No.
What am I looking at?
Well, that's just it.
She's carrying
some kind of fluid.
Uh, nothing else.
Let's see it.
- Vanessa, do you what
an amniocentisis is?
- Yeah.
Uh, Doctor Vonner checked out
some fluid last week.
Everything was fine.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with my baby?
Who is it?
Open it.
Oh my god!
Hi.
I'm here to kill you, kill Blade
and take the girl back to Marcus.
Like that's ever gonna happen.
Bonjour.
Marcus sent you?
Me and a team.
Where are they?
I had them first.
Excusez-moi, I need a drink.
Hello Vanessa.
I know you.
You worked for Doctor Vonner.
You're with the freaks.
Not exactly.
I'm one.
Word of advice, Marcus.
Don't speak to Domic
unless spoken to you.
You're not his favorite person
these days.
Charlotte!
Domic!
Your protégé has done quite well
for himself.
You know,
back in the day, I used to be
in the gladiator business.
Nothing like a good
blood sport, yes?
What are we talking about?
Well, why don't we start with the vaccine,
you've been making with the blood
of my people.
What's the cute name Marcus
gave it? Aurora.
I can't imagine many tears
being shed over the demise of
a thousand or so Armayans.
Can you imagine what the reaction
will be when they'll learn that
the House of Chthon, the high
and mighty Chthon
who styled themselves the leader
of the vampire nation,
the tireless support for the peace
between the Twelve Houses
has secretly been
developping a vaccine
that would give them,
and only them
total superiority over the
rest of their vampire brathering.
What do you want?
In.
You want immunity?
Yes.
Immunity.
And amnesty.
It is time for our exile to come
to an end as well.
The House of Armaya demands
full inclusion back into the
governing body.
That's impossible!
You tried to destroy us.
The folly of youth.
You've been keeping the Houses
in line for over a hundred years.
They'll listen to you.
And what you are going to say,
is "we welcome back Armaya
with open arms
and Domic, Domic deserves his rightful
place along side his fellow
Pure Bloods."
Just to be clear,
this is blackmail.
It's justice!
And in the events of
my untimely death
I have certain document detailing
your transgrations against m...
- I get it!
- Good.
When would you like this done?
Within the week.
I'll need more time.
You don't have it.
Armaya is back in
the fold by Friday.
Or by Saturday.
Chthon will be destroyed.
Domic!
How did you find out?
His name is Sands,
luckily for me.
He survived your funny games.
Mr Van Sciver, if I could just
say one thing.
Go to hell.
All of you.
Like life ain't hard enough,
we got you bastards
pushing your goddamn chess pieces
all over the goddamn board!!!
Lost pawns are sick of it.
You have my number.
You know he won't stop.
He'll keep wanting more.
Yes.
Like someone else I know.
How are you doing?
Sleepy.
Just close your eyes,
it will be over soon.
It wasn't supposed
to be like this.
I know.
I just wanted to have a baby.
What's inside me?
I don't know, sweetheart.
We're gonna get it out, ok?
You... are going to feel a tug.
Ok.
You're doing ok, you're doing ok.
It will be fine.
You're ok, you're ok.
I wanna kill them,
I wanna kill them for
what they've done!
They're gonna pay, they will.
They die too fast.
They need to suffer.
I know.
Do you even feel pain?
I want them to feel pain for
what they've done!
We do.
My little man.
Marcus had
incubated something.
Some sort of biological substance.
Is she alright?
She'll never have children.
I was forced to remove
compromised tissue, a lot of it.
I don't know what the long term
effects might be.
She's sleeping.
What happens now?
I'll figure out what this is.
Well, I gotta get this back to Marcus,
it's what he sent me here for.
Not all of it.
I need a sample.
And Vanessa?
She goes underground.
Get her as far away from me
as possible.
Blade, this isn't about Aurora.
Marcus is up to something else.
It could be even
something worse,
- I don't know...
- Later.
You know,
she has his mother's name.
Is she ready?
One moment.
It is time to go.
Don't be afraid, Vanessa.
You will be safe.
Where am I going?
I don't know.
And you won't know to, until
you'll get there.
As far as anyone else is concerned,
you are dead.
No one will come looking for you.
Come, you're free.
Like, I can't go home, ever.
No, no, no, you must very careful.
Many people have risked everything.
To make sure you and others like
you remain hidden from them. Here!
Tell them I said thank you,
tell them both.
If I see them again, yes.
I will do so.
Au revoir.
I'm done, I can't do this anymore.
I want out.
We're doing a good thing here.
I couldn't have done it without you.
Yes, you could have,
you don't need me.
What I need is more.
Information.
Locations, photographs,
plans, names...
- Oh, I can't do it!
- Yes, you can.
You're inside,
don't give up now.
This never gonna end, is it?
Marcus is expecting that.
This is all of it?
I got what I need.
What?
I oughta walk back into Chthon
and tell Marcus yet
another one of his assassination
squad has been wiped out.
You got away and Vanessa is dead.
Yet, somehow I wound up walking away
with whatever was inside of her?
Uh, he ain't buying that.
What are you suggesting?
I'm in a war.
With you.
I better look like it.
Collins?
So, I haven't heard from you
in the last 3 days.
Crime's still running.
That's not your problem,
Louisiana 's got that.
We're all done.
Get on the plane and come home!
You came back to early,
you weren't ready.
But you're not hearing me.
I'm gonna make this real simple,
you're relieved, you're completely
off this now!
Nat, look, I think...
I think I'm looking for a...
a monster.
Yeah, they're all monsters,
let someone else do it.
I have to do this!
Ray, I'm shit serious now,
this is not about
Sarah and Johanna,
if you try to work something out
you do it on the couch with Dr Bishop.
Do not screw up your carrier
over this now!
Just go home!
Sorry.
I'm sorry I lost the prize.
It's ok.
Krista's on the job.
Like I said...
I'm sorry.
Domic's weight in.
He knows.
He wants to enter exile
Heard of Aurora and he is forcing
Charlotte to plead his case to
the Pure Bloods.
He's humiliating her.
She doesn't see it that way.
You're humiliating her.
Sir, Krista's back.
Thank you.
I gotta go.
You rest.
She tells me you had a
qualified success.
What happened?
Blade happened.
Jakob and the rest of the team?
Gone.
Vanessa?
Disemboweled.
I salvaged what I could.
Blade got nothing.
You're certain?
Good.
There was no child.
What she was carrying
was more valuable than life.
Death?
We'll see.
If that's all,
I'd like to get to medical.
Of course.
Krista!
Excellent work.
I have great plans
for you in the future.
Happy to hear it.
Next time on Blade.
Donny?
Looks like your past is
only coming back to haunt you.
***, it's about me.
Derek?
Dad.
- Something's happening to me?
- Yeah, son.
He's going to find out what
he is soon enough.
I'm his father, I'll handle it.
We can stay together for a while.
We can stay together forever
if you want.
Mr Brooks?
Yeah.
I'm here about the boy.
I'm Abraham Whistler.
Transcript : Travis and Tagne
Synchro : Tagne
www.forom.com