Right now, terrorists are plotting
to assassinate a presidential candidate.
My wife and daughter have been kidnapped.
And people that I work with
may be involved in both.
I'm FederalAgent Jack Bauer.
This is the longest day ofmy life.
- Mr Drazen.
- You found Bauer?
- No, but we're doing everything possible.
- I'm pulling the plug on you.
You were supposed to frame Bauer for the
assassination of Palmer, but he's still alive.
- Give me a little more time.
- I'll give you 30 minutes. Then I take over.
- We found their inside person: Jamey.
- People died because ofyou.
- I didn't think anyone would die.
- Well, they did.
Get her out of those!
We need medical help.
Jack, Jamey tried to kill herself.
That was the clinic. Jamey didn't make it.
I got a call from Maureen Kingsley. She's
gonna publicly accuse my son of murder.
- And the second source?
- George Ferragamo.
He was your son's therapist for four years.
I wanted to talk about my son.
Whatever you leaked to Kingsley,
certain people
wanna stop you from confirming it.
You've covered up one murder, and now
you're threatening me if I don't keep quiet?
I'm trying to protect you.
There was a fire. They say it might have been
a broken gas line. He didn't get out in time.
It was murder.
Anything goes wrong, everyone
around the car dies, starting with you.
- I'm on my way to Teri and Kim now.
- You cannot go into an armed camp.
- Kim!
- Daddy! Oh, my God! I knew you'd come.
- Where are you?
- I found the people behind the Palmer hit.
You're one of 'em
unless you prove otherwise.
- Kim?
- It's OK. He's the one who gave us the gun.
- Why are you helping them?
- Cos I got Kim into this.
- You trust him?
- I do.
Hold on!
On the satellite photos
you'll see an old water tower.
Follow the creek bed and run like hell!
Stay down.
Keep moving.
Neill, cut them off at the service road.
- The rest of you, come up behind him.
- Ira...
How could you let this happen?
We're cutting them off at the service road.
Bauer, his wife and daughter. And Rick.
Make sure they don't double back.
- I thought I could handle him. I thought...
- Stop thinking.
OK, we... we have to keep moving.
- What if Dad isn't...
- No, your dad's OK.
He told us to meet him
by the water tower and we will.
We just have to follow the creek.
Let's go. Come on! Let's go! Come on!
- I can't...
- Shut up. You can and you will.
- I'm slowing you down.
- Yes, you are, so you'd better speed up.
Sh. Get down. Get down!
Where are you?
Yeah. I got nothing.
Sh. We can move.
Wait. Come here. Get down.
What are we gonna do, Mom?
We can't go back, we can't go forward.
They're everywhere.
I think... we can catch the road further up
where it cuts through the woods.
- Dad told us to follow the creek bed.
- We don't really have a choice, do we?
We'll go up here. Come on.
The subscriberyou are trying to reach...
Hey. The property where
they're holding Jack's family
was leased six months ago
by a company that doesn't exist.
I have to go over the tax records.
- You all right?
- Jack's still not answering his cell.
Well, he could've shut it off
to keep it from ringing.
- Or maybe something's happened to him.
- Oh, look.
If anybody can
take care of himself, it's Jack.
Plus our tactical units should be there soon.
Bundy's heading up the operation. He's good.
Maybe you were right.
I should have brought Green in sooner.
You let Jack make the call
because it was his family on the line.
- What could you do?
- Yeah.
Look, I'm sorry. Since this whole thing
got started, I guess I've been a little harsh.
A little?
OK, maybe a lot.
I just... I've been afraid, and I...
You don't have to explain. All right?
You wanna talk about us,
we'll talk about it later, OK?
- I just want you to know that it's nothing...
- You're bringing in Jamey Farrell's mother?
Yes, to pick up Kyle, her son.
Before she sees him,
I want the two of you to question her.
If she has information that can help
protect Palmer, I need to know.
- What makes you think she has?
- $300,000 was deposited in her bank account
over the last four months.
They killed George Ferragamo.
That fire was no accident.
I wanna talk to Maureen Kingsley,
then go right to the DA.
Wait until you have the facts
before you go off.
The facts? Ferragamo was killed
so I could get elected.
- You don't know that.
- Then what?
I'm just saying, let's take a beat, see how
we should play this, before we do anything.
There's only one way to play this, Mike.
Maureen Kingsley will get
the story of her career after all.
- David...
- And after I talk to her I wanna see the DA.
- Shouldn't you run this by Sherry?
- Why? So she can try to talk me out of it?
She's your wife, David.
This is her life too. She deserves to know.
- Has the compound been cleared?
- Yes. There's been a change of plan.
- Meaning?
- Bauer showed up here like I said he would.
- You have him?
- Not yet, but I will.
Congratulations, Ira. You may have
bought yourself a second chance.
My contract included killing Palmer.
I wanna make good on it.
The way you were talking, it sounded like
you handed it off to someone else.
Bring me Bauer's body.
Then we'll talk about the senator.
You'll hear from me soon.
Drazen?
Yeah. Either we eliminate Bauer
or Drazen eliminates us.
- And that's the only option here?
- Basically.
Getting Bauer's not as easy as it sounds.
He phoned in some
GPS coordinates to somebody.
Whoever that is, I'm sure they're
gonna be calling the cavalry in soon.
I say we just cut our losses
and get the hell outta here.
You don't just get out with these people.
They come after you.
They keep coming until they find you,
no matter where you are.
And when they do...
Believe me, killing Bauer
is our only chance of staying alive.
They should have been here by now.
Come here. Sit down.
Easy, easy.
Here, let me take a look at it.
OK. This is gonna sting for a while,
but you're not mortally wounded.
The bullet passed straight through.
It didn't hit any bone or major artery.
- You got any loose clothing?
- Yeah, in my back pocket.
I got it.
Take a deep breath.
- Wait. Hold up, honey, hold up.
- Are you OK?
Yeah, no, I just...
I just wanna check where we are. We...
We... we may have veered a little south,
but we should have hit the road by now.
I can't see it. Do you see it up ahead?
You don't know where we are, do you?
Mom.
We're lost, aren't we?
No.
We should just go straight.
- It should be just up ahead.
- Are you sure?
That'll help stop the bleeding.
That's good.
Mike's your advisor. What's his advice?
He agrees with me.
He thinks you're making a mistake
by trying to take them on.
- They've already covered up one death.
- No, you don't know about Ferragamo.
But even if you're right,
will turning this into a media circus
bring him back to life?
- That's not the point.
- Your career. And your family.
You're... you're throwing away
everything you've built
without any hard evidence
of what really happened.
The police will find the evidence.
No. They won't, because
Carl and the people he works for,
they will twist the system
to get the result that they want.
That's what they do, David.
And you'll be left with nothing.
Sweetheart, to fight these people
you need power.
The kind of power you'll have
once you become president.
We knew from the start
that this was going to be an uphill race.
But we're almost there.
Look at the polls.
- Sherry, I don't know.
- No. Think, David, think.
Think of the millions of lives you can
make better once you win the candidacy.
How can I do the job
when my own house isn't in order?
David.
I told them to wait for us here at the water
tower. You heard me say that, right? Dammit.
- What are you gonna do?
- I gotta go back and find 'em.
- Green.
- It's Jack.
- There's been a complication.
- I'm listening.
Teri and Kim are not where they should be.
I've gotta find them.
I need to let the team
know where to pick you up.
Tell them to meet us at a water tower,
north area of the compound.
Check your satellite photos.
It's overlooking a reservoir.
Alberta, if I'm not back when the team
arrives, they're gonna find a kid in here.
- His name is Rick. He's wounded.
- Who is he?
Someone who helped us get out of there.
- Three tactical units are on their way.
- How much longer?
- 10 minutes. 15, tops.
- OK, I copy. Out.
- Jack.
- What?
Thanks.
Don't thank me. Thank my daughter.
This whole thing,
I had no idea what was going on.
Dan said we were just scaring
some guys who'd backed out of a deal.
Yeah, well, when you started to see what was
happening, you should have done something.
He was my friend.
Hey, you kidnapped my daughter.
You're gonna have to live with that.
Son, part of getting a second chance
is taking responsibility
for the mess you made in the first place,
you understand me?
Good. I'll be back in a few minutes.
That shack over there. Maybe we can
find it on this to see where we are.
See? I don't think we're as far off as I thought.
Mom!
Honey, come on. Stay down.
Go, go.
Down. Down.
It's Gaines.
Everyone circle back to section five.
OK. When he gets
to the back of the shed, we'll go.
- What if he sees us?
- We'll be all right.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah, it's nothing.
- Mom, you keep saying that, but...
- It's gonna be fine, I promise, honey. It's fine.
- Mom!
- Teri, stay down!
- Jack!
- Are you both OK?
- Yeah.
- Come here.
This is Gaines. Who's shooting?
Whoever's shooting,
call in your position now!
Dammit! They're gonna swarm this place.
We gotta get outta here.
- Where's Rick? Is he OK?
- He's fine.
- Where is he?
- Waiting at the water tower.
CTU's sending a chopper.
We gotta get outta here now. Hold on.
OK, come on, it's clear. Come on,
we gotta move. We don't have much time.
Hello, Mrs Vasquez. Thank you for coming in.
- They said I could pick up my grandson.
- We'll take you to him soon.
- First we wanna ask you a few questions.
- Yes, I have a question too.
How can a woman bleed to death,
and nobody does anything about it?
We're sorry about Jamey, Mrs Vasquez.
But it wasn't like that.
My daughter's dead, isn't she?
Please... take me to Kyle.
We really do have to ask you a few questions.
- I'm not interested in your questions.
- Mrs Vasquez.
Your daughter was a traitor.
- What?
- She confessed before she died.
And if you withhold information,
you can be held as an accomplice.
If that happens,
who's gonna take care of Kyle?
What do you want to know?
IRS records show you earn $45,000 a year.
But an account in your name shows a series
of deposits adding up to more than $300,000.
It's... It's from Jamey.
So that Kyle would have enough money
in case something happened to her.
Who gave Jamey the money?
- She never said.
- And you never asked?
All this money in your account, and
you never once asked where it came from?
Kyle needs you.
Don't do anything to jeopardise that.
Maxton and Neill, you're the only two who
haven't checked in yet. Where are you?
One more time. Maxton and Neill.
- This is Maxton.
- Where are you? Why haven't you called in?
We're crossing the creek bed,
trying to cut off Bauer from the service road.
Not if you keep telling me where you are.
Give me the PalmPilot.
Neill is the only one who hasn't called in.
Maxton, what area was Neill patrolling?
Uh... the northeast side ofthe creek.
He split offon his own.
OK. They're coming from over there.
We can hit the road down a little farther,
avoid them completely. Come on.
Maureen? Don't make me get hotel security.
I know you're in there.
- Why are you shutting me out?
- I think we've said everything we need to say.
Can I at least come in?
Maureen, please. Open the door and let me in.
I know I asked you
to back off the story about my son.
But I've changed my mind.
Dr Ferragamo's dead.
- You already knew.
- I don't wanna hear any more.
What do you mean, you don't wanna hear it?
- I've left the network.
- What?
- When?
- You should leave it alone too.
That's my advice. As a friend.
They got to you.
Did they pay you off?
Because I wouldn't have thought
you were for sale.
They threatened you too.
- I'll see that you're protected.
- I have protected myself.
Maureen. You're withholding
evidence in a capital crime.
What evidence? Dr Ferragamo is dead.
His files have been destroyed.
- But the piece of paper with Keith's writing...
- There is no piece of paper.
Not any more.
There's still my word.
It counts for something.
It's not enough, Senator.
Not against these people.
I'm sorry.
- There's no radio.
- Bauer's been listening.
To every damn word!
Mrs Vasquez has received
two wire transfers since January.
Both from a holding company
called Luca Univox based in Belgrade.
Jack suggested a connection to Belgrade.
- He was on assignment there two years ago.
- Did you check for a connection to the hit?
These new files may give us a new angle.
So who do we know in Belgrade
who's keyed into the financial community?
Come on.
Can you call them?
Maybe. The chopper
should have been here by now.
- What about Rick? Isn't he meeting us here?
- Dammit. No signal.
Rick was wounded. He's in the water tower.
When the chopper arrives, he'll come out.
- So what are we waiting for?
- Kim.
- Shouldn't he at least know we're here?
- When your father says it's OK.
- There's no one even around. Dad.
- Kim, no!
Get back! Get back!
- It's a sniper rifle.
- What do we do?
Stay here. Don't move for anything
but the chopper. Do you understand me?
- Where are you going?
- He wants me.
Jack!
He's trying to draw us away from the women.
It's fine by me.
Once he's dead, they'll be easy.
I'll keep him pinned down.
Circle around till you get a clear shot.
- Dammit.
- That's right, Jack.
You don't have a shot from that distance.
- How much longer do we have?
- Until what?
Until your people get here.
I wouldn't wait around
to find out if I were you.
I don't have a choice.
The people I work for made that pretty clear.
Agh!
The DA's inside. You want me to sit in?
Give me a minute.
- Sir?
- It's OK.
He's with the campaign.
The DA's down the hall, Carl.
Waiting for me to tell a story.
- It's over.
- See, and I think it's just getting started.
Don't get stupid on me now, David.
- It seems I've been stupid for a long time.
- Then open your eyes for once.
This... the whole thing, it's one big machine.
I'm the oil that keeps the pistons pumping,
the motor turning, the wheels spinning...
Not any more.
I like you, David. I really do.
And I think you would make
one hell of a commander in chief.
I know what you did to Ferragamo.
Every engine produces waste.
It's the physics of the situation.
- Listen to yourself.
- Consider the alternatives.
A year from now, you'll either be promoting
your agenda for the nation,
or visiting your son in prison.
- A jury will believe that it was an accident.
- I'm not talking about the rapist, David.
I'm talking about Dr Ferragamo.
- Keith had nothing to do with Ferragamo.
- Of course he didn't.
But if somebody were
to mention the word "arson"...
You son of a bitch!
You planted something?
The people we both work for, David,
they know how to get what they want.
Hi, Mike.
What was that all about?
The DA's waiting in there.
What do you want me to say?
Tell him I'm sorry.
I have nothing to say.
I made a mistake.
I don't understand.
I'm running for president, Mike.
And I'm gonna win.
- Hey!
- Over here!
Hey!
Wait.
Federal agent! Drop your weapons!
Put your hands in the air!
- Mrs Bauer?
- Yes!
Put your hands down. Do you
or your daughter need medical attention?
- No, but my husband...
- Where is he?
- I don't know. He's somewhere up there.
- Go!
Come on.
Stay back.
Kim!
- Mrs Bauer, wait!
- It's all right. Kim!
Kim! Kimberly, stop. Kim!
Kim.
- Dad said he'd be in here. Where is he?
- Wherever he is, they'll find him.
- What if Gaines found him?
- He'd be dead.
They'd be carrying him
outta here in a body bag.
- No. He's gotta be here. I gotta find him.
- Just stop it, Kimberly.
I know you care about this boy,
but I need you to be here for me now,
and your dad needs
both of us to be there for him.
You're losing blood.
Not enough to stop me from killing you.
Maybe neither ofus has to die.
Like I said, Jack, I don't have that choice.
Then maybe at least
you can tell me what's going on.
Cofell. He mentioned
something about Belgrade.
That was a military operation.
How's Palmer connected to that?
- You were there, Jack. You should know.
- Let's say I don't.
Neither do I. The less I know,
the better I can do my job.
That'sjust the nature ofour business.
Then why did you bring my family into this?
That might have been a mistake.
They wanted to make it personal.
Who's "they"?
Put down the weapon, Mr Gaines.
We can protect you.
No, you can't.
Put down the weapon!
Good luck.
Federal agent! Drop your weapon!
Interlace your fingers behind your head.
Sir, we have Bauer in custody.
We also have another man down.
- Bring Bauer to the landing zone right away.
- Roger. Bringing him in.
- Sweetheart?
- Jack!
- Oh!
- Oh, thank God you're OK!
- Oh, thank God.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. This nightmare's finally over, right?
- Yes. Yes, I promise.
OK.
Agent Bauer, the chopper's waiting for you.
My family's been through hell.
I want them to fly with me.
- That'll be fine. Come on.
- OK.
- Sweetheart, put this on.
Jack and his family were rescued.
They should be here in 10 minutes.
Good news. But we need to move fast on
something else. A lead from Jamey's mom.
- Where was the money from?
- An offshore bank account.
- We traced the funds to Belgrade.
- Belgrade?
Before I tell you,
upgrade the threat assessment on Palmer.
- You need to give me more than that...
- The same account shows a transfer of funds
to an assassin based in Belgrade.
That's old news. The photographer.
No. Our contact over there says
this assassin left Yugoslavia this morning.
Which means he's probably already here.
- A second hitter.
- Mm-hm.
Visiontext Subtitles: Yasmeen Khan
ENGLISH SDH