Right now, terrorists are plotting
to assassinate a presidential candidate.
My wife and daughter have been targeted.
And people that I work with
may be involved in both.
I'm FederalAgent Jack Bauer,
and today is the longest day ofmy life.
You and Sherry
were childhood sweethearts?
- That's right.
- There's never been anyone else?
I'm running for president. I can't answer that.
- Come on.
- Are you flirting with me, Patty?
I don't know. I think I might be.
- I did what you told me.
- And?
I think it's working. But it's gonna
lead to other things, Mrs Palmer.
- Teri, I'm busy. Nina can talk to you.
- You are not gonna let my husband die!
No one is gonna let Jack die.
We just can't go through with the trade.
There's no difference.
Without your help he doesn't have a chance.
I am willing to trade the life
ofJack Bauer for that ofmy son.
OK, we're here. Here's Alexis. Where's Jack?
Drop the weapon!
You son of a bitch!
If your people deliver my brother
as promised, you'll live.
- What about my daughter?
- You'll hear from us when this is over.
Yeah!
South ofthe platform there's a car.
Ifyou want to see Kim alive, talk to no one,
get into it, and head toward Century City.
Yeah.
- Proceed to Palmer's hotel.
- What do you want me to do?
When your government abducted my father,
they also froze $200 million of our assets.
Palmer has the necessary
clearance to unfreeze them.
So everything that happened today
was because of money?
I wouldn't say that. That money is ours.
We'll call Palmer
at this number at exactly 10.45.
Once I receive confirmation of the transfer,
I'll give you further instructions.
What kind of instructions?
- You want me to take out Palmer.
- Well, of course.
That's why we let you go.
That's why we have your daughter.
- Jack?
- I'm still here.
Remember, we'll call at exactly 10.45.
I trust I don't have to tell you what will
happen if Palmer doesn't answer.
- Hello, Patty.
- You left the party early.
I wasn't in the mood. What's up?
I was just wondering if you had a chance
to look at the Dallas schedule.
- It's fine.
- Good.
Um, do you need anything else from me?
Sit down.
A little while ago, we started down a road
that was gonna take us to a dangerous place.
I know. And I'm sorry.
Are you?
Sorry?
I'm attracted to you, Senator.
I always have been.
Meet me in 20 minutes in room 907.
I'll be waiting for you.
Oh, David, good. I...
I, uh... need to talk to you for a second.
- I'll just make those changes to the schedule.
- Thanks, Patty.
I, uh... told Keith and Nicole
that we're going to stump it separately
for the next couple of days.
What did they say?
- They know we're not getting along, David.
- Fine. What are they going to do?
They'll stay with me.
Unless, of course, you want them with you.
No. I could use a couple of days alone.
Great.
We gotta work under
a couple of assumptions here.
The only way to find Jack is through Drazen.
The only way to get to Drazen
is if Alexis takes us there.
So we gotta devote all of
our resources to finding Alexis.
- Yeah, but he shed the trackers.
- I know.
So we use the satellite
and run computer simulators.
- Yeah?
- George, it's me.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. Drazen let me go.
- But I can't come in yet.
- What do you mean?
George, listen. Tell Teri I'm out.
I know she's worried about me.
IfDrazen calls, don't tell him that we talked.
It'll put Kim in danger.
- Fine. But, Jack, let us help you.
- George, I gotta go.
I don't like the sound of that.
- What do you think he's doing?
- If Drazen let him go for a reason...
Jack won't let us help him,
he won't tell us what he's doing...
Whatever he's doing,
he's trying to protect Kim.
What's the one thing we know
for sure that Drazen wants?
Palmer dead.
Jane, connect me with the Palmer suite,
Secret Service.
What's happening?
- I can't stop the internal bleeding.
- Do not let him die!
Father...
Alexie!
Do something!
I'm sorry. There's nothing more I can do.
No. Leave us. We're family.
First Mother and Martina...
Now Alexis.
- And it's Bauer!
- Andre, not yet! We still need her!
- Call him. Let him hear her die!
- Andre!
Uh, could you wait for me, please?
Thanks.
- Well?
- He wants to see me.
- When?
- Tonight.
He didn't waste much time, huh?
How are you doing?
- I told you, I feel really uncomfortable...
- No, no, Patty, please. Don't patronise me.
You feel uncomfortable, but not because
you're ready to be with my husband.
You feel uncomfortable because you're
doing it with my knowledge and consent.
Why are you doing this, Mrs Palmer?
It's... It's important for David's career
that I have his full confidence.
And I no longer have that.
And you want me to get it?
Yes. And report back to me.
- We both know what it's going to...?
- Yes. We do.
- And you're OK with that?
- No, I never said I was OK with it.
But I'm willing to accept it...
because it's necessary.
Your elevator's waiting.
Just make sure that Palmer
has an extra layer of security.
- It's gonna be a little difficult...
- Yes, I know.
Nina, got a minute?
- Hold on.
- This is important.
Paul, we're done. OK. What?
The schematics to the detention facility
where they were holding Victor Drazen.
They've been tampered with.
- Who has access to these archives?
- Division and District.
Can you find out who's had access
to these in the last month?
- Yeah.
- Well, do it. The sooner the better.
- You think this is a second dirty agent?
- Yeah.
What did Tony want?
He was just telling me why it was
so hard to pick up a thread on Drazen.
Listen, I need your help.
Teri Bauer's a basket case.
- I don't know what you think I can do.
- You're good with her. You calm her down.
Come on! I gotta deal with Chapelle,
DOD's still trying to pass the buck...
All right.
She's in the conference room.
I know.
- Is it over? Did they make the trade?
- Jack's safe. He's no longer a hostage.
Is he on his way?
- We don't know where he is.
- What?
He called in to tell us he was OK,
but he didn't say anything else.
- Why not?
- Drazen wants him to do something else.
That doesn't make any sense.
Why would he do anything for that man?
- I think it's to protect Kim.
- What are you talking about?
Teri, the reason that Kim isn't back...
- Oh, no, no, no.
- Just listen to me.
We think that's where Jack is now.
He's trying to bring Kim back.
He's not communicating with us...
to protect her.
I'm sorry.
The task we have given your father
is a simple one.
And if he does it...
will you let me go?
We will see.
- Jack, I just got your message.
- Senator, I need to see you right away.
- Your office said you might be coming.
- I am coming there.
- Why?
- I have a message from Victor Drazen.
They also said that Drazen has your daughter,
and you could be a threat.
They've added to my security. Secret Service
has been instructed not to let you near me.
They do have my daughter, but I'm not
coming there to harm you in any way.
- What does Drazen want you to do?
- He wants to speak to you at 10.45.
It's a scrambled phone
so that it can't be traced.
- What does he want to talk about?
- Money. I'll explain when I get there.
Just tell your people to let me through.
Drazen's people, who are holding
your daughter hostage, want me dead.
You're asking a lot, Jack.
They had my wife and daughter today,
and I still managed to save your life.
I'm not coming there to harm you in any way.
I give you my word, sir.
Hi.
Anyone see you come up?
No, I was careful.
Why don't you sit down?
Well, how much time do we have?
Don't worry about that.
I have something I wanna tell you, Patty.
Yes?
You're fired.
Pack up. Get out.
And don't bother to ask me
or anyone else on my staff for a reference.
Prospective employers
won't like what I have to say.
- I don't understand.
- I know what you're doing.
You're working with my wife against me.
Senator, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to deceive you like this.
But your wife insisted
and I didn't know what to say.
- "No" would have done it.
- I know, I know. I should have.
- It's just that... she can be scary sometimes.
- So can I.
Obviously I have made a terrible mistake in
judgment, and if there's anything I can do...
I want you out of this hotel in 30 minutes.
You gotta take a look at this. These six people
have accessed the detention-facility archives.
The first five were just doing
scheduled backups. Here's the sixth.
George?
George is the mole?
It's possible. He accessed
that file four days ago.
Why would he have done that
if he wasn't involved?
- You gotta call Chapelle.
- No, shut down his network access.
You can't let anything go in or out.
OK. I just gotta figure out
how I'm gonna do it.
- Where were you?
- Downstairs.
- Downstairs?
- Yeah.
In room 907... with Patty.
What?
Save your energy, Sherry.
No need to act surprised.
I fired her.
You know your problem, David?
You think everyone's conspiring against you,
when in fact we're just trying to help.
By putting another woman in my bed?
Do you realise how sick that is?
Oh, come on. We chose a certain life,
and we chose that a long time ago.
It's not about a house in the suburbs
and PTA meetings.
And whether you're willing to accept it or not,
we serve a higher purpose.
You are not qualified
to talk about higher purposes.
- Oh, I'm not?
- No, you're not.
We are about to move into the White House.
That's right. We.
You and I.
And all the issues, all the politics,
all the hard work
that's gonna help get us there...
I'm as much a part of that as you.
So don't even try to deny it.
Please, Sherry... don't go there.
I'm not begrudging a single thing, David.
I don't need the limelight.
- You sent her to spy on me!
- That's right! And do you wanna know why?
- Yes, I do.
- Because you need me to look out for you.
And if you cut me out of your inner circle,
like you threatened earlier today, you will fail.
In every way.
You need me, David.
What?
- Jack Bauer just arrived, sir.
- I'll be out in a moment.
We're not done here.
- Jack.
- Senator.
Convincing Secret Service to let you
come up to see me was difficult enough.
- They won't let me out of their sight.
- That's fine. All that matters
is that you talk to Victor Drazen when he
calls, listen to his demands and cooperate.
How did they get your daughter?
Senator, we don't have much time.
He could call any second.
- OK, you said this was about money?
- Yes.
$200 million of his was frozen
after he was abducted.
- And?
- He wants it.
He says you have the clearance to get it back.
He'll give you instructions when he calls.
That's why he sent you?
To get me to release his funds?
Once he has confirmation of the transfer,
he'll ask me to take action against you.
- To kill me?
- Yes.
Of course, I would never do you any harm.
He has my daughter. I'm trying to buy time.
Jack, I don't have the authority to transfer
those funds, and Drazen knows that.
- What do you mean?
- He knows our system. That money's gone.
I don't think that's the reason he's calling.
Senator, please, answer this phone.
OK, Jack. I'll do what I can.
I'll tell him what he wants to hear.
- I can't guarantee he'll buy it.
- Thank you.
- This is David Palmer.
- Senator Palmer.
It must be nice being reunited
with your friend Jack Bauer.
What do you want?
Drazen? Drazen?
He knows you can't get the money. Senator...
No!
Are you all right, sir?
A detonation of this magnitude
had to be military plastique.
- Get a powder residue. We'll try and trace it.
- Yes, sir.
- Where is he? David!
- Ma'am, this area's not...
Let her through. It's OK. Calm down.
- Where's Keith and Nicole?
- At the party. Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
- Oh, God.
Senator.
This is Jack Bauer from CTU,
the man who saved my life twice today.
- Mrs Palmer.
- The man that put your life in danger?
- Sherry, please!
- Status report on the senator?
Don't answer that yet. Senator,
we need to talk about this. My daughter...
Tell them you don't know yet.
This is Ron.
We don't have a 20 on the senator yet.
What's going on?
The man that planned this explosion
needs to believe that it was a success.
Wait a minute. You mean, you want
the world to think that David is dead?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Absolutely not.
David, what's this all about?
His daughter is being held hostage.
But we can't have people thinking
David was assassinated. It's preposterous!
- If we don't, ma'am, my daughter will die.
- Then what do you suggest we do, Mr Bauer?
We keep the senator quarantined
for a few hours.
We leak a story to the press
that he was killed in the explosion.
- You've got to be kidding.
- I've never been more serious in my life.
- No, it's not gonna happen. David, tell him.
- This is about the life of an innocent girl.
David, we cannot keep playing games
with the public and expect to keep their trust.
Senator, if we're gonna do this,
we need to do this now.
Go downstairs. Bring the children up.
Talk to no one. I mean it.
I need all the agents
that have seen the senator.
- Who is your senior chief of staff?
- Mike Novick.
Bring in Mr Novick as well.
As soon as Mr Palmer's family gets here, no
one is to enter or exit this area. Understood?
Now, Sherry!
- I'm very sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
- Are you sure this is gonna work?
- It has to.
Hey, Almeida. What's going on
with my network access?
- What do you mean?
- I can't access archives or Palmer's itinerary.
- I'll call ITS.
- I don't have time for that. Are you up?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Let's see.
Yeah, here it is.
So Palmer's still going to Dallas tomorrow.
Call Secret Service and find out
what time his plane leaves.
- Division's got it covered. I don't think...
- Hey, real simple.
Call Secret Service.
Find out what time his plane leaves.
And get my network up and running.
- What happened?
- Well, he found out he's cut off.
And he seems overly interested in
what happens to Palmer after he leaves LA.
- We should alert Chapelle.
- No, not yet.
If we go to Chapelle without evidence,
he'll slice us up.
- What about his access?
- I'm gonna have to restore it.
All right, but monitor everything
and send it to me.
Put it up on all the monitors!
Everybody, eyes on monitors.
Events are unfolding by the minute
in this tragic and stunning development.
The hotel has been sealed off. Only a limited
number ofpersonnel are allowed inside.
We have heard from a spokesperson
from the Palmer camp,
who hasjust confirmed that Senator David
Palmer has been killed in an explosion.
There is speculation this is related
to this morning's assassination attempt,
but at this time no one has been arrested.
We did it, father. We did it.
Ah, yes.
All right. I'll take care of the girl,
then we can leave.
Do not do anything until we know
that Jack Bauer is dead. Do nothing.
Sir, we just contacted Mike Novick.
He's on his way.
Agent Bauer, it's for you.
Thank you.
- Yeah?
- You're a very lucky man, Mr Bauer.
I was calling to confirm your death,
but I see you've survived.
Andre.
I have an offer to make you.
You've killed Senator Palmer.
I'm the last person on your list.
I'll make you a trade: me for my daughter.
Come to Port of Los Angeles. Dock 11A.
What assurances do I have
that you'll let her go when I arrive?
Sadly, none. But we've decided the sins
of the father need not be visited upon her.
Port of Los Angeles. Dock 11A.
I'll be there in 30 minutes.
And, Jack, if you bring your colleagues
or involve them in any way, we'll know.
I understand.
I have to go alone.
- Good luck.
- Thank you, sir.
Why are you doing this to us?
Yeah, Jack, I can tell him,
but you should really let us help you on this.
No, I can't, notyet.
Give us a general position,
so we can be nearby.
No. IfDrazen's got someone else working
on the inside, it could put Kim in danger.
All right.
- Let me speak to Teri.
- OK.
It's Jack.
- Jack?
- How are you holdin' up?
- Where are you? Do you know about Kim?
- Yes. I'm on my way to pick her up. She's fine.
- Where is she?
- I can't say now, sweetheart.
But I promise you,
soon she's going to be with you.
Thank God. What do you mean "she"?
What about you?
- I'm sorry. I meant to say both of us.
- Oh, good.
I just don't think I can take much more of this.
I need you both here, Jack.
I know, sweetheart. Look, it's almost over.
Just hang in there, OK?
OK.
- Teri?
- What?
- I love you.
- I love you too, Jack.
Honey, um...
There's something I have to tell you.
- I've been waiting for the right time.
- What is it?
You're gonna be a father.
Again.
What are you saying, that you're pregnant?
Well, yes, that's generally how it works, Jack.
- Jack?
- I'm still here.
I'm sorry, it was the last thing
I thought you were gonna say.
Are you all right with this?
Are you happy about this?
Oh, yes. I am.
I keep thinking that... maybe it's the
second chance we've been talking about.
Are you there?
- Yeah, I'm still here.
- Are you happy about it?
Yes. Yes, I'm happy about it.
I'm very, very happy.
Good. Are you sure everything's OK?
Yeah.
Sweetheart... I promise you
everything is gonna be OK.
It's just been a really, really long day.
Just get on back here
so we can all go home, OK?
OK.
Teri... I love you so much.
I love you too, Jack. I'll see you soon.
I had a sister once.
She was full of life... like you.
She was a photographer
and took hundreds of pictures.
I used to love looking at them.
Now I can't do that any more.
You know how she died?
Has anyone told you?
Your father killed her.
- My father would never kill innocent people.
- You wanted to know.
- I don't believe you.
- Oh, he says it was an accident.
But when a man goes
halfway round the world to set off a bomb,
he's responsible for
any "accidents" that result.
Has your father ever talked about his work?
About where he goes...
on those long trips overseas?
Of course not.
- He can't.
- Because he's a criminal.
My father is a good man.
No.
He's not.
Palmer's still alive. The suite at his hotel
blew up, but apparently he got out unscathed.
- Why the reports?
- I haven't been debriefed,
but I guess it makes sense
as a defensive strategy.
Palmer's safe as long as
the hitters think he's dead.
This goes no further than the three of us until
the public's made aware that he survived.
- What about the perpetrators?
- It's unclear.
Our intel is being refreshed
by Secret Service as we speak.
So, stay at your stations. Start rebuilding
profiles based on the incoming information
and we'll have a new plan
in place within the hour.
Have you spoken to Jack
since the first time he called?
Not me.
It doesn't matter.
This'll all be over soon anyway.
- Have you talked to Jack?
- Yeah, he called, but he won't let us help him.
It's kind of cold.
Do you mind if I have some coffee?
Aaargh!
Stop right there, Kim! Don't move!
Don't be foolish! You'll drown!
Hey. Have you talked to anyone else
besides me since Jack called?
No. Why?
It's... nothing. I'm sorry. Are you OK?
- Yeah. Everything's fine.
- Good.
Nina...
The past is the past, and until today
you were mostly a voice on the phone for me.
But I want you to know
that I have nothing but respect for you.
Thank you.
And I think... all three of us owe you our lives.
Well, that's a bit of an overstatement, but...
Actually, no, it's kind of an understatement.
There's something else I want to tell you.
I'm pregnant.
You are?
Well, that's... that's wonderful.
Yeah, it is.
That's great.
It's great.
- Well, I...
- Sure. Go ahead.
How are we going to do this without the girl?
Bauer has no choice but to trust us.
Oh, there you are.
We just got some new intel from Langley.
- Oh, good.
- Yeah, take a look at this.
Visiontext Subtitles: David Van-Cauter
ENGLISH SDH