Season 3 Episode 1
The Jailhouse Job
30 seconds.
Call it.
Two feds, but five cameras,
overlapping 180s,
response time 15 seconds.
Cameras are watching
yesterday's footage.
Locking down... Which elevator?
What?
Yes, I'm a go for elevator one.
Were you asleep?
It's very peaceful up here.
Besides, I sleep better upside down.
- You okay?
- My papers!
It's all right. I got 'em.
Hey, you.
You!
You should have some signs up
or panels
- or something.
- I'll go. I'll go.
Incoming.
You could have just taken
the keys off the guy's belt.
This is faster.
What the hell?
Get in!
- What do you mean "No"?
- It's a horrible plan.
None of it times out, no way
you can get to the car that fast.
But you have to admit, it'd be
a lot more dramatically satisfying
if I'm the one driving
the getaway car.
You know they record these calls.
I created a carrier signal
for our conversation,
but I'm dumping another conversation
onto the prison recording system.
- Spanish soap opera.
- Yeah. Check it out, man.
Look, it turns out
pepe's twin brother Peppi
is actually
Guadalupe's baby's daddy.
He don't want to do it.
- But I love jumping on elevators.
- I know.
This is my special elevator rig
he got me for Christmas.
You took the fall for us, so...
- After you lied to us. He's a liar.
- You took the fall for us.
You went to jail
so we wouldn't have to.
We get that, so we're square.
But now you got to let us
get you out of prison.
- But if we're gonna do that...
- Not all of us are convinced we should.
We have to hit you
at your next hearing.
- That prison's escape-proof.
- Guys, no.
I committed a crime,
I got caught,
and now I am gonna serve my time.
What kind of world would it be
if everybody that committed
a silly little crime went to prison?
Complete madness.
Did you get the kielbasa?
There's an earbud inside it.
Now, listen to me,
in no way, shape, or form are you gonna
break me out of this prison. Understood?
Okay, you know what?
Fine, Nate.
We're still out here.
We're doing the job.
We help people nobody else helps.
That's important.
You want to stay around and miss out
just because you got to figure out your
guilty conscience, that's your loss.
Yeah, Hardison, I was...
Wait, Sophie...
- Just
- Who? Me?
I don't use the name "Sophie" anymore.
I use my real name now.
Your real... What is that?
You know that they record
these calls, don't you?
That's Nate Ford, Mr. Worth.
This the man you want?
Yes, we'll need
all his court and prison records,
visitor logs, everything.
This is a privately run prison.
Corporate facilities do not obey
the same rules as public prisons.
My employer wishes you
to understand,
this is not a request.
We will not be providing
warrants, paperwork,
or any other form.
Warden, you will give us
all your files on Nathan Ford,
or you will find yourself
and your company
under state, federal,
and international investigation.
I am not a warden.
I am CEO of National
Prison Properties.
I built this company, five prisons,
from the ground up.
Impressive.
You know what they say...
That Rome was not built
in a single day.
But it burned in one.
Seamus Heaney.
That Irish guy you asked for.
Excellent.
Thanks. Billy, right?
Thank you. This could
not have been easy to find.
You seemed pretty down.
And we got to stand up
for each other, right?
You're all right, Billy.
Wish the judge thought so.
Appreciate it.
I think something's happening.
Thanks for your input.
You can move on now.
Wait, wait.
Stop, okay.
You don't have to do this.
Get the knife.
Come on. Let's go.
What was that about, Billy?
Remember that '88 gangbanger
that got beat to death last month?
His buddy think I did it.
Did you?
No, I found the body, all right, but
the guards say nobody else was near him,
- so now I'm wanted for it.
- Here.
That doesn't make sense.
The warden should have put you
in protective custody.
Look, I don't even know
why I'm in prison.
You want to hear what I did?
I drove up to new Hampshire
to see my girlfriend, all right?
I had beer in the trunk.
I crossed state lines.
I didn't even know that was illegal.
- You expect me to believe that?
- I swear.
I didn't even have a lawyer
for the hearing.
They said it was just a fine.
I plead guilty. Next thing I know,
I'm in here for eight months!
I'm a frickin' accountant, man.
All right, you're an accountant.
Wait. What is that for?
- It's kielbasa.
- I know that,
but what are you doing with it?
Don't...
Come on, man!
That's nasty.
In your ear. That's great.
We extended our hand of forgiveness
and you slapped it away.
Now go away.
I'm having some "Me" Time.
Please, I just want you to check
the records of an inmate,
Billy Epping.
- Fast!
- Who are you talking to?
William Epping's conviction was for
transporting liquor across state lines,
but his sentence was way longer
anyone received for this crime since,
like the Pilgrims, man.
- Talkin' to a frickin' sausage.
- That's weird.
Your warden was consulted
on the sentencing.
That's hinky.
Why are you...
Now, listen to me,
we're gonna check this out, okay?
- Which I'm gonna do.
- All right.
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
Why don't you gather the team and get me
background checks on the warden?
- You stabbed me!
- Come on, just a little. It's fine.
Did you find us a client in prison?
Yes, we are going
to help Billy Epping
and maybe take down
a warden at the same time.
Stop!
Who the hell are you talking to?
I'm gonna pass out.
Yeah. Just... Yeah.
How did I get started?
Hedge funds, actually,
and then a bit of
international finance.
But then 10 years ago,
I hit on this...
National Prison Properties.
Get the government out
of the justice business.
- Mister...
- Barrington-Jones.
Brilliant.
Corporate-run prisons, five facilities,
thousands of inmates,
it's tremendous.
The US has the fastest growing
prison population in the world.
It's like the real-estate boom.
Except, of course,
the problem with real estate...
You eventually run out of land.
You never run out of people
to put in prison.
We haven't had much success with
the private prisons concept in England.
Our investment firm
has large real-estate holdings
for construction of facilities.
You see, any yahoo can lay some concrete
and throw up some razor wire.
The profit comes
in proper management.
For example, the big money for us
is in prison labor.
Sorry?
Goods and services
made by prisoners in America...
$2 billion a year.
One out of every five office chairs
and desks "Made in America":
Made by convicts.
And those jobs are not
going to the Chinese
Bottom's up.
- Is this really the best plan?
- The infirmary's under lockdown.
There's cameras
on both sides of the door,
extra guards because the pharmaceuticals.
It's the safest place in the prison.
Plus, I got you a little extra insurance
coming right now.
Abernathy, MD.
Here's my C13-A state
employment certification.
There's my processing forms,
the A76/4...
You worked prison clinic before?
Have I worked...
Sorry. If you'll look on this,
you can see my history right here.
Framingham, Concord.
Hell, my roommate at Tufts
drives a Benz
and fixes little girls' noses,
rich ones.
I got shanked by my own scalpel
last year in the neck.
- Already. Welcome to Rockford.
- Thank you.
The guard will stay.
Yo, Ford...
Clear out.
In one minute.
Billy, Dr. Abernathy.
I'm gonna be taking a look at you.
If you do exactly what I say,
I'm gonna get you home...
Alive, okay?
- Thanks.
- Okay.
- Ford, come on. Let's go.
- Yeah, just...
I need to talk to you.
Oh, God.
What did you do? Did you do
something? What happened?
- Your tooth? Your mouth?
- It's like shooting pain through my...
- Hold up. That's infected.
- It's just a shooting.
I can take you down to dental.
I can take care of this right now
and you give me one second.
We'll be right back.
- I have to go with you.
- You have to go with us? Come on.
Make sure you get your earplugs, because
I'm gonna be sawing through some bone,
and the "Zzz" is really loud.
And the burning flesh
and stuff, I'll try to have...
We can just... You know what?
It's fine. Just right in here, sir.
And please have a seat.
It's just in case
the guards come in.
Restraints.
Here's an infirmary manual.
That's for the guards, right?
To people that run
a con on their own team?
Almost get people killed
'cause they're out of control?
Are we okay, Eliot?
Adam worth IV.
Harvard business school.
Old money political dynasty
in this state.
His daddy was a Governor.
His uncle was an Attorney General,
and his brother is...
the Congressman.
Adam here even took a couple
of early runs at Office,
Couldn't get elected
as a dogcatcher.
That's why he got into business.
- Hardison's working him.
- First, we have to figure out
how to nail the warden
on whatever scam he's running here.
Secondly, we got to get Billy
out of here in case things go bad.
Told you this place is escape-proof.
21st-century prison,
fewer guards, more tech...
Infra-Red cameras,
motion sensors, lockdown doors.
Does Parker have any ideas?
She's working with...
Sophie.
- What was that?
- I didn't...
A little pause there.
Sophie told us her real name. I'm not
allowed to say it in front of you.
- Seriously?
- Her and Parker...
they're running the judge.
How can you possible think
that the Santa Clara case was...
- Excuse me.
- It's all right.
But it's absurd.
- No other case has...
- This is yours.
come so close to almost destroying
democracy as we know it.
Honestly, I don't even know what
they teach you in law school these days.
Key card and checkbook.
Keys and appointment book.
And this?
Safe deposit box key.
I love a secret.
Yes, this is Mrs. Melvoy.
I'm calling about my account.
Account number...
0018345.
Yes, I got a call
about my safe deposit box,
that a payment was do.
Billy Epping...
And more...
A lot more...
All sent to Rockford Correctional.
Two years ago,
Judge Melvoy got a safe deposit box
right around the time he started
sending people down for hard time.
And I'm talking citizens,
not people like us.
Judge Melvoy's not the only one.
Four judges opened safe deposit
boxes at the same time.
There are hundreds of cases here,
and these are just the ones
that we've found.
Records I pulled off
of Worth's computer
show that each time
an inmate checks in at Rockford,
their judge gets an e-mail.
Now, it looks coded. I'm thinking
Cayman Islands bank account.
Hardison, private prisons
have a contract with the State
just like any company
that provides a service.
Now, do they have to maintain
a head count?
See, Rockford can't drop
below 70% occupancy.
If they do,
they lose their state funding.
No state money, they close.
And they came
very close two years ago.
So, private prisons
are like the hotel business.
They live and die
on occupancy, head count.
Now, worth wasn't gonna lose
$100 million in profit
just 'cause he didn't have
enough hard-cases to fill the prison.
He puts a few judges on the arm
to send him non-violent offenders,
easy prisoners to supervise.
- But why these people?
- Because they're citizens.
'Cause they're honest,
middle-class citizens.
These are the people,
they don't want to cause any trouble.
They can't afford a lawyer,
if some judge sends them away.
Yes, sir.
They were taught to trust the courts.
They believe in the system.
What you got?
Worth makes money
sending innocent people to prison.
I have just the thing.
Lovely suit.
Thank you.
Hand-made.
Paris.
Gonna have to change that,
Mr. Worth.
You'll only be wearing
American from now on.
Here's my card.
- This doesn't happen every day.
- No, it does not.
You'll remember this day.
This is the day you became
a United States Senator.
It's busy.
It is an election year, Mr. Worth.
Which leads me to my little problem.
Senator Camp.
He's a lock for re-election.
He was.
So, Mr. Worth...
These...
are from my sources at the Globe.
They want to run
the story this week.
You remember what I showed you.
Just try some different shapes.
And that pout that we talked about.
No, not that one.
I didn't show her that.
Just open your mouth.
Kind of... Just relax.
Try one up, one down.
Maybe...
Yeah. Shoot that.
I like that. That's gonna work.
- Looks good.
- I can work with that.
Why am I looking away?
Senator happy pants
picked the worst possible
time to get caught.
The deadline for filing for
the next election is Friday.
This story leaks, he resigns,
I've got less than 72 hours
to find me a candidate.
I have considered running,
but I don't have any campaign people.
Adam Worth...
a self-made man
who's dedicated his life
to keeping criminals
away from our children.
Tough on crime.
Tough on spending.
Tough for you.
Sample polls have
you 15 points ahead
without even running a single ad.
Women aged 18-49
just eat you up with a spoon.
Want to see your campaign posters?
Worth's on the hook.
Now, I give to give it to you, Nate,
nobody can read a mark quite like you.
He tried to run twice and failed.
That had to have been eating away at him.
Now, find me a way
out of this place.
Billy showed me where he found
the first dead gang member.
- Blind spot... no cameras.
- Nice coincidence.
Yeah, and Hardison checked
the incident reports.
All of them happened
in camera blind spots...
Places convicts
wouldn't know existed.
- Guards.
- They killed him, accident, whatever,
they let Billy here find him,
wouldn't be the first time.
Can we use the blind spots?
I really want a back door
out of this place.
I can't access
those cameras from here.
They're dumb.
They run straight to the server.
They could have upgraded the motion
sensors and infrareds since these plans.
You're gonna have to map it out...
Old-school.
Lockdown bolt.
Motion sensor.
And heat sensor.
Nate, if you could see this,
you would not be encouraged.
Yeah, I see it.
I hope Sophie has more luck
with the warden.
Who's Sophie?
You remember, we're not supposed
to use her real name with...
Right, Nate hasn't earned it yet.
Forgot.
The average Senate Race in America
costs $8 million.
You can buy a senate seat cheaper
than a house on Beacon Hill.
The trick is to come out strong.
If you have, say,
a quarter million dollars
of your own money in a campaign
fund when you announce,
I promise you will clear the field
of all the other candidates.
I'm going to be a Senator.
If you're serious.
We already have a federally
approved account set up.
You just have to transfer
your funds into it.
- Let's do it.
- I knew you were the right choice.
And you'll be matching my funds.
Miss Lucas, I need to know
that we're partners in this.
A quarter million from me,
a quarter million from the party.
You put in your money first,
then I put mine in.
I need to know if your are serious.
Of course.
It'll be done this afternoon.
Just wait till you see our money
go into the account,
and then transfer your funds in.
Very good.
Sorry.
This is your office.
All right, we cut that wire.
Look, once a lockdown is called,
all these sensors go hot
and those door bolts drop into place.
I got it!
The furnace room.
There's no sensors
because it's too hot.
They crawl straight down
along the heating pipes
until they reach the sewage system.
Parker, it's a 150 degrees in there.
The average human can
withstand that for 27 seconds.
- What? Come on.
- Worth is on the hook,
but with $250,000 of ours
as a buy-in.
Did I say "Ours"?
I meant what's left
of your life savings.
We took it out of your account.
- Any luck here?
- No.
Got it.
"B" Corridor,
through to the kitchen,
into the freezer,
into the freezer air exchange,
into the machine tunnels,
which will lead me to the roof
or the parking lot.
You got to beat the lockdown door.
There's lots of pressure on that bolt.
- There's motion sensors in the kitchen.
- And infrared in the machine corridor.
All to get to the roof
or the parking lot,
where you'll be trapped
and probably brutally gunned down.
Got a way out of that?
I'm working on it.
My bank just called.
The state party put $250,000
into my leadership fund.
I just moved in my matching funds.
Congratulations, Senator.
That means I need
the entire operation cleaned up.
Squeaky clean.
Whatever your guards are doing
for side income, it stops.
- There's gonna be a lot of grumbling.
- Then fire them.
What's the use of being non-union
if I can't fire people?
- Are there any loose ends?
- The Epping kid.
If the state decides to investigate
that gang murder,
put him in front of a Grand Jury,
they're gonna like him.
The cover story could come apart.
This is what happens when you don't
take care of things yourself.
My guys were just supposed
to rough the gangbanger up.
- Things got out of hand.
- So, make sure this time, personally.
Tomorrow, turn off the cameras,
go in the infirmary,
and kill Epping.
Case closed.
No guns.
Make it look like a prison hit.
Kill the cameras.
Mr. Barrington-Jones...
Welcome back.
Thanks for seeing me again.
I fly out tonight, but my shareholders
have a few more questions.
Supervisor Worth.
Mr. Worth, thank you for your help.
I was thinking
you should take a close look
at Nate Ford's visitor logs...
Especially the video.
Would you excuse me
for just a moment?
Nate, the cameras just went down.
- Okay, where?
- The whole system.
They faked a reboot.
It's down for five minutes.
Eliot, get ready.
They're coming for Billy.
- Push in closer.
- Yes, sir.
Parker, please tell me
you're at Hardison's new van.
Yeah, it's really nice.
Did you bring it?
Wait, are we doing that now?
Yeah, we're gonna
breaking out right now.
Sophie, I need you to help
guide me through it.
We're on the count.
Nate, when they call "Lockdown,"
every door
in the prison seals tight.
How you doing?
Look at me. Look at me.
A little sloppy.
New glasses.
I am an accountant, okay?
Come on, come on. Go, go, go, go!
Lockdown!
Call lockdown!
Copy that.
Lockdown. We are in lockdown.
Lockdown in 5, 4, 3...
We're not gonna make it.
2, 1...
Lockdown.
Newspaper folded eight times
can support a ton of weight.
Come on.
First Boston Independent Bank.
- How can I help you?
- This is Adam Worth.
I want to close an account.
Move money out of it right now.
- Which account, sir?
- $250,000, the Worth Campaign Fund.
I'm sorry, sir,
for a transaction of that size,
you're gonna have to come
to the bank in person.
That was Worth.
I stalled him,
but he's on his way to the bank
as we speak.
Mr. Barrington-Jones, I have to go.
What is that alarm?
A lockdown.
Bellows, what's going on?
Here you go.
Billy Epping is on the run.
I think that Ford guy is in on it.
Look, I don't have time for this.
Call me tomorrow,
- and we'll reschedule, please.
- No, if we just...
Don't forget your dry-cleaning.
And 3, 2, 1.
- Go. Do what I told you.
- All right, Good luck.
Motion sensor.
- Nate.
- Steam's filling up now.
Motion sensor beat.
Breathe.
And heat sensor cleared.
Last stop.
No reports from any of the patrols.
Get me the cameras!
Exterior. Show me the roof.
No way.
We're still on lockdown.
I've got men in the ventilation system.
I've got K9 teams
working the exterior fence.
- What's happening at the bank?
- I don't know.
- This smells like a setup.
- Sir, you got here just in time.
Someone else attempted to close
this account out earlier today.
But I still have it, right?
All my money in the account?
Yes. And the rest?
There's still another $250,000
in the account.
Yes, all of it.
I'll take all of it.
There!
It's Ford and Epping together!
That vehicle is still out there?
Come on!
Epping.
Sorry, sir.
I say.
There was an escapee,
we're checking all the cars.
My name is Lester.
Lester Barrington-Jones.
I've had a meeting with your warden.
This is...
- my secretary.
- Fiona.
Secretary.
Sure.
Sir, I need you to clear out.
'cause we're busy here.
Of course. Of course.
- Let's go!
- You, yeah.
I like this.
I like when we pretend to kiss.
"Pretend"?
An escape?
I've got news Crews.
I have a Governor on my call sheet.
Every contact I have is in jeopardy.
Mr. Worth,
Detective Captain Bonanno.
Massachusetts State Police.
- I think we have a lead.
- Thank God.
If we catch them before the week-end,
maybe we get out of this in one piece.
We have security video of Nathan Ford
abandoning his getaway car.
Wait. I know that parking lot.
- That's my bank!
- Yeah.
Actually, that's your car.
Is there a good reason you drove away
from your prison
in the middle of an escape attempt?
- Well, I was...
- This is my favorite part.
- He stole my dry-cleaning.
- Yeah, and it fits him really nicely,
Which is odd,
because I've met Nate Ford,
And he's a good
four inches taller than you.
So, what, you just happened
to have a custom-made suit
in your back seat perfectly tailored
for your accomplice?
Don't forget your dry-cleaning.
"Accomplice"?
Now wait a minute.
Epping is his accomplice.
They escaped together.
You got two problems with that.
First, if you're referring
to William Epping,
he's still inside this prison.
And second, while Nate Ford
was changing clothes in your back seat,
you were inside the bank
clearing out your account.
Yeah, that's right,
the one he put a quarter million dollars
into for the bribe, remember?
Did I say "Ours"?
I meant what's left
of your life savings.
Yeah, we took it out
of your account.
Yes, all of it. I'll take all of it.
Yeah, the only thing
we found in your car...
was this list of state judges.
- That could be anything.
- I don't know.
Nathan Ford is a very bad man.
I think we better get some warrants
and talk to these judges.
They could be in trouble.
- Give me your hands. Let's go.
- Tell me, Mr. Worth,
what kind of guy makes money
letting guilty people out of prison.
Get him out of here.
Where do you think you're going?
What have you done to my apartment?
I'm the landlord, and this place
was vacant. We needed an office.
I got staggered flights on Air France.
Nate, I put you on a train to New York,
- then you fly out on Air Uruguay.
- What are you tal...
Your passport has you as Juan Ford,
coffee merchant.
Now, look,
we all rendez-vous in Paris and...
Buona sera, signore Ford.
- I would prefer wine.
- Good for you.
- How did you know that...
- Some third party was at play?
Come on,
the entire plan depended
on Worth finding out Sophie was bent.
He was supposed to panic.
We were about to tip him off,
- but...
- I called him first.
A guy with my rap
who stings corrupt millionaires.
Winds up in a private prison
run by a corrupt millionaire?
I mean, how long did it take you
to put that together,
this wasn't just a jailbreak, was it?
It was an audition.
You are as good as they say.
Possibly too good.
I need you to take down...
Damien Moreau.
Damien Moreau?
Are you out of your mind?
Nobody touches Moreau!
Moreau finances the Sicilians, the
Russian mafia, the Colombian cartels.
He moves money
for the North Koreans,
stolen artifacts for Iraq,
nuclear materials for Iran.
Moreau is the big bad.
He is the central bank
for international crime.
Nate, these files are CIA,
FBI, Mossad,
- Japanese Security.
- So...
Who is this woman?
You're not the police.
I'n not the police.
Moreau buys the police.
He buys politicians.
And no law enforcement
or intelligence agency
can touch him.
You have six months
to take down Damien Moreau.
She wants to hire us...
- to go after Moreau?
- Absolutely not.
Just wait a second.
This is not a job.
If you bring me Damien Moreau,
you can walk away.
And nobody will chase you.
And if I fail?
You can stay in my prison in Rome.
Thick walls a thousand years old.
And we still use chain
for such a bad man.
What about my team?
They lead dangerous lives.
Thieves die all the time.
Now that you should not have said.
I don't know.
You seem highly motivated.
She's blackmailing us?
She's sort of...
Sucks to be on the wrong side
of that, finally.
Right now, they have the leverage, what
we have to do is we have to get it back.
We can't go straight
at a guy like Moreau.
They'll vaporize us.
Right, so what we do is we do like
we've always done in the past,
is we do jobs that help people.
Only this time, some of them
are gonna lead us right to Moreau.
I do have a pretty big client
list waiting for us to check out.
We back in business.
How's that going for you?
This? Thanks for asking.
Yeah, it's good.
When I realize that I tried being
a drunk honest man,
a sober thief, so...
I'm gonna try being a drunk thief,
you know?
Try that for a little while.
You're not going to try to save me,
are you?
You're a thief now.
You can save yourself.
Whatever you say, Dominique.
Caroline.
Miriam.
Raquel.
I get it.