Report to an explosion
at the Bellbridge port authority.
Both homeland security and the FBI
assure us this is not a terrorist act.
Be on the lookout
for a black town car.
The suspects are considered
armed and dangerous.
Season 2 Episode 15
The Maltese Falcon Job
The mayor's a federal witness?
Federal?
Every badge in a hundred miles
is looking for us.
Guys, they are ripping through
Nate and Tara's cover stories.
All their financials are blown, so,
until I know what they know,
No credit cards,
no debit cards, no atms,
nothing that can be
traced back to us.
Cash in hand only.
- Better and better.
- The mayor's not innocent.
He cut a deal with the feds
because he's guilty.
he's got somebody working
on the outside.
- He admitted he has an accomplice.
- Do we scatter or stay?
No, we scatter, we give
the mayor and his partner
time to cover their tracks
to get away with murder, literally.
We can't get anything done out here.
We need a hiding place.
When I contacted
the FBI team leader,
I put a worm in the operating system
in the sim card on her phone...
Hardison, geek spiral.
We can listen to what they say.
Look.
No, not a safe house.
Interpol wants Culpepper
someplace off our system.
We're taking him
to the Governor Hotel.
That's where we're gonna hole up.
The Governor Hotel?
- The hotel crawling with FBI?
- FBI and interpol.
It's the one place in Boston
they won't be looking for us.
We just got to get there first.
Room service.
All right.
Three, maybe four empty rooms
on this floor.
I steal that master key, he's gonna
notice it's missing pretty fast.
All right, Parker,
I need you to do a lift.
- She just said...
- No, not the key.
Just a towel.
Excuse me.
I stepped out to get the paper,
and then my door closed behind me.
I tried to find a house phone,
but you guys don't have those anymore.
Did I miss something?
She was naked.
In-room checkout.
This means that I have access
to the hotel's billing computers.
It's a big old backdoor
into every hotel room in america.
As of right now,
we have been here for a week,
and our reservations are good
for another week.
Courtesy of this man's platinum card,
Mr. Ogden Shields,
who has spent a lot of time
in the adult section of pay-per-view.
- Did he even leave the room?
- "Indy panties day"?
Hardison, I need background
on all the mayor's business partners
and all his little shell companies.
You want background checks
on this, a TV?
Yeah, I'll have super mario
and dig dug get right on that.
Guns, anything having
to do with guns.
I'm gonna go get some keys made.
I'm going to the gym. Make sure
I can charge stuff on the room.
I got you.
She really wants that car clean.
That's enough of that.
- Excuse me.
- That's all right.
Hello.
- I was down in the gym.
- The fitness spa.
Isn't the zen steam garden divine?
Delicious. I was down in the gym,
and I went back up to my room,
- and my key didn't work.
- No problem. Do you have any ID?
Who carries their ID to the gym?
- True.
- Ogden Shields, room 1104.
Here you go, Mr. Shields.
Let me reformat that card for you.
Parker, Eliot, meet me outside.
Tara, Hardison, stay in your room.
- Door closed.
- Why?
Yes, like the machine gun,
not the engine.
You've been a very bad boy today.
No, I did everything I was supposed to.
Please, agent Nevins, tell him.
The mayor's been
a cooperating witness.
A snitch. World loves a snitch.
I will not have you talking
to my witness like that.
Before you finish that thought,
let's review, shall we?
You allowed multiple suspects
to escape from a warehouse
completely surrounded by FBI agents
before they got away with $250,000
of FBI bribe money.
And they got away in your car.
Sure he's safe here?
You want to tell me
why that's any of your business?
Because, during the course
of my first investigation for Interpol,
the city of Bellbridge
drifted into my vision.
Your little operation came up.
Imagine my surprise and delight
when I saw Nathan Ford
in the FBI case files.
Nathan?
No, his name's Lionel Gitt.
That's adorable. Tell you what.
I'll have my people give you
everything you need to know
about Nathan Ford and his crew,
and you give me everything you have
on a man named Tony Kadjic.
All right, guys, this is Tony Kadjic.
He started out as a smuggler in Albania.
He left a lot of competitors
in shallow graves.
He's been indicted
for murder eight times
in four different countries
with zero convictions.
His shipping company
looks semi-legit
and is tied to governments
in the 'stans, central america.
It's got big government contracts,
including some for US Security forces.
Why do we care about him?
'cause he's big on the
surplus-weapons market.
- A polite way of saying arms dealer.
- His specialty is buying cheap guns
from third-world countries
and reselling them.
This tracks. So, the mayor
grifts the 9/11 money
that's meant to improve
security at the ports.
That, along with crooked cops,
makes the Bellbridge port
a perfect place for Tony Kadjic to run
his guns in and out of the country.
Interpol must be chasing
down the gunrunning.
Don't worry about Sterling.
Did you just say don't
worry about Sterling?
Yeah, don't worry about Sterling.
What, you don't think
I can beat Sterling?
I think in the last six months,
I've heard you talk about
beating the triads,
beating the russians, all right?
Maggie's boyfriend?
How'd that work out?
We all said
that meet was a bad idea.
But you got a taste for taking down
this mayor, and you can't resist.
- You want to walk away, walk away.
- That's not my job.
My job is to get your back.
I'm gonna do it all the way down.
But I need you to do your job.
- And what's that?
- Be Nathan Ford.
Be the person we came back for.
Listen, guys.
I'm trying to figure out why a group
of very rich, very powerful men
are trying to take out
a good, decent cop.
Are you gonna stick with me on this?
Is that enough?
Us too.
Good. Tony Kadjic
is the one who pulled the trigger.
I want to know exactly
what he's up to and where he is.
And how do you propose we do that?
Let's go steal a mayor.
That's still bugging me, man.
You guys on the move?
- We're both heading out now.
- And the mayor?
According to the
room-service charges,
looks like the mayor's taking
the edge off of captivity
with many tiny bottles of vodka.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
But I have mini-bar.
Gimme.
Great. Look who's back.
This is Sterling. I'm on my way up.
Target secured.
You help Tara and Parker.
I'm gonna stall Sterling.
- How?
- I'm thinking.
Agent Nevins says
you're to have full access.
All right.
Your name's Bob, right?
Yes, sir.
- You've been here the whole time, Bob?
- Yes, sir.
And nobody's gone in
or out of here, Bob?
No, sir.
Then would you mind explaining
where the hell the mayor is!
Housekeeping.
Stop. I got this.
Stop. I don't need help.
Clearly you do.
I got this. I got this.
Go on.
Eliot Spencer.
There! That's it.
The trunk, the mayor's in the trunk.
Find it!
I'm running down the taxi license.
Have the state troopers
set up roadblocks
on every highway in
and out of the city.
You got it.
Thanks for making it
interesting, Nate.
Where's the luggage going?
Nashua, New Hampshire.
Just like the picture, make sure
it looks exactly like his room.
Your honor.
Chair.
Where are the agents?
There should be two FBI agents
standing at the door.
- Did you have to?
- She saw our faces.
Put her in the tub with the others.
Mr. Joshua, get to work.
We don't have much time.
- I'm sorry. Please, don't kill me.
- What did you think?
A guy that throws around the kind
of money I do, that I'm not connected?
I didn't know that...
That you could just
throw me to the feds?
Look, I had to.
It was nothing personal.
I had to protect...
What?
The guns.
The guns, the guns.
Look, I'll cut you in, okay?
It's a sweet deal.
The cops are in on the payroll.
And the feds just turn their heads.
- It's foolproof.
- How do the feds look the other way?
I wear a wire, okay?
I help the FBI get other mayors
and congressmen,
and they...
they don't bother
with Tony's shipping business.
So Tony said to give them you,
to give you to the feds,
and then the heat would be off.
Mr. Gitt, it was just business.
Just business.
I'd like to meet Tony.
I don't know where he is.
I'll get him on the phone.
I can get him on the phone for you.
If you'd like me to get him
on the phone, I can do that.
All right. He's here.
Where? Where is he?
He's down at the docks.
He's on the boat.
We just got a shipment in.
And we've got some buyers
who are inspecting the guns.
Thank you very much.
See, that wasn't so
difficult, was it?
FBI's cleared the building.
We kidnapped a mayor.
I hope you realize
that even if we pull this off,
we're gonna get out of the city
with nothing.
So, Kadjic has
a shipment at the docks.
Hardison, stash the mayor somewhere else
and see what you can dig up.
If I can access the security
cameras at the port,
maybe the facial recognition
can find Kadjic.
Do a physical sweep of the docks.
Where you going?
Where's he going?
This is Tara.
Listen, I need a favor.
I need you to get me
in touch with someone.
I want to make a deal...
with Tony Kadjic.
You're not like them.
You couldn't take the risk
that you'd never come back here...
Not without picking up a few things.
You're nicked.
- Where's my witness?
- Do you know why you screwed up, Nate?
You forgot who you are.
It was always only a matter of time
before this Robin Hood fantasy of yours
brought you here...
to this end.
You're gonna lecture me
on who the good guys and bad guys are?
The FBI's protecting a corrupt mayor,
and the guy you want, Tony Kadjic...
Giving him a free pass.
Is this true, agent Nevins?
As far as we can tell, Mr. Kadjic
hasn't broken any american laws.
And as a favor
to a protected witness,
we don't harass
his business associates.
- Kadjic shot up a state policeman.
- Do you have proof of that?
The mayor's brought us
a dozen good cases.
- I made the right call.
- Well, it's out of your hands now.
I have plenty of proof
against Tony Kadjic...
Shipping manifests,
forged customs documents...
And against you, Nate...
Photos of you setting the bribe
with the mayor,
tape of you talking about the bribe.
Photos of your team
in their adorable little costumes,
all sitting in a secure FBI locker,
awaiting my next
irrevocable phone call.
What are you waiting for?
The only thing I don't have
is Tony Kadjic himself.
That must be very disappointing.
So I'm gonna make you a deal.
You find Kadjic,
tie him to the guns...
I'll give you a free pass.
Just this once,
you get to walk away
with your record wiped clean.
My team?
They go down,
every last one of them.
They deserve to go down.
They're criminals, Nate...
Thieves.
So that's the deal.
You bring me Kadjic and the guns,
and I cut you and you alone loose.
Because at the end of the day,
you're always right.
You're not a thief.
This is your second chance.
This is hopeless.
And it smells.
- How many ships left on the list?
- On a hundred.
Sweet.
- This is hopeless.
- And it smells.
Yes, like old clown shoes.
- Briny despair.
- Well, maybe Hardison...
What?
He's italian.
Bonanno's italian.
So now he's walking off?
Sparky, slow down.
It's me.
I screwed up.
Nate, is that you?
I can't hear you.
Listen, I need you to come back.
I need you.
No, speak up. I'm traveling, and...
Not the team...
me.
For me,
not for a con.
Listen,
I don't know who I am
anymore, Sophie.
And when I was chasing you,
and we were doing cons,
I knew who I was, but not anymore.
As crazy as this sounds, I need you
to tell me when I'm going too far.
I mean, it just...
it gets out of control,
and I just don't know who I am,
and you've always been...
... my compass. And,
you know, I care about you
more than you'll ever know, because I...
I...
you...
I can't hear you!
What rubbish signal.
It's safe.
It's all clear in my apartment.
I want you to stash
the mayor in a closet
And get the team over here.
- You got a plan?
- Yes, I do...
One that's gonna take
care of everybody.
Is it possible?
I'll need Eliot
and to buy some new supplies
and maybe five hours.
Plus I need to hack into
the cargo-shipping system at the docks.
What about the money?
- It's on short notice, but...
- use my accounts.
- That'll clean you out.
- Use them.
And what about you guys on your end?
I don't think we can make it
in through the main entrance,
I think we need to go up and then
make it down through from the roof.
- But you can do it.
- Sure. That's impossible.
- No, it's everything else.
- Definitely that, but our part, no.
All right, I'm gonna
set up the meet with Kadjic.
I said I knew where the weapons were.
I don't know if Kadjic's gonna be there.
Well, then, we're gonna have
to lure Kadjic to the weapons.
I mean, the whole plan depends on our
ability to confirm Kadjic
and the weapons being in the same place
at the same time.
Everybody ready?
Yeah. But remember,
once you're on that ship,
all that metal's gonna
mess with reception.
I won't be able to reach you
once you're below decks.
Okay, we're all set.
How do you know which one?
Liberian registry, italian ship.
- Bonanno's italian.
- Exactly,
il falcone maltese.
- I'm sorry, you can't go through here.
- Where are you going?
I'm just taking my sister to the
insurance company on the 10th floor.
- All right, right through there.
- Thank you so much. Thank you.
Ding, dong, we're home.
Don't move!
Yeah, over here.
Hold it!
Stay right where you are.
Okay, okay, why don't you tell Tony
Kadjic that the guy he sold to the feds
Is here to have a
little chat with him?
What are you doing?
Counting all the guys with guns.
How many?
A lot.
So, no chance of just going in
and trusting the fake I.D.'s?
Don't worry. No one's ever died
going in through an air duct.
That's comforting.
In worst case, you slip and fall,
break your legs...
Lay there for days,
scratching on the metal.
It's like a long metal
coffin... with wind.
Let's go.
Now, you said you'd call Kadjic
if we asked nicely.
That's just what you're going to do.
But when you call, I need you
to be scared for your life.
Can you be scared, boyo?
Yes, I could... I could. I could
be scared. I could be scared.
Thank you very much. I will be with
you momentarily. Please, after you.
Follow this gentleman.
Look, man. We got Kadjic, all right?
Let's just call...
No, not enough.
We need Kadjic and the guns.
Well, mr. Gitt.
You know my name.
I think we're past
pretending otherwise?
What is this for?
It's an apology.
- What for?
- For what's about to happen.
Call Kadjic.
Hello?
Do whatever they say, please.
They killed my FBI handlers.
They murdered them!
And they cut them into pieces
and put them in a bathtub
into a hotel bathtub!
Is this true?
To be fair,
he did most of the cutting.
- Thank you. I appreciate that.
- You work hard.
That's what we do to
people who lie to us.
You just killed my partner.
You need new partners.
God!
You're lucky. I was
going to leave tonight.
Some of my buyers insist on
seeing my goods in person.
Still counting?
I'm still counting.
All right, Hardison, you're in.
Transferring the files
and wiping the originals.
And it looks like each case
Has an evidence box
associated with it.
All right, man. Make the call.
All right, we got
to get you topside.
- Just a moment, please.
- Yes.
Listen, can we speak in private?
Of course.
Gentlemen, it's okay. Thank you.
Go look ter the buyers.
So, you know, you had a
good run with the mayor,
but he was too small for you.
You know, the work I do with
the ball parks and the malls...
- That's where the action is.
- Money laundering?
You know, that's
it's a very small word.
I... listen.
Do you have any idea how
much dirty money you can hide
in a $30-million
government-financed boondoggle?
I don't just clean your money.
I put it to work,
In the land deals, in the construction,
in the concessions and everything.
Wherever there's a buck to be made,
I squeeze a quarter out of the take.
You know, most guys, you give them
dirty money and everything,
they give you back, hey, some of it.
But you give me dirty money,
I give it back to you clean.
- All of it?
- Of course, all of it, yeah, plus...
A bonus 10% on the top
for letting me use it on my end.
Case number 1435.
- Can I help you?
- Case 1435.
That's box K-46.
Nobody's allowed to take
anything from that case.
You need the approval of
your field officer... Nevins.
I'm not taking anything out. I'm
entering evidence in. Here's my form.
That's different.
Paperwork and everything?
You know, you could tell
Nevins when you see her
She's owed me 20 bucks
for so long, it's...
Why stay and talk to the evidence guy?
What's he got to say?
That's why I was so upset
when you kicked me over to the feds.
You should be using me.
You understand we have to
be careful now, you know?
We have interpol. We've had the local
state police, everything.
- How'd you deal with it?
- Well, you know, Interpol...
The FBI keeps them off our backs.
Or at least they did,
until you got rid of their informant.
And the state police, well,
I had handled myself.
Match identified.
Damn, you finally found
something, half-pint.
Security photo taken
6:30 A.M. Today.
Answer me, Parker, please.
Answer me.
Damn.
Call Kadjic!
Parker, where are you?
Sorry, had a buzz from the alarm system.
I couldn't hear a th...
What?
Parke, what's wrong?
Excuse me a second.
Hello?
I'm sorry. I can't hear.
Who is this? Who?
Find the other one.
Find him right away.
Bridge.
Take us out past the 12-mile mark.
We have to dump a few things.
I have him.
- What do we do with this one?
- You just kill him.
Now I guess I will show you how
I deal with people who lie to me.
You're really strong.
I hang from buildings
with my fingertips.
It's not what you think.
I was setting up a meeting.
Actually, that was exactly
what I was thinking.
Bye, now.
Not for myself.
No, Tony,
this won't do at all, will it?
Miss Kroy, this
is of no concern to you.
Thank you.
Well, it is my concern.
You really think I'm gonna do
business with someone who starts
blasting away in the middle
of a meeting, do you?
You don't even know
who this bloke works for.
I don't have a problem with
you taking care of this.
Just...
just wait till me
and the other buyers are off the ship
before you start getting messy
I don't want to be charged as an
accessory.
There's something
wrong with the engines.
Lock him up.
Take him away. Lock him up now!
Hurry! Get out of here!
Come on, move, move.
Miss Kroy,
I apologize.
Glad we understand each other.
I'll get the hatch.
Come on.
13.
Move it.
Come here.
12.
11.
10.
All she asked was that I report
back to her every now and then.
Are we sure this is the fastest way?
Look. There's no traffic this way.
You were spying on us.
I was not spying.
I was...
An early warning system.
Sophie just... she was worried
Nate might go off the rails.
If it ever looked like he was spinning
out of control, I was supposed to call
and let Sophie lay in a backup plan,
Just in case.
But why not us?
'cause you were too
likely to forgive him.
I suppose getting busted by the FBI
and trying to bring down arms dealers
while kidnapping a mayor
does qualify as out of control.
I used my contacts to get Sophie
set up as a buyer for the guns.
You know,
you actually had me worried for
a second that you were gonna drop me.
That is silly.
Just get us out of this harbor.
I can't.
Someone sabotaged All
the electronics in the engine system.
What the hell is going on here?
- It took you long enough.
- What?
Freeze
One.
What?
Where's Nate?
I don't know, man. All this
metal is messing with the signal.
Took you long enough. Come on.
Zero.
You came back.
Well...
You needed me.
Come on.
Can't leave a job half-finished.
I don't want any excuses, okay?
Please.
Oh, thank god.
What you doing here?
I don't know.
What?
What are you doing to me?
Oh, my god.
Good. Come on. Let's go.
You chose the wrong man, my friend!
Parker touching.
Kind of, yeah.
I hate to cut goodbyes short,
but they're playing my song.
Keep out of trouble.
Or if you want to get
in trouble again...
So we're...
We're even, absolutely.
You be all right on your own?
What do you think?
There's not that many
ways out of here.
Eliot, when I arrange a rescue,
I do it properly.
Nobody move!
Where is Tony Kadjic?
He's locked in the bridge,
and the guns are stored
in boxes in the hold.
I'm glad to see you kept
your end of the deal, mate.
We have a deal.
Nate, what are you doing?
Stop messing around.
30 seconds, there'll be
another dozen guns on the deck.
You have any idea
what's going on right now, Sterling?
There's a fire
in the FBI evidence room.
And Hardison wiped
the servers of all the evidence.
- Where are you going with this?
- I've destroyed all the evidence
The FBI has on Culpepper and Kadjic.
You have no photos, no tapes.
You don't have anything.
You don't have a case on anybody...
Unless you arrest me...
And only me.
I agree
to turn state's evidence.
And I testify to what Kadjic told me,
How he put the hit on Bonanno.
I'll even give you Bonanno's
evidence against the gunrunning.
I can take these guys.
It's just 10 more yards
to the chopper, man.
Listen, guys,
I got you into this mess.
This is the only way to get you out.
And I can feel you thinking,
Sterling, and don't... don't bother.
And if you touch one of them,
the deal is off.
Nevins loses two years of work,
And your first case with interpol...
you're my case, or I have no case.
Exactly.
- We'll call it a draw, then.
- No, we do not take this deal.
Take one more step,
I'll shoot you myself.
All teams, move in.
Target is in custody.
Come here.
You guys are the most honorable
people I have ever met
in my life.
You've become my family,
my only family.
I won't forget that.
Now get them on the chopper, please.
Now!
Let's go.
Let's go, man.
What?
Come here.
You call me,
You tell me you need me,
so you can do this?
Watch your back, Sterling.
Where is our aerial support?
He's bleeding.
Get an ambulance here.
Who the hell is this guy?
I don't know.
My name's Nate Ford.
And I am a thief.