Leverage S01 E03
Translated by
Harak Aladin
from Beni Mellal
in Morocco
DAD.
DAD, ARE YOU ALRIGHT?
GET THE HOURSE???
THAT'S TOO LATE.
YEAH.
Nine deads
ONE HORSE SURVIVED. Bultimore
with smoke in his legs
My family has been training horses since civil war
NEVER had anything like THIS.
But you didn't own any of those horses, right?
That's not how it works.
Trainers raise them and brake them. They don't own them.
It's rich man's game.
But i've always dreamed to have my own horses.
so when this wall-street guy came to town
Mr. Foss, he said that he wanted to start his own horse franchise
Mr. Ford, he offered me 10% ownership.
Real ownership.
i took the deal.
and six months later, the horses aren't running and Foss is liking
He burded nine horses Nate.
9 of them. To get his investment back.
And he's running round blaming me for the fire.
Bad enough I lost my stable.
No one will never hire me again. I'm non insurable.
yeah.
Well Foss is up for 2 million dollar insurance payout.
So we can get you piece
of that money.
I don't wanna damn Fosse's money.
wh-i'm sorry, wh-what is it , that you do want.
Their scream.
In the fire Mr. Ford the horses scream.
Foss only has one horse left alive.
Get Bultimore for me.
I'll take care of him.
That's all I want.
For that son of bitch they never
being in the horse business again.
Nothing more.
YOU CALLED HIM.
WE NEED HIM.
YEAH, NO, WE DON'T.
I FORGOT HOW MUCH I LIKE
THESE SOUTHERN WELCOMES.
EIGHT YEARS,
NO PHONE CALLS, NO LETTERS.
YOU DON'T EARN A HOMECOMING PARADE.
HOW'S YOUR HUSBAND, AIMEE?
GONE.
SEEMS I HAVE A WEAKNESS FOR MEN
WITH ONE FOOT OUT THE DOOR.
EXCUSE ME.
SO WHEN YOU SAID YOU KNEW THE FAMILY,
YOU MEANT YOU...
KNEW THE FAMILY, HUH?
PLEASE TELL ME YOU
WEREN'T ENGAGED TO HER.
NO.
I-I MAY HAVE GIVEN HER A PROMISE RING, OR...
- A WHAT?
- So that.
NO, NEVER MIND.
WELL, THERE'S NO WAY
WE'RE GONNA DO THIS
IF I HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT YOU BEING STUPID
BECAUSE YOU'RE TOO INVOLVED WITH...
I'M NOT INVOLVED.
I'M -- I WANT TO HELP WILLIE.
DID YOU HEAR THE GUY'S STORY?
SCOUT'S HONOR.
WRONG HAND.
ALAN FOSS, HEDGE-FUND MANAGER
FOR SMITH & MARKEN IN NEW YORK.
HE MADE $40 MILLION IN THE LAST TWO YEARS.
AND HE PICKED UP SOME PRETTY
HIGH-COST, HIGH-PROFILE HOBBIES.
STARTED WITH HIGH-STAKES POKER
AND NOW OWNING RACEHORSES.
I THINK I HAVE A FEVER.
CAN I BE EXCUSED FROM THIS ONE?
OH. COME HERE.
LET ME FEEL YOUR HEAD.
NO, DON'T -- DON'T FEEL HER.
WHY DO YOU -- WHAT -- WHAT'S THE DEAL?
W-WHAT we --
I ONCE SAW A HORSE KILL A CLOWN.
- Bobbie
- NO!
Camden,illinois
20 years ago.
NO! UGH! AAH! NO!
I GIVE ME MY MONEY!
AAH!
AAAH!
I JUST REALLY DON'T LIKE HORSES.
MOVING ON.
SIX MONTHS AGO,
FOSS POURED A PILE OF CASH INTO BUYING
ALL OF THE HORSES FROM WILLIE'S STABLE.
AFTER THE FIRE --
MASSACRE.
THE MASSACRE.
OOH. YOU ARE A BIT HOT ON THIS ONE.
O-OKAY. HOT. YES.
EVERYBODY, Y'ALL WANT TO
TAKE OVER THE BRIEFINGS?
OKAY, I-I GO TO A LOT OF TROUBLE
TO MAKE THESE THINGS INTERESTING --
HAVE A LITTLE SOMETHING VISUAL
FOR THE VISUAL LEARNERS
AND THE AUDITORY LEARNERS.
AND I-IT'S JUST INTERRUPTION --
HEY -- I.Y.S.
YOUR OLD INSURANCE COMPANY HOLDS
THE POLICY ON FOSS' HORSES.
IS THAT GONNA BE A PROBLEM?
NO, IF I CAN FIND A WAY TO STICK
IT TO MY OLD BOSSES, EVEN BETTER.
OUR MISSION IS TO TAKE
FOSS' LAST SURVIVING HORSE
AND DELIVER IT TO ELIOT'S FRIEND WILLIE.
MEET BALTIMORE.
THREE WINS, TWO PLACES.
INSURED FOR $200,000.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THAT CONCLUDES THIS BRIEFING.
APPRECIATE YOUR ATTENTION.
NOW, HOW TO WE GET THE DAMN HORSE?
WELL, WHAT DO WE KNOW
ABOUT FOSS' SCHEDULE?
ACCORDING TO HIS ONLINE CALENDAR,
HE'S GOING TO A BIG RACE AT
KENSINGTON RACETRACK THIS WEEKEND.
MISS DEVEREAUX...
...HOW IS YOUR "SOUTHERN BELLE"?
HOW Y'ALL DOING?
(Turf club, kensington racetrack)
- WELL, HI, THERE.
- how are you?
NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
HE'S GOT TRIP 3s.
OW, IF I WANTED A GLASS OF ICE,
I WOULD HAVE ORDERED THAT, OKAY?
SO TRY AGAIN. THANKS.
AND A BOURBON. STRAIGHT.
WOW. LIKE IT.
I LIKE WHEN A WOMAN KNOWS
HOW TO ORDER A DRINK.
KATHERINE-BETH LOVERY.
BUT YOU CAN CALL ME KITTY.
ALAN FOSS.
AND YOU CAN CALL ME WHATEVER YOU WANT.
SO, ARE YOU HERE FOR BUSINESS OR PLEASURE?
A LITTLE OF BOTH.
I'M A BLOODSTOCK AGENT.
YOU IN THE MARKET FOR A HORSE?
GOT ANYTHING FAST?
I DON'T DEAL WITH SPRINTERS.
NO, NO, NO.
I LIKE MINE TO FINISH THE MILE.
I-I'M SORRY. UM...
I DON'T REALLY RECOGNIZE THE LAST NAME.
WHAT OWNERS HAVE YOU WORKED WITH?
I BROKERED THE DEAL FOR
THE LAST TWO DERBY WINNERS.
IT'S GOOD FOR BUSINESS,
BUT I'M A LITTLE SHY OF PUBLICITY.
HE'S GOT A $50,000 LIMIT.
HE BET ON KENTUCKY THUNDER.
IN FACT, ONE OF THE HORSES
RACING TODAY WAS MY SALE.
KENTUCKY THUNDER.
YEAH. I HEAR HE'S A GREAT HORSE.
I HAVE A COUPLE OF THOUSAND
IN SPARE CHANGE ON HIM.
WELL, THAT IS MY KIND OF SPARE CHANGE.
AFTER THIS RACE,
YOU LET ME BUY YOU A DRINK.
SADLY, ON THIS OCCASION, I HAVE TO RUN.
SEE, I HOST A MONTHLY POKER
GAME HERE AT THE TRACK
FOR SOME OF MY HIGHER-END CLIENTS.
UH, I'D LIKE IN ON THAT GAME.
HE'S GOT $50,000.
IT'S AWFULLY HIGH-STAKES.
$50,000 BUY-IN.
YEAH, I'D LIKE IN.
EVENING, GENTLEMEN.
MR. FOSS, THIS IS OUR FRIEND,
SHEIK KHALID FROM DUBAI.
HIS DADDY DID BUSINESS WITH MY DADDY.
OIL FIRST, THEN HORSES.
PLEASURE'S MINE. GOOD LUCK.
THANK YOU.
AND THIS HERE'S BRAD MACKIE,
- I'm MACKIE.
- ONE OF THE BEST TRAINERS IN TOWN.
- ???
- OH, REALLY? REALLY?
WELL, THEN WHY DOESN'T
HE WORK FOR ME, THEN?
WELL, EVENING, LADIES.
DIDN'T HAVE TO WAIT FOR ME.
BECAUSE I WORK FOR HIM.
I'D HAVE CAUGHT UP.
BOB GIBSON. WHO ARE YOU?
BOB, THIS IS ALAN FOSS --
- THE INVESTOR FROM NEW YORK.
- OH, YEAH --
THE ONE WHOSE STABLE BURNED DOWN, RIGHT?
YOU'RE THE GUY WHO HAD THE
STABLE BURN DOWN ??
YEAH? WELL, I KNOW YOU'RE
NEW AROUND HERE AND EVERYTHING,
SO WHY DON'T I JUST
GIVE YOU A LITTLE TIP --
DON'T LET YOUR STABLE
BURN DOWN, THERE, BOSS.
BOSSY.
WHY DON'T WE PLAY SOME CARDS?
ACTUALLY, WHY DON'T YOU JUST
HOLD ON ONE SECOND, PLEASE.
DO YOU MIND IF I, UH...
ANYBODY MIND -- I GOT THIS
OUT OF A GIFT SHOP TODAY --
PLAY WITH A FRESH DECK?
THAT'S A ROOKIE MOVE,
BUT I DON'T MIND.
I DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THAT.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST HAND HER THE
DECK THERE, UH, FOSSIL...
YEAH SURE. FINE ??
SO WE CAN PLAY SOME CARDS,
AND YOU CAN LOSE SOME MONEY.
AHH.
ALL RIGHT.
UH, I'M $40,000 LIGHT.
BUT I'M SURE, UH,
THIS WILL JUST BE WORTH --
WE PLAY FOR CASH
OR WE PLAY FOR HORSES.
NOW, YOU STILL GOT ONE OF THOSE LEFT,
OR DID YOU LOSE THAT ONE, TOO?
CUTE.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO PUT IN
MY LAST HORSE -- BALTIMORE.
WITNESS IT.
THANKS, DARLING.
SEE? 'CAUSE THAT'S HOW WE DO
IT WHERE I'M FROM, HOSS.
YOU'RE BLUFFING.
THERE'S FOUR 9s.
GOOD?
DAMN. MM.
"C. U."
YOU'RE A CHEATING SON OF A BITCH!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
WHY DON'T YOU MAKE SURE
JERSEY BOY HERE GETS MY HORSE,
NUMBER 1, AND YOU --
WELL, YOU CAN COME BACK TO PLAY
WITH US ANYTIME YOU WANT.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT? THIS ISN'T BINDING,
- SO GOOD LUCK.
- OH, IT'S NOT BINDING, HUH?
- NO.
- YOU HAD FOUR 9s,
AND I HAD FOUR JACKS.
FOUR 9s, FOUR JACKS.
FOUR 9... FOUR JACKS, I BELIEVE,
IS BETTER THAN FOUR 9s.
I'LL TELL EVERYBODY FROM VEGAS TO HOUSTON
THAT ALAN FOSS WELCHES ON HIS BETS.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT? I'LL TELL 'EM.
PLEASURE DOING BUSINESS.
I OWE YOU ONE.
THANK YOU.
WE'RE DONE.
HELLO, NATE.
STERLING.
WHY ARE YOU PLAYING POKER
WITH MY CLIENT, NATE?
ALAN FOSS IS YOUR CLIENT. HUH.
THE FIRE, YOU'RE INVESTIGATING
THE STABLE FIRE FOR I.Y.S.,
YOU GOT MY OLD JOB.
ACTUALLY, I HAVE YOUR OLD OFFICE.
VERY ROOMY.
ALLOW ME TO REPHRASE.
WHY IS AN EX-INSURANCE
AGENT PLAYING POKER
WITH THE SUBJECT OF AN OPEN
INSURANCE INVESTIGATION?
OPEN INVESTIGATION?
LOCAL COPS THINK IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
LOCAL COPS DON'T HAVE TO WRITE
A CHECK FOR $2 MILLION.
IT'S MY JOB TO MAKE SURE THAT DOESN'T --
OH, NATE, THAT'S PATHETIC.
THIS IS ANOTHER ONE OF THOSE
COMPLICATED LITTLE GAMES
THAT YOU LIKE TO PLAY.
ALL RIGHT, SO, YOU'RE HUSTLING FOSS,
TRYING TO PROVE ARSON
OR GET HIM ON FRAUD --
WHATEVER, AS LONG AS THE COMPANY
DOESN'T HAVE TO WRITE THE CHECK.
YOU'RE TRYING TO GET YOUR OLD JOB BACK.
YOU KNOW, OKAY.
YOU HAVE IT ALL FIGURED OUT.
I'LL JUST BACK OFF FROM --
FROM NOW ON.
NO. IT'S TOO LATE FOR THAT.
TELL YOU THE TRUTH, THOUGH,
I'D KIND OF GIVEN UP ON FOSS.
I LIKE THE TRAINER FOR
THE FIRE -- WILLIE MARTIN.
WILLIE MARTIN'S AN INNOCENT MAN.
WE'RE INSURANCE MEN, NATE.
WE DON'T CARE ABOUT WHO'S GUILTY
OR WHO'S INNOCENT --
JUST WHO PAYS.
STERLING.
SOPHIE DEVEREAUX.
HAVEN'T SEEN YOU SINCE...WHAT WAS IT?
THAT LITTLE COUP IN SIERRA LEONE?
THIS IS GETTING VERY INTERESTING.
WE NEED A...
NEW PLAN.
IS IT TRUE STERLING SPENT THREE
DAYS IN THE TRUNK OF A CAR
- WAITING TO CATCH SOMEONE?
- NO. NO.
- IT WAS FIVE.
- WHAT?
LOOK, I'M NOT SAYING THAT HE'S
BETTER THAN YOU WERE BUT --
- "WERE"? I-I'M SORRY.
- WE NEED TO GET WILLIE
THAT HORSE BACK AND GET OUT OF HERE VERY,
- VERY QUICKLY.
- IT'S A LITTLE TOO LATE FOR THAT.
I MEAN, STERLING THINKS THAT I'M
TRYING TO GET MY JOB BACK, RIGHT?
HE DOESN'T CARE ABOUT THE CLAIM ANYMORE.
HE'S JUST GONNA MESS WITH ANYTHING I DO.
IF I TRY TO KEEP BALTIMORE FOR MYSELF,
HE'S GONNA TRY TO GET
BALTIMORE BACK FOR FOSS.
IF I GIVE WILLIE THE HORSE,
WILLIE BECOMES THE TARGET,
AND BELIVE ME, YOU DON'T WANT TO BE,
- YOU KNOW, THE TARGET OF STERLING.
- ???
GREAT. SO, WAIT, WAIT.
YOU'RE SAYINGWILLIE LOSES THE HORSE
AND FOSS STAYS IN BUSINESS?
- NICE.
- NO, NO, NO. LISTEN.
I THINK I KNOW A WAY
WE CAN TACKLE BOTH -- I THINK.
SOPHIE, TRY TO GET FOSS HERE.
AND YOU GUYS KEEP A TAB ON STERLING.
RUN INTERFERENCE.
ELIOT, FIND US A STABLE.
AIMEE GOT US THE HORSES.
WE NEED HER HELP TO PULL THIS OFF.
SO ALL OF THESE ARE MINE?
UH, WELL, NO.
TRAINERS WORK WITH
A LOT OF DIFFERENT OWNERS,
SO ONLY A FEW OF THEM WILL BE YOURS.
BUT THE STABLES BELONG
TO THE TRAINERS, NOT THE OWNERS.
SO HIS OFFICE WOULD BE RIGHT DOWN THERE.
YOU CAN'T EVEN SAY MY NAME NOW?
NO, SIRREE.
HMM.
UH, AND THE LOGOS?
LIKE SHE SAID --MY STABLE.
THESE STABLES ARE ALL IDENTICAL.
THE ONLY WAY TO TELL THEM
APART IS BY TRAINER LOGOS,
SO HARDISON FAKED A COUPLE
OF THEM UP THIS MORNING.
ANYTHING ELSE SO YOU NEED
SO YOU CAN WRAP THIS UP
AND GO BACK TO BEING A
SOMEWHAT DISAPPOINTING MEMORY?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WERE FINE WITH THIS.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID YOU WERE
COMING BACK IN A THREE WEEKS.
OH, BOY, THIS IS PERFECT.
WHERE THE HELL IS HE?
INCOMING.
AND...STERLING.
ELECTRONIC LOCKS, ELECTRONIC THROTTLE,
POWER STEERING, KEYLESS ENTRY...
UH, YOU KNOW WHAT RUNS ALL THAT?
COMPUTERS?
OH, YEAH.
HELLO? POLICE?
LISTEN, I'M AT THE RACETRACK.
YEAH, I JUST PASSED A BLACK VAN.
I CAN'T BE SURE,
BUT I THINK I HEARD
SCREAMING FROM INSIDE.
AND THERE AS BLOOD, LIKE,
ALL OVER THE BACK OF THE DOORS.
SURE, YEAH, THEY COULD HAVE HAD GUNS.
WHO KNOWS?
YEAH, A BLACK VAN.
YEAH, SURE. I'LL HOLD.
HE'S LIKE NATE.
EVIL NATE.
LET'S FLEE NOW, TALK LATER.
I SURE DO APPRECIATE YOU
COMING ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE.
HOW COULD YOU --
GIBSON.
GIBSON, LISTEN, WE NEED
TO TALK ABOUT MY HORSE.
AND HOW NICE HE LOOKS
IN HIS NEW HOME HERE.
HUH, IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE TAL-- WHOA.
YEAH, NOT AS NICEAS YOU, DARLIN'.
GOOD THING THERE'S NOT A RULE
ABOUT SHORT SKIRTS IN HORSE STABLES.
YEAH, LET'S GO TALK.
UH, YOU -- I DON'T REMEMBER YOUR
NAME, BUT I NEED YOUR OFFICE.
- I'm gonna ask...
- NO, TODAY. TODAY.
NOT -- NOT -- NOT --
NOT TOMORROW. TODAY.
ALL RIGHT, GO.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK. MY INSURANCE
GUY'S A REAL PRICK.
HE SAYS UNTIL THE CLAIM CLEARS,
I CAN'T SELL THAT LAST HORSE.
YEAH, WELL, OF COURSE HE DID.
ALL RIGHT,??
UM. I WOULD LIKE TO BUY
BALTIMORE BACK, PLEASE.
OKAY, SO HERE'S $40,000.
NO, THE PRICE WENT UP.
IT'S $2 MILLION.
WHAT -- EX-- SAY WHAT?
I GOT THIS BIG DEAL COMING UP,
DON'T I, DARLIN'?
AND I COULD USE THE LIQUID CASH.
2 MILLION BUCKS.
YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU'RE RIDICULOUS.
YOU'RE A JOKE.
WELL, THAT'S THE WAY WE PLAY
WHERE I COME FROM.
LISTEN. WHY DON'T YOU AND I --
WHY DON'T WE GO TALK ABOUT HOW
MUCH MONEY YOU'RE GONNA MAKE ME.
AND YOU -- WHY DON'T YOU
CALL ME WHEN YOU'RE SERIOUS.
COME ON, THERE, KITTY.
OH, YOU'RE JUST GONNA GO WITH --
'CAUSE, YEAH, HE'S -- HE'S --
HE'S A REAL CHARMER.
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
I'M SORRY.
I'VE JUST SEEN THAT LOOK BEFORE.
THAT'S A BOB GIBSON SPECIAL.
WHAT, ARE YOU SERIOUS?! HOW
DO YOU EVEN PUT UP WITH THAT?
HE'S A LITTLE WORSE THIS WEEK
'CAUSE HE'S GOT THIS DEAL,
AND HE, UH...
ANYWAY, I'M SORRY HE DIDN'T
SELL YOU YOUR HORSE BACK.
AND WHAT IS THIS DEAL WITH KITTY?
W--
I CAN'T HELP YOU WITH THAT, MR. FOSS.
SEE, THIS INDUSTRY IS CHANGING.
YEP. WASTED MY TIME
WITH THAT PENNY-ANTE CRAP.
CHEAP HORSES, LOW-RENT TRAINERS, OKAY.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT I DID, THOUGH?
I CALLED MY HEDGE-FUND BUDDIES UP.
AND WE'RE GONNA FORM
INVESTMENT PORTFOLIOS,
ONLY WITH HORSES AND NOT STOCKS.
MODERNIZE THE SPORT
SO GUYS LIKE BOB GIBSON
WON'T KNOW WHAT HIT THEM WHEN
NEW YORK MONEY COMES TO TOWN.
SO YOU DO ME A FAVOR.
HERE'S HOW I CAN HELP YOU.
YOU EITHER JOIN THE REVOLUTION
OR YOU GET THE HELL OUT OF MY WAY.
SEE YA.
GREAT NEWS.
NOT ONLY IS FOSS NOT
OUT OF THE HORSE BUSINESS,
HE'S BRINGING IN MORE
MONEY AND MORE PARTNERS.
CAUGHT THAT. WORKING ON IT.
YOU'RE WORKING ON IT?
YOU SAID THAT YOU HAD A PLAN.
HE JUST SAID HE'S WORKING ON IT.
RIGHT, BUT YOU CONVINCED MY DAD
THAT THINGS WERE GONNA BE OKAY.
THINGS HAVE ONLY GOTTEN WORSE.
NOW, I-I APPRECIATE YOU TRYING TO HELP,
BUT IF YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE DOING, JUST WALK AWAY.
AT LEAST I KNOW YOU'RE GOOD AT THAT.
CAN'T LET IT GO, CAN YOU?
CAN'T LET IT BE THE PAST.
NO, I WAS FINE UNTIL THE LONG-LOST
HERO CAME BACK INTO TOWN.
- YOUR DAD CALLED ME.
- YOU COULD HAVE SAID NO.
WHEN DID I BECOME THE BAD GUY, HUH?
- I LEFT BECAUSE YOU GOT MARRIED.
- OH, YEAH,
AND THE FIRST 15 TIMES YOU LEFT?
I CAME BACK, ALL RIGHT?
- YOU'RE THE ONE THAT MOVED ON.
- NO PHONE CALLS.
NO LETTERS -- NOTHING!
ELIOT, WHAT KIND OF A PERSON DOES THAT?
WHAT -- WHAT REASONABLE
JUSTIFICATION COULD YOU HAVE
FOR JUST DROPPING OFF THE PLANET, HUH?
Tell us what you did with the monkey!
Where is it? Where is the monkey?!
I WAS WORKING.
NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
HEY, JUST LISTEN TO ME JUST FOR A --
- OH, DON'T START WITH YOUR STUFF.
- OH, DON'T.
YOU KNOW YOU CAN'T GET OUT OF THIS.
STOP.
COME HERE.
WHAT ABOUT THAT THING
YOU DID IN -- IN KAZAKHSTAN?
NO, STERLING KNOWS ABOUT THAT ONE.
AND YOU'RE SURE THIS ISN'T ABOUT
STICKING IT TO YOUR OLD RIVAL?
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
IT'S REALLY NOT WORTH PUTTING
THE REST OF US AT RISK.
NO, LISTEN, YOU KNOW,
STERLING IS GONNA DO
EVERYTHING IN HIS POWER
TO TAKE US DOWN, ALL RIGHT?
AND HE'S GONNA TAKE WILLIE WITH HIM.
SO I-I'M JUST TRYING
TO COME UP WITH SOME PLAN
THAT HE DOESN'T SEE A MILE AWAY
- WITH A BLINDFOLD ON.
- SAME THING WITH A ZEBRA.
- THEY BITE AND THEY NEVER LET GO.
- NO, NO, NO, NO.
- ???IN THE JUNGLE
- HOLD UP. WAIT, WAIT.
WHAT ABOUT MISTER ED?
YEAH, A TALKING ANIMAL
THAT NOBODY ELSE CAN HEAR?
THAT NEVER ENDS BADLY.
IT DIDN'T TURN OUT BADLY.
WILBUR LOVED MISTER ED.
HE LOVED HIM LIKE A
SECOND COUSIN TWICE REMOVED.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S IT. THAT'S IT.
WHAT? A TALKING HORSE?
NO. THE LOST HEIR.
WHAT'S THAT?
CLASSIC EUROPEAN SCAM.
YOU POSE AS A LONG-LOST
DESCENDANT OF THE ROYAL FAMILY.
AND WHEN YOU PULL IT OFF, WELL,
THE PAYOFFS ARE REALLY GOOD --
LOADS OF PARTIES, MONEY,
AND...A FABULOUS FABERGE EGG.
WHAT DOES THAT HAVE TO DO WITH HORSES?
WELL, WITH HORSES,
IT'S ALL ABOUT BLOODLINES.
THE LOST HEIR OF THE
ROYAL EQUINE FAMILY...
IS GONNA BE WORTH MILLIONS.
WE ARE GONNA SELL THIS GUY THE
GREATEST HORSE THAT NEVER LIVED.
GO AHEAD. I KNOW YOU'RE
ITCHING TO SAY SOMETHING.
I LIKE AIMEE.
I DO. I MEAN IT. I LIKE YOU BOTH.
I JUST -- YOU KNOW,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT COMES OF
CHASING THE PAST, YOU KNOW, ELIOT?
YEAH, WELL, SOPHIE, SWEETIE,
I DON'T THINK YOU AND NATE GET
TO SERVE ME THAT PARTICULAR MEAL.
OUCH.
WE'RE USING BALTIMORE AS THE LOST HEIR.
I HACKED INTO THE IFHA WEBSITE.
THAT'S THE DATABASE WITH
ALL THE HORSES' BLOODLINES.
NOW, ALL THAT INFORMATION
IS LINKED ON NUMBERS
TO MICROCHIPS IN THE HORSE'S NECK.
NOW, WE'LL LINK
BALTIMORE'S MICROCHIP NUMBER
TO A FAKE HORSE WITH A GREAT BLOODLINE.
THEN WE'LL DISGUISE THE
WHITE STRIPE ON HIS FACE
- WITH SOME PAINT.
- NO, NO. IT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
HIS LUNGS ARE STILL
MESSED UP FROM THE FIRE.
WELL, HE CAN STILL RUN.
HE CAN RUN, BUT FOSS
IS GONNA SEE HOW SLOW HE IS.
THAT PAINT THING --
THAT'S NOT GONNA HOLD UP
IF HE GETS CLOSE ENOUGH TO SCAN THE CHIP.
UH...
AHH.
WELL, WE NEED TO FIND A HORSE
THAT CAN RUN LIKE A CHAMPION.
WHAT ABOUT THAT HORSE FROM THE OTHER DAY?
KENTUCKY FRIED CHICKEN?
KENTUCKY THUNDER?
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
OH, WE STEAL AN ACTUAL
CHAMPIONSHIP RACEHORSE
IN ORDER TO FAKE ANOTHER
CHAMPIONSHIP RACEHORSE.
OOH, I LIKE IT.
WHOO-HOO, TODD? LINA WATTERS.
TODD HAZEN, RIGHT?
KENTUCKY THUNDER'S TRAINER?
YES. CAN I HELP YOU WITH SOMETHING?
GREAT. WELL, WE'RE ALL SET.
SET?
WELL, YOU ARE READY FOR
THE INTERVIEW, AREN'T YOU?
EXCUSE ME?
WELL, MY OFFICE HAS
BEEN CALLING YOU ALL DAY.
I'VE SET UP AN INTERVIEW
WITH SPORTS ILLUSTRATED.
A COUPLE YEARS AGO,
ALL THE CELLPHONE COMPANIES WENT
DIGITAL WITH THEIR VOICEMAIL SYSTEMS.
MAN, IT WAS LIKE SOMEBODY PUT A
BRAND-NEW SWING SET ON MY PLAYGROUND.
DAMN IT.
LIKE I SAID, BEEN CALLING YOU ALL DAY.
I HEARD YOU, MA'AM.
SO, LISTEN, THE REPORTER'S GONNA
BE AT THE TURF CLUB ANY SECOND NOW.
I HEAR YOU.
THANK YOU.
UM, LISTEN, IF HE'S NOT THERE,
PLEASE WAIT FOR HIM FOR HALF AN HOUR.
MAYBE AN HOUR...OR TWO.
HAVE A SNACK.
Good afternoon.
ANY SIGN OF STERLING?
NO. ALL CLEAR.
PARKER?
NOPE.
WHAT ABOUT THESE GUYS?
ANY TROUBLE GETTING THEM HERE?
Airport- Earlier that Day.
WELL, THE LITTLE ONE HAS
A BLADDER THE SIZE OF PEANUT.
SHE HAD TO GO TO THE BATHROOM
THREE TIMES ON THE WAY HERE
AND ONCE WHEN WE GOT HERE.
YOU EVER HEAR OF THE BEIJING JOCKEY CLUB?
YEAH, FLEW OUT THERE A FEW YEARS
BACK WITH A COUPLE OF BUDDIES.
WE MET WITH THE FOUNDER, J.P. CHANG.
HE, UH, WAS TRYING TO START
THIS HORSE HEDGE FUND.
- RIGHT IDEA, WRONG INVESTMENT.
- YEP. IMPORTED 600 HORSES.
ALL THE BEST BLOODLINES IN THE WORLD.
YEAH, FOR ALL THE GOOD THAT DID THEM.
COMMUNIST GOVERNMENT
CRACKS DOWN A YEAR LATER,
KILLS EVERY SINGLE HORSE.
600 THOROUGHBRED RACEHORSES DEAD,
AND NOBODY MAKES ONE CENT
ON THE INSURANCE PAYOUTS.
THAT IS THE REAL TRAGEDY, MY FRIEND.
THEY DIDN'T KILL 600 HORSES.
THEY KILLED 599.
WHAT?
THAT'S THE SURVIVING HORSE.
Come on.
THAT TIME BEATS EVERY DERBY
WINNER IN THE LAST DECADE.
HIS NAME'S FEI KUAI,
BORN SEPTEMBER 15th.
THAT'S A MONTH BEFORE
THE OTHERS WERE KILLED.
THOSE ARE THE ORIGINAL OWNERS.
THEY'RE TRYING TO UNLOAD HIM
BEFORE THE GOVERNMENT FINDS HIM.
WAIT, ARE THEY TRYING
TO SELL IT TO GIBSON?
FOR A FRACTION OF WHAT HE'S WORTH.
NO, NO WAY. NOT HAPPENING.
CAN YOU GET INTERNET
ON YOUR PHONE, MR. FOSS?
YES.
PULL UP THE IFHA WEBSITE.
I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
EVERY THOROUGHBRED WORLDWIDE HAS
THEIR BLOODLINES REGISTERED THERE.
PUNCH IN THAT NUMBER RIGHT THERE.
THAT'LL GIVE YOU THE
BLOODLINES OF THIS HORSE.
8-9-9-3-3.
NATIVE DANCER, WAR ADMIRAL, SECRETARIAT.
YOU GOT TO BE --
THIS HORSE IS A KENNEDY.
YEAH, IF YOU'RE GONNA START
A FRANCHISE, MR. FOSS,
THIS IS THE HORSE YOU NEED.
WHAT DID WE FIND OUT
ABOUT HIS INVESTMENT GROUP?
SIX INVESTORS.
THEY EACH MATCHED FOSS'
$2 MILLION SEED MONEY.
THEY PUT FOSS IN CHARGE.
ALL RIGHT, SOPHIE, GET IN THERE.
HE'S GOT $12 MILLION
WITH YOUR NAME ON IT.
MR. FOSS, HOW NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
- BRAD.
- MISS KATHERINE.
PARDON US, BUT WE NEED TO GET
THIS HORSE BACK TO HIS STABLE NOW.
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE, KITTY CAT.
I WANT TO BUY YOUR HORSE.
WHATEVER GIBSON OFFERED YOU,
I WANT TO GIVE YOU MORE.
I'M SORRY TO DISAPPOINT YOU,
BUT MR. GIBSON OFFERED THEM $11 MILLION.
GREAT. $12 MILLION BY TOMORROW.
This nice man also welcomes you. He likes your shirt.
Do you remember where you bought it?
I think it was a gift.
IF YOU HAVE THE MONEY BY
TOMORROW, THE HORSE IS YOURS.
YES! SLAP IT. SLAP IT.
OF COURSE.
IN THE CHINESE CULTURE,
IT IS CUSTOMARY TO TAKE A PICTURE
TOGETHER WHEN YOU TRANSFER A PROPERTY.
WHAT ARE YOU KID-- HELL, YEAH.
COME ON. LET'S DO IT RIGHT NOW.
TAKE IT.
LET'S DO IT.
SMILE.
YOU GOT TO GO AGAIN?
OF COURSE YOU DO.
IT'S RIGHT ON IN THERE,
RIGHT AROUND THE CORNER.
- GO ON. GO ON AHEAD.
- ok???
Hello. I have your camera.
Did you get some nice pictures?
I think so.
I have to go.
YOU KNOW, I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT AT FIRST.
STERLING, WELCOME.
BUT, THEN AGAIN, YOU DID DRINK
YOURSELF RIGHT OUT OF A JOB.
LOST YOUR HOUSE, YOUR WIFE.
PLENTY OF MONEY TROUBLES.
KEEP TALKING.
YOU'LL GET TO THE POINT EVENTUALLY.
YOU CROSSED THE LINE.
NATHAN FORD IS A COMMON CRIMINAL.
OH. "COMMON"?
WELL, THAT'S JUST HURTFUL.
I SPOKE TO MY CLIENT TONIGHT.
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT I TOLD HIM?
I DON'T THINK YOU TOLD HIM ANYTHING.
'CAUSE IF YOU HAD PROOF
THAT FOSS STARTED THE FIRE,
YOU'D BE GONE ALREADY.
I DON'T THINK YOU'D RISK
A $2 MILLION PAYOUT
JUST TO STICK IT TO ME.
NO, I THINK YOU PROBABLY
DID WHAT YOU ALWAYS DO.
YOU GAVE YOUR CLIENT JUST ENOUGH ROPE,
JUST ENOUGH TO HANG HIMSELF.
AM I RIGHT?
THIS TIME, NATE...
I THINK THERE'S JUST ENOUGH ROPE FOR TWO.
THERE'S NO WAY TO FAKE
THE NUMBERS ON THAT CHIP.
YOU FAKED IT BEFORE.
NO, NO, NO. I FAKED THE
INFORMATION ON THE DATABASE.
OKAY, NOW, WHEN FOSS SCANS THAT CHIP,
IF IT'S NOT THE SAME NUMBER
THAT SHOWED UP BEFORE --
OH, WE'RE SCREWED.
BASICALLY.
NOW, EITHER WE CUT
THE CHIP OUT OF THE HORSE
AND INSERT IT INTO ANOTHER ONE --
OR WE DELIVER KENTUCKY THUNDER.
NO, WE'RE NOT A LIBRARY.
WE CAN'T JUST TAKE HORSES
IN AND OUT AS WE LIKE.
KENTUCKY THUNDER'S GONE.
WHAT?
RACING?
WORSE. STUD FARM.
- OH.
- NO, NO.NO, NO, NO.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE NOT GONNA GET
FOSS TO WRITE A $12 MILLION CHECK
FOR AN EMPTY HORSE TRAILER.
THIS DOESN'T WORK
WITHOUT KENTUCKY THUNDER.
SO WE'RE GONNA STALL.
NO.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, NO?
STERLING'S GONNA CATCH ON.
FOSS IS GONNA GET COLD FEET, MAN.
NO. WE HAVE A CHANCE.
WE GOT TO GET THIS HORSE.
OK, LISTEN. I AM NOT GONNA
JEOPARDIZE THE REST OF THE TEAM
BECAUSE YOU HAVE SOMETHING TO
PROVE TO YOUR HIGH-SCHOOL SWEETHEART.
IT'S JUST NOT GONNA HAPPEN
OH, AND YOU'RE NOT TRYING
TO PROVE SOMETHING TO STERLING?
YOU'RE NOT TRYING TO PROVE
SOMETHING TO THE WORLD
EVERY TIME WE HELP SOMEBODY OUT?
WE'RE ALL TRYING TO PROVE SOMETHING,
JUST BEING HERE WITH YOU.
IF IT GETS TOO CLOSE,
I WILL PULL THE PLUG
AND YOU AND YOU WILL WALK AWAY.
AND THAT WILL BE THAT.
AND YOU -- WHO DO YOU HAVE
SOMEONE TO PROVE TO?
MYSELF...
YOU ARROGANT SON OF A BITCH.
CAN YOU HACK IT?
HACK A LOCK?
NICE.
YOU STILL REALLY DON'T
UNDERSTAND WHAT I DO, DO YOU?
PARKER, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
GO IN THROUGH THE AIR DUCT,
DROP DOWN, AND LET US IN.
BUT THE HORSES ARE IN THERE.
NO, NO, NO. THERE'S A BACK ROOM.
- THERE WON'T BE ANY HORSES IN THERE.
- WE NEED YOU TO DO THIS.
I NEED YOU TO DO THIS.
PLEASE.
LOOKS LIKE PARKER'S GONNA HAVE TO
CRAWL THROUGH THE AIR DUCT AGAIN.
GOD FORBID ANYONE ELSE WOULD LEARN
HOW TO FREAKIN' CRAWL ON THEIR
STOMACH THROUGH A TINY SPACE.
IT'S NOT ROCKET SCIENCE, PEOPLE.
Parker, you realize that
we can still hear you.
AIMEE... I'VE FOUND KENTUCKY THUNDER.
- He's a really, really big horse.
- OH, I'M SO SORRY.
UH, YEAH, SOMETIMES THEY KEEP HIM
IN THERE BEFORE HE GETS TEASED.
I DON'T WANT TO BE
IN A STALL WITH A HORSE
THAT'S ABOUT TO BE TEASED!
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME, PARKER.
Parker, hurry up!
SEE, YOU'RE NOT DEAD. GOOD.
DON'T BE SILLY.
HORSES ARE MUCH LESS MURDEROUS
THAN I ORIGINALLY THOUGHT.
ALAN, WHEN I MET YOU
AT THE RACES THE OTHER DAY,
I SAID TO MYSELF,
"KITTY, NOW, THIS IS A MAN
WHO IS GOING TO TAKE YOU PLACES."
ARE WE GOING THE RIGHT WAY?
DARLIN', I'M QUITE FAMILIAR
WITH THESE STABLES.
WE'RE JUST TAKING A LITTLE SHORTCUT.
STERLING'S GONNA MEET US HERE,
AND A FEW INVESTORS ARE COMING, TOO.
THEY CAN'T WAIT TO MEET FEI KUAI.
AND HERE WE ARE.
I'VE NEVER COME THIS
WAY BEFORE. IT'S FUNNY.
I'M JUST GONNA GO CHECK ON THE TRUCK.
YOU STAY RIGHT HERE.
RIGHT HERE.
HEY. DID YOU GET HIM TURNED AROUND ENOUGH?
I THINK SO.
HE DOESN'T SEEM THAT
FAMILIAR WITH THE STABLES.
OKAY, FOSS IS IN PLACE.
Where are you?
WE'RE CLOSE. ANY MINUTE NOW.
Listen, the hauler's gonna
be here in five minutes.
IF YOU'RE NOT HERE, FOSS IS
GONNA OPEN UP AN EMPTY TRAILER
AND THERE'LL BE NO LOST HEIR.
I SAID WE'LL BE THERE!
HARDISON, SHOW ME WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING AT.
I'LL BE DAMNED.
We're going to jail.
MY FATHER'S LOST HIS JOB,
HE LOST HIS HORSES,
AND NOW HE'S GONNA HAVE
TO VISIT ME IN JAIL.
THAT'S GREAT.
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE, YOU'LL HAVE
ALL OF US TO KEEP YOU COMPANY.
HEY, NOBODY'S GOING TO JAIL.
I PROMISE YOU.
WE'RE GONNA MAKE IT.
WHERE ARE --
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE NOT GONNA MAKE IT.
I'M PULLING THE PLUG.
ELIOT, BRING THE HORSE BACK
TO THE STUD FARM,
MEET US AT THE RENDEZVOUS SPOT.
Uh, boss, we might
have a hard time with that.
WHY?
OH, GREAT.
GREAT JOB NOT GETTING
EMOTIONALLY ATTACHED
OR DOING ANYTHING STUPID.
IT'S THE FRONT GATE.
THE HAULER'S HERE.
WELL, PERFECT. RIGHT ON TIME.
NO, WE GOT STERLING SHOWING UP ANY SECOND.
NOW, LISTEN, THIS THING -- IT'S OVER.
SO WE'RE GONNA DO THE
BLOWOFF RIGHT NOW BECAUSE --
WHOA.
PONY EXPRESS IS NEVER LATE, BOSS.
DIDN'T I TELL YOU I WAS GONNA KILL YOU?
OKAY. WE'RE BACK ON.
GIBSON CALLED. HE'S UPSET.
HE REALLY HAD HIS EYE ON THAT HORSE.
BUT I GUESS THE BEST MAN WON.
YEAH, WELL, I HAVE A WAY OF --
THINGS HAVE A WAY OF GOING IN MY DIRECTION.
- JUST LUCKY, I GUESS.
- I GUESS.
MR. FOSS, I GOT SOMETHING YOU
MIGHT WANT TO TAKE A LOOK AT.
YEAH, FIGURED YOU WOULD.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL DOUBLE-CHECKBEFORE MY
INSURANCE INVESTIGATOR TAKES A LOOK.
YOU KNOW, YOU WOULDN'T
WANT ANYTHING TO GO WRONG.
- RIGHT?
- GOOD THINKING.
THANK YOU.
SO, READY TO MAKE THIS OFFICIAL?
YES, I AM.
JUST SIGN HERE AND INITIAL THERE.
NOW, THERE'S JUST THAT
SMALL MATTER OF $12 MILLION.
$12 MILLION COMING RIGHT AT YOU.
WHY, THAT IS A LOVELY STRING OF ZEROS.
MY FRIENDS WILL BE VERY PLEASED.
RIGHT DOWN HERE.
I'M AFRAID I HAVE SOME
UNFORTUNATE NEWS, MR. FOSS.
HEY, STERLING, NOT RIGHT NOW, OKAY?
I'M SHOWING THEM THE HORSE.
THE HORSE YOU HAVE IN
THERE IS NOT FROM CHINA,
AND IT'S DEFINITELY NOT
THE LOST HEIR OF SECRETARIAT.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THAT HORSE IS KENTUCKY THUNDER.
WHAT?
THAT AIN'T KENTUCKY THUNDER.
WELL, OF COURSE IT ISN'T.
IT'S FEI KUAI.
0-2-2-1-3.
OKAY, OBVIOUSLY YOUR SCANNER ISN'T WORKING.
OKAY, I-I JUST PUT THE HORSE IN HERE.
HOW IS THIS HAPPENING?
WHAT IS GOING ON, FOSS?
???HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO KNOW?
WHAT HORSE IS THIS?
THEY NEED MEN LIKE MYSELF
TO, UH, SHOW THEM VISION.
IT'S BALTIMORE.
UM...E-EXCUSE ME.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
BECAUSE I LOST BALTIMORE IN A POKER GAME.
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU JUST BOUGHT HIM BACK.
AND YOU TRIED TO INSURE
HIM FOR $12 MILLION.
IN THE PREVIOUS CLAIM,
YOU INSURED THIS VERY
SAME HORSE FOR $200,000.
THAT'S INSURANCE FRAUD.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO DENY
YOUR CLAIM ON THE FIRE.
I THINK YOU OWE THESE
GENTLEMEN AN EXPLANATION.
I THINK HE OWES US $10 MILLION.
WHOA! WAIT!
HOLD ON!
LET ME JUST --
THIS IS NOT HA-- THIS ISN'T --
WE'RE GONNA --
WE'RE GONNA GET THE MONEY BACK.
DON'T "WE'RE GONNA GET THE MONEY BACK."
YOU'RE ON THE HOOK FOR FRAUD.
YOU'LL PAY THE DEBT.
$10 MILLION IS ALL I HAVE LEFT.
WE'LL SETTLE FOR THAT.
LOOKS GOOD. ALL RIGHT.
AND, UH...
WE GOT YOU JUST A LITTLE BIT
OF CASH TO GET YOUR STABLE GOING.
$12 MILLION MORE WILL BE
IN YOUR BANK ACCOUNT.
AND HERE IS... YOUR FIRST HORSE.
THIS IS LEGAL?
ABSOLUTELY.
THE FRAUD INVALIDATES THE SECOND SALE.
OWNERSHIP REVERTS BACK
TO THE PREVIOUS OWNER -- ME --
AND I'M GIVING HIM TO YOU.
I-I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
NEXT HORSE I GET,
I'M NAMING HIM MR. FORD.
MR. FORD.
WELL, I LOOK FORWARD TO PUTTING
A LITTLE MONEY ON MR. FORD.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
ELIOT, ELIOT?
YEAH, UH, COU-- CAN I --
COULD YOU GIVE ME, UH --
YEAH, YEAH. JUST -- YEAH.
SO...
I WAS WRONG.
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER
HEARD YOU SAY THAT BEFORE.
WRONG ABOUT WHAT EXACTLY?
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA BE
THE KIND TO SETTLE DOWN,
BUT, UH, I'M GLAD YOU FOUND A FAMILY.
TH--
THOSE GUYS?
I'M JUST SORRY IT COULDN'T BE ME.
* LIVING WITH ME, IT AIN'T EASY *
* WELL, I DO IT EVERY DAY
* AND SOMETIMES EVEN I
* I WANT TO RUN AWAY
* BUT THERE YOU ARE
* YOU'RE TRYING TO PLEASE ME
* AND YOU STAND YOUR GROUND
* THAT'S MORE THAN I DESERVE
NICE MOVE WITH THE
TOURISTS AND THE CAMERA.
DID YOU HAVE TO HIDE IN HARDISON'S
TRUNK ALL WEEK TO PULL THAT OFF?
YOUR CRACK TEAM HANDED ME THAT ONE.
A LITTLE SLOPPY, LETTING HER
HAVE BATHROOM BREAKS.
AND BRINGING KENTUCKY THUNDER'S TRAINER --
WELL, THAT WRAPPED THINGS UP NICELY FOR US.
MADE YOU LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT,
BUT HELPED US OUT.
AND THE PAPERWORK THAT YOU HAD FOSS SIGN
HELPED ME SAVE THE COMPANY
A PILE OF MONEY IN THE PAYOUT.
AND YOU KNOW FROM PERSONAL EXPERIENCE
JUST HOW MUCH THEY HATE TO WRITE A CHECK.
LOOK...
IT'S TERRIBLE WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR SON.
NO ONE'S DENYING THAT.
SUFFERING DOESN'T
AUTOMATICALLY MAKE YOU A HERO.
I NEVER CLAIMED TO BE.
YOU JUST THINK YOU'RE ABOVE THE LAW.
OH, NO.
I LIKE TO THINK OF IT AS I PICK
UP WHERE THE LAW LEAVES OFF.
I'M NOT GONNA BE SO NICE NEXT TIME.
NEITHER WILL I.
Translated by
Harak Aladin
www.tvsubtitles.net