Yeah, I'm still at work.
Well, it's better than being
alone in my hotel room.
No, I am not.
I am not obsessed.
I know what obsessed is.
This is not obsessed.
It's done. Seal the exits.
No one gets in or out.
Get this one up.
You are under arrest.
Wait a minute.
I think there's been
some kind of mistake.
The rich and powerful,
they take what they want.
We steal it back for you.
And sometimes, bad guys
make the best good guys.
We provide...
leverage!
Season 2 - Episode 12
The Zanzibar Marketplace Job
Two weeks in Tokyo.
We'd have a great time.
What are we stealing?
We don't steal anything.
We'd be tourists.
Not following you.
There you go.
- Thank you, sweetheart.
- Anytime.
- What?
- Really?
- What, I can't have a friend?
- Join a softball team.
Our next client...
Two kids, no job, pension gone.
State grabbed their land
under eminent domain.
So, these are all
your little lost sheep?
Excuse me?
You can't save them all.
I'm getting some coffee.
He's drinking again.
- I'm not an idiot, Tara.
- I was told this was a problem.
The drinking is not a problem.
It's a symptom.
Hey. All right.
Okay, so...
What we...
Eliot, I'm gonna ask you
not to do anything violent.
What? What are you talking about?
I only use violence
as an appropriate response.
Hello, Nate.
And this is?
James Sterling.
We used to work together.
Insurance.
He seems to rub Eliot the wrong way.
You think?
Hello, Sterling.
What are you doing here?
Actually, I came to offer you a job.
There's nothing you can say
to make us work with you.
It's Maggie.
Get him upstairs.
This Fabergé egg was commissioned
by czar Nicholas of Russia.
Being one of only 69
known to survive,
it's worth $9 million.
Maggie was working at the museum,
verifying russian artifacts
donated for an exhibit.
The night of the robbery,
she was the only person at the museum.
And there you have it.
- Who is...
- Maggie's Nate's ex-wife.
Okay. Is there any chance
she took the egg?
Maggie's the most honest person we know.
But besides that, she's okay.
Maggie's being set up.
You live and work here?
- I like the old place better.
- Do not mention the old offices.
Maggie is where,
precisely, right now?
Currently awaiting trial
in the Kiev jail.
When I heard that dear Maggie was
being held without bail, I rushed...
Please. As soon as you found out
that the Fabergé egg
that your company insures
went missing, you...
Rushed to the Ukraine.
Of course, I was unable
to clear her name.
- I assume you have another suspect?
- Absolutely.
Alexander Lundy.
International real-estate mogul.
Very rich, very powerful.
My only problem is that he
works at the american embassy,
which makes him untouchable
by normal law enforcement.
We got to book it. Our flight to Kiev
leaves in three hours.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Hang on.
- I'm not working next to this guy.
- No, you don't have to.
I'll work with him.
You have a different job.
- What?
- You're the retrieval specialist.
Retrieve my wife from jail.
Let's go!
Eliot, Hardison just got
to the police station.
They're waiting to see
the inspector in charge.
Good. Once you get her out,
you need to disappear.
She'll never see us.
How's Sterling's suspect?
You mean the financial
genius Alexander Lundy?
Yeah, definitely guilty.
- Alexander.
- Mr. Lundy.
Yeah, so, Mr. Lundy,
what does an economic liaison
do here at the american embassy?
I use my contacts from my business
in international real estate
to bring investments
to developing nations,
- such as those in eastern Europe.
- I see. Is that profitable?
Yes, very.
That's the point.
Profitable enough to buy
a $9 million Fabergé egg?
I like pretty things.
Anticipating discussion
of this topic,
I have brought copies
of the insurance paperwork.
I also brought a copy
of Mr. Lundy's schedule,
which will verify his alibi
on the day and night in question.
- Thank you...
- Sam. Sam Phillips.
Mr. Lundy is not
under investigation.
We'd like to resolve this rather awful
situation as quickly as possible.
That's very fair of you.
I personally have no doubt you will get
what's coming to you very soon.
No.
Maybe we've been unclear.
We were sent by the american embassy.
We have documents
authorized by your government,
requesting the release of Maggie Collins
into the US embassy's custody.
No.
Can I ask why you're being
so dismissive of my fine documents,
which took a lot of work,
personal time, research?
If I release miss Collins,
I have no guarantee
she will return for trial.
She will run straight
to american embassy,
where she will be untouchable,
and I will be made fool.
Nyet.
- That means "no."
- Yeah, I got it.
You cannot out-bureaucrat
A former soviet union bureaucrat.
These guys gamed the most corrupt system
on Earth for 50 years.
Paperwork's not gonna cut it.
They're used to trading favors,
not forms.
- Hang on. Wait, wait.
- No.
Look,
I didn't want to have
to pull this card, all right?
I'm trying to use discretion here.
Do you have any idea
who this woman's lover is?
Still, you are not allowed
to leave the country, of course.
I understand.
And, please,
give the minister my best.
Anytime I can help,
he should call to me directly.
I will. Thank you.
I'm sorry. What minister?
Yes, of course.
"What minister?"
Do not worry.
The men were very discreet.
You are not releasing me
because you think I'm innocent.
What did these men look like?
That lying son of a...
I mean, look at these financials.
The credit crunch wiped him out.
He's maybe three, four months
from declaring bankruptcy.
Lundy offers the egg up to
the museum for the exhibition
so that it falls
under their insurance policy,
hires a little local muscle to help
with the heist tidy payout.
I just need some proof.
It was an inside job.
Average keypad hack time
is 1 minute, 9.3 seconds.
Inner door access card takes at least
30 seconds for anybody but Hardison.
And then the vault was
an old Mark II Remington.
In and out average...
7 minutes, 40 seconds.
But these thieves,
they did it in 5 minutes, 12 seconds.
Maggie had the best access,
so the real thieves only had
to get her codes and badge.
Yeah, only way they could
pull it off that fast.
How long has she been sitting...
Maggie's on his calendar.
He had lunch with her the day of the
heisting to discuss his collection.
So, while he's keeping her
busy at lunch,
his men take her ID cards
and access codes,
and she gets framed for the heist.
Oh, boy, I'm gonna nail
this son of a bitch.
I can explain.
Maggie, it's not what you think.
It's your first time being a fugitive,
so I made you a bag...
Thank you, Parker.
It's not that I don't appreciate
getting out of jail...
- I just can't live my life a fugitive.
- But you're not.
Passports, money, lock picks.
You were released, not broken out.
Toothpaste, explosives.
Do not mix these up.
Thank you, Parker.
But you released me to run.
I'm not going anywhere
until my name is cleared.
That's what I'm here to do...
To get the egg back, to clear your name.
You're clearing my name with thieves.
No offense, Parker.
At what?
Actually, Nate's been rehabilitated.
He's here on official IYS business,
as a consultant.
I brought him on.
You've gone straight?
The only reason they're here
is to deal with the authorities
And to get you released.
They're not staying.
Absolutely not.
I don't trust them.
- They don't trust me.
- Eliot already punched him.
You know, it's all aboveboard.
It's perfectly legit.
The best thing you could do would be
go back to the hotel.
I'll call you.
- I promise.
- This looks like gum. Not gum.
- Diamond-edged file blade.
- That's great.
She needs this stuff.
I'm just gonna help you with this.
Crime suits you.
- You're becoming a much better liar.
- Thanks.
Let's nail this Lundy
before Maggie figures that out.
So, I took your advice
and did the whole touristy thing.
Went to the museum,
and it was amazing.
- You see?
- Yeah.
They have a guardian T-840 system.
I've only seen those things in books.
And the motion detectors...
gorgeous!
Six digital receptors. Six!
- What about the paintings?
Finally.
Finally, somebody who can help us
with this marriage visa.
This is Luba. I want her to get back
home to the states with me.
It's true love.
- We meet on internet.
- We did, we did.
- You've got the wrong person.
- The girl at the front, she said...
She said that you was
the man with the...
You're right. You're not, this ain't...
It's not you. I am terribly sorry.
That's fine.
Let's just get this cleaned up.
You know how it is
with the girls on the internet.
- Sometimes they ain't girls.
- Right.
Right, right.
- Best of luck.
- Spacibo.
Alexander's got a travel visa
to the united arab emirates.
He's also setting up accounts
in the caymans,
Macau, and switzerland.
Countries with no extradition treaty...
Tax havens.
Doesn't look like someone who's going
to wait around for an insurance payout.
And this guy showed up on his phone.
I know him. That's Adrian Chernov.
He's a fence.
A fence?
- So, he's selling it.
- Sure he's selling it.
He's gonna sell that egg on
the black market and run.
I got to hand it to the guy.
It's a good plan.
- I feel bad for screwing it up.
- Really?
I don't.
Hardison, can you get chernov's
location for Tara and Eliot, please?
Chernov.
I got this one.
Really? What are you gonna say to him?
Because we got no cover story.
- We got no background on this cat.
- That's it, then. I won't say anything.
Really. Not one word. Just when he turns
around and looks at you,
do that thing with your eyes
that scares people.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You know exactly
what I'm talking about.
What the...
Who the hell are you?
Do I know you?
Did Samuels send you?
I paid them off.
I took care of it.
Oh, god.
Please. Is this about the item?
I didn't know.
No one told me.
Wait!
Here.
This is all I have.
I'll back out.
I'm sorry.
Sorry!
What we imagine is always
so much better than the reality.
Like love?
It's blank.
What the hell is this?
It's a Zanzibar marketplace.
The marketplace
is a one-time event...
crops up in a city after an
important piece has been stolen.
You should have seen Stockholm
after the Rembrandt heist.
Parking was a bloody nightmare.
How do people find out about it?
Well, the prospective buyers are invited
by their black-market contacts.
They show up,
they verify the merchandise,
and they make a sealed bid.
Shine an ultraviolet light
on that card.
Seriously?
You have one just laying around?
The bidder's ID number and the time
of the auction's encrypted on the card.
The bidders write their bid
on the back of the card...
One number, no zeros,
and then they hand it
to the seller in a sealed envelope.
They leave town immediately.
A week later, if they win,
they transfer the money,
and the merchandise is couriered
to them by messenger
- as soon as the heat's died down.
- So, no names,
no contact with the money
or the item?
Nice.
A marketplace means multiple buyers
all at the same time.
- Where's he gonna do this?
- At the embassy.
The american embassy is
having a party tonight.
Perfect cover.
Embassy's a great place to
store stolen merchandise.
Pretty much american territory. Local
cops can't even get through the gate.
Even if we can prove
that Alexander has the egg,
police can't touch him,
search for it.
If we can't let loose the dogs of law
enforcement on him, what do we do?
We steal the damn thing back.
Best be right about all this.
I pulled a lot of strings
to get tickets for all of you.
All of you?
Wait, no, Hardison... he's in the van,
eating stale candy
while all you get to dine on canapes
and champagne.
- I love canapes.
- I'm terribly sorry about that.
The company has to draw the line
somewhere.
I can assure you it has nothing to do
with our little incident last year.
You mean the incident
where I came within 5 feet
of blowing your ass up?
I'm sure it has nothing to do
with that at all.
Van smells like cabbage.
How do you put up with all
this nagging in your ear?
I've learned
to block most of it out.
Okay, guys, Tara's on the grift.
She's got the bidding envelope,
So she's gonna head
into the auction.
There's something
I need to tell you.
Now, guys, once she spots the egg,
Eliot, Parker, you move in
and clean it out.
How are we gonna turn Lundy
over to the cops?
Well, we're not.
We're gonna get the egg,
and then Sterling's gonna use his pull
with IYS to clear Maggie.
Clearing Maggie is the priority.
It's on the tip of my tongue.
Yes.
That.
Try to have fun, now.
Alexander's seen you with me,
so you can't be the bidder.
- Eliot, you're first team.
- He needs the envelope.
So get it to him. Make sure Maggie
doesn't see Eliot or parker.
Parker, double reverse on three.
I thought you said
your friends were gone.
- You know, she's not...
- Tara Carlisle.
- Hi. Maggie Collins.
- Hi.
Mr. Ford, Maggie told me
how you helped her get out of jail.
- Thank you so much.
- Don't mention it.
After all, what was I supposed to do,
Let her sit and rot in a ukrainian jail
to think about the poor choices
she's made without setting things right
r explaining herself?
Cheers.
Sorry.
I'm a little bit lost.
I have one of these.
Here you go.
All right, Nate, he's hired
some local security on the payroll.
Watch yourself.
So...
- You guys are...
- Yes, we are.
And you and Tara are...
Yes. Very much so, yes.
Mr. Ford,
how's the investigation coming?
Actually, we're kind of moving in
on someone right now.
Most thieves aren't nearly as smart
or good-looking as they think they are.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lundy,
but the ambassador is leaving.
- I think we should...
- Yes.
I apologize, but duty calls.
It was nice to meet you.
Hey, I'm not Sophie.
You want to drink, go ahead.
I'd drink, too, if I were you.
Smart, handsome, successful.
You know, I think he's
younger than you, too.
Okay, you guys,
Alexander's on the move.
Don't let that egg
out of your sight.
All right, they're about
to present the merchandise.
- They're bringing it out right now.
- Yeah.
All right, slight problem.
Smart.
Eliot, get them to prove that it's not
an old recording. I'll trace the signal.
Pardon me. I'm sor...
Am I the only one that. How do we know
that this is not a recording?
Could you ask him to move it?
Resituate the egg.
Now, worst-case scenario, that room
you're looking at is 100 miles away.
I am checking the internet traffic
in and out of the embassy network.
Just get me a few more seconds.
Excuse me.
Can... can you have him show me
A five, three, five,
two, two, please?
Show us five, three, five, two, two.
You're out of time, Hardison.
Nothing coming out of the pipeline
is big enough to be that camera feed.
That room is inside the building.
Eliot, do you see any wires
running into the laptop?
Okay, that means they're running it
off their ad hoc wireless network.
All I have to do is isolate
the camera's I.P. Address.
See, all the cold-war embassies
Were honeycombed with secret corridors
And secret rooms
for listening posts,
But none of them are used anymore.
Parker,
I'm sending you the map right now.
Just follow the ping.
That's your egg room.
I got it.
I know exactly what you mean.
What you mean.
Sorry to interrupt this.
- Can I get two minutes?
- Oh, sure.
- Bye.
Yeah, Alexander seems, nice.
Yeah, he is.
And Tara seems so sweet.
She's a foreign aid worker.
Really? I mean, really.
Yes. Really.
So, what happened to Sophie?
That got a bit complicated.
Right, because you're
such a simple man.
Anyway, I should go find Alexander.
Yeah. You know, I'd actually
like to talk to him, too.
You know, maybe we can go together,
See what he's up to...
Together.
I'm right outside the door.
There's no sign of Alexander down here.
Your bids, please.
All right, parker,
They just shut off the
feed to the egg room, okay?
Whoever's in that room
is gonna be coming out.
I can't get past him.
I'm out of position.
Me too.
- What are you doing there, buddy?
- You are interfering
with the natural
course of my events.
Listen...
Maybe you can help me.
I'm supposed to meet my brother's...
It's a secret. It's a secret.
- Can you help?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Cool. You come with me.
- And get my bottle. It's empty.
- Okay. You sure? You're very strong.
- Thank you.
Oh. Careful now.
I've got the package.
Great. Let's clear out before
they realize the egg is gone.
Anyone seen Nate?
You're welcome.
I don't know how you
people ever manage...
Oh, I'm sorry, man.
That just happens sometimes
with the ear buds...
You know, feedback.
As I was saying, the method...
Sorry.
This isn't gonna stop until I...
Stop talking. Shh. Please.
Where's Nate?
I swear I saw him duck in here.
Yes, but we haven't checked
the southeast corridor,
And, you know, I'd really like to give
him the good news myself.
I've heard that voice before.
What?
You don't even know that you do it,
do you?
I'm sorry, doing what?
That's your intercom voice.
You lied to me!
Wait, wait, wait. Maggie, Alexander...
you need to know...
- Do not drag him into this.
- Well, he's already into this,
More than you
I hate to be the one to tell you.
- Nate!
- No!
What?
No offense, but I think I
was better off in jail.
I think we were tasered...
Same thing that happened
to me at the robbery.
Did...
You see who did this?
Yeah, they looked
like security guards from the embassy.
Yeah, Eliot warned me about that.
I already tried it. It's locked.
Come on, come on.
- I just said it was locked.
- Yeah, no, I know. It's just,
Men.
This isn't good. I can't get him
on the cellphone, not on the comm.
Case is closed, people.
The egg is back.
I'm sure Nate is breaking it to Maggie
about her continued poor choice in men.
It's Nate's cell.
We have your people.
No police.
Await further instructions.
What are you doing?
Calling the police.
They don't get to dictate to...
We're not calling the cops.
Two hostages means they can
kill one to make a point.
All right, listen.
There's three types of
calls we can get next.
One... amateur.
Cash and a dump site.
Number two... professional.
That's wire transfers and multipl
e-location drop-offs.
And three... targeted.
- Targeted toward us?
- No.
Towards a specific ransom demand...
Not cash.
- You're not risking a 9 million...
- It might be the only chance.
On a hunch!
Let me run this.
We track the calls, find out whoever
it is, have the police surround...
Sterling,
I'm the retrieval specialist.
That's my job.
Your friends' lives
hang in the balance,
And you're gonna take your cues
Off a punch-up artist instead of me?
Call me when you need me.
'cause you will need me.
Basically, we're looking
for anything to help us get out of here.
Nate? At the party, you were trying
to tell me something about Alexander.
- We can deal with that later.
- No. Why don't you just tell me now?
- Getting you out is the priority.
- Why don't you tell...
You don't understand! You don't have
to do this! I'll give you anything!
Take my watch!
It's a patek phillipe!
Oh, thank god!
It's Alexander. He's gone crazy.
That's what I was trying
to tell you upstairs.
There's no sign of Alexander
at his home or the embassy.
And his embassy car has been signed out.
He's spooked.
He's angry. We took his payday.
All right, all right.
Go.
If you follow our instructions,
Your friends will be
returned unharmed.
We agree. Tell us what you want.
You owe me $9 million.
- It's alex. It's Alexander.
- I still have a buyer for the egg.
Return it,
and I return your friends.
I want proof of life now.
Agreed.
Yeah, we got Alexander's financials,
And he's three months from bankruptcy,
the theft was definitely an inside job.
I think you were right. I don't think
we should talk about this right now.
I know it is difficult hearing this
about your boyfriend. I get that.
Boyfriend? We date, Nate.
We go on dates.
That's probably not as exciting as
stealing art with your new friend Tara.
I'm not dating Tara. Now, what you do is
you make a cut here...
I knew it. You're dating Sophie.
I'm not dating Sophie, either.
I'm not dating anyone.
But good for you, moving on
with a thieving kidnapper.
- That's terrific.
- Alleged thieving kidnapper.
- Call it...
- No, it's all true.
I found some irregularities
in mr. Lundy's finances.
He told me they were no problem.
He took the files,
Which, of course, tipped me off.
I knew something was wrong.
- There's our proof of life.
- I didn't have access to all his books.
I was in that room earlier.
- That's the room the egg was in.
- They're at the embassy.
But it doesn't do us any good. We can't
storm it, and the police can't touch it.
- Immigration papers, which,
- You know, my team found.
Your team?
I thought you said your team had gone.
You lied to me.
You've been lying {\to
me }since we got here.
then he told me
he was going to kill me, and his
- men threw me in here like an animal.
- I was lying to you for your own good.
little hint for
your next marriage...
That excuse does not fly
with any woman on earth.
Next marriage? Really nice to say.
You know what?
I've heard that before.
Heard what?
What are you talking about?
Are you actually having
this argument now?
- She started it.
- He started it.
I've sent you the address.
Come alone at dawn.
Bring the egg...
Or your friends die.
Okay, the address Is one of
Alexander's construction sites...
Local project.
Abandoned after his
business got in trouble.
Now we have to go convince Sterling,
who hates you...
Us. Hates us.
To loan you a
$9 million antique So you can
bring it to a ransom drop?
Listen...
we know who's behind this, all right?
We know what they want.
We have the upper hand here.
We do.
Well, that was close.
You owe me $9 million.
Give me that.
The thing everyone screws up when
they fake their own death...
No body.
Well, that can work, but it
leaves no suspect for
the police to chase.
- You won't get away with this.
- No,
you will. Of course.
I've left an evidence
trail a mile wide...
Visa applications,
accounts in offshore banks.
- You were my friend!
- I was your employee.
And thanks to your screw-ups,
I was an employee with no pension,
no savings,
no nothing.
That was really,
really unacceptable to me.
It's a good plan.
What?
Listen, I spent 20 years chasing,
You know, guys that faked
their own death. I mean, this one...
- it's pretty well thought-out.
- Exactly.
Alexander Lundy, desperate for cash,
turns to violence.
And his poor assistant, Sam,
loyal to the last,
caught in the cross fire
at a ransom drop gone bad.
- Cross fire?
- More like a blast radius.
That Alexander Lundy is crazy.
Sam, don't do this, please.
I'll pay you! I'll pay you anything!
Pay me? With what?
You can't even put
walls in this place.
- When Nate's people get here...
- Oh, they should already be here.
Just not, you know, here.
- Go.
- Put the egg in the elevator.
Send it down.
We send your people up.
- I want proof of life.
- So do I.
Picture of the egg. Now.
Your man's persistent.
Well...
He'll be dead in
about two minutes, so
it doesn't really matter.
You're never gonna get out
of the country.
Oh, but the embassy
car is waiting outside.
Straight to the airport,
right past customs, and into a
private jet,
all in Alexander's name.
We'll be in south america
by the time they're through
hosing you and your friend
up there off the walls.
Your friends for the Fabergé egg.
Put it in the elevator.
It's on its way down.
Come on, come on!
- Can you defuse it?
- I'm trying.
When I get it, I will.
Nate...
What?
Get the car started.
Excuse me.
I just have to grab that bomb.
Oh, my god.
The, uh, elevator stopped.
Yeah.
Go.
It's okay.
First bomb's always the hardest.
You know,
it's not that embarrassing.
I do not want to talk about it.
How did you get the elevators to stop
without the numbers stopping?
I sped them up 1.5 seconds per
floor for the first 10 floors...
And then I sent them down regular
speed for the last 10 floors.
There was a 15-second window in
the middle for Parker to work her magic.
- Looks like I missed the party.
- They do what we thought?
Ran right to their little embassy car
and headed straight for the airport,
fast as they could.
This is an embassy car.
You were speeding.
American embassy.
You cannot pull us over
or give us a ticket. Now, we are late
- for a flight...
- This not a embassy car.
Does not have embassy plates.
Please, officer,
don't be ridiculous.
This...
this isn't right.
Listen.
- Listen to me.
- Plates are reported stolen.
Against the car. Now!
Against the car!
The plates have been switched!
This is a sovereign vehicle of
the United States government!
- You have no authorization.
- Be quiet! Put your head down!
How did...
Webcam.
No sound the first time I saw it.
Can you have him show me a five,
three, five, two, two, please?
Then they turned up sound for proof of
life. why would they turn up the volume
during the second show?
- There's our proof of life.
- I was in that room earlier.
- That's the room the egg was in.
- They're at the embassy.
But it doesn't do us any good. We can't
storm it, and the police can't touch it.
Was it because they wanted us
to hear Sam's performance
101, man.
After that, you don't have to be
a rocket scientist To figure it out.
You know,
people underestimate you, Eliot.
That's kind of the point.
Where's the egg?
In order for us to,
Get the egg from Sterling,
he made some additions to the plan.
Inspector, what is it that you can
tell us about this case at the time?
Well, we catch people
on way to airport.
We catch...
Inspector.
Excellent, excellent work.
- I see you got my call.
- What call?
When I realized who was responsible
and overheard
they were trying to make
their escape to the airport,
well, here you go.
I had to stick close.
These men are responsible for...
responsible
for stealing the Fabergé egg.
- Can I get a name?
Sterling.
Jim Sterling.
And that's not all.
Today, based on his work
recovering the priceless artifact,
James Sterling was invited
to join interpol.
He's a real-life Sherlock Holmes.
Interpol?
Seriously?
Sterling's career gets another
boost off of our hard work.
- We didn't even get paid.
- Nope.
I hate this guy.
Now you're part of the team.
Should have known it
would be this place.
Can you stay in town?
No, I have to get back to L.A.
But not...
Alexander?
He had issues.
Bankruptcy,
political fallout, the whole
"freaking out when he thought
there was a bomb" thing.
Yeah, but I wouldn't be too
tough on him about that.
Parker's right.
The first bomb is the hardest.
Yeah, he's...
Anyway...
I'm sorry I lied to you, Maggie.
So am I.
This isn't what I want to do.
Oh, now, that's the lie.
No, no. I...
Well, things have been
kind of tough lately, so...
There's Irish whiskey in that coffee,
isn't there?
Yeah.
A little bit.
- Sorry.
- It's not the liquor that worries me.
It's the fact that you're
hiding it in your coffee cup.
I meant what I said before.
I really like the man
that you've become.
Too bad you don't.