- Can I get you boys any refills?
- No, thank you, Cora.
- Can I get that back on the way out?
- If you're good, Mr. Cabella.
- Rules are rules.
- Listen, honey.
Our condolences.
Your father was a kind host.
It's hard to see
his empty chair there.
He was the best of us.
Yes.
To John McRory!
Is that mistress Cora McRory?
I don't believe we've met, mister...
Mark Doyle.
This is Liam.
This is Liam's brother.
My sympathies, by the by.
Forgive me for conducting such dirty
business on your day of mourning,
but himself owed me a debt,
and I've come by to collect.
My father owed you money?
He took out a loan 12 months ago...
$5,000.
With interest, it's $15,000
and come due today.
- $15,000? I don't have that...
- Unlike yankee banks,
I don't give unsecured loans.
Your dad put up his pub
as collateral.
The bar is all he had.
In this life,
some are given to need,
some provision.
My boys tell me
you're the sole heiress.
So...
$15,000. Pay up.
Or, if it's easier for you,
I'll take the pub.
Thank you, Liam.
Go on, love.
Collect yourself.
Check your assets.
We'll wait for exactly two hours.
So, this is paying respects?
Absolutely, yeah.
I mean, it's an irish wake.
You know there's a poker game
going on in the back room?
At one time or another,
every man in this neighborhood played
in John McRory's friday-night game.
It's an honor. Hell, my father
played in it for 10 years before...
Then this was your father's local?
This was my father's office,
right here.
And he held court
right there on that stool.
And he would just...
I grew up in this place.
That must have been
an interesting education.
We can work something out.
Now, what have we learned, Nathan?
Don't gamble
with another man's money.
Good lad.
Yeah, better than prep school.
- What kind of crook was your dad?
- Parker, you just...
He ran numbers.
Let me get this straight...
So you stop stealing, you stop drinking,
and you moved upstairs
from a thief bar?
He did. I get that.
You don't get that?
- Why does nobody else get that?
- No, the thing about it is...
Now it's just a neighborhood bar.
Back in the day, you never knew
who you were drinking next to.
You had the mob on one side,
the law on the other.
Times have changed.
Not that much, but...
Cora here...
I remember the day she was born.
She grew up here, too,
and she turned out all right.
Cora?
Redheads burn the hottest,
don't they?
Easy.
She's like my niece.
She's not like
your daughter, though.
No, like my niece.
So I don't want you to like my niece
'cause she's like my niece.
- I don't like your niece.
- You know what I mean.
There. That's all we have.
Let's see, now.
$210.
Noted.
Well...
That's only $14,790 to go.
The rich and powerful,
they take what they want.
We steal it back for you.
And sometimes, bad guys
make the best good guys.
We provide...
leverage!
Season 2 - Episode 11
The Bottle Job
His name is Mark Doyle.
He's irish.
You know, he says dad took out
a loan from him a year ago.
I didn't believe him at first.
Thank you.
But I realize...
that it was just before
the cancer took mom.
You know, I tried to help him
with the bills.
He swore he had it under control.
I could have stopped this!
Well, no, listen. This guy Doyle...
He's a loan shark.
I don't think you could have helped.
But maybe we can.
No, he wants $15,000
in the next two hours,
Nate, or he's taking the bar.
I can't get that kind of money.
In two hours?
Why don't you do this, okay?
Why don't you go back downstairs
and tend to the guests.
And we'll try
to figure out something here.
Okay?
Thank you.
Why don't we just send her
to the police?
I don't use them,
but this is what they're for, right?
No, if Cora says to the police
that she owes Doyle money,
Doyle denies it.
Six months later,
he comes and burns down the bar.
And that's assuming that he doesn't have
a couple of local police on the arm.
That's what sucks
about the credit crunch.
Honest people can't get loans,
sharks move in.
12 points on the interest
every month...
There's no way to get out
from under that.
I don't care. You don't collect debts
at a wake. You just don't do it.
Want me to go downstairs,
break this guy's knees?
we need some reconnaissance, like,
why is this irish loan shark here?
And what is this 2-hour timetable?
Why don't you call Tara?
Tell her we got a job.
What's the game?
- 20 questions.
- I'll do it in 10.
- That one?
- Right there.
I'm Trish, and I'm lonely.
Shot of Jamie, rocks.
That's only a bit of irish.
How'd you like a whole lot of irish?
And what do you do?
Typical. Only americans ask
for your occupation before your name.
I'm a bank, sweetheart.
- You're a bit short for a bank.
- Very clever.
It's a family business, mine...
Based back in Belfast.
I'm the VP in charge
of overseas expansion.
Slow down.
I love it. I love it.
Nothing but cash and an ID.
I'm running it, but we got
next to nothing on this guy.
No bank accounts, no credit cards.
He's totally off the grid.
Mark Doyle, loan shark.
If I were ashamed,
I couldn't do my job, could I?
I provide a service
for people with no recourse,
help those
with nowhere else to turn.
Society needs me.
Right. But isn't it...
Illegal?
As me da says, we pick up
where the law leaves off.
Got something on dear old da...
Tim Doyle. He not only runs
the family loan-sharking business
but used to kill people
with nail bombs for the IRA.
I convinced me da to let me open
a branch over here in Boston.
Grow the business, as it were.
For 200 years, America took
Ireland's best and brightest.
I'm just here
to collect the interest.
You are so smart.
So...
Why is it that everyone else
is broke and you're not?
Cash only, love.
That's the secret.
Numbers on a screen can be manipulated,
but a cash business endures.
It was good enough for my da and his da.
It's good enough for me.
I got plane tickets.
Doyle's headed for Belfast
in a couple of hours.
That explains the deadline.
But why take the bag of cash?
Tara, I need you to ask something.
How long are you in town?
Leaving tonight.
Annual review, sort of.
Show my new branch
of the business is profitable.
How profitable?
That's not all of it, mind.
Just enough to repay me da
for his investment
and prove that this branch
is very profitable indeed.
Well, then...
You can buy a girl a drink.
I'll be right back.
Same again.
We can't just steal the note.
It's only gonna tick this guy off.
- Can we con him in two hours?
- More like an hour and a half.
We can't pull something
together this fast.
50 bucks. I got 50 bucks.
I need you to tell me what live sports
are being broadcast right now.
Tara, set the hook.
You guys, I need cash.
No. It's impossible.
You want to run the wire...
in two hours.
One and a half.
Wire's three weeks, minimum.
Look at it as
the wire in a bottle, okay?
No one's ever done it
doesn't mean it's impossible.
It does.
- What are we supposed to do?
- Have some respect...
Borrow the wake to save the bar.
Okay, guys, nothing fancy.
Classic wire.
You delay the sports feed.
Now I know what's gonna happen,
he doesn't, I get him to bet.
Now, where's my cash?
It is 9:00 pm on a friday night.
All the banks are closed.
- ATMs.
- Daily withdrawal limit.
If y'all want me to do an electronic
wire transfer of 100 grand
between the Caymans and Madagascar,
I can do that.
But if you're talking cold, hard cash,
you're out of luck. I'm sorry.
Just use your little slimmer thing,
and gank the ATMs.
It's called a skimmer.
But thank you for trying.
I don't have that thing anymore.
We're the good guys now.
I haven't used that thing in months.
Months?
We've been the good guys
longer than that.
Well, we had a break.
Can we please focus?
Emergency fund.
What are you doing?
What, you thought I kept old Nate around
for sentimental reasons?
Relax.
Just a little over nine grand.
That enough?
Yeah, I don't need enough to win,
just enough to lose.
It's perfect.
- I'll take care of the muscle.
- All right.
Hardison, let me know
when you got control of the feeds.
Here.
This is the cable to the television
in the bar downstairs.
We're ready down here.
I'm about to splice...
Well, everything.
- Perfect.
- Come on, Trish. Don't be like that.
It was nice meeting you, Mark.
Thanks a lot, you goby.
I was making headway there.
Sorry. I'll make it up to you.
Get this guy a drink. Whatever he wants.
Give me an empty glass
and a bottle of the most
expensive scotch you've got.
Well, well-played.
- What's the story with the blonde?
- The blonde, yeah...
I used to go out with her
until I broke her brother's kneecaps.
Gambling debt. You don't pay,
you don't walk, in my book.
I don't care who you are.
All right.
I'll drink to that.
Have a seat.
- Get him a glass, will you?
- That's very kind of you.
What's your name?
Name's, Jimy.
- Jimmy Ford.
- Good to meet you, Jimmy.
Slainte!
Okay, we are up and running.
Now, I've set the tv in the bar
on a 20-second delay.
Sisko just hit a jumper
from the baseline.
We need info from the bodyguards,
but I'm burned.
On it.
You make book on this game?
How about a little action?
Without the juice, of course.
All right.
$100 that Sisko misses.
I'll take that.
...to Sisko.
He's picked up by Wanzer.
Sisko from 20!
Bomb!
For a bookie, Jimmy,
you're not much of a gambler.
What's your problem?
You remind me of my sister.
It's all in the wrist.
How are you? Good to see you.
Can I buy beers for my boys and for me.
We're gonna play a little darts here.
Do that again.
All right.
I'll show you how to do that.
I'll take this one.
- Take these.
- Right.
There it is.
Look at that... some ale.
Let me get these for the boys here.
- One for you.
- Cheers.
Good game.
- You like that?
- Love, give us a whack.
There you go, right?
Feisty little thing.
I got their cellphones
and their wallets.
Also lifted this...
Doyle's ledger.
It's written in code.
All right. Another $500...
that he misses.
- Done.
- He puts it up again and drains it!
I almost feel bad taking your money.
What, you too good to drink with me?
No, I'm not betting again
if you have the advantage of me,
Jimmy boy.
Well, you're right.
I mean, I might as well.
You know, I mean,
I'm getting my ass handed to me.
You know, drowning
my own sorrows here, right?
So, this is...
Not good.
I'm grabbing all I can off of Liam one
and two's cellphones.
We may be able to use
any common GPS coordinates
to triangulate the location
of Doyle's office.
And I'm close
to decoding this ledger.
- Names?
- And alphanumeric substitutions.
You know how to read that?
Yeah, I trained in cryptog...
Never mind.
Archer just got robbed.
Layup at the other end.
Okay, $1,000 says
Archer gets schooled.
No way.
He looks. Now he drives the lane.
Ball stripped by Arnie Risen!
Now the pass to Myers...
Archer gets payback,
double or nothing.
- No, turnover. You're good.
- Inbound by Archer. He throws it away!
Who are you throwing it to?
There's no one there!
What the hell?
I'm playing with your money anyway.
For a loan shark, you're not very good
with money, are you?
So I got Mike Duffy, 78 oak street.
Borrowed money to put his mom
in a nursing home.
- Alison McCoy.
- I got her.
Special-needs child.
School bills.
You know, Nate,
we just cracked this ledger,
and Doyle is way deeper into this
neighborhood than we thought.
Boston wins with a three-pointer.
That pile of cash in front of you
looks mighty inviting.
I got a plane to catch.
One last bet?
Well, I mean, there's
almost $10,000 here.
You have the cash to match it?
My cash has other obligations.
- I'm not gonna take a marker.
- You don't have to take my marker.
Take hers.
- How do I know she's good for it?
- You don't.
That's why it's called "gambling."
How's it going?
You boys doing good?
What's Nate thinking?
He's not.
Nate, you got 10 seconds.
- Place the damn bet!
- Don't be cocky, Nate.
All right.
Let it ride.
Boston wins?
Done.
Yeah, baby! Yeah!
That's what I'm talking about
right there!
I didn't realize you were quite that
into basketball.
Basketball? Woman,
we just pulled off the wire in the time
it takes to get a pizza delivered.
This is a big win... big!
They're gonna talk about this one.
Three pointer... he got it!
He got it! Boston wins!
No hard feelings, right?
You know what?
Good riddance.
That bitch is your problem now.
It was a fine way to kill some time.
I come back, maybe we can do
some real business, Jimmy Ford.
You're on.
We got lucky on that one.
- We're not letting him go.
- But we saved the bar.
We're not letting him go.
The night's just getting started.
He goes back to Ireland
and flashes that money at his father,
he'll be back here within a week
with more muscle, heat, and protection.
And then he'll be in every corner.
We won't be able to pry him loose.
How can you be sure?
Because that's what my father did.
No, I know this guy.
I know what he's about.
Right now, right here...
This is the time to put a spike
in him for good. It's our only shot.
Final sh...
Do you have another con
up your sleeve?
No. Yeah. Well, this one's
maybe a little bit more...
impossible.
Guys, let's go to the storage room.
Tara, stall him. Stall him.
- Hey, beautiful.
- Don't "beautiful" me.
Sorry. Men's business.
Money's money, love.
Look, I'm heading out.
- Give you a ring when I'm back?
- You're not going anywhere.
It's turning into
a blizzard out there.
Doesn't look too bad.
I couldn't get to
the corner shop for smokes. But,
you want to sit in the tunnel
for three hours, be my guest.
Can't have that.
Liam's brother here is claustrophobic.
Fair enough.
Let's check
the weather on the telly.
Yeah, let's check
the weather on telly.
Check the weather on wh...
Woman, you did not.
Okay, so we're gonna lure him
into a high-stakes poker game.
Except we have no high stakes.
- And no poker game.
- I got enough to slow-play for maybe
a half-hour or so. Hardison,
have you found Doyle's address yet?
I'm a little busy.
This green blanket have
any special memories?
No. Why?
No reason.
The computer's still grinding out
the cellphone information.
I will hit you
as soon as I get an address.
- I think this thing needs batteries.
- Here. I got it.
Okay, you guys hit the road.
Hardison's gonna text you the address.
Now, Doyle... He deals in cash.
The rest of it will be at his office,
so bring it to me.
His money? You want to play
against Doyle with his own money?
If we pull this off, Doyle is gonna
leave every dime he owns on that table.
Now, I assure you, his father
will never forgive him for that.
What if I can't crack his safe?
Seriously? Come on.
Let me ask you one more question...
Would you even consider trying this
if you were sober?
I'd consider it.
There you go.
Thank you, Chet. So...
We are really snowed in here,
up in...
Wrong side, Hardison.
Seattle,
but it's way worse here in Boston.
The highways are jam-packed.
The turnpike is shut down
at the 495 interchange.
No flights in or out of Logan
for a couple of hours. You know what?
If you are a stay-at-home mom,
you break out the wine and the xanax,
because we are having
snow days here, people.
Back at...
Give me a sec.
All clear.
Is that my jacket?
You know what, man? You're lucky
I'm not wearing your underwear.
And the next time
y'all call me,
it better be for something easy,
like faking a moon landing.
Tara...
Here's what I need you to tell him.
All right, give me a few minutes.
Wait here.
Looks like we have some time
to talk after all, macushla.
Should have played with me
instead of Jimmy the first time.
- Fair enough.
- You wouldn't have got cheated.
- Can I get a rum and coke?
- Wait, what?
He cheated you.
He does it to all the tourists who come
in the bar. Rum and diet coke, actually.
Explain.
The crappy cable tv in this bar...
The sports channels are all
on a local 5-minute delay,
so Jimmy spots a mark, calls a friend
who's watching on satellite,
and he gets the action
texted to him on his phone.
You didn't see him
looking at his phone?
He ran you right up.
Why didn't you tell me this
the first time?
Men's business.
You hurt my feelings.
Stay here.
I'm gonna kick his arse...
Then I'll be back...
Hurt your feelings a bit more.
All right.
- Nate, did you find the money?
- I need you. Tara?
Here's the trick.
We're not gonna cheat him.
He's gonna cheat us.
- Who's Tara?
- Wait, you can't go back there.
- Wait. He's playing cards.
- So?
So, it's a protected game.
You've heard about McRory's.
Everybody comes here.
Everybody back in that room
is a heavy hitter.
- How heavy?
- Local families...
Irish, some italians
from the North Shore.
Sometimes a guy comes up
from Providence.
But you start something in there...
Look, come back to the bar.
Buy Trishie a drink.
Ford's back there playing?
I'm not a bad card player myself.
I don't know about this.
My brother's not so sure, either.
See? Liam and...
Liam's brother are right.
- He's already shown he can beat you.
- Cheat me and nobody cheats a Doyle.
It's not like you can go in
and cheat him back.
He's the best at this.
This is how he makes a living.
Your father never has to know
that you got burned.
Your dad never has to find out.
He was sweet on you, right?
He didn't see you with me just now.
- I don't think so.
- What would he do
if you went in there
and sat on his lap?
What would you do?
I think this'll work.
- This'll never work.
- Of course it will.
Gentlemen,
I have a proposal for you.
- Who the hell are you?
- Mickey, this is Jimmy Ford's son,
Nate.
You anything like your father?
With the guys he's playing with,
pulling something's too risky.
You help me clean out Ford,
you earn 5%.
10%.
That a girl.
10% it is.
Okay, let's keep it simple...
You cozy up to him
and give me either
"Tom"
or "George."
Tom is bad for me.
George is good for me.
So if Ford has, say,
pocket aces, you will...
Good girl.
I don't know about this, Cora.
Listen, I'll take the heat
if anything goes wrong.
All you guys got to do
is just keep playing.
Please...
For dad.
Buy-in's 20 bucks.
Okay. All right.
Blues are ones.
Whites are five.
Okay, now, listen, he may want
to buy in for slightly higher.
Are you okay with making him
think there's more in the pot?
The less I know about this,
the better.
He's in.
I'm supposed to be softening you up.
All right.
- Could I borrow him for one sec?
- What?
These locals don't look
anything like mob guys.
No, they're McRory's friends.
They're all I got.
You actually think Doyle's
gonna buy their act?
They'll be fine, okay?
Everything's fine.
Hardison, you find out where Doyle keeps
the rest of his money?
Using the Liams' cellphone,
I've been able to map
the GPS fingerprints of their recent
calls and analyze their patterns
- of movements throughout the city.
- He led us to a warehouse.
We're in now.
I'm sorry... "led you"?
"Led you to the warehouse"?
I had two cellphones and two minutes.
Do you know who else can do what I do?
CIA, MI6 and me.
Okay, Eliot,
I want every last penny of Doyle's
to end up on that table.
- We'll clean it out.
- Yeah, if we can find it.
Seriously,
you want me to find the safe
for you, too, now?
I got you to the warehouse.
Go find someone to punch.
Now, what I need you to
do is let him win slowly,
until the money gets here,
then flip him.
I want him walking out
of here with nothing.
You do realize this is insane?
You didn't say "impossible."
You're softening.
She warned me you were a drunk.
Yeah, it's different than before.
Before, I used to think I was okay
when I was drunk.
And now?
Now...
I know I'm not okay.
20 grand. Good.
Stay right here.
If Ford walks out
with any money left,
follow him around the corner
and take it back.
Evening, gentlemen.
What do you think you're doing, Doyle?
This is an invite-only game.
- Then invite me.
- Well, it's not my call. Listen.
You know who these guys are?
That's Mickey Donnelly,
Johnny "the fist" Cabella, Danny McCann.
I can't cross them.
Cash plays?
- Cash plays.
- Nice.
A lot more where
that came from, boys.
All right, ante up, gentlemen.
The game's five-card draw.
Mickey?
What do you do?
Let's be interesting about it,
shall we?
I'll see that and add another five.
I'll call.
Just give me two.
All right, we got it.
- Too rich for me.
- You're done.
I'll see you.
Call.
- Well, not for me.
- I only got a small pair.
You're bluffing.
Don't bet your nancy.
1, 2, 3.
Yeah, I'll see you.
I'll double it again.
You'll see me on the next hand.
I'm out.
Who's it to?
- I believe it's on Jimmy.
- Are you out, big man?
Hang on. I'll see you.
Call you.
Nicely done.
Nice hand, Mr. Doyle.
Running a little low there, Ford.
Relax. My niece is coming
with more cash.
I'll buy back in. Not a problem.
I'm gonna get a drink.
All right, ante up.
What's the ETA on the cash?
We're at the safe.
Parker wants to take it out
for dinner and drinks first.
This is a glen-reeder prestige
from the '20s.
So many memories.
- All right, tell her to pick it up.
- Come on, Parker.
I would move a lot faster
if you weren't stomping around.
It's not me stomping.
I don't stomp.
We are gonna do some serious business
in this town, my father and me.
You gents are huge in this town.
We should get to know each other.
- Sure.
- We're already making our mark.
Like Mickey.
You remember that deal went down
with the O'Hares last autumn?
- I remember it.
- You involved in that?
You could say that.
That job would have been a mess
without me.
I was the one who told them
to use cigar boxes
instead of orange crates.
Ford, are you buggering off already?
No, I'm in.
Eliot, Parker, hurry up.
Hey, come here.
Would you...
I can't hear a thing!
- I had it.
- I am trying to work here.
Hurry up.
I'm out.
You out of your league, Ford?
Just in time.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Cash plays.
What's wrong there, Doyle?
Cash plays, right?
Let's see, now.
- $210.
- Noted.
What kind of eejit
do you take me for?
Doyle, what are you getting
so upset about?
- We're just playing a little game here.
- I know the game you're playing.
You're all playing it together...
With my money!
This is my mark.
I've just spent the last year
running the only bank that would lend
to any plank and neddy in this hole.
And I marked every damn dollar
I collected...
Like so.
So you're a loan shark!
I'm a loan shark.
And these are my teeth.
No one cheats a Doyle.
I'd put that thing down.
- You don't know who these guys are.
- I know exactly who they are.
A bunch of local thicks you recruited
for this little game of yours.
Game's over, boys.
Start handing over your money.
I'd put that gun down if I were you.
What, this another prop
for your wee game?
Yeah, and this is a prop I got
from the Boston Police Department.
You point that gun at me again,
and I'll be calling my friend
in the coroner's office.
You're a friggin' guard?
I think he prefers "detective,"
don't you, Mickey?
Sergeant detective, organized crime
division. And these are my friends,
lieutenant Cabella
and captain McCann.
Nice to meet you.
What the hell is going on here?
Gentlemen,
I have a proposal for you.
- Who the hell are you?
- Mickey, this is Jimmy Ford's son,
Nate.
You anything like your father?
What's your proposal?
Okay, you let me and my friend
Doyle, in on your game,
and I guarantee you he will leave
all his money on the table
and confess to at least one felony,
probably more.
So you're telling me this Doyle kid's
gonna march right in here,
confess to a crime,
and give us all his money?
If all goes to plan.
I don't know what kind
of schmuck would do that,
but I'd sure as hell pay to see it.
This is entrapment.
Entrapment? You think so?
What do you think, captain?
As I recall it,
I'm pretty sure he came in here,
put his money on the table,
and asked into our game.
And if memory serves,
he confessed to being party
to that O'Hare job
down by the docks last year.
We're already making our mark.
Like Mickey.
You remember that deal went down
with the O'Hares last autumn?
- I remember it.
- You involved in that?
You could say that.
That job would have been a mess
without me.
It was me who suggested they use
cigar boxes instead of orange crates.
First break we've had
on that case in months.
All right. All right.
Fair enough.
How's about I walk away
with what's mine,
you walk away with what's yours?
And for your understanding,
I'll make a little contribution
to your retirement fund.
All right, now listen to me.
This is what you're gonna do.
You're gonna leave this bar,
you're gonna get out of town,
you're gonna go home to daddy,
tell him that your business went bust.
Or I will tell him that you gambled away
all his profits to a roomful of cops.
You will never set foot
in this town again,
or they will throw your ass in jail.
Understood?
Yeah, and one more thing.
Get out of here.
You're exactly like your father.
So, I guess this is...
All evidence?
Never make it back
to the people it belongs to.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I've been at the movies
all night long.
Me and Johnny here had tickets
to the game today.
Great game.
The ledger?
Every name.
I mean, I'm still gonna take my...
Yeah. Take your cut.
I'd expect nothing less.
- Take it.
- Oh, my god!
I can't believe you actually
pulled this off in two hours.
Hour and a half.
I'm softening.
Definitely softening.
You guys get it squared away?
Yep.
Every last dollar.
Every last one.
On the house.
It's the least I can do.
You guys saved me today.
All of us.
Thanks.
I'm kind of beat.
I'm gonna head upstairs.
Wait, I'm sorry.
Wait, where?
Upstairs, where I live.
Okay. Cool. That's cool.
Except how about this?
You stay down here a couple more hours,
get an appetizer...
- Cora, what's good on the menu?
- Calamari's really...
- Calamari?
- I don't really actually want calamari.
- I want to go to bed.
- Cool. You can, in a minute.
- Y'all want to help me?
- I ain't. This is your mess.
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
What mess?
It's nothing. It's not a me...
- I don't clean. I'm going home.
- You don't clean?
- There's no maid service.
- If it was money, you'd swing that.
- I bet that much.
- I'm not doing it if she's not going!
It was really nice
meeting you, Cora. You too.
Thanks for everything.
He's the one you ought to thank.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
No. It was nothing.
You remind me of your old man
sometimes.
That's just an awful thing
to say to someone
who has saved your ass today.
Come on.
He has good qualities, Nate.
You've just never been able
to see them.
He uses people and takes advantage
of them. Come on, you know that.
He takes care of his friends...
Like you do.
My dad would be really grateful
for what you did here today.
Your dad was a good man.
He was.
But they all have their flaws.
To fathers.
BorderLine Crew on www.U-Sub.net