My sister and I
Began the reclamation
project 40 years ago.
We recover art looted from
Nazi occupied countries
during the shoah.
There is one piece in particular
That we have been trying
to recover for some time.
It's a Gustav Klimt.
I love the symbolists.
It belonged to my father.
He smuggled it out just before...
the painting made it out of Europe.
He did not.
Mr. Ford,
I have searched my entire
life for that painting.
Now we know it is here in Boston.
Oh, well, if it's on display, then
you can make a claim with the museum
- If you think you have provenance.
- It's on display...
but not in a museum.
Mr. North bought the
painting on the black market
Knowing full well its history.
- He's got it hanging up in his office.
- Yeah.
We have tried every legal avenue,
But he even bribed a
judge to dismiss the case.
North owns the largest
software company in the state.
He has unlimited money
and twice as many lawyers.
Can you help us?
It's what we do.
Montgraft & Associates. One moment.
Can I help you?
Speak to the boss.
Yeah, uh, detective, uh, Marlowe.
This is detective Archer.
- Is there a problem?
- Yeah, we have a, uh, warrant here
To, uh, search your, uh, premises.
Your boss is a wanted man, young lady.
Close it up. I think
something's going on.
I don't like this going through the
wrong office. It feels like cheating.
North is one of those guys who has the
latest everything, including security.
His office is one big mousetrap.
What, so instead we don't
even try? That's weak.
This is it. The Klimt is
behind the wall right here.
Mr. Montgraft is in
New York on business.
He probably skipped town.
Halfway to Canada by now.
No, he's supposed to be back tomorrow.
Yeah, well, no, he's not coming back.
And, uh, you better hope and
pray he doesn't come back.
You're just his type.
Oh, yeah.
What do you mean, "his type"?
Well...
It can't be that hard.
You crazy? The man has a pdx-500
rotating encryption system.
Rotating.
Do you even know what that is?
Some other crew might be crazy
enough to tackle that system head on,
But it's an impossible hack.
They would have to tap
the network directly
From a terminal inside the office.
Even if they did get into the system,
They would only have three
minutes of access time
Before the encryption program
resets itself and locks them out.
Timer is set. Three
minutes and counting.
I still think I could get in.
You're good, but nobody's that good.
In and out in under three
minutes is bad enough.
But north's office has a pressure sensitive
floor and thermal detectors
That operate under an
entirely different system.
I guess cheating has its advantages.
It's easier to hack a wall than
a high tech security system.
And now the Klimt is ours.
Did he ever express an interest in
the color of your toenail polish?
What? No.
Did he have wood chipper?
Did he ever ask you to come to his home
To see his wood chipper?
No.
We got a problem.
- What?
- At least we got a painting.
Maybe they won't notice the difference.
"Dogs playing poker"? Seriously?
Sophie?
Maybe he saw the magazine
photo and spooked.
The man bought holocaust
art on the black market
And hung it for display in his office.
You think he care if
anybody knows he's got it?
Guys, just a minute, all right?
We got beat. Somebody
beat us to the punch.
So I just got off the
phone with our clients.
Told them we couldn't recover
their dead father's painting.
Anyone want to explain why?
Where's Sophie? I'm on it.
Nazis!
Maybe they want the stuff
back that they stole.
You know? Secret Nazis.
It's going to voicemail.
I'm gonna try comms.
Sophie?
So--
Hey.
Nate wants to
know why you --
I'd say that's a pretty good reason.
How you doing?
Oh, you know.
Yep, that's a bomb.
I recognize that circuit.
It's motion triggered.
Any sudden movement's gonna
cause displacement of the water.
It'll set it off.
- Is that C4?
- Oh! Parker...
please don't poke at the
motion sensitive bomb.
So, uh... secret admirer?
Well, it's no secret they want me dead.
What do you think, man?
I'd have to reach into
the vase to disarm it.
It'd go off.
Well, let's not do that, then.
Do you have any instant pudding?
The powder hardens the liquid,
Tricks the bomb into
thinking it's not moving.
Should give you a little wiggle room.
- Very little.
- All right.
What's the plan, Eliot?
How fast can you run?
All right. Everybody get
out of here right now.
I'm gonna stay. I'm gonna
stay with Sophie, all right?
We're not leaving you, Sophie.
Look, I appreciate what
you guys are trying to do,
But just -- If you don't
get out of here now,
Then -- Then I'm gonna kill
you myself when this is over.
So just...
just get out!
All right. Don't throw it up in the air.
The device will hit the
bottom and it'll go off.
Just let go and drop it.
Okay.
You too. Go on.
No, I'm staying. I'm staying right here.
Listen, it's gonna be
fine, Nate. You know me.
Sophie.
Please.
Do it exactly the way he said.
www.1000fr.Com
presents
Capture:FRM@∑ÎŒµ - Sync:FRS@”Í‰Ï
corrections honeybunny, chamallow35 and aydin1954
She had a way of taking
care of people, you know?
She was a sister...
she was best friend...
all rolled into one.
I'm gonna miss
you, Soph--
So-O-O-O-O
much, Katherine.
Katherine and I have
known each other forever.
Almost two years.
Yeah, I know that probably
doesn't sound like a lot to you,
But it is to me.
I never really had many friends.
Which is why losing her is so hard.
It's so creepy.
I mean, she's really dead.
I was just talking to her and
now she's just laying there.
- She was just laying there. Can you hear me?
- Parker
I'm -- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, y'all.
What -- What
she really means
Is just, um, Katherine was like family.
And sometimes, friends are
all the family that you have.
So... you
-- You good?
Come on. Just -- Let
-- Just keep going.
You got all hysterical and emotional.
See any suspects?
No one jumps out at me.
Me neither.
What makes you so sure
they're gonna show up?
Listen, when you go through the trouble of
killing someone the likes of a Sophie Devereaux,
You make sure they're dead.
Not much of a turnout, is it?
Jesus. You're dead. You're
not supposed to care.
I mean, is this it? Huh?
Buried in a stranger's
grave, hardly any mourners.
- It's not you.
- It is me.
Well, at least, it's the
me that anybody knows.
Yeah, listen, Kat, you
got to get out of here.
You're gonna blow the con.
No. It's fine. No one's
gonna recognize me.
How's that?
Nate, I'm acting.
The lord is my shepherd,
I shall not want.
It's a shame, really.
So beautiful, so...young.
You know her well?
Yeah, we were friends a long time.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Yours, too.
How do you --
How did you know Katherine?
Katherine?
When we knew each other,
She, um... she went by a different name.
Actresses.
I suppose we should take
something to heart from this.
Mistakes can get you killed.
It was an accident.
Gas line broke.
That is the story. Right.
And now let us be
comforted by the words of...
lets get out of here.
Friend of yours?
Well, if by that you mean
Murderous, treacherous
backstabber, then yes.
Yeah, I thought so.
Seemed like your type.
What are you doing?
Security-Camera footage
from Sophieís apartment.
Trying to see who delivered the bomb,
But with nothing for reference, facial
recognition can't narrow it down.
No need.
I know exactly who's to blame.
Marcus Starke.
Brilliant grifter, even better forger.
Stop it.
It's like you're haunting us.
Parker, I'm not really dead.
- I'm not dead!
- Okay.
We used to work together.
We did the Copenhagen job in '97,
The Berlin Polytech job in '98,
And, Nate, remember -- Remember
that great run in Moscow?
"That great run"?
I chased you for three months.
Well, uh, technically, you chased us.
Sorry.
Are you saying that you
saw other teams before us?
Really just another Nate before Nate.
Let me ask you a question
-- What bugs you more,
Is it the fact that he
was with Sophie first
Or that he outsmarted you?
Moving on.
Starke doesn't keep a permanent crew.
He specializes in whiz mobs.
He puts a team together,
They slam into town for
one high profile job,
And then they scatter.
...73, it's a white...
but usually
they do one same--
They do one smaller job first
Just to work out the kinks in the team.
Like our clients' painting, for example.
Wrong place, wrong time.
Starke must have seen me,
And now that I'm one of the good guys,
Decided to get rid of me, because...why?
Because...
because I know his scams.
Because... I know his favorite scam.
CafÈ and a moonlit terrace..
- The Mona Lisa variant.
- There are security... oooh!
That was the first one I learned.
In 1911 the Mona Lisa was stolen.
And the con man who did it
made six identical copies.
And then they put them
on the black market,
And each buyer thought
that they had the original.
So dude sold the same
painting six times.
- Yep.
- Hardison,
Pull up all the auctions in
Boston in the next two days.
Starke never stays in a
city more than two days.
Wait a minute.
Not -- Not museums?
No, no.
Starke likes to use auctions
To figure out who wants the painting.
He picks who he's
gonna sell the fakes to.
That bit was actually
my part of the scam.
I made that up.
It's good, isn't it?
That's still a lot of paintings.
Yeah, it's high-Profile.
A scam like this requires
a lot of publicity,
Paintings $10 million or more.
He does all his
own forgeries --
Post impressionists, late 1800s.
There. That's it.
Van Gogh.
He has a soft spot for van Gogh.
Let's just make it five.
And that is the Mona Lisa scam.
So we just -- We call the
cops. We have them show up.
No. Starke goes down for this,
There's no guarantee we can get
that painting back for the Mercers.
He even smells the
police, and he's gonna run,
And we'll get nowhere near it.
He did try to kill you, Sophie.
We risk our lives all the time. I...
no. We need to barter.
We need something to trade
for the Mercers' painting.
Such as?
That.
That's what he's come for.
That's what he wants.
We just got to get there first.
Okay, parker. Talk to me.
Present.
How we doing?
What's going on
security wise at this place?
Well...
the usual countermeasures.
Nothing we can't handle.
Actually, I'm more of a jack man myself,
But when in Rome...
thank you, sweetheart. Uh-Huh.
I wish Sophie was here.
She's the one who likes to
play all this dress up stuff.
I miss her.
I'm not dead. I'm right here, Parker.
So, this is, um...
it's what you do, right?
You take footage of us on
cons and you -- You -- You --
Download it into that?
Yeah, I analyze it, I monitor comms,
I scan for a police
frequencies, I --
You had no idea I do all this, did you?
Well -- Do--Does
nobody respect the van?
The van is important.
What -- What is that?
It's lemon zest tea.
I got to tell you, it's
-- It's a little bit --
It's a little bit whiffy in here.
It smells like hard work.
That's what it smells like.
D--
Whiffy.
Okay, guys, I've got the
auction house manager in sight.
Now, if you take his wallet and badge,
It should be a cakewalk.
Eliot, check out the back corridor.
I think I see an access point.
That was some nice things
you said at my funeral.
Wait.
We -- We trust Nate to
make sure the plan works.
We trust you to make sure
we're all ok.
It's a blind spot in the
cameras if you can find it.
Hello?
Who is this?
Oh, I probably shouldn't, but I will.
Got the badge. Just
need to get the wallet.
I said, "who is this?"
Hey. Uh...
you are bumping into my
baby monitor frequency,
So what I'm gonna need you to do,
'Cause little Shiloh
needs to take a nap,
Is turn yours off, 'kay? Thanks.
Your baby is incredibly intelligent.
He just attempted to launch a
multiple variant computer worm
At my baby monitor's firewall.
Guys, we have a visiting team.
Switching to backup comm frequencies.
Eliot, they're here. They're here.
Who are you talking about? Who's here?
Excuse me. Waiter?
Yes, sir.
Hardison, what do
you mean? Who's --
Who's?
Nathan Ford.
I -- I cannot believe I didn't
recognize you at the funeral.
Of course, I was blinded by grief.
Guilty conscience?
Call them off.
Not gonna happen.
You best clear out.
No speak English?
Good to see you. Have a nice night.
My phone.
He got my phone!
Word is on the street that
you run the nastiest crew
This side of the Atlantic.
Well what?
Come on. Everybody knows.
You robbed a bank and
you -- You framed a judge.
You rigged a jury to steal
a million dollar settlement.
I hear that you even
conned the Irish mob
Out of a couple of million
dollars just this year.
Now, that's style.
That's one way of looking at it.
Nate, if you tell him the
truth about us, we're blown.
You cannot tell him about our clients
Or about us helping people --
He's gonna use that against us.
If you know about us,
Then you would know
to get out of my city.
It's still your city, Nate.
I'm -- I'm just
gonna take her out
For one night of cheap fun.
I'll get her back to you in the morning.
I know this style. This is chaos.
Chaos.
I heard you were in
jail. Guess I was wrong.
Hardison. I heard you sucked.
Guess I was right.
Hardison!
I seem to have lost my wallet.
Where's my I.D. Card?
Folks, uh, we're gonna
close a little early today.
We appreciate you attending the gallery,
And if you could please head
toward the exits at this time,
I'd appreciate it.
Thank you very much.
I want the security
detail tripled tonight.
Call the police.
I want a patrol car
drive by every 10 minutes.
Are these motion sensors ready?
We haven't tested them.
Turn them on. I want
everything in lockdown.
Your people blew it.
Uh, my people never make mistakes.
What about Sophie?
Is that a warning?
Take it how you want.
Let's go.
Okay, now, we know Starke.
This guy goes by the name Apollo.
I've chased him a
couple of times --
Infiltration, physical security.
People in that line of high risk
work tend to be very unstable.
We could use that. Write that down.
Now, this person here's
ex-Mossad, sealed records.
Raquel Diane used to work
both sides as a mercenary.
Raquel Diane. I know that name.
You were scared to fight a girl.
She'd mop the floor with
you, Hardison. I don't care.
Seriously. She actually
killed a guy once with a mop.
It's a funny story, actually.
She broke the mop and took --
Eliot. Eliot.
Now, this here's Colin Mason,
Otherwise known by his
hacker handle as "chaos."
As...whatever.
Hacked the pentagon, the NSA.
The CIA computer guys call
him the Kobayashi Maru.
- What the hell is that?
- None of y'all got that? Seriously?
- Star Trek.
- Thank you.
How's this gonna play out?
He's been challenged, okay?
His -- His pride's hurt.
His -- His ego's at stake.
He's --
He's gonna --
He's gonna come up with
a bigger, riskier plan.
Are you talking about Nate?
- Nate, yeah.
- There's no way...
There's no way this crew is gonna get
to that painting before we do -- No way.
We're not giving up on our only
hope of helping the Mercers.
They've waited their
entire lives for justice,
And we're not gonna fail them now.
Yeah, yeah. That. Sure. Yeah.
- But, I mean, who does this guy...
- Think he is?
Nathan Ford, that's who.
Hey, what did he say
about Sophie Devereaux?
Did you kill her?
Don't listen to that. Come on.
We fooled them the first time.
We didn't even know they were there.
This time, we know their
names, we know their...
M.O., we know their
strengths, weaknesses.
No, no, no. I have noticed a
distinct lack of weaknesses.
We know their target, and even
better, we know their timeline.
That painting's going
up for auction tomorrow,
And it gets sold, it
walks out that door.
- That means they have to hit it...
- Tonight.
Now, we've been working
on this for weeks.
We got to go in hot, in
and out before they even --
Tripled security
since today --
We barely had time to check out
the cameras, the motion sensors.
Whatever happens, one way or another,
We are walking out of
that auction house tonight
With that painting, no matter what.
We are gonna get that painting.
No matter what.
Got it?
Got it.
Good.
You got it?
Yeah.
Now...
let's go steal...
ourselves a masterpiece.
Okay. Cameras, all check.
Motion sensors active.
We'll fire up the lasers after patrol.
Head out.
And that's a steal by...
game on.
The security cameras are spoofed.
They don't see anything
until we want them to.
Motion sensors?
I'm still working on those.
Yeah, well, work faster.
Sophie, are you in position?
I don't think I've driven in
the front of one of these before.
Emily!
- Sir.
- Let me in!
What are you doing?
I'm here to see Emily.
There's no Emily here.
What?
Wait, sh--
She moved?
Emily...
Hah hah
I tried to say to her
I'm sorry and I don't --
Because, as men, we're
taught to hide our emotions.
You share or you pay the price.
Yeah.
Next left, two intersections.
Okay, the gallery room
should be directly below --
Uh -- Uh-Oh. Wait.
F-Freeze. Freeze.
"Uh-Oh?"
That's not what I want to hear.
One of the motion sensors triggered.
Motion sensors triggered.
Call the secur--
Oh, man!
A bird got in here.
Turn off all the motion sensors
until we can get this damn thing.
A bird?
How did
a bird --
Uh-Oh.
What's with all the "uh-ohs"?
You wouldn't hit a girl, would you?
I have the cameras now, Hardison.
Now I have the cameras
and the motion sensors.
No...
I have the cameras
and the motion sensors.
Look!
I also have the lasers.
On the right side for
a 3-Pointer. No good.
It's off the back of the rim.
And Watson ends up with
it on the long rebound.
Those motion sensors
going off, that was weird.
Go home. Sleep it off, bro.
We should go hit the main gallery.
No, wait -- W-W--
J-Just maybe wait.
What is going on, guys?
Motion sensors went off, sir.
I already checked that
out. Everything's secure.
And who's this?
Uh... he just got lost. No problem.
Sir, you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm Nathan Ford. I'm with
the insurance company.
Can I help you?
Why don't we just walk
over here, sir? Come on.
I got this.
What kind of bird did you use?
North American Kestrel.
It's small bodied, but its
wingspan is expansive enough
That it sets off the motion detectors.
I would've gone with
the Scarlet Tanger.
Similar wingspan, but the brighter
colors are more distracting.
Yeah. That was my second choice.
That's the wrong way.
You're going to come out on
the wrong side of the room!
Go! Your exit is directly
above that painting!
So I told them, I'm with
the insurance company,
You know, to help smooth things over.
They were just super helpful.
All right.
Blueprints, security codes. Great guys.
And now the lasers.
Goodnight, Hardison.
P-P-Parker, the
lasers are on! Freeze!
Nate, he locked me out.
He has total control of security.
Parker?
Can't move.
Eliot?
Eliot?!
You all out of tricks, Nate?
Oh, I think he has one more.
Sophie?
You're not...
dead, yes.
You went through all
this just to set me up?
Mnh-Mnh. No.
We went through all of this to save you.
No, no.
Stay down.
Now, Hardison.
Can't hack a classic.
A gun?
- Don't move!
- What are you doing?
I got him! He's in here!
Get down.
Not me. Him.
When the hell did the cops get here?
The police are outside!
Come on!
Guys, guys.
This woman claims she's a cop.
Uh, yeah. They're parked outside.
There you are.
Back up is checking the roof.
All right, good. I'm gonna
have this dusted for prints.
Okay.
Caught another one down in the air vents
With this rope and climbing gear.
Come on.
Quick thinking, what you did,
Setting off all the alarms like that.
You're gonna be heroes.
Yeah, well, that's what they pay us for.
They should pay you
more. You are my hero.
Guys, you are the salt
of the earth, seriously.
You are the red in the red cross
And in the red, white, and blue.
I got to go.
All right. Back to your
posts. Come on. Let's go.
This is saving me how?
Well, at first,
I thought it was you
that sent me that bomb
To keep me from ruining
this gig for you,
But then you said something to Nate.
Word on the street is
That you run the nastiest
crew this side of he Atlantic.
No reason to put a bomb
in Sophieís apartment
If you thought she was still a thief.
Well, of course she's still a thief.
She's Sophie Devereaux.
You know, I wanted to
recruit you for this gig.
Did you tell anyone else
That you wanted to
invite me to the party?
Yeah, my
-- My...
my crew.
And, you know, once Hardison got
decent pictures of all of them,
Well, you know, the
rest was, uh, was easy.
It's a match, baby.
Yeah.
I knew that she was trouble
From the second you said her name!
Now, why would you want to kill Sophie?
Come on, Starke.
I had set up the perfect double cross,
And then you want to go
and bring in a new player
At the last minute?
"Oh, and by the way, guys,
That new player is gonna
be Sophie Devereaux."
There's no way I'm gonna try
to out con Sophie Devereaux!
And I hate to break it to you, Starke,
But she was the one that
everybody was always scared of.
It was never you.
I've got a feeling there's a bomb
Very similar to the one they sent me
Waiting for you your getaway car.
Sophie, come on. I'm not an amateur.
I'm not gonna let a keyboard
monkey like that con me.
Where is your car?
And if we hadn't come along,
When, exactly, do you think
you'd be getting in it?
Well, right about...
why, that little son of a bitch!
I don't think he's
your problem now. I am.
Well, what do you want?
A deal.
Yes. Your people in trade for the first
painting you stole, the Gustav Klimt.
Do I look like Moses?
They're not my people.
Your reputation will be ruined.
Starke gets his whole team busted.
So much for the mastermind.
No one's ever gonna work with you again.
And, of course, to top it all off,
We do have the, uh, van
Gogh that you came for.
Oh, well...I mean...
I'll trade you for that.
You really do run the nastiest
crew this side of the Atlantic.
- We'll be in touch.
- Yes, you will.
So, who's Emily, then?
Eighth grade. I was crazy about her.
Little temptress, huh?
Oh, you could say that, I guess.
Go.
I can top that.
Frag grenade, somalia.
Myanmar.
Sniper.
I was a sniper in Myanmar for a while.
- When?
- 2003.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
no. We can't have that.
Handcuffs. Y'all nasty.
So, when I heard this painting
belonged to somebody else,
I was so, uh...
- dismayed?
- So...
uh... more, um, shocked. Shocked, maybe?
Shocked.
Uh, my associates and I just
decided we had to return it.
- Oh, God bless you!
- That's okay.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- God bless you.
Enough of the hugging.
After 70 years, to see justice done...
you are a fine man.
So...where's mine?
You know, the Sophie
Devereaux I knew --
She'd never waste her time like this.
What happened to her?
Well...
she died, remember?
Come on.
It wasn't so bad being the good guy.
Oh, please.
You ran a couple of cons,
You committed about 12
felonies trying to blackmail me,
And you handed over a stolen masterpiece
Just to get what you wanted.
You're still thieves.
And in the end, I still win.
You did give him one of
the fakes, didn't you?
Yes, of course.
He got my phone!
Go, go! Go!
Thanks for letting us use the real one.
Yeah. I hate loose ends.
Listen, I don't mean to be rude,
But my flight to Paris
leaves in 10 minutes.
No problem, sir.
Routine question about
your checked baggage.
Oh, okay, great.
Wait. Um, I don't have
any checked baggage, so...
that's your name, isn't it?
That--
I, um... I...
Starke was right.
I'm not Sophie Devereaux anymore.
I haven't been for ages. I...
you killed her, you
and your silly crusade.
- It's just a name.
- No, they're not just names, not to me.
All my aliases, every
one of them, I --
I know when their parents died.
I know when they had their first kiss.
- I --
- Sophie.
You're the closest thing I've
ever had to a real friend,
And I've never heard
you say my real name.
How sad is that?
So tell me.
Let me -- Let me finish
burying Sophie first.
Finish burying the rest of them...
until all that's left is me.
Just me.
And how long will that take?
welcome
to www.1000fr.Com and addic7ed.com