Mr. Maranjian, please stand.
Do you have anything to say
before the court renders its sentence?
Perhaps an apology
to your victims here in court.
I don't want to take up
any more of the court's time.
Very well.
Mr. Maranjian, you were
a hedge-fund manager...
who supported a lavish lifestyle
by robbing your clients blind...
in some cases, wiping out
their entire life savings.
The money was never recovered,
and you've shown no remorse for your actions.
However,
the government has indicated...
that you have provided substantial assistance
in the prosecution of other cases.
With that in mind
and with credit for time served...
the court hereby sentences you
to 18 months in prison.
No!
Order!
Mr. Maranjian is hereby remanded into
the custody of the U.S. Marshal Service...
to begin his incarceration
at Fort Walton Beach, Florida.
We're adjourned.
I can't believe it.
Easy.
Come with me.
The rich and powerful,
they take what they want.
We steal it back for you.
And sometimes, bad guys
make the best good guys.
We provide...
You're lucky they just
gave you a warning, Ronald.
How do you know my name?
Oh, that. Yes, well,
I think this belongs to you.
- You guys cops?
- Uh, no. No.
We are in the restitution business.
We're trying to help Eddie's clients.
- A little late for that now.
- No, no, no, no.
The judge says the money
Eddie Maranjian stole is gone.
We don't believe that. Eddie liquidated
$400,000 right before his trial.
And it looks to us
like it's still in this town.
And we came here to find it
for you and the other victims.
Nobody wants to see this guy
just get a slap on the wrist, Ronald...
I mean, but killing him?
He's a thief, not a murder.
My sister Natalie, she wasn't
a big shot, you know?
She was a widow.
Her husband worked his whole life,
left her enough to live on.
Then she met Eddie.
He was smart, responsible,
and Armenian, like us.
Yeah, well,
they call these affinity crimes...
people who prey on
fellow members of ethnic groups.
Eddie took my sister's money.
Then she got sick.
Only she didn't see a doctor or tell anybody
because she didn't want to be a burden.
My sister died in a hospital bed,
and it didn't have to happen.
But Eddie, oh,
he's just a thief, right?
Eddie's new address in Fort Walton Beach,
Florida, is the original "Club Fed".
He's got his own nine-hole golf course.
Vegan menu.
This dude can play frisbee with the guys
from Enron in the quadrangle.
I hate those guys.
18 months in a country club, this guy.
Yeah, and then when he gets done, he gets
to come home and collect his hidden cash.
All right, so if this guy
is not afraid of prison, then...
what incentive does he have
to tell us where the cash is?
I'm thinking.
Nate, I hate to rush you, but Eddie goes
to the prison in an hour, so...
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What are you more afraid of
than-- than prison?
Death?
And what are you more
afraid of than death?
Oh.
Nice suit, Eddie.
Maybe when you get down there,
you can trade it for a pack of smokes.
You think people handed me
their life savings because of a...
because of a suit?
Are you gonna tell me it's
'cause you're a financial genius?
I like you, Charlie.
You don't seem like a typical fed.
I'm gonna give you a little lesson
in hedge funds.
I don't put on a suit and say,
"Give me your money."
I do the opposite.
I disappear.
I become a rumor...
an exclusive club
open only to select people.
People like your buddy Bob here.
One day, you realize he's been in the club
for a while, making big returns.
Bob, someone you know, respect...
That's the key.
Because now I've shifted your fear.
You're not scared
of losing money anymore.
You're scared of losing out
on making money.
It's not about the suit, Charlie.
It's about shifting fear.
Not much chitchat between you two.
You lovebirds have a little tiff?
- We just started working together.
- Don't talk to him.
Lighten up, Bob.
I'm just making conversation.
You know,
we've all got our jobs to do.
Your job is to babysit scumbags.
And I--
I have to work on my slice.
What's the matter, Eddie,
don't like rats?
Oh, but you haven't seen a rat
till you've been in a Florida prison.
Just making conversation.
Yeah, you want to converse with me, all right?
These guys, man. I told you...
- you got to stop talking to these guys.
- I know.
I took one of these guys just like him
down to Tallahassee once.
Yeah.
I'm telling you, those rats are as big
as the baby gators down there.
Wait till he gets a good look at them.
Yeah.
You been down there yet?
Oh, great.
Thanks for taking a look at him, doctor.
You got me out of jury duty.
I should be thanking you.
Pupils are dilated.
Mr. Maranjian.
Mr. Maranjian, what state are we in?
Massachusetts.
What's your birthday?
June... June 8th.
No, no, no. Take it easy.
Take it easy. That's it.
- Did he suffer any head trauma?
- Yeah, he got punched out in court earlier.
Oh, well...
I'd say he has a concussion. Of course,
I'll have to do an MRI to be sure.
Yeah, well, he can get one
at the prison infirmary.
- Our flight leaves in about an hour.
- I don't think you understand. No, no.
He's not going anywhere. This is very serious.
This man could have a subdural hemorrhage.
He is not cleared to fly
until I fully check him out.
I'm gonna make arrangements
for a transfer.
- Okay. So, what do we do now?
- Well, I just sent Eddie to the hospital, so...
let's go steal us a hospital.
So, let me get this straight.
- You're a doctor.
- Yeah.
What if someone asks you
to deliver a baby?
- I'd say I'm not an obstetrician.
- What? A what?
- A baby doctor.
- Oh, well...
what if there's a train accident
and there's stretchers everywhere...
and someone points to you and says,
"Hey, you, help me with this sucking chest wound."
I would stick my hand in the chest
and hope for the best.
Oh, you are so not operating on me.
- Okay, do you have-- Do you have the list?
- Yeah
Yeah?
All right, go shopping.
...jurisdiction order 23.
Hey.
I put speakers in Eddie's room
and every 3 feet down the hallway.
So if you want to hear footsteps coming
toward you, you slide the cursor this way.
And walking away...
this way. I made you a master audio file
with all the stuff we recorded...
plus the sound effects. You mix them
any way you want. You're the deejay.
- Looks good. Hey.
- Hey.
Are you sure there's no patients
on this floor?
No. They use this place
for storage. We own it.
All right, well, here's the stuff from the van
plus almost everything from the list.
And by the way, nurses haven't worn skirts
with white stockings since the '70s.
- Sorry.
- Guys, listen up.
Eddie is here for an MRI.
That gives us two hours.
I don't need to tell you that's not a lot of time.
You might be playing multiple parts in this one.
Parker and I are the medical team.
Sophie, you're next door as the patient.
- What are you doing?
- Eliot and Hardison--
- This is my shirt.
- No, give me the shirt.
- Give me the shirt.
- Guys, guys.
No, wait. I- I can't wear a size-16 neck.
Okay, I got to breathe.
I got to wear my scrubs underneath
the uniform. I need a bigger neck.
Just keep your eye on the marshals, all right?
We got two hours starting... now. Go.
- If you don't give me that shirt--
- Listen to me, son, you need those fingers...
to type on your
little keyboard, don't you?
So you know, a bully is just a cowboy
with low self-esteem.
- What was that, now?
- I said what?
My insecure ass is
gonna be wearing this shirt.
Mr. Maranjian?
Time for your MRI.
- Could you remove his restraints, please?
- What?
There's no metal allowed
in the MRI chamber.
I'll cut him loose
when we get to the door.
Relax Bob.
You're only taking off my chains
so they can stuff me in a tin can.
You're not claustrophobic,
are you, Mr. Maranjian?
Because you've got nothing
to be afraid of.
- Lets go over the code.
- What code? We're a couple of cops.
Unarmed cops who may need
to communicate in code.
So look, I'll casually
mention "Star Trek".
- Great. 'cause that comes up a lot.
- It does.
Look, i- if I mention "Star Trek"
one, three, or five--
Then everything's okay
because the odd ones suck.
But if I mention two, four, or six,
then we're in trouble.
So, say I mention "The Search for Spock",
what do you do?
I don't have a TV.
Everybody has TVs.
Dead people have TVs.
Damn it.
You're back again, Mr. Trent.
You know these kids with their skateboards.
It seems like he's getting hurt a lot lately.
Mr. Maranjian...
lets see if we can't get you
out of here in a jiff.
Take your time.
I'm in no hurry.
Pull up your sleeve, please.
- Let me see your wrist.
- Thank you.
Ooh.
Oh, that must be very itchy.
When did you get that rash?
I never noticed that before.
Oh. Really?
Huh-- nurse, we're gonna have
to do some tests before the MRI.
If you could bring Mr. Maranjian
to the eighth floor, please.
Eight?
Are you sure?
Did I not make myself clear?
- Uh, is something wrong?
- No, no, no. Not at all.
It's just-- It's routine.
We'll have you back down here in a jiff.
Nurse, if you could take him out
the side door, that would be great.
All what we got to do is keep
these marshals out of the MRI room.
I don't know why you had to bring
stupid-ass doughnuts, man.
- You're not even ready.
- I am ready. I am 97.10% ready.
Hey, there.
Ted Crichton.
- Bob Corville.
- Nice to meet you.
- And, uh, Charlie Merrill.
- Charlie!
Well, I- I'm Greg Michaels.
It's just a little welcome
from the Belbridge P.D.
Hey, appreciate it.
Hopefully, we'll be out of your hair
pretty soon here.
Oh, don't worry about it, man.
They get better medical than we do, huh?
Whatever happened ********
Oh. Buy me dinner first.
Marshals' orders.
Hi.
I'm Bridget.
Eddie.
I'd shake your hand but...
Wow!
- You a hardcase or something?
- I am going to prison.
Really? Ooh.
Can you pass along
a little message to my ex?
Actually, it's some photos of me.
Ah, this day just keeps
getting better.
How is this supposed to work?
I barely dosed him with rohypnol.
It must have worn off by now.
Especially with the rash.
Yeah, look at him.
He's-- he's totally fine.
This thing--
I need you to read on the...
- P.A.?
- P.A. thing, yeah.
- You want me to make announcements?
- Yeah, could you, uh...
You're really, uh, are selling
the whole hospital experience.
Mm, no. But that's not
what I'm selling.
I get up to use the jukebox...
and this little skank goes
and parks herself on my bar stool.
And I'm like, "No, no, no. I got dibs on that."
And you know what she does? Nothin'.
Like I'm not even there.
Dr. Burns, please report
to the cardiac ward.
Dr. Burns to the cardiac ward.
Infectious disease unit,
please pick up line 23.
Infectious disease, pick up 23.
See, y- you tell someone
they have a bunch of symptoms...
and the information gets processed
in the executive center of the brain, right?
It's job is to question assumptions,
start an argument.
But if you suggest symptoms,
you can bypass all that.
- Like subliminal advertising?
- It's actually neurolinguistic programming...
you know, the gateway to the amygdala,
which is the fear center of the brain.
You asked what we're selling.
That's-- That's what we're selling.
- So we're selling...
- Fear.
- Oh. Fear.
- Yeah.
- Cool.
So, I eyeball the bartender, Casey,
and I'm like, "Hey, back me up here."
You know what he does?
Looks away. Yeah.
And we used to go out. You know, not out out,
but, like, you know, hook up.
So I figure,
I got to take care of this myself.
We interrupt this broadcast
to bring you this special report.
Eddie? Eddie, hey, I'm talking here.
Did you--
Did you see that?
- What?
- It said "special report".
- It was there for a second, and then it was gone.
- Huh?
"Special report", huh?
Hey, maybe someone
took a pop at the pope.
It could happen.
Are you with the center
for disease control?
This is an escaped contagion.
This is a military jurisdiction order 23.
All right, no one goes in or out.
So, I go to the bar, right? And this blonde
who looks like my partner in a tube top...
has a handful
of this brunette's hair, right?
So, the brunette's screaming,
"Give me back my weave!"
W- what is the blonde
supposed to do, sew it back in?
I can't believe what
you guys have to do, man.
You guys are nuts.
Whoa, whoa. Excuse me. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We've got an inmate in here.
Three-car accident on the interstate.
He's gonna have to wait.
Come on.
That's your inmate?
We've got a runaway.
W- what...
- How the hell did this happen?
- 14 years-- I have never lost a prisoner.
I'm not starting today.
- Attention, all law-enforcement personnel.
- Hey, Bob. Bob, Bob, Bob.
Is that the best way to play this?
I mean...
Come with me.
You were supposed to be watching that guy.
I mean we were supposed to be watching this guy.
This is a career-ender, for all of us.
What are you suggesting?
All right, there's cameras
all over this hospital.
Okay, I say we check the footage.
We go room by room until we find him.
This never happened.
- My wife just had a baby.
- His wife just had a baby.
Okay.
But when I say we're done,
I'm calling it in.
- You got that?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- So much for having two hours.
- We're gonna stick with the original plan.
We're just gonna move things up.
Eliot, lose the uniform. Sophie, it's time.
I step away for, like, two minutes,
and you know what she does?
She takes your barstool.
You told me already.
- Is it getting... hot in here?
- Shh!
Anyone, nurse?!
I think I'm bleeding!
I can't...
Ohh!
Ohh! Ohh!
I don't feel good!
Aah!
I don't feel so good!
- What is it, doc?
- Pulse is tachycardic.
I need two units of packed RBC
and two of FFP I.V. Stat.
Start a central line
and get a 12 lead, please.
- What's happening, doc?
- You're gonna be fine...
but I just need you to relax.
Prepare to intubate.
Ready to intubate.
- Doctor, she's bradying down!
- We're losing her.
Clear!
- Again!
- Clear!
We're losing her fast!
Come on! Come on!
I'm gonna try one more thing.
All right, that's it.
That's it.
I'm calling it.
Time-- 6:22 p.m.
Nurse, what's going on?
Nurse!
I'm-- what is going on?!
Hey, nurse!
Nurse!
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Wait. There.
Is-- is that him right there?
- Right there with the, uh... Yes, him.
- No... No.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- What about here?
- No.
- It looks like him.
- Are you sure, man?
- No!
This is the last of the footage.
Looks like Eddie's
still in the hospital.
But why would he do that?
That doesn't make any sense.
Well, if we think he's gone...
then that moves the search outside.
It spreads us thin.
He just waits for the right moment
and walks right out the front door.
- You're right.
- Yeah.
Which means we'll have to account
for everybody in the building.
Sure.
- Greg, right?
- Yes.
- Where's your partner?
- Uh, he's answering a call from dispatch.
He's trying to buy us some time.
Well, you tell Ted to get down here
because you and he are covering the north side.
- You and I-- We got the south wing. Let's go.
- Sure thing. Yippity-skip.
- Uh, me and Ted-- We'll meet you downstairs.
- All right.
North wing with Charlie.
I got it.
Tell me why I just pulled
two sets of car keys off these guys.
- Why would they be riding separately?
- I'll gonna go check it out.
Eliot. Eliot.
Eliot.
Yeah, well, we can't keep disappearing
on these guys. Bob's barely hooked as it is.
Yeah, I'm at the hospital.
The kid's a klutz.
Hello?!
Is anyone there?!
Nurse! Nurse!
Hello?!
Can anyone hear me?!
Please!
- What do we do now?
- Now? Now we wait.
This is the stall.
It's no different than any other con.
Wait, his nose.
Is that...
- real blood?
- I'm-- I'm bleeding!
I'm bleeding!
- Yes. Yes, it is.
- Hello?! Can anyone hear me?! Please!
Did you just give a guy a nosebleed
with the power of your mind?
Amygdala mania.
Almond tonsils.
Is it just me, or has Nate gotten
a little sadistic since he quit drinking?
Is it just me, or does that make him
even more attractive?
Eliot, can you talk?
What's Charlie doing?
I haven't gotten there yet.
No wonder I couldn't hear you on my coms.
Eliot, stop checking out the nurses...
and get your ass down to Charlie!
I'm on my way, all right?
Shut up.
Excuse me, sir. Can I talk to you
for a second, please?
Wait here.
What seems to be the problem?
How did your son break his arm?
He fell off his skateboard.
- He fell off his skateboard.
- Yeah.
That bruise on his cheek's a week old.
The one on his neck is three days.
He get that falling, too?
- You don't believe me? Ask him.
- Why, huh?
So I can hear how well his daddy
taught him to lie?
If you're gonna arrest me, go ahead.
I'll be out in five minutes.
I ain't gonna arrest you.
Randall Trent, 73 Austin Street.
I got my eye on you now.
How many guys
don't even see their kids?
I bet this place is full
of deadbeat dads.
But a man who provides for his family,
who shows his son a firm hand...
he's the bad guy?
Go back to your speed traps.
Hello?
- Who the hell is that?
- That is hospital security.
We didn't have a chance
to break down their schedule.
Okay, looks like someone's
crashing our party. Sophie, you're up.
You know, I once had to play
six parts in "Nicholas Nickleby"...
and Mrs. Squeers and Phib
had a bloody song together.
- Is anybody up here?
- I'm down here!
Please!
Hello?
You have been exposed to an antigen
that is repelled by water.
Do not move until you hear
further instructions.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Why is this a rental?
Hi, I'm calling from the
Patrolman's Benevolent Association.
Yeah, I'm trying to get in touch with two of
your officers-- Greg Michaels and Ted Crichton.
Yeah.
You don't?
Our files must be out of date.
Thank you.
Eliot...
You remember when Eddie got a slap on the wrist
because the judge said he provided...
"substantial assistance"
to the government?
Yeah, well, it looks like Eddie
ratted out the Armenian mob.
And Marshal Charlie-- He ain't a fed.
He's a hit man sent to kill Eddie...
unless duct tape and lye are
standard issue for a Deputy U.S. Marshal.
E- Eliot. You--
Eliot, are you there?
Can you hear me?
Charlie, hi.
- Any luck?
- No.
He could be anywhere.
Check the drawers.
This job never gets
any easier, does it?
No, it does not.
Would Dr. Ralph O. Khan
please report to surgery?
Dr. Ralph O. Khan,
report to surgery.
Ralph O. Khan!
You picked the wrong day
to mess with me, Charlie.
Come on.
Punk.
Please!
I-- please, help me!
Please, somebody help me.
Somebody, help me.
Mr. Maranjian,
we need you to settle down.
Settle down?
What the hell is going on here?
That woman next to me-- She came in here.
- She was fine, and now she's dead!
- She was not fine.
What was wrong with her?
- What was wrong with her?!
- We're trying to find out.
You see, the soviets had a program.
They were trying to weaponize
the Marburg Virus.
It's all very, very, very secret.
And we're finding that the accelerated
incubation period of the dozen cases...
- that we've--
- Dozen cases?!
Yes,
That we've studied...
are all...
it's, um--
Well, we've...
Oh, God.
- Oh, God!
- Dr. Foster!
Oh, Go-o-d!
You think you can just ignore me,
like I don't have any feelings...
like I never sat there,
never listened to you talk all night.
Hardison, have you been talking
the whole time?
I wouldn't have had to if you
didn't turn off your daggum com!
I took care of the fake marshal.
Where's the real one?
Eliot, it, uh, looks like
he's in the stairwell on his way to...
Oh, no.
That ain't good, man.
I'm fine. You know, the rash...
- is localized.
- I know.
I just need an anti-inflammatory, nurse.
And give me--
- What are you doing?
- I'm sorry. Order 23.
Wait. Where are you going?!
You can't just leave me here!
Please, nurse, let me--
Let me talk to CDC in Atlanta.
- I can't. They're coming.
- Who's coming?!
Wait, what's order 23?!
Is it to leave us here to die?
Please, get me out of here.
- I am not sick!
- Don't listen to him.
Variant "U" cannot be released
into the general population!
Shut up!!
- It's not my decision!
- Is it for $400,000?
Is it your decision then?
I have it.
Near here, and I'll take you there.
All you have to do is let me go, please.
No! No!
No! No! No! No! No!
You're making a big mistake!
Everyone's gonna die!
Oh, damn!
Attention,
all law-enforcement personnel.
Code 10-98.
I repeat, code 10-98.
Escaped prisoner
leaving county general...
possibly armed and dangerous.
"Ralph O. Khan"?
Man, you see what ideas you come up with
when you got no blood flow to your brain.
Oh, man. Come on.
Hey.
How's the arm, my man?
- It's okay.
- Yeah?
My name's Eliot.
What's your name?
Randy.
Oh, I like that name.
I got an uncle named Randy.
There sure are a lot of cops
around here, huh?
You know, if you wanted,
you could go up to one...
and tell them
what happened to your arm.
Hey, Randy.
You don't have to be afraid anymore.
Dad knows these cops, you know?
They come to my house.
They'll drink beer.
I mean...
I can't.
Eliot.
Come on, man.
We got to go.
Nice meeting you, man.
Parker, we're blown.
Cops are everywhere.
They've got the hospital on lockdown.
We're gonna have to hug the wall
and wait for the camera to pass, okay?
The exit's right over there.
Thanks. I see it.
A deal's a deal.
So, what happened, Eddie, huh?
You got a little bored during your trial,
you started looking around, and you thought...
"What's the last place someone would look
for stolen money in this town?"
What's so funny, Eddie?
I'm just thinking about all
the crimes you committed today.
Burglary, assault, kidnapping.
I'm going to prison for 18 months.
But you-- every one of you...
is looking at 25 to life!
I know your faces. I know all your faces.
I am really good with faces.
You're gonna pay
for what you did to me.
Right now!
Stop! Hey!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Please!
They're in there!
- Get on the ground! Get on the ground!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
They're in there. They told me I was gonna die.
I was in the hospital. They locked me in a room.
- It's not was you think!
- Get on the ground now!
Okay. Okay, but listen.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I'm the victim here!
They're in there!
Sir, you assaulted a security guard!
You tasered a nurse!
- You escaped federal custody!
- No!
- No, I didn't! No!
- Get on the ground right now!
- On the ground now!
- I'm not trying to escape!
I'm running for my life!
You're not listening!
Please, listen.
I didn't do anything wrong. I didn't--
You don't get it.
You don't-- please, listen.
- Let me explain! Look--
- Yeah, that's the guy.
Can you listen-- Can you listen to me, please?
They're in there. They're gonna get away.
Yeah. Yeah, that's the guy.
That's the guy
that did this to me.
That's what they want you to think!
None of it's true!
I'm telling the truth!
I'm t-- wait.
Look, please, if you'd just listen.
Listen! Please, listen!
None of you are listening to me!
None-- none of it--
That's them! Do you see them?!
That one was trying to be a doctor!
And t- that one's a nurse!
That one's a nurse!
So, here's everything you need
to know about criminal law.
Every crime has two elements--
Actus reus, the act itself--
And mens rea--
Literally "The Guilty Mind."
- Wait. Now you're a doctor and a lawyer?
- Yes.
Now, for escape, the prisoner
has to both break out of custody...
and show the intent to escape.
Wait, so if, let's say, a prisoner was taken
hostage during a jailbreak...
then he wouldn't be guilty of escape.
- That's a perfect example.
- Kiss ass.
Which brings us back
to our friend Eddie...
and how the brain reacts to fear.
In the heat of the moment...
Eddie didn't ask himself
a simple question--
Who would doubt his guilty mind?
I hate the morgue.
These things all look the same
to me, you know?
We're looking for an A-17.
Alpha-1-7.
Oh. Yeah.
Oh, sweet news, guys. A couple of units
picked up our guy up downtown.
He had a mental breakdown
or something...
complain about the plague
or locusts or, like, hemorrhoids or...
Well...
There it is right there.
- A-17.
- Wow, that's great.
- Oh!
- Oh.
- Look.
- Oh!
Whoa!
He lunged at me.
You saw that, right?
I'm writing this in my report.
He's supposed to be dead.
What the hell? What the hell?
That guy.
Oh, God.
What's wrong, Bob?
It's been a hell of a day, Ted.
I got duped by a fake marshal...
and let my first prisoner escape.
That's not the way I see it.
What do you mean?
"A courageous U.S. Marshal
put himself in harm's way...
"by allowing a contract killer
to infiltrate his team...
in an effort to derail a plot to murder
a cooperating federal witness."
That's my report.
This is your collar.
That's good,
but I can't let you do that.
I'm the one that told you not to make the call.
You said, "I'm gonna call it in."
I said, "No, no, no, don't."
So, it's only fair.
Damn right it is.
You and your partner-- You're all right.
I don't know how to thank you, though.
Do one thing for me.
You got it.
Randy?
I'm Deputy United States Marshal
Robert Corville.
I'm from Boston.
I think you and I need to talk.
Who are you talking to out there?
Come on.
It's all right, son.
You're gonna be okay, Randy.
www.tvsubtitles.net