Www.1000fr.com presents
Leverage S02 E09
Capture:FRM@ÏÄ·ç
Sync:FRS@¹ÅµÂ Jingshan
- Mr. Kimball?
- Huh?
It's Ruth.
Ruth Walton.
Gigi?
- No. Ruth.
- Huh?
I'm the charity director.
These are the children
you helped.
You wanted to see them,
remember?
I've been trying to see you for months,
but your lawyer has cut you off from everyone.
What are you doing here?
Mr. Kimball,
listen to me.
Don't let him do this.
You have to fight.
Get out -- now.
- This is a public hospital.
- And this is a private wing,
named after this man, in fact.
- You're trespassing.
- Oh, call a cop.
Okay. Police.
Let's go.
Mr. Kimball, this man --
he's trying to take your money.
Gigi. Oh, Gigi.
No, it's Ruth.
I'm your friend!
Gigi!
- Who's dead?
- No, no. Everybody's okay.
- Can I...
- huh?
I-I...
Oh. Y-You scared
the life out of me.
Listen, you can't just show up
here without any --
You've got to come back.
Um...
I thought you were all
doing fine without me.
Oh, yeah.
No, we're doing fine.
I mean, yeah.
Everything's --
i mean, it kind of went from a quintet
to what we are now -- a quartet.
I mean, it's like,
we still know how to play.
W-we sound good, you know.
But something is, uh,
sounding a little bit, uh...
you know, wrong.
Huh.
Well, I hope that I'm --
I really hope I'm not the violist
because when I was little,
my mum made me have lessons,
and I was rubbish.
I was completely rubbish.
I can't play a note.
- Not a single note.
- Please come back.
We need you.
They need me?
Or you need me?
I, uh...
I'm meeting a new client
tomorrow at 10:00 AM.
You'll be there, right?
- Nathan Ford?
- What?
- Are you Nathan Ford?
- Yes.
I'm Tara Carlisle.
I'm Ruth Walton's attorney.
She's running late. I'm sure you know
that Bennett Kimball passed away last week.
I'm sorry. Ruth didn't
mention an attorney.
W-why are you here?
Oh, that's Ruth. We can talk
about this later.
Hi. You must be Nate.
Hello.
I just heard about Mr. Kimball,
and I'm sorry.
Blue irises.
They were his favorite.
Uh, so, why don't we sit down?
Uh...
so, how did you meet him?
I run a nonprofit.
We move children
from foster care into adoption.
One day, I got a call
from Mr. Kimball.
He said he'd read about us
in the newspaper and wanted to help.
I figured he'd make a donation,
and that would be that.
His checks kept coming,
each one bigger than the last.
Yeah. That's not so unusual.
You know, men like Kimball-- end of their lives,
you know, they're looking for redemption.
Are you gonna just
write down what I say? Is that the deal?
Yes. Ruth, go on.
Well, when his health started to fail,
I would visit him,
show him pictures of our kids.
It would really cheer him up.
And that's when he told her
about his will.
Yeah, yeah.
She's actually doing fine.
- You don't really need to...
- I'm sorry.
Sorry.
A few months ago, Mr. Kimball told me
he had drafted a new will,
leaving his entire estate
to my charity. I was stunned.
Yeah. Did he ever show you
this new will?
No, after that, his lawyer, Peter Blanchard,
wouldn't let anyone see him.
I knew he was doing badly, so...
Last week
I snuck into his room.
He didn't even know who I was.
He kept calling me Gigi.
It's all right.
It's okay.
Well, Ruth, here--here's the thing.
I mean, will or no will,
we're gonna make sure that
Mr. Kimball's wishes are followed.
Yes. The law will see to that.
Thank you.
I'm gonna
bring these to him.
So, I guess we're gonna have
that talk now.
I checked you out,
Mr. Ford.
Half my sources say
you're a vicious thief.
The other half claim
you're some sort of high-tech vigilante.
I like that.
I should put that on my card.
There's a process
to get Ruth Walton justice.
- It's called the probate court.
- Right.
The probate court, where Ruth will walk in
with a sad story and no executed will.
Yeah, let me know
how that goes for you.
Okay.
I know we're in trouble.
But the only reason
I let Ruth come to you
is on the condition that I know
everything you're doing.
- No.
- You're taking me with you.
Wherever you go,
whatever you do, I'm there.
Not gonna happen.
I don't just have a responsibility
to Ruth as my client.
I believe
in what she's doing.
And for that reason, I am willing to put
my feelings about you aside and work with you.
Now, if helping Ruth
is really your only agenda,
shouldn't you be willing
to do the same?
Either I am in,
or Ruth is out.
It's your choice.
They are gonna hate this.
I hate this.
You do not let Vicki Vale
into the Batcave ever.
First, this is my home,
not a cave.
And, second, we're not gonna
allow her up here.
Sophie would never approve.
Call her.
We can't just
keep calling Sophie.
Oh, okay.
I see how it is.
We can't call her, but you can go off
and have a little secret meeting with her.
Secret meeting?
What are you talking about?
I was in Harrisburg,
researching a client.
Wow,
'cause you know what?
Your passport got dinged going through
Heathrow Airport yesterday.
Heathrow's in London.
I guess you couldn't get
a direct flight over to Harrisburg.
Well, it's hard when you do
the same-day booking.
Yeah, 'cause you had to go
with the --
Did you realize that London is the home of
the most surveillance cameras in the world?
- Really?
- Who feels like playing "Where's Waldo"?
- Oh. Yeah.
- I do.
Oh. There's Waldo
right there.
Waldo Ford.
Oh, oh.
Is that Big Ben and you?
Wow. You got twins
and triplets everywhere.
And looky there. 11:18 AM.
Standing outside
of Sophie's apartment,
looking quite pensive.
Aww. He's rehearsing
what he's gonna say.
I've seen him do that.
All right, all right,
all right, guys. Okay.
Yeah. You caught me.
I went to London. Yeah.
I saw Sophie.
And she's not coming back.
Not now or not ever?
I don't know.
And I don't--
I don't think she knows either.
So, uh... that's that.
Could you please take the...
Thank you.
Can we get back to work?
This, uh...
Tara Carlisle --
Hardison, maybe you can just do
a background check on her.
And if everything pans out,
I don't see why we can't have an outsider,
just this once,
tag along. Hmm?
Okay. Why don't
you run it for them?
Meet the late,
great Bennett Kimball.
He made his fortune
the old-fashioned way --
polluting, union busting,
employing sweatshop labor.
His personal life
was even worse.
Drunken-driving accidents,
chasing women, paying off the mob.
Then why haven't
we ever heard of the guy?
Because, to the rest of the world, Bennett Kimball
was a pillar of boston society...
thanks to one
very hardworking lawyer.
Meet his longtime attorney,
Peter Blanchard.
This is
an interesting guy.
He's a blue-blood Harvard law graduate
who turned into Kimball's personal janitor.
Dude would pay off the cops,
pay hush money, God knows what else.
And he was rewarded by being named the executor
and sole beneficiary of Kimball's estate.
See, Kimball didn't have any kids.
He had a couple ex-wives way, way back,
but Blanchard's the closest
thing he has to family.
Yeah, well, I guess this Blanchard guy
didn't count on his client having such a giving side.
It's funny how that works.
What happens to rich people
when they know the end is near.
It's really,
really amazing.
Okay, I don't know that we have
a legal angle to play on this one,
'cause, in three days,
he is going to present the will in probate court
and assume control of the estate.
And our client's charity
gets nothing.
Now, Blanchard was the keeper
of Kimball's secrets, so...
Yeah, so that's our way in,
right there.
You want a skeleton
from his closet.
Absolutely, and there's got
to be tons of skeletons.
I mean, we want something so scary that the mere
mention of it makes this guy run for his checkbook.
So, if that weren't hard enough,
we've got the chaperone
to think about.
Tara Carlisle.
She checks out.
Civil-rights lawyer,
does a lot of pro bono work.
Collects lost causes
like kittens.
Well, she's honest.
Crusader.
Incorruptible.
And one sexy
librarian.
Guys, uh, I'd like you
to meet Tara Carlisle.
She's our client's attorney.
She's gonna be joining us today.
I'm here because I believe
we share a common goal.
I just want to make sure
it's done the right way.
Now, you said you had something
we could use against Blanchard?
Okay, well,
behind these prison walls --
or, um,
prison shrubs here
is Kimball's former
business partner, PJ Orson.
He's doing 10 years
for embezzlement.
Kimball's company paid $50,000 to a company
called Lamond Holdings back in 1980.
That? Yeah. She does that.
It's okay. Go ahead.
Lamond Holdings is a Vegas
front company for the mob.
Yeah, $50,000 used to be the going rate
for a contract killer in those days.
You think Kimball paid
to have somebody killed?
Okay, now what we're gonna do right now
is we are going to go undercover.
- And --
- Why don't we go talk to Mr. Orson?
No, the best lie is the truth, Mr. Ford.
I think if we go in there, and plead our case,
Mr. Orson will want to talk to us.
Mr. Orson,
I don't understand.
If you tell me why you made
that $50,000 payment to Lamond Holdings,
I could write a letter to the judge,
possibly get your sentence reduced.
Reduced? This is minimum security.
I love it here.
No ex-wives hounding me for alimony.
A great bunch of guys to hang with.
I mean,
why would I help you?
Listen, sweetie, I got to go.
I got a cooking class.
You have a great day.
Well... I guess that went pretty well.
Okay, Hardison, Eliot, I want you to
put the squeeze on Orson.
Parker,
case Blanchard's office.
I want to know where he keeps
his dirty files.
You, why don't you come
with me?
I'm about to become
a really terrible lawyer.
You can watch.
I think he is.
Look, Blanchard's here at the same time you are.
That's a coincidence.
No, no, we hacked into his
online appointment schedule.
I mean,
yes, what a coincidence.
Why don't you wait for me
outside?
What are you gonna do?
Make an appointment with --
You'll see.
Um...
hmm.
Yes.
Hi, there. Listen. Jimmy Popodokolos,
Las Vegas. Attorney-at-law.
I'm here to talk to the judge
about the Kimball probate hearing.
- Okay, Mr. Popodokolos.
- Okay. Thank you. Yeah.
- Very important. Thank you.
- Sure.
After batting in the big leagues,
this will probably be like T-Ball for us anyway.
How does it work here?
Uh, well, if an inmate
gets three disciplinary marks,
he gets shipped to
maximum-security prison in salem --
- No, no, no, no, no. No.
- No excuses.
He said maximum security.
- I got bad, bad. I remember things, man.
- It's okay, Roger.
This man survived the riot of cellblock "H," man.
How are you gonna bring that up?
Oh. No, no, no.
Look, look.
Nothing like that
ever happens here.
I mean, half these guys
are CEOs.
- CEOs.
- Ah. For example, Mr. Orson here.
He's been a model prisoner
for the last five years.
- Nice haircut, Frank.
- Oh, thanks.
Uh... yeah.
I want you to meet
officers bagley and hilts.
Hilts.
This is bagley.
They just transferred here
from salem.
Wow, can't remember the last guards
that came here from salem.
- Hey, Frank.
- Well, uh...
Don't do that.
They made the transfer on account of
what happened to me during the riots, man.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
There was a riot?
I didn't hear about it.
I'm not even supposed to talk
about it. I'm sorry.
But the BOP is trying to keep it hush-hush
'cause they didn't even keep the riots down.
They just let the gangs take over.
They was all up in there, man.
Do you know
who the Mexican cartel is?
They was all up in there
with the Aryan nation and the fruits of Islam.
Everybody was up in there.
Colors -- purple, red.
And then they was
just hitting people.
- It's not your fault.
- This is not your fault. All right.
- You can't be that close to the prisoner.
- No. No. No.
- You know that?
- It's can be, but he's in my personal space.
Too bad you're not
working on Sundays.
You're gonna miss
the omelet bar.
- Omelet bar.
- Pardon me, Roger.
- Is this guy giving you any trouble?
- No. Why?
Well, because I just got
the report of an inmate
that matches his description
that may be carrying a weapon.
Can you stand for me, sir?
- No.
- Only thing I'm carrying is his queen.
- I... you got me, PJ.
- Yeah.
- Officer.
- Oh.
Sorry, PJ. You know,
it's regulations here.
Whoo!
- What is it?
- Roger. Roger.
It's a shiv. It's a shiv.
- That's a shiv.
- This is outrageous. Why would I do that?
'Cause you're Aryan nation. You said
you coming to get me. I knew you looked --
He said you was gonna cut my head off
and put it in a little bucket.
Great job screening
your inmates here.
When's the last time someone's
checked this man's cell?
Uh, cell.
You mean his bunk?
Bunk?
- Frank, Frank. You know that.
- Bunk.
That's not mine.
You know that.
- Clear!
- Frank, tell them. Frank.
That man was gonna shank me
over an omelet.
Two eggs and a slice
of government cheese.
Is that what my life
is worth?
You better go
and get away from me.
- Move, move.
- Yeah, yeah. Sure.
My God,
he is Aryan nation.
This is absurd.
I'm not in a prison gang.
I'm in the rotary club.
I don't even know
what to make of this.
Well, let me see
if I can help you out.
You see, two guards come down
from the maximum-security prison in Salem,
and, in the course of two hours,
we uncover the leader of the Aryan nation.
- Now, what does that tell you?
- Huh?
You're sitting
on a powder keg, son!
I have to report this. Yeah.
Y-you --
You're reporting me?
That's two strikes.
One more,
and I go to Salem.
I can't go
to maximum security.
You know, I'm gonna have to
call my little boy,
tell him, "Daddy's not gonna be
home for a while.
Just be strong for your mama.
Be strong, little Lamond."
Holdings.
Okay. Who are you guys -- feds?
Playing hardball?
I'm sorry,
what are you--what?
Listen, listen.
The payment to Lamond Holdings
was made to someone named George Gilbert.
- Who is George Gilbert?
- I don't know.
Blanchard said to keep it to ourselves
because the mob was involved.
That's all I know.
I swear.
I don't want to die
in a prison riot.
Please,
call off your dogs.
Sorry, PJ. Time's up.
All right, so, Blanchard paid the mob $50,000
to kill someone named George Gilbert for Kimball.
This should be
an interesting meeting.
What dog--
Do I have dogs?
Nate, I've been searching for
a George Gilbert with mob ties circa 1980,
and I'm coming up empty.
Are you sure your intel is correct?
I'm positive.
Listen, Hardison,
if we cancel this meeting,
we lose all credibility
with Blanchard. All right?
It's our only shot.
So, please, get me an answer.
I got you.
Peter Blanchard.
Jimmy Popodokolos, uh...
Esquire.
I like to know
who I'm dealing with.
"James Popodokolos.
"Graduated from University Nevada,"
Reno Law School, 1993.
"Took the Nevada bar exam
three times.
Disbarred two years ago."
No. Uh, suspended. Okay?
It was turned
into a suspension.
Yeah. I mean, you can
call them up. I'm good to go.
What brings a suspended lawyer
from Las Vegas to my office today?
Can I just... You strike me
as a Harvard man.
- Class of '77.
- I knew it.
If I'm sitting here,
and I'm thinking
what it must have been like
for a guy like you, a Harvard man,
to get those calls at 3:00 in the morning
from Bennett Kimball --
sports car wrapped around a tree,
another pimp with an unpaid bill.
See, I like to know
who I'm dealing with, too.
What do you want?
I want to tell you
a story...
A story about man
who wrote a check for $50,000
in 1980 to Lamond Holdings.
I wrote a lot of checks to
a lot of companies. So what?
So, well... I happen to know
what the payment was for.
So, you know, we can --
We can do this game,
or you can start
talking compensation.
And let's just get to it.
All right, because it's what I do.
Nate, Nate, the payment was not
for George Gilbert.
It was for Georgia Gilbert.
It wasn't a contract killing, man.
I'm so--
You -- You've got nothing.
Bra, you in there
with nothing.
Better talk about your mama.
Okay, I got you.
Look.
Georgia Gilbert --
She was a stripper.
She moved to vegas
back in 1980.
Lamond Holdings was set up
to pay her $50,000.
- You okay?
- Um...
Georgia Gilbert.
Name ring a bell? Stripper.
Yeah, your blue-blood
client Kimball
fell in love
with a striper, didn't he?
I know
what you did here.
You sent her out to Vegas
with $50,000
that was laundered
through a holding company.
That's -- I bet you didn't
even tell Kimball something.
Or if you did, what?
She ran away?
It was for his own good.
He wanted to marry her,
for God's sake.
Mr. Popodokolos,
I will see that
it would have been a scandal.
But Mr. Kimball is dead.
I don't see the...?
You don't see the relevance?
No.
Georgia Gilbert
was pregnant.
Hmm?
Is that relevant?
Hardison,
was she pregnant?
Like, how would I know?
I can't even find the girl's
social security number.
Just give me 5 seconds.
Can I please have
5 seconds?
How would you know?
She wouldn't say anything.
I mean, you sent her
out to Vegas,
and the local syndicate
probably said,
"We're gonna put you in the ground
in cement if you ever contact Kimball."
What you have here
is a situation
where your millionaire's
natural-born daughter
has come out of the woodwork
and wants a payout.
- Where is she?
- Who?
- The daughter.
- Of Georgia Gilbert?
- Mm-Hmm.
Is it safe to see her now?
Sure.
All right.
Safe to meet her.
We're talking a safe environment?
Oh! Safe!
Uh, yeah.
Come on in.
Mr. Blanchard, I'd like you
to meet Lizzy Cantrell,
born Lizzy Gilbert.
What was she doing
out there?
Um... stealing.
She has a meth problem.
I... do.
I love meth.
But she cleans up
really nice for a judge.
You know, and,
oh, boy, when she starts crying
about how, you know --
Growing up without daddy, huh?
Whoo, yeah!
That's why
I love the meth.
- You're playing me.
- Oh, really? Playing you. Fine.
All right, let's go
to a judge right now, huh?
Yeah, or strike a deal
with her right now.
Strike a deal with her
just like you did with her mom.
Only add a few zeros --
Add a few --
Really?
Bye-Bye.
Come on.
Let's go, Lizzy. Let's go.
- We're gonna go get meth.
- We'll go get you some meth.
I was one digit away
from cracking that safe. One digit.
Yeah, no, this is much,
much better than the safe.
I got everything on Georgia Gilbert,
and I mean everything.
She was born
May 15, 1960.
Graduated St. Mary's.
She failed
her driver's test three times.
She's color-blind. She wears
a size-6 dress, size-8 shoe,
and how in the world
did you know she was pregnant?
Wait, she was pregnant?
Yeah. Gave the baby up for adoption.
What happened to Georgia?
She died in 1985. Cancer.
Tough draw.
Well, it wasn't really a guess.
I mean, for decades, Kimball --
He had a lot of women
on the side.
Avoided a lot of scandal, right?
So, what made him decide to marry
Georgia Gilbert over all those women?
Blanchard paid her off, and Kimball
just thought she ran out on him.
Now, how did you know
that the baby was a girl?
Oh. Oh, yeah. No, that --
That was a guess.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, but, you know,
that's a 50/50 deal.
Why don't you find
the real daughter?
Adoption records are sealed.
Paper only.
I have a reference number,
but nobody?
All this is good up until
Blanchard wants a DNA test.
I got to admit say,
even with my bag of tricks,
I can't rewrite
Parker's genetic code.
Yeah, so we just have to convince him
that asking Ror the DNA is the worst
possible choice he could make.
- How do we do that?
- We don't.
Then this lowlife extortionist
comes into my office
and says that he's found
Kimball's lost daughter.
Yes. He was here, too.
Wanted a payoff.
Now...
I know you and I are
on opposite sides of this,
but I think we can agree
that this Popodokolos fellow?
Has no regard for the law.
He's seedy. He's a disgrace
to the profession.
- I say we get?
- Absolutely.
Of course, once we enter
the DNA into evidence,
then we have to live with it.
So if she is the daughter,
she gets everything.
This file is from Popodokolos.
I tied the adoption-reference number
to the medical records
of one of Parker's aliases.
Social security, taxes,
long record of drug offenses.
Anybody sht of the CIA
Is gonna believe that is Kimball.
I'm beginning to think
we should consider a settlement.
No. Absolutely not. My client's
position is that we will fight this
in probate for years
if we have to.
Years?
So, how was I?
I think you were enjoying
yourself there at the end.
No. Well...
maybe a little.
And now we see if Blanchard
is a gambling man.
Right? Want him to be?
Not a gambling man.
Okay.
Hmm.
Well of it checks out,
so if we get a DNA test --
If a DNA test goes into evidence,
There's no turning back.
This is not an inheritance.
I earned this.
I did things no lawyer,
No one should be asked to do.
She cannot show up
at that hearing tomorrow.
So pay her.
Things happen to drug addicts.
In a strange city,
don't know a safe place to?
Things happen.
Cindy...
Set up a meeting with Popod?
The girl.
Lind will tell you
where and when.
Ms. Carlisle,
are you ready?
Uh, I never thought
i would say this.
But I hope Mr. Ford
because I don't think we have a case.
By the time the hearing starts,
We'll have a check in our hands.
This is where he said.
Nate!
You want this?
Well, he was convinced,
all right.
Good plan.
No, no, no.
This is. This is good.
We get you to the hearing,
???
Just to keep you from getting
in front of that judge.
But just get make sure
that Parker, uh...
Make sure she gets
to the hearing...
No matter what.
They had backup.
They're on the way
to the courthouse.
She can't get to that hearing.
Thanks.
Calling like he said.
You heard shots,
found him like this.
Tell them the blonde did it,
And she's headed to the courthouse.
Are you kidding me?
Look at this.
Hardison,
give me some good news.
Well, I got some news for you.
They just put out
an apb on parker.
It says she's a late-20s
Caucasian women
who shot a officer, she's
an addict, and she's armed.
A trifecta.
Hardison, how good's
the description of her?
- Freeze! Police! Hold it right there!
- Pretty good.
Hold it!
Stop right there!
Chard, your? Just --
Went to inform a drug addict
That we would not
be blackmailed.
She flew into? And gunned him down.
- That will never hold up.
- Maybe.
Is she willing to bet 5 to
10 years of her life on that?
Smartest thing for her to do is crawl
back to Vegas and just disappear.
All right, Hardison, listen?
You got to delay him.
Buy us some time.
How do you expect me
to do that?
I don't know.
Use your imagination.
Just use my imagination.
Yo, my man.
Can I have that?
Yeah.
We're cut off.
We're gonna have to get rough.
I ain't hitting cops.
I look forward to seeing you
explain that.
Anyone besides you
gonna wander through that door?
Your honor, I don't know what could
have held up the other lawyers.
Next person walks through
that door, we're starting.
- Ohh!
- Oh, oh. I'm sorry, man.
- Are you okay?
- Don't worry about it. I'm fine.
I'm good. I'm good.
I'm fine?
No, got it?
Are you okay,
Mr. Blanchard?
It's all right, Don.
Everything's fine.
Oh, thank you very much
okay.
- My bad, man.
- No problem, no problem.
Okay
Hey. You, sir,
have a swell day.
- You, too.
- A swell day.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Oh.
These aren't my keys.
Oh, my God!
??? Naked
for everyone.
Gun. Gun.
- Hold it!
- No!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wait a minute!
Whoa! Stop!
Take it easy.
All right. Be cool.
All right. Nothing's gonna
happen to anybody.
Just settle down.
Not using?
Hold on. Stop.
Chill. All right?
Nobody's gonna get hurt.
Drop it!
Listen, it's probably best if you pretend
that you never saw us. Okay?
Stop!
Nate, I did do, but --
Peter Blanchard,
your honor.
My apologies,
but I was held up at security.
Security is always there.
You should take that into account.
Now, Mr. James Popodokolos
has entered an appearance.
Do we know where he is?
We should perhaps wait --
I do not believe he will be
coming in, your honor.
Fine. We have a full docket today.
Let's get this thing moving.
Nate, I hope you have a plan "B"
or "F" or something? First half alphabet.
Yes, but it depends
on our Ms. Carlisle.
The librarian?
Ready, Ms. Carlisle?
Yes, your honor.
All right.
Eliot, what's your 20?
Every entrance is covered.
Parker's trying to find
another way in.
Okay, Parker,
forget about the hearing.
I need you to do something else.
And when you saw Mr. Kimball last week,
What was his mental state?
He didn't even know who I was.
He kept cag me Gigi.
How did that compare with your last visit
with him months ago?
It was completely different.
He was frail then,
but his mind was still sharp.
Thank you.
No further questions,
your honor.
Your witness,
Mr. Blanchard.
These are Bennett Kimball's
medical records,
which I have entered
into evidence.
They state that he was declared
incompetent over two years ago.
Isn't it true, Ms. Walton, that even if
you could produce this new will,
which you can't, it would have been the product
of a man deep in the throes of dementia?
No. He was fine.
He was fine.
???Olos.
Sorry for my tardiness.
Judge, we're
already under way here.
And I don't want to go
through this a second time.
- Mr. Popodokolos...
- that's me.
...has filed that he represents
a missing heir.
Hmm?
I will hear him out.
Now?
Mm-Hmm.
Yes, now.
Uh, yeah.
Your honor, if you just give me a moment
collect my thoughts, gather my papers, and...
yeah, and, again,
sorry for the tardiness.
And, uh, I like a wise
latina judge. I like it.
Thanks for keeping it going
till I got here.
You can't pretend to be a lawyer
in a courtroom.
Well, stick around. I'm about to
practice micine, too.
Your honor, I'd like to offer
into evidence
these documents
showing a payment
that Mr. Blanchard
made to a Georgia Gilbert,
A woman I contend
bore Mr. Kimball's child.
Yes, your honor.
Mr. Popodokoli--
It's Popodokolos.
Pokodolokos.
- Pop-- Pop--
- Popodokolos.
This man spun
these fairy tales in my office.
It's a shakedown
from a disbarred...
Suspended.
...ambulance chaser from las vagas.
And he says that he found
Bennett Kimball's daughter.
So, I only have one question for him.
Where is she?
I could produce her,
your honor,
if you just allow me to ask
the witness one question,
one question
to the witness.
Please.
- Okay?
- Ask.
Thank you, your honor.
Ms. Walton...
What color is my tie.
I don't know.
I'm color-blind.
Hmm.
Color-blind.
You're, uh...
Ah. Yes. What I have here,
your honor --
These are the medical records
for Bennett Kimball,
which Mr. Blanchard here was kind enough
to offer into evidence...
Which he was. Now, it states
that Mr. Kimball is color-blind.
Hmm.
Now, what we have here is --
It says that Georgia Gilbert
is color-Blind.
On the Massachusetts application
for a driver's license.
Blue irises.
They were his favorite.
She failed
her driver's test three times.
She's color-blind.
Now, it's rare for a woman
to be color-blind.
It takes a color-blind father,
a color-blind mother
to produce a child
who's color-blind.
Wait, are --
Are you saying
that I'm Bennett Kimball's
daughter?
???
You opened the door,
counselor.
It's no coincidence, is it, that you started
a program helping foster kids get adopted.
No coincidence.
Is it, Ms. Walton?
No. I was adopted myself.
Yes, in 1982.
You were 2 years old.
State of Nevada.
Yes.
And the last time
you saw Bennett Kimball,
he called you
by a different name, didn't he?
What was it?
Gigi.
No, it's Ruth.
- I'm your friend!
- Gigi! Gigi!
G. G. Yeah?
Georgia Gilbert.
G. G. Hmm?
That's who he was looking at
when he saw you at that day.
Your birth mother...
The woman he loved and lost in 1980.
Your honor...
Bennett Kimball
didn't call Ms. Walton here
out of the blue
to donate money to her charity.
He searched for her.
He searched for his daughter.
I move to strike Mr. Popodokos' evidence
from the record based on the fact
that I haven't been able to get adequate time
to review these outlandish claims
and prepare a proper response.
- Popodokolos.
- Popodokolos!
I agree, your honor.
And I would also like to add a motion
to compel a DNA test to put to rest any doubt.
That my client
is Mr. Kimball's daughter.
The truth will win out.
Motion granted.
When we?
???
We're adjourned.
You honestly think
this will hold up?
You know, for a Harvard man,
you're not too sharp there.
You know, you tried to keep
Kimball's daughter out of the courtroom,
she walks right
in the front door.
Sorry I'm late.
I was just at your office
cleaning out your safe.
Hey, Parker,
forget about the hearing.
I need you to do something else.
Those files -- Whoo! --
That was a lot of dirt.
I gave them
to your special cop friend.
Oh, who's not too happy
with you, by the way, since you shot him.
I guess you can't pay him off
With any of the Kimball estate money.
What the hell is this?
Hey, you don't understand!
These people are thieves!
???
And if he's Greek, I'm?
So, do you still think law
is the only pathway to justice?
Now more than ever.
I'd like to think that you
learned something from me today.
Certainly.
Why would he go to all that out trouble
to find me and noll me he wasy father?
Well, I mean, think about it
from his perspective.
If he had told you the truth, how do you
think you would have reacted?
I would have asked him
why it took him so long.
I would have been
really angry.
Yeah, so instead, it's like
he got to start from scratch.
And by leaving his fortune
to your charity,
it's almost like he's atoning
for mistakes he made in his life.
The kind, generous Bennett Kimball
is the one I knew,
And that's how
I'm gonna remember him.
My lawyer? I never met
her before this week.
She told me she was with you.
Took you long enough.
- Who are you?
- Tara Cole.
I'm a friend of Sophie's.
She said you guys were shorthanded,
asked me to help. It's all in there.
So. You help out lying to us?
I wanted to see
just how good you really are
and show you just how good I am.
You can consider it my audition.
I bet you're not even
a lawyer.
- Oh. Sophie was right. You are adorable.
- Excuse me?
See how good we are?
Hey, hold on!
Hey, hey!
Guys, guys.
She's right. Sophie did send her.
And Sophie asked us
to give Tara here a shot.
Well play.
Welcome aboard.
Thanks.
Adorable.
Whoa, whoa, hold up. Mnh-Mnh.
Hold up, hold up. What is this?
Oh?
For my cut of the inheritance.
Hey, I'm not a candy striper.
This is my job.
There. See?
We're getting paid already.
It's gonna be fun.
Minor Edits by: VeRdiKT
[SubScene.com]