Leverage
S1E11
COME TO BED.
IT'S 4:00 A.M., AND YOU HAVE TO
BE AT WORK IN THREE HOURS.
I KNOW.
I'M ALMOST FINISHED.
YOU SAID THAT
TWO HOURS AGO.
FIVE MORE MINUTES.
I'M COUNTING.
ENOUGH STUDYING.
GLORIA.
GLORIA!
ERNESTO.
ERNESTO!
NO!
NO-O!
I DID MY JOB.
YOU TOLD ME TO GET US
INTO THE PENTHOUSE.
YEAH, BY FOLLOWING
MY PLAN, PARKER.
-WHAT?
-BY GETTING US ALL IN SAFELY.
DID THE ELEVATOR DECAPITATE YOU?
DID IT DECAPITATE YOU?
ACTUALLY, FROM THIS ANGLE,
IT LOOKS PRETTY CLOSE ON
THE DECAPITATION.
A4.
YOU NEED TO
GO TALK TO HER.
IT'S NOT THE FIRST TIME
SHE'S GONE LOCO.
-PARKER?
-I'M SERIOUS.
PARKER, I THINK
WHAT EVERYONE'S FEELING
IS THAT IF YOU WANT TO TAKE
INSANE RISKS ON YOUR OWN TIME,
THEN GO AHEAD,
BUT WHEN WE'RE ON A JOB,
YOU HAVE TO CONSIDER
THE REST OF US.
-EXCUSE ME.
-THIS ISN'T FOR ME.
IT'S ADDRESSED TO SOMEBODY
NAMED ALICE WHITE.
YOUA REALICE WHITE.
IT'S ONE OF THE ALIASES
I MADE FOR YOU --
VEGETARIAN, BOOKKEEPER.
SHE HAD A PRETTY WILD TIME AT
HER SISTER'S WEDDING IN PHOENIX.
YOU SHOULD CHECK OUT
HER FACEBOOK PAGE.
ALICE WHITE
HAS JURY DUTY.
DAMN, I AM GOOD.
YEAH,
CONGRATULATIONS.
ALICE THANKS YOU
FOR GETTING HER OUT OF IT.
NO. NO.
JURY DUTY -- A PLACE WHERE
YOU HAVE TO FOLLOW INSTRUCTIONS.
WHERE YOU HAVE TO CONSIDER
OTHER PEOPLE'S POINT OF VIEW.
-THERE'S GONNA BE
NORMAL PEOPLE THERE, NATE.
-NO, NO, NO.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING OUT OF THIS.
ALICE WHITE IS REPORTING
FOR JURY DUTY.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture: ив╬х
Sync:VinE
ERNESTO VARGAS WAS A HUSBAND,
A FATHER OF TWO DAUGHTERS,
A WAREHOUSE MANAGER,
AND HE WENT
TO NIGHT SCHOOL.
HE NEEDED MORE ENERGY.
SO HE BOUGHT THIS.
FastLife.
IT'S AN "ALL-NATURAL
ENERGY SUPPLEMENT"
THAT WAS PRODUCED BY THAT MAN,
WILLIAM QUINT.
WE'LL SHOW THAT FastLife CAUSED
ERNESTO VARGAS' FATAL HEART ATTACK,
AND THAT MR. QUINT KNEW THE
DANGERS THAT HIS PRODUCT POSED
WHEN HE PUT IT ON THE MARKET.
ALL ERNESTO WANTED
WAS MORE TIME.
AND THAT'S THE ONLY THING
WE CAN'T GIVE HIM.
I HOPE THE REST OF THIS CASE
IS THIS GOOD.
WHAT'D YOU HAVE FOR BREAKFAST?
YOU SMELL LIKE GRAVY.
Order.
MR. LOUIS, ARE YOU READY TO MAKE
YOUR OPENING STATEMENT?
YES, YOUR HONOR.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
DO IT JUST LIKE
WE REHEARSED, HENRY.
IT'S BEEN TAILOR-MADE
FOR THIS JURY.
We all want to believe that future
tragedies can be prevented
IF WE HOLD SOMEONE,
ANYONE ACCOUNTABLE.
Maintain eye contact.
YOU'RE LOSING
JUROR NUMBER 4.
BUT COMMON SENSE
WILL TELL YOU
THAT NOT ALL TRAGEDIES
CAN BE PREVENTED.
AND WHEN YOU RUSH
TO JUDGMENT...
lives are ruined,
and an honest businessman can
have his life's work destroyed.
WHO IS SHE?
WHAT IS SHE LOOKING AT?
ALICE WHITE --
BOOKKEEPER.
SHE'S BEEN ZONING IN AND OUT
ALL MORNING. COULD BE CONFUSED.
NOTHING'S MORE DANGEROUS
THAN THE CONFUSED
WHEN THEY THINK
THEY KNOW SOMETHING.
SO, MY VIDEO WALL PLUS DIRECTV
NFL SUNDAY TICKET IN HD.
-INCREDIBLE.
-WHAT DO YOU THINK?
-GREAT.
-RIGHT.
-YEAH.
-RIGHT?
I THINK IT'S FUNNY.
YOU KNOW, IT REMINDS ME
A BIT OF RUGBY,
EXCEPT -- WELL, YOU AMERICANS,
YOU WEAR THE HELMETS
AND THE PADS AND EVERYTHING
SO YOU DON'T GET HURT.
-OH, YOU DIDN'T.
-WHAT?
PARKER, HOW IS
JUROR NUMBER 6 TODAY?
-GOOD. OKAY, HERE IT IS.
-FUMBLE!
I THINK THERE'S SOMETHING DIRTY
GOING ON WITH THIS TRIAL
AND THE WOMAN WHO LOST HER HUSBAND'S
GONNA GET HURT EVEN WORSE,
AND THAT WE SHOULD, UM,
YOU KNOW, GET INVOLVED.
INVOLVED?
WHAT -- WHAT DO YOU --
NO, NO, NO. NO, NO, NO.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THEY HAD HIDDEN CAMERAS,
AND THE LAWYERS HAD COMMS
LIKE OUR COMMS.
FIRST, MOVE.
SECOND,
NOBODY HAS OUR COMMS.
PARKER, LISTEN, THERE IS NOT
SOME EVIL CONSPIRACY
LURKING BEHIND THE CURTAIN
OF EVERY ROUTINE CIVIC ACTIVITY.
I MAKE OUR COMMS.
ME. I MAKE 'EM.
AIN'T NOBODY
GOT OUR COMMS.
NOW, WHAT'S HAPPENING IS,
YOU'RE ON A BORING JURY TRIAL.
OKAY?
NOW, COULD YOU...
PARKER! JUST...
YOU KNOW,
SHE'S NEVER DONE THAT BEFORE.
WHAT, STORMED OUT?
COME ON.
NO.
ASKED FOR OUR HELP.
WHAT?
LISTEN, THERE IS A REASON
WE PUT HER IN A JURY TRIAL.
YOU KNOW, MAN, WHEN I WAS A --
WHEN I WAS A KID,
I WAS LIKE 8 YEARS OLD,
I HAD A FOSTER MOM
WHO WAS JEHOVAH'S WITNESS.
SHE USED TO DRESS ME UP
IN A SUIT AND A BOW TIE
AND TAKE ME DOOR-TO-DOOR
TO SPREAD THE WORD.
BLACK NEIGHBORHOODS, WHITE
NEIGHBORHOODS -- DIDN'T MATTER.
I WOULD KICK,
I'D SCREAM, OR WHATEVER,
BUT SHE WOULD SAY
"ALEC, YOU NEED TO LEARN
HOW TO TALK TO PEOPLE."
SEE, EVERYTHING I LEARNED
ABOUT PEOPLE,
I LEARNED RINGING DOORBELLS
AND -- AND --
AND BEING IN A BOW TIE.
PARKER NEVER HAD THAT.
I MEAN, JUMPING FROM
A SKYSCRAPER, SHE'S COOL.
BUT MAKING SMALL TALK?
THAT'S -- IT'S LIKE PURE TERROR.
JUST CUT HER
SOME SLACK.
HOW ABOUT THEM COWBOYS?
WHAT'D I MISS?
NOTHING.
ALL RIGHT. UH, ELIOT,
GONNA NEED YOU TO GO WITH PARKER
TO CHECK SOMETHING OUT.
ALL RIGHT.
-YEAH.
-NOW.
-RIGHT NOW?
-YEAH, RIGHT NOW. YEAH.
-LIKE, NOW?
-YEAH.
JUST GO GET PARKER.
THANKS FOR THE BEER.
Tell you what,
THIS IS NOT HAPPENIN', BUBBA.
YOU AIN'T TAKIN' MY BEER.
I'M OUTSIDE.
YOU'RE LATE.
HEY, I JUST SPENT EIGHT HOURS
SITTING IN A PLASTIC CHAIR
WHILE SOME AMBULANCE CHASER
CALLED ME A KILLER.
I PAID FOR THAT CHAIR.
YOU DON'T LIKE IT, GO HOME
AND SUCK BACK SOME INCENSE.
ALWAYS A PLEASURE,
MS. EARNSHAW.
WHO'S EARNSHAW?
HARDISON?
I'm on it.
THINK MAYBE I SHOULD SETTLE
THIS CASE AND BE DONE WITH IT.
IT'S NOT
UP TO YOU ANYMORE.
YOU WANT TO BUY MY COMPANY,
BUY IT.
YOU DON'T, DON'T.
BUT IT'S MY TOCHES
THAT'S ON THE LINE HERE --
THE ONLY THING
YOU HAVE ON THE LINE
IS YOUR PENNY-ANTE
GRANOLA COMPANY.
I COULD LOSE EVERYTHING.
WINNING IS THE ONLY OPTION.
YOU GO BEHIND MY BACK
AND TRY TO SETTLE THIS CASE,
I WILL BURY YOU.
ARE WE CLEAR?
THAT KIND OF JURY PROFILING
COSTS A FORTUNE.
TRIAL, THEY SAID
QUINT'S COMPANY WAS TINY.
NOW WE SEE...
WHAT THEY SEE.
DAMN.
THEY HACKED
THE COURTROOM'S SECURITY FEED
AND PLANTED
THEIR OWN CAMERAS.
THAT'S WHAT
I WOULD'VE DONE.
THEY GOT THERE FIRST.
ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE A NEW CLIENT.
APPARENTLY, THERE IS
AN EVIL CONSPIRACY LURKING
BEHIND THE CURTAIN
OF EVERY ROUTINE
ET CETERA, ET CETERA,
ET CETERA.
GLORIA VARGAS
IS SUING WILLIAM QUINT
OVER THE WRONGFUL DEATH
OF HER HUSBAND.
NOW, IT SHOULD BE A SIMPLE,
LOW-STAKES WRONGFUL DEATH SUIT.
BUT QUINT HAS HELP.
TOBEY EARNSHAW,
OF EARNSHAW PHARMACEUTICALS.
FATHER FOUNDED THE COMPANY,
AND HE'S STILL C.E.O.
WHY DOES A DRUG HEIRESS
CARE ABOUT  A LAWSUIT
AGAINST A TINY
SUPPLEMENTS COMPANY?
'CAUSE WITHOUT TELLING DADDY
OR THE EXECUTIVE BOARD,
EARNSHAW SANK $20 MILLION
INTO R&D FOR FastLife
IN ANTICIPATION
OF BUYING THE COMPANY.
SEE, LIVE HERBALLY
LOSES THIS TRIAL,
THEN THOUSANDS OF OTHER
LAWSUITS JUST LIKE IT
WILL FALL OUT OF THE SKY.
THE BUYOUT FALLS THROUGH.
YEAH, AND EARNSHAW'S
OUT ON HER ASS.
TO PROTECT AN INVESTMENT
SHE KNOWS KILLS PEOPLE,
EARNSHAW IS GOING TO DESTROY
THIS YOUNG WIDOW.
WELL, THEN, WE HAVE TO WIN
THE COURT CASE FOR GLORIA.
WE CAN'T.
NO, GUYS, WE GOT INTO THIS
WAY TOO LATE.
I MEAN,
THE BEST WE CAN HOPE FOR
IS TO CON QUINT
INTO A SETTLEMENT.
WAIT A MINUTE. EARNSHAW TOOK
SETTLEMENT OFF THE TABLE.
OH. THEN, YOU KNOW, WE TRY TO
CONVINCE HIM TO PUT IT BACK ON.
HELLO.
EARNSHAW JUST RAN A CREDIT CHECK
ON ALICE WHITE.
WHO'S ALICE WHITE?
-YOU ARE!
SHE'S GONNA BUY THE JURY.
NOT IF WE...
STEAL IT FIRST.
WHO PLAYS CHESS?
I PLAY.
OF COURSE YOU DO.
A CHESS GAME HAS
THREE STAGES, RIGHT?
I MEAN, YOU GOT YOUR OPENING,
MIDDLE, AND END GAME.
IN THE OPENING, YOU WANT TO
TAKE CONTROL OF THE BOARD,
AND YOU WANT TO
LINE UP YOUR ATTACK
PROTECT THE KING,
WHICH, IRONICALLY,
IS THE WEAKEST PIECE YOU HAVE.
YOU KNOW THIS IS A TRIAL,
RIGHT?
EARNSHAW HAS ALREADY OVERPOWERED
THE VARGAS DEFENSE,
AND SHE'S BUYING A JUROR.
NOW, THAT IS A FAST,
AGGRESSIVE OPENING GAMBIT.
REALLY IS. SO, WE NEED TO
BREAK HER MOMENTUM HERE.
SO, PARKER, WHAT I NEED YOU TO DO
IS I NEED YOU TO --
WE NEED TO STALL THE TRIAL.
SO, YOU'RE GOING TO GET ALL
OF THOSE JURORS TO TRUST YOU.
UM...HOW?
CONVERSATION. COMPLIMENTS.
YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
-OKAY.
-Okay.
AND THIS IS EMILY.
SHE'S THE ELDEST.
AND HER SISTER ANNE.
AND LITTLE CHARLOTTE --
SHE'S THE BABY OF THE FAMILY.
THAT ONE'S REALLY CUTE!
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH THAT ONE?
IT LOOKS LIKE A DOG
IN A BABY SUIT.
FIGURE OUT WHAT
HER LINE OF ATTACK IS.
GO DIGGING.
FIGURE OUT WHO HER PAWN
ON THE JURY IS.
I'VE GOT FINANCIAL TRACES
ON ALL THE JURORS' ACCOUNTS.
AND IF IT SHOWS UP
AS CASH IN A SUITCASE?
GO DIGGING.
IT'S YOUR TURN
TO BE IN THE DUMPSTER.
NO, MAN, NO. I-I HAVE --
I HAVE PEANUT ALLERGIES.
WHAT IF SOMEBODY THREW IN
SOME EXTRA CRUNCHY SKIPPY?
THEN, YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST
A- ALL UP IN MY VOCAL AREA, MAN.
DO YOU WANT TO GIVE ME
MOUTH-TO-MOUTH?
NO, NONE OF US WANT THAT.
HELL NO.
HEADS UP.
SOPHIE...
GO AFTER HER KING.
OLIVIA SMITHE-PATEL,
CHIEF MARKETING OFFICER
OF MUMBAI INTERNATIONAL LIMITED.
MUMBAI? INDIAN?
HALF -- BRITISH FATHER,
INDIAN MOTHER.
NAMASTE.
I'M VERY SPIRITUAL.
YOUR REPUTATION
PRECEDES YOU.
I HAVE A ZEN GARDEN.
MUMBAI IS LOOKING
TO BRANCH OUT
FROM PRESCRIPTION MEDICATIONS
INTO THE HERBAL-SUPPLEMENT MARKET.
WE WERE THINKING AN ACQUISITION
WOULD BE THE BEST PLAY.
YOU WANT TO
BUY MY COMPANY?
I'M SORRY.
I ALREADY HAVE ANOTHER OFFER.
NO, WHAT YOU HAVE
IS A JOKE.
NOW YOU HAVE AN OFFER.
I RETAIN STOCK OPTIONS,
CONTROL OF THE COMPANY.
-THAT'S --
-MUCH, MUCH BETTER
THAN EARNSHAW'S OFFERING YOU.
MR. QUINT, EVERY C.E.O.
OF EVERY COMPANY
THAT EARNSHAW'S BOUGHT
HAS BEEN FORCED INTO EARLY RETIREMENT.
AS SOON AS SHE BUYS YOU OUT,
SHE KICKS YOU OUT.
WE'D PREFER TO KEEP THE MAN
THAT BUILT THIS COMPANY,
HONOR THE SPIRIT
THAT BUILT THIS HOUSE.
UH, HOW MUCH MONEY
ARE WE TALKING?
YOU S-- YOU SERIOUS?
I FLEW 14,000 KILOMETERS
TO GIVE YOU THAT NUMBER.
IT'S A VERY LONG TRIP.
THAT'S A VERY LONG NUMBER.
QUINT'S ON THE HOOK --
HE WENT TO MUMBAI INTERNATIONAL LIMITED'S
WEBSITE TO CHECK OUT SOPHIE.
IT'S A REAL COMPANY?
COVER STORY'S BETTER
THAT WAY.
JUST, UH, CHANGED THIS...
TO THIS.
NICE.
ANYTHING IN THE GARBAGE?
UH, JUROR NUMBER 1,
THAT'S THE JURY FOREMAN.
THERE'S NOTHING HINKY
IN HIS FINANCES,
BUT IN HIS GARBAGE, I FOUND
AN ENVELOPE FROM PASSPORT,
RECEIPT FOR TWO TICKETS TO FIJI,
LUGGAGE, SOME OF THESE.
YEAH, WRAPPERS
FOR U.S. CASH, YEAH.
SOMEBODY CAME INTO CASH
AND JUST HAD TO COUNT IT.
THEY'VE PAID OFF
THE JURY FOREMAN.
OKAY, TODAY DID NOT GO WELL,
BUT THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW,
WE LEARN WHEN WE FAIL.
WE'RE GONNA --
WE'RE GONNA GO BACK TO BASICS,
AND WE'RE GONNA DO
A LITTLE ROLE-PLAYING.
GONNA START WITH --
WITH PERSUASION TECHNIQUES.
SO, ELIOT HAS AN APPLE.
ALICE HAS AN ORANGE.
I LOVE APPLES.
APPLES ARE MY FAVORITE FRUIT.
GOOD FOR YOU, SPARKY.
I- I DON'T HAVE TO SIT HERE
-AND TAKE THIS CRAP.
-GO ON. JUST DO IT FOR ME.
YOU HAVE AN ORANGE,
ALL RIGHT?
NOW, CONVINCE ME
THAT I WANT THE ORANGE,
NOT THE APPLE.
I'M GONNA TAKE A BITE.
I PUT A RAZOR BLADE
IN THAT APPLE.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
MAYBE.
BUT DO YOU KNOW WHATDOESN'T
HAVE A RAZOR BLADE IN IT?
THIS ORANGE.
DON'T YOU WANT IT?
YOU FELL FOR THAT?
THANKS.
THE FOREMAN'S THE PAWN?
MAKE HIM GO AWAY,
PARKER.
SORRY. EXCUSE ME.
Help you?
EXCUSE ME.
HEY, DO YOU HAVE THE TIME?
HAS ANYONE SEEN MY WATCH?
IT WAS A GIFT
FROM MY GRANDFATHER.
MY LOCKET!
SOMEONE STOLE MY LOCKET!
-OH, MY!
-AW, GEESH!
MY WALLET!
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHERE THAT CAME FROM.
He stole our stuff.
I DIDN'T DO THAT!
THANKS.
SORRY. EXCUSE ME.
HELP YOU?
EXCUSE ME.
SOMEBODY ELSE
LOSE A WATCH?
THERE YOU GO.
HEY, I KNOW WHO OUR
NEW FOREMAN SHOULD BE.
HERE'S TO THE NEW FOREMAN.
-TO ALICE.
Jury foreman?
I KNOW.
YOU SAID
IT WAS IN THE BAG!
MR. QUINT,
I AM WHO I AM TODAY
BECAUSE I KNOW HOW TO TURN
EVERY FAILURE INTO A SUCCESS.
I WORK EVERY ANGLE.
I ANTICIPATE EVERY CONTINGENCY.
-HELLO?
-Mr. Richards.
I'D LOVE TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOME EXCITING
RETIREMENT OPPORTUNITIES.
Where's the Vargas lawyer?
I HAVE NO IDEA. THE BAILIFF
JUST SAID HE DIDN'T SHOWED UP.
YOU HEARD?
WHAT HAPPENS IF THE VARGAS'
LAWYER JUST DISAPPEARS?
MISTRIAL.
BUT EARNSHAW
NEED A WIN.
CLOSE ENOUGH. MISTRIAL MEANS
THEY'LL HAVE TO START ALL OVER AGAIN.
GLORIA VARGAS CAN'T AFFORD
ANY MORE LAWYERS.
SHE'LL HAVE TO
DROP THE SUIT.
WE TAKE A PAWN.
EARNSHAW TAKES A KNIGHT.
LUCKY FOR US,
WE HAVE MORE THAN ONE.
ALL RISE. ??
THE HONORABLE
JUDGE KELLY DURHAM.
Be seated.
MRS. VARGAS, DO YOU HAVE ANY
IDEA WHERE YOUR ATTORNEY IS?
MRS. VARGAS,
I MAY HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO DECLARE A MISTRIAL.
FORGIVE MY TARDINESS,
YOUR HONOR.
I'LL BE ACTING AS ATTORNEY
FOR THE PLAINTIFF.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
I'M JOSEPH MILLER. I'M YOUR NEW
COURT-APPOINTED ATTORNEY.
THEY HAVE COURT-APPOINTED
ATTORNEYS FOR CIVIL LAWSUITS?
DO YOU TRUST YOUR GOVERNMENT,
MS. VARGAS?
WHY, YES, OF COURSE.
THEN LET ME HANDLE THIS.
HE'S NEVER GONNA WIN
THIS CASE.
-HE JUST HAS TO STALL FOR TIME...
-PERMISSION TO APPROACH THE BENCH?
...LONG ENOUGH FOR QUINT
TO TAKE YOUR OFFER.
Come in up.
UH, Y-YOUR HONOR,
I DON'T LIKE TO TRASH-TALK,
BUT MY PREDECESSOR
WAS NOT AS THOROUGH
AS HE COULD HAVE BEEN
WHEN PRESENTING THIS CASE.
FOR EXAMPLE, I, UH --
I WOULD LIKE TO ADD SOME
WITNESSES TO THE WITNESS LIST.
IS -- IS THAT
A HIGH SCHOOL YEARBOOK?
YES, IT IS.
YOU SEE, MY INTENT IS TO SHOW
THAT ERNESTO VARGAS LED AN ACTIVE
AND VERY VIBRANT LIFE,
AND THESE 430 PEOPLE
WILL TESTIFY
THAT HE DID SO
EVEN AS A YOUTH.
MOTION DENIED.
O- OKAY.
UM...YOU KNOW,
I HAVE PHOTOS
THAT I WOULD LIKE
TO INTRODUCE
FROM A VACATION --
THE OPPOSING COUNSEL WATER-SKIING.
IT'S ALL FROM HIS WEBSITE --
VERY PUBLIC.
I OBJECT.
AS WELL YOU SHOULD.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE DOING THAT.
SERIOUSLY?
I MEAN, HE DOESN'T
HAVE THE BODY.
COUNSELOR,
ANYTHING ELSE?
UH, ACTUALLY...
I HAVE
QUITE A FEW MORE THINGS.
I JUST FEEL LIKE HE WENT ON
AND ON FOREVER THIS MORNING.
I'M STARVING!
ME TOO.
I COULD KILL FOR A STEAK.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
A VEGETARIAN.
OH, YEAH.
I MEANT A BEAN STEAK --
A STEAK
MADE OUT OF BEANS,
HELD TOGETHER
WITH SOY GLUE.
ALICE,
WE ALL CHEAT A LITTLE.
I MEAN,
I'M A NUTRITIONIST,
AND I SPEND ALL DAY
TEACHING PEOPLE TO EAT HEALTHY.
BUT IF I HAVE A BAD DAY,
I GO HOME AND PLOW
INTO A TUB OF ICE CREAM.
WAIT!
WAIT A SECOND.
THAT WAS A SECRET. YOU JUST
TOLD ME A SECRET, RIGHT?
THAT'S SOMETHING
FRIENDS DO.
WELL, I GUESS SO.
YOU'RE THE NICEST ONE HERE.
REALLY?
I MEAN, THANKS.
WHO IS THIS GUY?
I WANT EVERY FRAME
OF THIS FOOTAGE ANALYZED.
I WANT THE ANALYSTS
WORKING OVERNIGHT.
I NEED TO
ASK YOU SOMETHING.
LUNCH IS ALMOST OVER.
GET BACK TO THE TRIAL.
JOSEPH MILLER --
GEORGETOWN PRE-LAW,
HARVARD LAW WITH HONORS --
THIS CAN'T BE RIGHT.
THIS GUY'S HOURLY RATE
HAS TO BE MORE THAN
WHAT OUR GRIEVING
WIDOW MAKES IN A MONTH.
MA'AM,
IT ALL CHECKS OUT,
UNLESS GLORIA VARGAS
FOUND SOME GUY
WHO CREATED A C.I.A.- LEVEL
COVER STORY AND FAKE IDENTITY.
WHAT'S MY POSITION
AFTER THE SALE?
I KNOW, AFTER THE SALE,
I HAVE STOCK,
BUT WHAT AM I -- WHAT AM I
DOING IN THE COMPANY?
MAKING POTTERY
IN NEW MEXICO.
WHATEVER YOU LIKE TO DO
WITH YOUR FREE TIME, MR. QUINT.
WELL, WHAT IF I
WANT TO STAY?
I HAVE INVESTED MILLIONS
INTO LIVE HERBALLY.
I HAVE INVESTED
MILLIONS INTO THIS TRIAL.
WHAT EVER YOU WANT
IS IRRELEVANT.
WHY DID YOU OFFER ME
THAT MUCH MONEY?
GETTING NERVOUS
ABOUT YOUR TRIAL?
It's twice
what my company's worth.
WAIT. WHO'S THAT?
THE GUY TALKING
TO THE VARGAS LAWYER?
NO. HER.
RAID QUINT'S COMPUTER,
HIS CALENDAR, HIS E-MAILS.
PULL OUT THE CALL LOGS AND
THE GPS RECORDS FROM HIS PHONE.
I WANT TO KNOW
WHO THAT IS.
INDIA IS A VERY EXCITING PLACE
RIGHT NOW, MR. QUINT.
MILLIONS OF LOCALS WORKING
OUTSOURCED AMERICAN JOBS --
TELEMARKETERS,
CUSTOMER SERVICE --
ALMOST EXCLUSIVELY WORKING
GRAVEYARD SHIFT.
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE WHO
DESPERATELY NEED TO STAY AWAKE.
FastLife WOULD BE
A SENSATION IN INDIA.
HOW MANY SALES
ARE WE TALKING?
INDIA HAS A BILLION PEOPLE.
ALL I NEED IS FOR YOU TO SETTLE
YOUR CURRENT LEGAL MATTERS.
WE CAN'T GO INTO BUSINESS
WITH YOU WITH BAD PRESS.
EARNSHAW SAYS
IF WE SETTLE,
WE OPEN OURSELVES UP
TO OTHER LAWSUITS.
WE DON'T CARE
ABOUT MORE LAWSUITS.
WITH A BILLION PEOPLE
IN THE WORK FORCE,
A FEW DEATHS
WON'T RAISE AN EYEBROW.
GOVERNMENT
WON'T CRACK DOWN?
MR. QUINT, IT TAKES FIVE YEARS
TO GET A PARKING PERMIT.
THI-- THIS TRIAL'S
GOT ME PINNED DOWN.
I- I NEED TO SEE
YOUR OPERATIONS.
OF COURSE.
WELL, I COULD, UH --
I COULD ARRANGE A VIDEO CONFERENCE CALL
WITH OUR HOME OFFICE.
OF COURSE, MUMBAI IS
12 HOURS AHEAD OF TIME,
SO IT'LL HAVE TO BE
AROUND MIDNIGHT TONIGHT.
SHALL I SEND A CAR
TO PICK YOU UP?
INCHES AWAY.
NO, NO.
NO, I-I CANNOT STALL
ANY LONGER.
NOW, LISTEN,
THIS IS THE MIDDLE GAME.
THIS IS WHERE WE TRADE PIECES.
WE LOOK FOR WEAKNESSES.
YOU HAVE TO BUY SOPHIE
A LITTLE MORE TIME TO MANEUVER.
I LITERALLY CANNOT MAKE THIS
SLOWER OR ANY MORE BORING.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHY THEY SAY
JUSTICE WEARS A BLINDFOLD?
SO YOU CAN'T SEE
THAT JUSTICE IS ASLEEP.
I AM SURE THERE'S
WHOLE RESERVOIRS OF BORING
YOU HAVE YET TO PLUMB.
SLIDE 162. THIS IS --
THIS IS GOOD STUFF.
DR. GOLDFARB, HI.
CAN YOU TELL US
HOW THE CHEMICALS
WORK THEIR WAY
INTO THE NEUROTRANSMITTERS?
IS THIS GOING ANYWHERE,
COUNSELOR?
OH, I ASSURE YOU,
YOUR HONOR,
THE NEXT HUNDRED SLIDES
ARE ESSENTIAL.
Mumbai International Limited
already has a presence in the urban centers.
With FastLife,
we believe we can expand
across the entire continent.
I HAVE TO SAY,
I'M IMPRESSED.
As we are with you.
It's not every day
we can do business
with someone so enlightened.
WELL, IT'S NOT EVERY DAY
I GET AN OFFER
FROM SOMEONE
LIKE MS. SMITHE-PATEL.
I think that you'll find us
a nurturing corporation to grow with.
You'll pardon me.
I'm running late.
YES.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME.
THANK YOU, AVI.
SO?
I NEED TO SLEEP ON IT.
I'M AFRAID I CAN'T GIVE YOU
MUCH MORE TIME.
SETTLE YOUR LAWSUIT,
MR. QUINT.
THEN I'M SURE
WE CAN DO BUSINESS TOGETHER.
-GOOD. HE'S GOOD.
-WHAT I TELL YOU?
THANK YOU FOR COMING IN
ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE, DONNIE.
DINNA FASH YERSEL, LADDIE.
-WHAT ARE FRIENDS FOR?
-EXACTLY.
-BEER'S ON ME SOON.
-OH, YOU REMEMBER THA.
-HE'S VERY GOOD.
-WHAT I TELL YOU?
HEY. UH, IS THIS SOMETHING
ALICE WOULD WEAR?
YEAH.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
RELAX.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
QUINT IS GONNA CALL US
AND SETTLE BEFORE WE EVEN
GET TO COURT, SO...
I GUESS ALICE
WASN'T SO BAD.
HER SHOES ARE
MORE COMFORTABLE THAN MINE.
THAT'S BECAUSE
THEY'RE YOUR SHOES.
SHE LIKES RAINY DAYS.
GUYS.
LOOK AT THAT.
Are you kiding?
I can't believe this.
EARNSHAW BOUGHT MUMBAI.
SHE'S PROTECTING HER INVESTMENT,
ELIMINATING THE COMPETITION.
WE ARE SO SCREWED.
SHE JUST SPENT
MILLIONS OF DOLLARS
ON A COMPANY
I DON'T REALLY WORK FOR.
Sign here.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT IS HAPPENING HERE?
JUST SIGN THE PAPERS.
HOW DID SHE EVEN KNOW
WE WERE TALKING A DEAL?
'CAUSE THEY'RE NOT JUST
WATCHING THE JURY ROOM.
THEY'RE WATCHINGQUINT.
READING HIS E-MAILS,
TRACING HIS PHONE,
PROBABLY GOT A FEW GUYS
ON HIM.
WHAT ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO DO NOW?
WE WIN THE TRIAL.
I'M SORRY.
THE IMPOSSIBLE TRIAL?
THE TRIAL
THAT CAN'T BE WON?
YEP. THAT ONE.
NO, NO.
LOOK, YOU TOLD --
YOU TOLD ME
ALL I HAD TO DO WAS STALL.
I CAN'T WIN
A REAL JURY TRIAL.
WHY NOT?
I'M NOT A REAL LAWYER!
I'M A PRETEND LAWYER.
OH, COME ON, YOU DON'T THINK
SO-CALLED REAL LAWYERS
AREN'T JUST PRETENDING AND
TRYING TO BE IN DADDY'S SHOES?
BY THE WAY, THE GUY
YOU'RE GOING UP AGAINST
IS GETTING LINES FED TO HIM
FROM SOMEONE IN A WAREHOUSE.
NATE, ALREADY RESTED
MY CASE, OKAY?
ALL I HAVE LEFT IS MY CROSS-EXAMINATION
OF THEIR EXPERT AND MY CLOSING.
A JURY IS 12 PEOPLE.
JUST TALK TO THEM.
YOU'VE BEEN DOING IT
YOUR WHOLE LIFE.
JUST PUT ON YOUR BOW TIE
AND RING THE DOORBELL.
I CAN'T DO IT.
I CAN'T CONVINCE
A WHOLE JURY.
WE WORKED ON PERSUASION
TACTICS ALL WEEK.
YOU DID REALLY WELL.
YEAH, WITH YOU GUYS.
PEOPLE ON THIS JURY
ARE NORMAL.
THERE ISN'T A SINGLE
NORMAL PERSON ON THIS JURY.
THE OLD LADY WHO KNITS
POTHOLDERS AT LUNCH ISN'T NORMAL?
THE ONE WHO KEEPS SHOWING YOU
PICTURES OF HER GRANDCHILDREN?
HAVE YOU NOTICED ANYTHING
UNUSUAL ABOUT THE PHOTOGRAPHS?
NO.
WELL, SHE HASN'T SEEN THOSE
GRANDCHILDREN IN YEARS.
SHE'S --
SHE'S LYING TO EVERYONE
THAT THEY'RE STILL
ONE BIG HAPPY FAMILY.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
PARKER, I READ PEOPLE
FOR A LIVING.
THAT'S MY THING.
OKAY, CHARLIE,
THE MESSENGER GUY --
YOU KNOW,
THE ONE WITH FIVE KIDS?
GAY?
BULIMIC.
TREVOR, THE FRAT BOY,
HOWEVER -- YEAH, SUPERGAY.
WHAT ABOUT PEGGY?
ACTUALLY, PEGGYIS
DISGUSTINGLY NORMAL.
BUT THE REST OF THEM --
THEY ALL HAVE
THEIR OWN ALICE WHITE.
YOU JUST -- YOU JUST HAPPENED
TO GIVE YOURS A NAME.
OKAY, WE DON'T HAVE
COURT TODAY,
BUT WE DO HAVE
SOME WORK TO DO.
AM I GONNA LIKE
THIS WORK?
UH, NOT THE FIRST PART.
WE'RE FOLLOWING QUINT NOW.
DANG!
WHERE'D THIS GUY
COME FROM?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
MAN!
PLANTED THE DEVICE
IN QUINT'S ENGINE,
TOOK CARE OF THE GUYS
THAT EARNSHAW SENT AFTER QUINT.
AND YOU SHOULD HAVE HIM
IN...THREE, TWO...
...ONE.
PROBLEM?
WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU?
I'M CLOSE TO RESTING MY CASE.
MY CAR JUST DIED.
I'LL GET THERE WHEN I CAN.
YOU SURE YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
ARE YOU KIDDING? I'VE BEEN
OFF THE GRID FOR YEARS.
DON'T GET ME WRONG.
ELECTRIC CAR'S
A GOOD WAY TO START,
BUT YOU CAN MAKE FUEL
FROM YOUR OWN BODILY WASTE.
DO YOU COMPOST?
THE FEELING WHEN --
WHEN YOU CLOSE THE DIGESTIVE-TO-
INTERNAL COMBUSTION CYCLE --
I CALLED TRIPLE "A."
-YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
-NO, IT'S --
IT'S -- IT'S OKAY.
HERE'S -- HERE'S YOUR
PROBLEM RIGHT HERE.
WHERE?
-IT'S JUST RIGHT HERE.
-THAT?
IF YOU JUST LOOK AT THAT, YOU'LL
SEE WHERE YOUR PROBLEM IS.
I'M LOOKING, BUT I DON'T KNOW
MUCH ABOUT CARS.
I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING
AT ALL.
WHAT IS THIS?
MR. VARGAS HAD
AN ENLARGED AORTA,
POSSIBLY THE RESULT
OF RHEUMATIC FEVER AS A CHILD.
THIS IS WHAT CAUSED
HIS HEART ATTACK.
SO, IN YOUR MEDICAL OPINION,
WHAT ROLE DID FastLife PLAY
IN MR. VARGAS' DEATH?
IT PLAYED NO ROLE
WHATSOEVER.
NO FURTHER QUESTIONS,
YOUR HONOR.
YOUR WITNESS, MR. MILLER.
I'M -- I'M SORRY.
FOR WHAT?
ME.
YOU DESERVE BETTER.
YOU'RE THE BEST LAWYER
WE EVER HAD.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WE'RE WAITING,
MR. MILLER.
RIGHT AWAY, YOUR HONOR.
DR. PATEMKIN...
UH, THIS IS NOT YOUR FIRST TIME
TESTIFYING AS AN EXPERT, IS IT?
NO, IT IS NOT.
NO, NO. IN FACT, YOU'VE TESTIFIED ALL
ACROSS THE COUNTRY --
HOUSTON, CHICAGO,
ST. LOUIS. IS THAT CORRECT?
YES.
THAT IS,
UNTIL LAST YEAR.
FOR THE LAST 12 MONTHS,
YOU'VE TESTIFIED ONLY IN
THE STATE OF CALIFORNIA?
-THAT SOUNDS RIGHT.
-OBJECTION -- RELEVANCE?
IT GOES TO HIS QUALIFICATIONS,
YOUR HONOR.
NOW,
FOR THIS LAST YEAR,
YOU'VE ONLY TESTIFIED IN TRIALS
THAT YOU COULD DRIVE TO.
I WOULDN'T CHARACTERIZE IT
LIKE THAT.
IS THAT BECAUSE YOU'RE ON
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT'S NO-FLY,
OR, AS IT'S MORE COMMONLY KNOWN,
THE TERRORIST WATCH LIST?
I'M ON THE LIST,
BUT I'M NOT A TERRORIST.
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT
SEEMS TO THINK SO.
WHY ELSE WOULD THEY
PUT YOU ON A LIST
WITH SUCH PEOPLE
AS OSAMA bin LADEN,
SHEIKH KHALID MOHAMMED?
LOOK, YES,
I'M ON THE NO-FLY --
TERRORIST -- TERRORIST.
...NO-FLY LIST, BUT IT HAS
NOTHING TO DO WITH TERRORISM.
THERE WAS AN INCIDENT.
OH, INCIDENT.
OKAY.
WOULD THAT HAPPEN TO BE
THE INCIDENT
ON FLIGHT 732
OUT OF ST. LOUIS,
WHERE YOU -- YOU FONDLED
A FLIGHT ATTENDANT'S BUTTOCKS?
OR WOULD THAT HAPPEN
TO BE THE INCIDENT
ON FLIGHT 1433
OUT OF CHICAGO,
WHERE YOU DRANK
17 TINY MARGARITAS,
YOU TOOK YOUR PANTS OFF,
YOU STOOD UP ON THE DRINK CART,
AND YOU SANG, QUOTE,
"I'M A SEXY MONKEY"?
I HAVE NO RECOLLECTION
OF THAT.
I'M NOT SURPRISED,
BECAUSE IT WAS NOT ONE,
IT WASN'T TWO,
BUT IT WAS 22 INCIDENTS
OF DRUNK AND BELLIGERENT,
GRAB-ASSY BEHAVIOR
THAT LANDED YOU ON THAT LIST.
MR. MILLER.
-OBJECTION!
-**
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT,
YOUR HONOR?
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT HAS
DETERMINED THAT THIS MAN
IS NOT QUALIFIED TO RIDE ON AN
AIRPLANE, LIKE OSAMA bin LADEN.
HOW IS THIS JURY
SUPPOSED TO RELY ON HIM
TO RENDER
A SOUND MEDICAL OPINION?
-IT DOESN'T --
-NO FURTHER QUESTIONS.
I'M IN RECOVERY.
WE ARE DONE.
YOU MAY STEP DOWN, DR. PATEMKIN.
SOPHIE,
GIVE ME AN UPDATE.
I'VE HIT
THREE OUT OF FIVE.
OKAY, WRAP IT UP.
HARDISON'S ABOUT TO GIVE
HIS CLOSING STATEMENT.
MR. MILLER.
YOU KNOW, A WEEK AGO,
YOU WERE ALL STRANGERS.
AND THEN THE SAME THING
HAPPENED TO ALL OF YOU.
YOU GOT THAT ENVELOPE.
YOU KNOW THE ONE.
COMES IN THE MAIL.
IT SAYS "COUNTY OF LOS ANGELES"
ON THE TOP.
YOU OPEN IT LIKE THIS --
"OH, GOD."
YOU KNOW.
A WEEK PASSES.
YOU WATCH THE WITNESSES
PARADE THROUGH.
YOU LISTEN
TO THE LAWYERS ARGUE.
SUDDENLY, YOU'RE NOT
STRANGERS ANYMORE.
SOME OF YOU
HAVE EVEN MADE FRIENDS.
IT'S NOT AS BAD
AS YOU THOUGHT, RIGHT?
BUT THEN THE JUDGE
ASKS YOU TO DELIBERATE.
THEN YOU HAVE
A MOMENT OF DOUBT.
"I'M NOT A DOCTOR
I'M NOT A SCIENTIST.
"HOW CAN I TELL IF ERNESTO VARGAS
DIED FROM USING FastLife?
H- HOW CAN I BE SURE?"
BUT THAT ENVELOPE
ENTRUSTED YOU
WITH THE MOST IMPORTANT
OBLIGATION OF CITIZENSHIP,
AND THAT IS
TO FIND THE TRUTH.
IT'S SO IMPORTANT THAT WE DARE
NOT GIVE IT TO ONE PERSON
BUT TO 12 STRANGERS.
NOW, ALL I ASK IS THAT YOU --
YOU GO INTO THAT ROOM
AND YOU WORK TOGETHER
AND YOU FIND THE TRUTH.
I HAVE FAITH THAT YOU'LL REACH
A JUST DECISION.
TAKE IT
AS A COMPLIMENT.
HOW'S PARKER DOING?
LET'S FIND OUT.
YEAH,
IT'S THE END GAME --
ALL ON HER NOW.
IT'S ODD.
WHAT?
WE TAKE A JUROR,
AND OUR JUROR GETS REMOVED.
WE TAKE THEIR LAWYER.
ANOTHER LAWYER SHOWS UP.
A COMPANY TRIES TO TAKE QUINT.
I TAKE THE COMPANY.
IT'S ALMOST...
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
OKAY.
THOSE ARE MY ARGUMENTS,
WHY I THINK WE SHOULD DECIDE,
YOU KNOW?
I KNOW I'M JUST ONE OF YOU GUYS,
BUT THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
WHY DON'T WE TAKE A POLL
TO SEE WHERE EVERYONE STANDS?
WHO HERE FINDS IN FAVOR OF THE
DEFENDANT, LIVE HERBALLY?
YES!
IT'S OURS!
QUINT'S ON HIS WAY OVER.
YOU CAN TELL HIM THE GOOD NEWS.
WE ARE NOT GOING TO TELL
MR. QUINT ANYTHING.
DO YOU KNOW WHY HE DIDN'T
SHOW UP IN COURT TODAY?
CALLED ME ON HIS CELL,
SAID HIS CAR BROKE DOWN.
I'VE BEEN TRACKING QUINT
VIA HIS PHONE'S GPS.
HE TOLD YOU HIS CAR WAS DEAD,
BUT WE PINGED HIM VISITING SEVERAL LOCAL
OFFICES OF MY TOP COMPETITORS.
HE WAS OUT THERE
SEARCHING FOR A BETTER OFFER.
TIME TO TEACH MR. QUINT
ABOUT KARMA.
ANY NEWS?
NOT YET.
LET'S TALK BUSINESS.
NOW?
BEFORE THE VERDICT?
I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA WAIT
TILL AFTER WE WON.
THIS TRIAL HAS GIVEN ME
NEW PERSPECTIVE.
NOW I KNOW THAT YOUR COMPANY
DOES NOT JUST HAVE ONE PRICE.
IT HAS THREE.
IF YOU WIN THE TRIAL,
YOUR COMPANY IS WORTH THIS MUCH.
THAT'S A LOT OF MONEY.
ASSUMING, OF COURSE, THAT YOU CAN
FIND SOMEONE WILLING TO PAY IT.
AND THAT'S NOT GOING TO BE
MUMBAI INTERNATIONAL LIMITED, IS IT?
IF YOU LOSE THE TRIAL,
YOUR COMPANY
IS WORTH THIS MUCH.
BUT IF YOU SELL TO ME
RIGHT NOW,
YOUR COMPANY IS WORTH...
THIS MUCH.
I'M THE ONE
TAKING THE RISK HERE.
CHANCE.
CERTAINTY.
NOW, MR. QUINT, I KNOW
THAT YOU ARE A SPIRITUAL MAN,
JUST HOW MUCH
DO YOU TRUST FATE?
YOU'VE MADE
A GOOD DECISION.
HELLO?
JURY'S BACK.
THANK YOU.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN OF THE JURY,
HAVE YOU
REACHED A VERDICT?
WE HAVE, YOUR HONOR.
MADAM FOREMAN,
PLEASE READ THE VERDICT.
IN THE MATTER
OF GLORIA VARGAS ET AL
VERSUS LIVE HERBALLY INCORPORATED,
THE JURY FINDS
IN FAVOR OF...
THE PLAINTIFF...
YES!
...IN THE AMOUNT
OF $5 MILLION.
WHAT THE HELL
JUST HAPPENED?
WHO HERE FINDS IN FAVOR OF
THE DEFENDANT, LIVE HERBALLY?
WHO WANTS PIZZA FOR LUNCH?
WHO HERE FINDS IN FAVOR OF
THE DEFENDANT, LIVE HERBALLY?
IT'S OURS.
YOU!
THIS IS YOUR FAULT!
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU WENT LOOKING
FOR A BETTER OFFER.
WE TRACKED YOU
ON YOUR CELLPHONE
WHEN YOU HAD YOUR MEN
BEAT UP MY SECURITY DETAIL!
WHAT MEN? I DON'T HAVE MEN.
I- I WEAR SANDALS.
AND I HAVEN'T
BEEN ANYWHERE.
Sophie, give me an update.
I'VE HIT
THREE OUT OF FIVE.
DO YOU HAVE
AN APPOINTMENT, MISS?
UM, NO.
BUT I WAS JUST LEAVING.
REMEMBER ME?
LOOKS LIKE
YOU SHOULD HAVE SETTLED.
OH, SWEET MERCY.
COOKED FLESH.
CAN WE HAVE FAST FOOD EVERY TIME
WE MAKE THE BAD GUYS GO AWAY?
DID YOU REALIZE
WHAT YOU JUST DID?
WHAT YOU DID -- YOU WON
A JURY TRIAL WITHOUT CHEATING.
WITHOUT CHEA-- I HACKED
A GOVERNMENT NO-FLY LIST
AND USED IT
TO HUMILIATE A WITNESS.
EXCESSIVELY -- "CHEATING
EXCESSIVELY" IS WHAT I MEANT.
BUT, I MEAN,
THINK ABOUT IT,
I MEAN, IF YOU APPLIED
YOURSELF, HARDISON,
YOU COULD BE
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I COULD. I COULD.
YOU KNOW, NEXT WEEK, I THINK
I'M GONNA BE AN ASTRONAUT.
WELL, THAT'S NOT REALLY
WHAT I MEANT.
I MEANT IF YOU STUDIED --
YEAH, IF I --
WHO NEEDS TO STUDY?
YOU KNOW,
I'M GONNA BE A SURGEON.
A SURGEON -- E.R.
SURGEON.
HEY, IT'S PEGGY FROM THE TRIAL!
SHE WANTS TO HAVE COFFEE
NEXT WEEK.
ALICE MADE A FRIEND.
I'M GONNA TELL YOU
ONE MORE TIME.
YOU MADE A FRIEND,
NOT ALICE.
OH, COOL.
WELL, THINK SHE'D WANT TO
STEAL A PAINTING WITH ME?
START SMALL, PARKER.
TRY COFFEE.
OKAY.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net