ALL RIGHT, SWEETHEART.
WE ARE NEAR NAJAF.
I'M NOT ALLOWED TO SAY EXACTLY WHERE.
HEY, DWIGHT, SAY HELLO TO JENNY.
- HE'S CHEATING ON YOU!
- NICE.
WITH A CAMEL-- A DRUNK, SLUTTY CAMEL.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, IT WAS ONE TIME, OKAY,
AND THE CAMEL'S BEEN TEXTING ME,
BUT IT'S OVER, I PROMISE.
HELLO? PSD.
HEY COME ON??
YOU SEE THOSE GUYS?
PRIVATE CONTRACTORS.
THEY MAKE 700 BUCKS A DAY.
I MAKE 7.
HEY, YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT THEY GOT TO DO?
THEY GOT TO --
DWIGHT!
...THEY GOT TO DO?
THEY GOT TO--
DWIGHT!
JENNY YOUR fiancee?
WELL, SHE WAS, BUT...
OH. OH, I'M SORRY.
I'M NOT MAD. IT HAPPENS.
LOOK, I DON'T WANT CHARITY.
WE ARE NOT A CHARITY.
(LEVERAGE S01E02)
I JUST WANT MY REHAB.
AND IF I'M GONNA WORK --
AND I WANT TO WORK --
DR. LAROQUE SAYS I NEED ANOTHER
YEAR AND A HALF OF HARD-CORE REHAB,
MAYBE TWO MORE SURGERIES.
CASTLEMAN SHOT ME UP.
I JUST WANT THEM TO PAY MY BILLS.
NO MORE, NO LESS.
HMM.
THE ARMY INVESTIGATION
DETERMINED YOU WERE --
WHAT, THEY SAID YOU WERE HIT BY INSURGENTS?
YEAH, THAT'S BECAUSE CASTLEMAN REFUSED
TO COOPERATE IN THAT INVESTIGATION.
AND THEY CAN DO THAT?
NO ONE'S STOPPING THEM.
THEY'RE COWBOYS. THEY GO OFF
ALL THE TIME -- BOOM, BOOM.
YOU KNOW,
I JUST WANT THEM TO DO RIGHT BY ME.
PARDON ME, MR., UH...
OH, UH, NATHAN FORD.
YOU'RE DR. LAR--
COULD I TALK TO YOU OUTSIDE?
DOC, HE'S COOL.
I FOUND HIM ON THE INTERNET.
YES, THAT NEVER GOES BADLY.
WITH ME.
UH, YEAH.
I'LL BE IN TOUCH.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@∑ÎŒµ
Sync:FRS@”Ó“‚
YOU CAN'T JUST COME IN HERE
AND GET HIS HOPES UP.
YOU KNOW, I'M JUST HERE TO PROVIDE OPTIONS.
- THERE ARE NO OPTIONS!
- THE VETERANS HOSPITAL --
...IS 400 MILES AWAY AND
HAS A 5-MONTH WAITING LIST.
EVERYBODY IN THAT REHAB ROOM IS A RESERVIST.
WHEN RESERVISTS GET OUT,
THEY GET SENT HOME,
NO MATTER WHERE HOME IS
OR HOW FAR IT IS FROM
THE TREATMENT THEY NEED.
NOBODY THOUGHT THIS THROUGH.
WE'RE NOT A RICH HOSPITAL.
I CASHED IN EVERY FAVOR I HAD
TO TAKE CARE OF THESE KIDS
FOR AS LONG AS I COULD BUT --
I HAVE TO GO BACK IN THERE
AND TELL PERRY WE CAN'T TREAT HIM ANYMORE.
I HAVE TO DO THAT.
RUN YOUR SCAM ON SOMEBODY WITH MONEY.
IT'S NOT A SCAM. I'M HERE TO HELP.
PEOPLE DON'T JUST SHOW UP TO HELP.
THAT'S NOT THE WAY THE WORLD WORKS.
HARDISON, CALL THEM.
WHY?
I CAN'T LIVE LIKE THIS ANYMORE!
THE LIES AND THE FILTH!
NO! HELP ME! I JUST --
I WANT TO BE CLEAN.
I WANT TO BE CLEAN!
Hollywood
YEAH.
YOU UNDERSTAND THIS IS
A SOAP COMMERCIAL, RIGHT?
UH-HUH.
WELL, WHEN I THOUGHT ABOUT PEGGY,
I CAME UP WITH THIS IDEA
THAT THE DIRT IS REALLY THIS GIANT,
LIKE, METAPHOR FOR SIN.
YOU SHOULD TAKE THAT.
NO, NO. YOU SHOULD TAKE THAT.
HELLO?
WHEN?
PEGGY KILLED HER FIRST HUSBAND.
TH-THANK YOU.
berlin
IS THAT YOU OR ME????
IT COULD BE IMPORTANT.
DOES YOUR MAMA HAVE YOUR NUMBER?
YEAH.
NOTHING. WHY?
Monago
PARKER.
OH, SH-- NO, I WASN'T SHUSHING YOU.
Los Angeles
- FROM THE FIRST JOB?
- YEAH.
I PUT ALL THAT MONEY
IN A SWISS BANK ACCOUNT.
MILLIONS OF DOLLARS,
YOU DIDN'T BUY ANYTHING?
I DON'T LIKE STUFF. I LIKE MONEY.
I BOUGHT A LITTLE RETIREMENT HOME IN IRELAND...
???
AND DUBAI AND TOKYO.
- WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- YEAH...
I'M NOT ABOUT TO
TELL TWO KNOWN THIEVES
WHAT I DID WITH MY
MULTIMILLION-DOLLAR PAYOUT.
DON'T YOU TRUST US?
OKAY.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT IS THIS?
THIS IS OUR NEW COVER STORY.
WELCOME TO LEVERAGE
CONSULTING & ASSOCIATES,
FOUNDED IN 1913 BY THE GREAT
HARLAN LEVERAGE III.
I'M SORRY.
NATE IS GOING TO KILL YOU.
DID YOU PAINT THAT?
I'M GIFTED.
THAT'S WEIRD.
NOW, LEVERAGE CONSULTING IS SQUEAKY CLEAN.
ALL CORPORATE TAXES ARE ON RECORD
AS PAID FOR THE LAST 90 YEARS.
ALL YOUR IDENTITIES AS PARTNERS.
PAYROLL TAXES ARE PAID.
YOU GUYS HAVE PENSION PLANS AND DENTAL.
THOSE ARE EMPLOYMENT RECORDS,
CASE FILES, AND COMPANY NEWSLETTERS.
IN 1998, I WON THE SACK RACE
AT THE FOURTH OF JULY PICNIC.
- COOL!
- NOW, THESE --
THESE ARE YOUR OFFICES.
NOW, YOU CAN BRING SOMETHING,
LIKE A PHOTO OR,
YOU KNOW WHAT, A PLANT.
I'M A BIG SUPPORTER OF DANDELIONS.
HARDISON.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU SPENT YOUR
SHARE OF THE CASH ON ALL OF THIS.
ME, NO. HELL NO.
NATE PAID FOR ALL OF THIS,
YOU KNOW, WITH WHAT HE HAD LEFT.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, AFTER
HE GAVE THE REST OF IT AWAY.
WHOA. WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- HE GAVE IT AWAY?
- YEAH.
ALL OF IT, EVERY LAST PENNY.
IT WAS, UH, TO, LIKE,
LIKE SOME CHILDRENS HOSPITAL
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT, BUT...
THIS...
THIS IS MY MASTERPIECE.
NICE.
MY MAN.
LONG VERSION OR THE SHORT VERSION?
SHORT.
- SHORT VERSION.
- SHORTEST.
PHOTO AND VIDEO FORENSICS PROGRAMS,
BACK DOORS INTO EVERY ELECTRONIC
BANKING SYSTEM IN THE WORLD,
RUNNING HEURISTIC DATA CRAWLERS ALL
OVER THE NEWS SITES TO FIND OUR CLIENTS.
OH, ALSO...
THIS IS THE SHORT VERSION?
...FACIAL RECOGNITION DATABASE
TIED INTO CIA, NSA, AND THE FBI.
BUT THE REAL PIËCE DE RÈSISTANCE...
...DIRECTV HD TOTAL SPORTS PACKAGE --
NFL, NBA...
AND I THREW IN A LITTLE BIT OF HOCKEY
'CAUSE I KNOW YOU PEOPLE LIKE THAT.
HOCKEY.
ALL RIGHT, STOP KICKING THE TIRES.
YOU WANT TO TAKE HER FOR A SPIN?
YOU SEE THOSE GUYS?
PRIVATE CONTRACTORS.
THEY MAKE 700 BUCKS A DAY.
I MAKE 7.
HEY, YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT THEY GOT TO DO?
THEY GOT TO --
DWIGHT!
OUR CLIENT IS THE CAMERAMAN,
CORPORAL ROBERT PERRY.
HE SAYS THAT THE CASTLEMAN
CONTRACTORS SPOOKED
AND STARTED FIRING.
5.56 NATO ROUNDS...
MIXED IN WITH SOME 9 MILLS
FROM THE SUBMACHINE GUNS.
INSURGENTS WOULD HAVE USED
AK-47 WITH 7.62 AMMO --
HAS MORE OF A "CRACK."
CONTRACTORS SHOT THEM UP, ALL RIGHT.
YOU I.D.'d THE WEAPON
FROM THE GUNSHOT SOUND.
IT HAS A VERY DISTINCTIVE SOUND.
CASTLEMAN SECURITY IS HARD-CORE, FOLKS,
A BILLION-DOLLAR COMPANY.
THEY GOT FAT GOVERNMENT CONTRACTS
EVERYWHERE WE GOT TROOPS.
THAT'S CHARLES DUFORT, C.E.O.
HE'S VERY PARANOID
AND VERY PROFESSIONAL.
I WANT TO GET THIS CLEAR RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS A PRIVATE ARMY
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT TAKING ON.
THEY GOT THEIR OWN INTEL ASSETS.
THEY GOT A LOT OF TRIGGER-PULLERS.
YES, AND LOBBYISTS IN
EVERY OFFICE IN WASHINGTON, D.C.
THE PROBLEM WITH A COVER-UP
IS ALL THE PAPERWORK IT TAKES
TO KEEP THE LIES STRAIGHT.
INTERNAL E-MAILS, MEMOS.
EXACTLY.
- SO...
- LET'S GO TO WORK.
SO, WE STEAL THE EVIDENCE
AND THREATEN TO EXPOSE THEM.
- BLACKMAIL.
- AH, YES...
BUT JUST ENOUGH BLACKMAIL
TO PAY FOR PERRY'S REHAB --
MAYBE A COUPLE OF MILLION MORE IN DAMAGES.
NEVER HOLD UP IN COURT.
AH, BUT THAT'S WHY
CORPORAL PERRY IS LUCKY.
HE DOESN'T HAVE LAWYERS.
HE HAS THIEVES.
HARDISON.
NEXT TIME, I WEAR THE SUIT.
Dufort's here.
I'll make contact.
SEE WHAT YOU CAN SQUEEZE OUT OF HIM.
PARKER, HARDISON, TIME TO HIT HIS OFFICE.
I-I GOT TO GO BACK TO THE OFFICE.
I-I JUST REMEMBERED SOMETHING.
WHAT?
I JUST REMEMBERED GRAVITY...
AND THE SQUISHINESS
OF ALL MY MANLY BITS.
I DESIGNED THIS RIG MYSELF.
THE LINE IS CARBON FIBER,
FIVE-POINT HARNESS.
WEIGHT SUPPORT HERE, HERE, AND HERE,
AUTOBRAKING RESISTANCE
ON THE MAIN PULLEY BACK HERE.
OKAY. OKAY. C-COOL.
SO IT'S TESTED?
NOT YET.
NOT Y--
WELL, WHEN THE HELL
WAS YOU GONNA TEST IT?
OHH!
YOU BIG BABY.
SERIOUSLY?
OKAY, HARDISON, PARKER, GUARD
SWEEPS ARE EVERY 10 MINUTES.
THAT MEANS YOU GOT 9 MINUTES, 30 SECONDS.
I'M WORKING ON IT.
CASTLEMAN IS GONNA BE VERY HAPPY
WITH THE NEW APPROPRIATIONS BILL.
- PARDON ME, CONGRESSMAN.
- YES.
LILY McREADY. I'M WITH EXECUTIVE ORDERS.
THEY'RE A LONDON-BASED
DEFENSE CONTRACTOR.
- CHARLES DUFORT.
- OH.
EXECUTIVE ORDERS DOESN'T
WORK FOR THE U.S. GOVERNMENT.
YET.
PERHAPS WE COULD DO SOMETHING ABOUT THAT.
YES, WELL, UM, IT WAS
VERY NICE TO MEET YOU.
NOW, YOU'LL HAVE TO EXCUSE ME.
YOU'RE NOT POACHING, ARE YOU?
APPROPRIATIONS BILL 718.
THOSE ARE OUR DEFENSE CONTRACTS.
DON'T EVEN BOTHER.
MR. DUFORT, SURELY THERE'S
ENOUGH WAR TO GO AROUND.
I RATHER LIKE YOU.
HARDISON, HARDISON, WHAT'S ...
WHAT'S THIS BILL THEY ARE TALKING ABUOT?
YOU KNOW, I'D LIKE TO
GIVE YOU THE SCHOOLHOUSE ROCK,
BUT THIS MAN HAS AN RFID SECURITY-CARD
READER ON HIS POWER SUPPLY,
SO I'M A LITTLE BUSY.
OOH, OLD-SCHOOL.
I FOUND A SAFE.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BELIEVE THIS.
IT'S VOICE-ACTIVATED.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
ONE PROBLEM AT A TIME.
UR, SOPHIE, I'M GOING IN.
WE NEED TO GET AN RFID CARD TO ELIOT.
MY COMPANY'S FOCUSED ON MEETING SENATORS,
BUT I'M THINKING CONGRESSMEN.
YOU KNOW THE GREAT THING ABOUT CONGRESSMEN?
50, 100 GRAND WELL SPENT
WILL GET ONE ELECTED.
BUT THEN, ONCE THEY'RE IN,
THE INCUMBENCY RATE IS OVER 95%.
SO YOU CAN GET, ON AN AVERAGE,
18, 20 YEARS OF USE OUT OF ONE OF THEM.
IN THESE UNCERTAIN TIMES,
BUYING A UNITED STATES CONGRESSMAN
IS ONE OF THE BEST INVESTMENTS
A CORPORATION CAN MAKE.
OHH, I JUST THREW UP
IN MY MOUTH A LITTLE BIT.
I'M A PROFESSIONAL CRIMINAL,
AND I FIND THAT DISTURBING.
???
WELL,???
NO, OVERTHROWING THE GOVERNMENT
IS TOO HARSH A WAY TO DESCRIBE IT.
WE JUST HELP THEM ALONG.
IT WAS A ??
??
???
- ??
- ???
???
SHOULDN'T BE TOO HARD TO GET OUT AND WASH.
OH??
OH, THIS IS THE FIRST DAY I'VE WORN IT.
THANK YOU.
LET ME SEE IF I CAN GET SOMEONE
TO HELP YOU WITH THAT. EXCUSE ME.
- YEAH, GARCON?
- YES, MA'AM?
COULD YOU, UH,
COULD YOU POSSIBLY HELP US?
- WE'VE GOT A LITTLE STAIN ON THIS JACKET.
- ??OH LOOK AT THAT.
- LET ME TAKE CARE OF THAT FOR YOU.
- ??
- IF YOU ??
- LET ME, UH, KEEP THIS.
A MAN IN MY POSITION
SHOULDN'T FORGET HIS WALLET.
THAT'S EMBARRASSING.
THANK YOU.
HERE YOU GO, SIR.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
THERE'S NO MAGNETIC STRIP.
IT'S A LITTLE RADIO FREQUENCY.
JUST... JUST PUT IT UP NEXT TO
THE PHONE THAT I GAVE YOU.
I'M IN.
PARKER, WHAT'S THE STATUS
OF THE VOICE LOCK?
I'VE BEEN SAMPLING DUFORT'S SPEECH,
BUT I STILL NEED A FEW MORE SOUNDS.
How many?
OH, I ONLY NEED THE SOUNDS
"PUH," "TUH," "OOH," "UH,"
"EH," "OH," "AH,"
"KUH," "AY," "EFF."
AH, ONLY THOSE.
ELIOT?
I'M ON IT.
HELLO.
- OOH.
- MMM.
APPETIZER, SIR?
SURE. WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
I'VE GOT THE P‚TES D'ESCARGOT
AVEC BEURRE D'ARGENTINE...
AND WHAT LOOKS LIKE
OLD DUCK, KIND OF GREASY.
I GUESS I'LL HAVE THE FIRST ONE.
BUT OF COURSE.
WELL?
MAY I HAVE SOME?
THE GREASY DUCK?
OOH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I WOULDN'T HAVE THE GREASY DUCK.
NO, I WOULDN'T SUGGEST IT.
NO, THE OTHER ONE!
THE P‚TES D'ESCARGOT
WITH THE BEURRE ARGENTINE!
EXCELLENT CHOICE.
PRETTY GOOD. YOU GOT MOST OF THEM.
OKAY, NOW ALL I NEED IS
"EFF," "UH," AND "KUH."
THIS IS SHRIMP!
???
IT'S SHRIMP, YOU STUPID FU--
OHH! THERE THEY ARE.
REALLY LOUD, TOO.
OKAY, SOPHIE, START THE WALKAWAY.
I was wondering,
could I drop by your office?
Anytime.
Where are you going?
PLAYING A HUNCH.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, PLAY IT FAST.
HARDISON, WHAT DO YOU GOT?
YOU GOT THREE MINUTES.
TOO MUCH.
I GOT ALL OF PERRY'S MEDICAL RECORDS.
??SURE, THAT'S --
THAT'S PRETTY NORMAL,
BUT I'VE GOT PSYCH EVALUATIONS,
HIGH-SCHOOL RECORDS.
THEY'RE READING HIS E-MAILS.
TAPPING HIS PHONES.
I'VE GOT SURVEILLANCE PHOTOS OF PERRY
HERE FROM THE HOSPITAL YESTERDAY.
WHY ARE THEY SPENDING SO MUCH
MONEY WATCHING OUR GUY?
I MEAN, THE INVESTIGATIONS OF
THE SHOOTING WERE DONE MONTHS AGO.
SEE THOSE GUYS?
PRIVATE CONTRACTORS.
BECAUSE IT'S NOT ABOUT THE SHOOTING.
THE COVER-UP HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH THE SHOOTING.
IT'S ABOUT THE TRUCKS.
CONGRESSMAN.
UH, YES?
YOUR SUPPORT ON THE NEXT APPROPRIATIONS
BILL WOULD BE VERY HELPFUL.
WE'VE ALREADY EARMARKED THE
NO-BID CONTRACTS FOR CASTLEMAN.
- THEY DESERVE IT.
- NOBODY'S PERFECT.
LOOK AT ALL THE TROUBLE THEY HAD
WITH THAT SHOOTING IN NAJAF.
I'M SORRY?
I DON'T REALLY FOLLOW
THAT SORT OF NEWS.
I JUST REVIEW THE CONTRACTS.
OF COURSE.
EXCUSE ME.
PARKER, HARDISON, BUG OUT,
GO BACK TO THE OFFICE.
WE'RE GOING TO THE HOSPITAL.
YOU NEED TO TALK??
THE SHOOTING WASN'T AN ACCIDENT.
PERRY ISN'T A VICTIM. HE'S A WITNESS.
CASTLEMAN STRIKE YOU
AS THE KIND OF COMPANY
THAT WOUEP A WITNESS ALIVE?
HE'S NOT IN HIS DAMN ROOM.
I'M CHECKING ALL THE CORRIDORS
THAT ARE CONNECTED
TO THE EXTERIOR DOORS.
SORRY, DOC,
I KNOW IT'S CLOSED, BUT --
MR. FORD?
WE GOT TO GET YOU OUT OF HERE NOW.
WHY?
CASTLEMAN.
- ???
- SOPHIE DEVEREAUX. OOH!
- ???HERE WE GO.
- WATCH THOSE HANDS, MR. PERRY.
I'M IN A WHEELCHAIR.
I'M NOT BLIND.
LET'S GO.
IT AIN'T GETTING CLEAR.
I CAN'T FIND --
EXCUSE ME, DO YOU WORK ON THIS FLOOR?
I, UH -- WHAT FLOOR IS THIS?
I'M IN ORTHOPEDICS, SO --
HEY! HEY!
GET THE ELEVATOR!
MR. FORD!
HELLO.
AAH!
GO!
WE GOT ALL THIS STUFF
ONE OF THE CASTLEMAN HITTERS.
???
THIS IS A SUICIDE NOTE.
THIS GUN IS REGISTERED
IN ROBERT PERRY'S NAME.
THE BILL OF SALE BELONGS TO A
SHOP A MILE FROM HIS HOUSE.
I GOT PERRY SQUARED AWAY IN A SAFE HOUSE.
PLAYTIME'S OVER, NATE.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
UNTIL THEY COME AFTER US.
THE TALL ONE,
THE WAY HE USED THE˙KNIFE --
EX-MARINE, PROBABLY FORCE RECON.
YOU I.D.'d A GUY
OFF HIS KNIFE-FIGHTITYLE?
IT'S A VERY DISTINCTIVE STYLE.
THAT'S FOR LATER.
I DIDN'T SIGN UP FOR AN THIS.
WHAT I DID BEFORE, NO GOT HURT.
STOLE PAINTINGS FOR A LIVING.
I NEVER HURT ANYBODY.
I ACTUALLY HURT PEOPLE, SO...
NATE, IF ANYTHING
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED --
YOU KNOW, YOU GUYS CALLED ME.
YOU... YOU REMEMBER?
YOU BEGGED ME TO RUN THE CREW,
AGREED TO PLAY BY MY RULES.
NOW, WALK OUT IF YOU
HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THAT.
WALK OUT ANY DAY IF YOU
IT'S SIMPLE.
WE FINISH THIS ONE.
JUST ONE.
HOW DO WE HIT 'EM?
CONGRESSMAN JENKINS. HE'S OUR IN.
HE LOOKED ME STRAIGHT IN THE EYE
AND TOLD ME HE NEVER
EVEN HEARD OF THE SHOOTING.
SO?
LOOKED ME IN THE EYE?
???THEY'RE NOT LOOKING ME IN THE EYE.
MEN ONLY REALLY LOOK A WOMAN IN THE EYE
WHEN THEY'RE MAKING
THE EFFORT TO LIE TO HER.
WELL, YOU CAN'T ARGUE WITH THAT.
NOTED AND FILED.
ALL RIGHT, JENKINS IS
DUFORT'S PET CONGRESSMAN.
LET'S SEE IF WE CAN GET HIM TO BIT
THE BEST WAY TO GET TWO PEOPLE
TO REVEAL A SECRET --
GET THEM TO TURN ON EACH OTHER.
MAY I PUT THAT AWAY FOR YOU?
THAT DIDN'T SOUND LIKE A QUESTION.
WASHINGTON,DC
CONGRESSMAN JENKINS.
OH, UM.
EXECUTIVE ORDERS, THE EUROPEAN COMPANY,
FROM THE FUND-RAISER, RIGHT?
THAT'?RIGHT.
I REMEMBER YOU FROM THE FUND-RAISER.
PLEASE.(Los Angeles)
TOM ABRAMS. YOU CAN CALL ME TOMMY.
YOU DON'T WORK FOR
CONGRESSMAN JES, DO YOU?
I DO NOT.
NO, I WORK FOR CONGRESSMAN
CALLOwAY, FROM UPS.
WE ALREADY HAVE ENOUGH FRIENDS
ON THE APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE.
EUROPEAN COUNTRIES WILL AHE UD STATES
IN THEIR FOREIGN OPERATIONS
IF THEY KNOW THAT EUROPEAN COMPANIES
ARE GONNA REAP SOME OF THE BENEFITS.
SOME HELP IN THE APPROPRIATIONS BILL --
I SUPPORT AMERICAN COMPANIES.
- LIKE CASTLEMAN?
- LIKE CASTLEMAN.
AND THEY SUPPORT, UH, THE COUNTRY.
WELL, I'M HERE BECAUSE CONGRESSMAN
CALLOWAY WANTED ME TO LET YOU KNOW
THAT HE'S OPEN TO DISCUSSIONS NOW THAT
CONGRESSMAN JENKINS HAS GONE SOFT ON YOU.
JENKINS AL DELIVERS.
JENKINS TOLD MY BOSS, TO HIS FACE...
THAT HE'S TIRED OF COVERING FOR YOU.
WE'VE BACKED HIM FOR YEARS.
WELL, JES WANTED MY
BOSS TO MEET THIS WOMAN
FROM A BRITISH COMPANY --
EH...UH....
EXECUTIVE ORDERS.
I DIDN'T PICK YOU AT RANDOM, CONGRESSMAN.
CASTLEMAN CAN BE A FICKLE FRIEND.
RUMOR HAS IT THEY'RE
LOOKING FOR SOME FRESH BLOOD.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
IF YOUR EARMARKS
AND YOUR NO-BID CONTRACTS
ARE STILL IN THAT APPROPRIATIONS BILL,
???
BUT IF THEY'RE NOT,
WELL, CONGRESSMAN CALLOWAY WOULD
BE OPEN TO ENJOYING THE SAME FAVORS
THAT JENKINS HAS ENJOYED
FOR ALL THESE YEARS.
BUT OF COURSE,
JENKINS HAS NEW FRIENDS NOW.
YOU SHOULD LOOK OUT
FOR THE SIGNS, CONGRESSMAN --
MISSED PHONE CALLS...
NO MORE LITTLE FAVORS.
THOSE ARE THE SAME SIGNS THAT
YOUR WIFE IS CHEATING ON YOU.
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO WHEN THAT HAPPENS?
PLAY THE FIELD.
THANKS VERY MUCH FOR COMING, TOMMY.
PLEASURE.
CONGRESSMAN JENKINS IS VERY CAREFUL.
IRECT BRIBES,
BUT HE'S RENOVATING HIS HOUSE,
AND SO FAR, HE'S RECEIVED
OVER $600,000 WORTH OF WORK
FOR A LITTLE OVER 50 GRAND.
CASTLEMAN OWNS THE CONTRACTING COMPANY, HUH?
I MEAN, HE'S GOING THROUGH LIKE
THREE SHELL COMPANIES, BUT, YEAH.
THIS MAN LOVES HIS HOUSE.
JUST CHECK OUT HIS
WEB-BROWSING HABITS. LOOK HERE.
YOU SEE, THE MAN SPTHREE WEEKS PICKING
OUT THE PERFECT MAHOGANY WOOD PANELS.
THIS SITE IS LIKE WOOD PORN.
IS HIS HOUSE FINISHED?
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
CAN I OWR PHONE?
HELlo. YES.
I'D LIKE TO CANCEL DELIVERY ON SOME
MAHOGANY WOOD PANELING, PLEASE.
- ??
- THE JENKINS HOUSE, YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT, DO ME A FA MAN.
JUST GO AHEAD AND CANCEL THE WHOLE ORDER.
YES, SIR.
WHAT'S HE DOING?
YANKING THE CONGRESSMAN'S CHAIN.
AHA!
PARKER STARTED HER RUN YET?
JUST NOW.
YOU KNOW, I STILL THINK
IT WOULD BE EASIER FOR ME
TO JUST HACK THE BILL
IN THE PRINTER QUEUE.
NO, NO. NO COMPUTERS, NO.
A BILL IS PUT INTO A WOODEN BOX ON THE
CONGRESSIONAL FLOOR CALLED THE HOPPER.
A WOODEN -- WHOA, WHOA.
A WOODEN -- A WOODEN BOX?
- A WOODEN BOX.
- woOD?
OH, WE CAN PUT A MAN ON THE MOON,
BUT ALL OUR LAWS
GO INTO A WOODEN BOX.
WHAT WE NEED TO DO IS,
WE NEED TO GET DUFORT
TO BELIEVE THAT JENKINS
IS ABANDONING HIM,
THAT JENKINS SUBMITTED
THE APPROPRIATIONS BILL
THAT DOE HAVE ANY OF THE
USUAL COntRACTS FOR CASTLEMAN,
WHICH MEANS THAT WE HAVE TO PUT
OUR OWN PAGES INTO THE BILL.
THAT MEANS THE ONLY PLACE
THAT WE COULD GET AT IT WO--
AHH! OKAY.
- ???
- ??
I MEAN, BREAK A LAW,
EVERYBODY'S DONE THAT.
- MY MAMA'S DONE THAT.
- UH-HUH.
BUT STEAL A LAW...
OH, SHE'S GONNA BE A LEGEND, BABY.
THE EAGLE HAS LANDED.
- IT'S IN. UHH!
- GO AHEAD, GIRL.
SEXINESS, UHH!
I LIKE IT.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO EASE UP
ON THAT A LITTLE BIT.
- I'M JUST SAYING,
- YEAH.
BETWEEN ME AND YOU.
NEVER LEAVES THE ROOM.
HI, SO, HOW WASHINGTON?
WELL, VILLAINS, CON MEN,
WOLVES IN CHEEP'S CLOTHING.
I FELT RIGHT AT HOME.
THIS IS PRETTY AMAZING.
LISTEN TO THEM.
??This is your
contractor's problem.
Oh, please. Let's not pretend.
You pulled all our earmarks
from the appropriations...
THERE'S ABOUT AN HOUR OF THIS,
BUT HERE'S THE HIGH POINT.
Somebody screwed up.
I've always been there for you.
I called Manila.
I cleared customs for
you in Los Angeles.
And that was a risk!
NOW, AFTER THAT,
THERE'S -- IT'S --
WELL, WHATEVER YOU CALL THE "RICH
GUYS ON TELEPHONES" VERSION OF MAKEUP SEX.
BUT NOW WE KNOW,
CASTN MAKES A THOUSAND SHIPMENTS A MONTH.
BUT ONE SHIPPED THROMANILA,
RIGHT AFTER THE SHOOTING,
LINKED TO PHONE RECORDS
OM THE CONGRESSMAN.
THEIR SHIPMENTS COME THROUGH HERE.
NOW, SOMEWHERE IN THIS
MADNESS IS CONTAINER 541.
IT'S CURRENTLY SITTING
AT THE PORT OF LOS ANGELES.
WHAT'S IN IT?
NO IDEA, BUT IT'S MOVING IN TWO DAYS...
HEADING TO THE MAIN CASTLEMAN
STORAGE FACILITY IN KANSAS.
NOW, THAT --
THAT'S WHY THEY TRIED TO HIT
PERRY, RIGHT THERE, THAT'S IT.
YEAH, WANTED TO TIE UP ALL THE LOOSE ENDS
BEFORE THEY TUCK THIS
ONE AWAY AT HOME BASE.
WHAT DO YOU SHIP IN A CRATE FROM IRAQ?
OH, BOY.
SOMETHING WORTH KILLING FOR.
Port of Los Angeles
HOW'S SECURITY?
DOCKYARD ENTRANCE IS NO PROBLEM.
THERE IT IS. IT'S 541.
HOLD UP, RAMBO.
OKAY, NO LASERS. NO MOTION DETECTORS.
NO VIBRATIONS, NO -- WHOOPS.
WHAT "WHOOPS"?
THERE'S A WEBCAM.
I'M PICKING UP ITS
BROADCAST ON MY PHONE.
I SEE IT, UP ON THAT POLE.
I JUST HAVE TO SPOOF THE I.P. ADDRESS
AND OVERLAY A DIGITAL
DUPLICATE ON THE Wi-Fi AND --
- OR THAT.
- LET'S GO. COME ON.
I'M SORRY IT WAS TOO FAR
AWAY FOR YOU TO PUNCH.
I'M SURE THAT ALLY FRUSTRATES YOU.
POSITION ONE, WHAT'S YOUR STATUS?
???Just done walking the perimeter.
COPY THAT. I'M ON MY WAY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS IN THERE?
ARTIFACTS FROM BAGHDAD MUSEUMS,
MAYBE SOME FROM THE SADDAM PALACES.
NO, I BET IT'S WEAPONS.
A LOT OF BACK-ALLEY ARMS-DEALING
GOING ON IN A WAR ZONE.
MONEY'S GOOD, TOO.
HEY! LINE OF SIGHT.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE AWAY
FROM THAT CONTAINER.
SOMETHING'S WRONG WITH THE WEBCAM.
GET SOME MEN UP THEREp
AND FIX THAT WEBCAM.
I WANT IT WORKING IN AN HOUR. MOVE.
OKAY.
THAT'S WORTH KILLING FOR.
ULTRAVIOLET CHECKS OUT,
PAPER CHECKS OUT.
THE WATERMARKS, THE INK,
IT ALL CHECKS OUt.
THERE'S A WHOLE CONTAINER OF IT,
FROM IRAQ OF ALL PLACES.
IT'S GOT TO BE COUNTERFEIT.
NO, IT'S REAL.
IT FEELS(zEAL.
HEY, WHAT DO YOU GOT GOING ON?
YOU AND HARDISON?
WHAT IS IT, LIKE A CREEPY CONTEST?
I DON'T KNOW, WHAT IS IT,
$200, $300 MILLION IN U.S. CURRENCY.
WHAT'S IT DOING IN IRAQ?
WE SENT IT THERE.
WHAT?
BEGINNING OF THE IRAQ WAR,
MY OLD COMPANY HELPED INSURE
THE LARGEST CURRENCY TRANSFER IN HISTORY.
BILLIONS AND BILLIONS
IN 1s, 5s, AND 20s, ALL CASH,
SENT TO IRAQ FOR RECONSTRUCTION.
BRIBES.
AS NEEDED.
$9 BILLION WENT MISSING.
WAIT. BILLION WITH A "B"?
$9 BILLION
OF U.S. TAXPAYER MONEY JUST...
DISAPPEARED?
CASTLEMAN GETS A CUT OF THE BOOTY.
THE DAY THEY GO TO MOVE IT,
REAL SOLDIERS,
THEY SEE THE TRANSFER.
ONE OF THE CONTRACTORS
SPOOKS, STARTS SHOOTING.
YEAH, BUT CORPORAL PERRY
DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING.
WELL, THEY DON'T KNOW THAT.
BUT CASTLEMAN'S
A BILLION-DOLLAR COMPANY.
WHY WOULD THEY EVEN CARE
ABOUT THIS CASH?
BECAUSE IT'S CASH.
YOU KNOW, MONEY IS MONEY.
THAT'S ONE THING.
CASH IS A WHOLE OTHER THING.
FOR ALL THE MONEY IN THE ECONOMY,
THERE'S ONLY ABOUT $500 IN CASH
FOR EVERY AMERICAN, THAT'S IT.
UNTRACEABLE SMALL BILLS --
PERFECT FOR SLUSH FUNDS, OR, UM...
IMPROVEMENTS FOR A U.S. CONGRESSMAN.
SMALL-TIME DONORS,
YOU KNOw, FOR RE-ELECTION.
NO ELECTROTRAIL.
IT'S MONEY-LAUNDERING.
HOW SO?
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
CASTLEMAN USES THE ILLEGAL CASH
TO RE-ELECT HIS CONGRESSMAN.
CONGRESSMAN GETS HIM NO-BID
CONTRACTS FOR GOVERNMENT JOBS.
AND THEN THE GOVERNMENT...
...PAYS FOR HIS SERVICES
WITH LEGAL MONEY.
AND THERE'S THE CIRCLE RIGHT THERE.
THEY TURNED THE ENTIRE U.S. GOVERNMENT
INTO A MONEY-LAUNDERING SCAM.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- ???I'M IMPRESSED.
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D SAY THIS, EVER --
THAt IS JUST WAY TOO MUCH MONEY TO STEAL.
NO, YOU'RE NOT GONNA STEAL IT.
YOU DON'T REMEMBER?
YOU'RE THE GOOD GUYS NOW.
YOU'RE GONNA GIVE IT BACK.
Port of Los Angeles
CHECK THE PERIMETER.
START YOUR ROUNDS.
THE CAR IS RIGHT OTHERE!
- ???you two.
- I TOLD YOU
WE SHOULD HAVE TAKEN THE SHUTTLE BUS.
I PAID THEM $2,000 FOR FOOD POISONING.
THEY'RE NOT GETTING ANOTHER CENT!
I HAVE TO HEAR THIS AGAIN?
HEY, HEY, YOU, HEY.
COME HERE, COME HERE.
WHERE'S THE PACIFICA CRUISE,
THE PARKING LOT?
YOU PEOPLE HAVE TO
MOVE AWAY FROM THIS AREA.
YEAH, WELL, I'M TRYING TO, JACKASS.
JUST TELL ME WHERE MY CAR IS!
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT,
START A FIGHT, WHY DON'T YOU?
- AAH!
- OHH!
EXCUSE ME.
YES, SIR?
- hey yes.
- CONGRESSMAN!
- Hello, WHAT A PLEASURE!
- LOOK, I PAID A FORTUNE
FOR THESE MAHOGAANELS,
AND I'D LIKE TO KNOW
WHERE THE HELL THEY ARE.
I CAN HELP YOU WITH
THAT RIGHT HERE, SIR.
THEY CHANGED THE LOCK.
JUST DO WHAT YOU DO.
I MEAN, WHATEVER. WHAT YOU NEED?
NAH. MNH-MNH.
STOP ALL THAT PLAYIN'. MNH-MNH.
HELL NO.
AFTER SQUEEZING OUT THREE BRATS --
- AAH! HERE WE GO AGAIN.
- TREATS ME TO A LITTLE ROMANCE,
- HEY,
- JUST A LITTLE?
HEY, YOU TWO!
BACK TO YOUR POSTS.
WHAT'S TH--
- I KNOW YOU.
- WHAT?
???
???where are you go?
NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
NO!
PERIMETER, PERIMETER,
THERE'S A WHITE TRUCK COMING AT YOU.
DO NOT LET IT PASS.
stop that truck.
come on, come on.
GET OUT OF THE WAY.now!??
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
GRADY! WHAT'S GOINg in here?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WE'RE MOVING THE CONTAINER TODAY.
NOW, WHAT'S HAPPENED?
THE CONTAINER'S EMPTY.
go, go.
GET OUT OF THE TRUCK.
AND JUST WHERE
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING?
I'M JUst TRANSRTING.
NO, YOU'RE JUST GONNA OPEN THIS TRUCK.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU WORKING FOR?
YOU STUPID SON OF A BITCH!
I WILL BURY YOU!
YOU GET YOUR DAMN HANDS OFF ME!
YOU DON'T THINK WE KEPT
ALL OF YOUR e-MAILS,
ALL OF YOUR PHONE CALLS?
YOU GO DOWN WITH US ON THIS.
WHAT IS "THIS"?
THIS IS THE CONTAINER!
THE CONTAINER?
THE CONTAINER WITH THE IRAQI MONEY?
OPEN IT.
OKAY, I SEE WHAT THIS IS.
THIS IS RACIAL.
THIS IS ABOUT MY ETHNITICITY, AIN'T IT?
UH-HUH. IT'S 'CAUSE I'M JEWISH?
I'M SUPPOSED TO BELIEVE THAT
YOU JUST HAPPENED TO BE HERE
ON THE DAY THAT A COUPLE OF HUNDRED
MILLION DOLLARS IN CASH GOES MISSING?
HEY, DON'T BLAME ME!
I HELPED YOU SMUGGLE THAT
MONEY THROUGH CUSTOMS.
I BROKE LAWS. I COULD GO TO JAIL!
CONGRESSMAN?
IS THIS THE CONTAINER, CONGRESSMAN?
- UH,
- WHAT?
YOU CALLED US, CONGRESSMAN.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
UH, YOU, UH, MUST BE
MISTAKEN ABOUT THIS.
JUST 'CAUSE A BROTHER
LIKES MATZA-BALL SOUP,
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
SAMMY DAVIS --
OPEN THAT DOOR...
OR I OPEN YOUR HEAD.
NOT THIS ONE. THIS IS 542.
WHAT?
YOUR PHONE CALL SAID 541.
SIR, YOU'RE HOLDING THE KEY.
OH, YEAH, UM...
I'M JUST BACK FROM WASHINGTON FOR A DAY,
AND THEY SAY I HAVE TO
PERSONALLY COME DOWN HERE.
GIVE YOU A MAP TO YOUR
CONTAINER RIGHT THERE.
AND ONE SECOND. HOLD ON.
I'LL GET YOU THE KEY.
- DON'T. DON'T.
- THEY'RE WATCHING US.
- THEY'RE FILMING US.
- DON'T.??
CHARLES, HELP ME HERE PLEASE.
NO!
CONGRESSMAN, WHAT IS ALL THIS?
WHAT HAVE YOU UNCOVERED HERE?
I HAVE UNCOVERED...
CORRUPTION.
THIS IS CHARLES DUFORT
FROM CASTLEMAN SECURITY.
AND IN THE COURSE OF HIS COMPANY'S
VERY PATRIOTIC WORK IN IRAQ,
THEY DISCOVERED A MASSIVE
THEFT OF U.S. CURRENCY.
OUR INTEL REVEALED
THAT THIS CONTAINER LEFT
IRAQ SOME TIME LAST MONTH.
I KNEW THAT I WOULD NEED HIGH-LEVEL
HELP UNRAVELING THIS CONSPIRACY,
SO I CALLED THE MOST HONEST MAN THAT I KNOW,
CONGRESSMAN JENKINS.
AND I WANT TO TELL YOU THIS --
I, FOR ONE, AM NOT GOING TO STAND BY
AND LET THIS SORT OF
WAR-PROFITEERING CONTINUE.
DON'T YOU BLAME ME!
I HELPED YOU SMUGGLE
THAT MONEY THROUGH CUSTOMS.
I BROKE LAWS.
I COULD GO TO JAIL!
GET YOUR DAMN HANDS OFF ME!
...WE KEPT ALL OF YOUR E-MAILS,
ALL OF YOUR PHONE CALLS?
YOU GO DOWN WITH US.
CONGRESSMAN, IS THIS A CONFESSION?
- THERE'S AN EXPLANATION FOR EVERYTHING.
- ???YES, SIR,
AND WHAT IS THAT EXPLANATION?
UH...
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN
INVOLVED IN THIS SMUGGLING?
OH, CRAP.
WE'RE GONNA LEAD WITH "CRAP."
- WHAT'S THIS ABOUT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
MR. FORD SAID HE WANTED US
DOWN HERE RIGHT AWAY.
HI, GUYS.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
SHOW THEM.
AN EMPTY TRUCK?
NOTHING UP MY SLEEVE.
- IS THIS STOLEN?
- NOT ANYMORE.
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO WITH IT?
PAY FOR CORPORAL PERRY'S REHAB.
AND SOME OTXER GUYS' REHABS.
PRETTY MUCH WHATEVER YOU WANT.
DOC, A CUTE BLONDE SHOWS UP
WITH A COUPLE MILLION DOLLARS,
I SAY WE TAKE THE WIN.
THANK YOU.
CORPORAL.
THE WORLD DOESN'T WORK THIS WAY.
SO CHANGE THE WORLD.
* I SHOULD KNOW
WHO I AM BY NOW *
OKAY.
*...THE RECORD STANDS SOMEHOW *
* THINKING OF WINTER *
WE GOT IT, we... WE GOT IT.
WE CAN TAKE CARE OF EVERYBODY.
*WHILE I WAIT *
I GET HALF, RIGHT?
NO, YOU DON'T GET HALF.
YES, I DO! I GET IT HALF.
ANYBODY WHO WANTS TO WALK
AWAY CAN DO IT RIGHT NOW.
* AND I REMEMBER... *
ONE MORE.
MAYBE TWO.
* OF YOUR NOVEMBER DOWNTOWN *
I BOUGHT A PLANT.
NICE. TEAM SPIRIT.
WHAT DOES IT DO?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GAVE
ALL YOUR MONEY AWAY.
YOU DIDN'T BUY YOURSELF ANYTHING?
I BOUGHT A CAR.
PROBABLY A STATION WAGON.
- AN ELECTRIC CAR.
- OF COURSE.
HOW SWEET. DO YOU
HAVE TO WIND IT UP?
EH, JUST TRYING TO BE RESPONSIBLE.
RESPONSIBLE?
YOU KNOW, IT SUCKS TO BE THE GOOD GUY.
YOU HAVEN'T FIGURED IT OUT YET, HAVE YOU?
JUST 'CAUSE
YOU'RE THE GOOD GUYS NOW...
DOESN'T MEAN YOU CAN'T HAVE
A LITTLE FUN ALONG THE WAY.
WHOO-HOO.
- OH, BOY. MIDLIFE CRISIS.
- ABSOLUTELY.
DEFINITELY MIDLIFE.
TOTALLY MIDLIFE CRISIS.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net