Kids, your uncle Barney had been
called a lot of names over the years.
Jerk!
Bastard!
Barack Obama Jr.?!
And yes...
we can.
But there's one name none of us
ever expected to hear him called.
Boyfriend.
Barney Stinson is my boyfriend.
I've said it, like, a hundred times
it still sounds weird to say.
Anything sounds weird
if you say it a hundred times.
Bowl.
But other than that,
things are good?
I don't know.
I think Barney's been single
for too long.
Like, the other night,
I wake up at 4:00 a.m...
Barney, are you awake?
This is not a one-night stand.
We're dating. Come back to bed.
That's happened three times. And
it's not just that, it's other things.
What's wrong?
It was just one thing after another
at work today, and then...
I found out my aunt's
in the hospital.
I'm just, I'm feeling
so overwhelmed and it's just...
What you need to do
is talk through this stuff.
Thanks.
And then, once you're
off the phone with Lily,
I'll be down in the bar
ready to have sex. Okay?
Look, I'm not the touchy-feely-est
person in the world, but...
- a little more effort would be nice.
- I understand.
I guess, in a lot of ways,
Barney doesn't stack up.
I mean, you've had some pretty
incredible boyfriends.
No, that's not it.
I don't know.
Maybe he just
doesn't have it in him.
Maybe is whole thing's
a big mistake.
- She really said that?
- And she meant it.
Trust me. I dated Robin for a year...
if you don't want to lose her,
you gotta try a little harder.
Be more attentive to where
she is emotionally. Just...
- be present.
- Yes, totally.
Only thing, and this is just me...
I like my testicles attached
to my body, rather than rolling around
next to some eyeliner
in Robin's purse. Stinson out!
But then a funny thing happened.
Over the next couple weeks,
Barney was thoughtful,
considerate...
sweet.
In short, the perfect boyfriend.
Which, to Robin,
meant only one thing.
- He's cheating on me.
- What?!
Why else would he buy me flowers?
He's gettin' some on the side.
Barney's not the type of guy
who would... go on.
Plus, he keeps saying
he's working late.
But when I call his office,
they say he left hours ago.
- That doesn't prove anything.
- Yes. Proof.
Good word.
I'm glad you brought that up.
Barney's briefcase.
He forgot it here this morning.
- And what do you plan on doing with it?
- We, we...
you and I... are going to open it up
and look for evidence.
Ted probably has a sledgehammer
around here somewhere.
Stop! Stop! Eye contact.
Listen to me.
Robin Scherbatsky is many things:
friend, confidant, occasional
guest star in some confusing dreams
that remind me a woman's
sexuality is a moving target.
But she is no crazy,
jealous stalker-bitch.
Let go.
I've been down in the basement storage
area going through all the stuff that
Lily and I left behind when
we moved out. I'm sorry Robin.
We should've cleared it out
for you much sooner.
- There's a basement storage area?
- You're not upset. Good.
Baby, guess what I found.
- That's great, honey.
- What the hell is that?
Marshall got it in college.
He used it as a nightstand for years.
Until we found out that Lily
was allergic to barrel resin
- Barrel resin?
- Just go with it.
- You need a hand throwing it out?
- No, I'm not...
I'm not just going to throw her out,
okay? Mabel's like family.
So... what are you going
to do with Mabel?
I want to give her away... to a lucky
new owner. Do you know anyone?
Let me think.
Do I know any rodeo clowns?
That's weird, I do. But even Lenny
wouldn't go near that mess.
He's not going to have the chance,
because I am putting old Mabel
in the Bermuda Triangle.
"The Bermuda Triangle"
was the name we'd given
years earlier to the curb right
in front of our building.
Whenever we wanted to give something
away, we'd put it right there.
It was uncanny.
This is so exciting.
Right now there's some out there
who has no idea that tonight
they're going home with just...
just the best barrel.
Let's just hope they're not allergic
to barrel sin like Lily here.
Be cool, baby. Damn!
- See you, sweetie. Good luck.
- Bye, babe.
- Now, can we please get out of here?
- I'll grab my coat.
A college notebook?!
My God, he's cheating on me
with some college girl.
I knew there was a skank but
I thought she'd at least be dumb.
"Birthday: July 23. Favorite hockey
team: the Vancouver Canucks.
Age: 29, but tells people
that she's 26."
My God, these are notes about me.
Or some 29-year-old version of me.
I hope I'm not too late!
I want to see the look of joy
on the new owner's face!
She's still there!
Okay Mabel, let's find
you a new home.
Here comes a guy!
He has walked,
walked right on by it.
He's probably rushing home to
get a handcart or something.
Hey, better hurry up, pal.
What are you guys doing with
Barney's secret Robin notebook?
Let me rephrase that.
Did you...
two ladies lose some weight?
What do you know
about this, Marshall?
Why would Barney have a notebook
full of information about me?
The truth was...
Barney was taking a
night school class taught...
by me.
Welcome
to Robin 101.
Synchro: Mickeyte & MiniBen314
Traduction: Dark_Chii,
Eomyn, Lino72, Litéo & MiniBen314
Relecture: MiniBen314
How I Met Your Mother
5x03 - Robin 101
par la "Have You Met Team"
pour www.forom.com
Why is Ted teaching
a class about me?
It all started a few weeks ago.
... rather than rolling around next
to some eyeliner in Robin's purse.
Stinson out!
Stinson back in.
Say...
hypothetically, I did
want to change who I am
to become a better boyfriend to Robin,
which I do not!
What kind of changes
are we talking about?
Why, I mean, there's just so much
you need to know about her.
Okay, for starters,
don't ever cry in front her.
And whatever you do,
don't cry in front
of her four times.
- What should you talking about?
- Fantasy football.
They realized they couldn't talk about
this stuff at the bar, and
since you live with Ted,
they had to find someplace safe.
So... Ted's classroom.
"How To Date Robin Scherbatsky."
Lesson one.
Now, even though she puts up
a tough exterior,
what Robin really wants,
deep down...
I'm bored.
- You said you wanted my help.
- Can we draw boobs on the chalkboard?
- We did that all ready.
- No, like, really big boobs.
No. Look, I need this, too.
I've only been a professor a few weeks.
Being up here...
it's good practice for me.
Can we have class outside?
What Robin really wants deep down...
What? I'm tweeting about you.
You should be flattered.
How do you spell...
"H's" or no?
You were just... like, the worst
student in the world, weren't you?
They said I had A-D...
something.
Can we have class outside?
Barney, I'm only gonna
say this once,
so listen up.
I love you
and I love Robin.
And I want to make this work.
So if you give me
a few weeks of attention,
I could give you
a lifetime of happiness.
Can you do that for me?
Do you think I should get Sports
Illustrated for 70% off the cover price?
Can we have class outside?
I got to find a way
to reach this kid.
"Class number two."
"Top ten Robin Scherbatsky facial
expressions and their meaning."
Now, notice the vacant eyes,
the pale, queasy expression,
suggesting nausea.
- What do these mean?
- You guys just had sex?
Wasn't me.
Dude! I worked really hard
on these slides, okay? Can we just...
This look is hunger. If you ever see
Robin looking like this,
get some food in her quick,
or one of two things will happen.
One:
weird, out-of-context laughter
or two:
spontaneously falling
to sleep in strange places.
But...
the most important facial
expression of all?
That's a building.
That's for my class.
The Flatiron Building.
Fun story about it. It was designed
by Chicago's Daniel Burnham
in the Beaux-arts style.
This architectural...
The most important facial expression
of all.
Flared nostril ridges.
Wide, unblinking eyes.
If you ever,
ever see this face, Barney,
run.
And don't... take a picture of it.
She will punch you.
And you will cry...
for the third time...
that night.
Which brings us
to an important point:
defusing the bomb.
"Defusing the bomb"?
What does that even mean?
"Three topics to distract Robin
from being mad at you."
"Distract me"?
That is so condescending.
These guys are really
starting to piss me off!
"Immediately switch the conversation
to one of the following,
unless you want Robin to start
throwing her shoes."
"Vancouver Canucks
2004 division title."
What?! That's not distracting.
That's just talking about the story
of a scrappy little underdog team
that prevailed despite
very shaky goal ending
and, frankly, the declining
skills of Trevor Linden.
"Proper gun cleaning
and maintenance."
You have to clean your gun.
My uncle had a filthy old shotgun,
blew both his thumbs off
trying to shoot a beaver.
You want to distract someone,
make them watch my uncle
try to eat corn on the cob.
"Emperor penguins."
Did you know that
before intercourse,
the male and female emperor
penguins bow to each other?
Mr. Penguin.
Mrs. Penguin.
Oh, God, silly penguins,
acting all fancy.
What were we talking about?
Looks like we got a taker.
Oh, come on, dude.
You know you want to
a guy like you, beard, no mustache.
You're exactly the kind of guy
who could use a sweet barrel. Do it.
That's not a fire hydrant!
For shame, Sir.
For shame!
I bet you couldn't even grow
a mustache if you wanted to.
- Neither can you, sweetie.
- He doesn't know that, baby! God!
Ted's only teaching Barney
horrible things about me.
I don't know. Check this out.
This is actually kind of sweet.
Now, we all know Robin's not
what you'd call "touchy-feely."
She doesn't say, "I love you",
like a normal person.
Instead, she'll laugh,
shake her head, give you
a little smile and say:
"You're an idiot."
"You're an idiot"?
If she tells you you're an idiot,
you're a lucky man.
And if she does say "I love you",
she's already broken up
with you in her mind.
I think's nice
that Ted knows you that well.
Too bad it's next
to a page entitled...
"Robin Scherbatsky's
surprising erogenous zones."
Right knee...
ticklish.
Left knee...
Does lefty like that?
Lefty like that.
I can't believe I'm taking
sexual advice from Ted Mosby.
That's like taking
fashion advice from...
well, Ted Mosby.
Here's a good one.
"Top five things never
to do around Robin."
"Never, ever play the
"Guess Who" game with her".
What do you mean?
Guess who?
It's me!
Number four: "Unless you want
to see it 80 times a day,
for the next month, never
show Robin a YouTube clip
of an animal playing
a musical instrument."
Do you have a problem
with this class?
It's boring as hell and
I'm not learning anything.
Maybe the problem is your attitude.
You're not listening to a word I say.
Can you hear this, Professor?
Or should I turn it up for you?
It may not have been
a thumbs-up, kids.
You think you're not
learning anything?
- Pop quiz.
- What...
When Robin's PMS-ing, what kind
of chocolate should you get her?
- Trick question. Get her butterscotch.
- Correct! Why?
Butterscotch is to Canadian women
what chocolate is to American women.
What is Robin's dream job?
To become the most successful
female TV journalist of all time.
And if she achieves that,
will she truly be happy?
Robin's deep-seated need
for attention can traced back
to her father's emotional distance, and
no amount of success will ever make up
for what she truly needs, which is
six simple words from her Dad,
"Robin, I'm proud of you, eh?"
But I guess you're right.
You haven't learned anything.
Sorry to have wasted your time.
"O Captain! My Captain!"
How good was Dead Poet's Society?
I know, right? The end? Tears.
Can I just say that
my deepest need in life
is not to have my father to say,
"I am proud of you, eh?"
Than why are you crying right now?
- I'm not crying.
- Oh, sweetie.
- Can I get you some butterscotch?
- Stop it.
Wait a second. It says here that
the class meets at 6:15 on Tuesday.
- So?
- That's right now.
Now, as you can see,
well over 50% of the blankets
have been dragged onto her side.
Make no mistake.
Robin Scherbatsky
is a classic,
textbook...
cover hog.
- Any questions?
- I have one.
Yes, Robin?
Flared nostril ridges.
Wide, unblinking eyes.
I got this.
Emperor penguins... crazy?
What the hell do you
two think you're doing?
Did you sells out?
I was vulnerable.
I said good-bye to
a very dear friend today.
Dude, it's a barrel!
- You're giving Mabel away?
- I have so many questions.
Why would you do this?
What were you thinking?
Who the hell is that guy?
That's Shin-Ya. He's sort of
been auditing the class.
"Auditing"?
I tried to explain to him
it wasn't a real class,
but I don't think he speaks
much English.
On the bright side, he came
in handy standing in for you
- during the role-playing exercises.
- Wait. You did role-playing exercises
where I was played by Shin-Ya?
You know, I can't believe you, Ted.
You actually think you're
some kind of an expert on me?
He is an expert.
He's a great teacher!
Kiss ass.
You know, half the stuff in this
notebook is patently wrong.
Really? Name one wrong thing.
"Robin Scherbatsky's surprising
erogenous zones"?
Let me clear something up
for you, Ted.
Does lefty like that?
The right one's ticklish, I guess.
But the left one, yeah,
I'm glad you're back there.
Because that is just some
sweet, sweet lovin'.
Noted.
- That was a lie?
- We had just started dating.
I was being nice.
And you.
You know, I got it into my head
this week that you were cheating on me.
I even broke open your briefcase
to look for evidence.
That is a huge
violation of my privacy!
Go on.
You know, in a way, I was right.
You cheated. You can't get
some crib sheet on dating me.
That's not how it works.
If we didn't figure out how to be with
each other in a real, honest way,
I don't see the
point of even trying.
What do you want?
Look.
All that stuff I told Barney...
It was personal between you and me.
I'm really sorry.
I guess I'm impressed
by how much you remembered.
It's funny.
When you date someone,
it's like you're
taking one long course
in who that person is
and then, when you break up,
all that stuff becomes useless.
It's the emotional equivalent
of an English degree.
I guess I just liked the idea of
putting all my Robin Scherbatsky
knowledge to good use, you know?
Since you know me pretty well...
am I fooling myself
with this whole Barney thing?
I don't know.
I will say this, though.
I've seen Barney work
very hard to get women.
I've seen him work very
hard to get rid of women.
I've never seen him work
this hard to keep one around.
I was going to give him an A.
Well, B+...
Shin-Ya kind of screwed up the curve.
Before you say anything, I am done
with this stupid Robin 101, okay?
Here, I'll get rid of the notebook.
But there's... there's something that
I did want to say to you.
Robin, I have been
with a lot of women...
blondes, brunettes,
redheads,
big boobs,
small boobs,
medium boobs,
some boobs that were big,
but kind of in a bad way.
The point is... boobs that pointed
in opposite direc... The point is...
I'm really scared that
you're going to dump me
and that's why I did this
and I'm sorry.
You're an idiot.
You know...
That notebook... does contain
a lot of personal info,
and I think it has my home address.
And your work address.
Guys! If you don't want the barrel,
can you sit somewhere else? Cause...
You're scaring away
potential takers.
Designed by Chicago's Daniel Burnham
in the Beaux-arts style,
this architectural gem
was the first of its kind...
- Professor Mosby?
- Yes, Susan?
That's a woman drinking beer
on the toilet.
Right. That...
was Daniel Burnham's wife.
She was a troubled,
troubled woman. We are moving on.