Energy ball.
Nice teamwork.
You mean, nice sister work.
We are definitely
getting better at this.
Well, we should be,
we've been doing it long enough.
- I think we're ready.
- So do I.
I don't.
- Something is still missing.
- What do you mean?
How many more demons
do we have to vanquish?
We've been training for this
for, like, eight years.
Five for me.
But still,
we've mastered their powers.
Their individual powers, yes.
But you're still missing
their collective power.
The power of three.
And until you get it,
you will never truly replace
the Charmed Ones.
Anyone down here?
Big box and high heels.
Need some help.
Just a sec.
Sorry. Do you need help?
Well, I did.
Now I just need a sec.
Okay, well, since I have you...
Piper, I'm kind of running late.
I have to go sign the loan docs
and I want to stop by the condo
before work.
Loan docs?
Wow, I didn't realise
this was moving along so quickly.
But, you know, I've been so focussed
on getting Leo back.
Yeah, I know.
But I have made a list of seers
and oracles
and anyone that might be able
to foresee
who we'll have to fight
in order to get him back.
Great. Okay, well, call me
if you find anything.
Well, I was thinking...
I was thinking that maybe
you should take my Jeep
because my car holds so much more
than yours does.
- Doesn't it?
- Right.
Piper, are you sure
you're okay with me moving out?
Yeah, of course I am.
I mean, we can't be
roommates forever.
That's just weird.
Okay. Well, here I go.
What am I gonna do?
I'm supposed to have a date
with Henry tonight
and he is in the worst mood.
He's lost his car keys,
he's lost his wallet,
he's locked himself
out of his apartment,
and I need him to be in a good mood
for what I want to do tonight.
We aren't talking about sex, are we?
No, we're not talking about sex.
I finally screwed up my courage
to tell him, you know, that I'm a witch
and I feel like I have to do it tonight,
otherwise I might wuss out.
I really need to know
if he's okay with who I am.
You've been through this a lot,
Pheebs. Got any advice?
Well, hope he doesn't faint.
No, I don't know.
I mean, I haven't had any success
with these things.
Just ease into it, you know,
try to lessen the blow.
Okay, how?
Maybe call in
some reinforcements?
Maybe ask some of your
magical friends
to help him have a better day
so you could have a better night?
Like fairies or something?
Sure, fairies, leprechauns,
whatever.
Good luck.
Pheebs?
I was actually hoping that maybe
you could help me narrow down
the list a little bit before you go.
Oh, Piper, I'm really late.
Oh, okay.
Well, you know, it's just Leo.
Really, come on.
All I need is one little premonition.
- How hard can it be?
- Okay.
What more do we have to do
to convince you?
Convincing me is irrelevant.
We'll only get one shot
at freeing our brethren.
We know that, Savard.
We also know that there's a reason
why our kind has been enslaved
for centuries.
The Slave King
is no ordinary demon.
We escaped.
Yes.
So we could return
with enough power to destroy him,
a power I'm not sure we've got yet.
But we've spent the last eight years
replicating the greatest power there is.
Charmed power.
And we've not only studied
every aspect of what they know
and who they are.
We've infused our blood
with their magical blood,
so that their power is our power.
Which means we may already have
the power of three.
But you haven't showed it yet!
In any test or trial.
Which means you don't have it.
And you need to get it
if we have any hopes
of destroying the Slave King.
There must be a way.
Think back.
Tap into your knowledge
of the witches.
Phoebe was stuck
in a genie's bottle once.
If we could trap her in it again,
maybe we could command her,
master to genie, to tell us how.
Forget it.
Leo got rid of the bottle.
What about using the sword,
Excalibur?
No, only Wyatt can wield it.
Okay, maybe I could pose as Paige,
trick the Elders into helping us.
Right, like that's gonna work.
Look, do you have any ideas?
Or are you just gonna shoot down
all of ours?
At least I don't come up
with stupid ideas.
- Stupid?
- Hey!
Knock it off.
At least you've got
the sibling rivalry down pat.
Wait. The dollhouse.
It's a magical replica
of the real house, isn't it?
Which is believed to be magical
in and of itself.
The house is
the witches' power base,
has been for generations.
So?
So if we could trap all of them
inside the dollhouse...
Like Piper was trapped
once before...
Then we've got
the power of three contained.
And if we're in the real manor
while they're in the dollhouse...
We might be able to channel
the power of three into us.
It just might work.
Anybody up there?
Hello?
Billie, what are you doing?
What else?
Still trying to find my sister.
Trying to figure out what
this symbol means or where it leads.
I figure it has to be demonic, right?
- No, I mean...
- I mean, if it's in her diary,
you'd think I'd be able to find
something about it in this book, but I...
Billie, what are you doing
in Phoebe's room?
Oh, well, she said
I could hang out in here
because she's not gonna be using it.
Is that okay?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
I mean, you know, if she's not
gonna be using it anymore.
Maybe I should just take this stuff
to my dorm.
Oh, no, no, no. Don't be ridiculous.
I just, you know, I wish she would have
said something, that's all.
Is that her spirit board?
Yeah, she said I could borrow it
to try and contact Christy.
Can I?
Yeah, you know.
Sure, if you want to start
paying rent.
Just kidding.
Can I borrow the "Book?"
Hey, where did it go?
Hey, there. Okay, here's the thing.
My sort of hopefully-
he'Il-become-my boyfriend, Henry,
he's having a bit of a problem
losing things,
like a wallet, his keys, you know,
stuff like that.
And, not to cast any aspersions
on your character,
you guys are known
for the kind of sticky-finger problem.
So I was wondering
if you could go back to your people
and tell them
to put everything back.
That would help me so much
because I really, really, really need
his undivided attention tonight.
Thank you.
Paige, what are you doing?
Just taking Phoebe's advice.
Really, it's the most amazing thing.
I mean,
first my keys turn up in the laundry,
then one of my parolees
finds my wallet.
- Still has everything in it.
- That's great.
My 49ers hat, I lost it in high school,
my letterman's jacket.
It's like everything is turning up,
it's crazy.
Very subtle.
I mean, very...
Very lucky.
Some would say magical.
Yeah, I don't know, but I'll take it.
So, good. We still on for dinner?
What's so important
you can't tell me now?
You're just gonna have to wait
and hear all about it tonight.
Seven o'clock okay?
Look, Paige, five of my parolees
have job interviews tomorrow.
They all asked me to write letters
of recommendations for them tonight.
Okay, write them.
Yeah, well, that's a little easier said
than done.
I'm not a writer, Paige.
But look, please don't think that
I don't wanna go out with you, okay?
I do. I have all this work.
I don't want to let these guys down.
Who knows? Maybe I'll get inspired.
I think you should count on that.
I'll see you at 7, Henry.
Being of creativity
Show yourself to me
Hey, Muse, right?
Could you do me a huge favour
and inspire my friend Henry in there?
I'd really appreciate it.
Thank you.
Phoebe, Piper is on line 2-5.
Okay, got it.
Hey, what's up?
Have you ever heard of a wizard
named Zakal?
No, why?
Well, he's been around for ages
and supposedly
he's very well-connected.
He worked for the Source
back in the day.
Are you typing?
No. No, I'm not writing,
of course I'm not writing.
Phoebe, this is important.
- This guy could know who's after us.
- Or not.
Look, sweetie, bringing Leo home
is the most important thing
in the world.
To all of us.
But it's not gonna happen overnight.
It's also not gonna happen
if we don't try.
Yeah, but we have been trying.
And we can't just stop living our lives,
you know?
I mean, you said so yourself.
Yeah, well, I didn't mean it.
Look, I just don't want to lose
this lead, okay?
He could know something.
All right, look,
I haven't signed the loan docs yet,
- so why don't I swing by after work...
- Well, you have my car.
And the car seats are in my car.
Well, I have to drop the kids off
at Dad's, don't I?
Okay, you know what?
I'm beginning to think
that you're sabotaging me moving out.
Are you kidding me? Please,
I've already rented out your room.
Oh, by the way,
could you do me a favour
and pick up some mandrake root
on your way home?
If this guy Zakal
doesn't wanna be cooperative,
we may need a vanquishing potion.
Okay? Thanks.
Hi.
Hello.
I've always admired
her sense of fashion.
Keys are in the pocket.
Remember,
get the sisters to use
the power of three as soon as possible
so we can see
if it's going to work or not.
But we have no idea
what's going on in their lives right now.
Just wing it.
Be yourself.
Or rather, be Phoebe.
Just don't get too eager.
You'll tip the sisters off.
Piper?
Paige?
First time's a foot.
Next time,
a fireball.
Hey, good, you're back.
How'd it go with Henry?
Oh, not so hot.
I had to summon a muse.
Oh, fairy wasn't cutting it?
No. I cannot believe how hard it is
just to tell somebody about magic.
Just wait till you have to explain
demons to him.
Which, by the way,
we will be going after one
if Phoebe ever gets home.
- It's a big adjustment, huh?
- No.
I mean, she's moved out before.
Right. Are you okay with it?
Why does everybody
keep asking me that?
Oh, I don't know.
Because you guys have lived together
since the age of zero?
Believe me, I'm fine. Really.
Really. I just need her to help me
with this wizard and that's all.
Oh, hello.
- Hey, there.
- Can I come in?
Of course you can come in,
don't be ridiculous.
- Thank you for coming.
- Well, great.
- Whatever you need.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
So what do you need?
The mandrake root?
Oh, right, the mandrake root.
Where exactly
do we keep that again?
You were supposed to get some
on your way home.
You know,
for the whole wizard situation.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Are we gonna need the power of three,
by any chance, for this?
You know we will.
What's the matter with you?
Oh, you know, it's just...
Oh, it's probably just the move.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, so let's see
where I put that mandrake root.
Oh, yeah, here it is.
Now, let's go get those demons,
shall we?
How'd that feel?
Last time.
Have you or have you not foreseen
any threats against us?
I'm old. I'm afraid my visions
haven't been very reliable lately.
- Oh, bull. Let's just vanquish him.
- Wait.
You don't have to do this so quickly.
We could probably
get some stuff out of him.
Help us and we'll spare you.
All I'll tell you is,
that by the time you figure out
which demon is after you,
it'll be too late!
- All right, you know what? Forget this.
- Phoebe, no, no, no!
I did it.
Yeah, you did it. Why?
What do you mean? He's a demon.
We vanquish demons.
I mean, that's what we do, right?
Yeah, actually,
but we could have made him talk first.
No, not Zakal.
I mean, you know,
it's not like he was gonna say anything.
Well, he's certainly
not gonna say anything now.
What the hell were you thinking?
- Well?
- It worked.
She blasted Zakal
right out of his robe.
Using the power of three?
- Definitely.
- All right.
It's time to switch one more sister.
Wait, one more?
Why not both of us?
I mean, we know we can channel
the power of three now,
so let's just go vanquish
the Slave King.
We cannot vanquish him
without the potion, which means
we need a witch to find it for us
in the "Book of Shadows. "
So why don't we go look for it?
Because you might be able to fool
the sisters,
but you cannot fool the "Book. "
It senses evil.
He's right.
You'll go.
Play on Piper's desire
to get Leo back.
Make it look like the Slave King
is behind it all.
She will do anything
to get her husband back.
Wait a second,
I'm still talking to you.
Well, I said I was sorry.
What more would you like me to say?
I want you to tell me why you did that,
why you didn't wait for my cue.
Well, because I was afraid
we were gonna be attacked.
Yeah, well, I'm afraid of losing Leo.
Okay, don't use the guilt card with me
like you did with Cole.
Cole?
Can you think of perhaps
a maybe more recent example?
Well, yeah, I can
but I can't right now,
- because I'm a little flustered.
- Guys.
I cannot believe that you care more
about getting back
to your new condo than Leo.
How can you even say that?
Well, do you have
another explanation?
Well, yes. I do.
But I'm not gonna tell you.
Phoebe?
Billie.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Well, you told me
I could use your room, right?
Oh, yeah. Right.
I just meant
I didn't know you were still here.
- Do you want me to leave?
- No.
No, don't be silly.
So why don't you tell me about
how your search for Chrissie is going.
You mean Christy?
Yeah. Yeah, you know what I mean.
Whatever.
First, all she cares about
is her stupid condo,
then she comes back here to help,
and now she's suddenly
trigger-happy?
She's all over the map.
I'm sure there's some
perfectly good reason.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I am still waiting for it.
- Maybe she was just flustered.
- Flustered?
If anybody has the right
to be flustered around here,
it would be the newly single mom.
You're right.
Now I have to go find
another damn wizard.
Where is the "Book?"
I guess it's still in the attic.
Hey, mister.
- You better not be cancelling on me.
- I'm not.
Unless you're breaking up with me,
then maybe I should.
Oh, got you scared, huh?
A little bit, little bit.
I finished those letters.
And wrote you a love letter.
- Got inspired.
- I can't wait to hear it.
Assuming you still want
to read it to me.
Why wouldn't I?
Henry, they need you
down at the station. Now.
Hang on a second, Paige.
What's going on?
GPS went down
on your parolees' transmitters.
- Sergeant needs you to find them.
- Great.
- Well, what does that mean?
- It means I gotta go.
What about dinner?
Sorry, Paige, bad luck.
I'm not on call, you know.
Look, I'm not in the mood, okay?
Really, really, I'm not.
And besides, you guys owe me.
Oh, remember a little somebody
named Shamus?
So now it's blackmail, is it?
No, it's not blackmail.
Look, I just need my boyfriend Henry
to have a little bit of luck,
which is why I need your help.
So just please, go meet me
at the police station in an hour
and I will explain
everything to you, okay?
All right, but don't be late.
I'm a busy leprechaun, you know.
Don't you just hate leprechauns?
You know what to do.
Yes.
I think I do.
Welcome to the dollhouse.
We're trapped,
and even worse than that,
we're really, really small.
Okay.
Are you saying that that means
there's no way out of this place?
Well, unless
you wanna get squished.
This can't be. I have a date tonight.
Sorry, can't miss it.
Give me your hand.
We're orbing out of here.
Yeah, but...
Why didn't that work?
What is wrong with my powers?
See, that's what
I'm trying to tell you.
I think our powers
were downsized as well.
Rock.
Who's he?
He's the demon that replaced us
with look-alikes,
which, by the way, I can't even believe
that you didn't notice that wasn't me.
Well, sorry.
You only vanquished a wizard with us.
I mean, she van... She... Her...
The not you...
Whatever.
Wait a second.
We used the power of three.
Yeah, I think that's part of their plan.
They keep us here
and then use the power of three
to vanquish some guy
named the Slave King
and unfortunately, us.
Well, we have to get to Piper somehow
before they do.
Yeah, but how?
So then I tried to match the symbol
with the council
but it wasn't a direct match,
it just didn't work.
I don't understand.
Yeah, you know what?
That's just a really boring story.
- Boring?
- Yeah.
I think you should just give up.
I mean, it's not like
you're gonna really find her anyway.
Paige, don't start with me, okay?
- I have a headache.
- Forget it, lady.
I'm on to you.
What do you mean?
Relax. It's just me, Patra.
Oh, thank God.
This sister stuff is taxing.
Don't worry, it'll all be over soon.
There you are.
If you two are up here
to gang up on me, forget it.
No, of course not.
Phoebe has come to apologise,
haven't you, Phoebe?
Really?
Okay.
I'm listening.
Well, Piper, I just wanted to say
that I'm sorry
for not being myself lately.
And if it seems that I don't care
about what you're going through,
- I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry too.
Well, great.
Now that that's taken care of,
- I've got a lead.
- What? How?
Whitelighter grapevine.
Turns out there's a fast-rising demon
in the underworld
known as the Slave King.
Oh, the Slave King.
Yeah, I've heard of him.
Really? I haven't.
Well, the Elders have.
What do you say we track him down
and see if we can find anything?
I don't know. I think we should focus
on this demonic seer I found.
No, no.
The Elders say he's pretty evil.
He's enslaved an entire demonic race
for centuries now.
Well, that actually sounds
like a good thing.
No, it's not.
He's forcing them
to do his demonic bidding.
It's just something
we should check on, that's all.
- What have we got to lose?
- Yeah.
You two seem awfully gung ho
about this.
Well, anything to find Leo, hon.
Should we look at the "Book?"
I can't believe I'm being stood up
by a witch.
- So you see anything?
- Not yet.
Why didn't you meet me
like you said?
Oh, I'm sorry. You are?
Someone who's got better things to do
than chasing the whims of a witch.
No matter how good you've been
to the little people.
Well, I've just been busy
helping my sister.
Well, I was just trying to give
your boyfriend a little luck.
That is what you want, isn't it?
That sounds just swell.
So how about you go give that guy
some luck?
Scamper off, skedaddle.
Go with God.
Fine. But after this, we're even.
Now, where were we?
Hey, Henry, you're in luck.
- Look who I found.
- Jamison, where did you find him?
I was just walking in
and there he was.
Walked right up to me
and turned himself in.
Henry.
I got two more for you.
Caught them
just before they left town.
Where'd you find them?
I've been looking for them for weeks.
Yeah, it's Mitchell.
What?
I just won 10 thou...?
I just won 10,000 dol...
I just won $10,000!
What is going on today?
Well, he's powerful
but he's no seer.
I don't know why he would know
who's after us.
Maybe the Elders don't know
what they're talking about.
Well, who are we to question them?
We question them all the time.
Right. Maybe this time
they just know something we don't.
Okay, can we get on with this?
I have to get to work.
Any vanquishing potion in there?
No.
Okay, well, we can make one, right?
There should be one
in the back of the "Book,"
just flip to the back of the "Book. "
I know, thank you.
What was that?
Did you see that?
See what?
You didn't see that?
That was weird. I felt like somebody
was calling me or something.
That is odd.
Is that the potion?
All right,
what is the matter with you two?
This:
Cave.
It's about time.
Okay, we're gonna need
some henbane,
gypsy's blood and hemlock root.
Together again.
Oh, Piper, are you okay?
No, you punched me.
I did not punch you.
It was her demonic double.
What? What are you talking about?
We've been replaced.
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't tell me
we're stuck in the dollhouse.
Well, it seems to be an annual event
for you.
Oh, I should have known
they were demons.
Speaking of demons,
did they mention
the Slave King to you?
Yes, right before I showed them
the vanquishing potion.
Oh, great.
Okay, well, there's nothing
you could have done.
Maybe if I'd
been around more lately.
No, forget about it, Phoebe,
it wasn't your fault.
The question is,
how do we get out of here?
We couldn't even call you
with the lost-witch spell.
Oh, that was you.
I thought I felt something.
- Maybe it'll work on Billie?
- How?
We don't even have enough power
to cast a spell.
No, but maybe we have enough
to get through to the spirit board.
Do you think Grams
made a replica of that?
Christy?
D- O-L-L
H- O-U-S-E.
Dollhouse?
You guys,
the weirdest thing just happened.
- Not now.
- Mustard seed.
No, but you don't understand.
The spirit board, it worked.
I actually got a message.
What kind of message?
Well, it spelled out "dollhouse"
and I don't think that was from Christy,
but you guys have a dollhouse, right?
- Actually, we got rid of it.
- Keep stirring.
But I thought I saw Wyatt
playing with it a few days ago.
We'll look for it later.
We have a demon to vanquish.
Don't you think
this means something?
I do believe that my sister
just asked you to leave.
- Excuse me?
- Are you dense?
We really don't have time
for your crap right now.
This is a joke, right?
You guys have to be joking.
Do we look like we're joking?
Did anybody ever tell you
what a giant pain in the ass you are?
What?
I don't know
why we keep you around.
- But...
- Get rid of her.
Gladly.
Front porch.
That was fun.
You think we were too hard on her?
- I would hate to have blown our cover.
- Doesn't matter.
We don't have to look
like the Charmed Ones anymore.
We've got the power of three.
It's time to free our kind.
How dare you escape me?
And how dare you return!
Come closer.
You would have been wise to have
taken your own lives on the outside
rather than suffer through how
I'm going to take them for you.
Where's the other? Savard.
He's waiting for us
to bring him the good news.
Good news? What good news?
Of your demise.
- Kill them.
- Now.
It worked.
We did it.
I don't believe it.
Just out of curiosity,
if this doesn't work, what's plan B?
This is plan B.
Billie was plan A.
Well, remind me to evict her
if we get out of this.
You sure this is gonna work?
Well, I hope so. It's your plan.
You have a point there.
Okay,
do it now.
Pointy thing.
Oh, it only moved a little.
Well, maybe that's because
I am little.
Okay, well, try again. Keep trying.
Pointy thing.
Better. Better.
Okay, Piper, you're up.
Hey.
Hello? We'd like to have a little chat
down here.
Okay, a little to the left.
Pointy thing.
- Perfect.
- What do you want?
You.
Let's get out of here.
- Where's Savard?
- Savard?
Oh, I think
they have a height advantage.
Our kind is finally free,
but now Savard will never see it.
I don't understand.
How could they have killed him?
I don't know, but they did.
Okay, if Billie doesn't show up
in, like, two seconds, we're doll parts.
Hang on,
there might be another way.
Talk fast.
Well, our individual powers
are diminished,
but not the power of three.
- Obviously, they're using it.
- Talk faster.
Well, if we can get them
to stop channelling us
and use their demonic powers,
then we can get
the power of three back, you know?
Theoretically speaking, right?
All we got are theories.
This is for Savard.
Hey, hang on a second,
what are you doing?
What, you're gonna kill me
with my own power?
What are you, kidding me?
How insulting. Let alone boring.
Yeah, show some pride,
you know what I mean? Be original.
You guys must suffer from really low
self-esteem, near as I can figure.
Which is clearly why
they had to steal our powers.
That must be very humiliating.
Oh, thank God.
I knew you guys wouldn't really be
that mean to me.
I know I can be
a huge pain in the ass sometimes...
Billie, zip it! Go get the "Book. "
Oh, the "Book," right.
Find the power-switching spell.
Switch...
Switch bodies with powers
and then, you know, improvise.
Okay, who are we switching?
Them.
I thought we booted your ass out.
You did, but they didn't.
What's theirs is yours
What's yours is theirs
I offer up this gift to share
Switch the bodies through the air
Well, you wanted to live like us,
now I guess you get to die like us.
Oh, crap.
Well, they say imitation
is the greatest form of flattery.
Well, they do.
Hey, Henry.
Yeah.
- Guess what?
- What?
I like you.
Hey, Paige.
- Guess what?
- What?
I like you too.
I tell you, this day is getting a lot better
than how it started.
Yeah, so far.
Why do you keep
saying things like that?
What do you have to tell me?
Come on, it can't be that bad.
Rooftop picnic, starlight, candles.
Wait, wait. I want to guess first,
actually. Hold on.
Let me see.
You used to be a man before.
No, that's not true, right?
Good.
Come on, tell me, what is it?
I don't think you're gonna like it.
You try me.
Have you ever wondered
about the kind of strange things
that happen with me and
kind of since you've known me?
Like why was I there,
trying to help your parolee?
How did I find that baby's father
so quickly?
How did you get that guy
to tell the truth?
How did you get shot
and miraculously survive?
And even little things like today.
Finding your keys and your wallet,
and then there's
that winning the $10,000 thing,
which you should probably give
to charity, because that...
- You know...
- Okay. Okay.
What are you trying
to tell me, Paige?
Do you believe in magic?
I don't know.
I don't think about it much. Why?
I think it's time that you did.
Lights.
I'm doing that right now.
How?
I'm a witch. I have powers.
I can make
these kinds of things happen.
I'm not the kind of witch
that rides around on broomsticks
or the hat or with the little black cat,
that sort of thing.
I use my powers for good.
I help people.
And this is not going well
and I can see how completely
scared off you are from me.
The door's right there
and it won't hurt my feelings.
Paige.
- What?
- Look at me.
I'm not afraid.
Hang on. There's just one more.
Really?
I thought I grabbed all the boxes.
Well, this one
I kind of put together for you,
just in case you need more herbs
or potion vials or crystals,
or, you know, CliffsNotes
of the "Book of Shadows," just in case.
Just in case a demon attacks.
Yeah, don't laugh. It's gonna happen
and you know it.
And when it does, you know,
you're gonna be alone.
Piper, I'm just moving into town,
you know, it's not that far away.
Yeah,
but it's not down the hall.
That's true.
You know,
if you don't want me to go...
No.
You've gotta go.
You know, there's some blonde chick
asleep in your room.
I'm just a little sad.
But I can be a little sad.
Absolutely.
I'm sad too.
It's just, you know,
it's been a lot of change.
You know this will always
be my home, right?
And that will never change.
I mean, this is family.
Yeah.
Okay, you gotta go.
See you.