Yeah, no, I realise we haven't had
a band in a couple of months,
but, you know,
haven't you read the papers?
I've been helping Homeland...
...Security.
That even sounds ridiculous to me.
I don't get it.
It's, you know, two lousy months
and suddenly I'm ice-cold.
Well, bands will be back.
P3's still the hottest club in town.
Oh, yeah? When? Hey, watch it.
Sorry. You want me to talk to Smitty?
I'm playing golf with him this afternoon.
No, I don't like that guy. He's slimy.
Yeah, but he's got connections.
He got you the Donnas.
Fine. Let him win.
- Morning.
- Hi.
I didn't know Leo golfed.
Yeah, he does, but not very well.
Don't tell him.
Why are you so dressed up?
Well, the Elders have assigned me
a charge, a future whitelighter.
But is that a good thing?
Yeah, it is if he's cute.
- Don't you ever answer call waiting?
- Why?
Well, Agent Murphy's been trying
to get through.
- He's got a case for us.
- A case?
What are we, Charlie's Witches?
We don't work for him.
Well, apparently he seems to think
that we do.
Especially after reminding me
over and over
that he bailed us out of our little jam.
- That's blackmail.
- No.
- That's your taxpayer dollars at work.
- Yeah, well, I can't.
- I have to go deal with a charge.
- No, no, no.
You are not dumping this
in my lap, missy.
I am very busy too.
I have dates, lots and lots of dates.
Are you trying to get pregnant
again?
No, I'm trying to find love.
So I don't have any more time
than you guys do
to go through cold cases.
What do you mean cold cases?
Well, there are cases
that Murphy seems to think
have some supernatural angle
to them.
So he wants us to go through boxes
to see if we can find anything.
How many boxes?
You have got to be kidding me.
Agent Murphy says he wants you
to start with these.
They're rated Para-7 Suspicion
and higher.
- Para-7?
- Paranormal.
Don't forget to wear protective gloves.
We don't want the evidence tainted.
Wait a minute,
where are you going?
Hey, you can't just leave us here.
- This can't be legal.
- Well, apparently it is.
Let's just get this over with
so we can find something.
You know, Agent Murphy can't
make us do this on a weekly basis.
It's boring.
Well, if he does, we'll just turn him
into a frog or something.
Don't you answer that.
Hello? Hey, how's it going?
- Of course I can make it.
- Piper, no, you cannot.
Okay, see you later.
I gotta go. It's Leo's music buddy.
He's trying to get me a band.
- It's very, very important.
- All right.
You should probably leave those off
because you'll get a premonition
easier without them.
Okay?
So I'll be back in a jiffy. Okay?
See you later.
I need more power.
You said you'd find it for me by now.
I'm doing everything I can, Zira.
I've got feelers out everywhere.
I don't know how much longer
I can take answering to that brute,
let alone all the others.
- I'm getting restless.
- And I said I'm working on it.
Where's the potion?
Why isn't it ready yet?
It will be, Tai, I assure you.
It better be,
or I'll find a new sorceress.
I'll show him and his kind
who's replaceable,
even if I have to kill
every last male demon to do it.
It's time for females to rule.
Especially this female.
The battle of the sexes is universal,
going back to Adam and Eve.
In fact, men and women
are so different
that you have to wonder
how we get along at all.
What stops us
from killing each other?
The yin-yang theory explains it best.
Yang, male is cold, hard
and unbending.
Yin, female,
warm, soft and yielding.
But notice the dots.
A little bit of each in the other
for balance.
Billie, have something to add?
No. Nothing he'd wanna hear
anyways.
- Try me.
- Okay.
I think this whole thing
is just a little outdated.
It might used to have been
more clear-cut,
but now men are just wimps or thugs.
It's women that are balanced.
I rest my case.
I see your point, but like it or not,
behind every good man
is a good woman, and vice versa.
- We need each other.
- Hardly.
I'm around amazing women
all the time that don't need guys.
I mean, history proves
that women are the stronger sex.
Let's think back to goddesses,
queens, Muses, witches...
Witches, women, same difference.
- You don't mean witches, you mean...
- Shut up, sicko.
The only way
there will ever be any balance
is if women get the chance to rule.
Except history doesn't support
your theory.
When either sex becomes dominant,
it's a fiasco.
- Yeah, for you guys.
- No, for everyone.
We're different for a reason.
Buy it or not, the yin-yang theory
will be on the midterm today.
Oh, sorry, gotta take this.
Phoebe? Hi.
Demons? Okay, I'll just get a cab.
All right, bye.
Sorry, I gotta go.
It's a family emergency.
Well, the problem is it's a Catch-22.
No band wants to play a club
that hasn't had a band,
and while on the other hand,
I need a band.
That is a problem.
Yes, but not an insurmountable one,
right?
Yeah, that's true.
You guys have a great track record.
I mean, you used to book
a lot of talent.
And we still can, it just takes one.
- You're not gonna get a headliner.
- Okay.
Well, what if we do a benefit
for the hurricane victims?
Maybe I can get you a chick band,
but that's about it.
A chick band?
But it won't help much because
there aren't very many hip ones.
I'm sorry, but there's a lot of hugely
successful female bands around.
Yeah, but you're not gonna
get any of them.
Well, why not? We used to.
- Don't get all emotional on me, baby.
- Oh, no, this is not emotional.
Would you like to see emotional?
Because I can get emotional.
Okay, look, Smitty, bottom line is
we really could use your help.
So maybe there's somebody
who owes you a favour?
Oh, no, I don't need no favours
from him.
Okay.
Well, Liz Phair
is passing through town.
She likes a good charity.
But we'll talk later when
the old ball and chain isn't around.
Why were you so nice to him?
Why did you not throw him out
on his macho-pig ass?
Because I am trying to get you a band.
Okay, Smitty has a point.
The music business is all about
what's current.
Well, currently I am very irritated.
Okay, well, then you need
to take a deep breath and relax.
Oh, I see, now you think
I'm being overly emotional.
Not at all. It's all good.
All I'm saying is I have coffee at 6,
a dinner date at 8,
so if Billie's not here...
Believe it or not,
I'd rather be helping you
than being where I'm at right now.
Why? Where are you?
I'm...
...on skid row.
Trying to figure out how to introduce
myself to my new charge.
Well, what's stopping you?
I have to wait for the other felon
to leave first.
- Why?
- Apparently this kid's at a crossroads.
I'm supposed to help him figure
how to make the right choice.
Like that's gonna be real easy.
Okay, well, back
to our little problem here...
- I already told you...
- Don't tell me no, punk. You owe me.
- Gotta go, he's getting beat up. Okay.
- Wait... But...
I'm trying to stay out of trouble,
Donnie, that's all.
Yeah? Well, you don't drive
and you gonna be in a world of trouble
with me.
- You got that, Speed?
- Hey!
You better show up, punk.
Are you okay?
Who are you?
I'm someone who saved you
from getting your ass kicked.
- That's who I am.
- Lady, I don't think so.
Speed, I know who you are.
I'm just trying to help you.
What are you,
my guardian angel or something?
Yeah, or something.
Wait.
You dented my hood.
That's gonna cost you.
It wasn't what you think, all right?
The dude tracked me down.
Leave him alone
or I'm gonna call the cops.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't bother,
that's where he's headed already.
You're a parole officer?
Look at that,
your girlfriend can read, huh?
What'd he do?
Broke parole,
consorting with a known felon.
Man, that's not what happened.
Come on, you gotta believe me.
Actually, no, I don't.
I wouldn't hang around out here, lady,
if I were you.
Not dressed like that.
Wow, these are so Greta Garbo.
Hey, now, there's a woman that didn't
need a man to make her feel complete.
Hey, Billie, those are evidence,
okay?
And not to mention
somebody probably died in them.
Hello?
No, I said, "I'm dying to see you. "
It just must be a really bad connection.
Now, this is the kind of bondage
men want us in?
I don't know
why you bother hooking up.
After seeing this guy in my class,
I am so sure women should be on top.
- Do you mind?
- I'm sorry, I meant that metaphorically.
Yeah, well,
I'm speaking to a guy, okay?
- And he means metaphysically.
- Yeah, see, that's the thing.
Men just keep using their little heads
to do all the thinking for them.
You know, this whole yin-yang thing,
it's a complete hoax.
I mean, look at this lame gig.
Once again the male establishment
is using women's awesome skills
for their busywork.
You know what, I gotta go, okay?
Yeah, I can't wait to see you too.
Sunday. All right, thanks, bye.
Hey, can we lay off
the male-bashing, please?
Sorry, I've just had one too many
lame dates lately.
I don't understand, everyone I go out
with is so immature and childish.
Does that ever change?
Do they ever grow up?
Well, if I ever get out of here,
I'll let you know.
Hey, check this thing out.
No, no. No.
What just happened?
We're screwed,
that's what happened.
Look at that.
This is unbelievable.
Piper takes the car, Paige orbs.
Does anyone stop and think
that Phoebe can't orb?
No, of course not. Why?
Because it's all about them.
Okay, hi, yeah,
I can't get this thing off.
Yeah, don't even bother.
It's gonna take a spell or a potion
or some kind of emotional epiphany.
- That blows. Are you sure?
- Hello? Voice of experience.
I've been turned into a mermaid,
a mummy, a genie, okay?
Trust me, I know these things.
I can't believe this. I feel so stupid.
I had to put the belt on.
It's okay. Just think of it as initiation.
It happens to the best of us.
So it's not that bad?
Oh, no, it's bad. It's very, very bad.
Hey, superhero babe, over here.
- Please, someone vanquish me now.
- Okay, we gotta get you out of here.
Hey, taxi!
Hey, where's she going?
- What the hell did you do to my cab?
- Put it back. Put it back.
Put it back. Good. Let's go.
A dormant power
has just been activated.
What do you mean dormant?
Well, judging by its intensity
and frequency of the emissions,
I thought it was
the Crystal of Kasimar.
But, oh, it's even more powerful
than that.
The Golden Belt of Gaea.
"The goddesses' gift to Hippolyta
endows the woman wearing it
with transcendent powers. "
- I'm sold. How do I get it?
- Trust me, you don't want it.
It would destroy you
the moment you put it on.
- You're evil.
- Then what good is it to me?
Well, you could still appropriate
its powers
by getting the woman who's wearing it
to do your bidding for you.
How, if she's good?
The belt's power will compel her
to use its force
whether she wants to or not.
In time, it'll drive her to madness,
consume her.
Of course, if you were to befriend her
before that...
Then I can get her to use the powers
for me, to get rid of Tai.
How do we find her?
There you are.
What about Jake,
did he check in yet?
Hey, excuse me, you almost hit me.
Hey, I'm gonna call you back.
Yeah, yeah. Excuse me?
Before you peeled out of there,
you nearly hit me.
Sorry about that.
Is that what you came
all the way down here for?
Yeah, that and just to, you know,
check and see how Speed's doing.
Let me guess, missionary?
Social worker? Do-gooder?
Homeland Security, actually.
- Really?
- Check it out if you want.
All right, I think I will.
So, what does Homeland Security
want with a street thug like Speed?
- He's not a thug, he's a kid.
- Oh, no, no, no, he's 18.
- Barely.
- Barely counts. He's gonna learn that.
Where's he supposed to learn, jail?
No, we try to scare him
so that maybe he won't go back to jail.
Here you go, Henry. He's all yours.
- Thanks, Frank.
- What's she doing here?
She's looking out for you,
so don't let her down.
Hey, from now on it's for real,
you got that?
No more juvie passes.
Next time it counts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You feds keep your books open
on this one.
Something tells me
you'll see him again.
No, we won't.
He's destined for greatness.
You hear that?
I'm destined for greatness.
Yeah, yeah, you don't make
your 4:00 check-in with me,
you're gonna be destined for prison.
Go, I'm gonna take you home.
How many times
do I have to say it?
I'd rather lose the club than have
somebody like Smitty help me out.
You're letting your feelings about him
get in the way of good business.
Oh, so basically,
you agree with him.
Now not only am I emotional,
but I am also, in fact, stupid.
- That's not what I meant.
- At least I hold on to my principles.
Okay, let's stop with the mudslinging
and think about this rationally.
Oh, so now I'm irrational?
No... Yes, you're being irrational.
Smitty has amazing connections.
It doesn't make sense
to alienate him.
Okay, fine, you know what?
You deal with him, man-to-man,
all right? More power to you.
Sorry.
Yes, she's a superhero,
but, no, you can't get mad at her
- because it's your fault.
- My fault?
Yeah. She tried on a belt
in one of the boxes
that you were supposed
to be going through.
- I couldn't help myself.
- Oh, no, really?
Enough with the chatter.
We have to figure out how to get it off.
It's not gonna be easy.
That looks like Hippolyta's belt.
"Hippa" who?
Wait, wait, wait, I know her
from my Mythology class.
Greek queen, super powerful,
wanted to create
men and women equal.
Wait a second,
didn't Hercules butcher her?
- That's the one.
- Oh, that's just great.
Oh, no, why'd you go and do that?
Who's gonna pick up the kids?
- What do you mean?
- Leo, look at yourself.
All right, turn him back right now.
I don't know how. I didn't do it.
This did it.
All right, fine.
Did you just try and kill me?
- Whoa, easy.
- Billie, relax. Of course not.
What's the matter with you?
I don't know. That was really weird.
Please get this off me.
To the "Book. "
All right. What aren't you telling us?
And don't think just because
you're invisible that I won't...
Okay, I know the goddesses
who made the belt
came up with a way to take it off,
but if we can't figure out
what that was, Billie's gonna die.
Oh, like the woman who wore it before
who ended up in Murphy's cold case.
Probably. I mean, the belt holds
enormous power, Piper.
It seduces the wearer
before it drives her insane.
We gotta fix this
before it goes horribly wrong.
Like it's not already.
All right, that's not funny.
Move it. Move.
Where's this belt?
It won't just come to you
on its own, Tai.
- It must be lured. She must be lured.
- How?
By attacking an innocent, a female.
But it must be more
than just an attack.
You'll need to torment her
if you wish to compel the mistress
of the belt to come to her aid.
I brought my demons here
to torment one innocent?
No. You brought them here to help you
get power beyond your imagination.
Imagine your status in the underworld
when you bring such a trophy back.
All will bow to you if, of course,
you can take the belt away from her.
It won't be easy.
I think I can handle
one lousy woman.
So strong.
Still, better safe than sorry.
I'll prepare for the belt's arrival.
Okay, you just sit down right here
and relax
until we can figure out a way
to get that thing off you.
If we can.
If we can,
we should soon before she turns
any more men invisible.
You and I both know something
horrible is gonna have to happen
before we can get her
out of that getup.
- I scratched my pretty belt.
- Oh, dear.
Now it's her pretty belt.
What does that mean?
It just means that maybe the belt
is starting to affect you.
I don't think the belt
is starting to affect me, okay?
I would know if...
Hold on. I think I'm getting a call.
- A call?
- Yeah. I'll be right back.
Help. Anybody, help!
Over here. We're coming for you.
Dear God, help!
That's no way to treat a woman.
- Get the belt.
- I don't think so.
Men.
Sweetie, honey, are you all right?
Yeah, except for the fact
nobody can see me.
And the fact
that the girl that did it to you
is out doing God knows what.
We have to find her.
Whoa, watch the door.
Sorry, I'm still getting used
to this blurring thing,
but, oh, is it fun.
Fun? You're having fun?
We were worried about you.
Where have you been?
Well, let's see.
I rescued a woman in distress,
I killed off a bunch of male demons,
and I scratched my pretty belt again.
Okay, Billie, I think you're getting
a little too attached to that thing.
Yeah, until we get it off,
maybe you should kind of stay put.
No, I don't wanna take it off.
It makes me feel powerful.
See, that's a problem.
Actually, here's a problem:
Why are men so threatened
by powerful women?
Hey, look, I'm busy.
I'll call you when I have time.
There is nothing worse
than a needy guy.
Ladies, I think the belt's
affecting you too.
Oh, shush it, will you?
Is there any way you can make
his voice disappear?
Which means it's growing stronger.
Oh, you are such a downer.
No wonder I made you invisible.
My midterm. Almost forgot.
Oh, hey, could you make Leo
visible again before you go?
Really? Why?
Well, he's gotta play golf apparently
to get me a band.
So, what can I tell you?
It's a man's world.
I guess I can try.
Oh, it worked. Right on.
What the hell just happened?
I think her powers
are getting stronger.
- And taking her over.
- Well, then we have to stop her.
He wants to go after her again.
I can't hold him off much longer.
Why didn't it work?
Why didn't she kill him?
- I'm telling you, we're almost there.
- How do you figure?
Tai's alive,
male demons are still in control,
but I don't see any Wonder Witch
to help me change things.
She killed his gang, didn't she?
That means the belt's hold on her
is strengthening.
Now, soon she'll be
so intoxicated by it,
you'll be able to make your move,
turn her.
Not if Tai kills me first.
Then use your wiles to hold him at bay
until I can find her.
She will be yours for the taking
in no time.
You'd better be right,
or else there'll be one more
male demon to become extinct.
Speed. Finally.
Where have you been?
- What are you doing here?
I'm supposed to be here.
I'm the parole officer, remember?
How did you get in?
That door was locked.
- I have my ways.
- Really? I'm listening.
- Look...
- No, you look.
- I don't know what your name is...
- My name is Paige.
Okay, Paige. I have a job to do
and a parolee to bust.
- What do you know about that?
- I don't know anything.
- I just came here to talk to him, okay?
- Talk about what?
Talk about his future.
You know, how not to blow it.
You think that's all it's gonna take
to keep him out of trouble?
- Just some talk?
- Well, it's a start, isn't it?
Why do you believe in him
so much?
- Why don't you?
- No, I used to, for the last ten years.
I'm getting pretty tired
of trying to save his useless ass.
Great. Don't. I'll do it.
You'll do it?
- You're a little late.
- What do you mean?
I mean he's not here, is he? No.
Which means he's with Donnie,
which means Donnie talked him
into the job.
- Jobs are good things.
- Not that kind of a job.
Robbing a liquor store.
Yeah, that's right.
And the cops know all about it,
and they're gonna bust him
in the act.
No. No, Speed's not gonna be there.
I got 20 bucks says he will.
I have 20 that says he won't.
You're on.
- Let's go.
- Where?
And prove you wrong.
After you.
Twenty minutes, guys.
Twenty minutes.
- Talk about tacky.
- Hey, super babe.
I could use some action.
Test's half over. Time you have left,
you'll be lucky to get a C.
Wouldn't expect anything more
from a sexist pig like you.
- Excuse me?
- Well, you have to admit
your theories are slanted
to more of a male perspective.
So is the superhero costume
a comment on the male hierarchy?
- I assume you're making a statement.
- Yeah, that she's hot.
Shut up, pig.
- What are you laughing at?
- Hey, chill out.
Wait, stop, this isn't necessary.
This isn't right.
This isn't what you wanted, is it?
- I can help you.
- Who are you?
Someone who understands.
Come with me
and all your questions
will be answered.
Can't believe we missed her.
Well, at least she left before
the entire class killed each other.
You mean before the girls
killed the boys.
Sounds like history's repeating itself.
Hippolyta tried to use the belt
to create harmony between the sexes.
- Blew up in her face too.
- Dare I ask what happened next?
Well, she retreated
to an island of women,
killing any man who dared enter.
Well, one must've gotten through
because Billie said
Hercules killed her.
Which is why
everyone who's worn the belt since
has tried to rid the entire world
of men.
Oh, great.
Just when I start dating again.
You know,
that means Wyatt and Chris too.
Oh, come on, what are the possibilities
of this really happening?
I mean, other people
have worn the belt before
and men are still walking around.
But Billie was a powerful witch
before she put the belt on,
which pretty much makes her
invincible.
She could do it,
or at least kill a lot of men trying.
So, what, our only hope is that the belt
drives her insane and kills her first?
No, we have to figure out a way
to get the belt off of her
and contain her, obviously,
so she doesn't do any more harm.
If we can find her.
- Guess I won't be golfing after all.
- No, actually, I think you should.
You're the target.
I want you as far away as possible.
You're vulnerable to the belt's powers,
I'm not.
Yeah, I know,
but now that we know what to expect,
we'll keep our distance, I promise.
Now, really, you should go.
And, you know, if you find me a band
in the process,
that wouldn't be such a bad thing.
Don't you see?
Women have evolved
while men have grown more barbaric.
Your destiny is to unite women,
bring peace into the world.
And I can help.
- But you're a demon.
- But I don't want to be.
Nor, with your powers,
will I have to be any longer.
This whole
good-versus-evil paradigm,
it's all been fostered by men
to divide us
because they can't create life,
so they try to destroy it.
- I don't know.
- Oh, think about it.
We're at Magic School.
It's filled with demons,
which means if I wanted you dead,
you would be.
What do you want?
Peace, harmony...
...just like you.
With women ruling,
good and evil goes away.
All walks of life live as one.
Of course, we may have to kill
a few demon in the process.
- But that's where you come in.
- I should talk to the sisters first.
They don't believe in a women's utopia
like we do.
They're stuck in the old ways,
battles.
No, no, they're very strong women...
Who have been corrupted
by the male hierarchy.
They're scared of change.
They'd do anything to stop you.
Which is why it's so important
we take over Magic School.
Make it our base. Peace, unity.
Think about it.
She's not well. She'll be dead soon.
She just needs to live long enough
to kill Tai.
Then no one will dare challenge me.
You all right?
Yeah. I just have to go
to the bathroom, that's all.
Oh, why didn't you say so?
There you go. I won't look.
That's disgusting.
- First stakeout, huh?
- No, I've been on lots of stakeouts.
- What?
- I don't know.
I'm still trying to figure you out.
- Why?
- Because I can't, that's why.
I do like a challenge though.
Suspect vehicle approaching
south on Larson. Over.
Suspect vehicle is in position.
Two black males,
considered armed and dangerous.
Stand by. Over.
- Damn. Looks like you lost our bet.
- He hasn't done anything yet.
- Boy, you are an optimist, huh?
- No, I just have faith.
Yeah. So do I.
Yo, chill, dog.
- Look, I don't wanna be doing this.
- Yeah? Well, it's too late.
- We all set up?
- What are you waiting for?
- Drive to the front.
- Look, I can't.
- I don't wanna be doing this. I can't.
- The hell you can't.
Drive, damn it.
- All units engage. Engage.
- Stay here.
You son of a bitch.
Police! Freeze! Don't move!
Don't move. Freeze.
You owe me 20 bucks.
Give me your hands.
Give me your hands. Now, cuff him.
This isn't working.
Either Super Billie's
completely taken over
or she just doesn't wanna be found.
Well, we could try
the to-call-a-lost-witch spell.
If there's any witch left in her,
it should bring her back here
whether she likes it or not.
Well, what if that doesn't work?
Well, then mankind
has got a serious problem.
I should've stopped her.
Don't worry about it,
it's a job hazard.
It would've happened
sooner or later.
She's gonna be upset
when she comes back.
Think we should call for Paige?
No, she's got her own innocent
to save.
Besides, if Billie gets here
and we can't handle it,
we'll call for her.
Power of the witches rise
Course unseen across the skies
Come to us who call you near
Come to us and settle here
What'd you do that for?
Oh, we were just worried about you,
that's all.
That's bull. You just don't want me
to create my utopia.
- Your what?
- Are you kidding? We love utopias.
I mean, we're witches, you know?
We're into the girl power.
Fine. What do you want?
We just wanna talk, you know,
see how you're doing. Now.
- You lied to me. Zira was right.
- Zira?
There's no wrath
like a woman scorned.
We have got to find her
and bring her back here
because I am not cleaning up
this mess.
Zira...
...I'm all yours.
So maybe we could try the spell again
and bring her back?
And do what with her?
Watch her
destroy the rest of the house?
- I mean, we can't contain her.
- There's gotta be a way.
Hey, I guess Billie's still
wearing the belt, huh?
- You think?
- Oh, nice.
You're out playing golf
while we're trying to save your gender.
No, I told him to,
and it's a good thing I did
because Billie might've killed you.
She's getting worse, isn't she?
Yeah, and she teamed up
with a demon.
If I were a guy,
I'd definitely be a little nervous.
Any chance they went back
to Magic School?
Maybe. Why?
Because if they did, we might be able
to get the belt off her there.
The goddesses' spell's gotta be
in one of the history books.
It's gonna be pretty tough
to get by her unseen.
Well, I think unseen is the answer.
You wouldn't listen to me, huh?
- You just had to do something stupid?
- Hey, easy.
- Oh, man, you don't understand.
- No, I understand.
You screwed up,
that's what I understand.
Why don't you listen
to what he has to say?
I don't like this better than you.
I don't have any choice.
He's an accessory to robbery.
I'm gonna take him in.
I'm telling you,
that's not the way it went down.
Okay, why don't you tell that
to the judge?
Wait. What happened?
- What happened to you?
- That's what I was trying to tell you.
Donnie stuck me
because I wouldn't drive.
Then what the hell
were you doing there?
Just forget it, man.
No. No. If what he's saying is the truth,
then that makes him innocent.
- That's not my call.
- Yeah.
It is your call
whether you take him in or not.
Why don't you check the other guy's
knife? If his blood is on it,
then he's exonerated.
Let's go. Excuse us.
What?
- You set me up.
- It's called evolution, Tai.
- Your kind's irrelevant.
- You fool, she's just using you.
There's no battle of the sexes.
The eternal fight
is between good and ev...
I can't believe he's finally dead.
It's almost anticlimactic.
- Is he really gone?
- You missed one.
Are you all right?
You don't look well.
- I don't feel very good.
- It's all right. You just rest.
It'll be all over soon, I promise.
Sooner than you think.
- What are you doing here?
- Oh, we've come to save you.
- Again.
- You can't save her. It's too late.
- Wanna bet?
- Book.
They're after your belt. Kill them.
- Leo.
- No!
Say the damn spell.
For all the world to work as one
In harmony it must be undone
Belt.
All right, come out, come out,
wherever you are.
- It's nice to see you.
- It's good to be seen.
- What happened?
- Leo just saved your life.
Yin-yang working together
just like it should be.
- Good job, yang.
- Thanks, yin.
Now, come on.
What are we doing?
Yeah, inspector, it's Henry.
Hey, by any chance did that kid Donnie
have a knife on him
when he was arrested?
Have blood on it?
No, no, no, it's nothing.
I was just curious. Thanks.
- Turn around.
- What's up?
I'm letting you go, that's what's up.
Wait, so you mean you believe me?
This time.
Go.
Hello?
So do you want cash
or can I send you a check?
- Henry?
- You were right about the kid.
- He was clean.
- How did you get my number?
Oh, you're not the only one
with connections.
I see.
Hey, Speed owes you.
- I owe you too.
- Just doing my job.
Well...
...good night.
Good night.
That better be a virgin colada.
I don't wanna lose my license
the same night I land Liz Phair.
Don't worry, I think I've caused enough
trouble for you guys for one day.
You were bound to turn into something
eventually.
Yeah, but Wonder Witch?
Not to mention
I almost terminated an entire gender.
- Yeah, but the point is you didn't.
- Thankfully.
Yeah, I just wish I still wasn't
so confused about men.
Don't worry,
they're just as confused about us.
- I know, but I'm still a little gun-shy.
- It's okay. You have time.
Ladies and gentlemen,
put your hands together,
welcome to P3 Liz Phair.
- I'm so excited.
- I still can't believe Leo got her.
Yeah. Well, you know,
guys, golf, go figure.
To the mystery of men.