NARRATOR: Previously on
Battlestar Galactica.
Hi, we're...
We're kind of lost, again.
We're trying to get
to the ClC. Could you...
No talking, no talking,
please.
No cheating.
Hold it up, a little higher.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Sneaky.
Eight, nine...
Start again.
You aren't serious.
Zero...
I've asked you here
to find out why
the Cylons hate us so much.
It's what you said
at the ceremony.
That humanity
was a flawed creation.
And that people still
kill one another
for petty jealousy
and greed.
You said that humanity
never asked itself
why it deserved to survive.
Maybe you don't.
(KEYBOARD KEYS CLlCKlNG)
SESHA: Sleeper agents
within the Fleet.
Takeover by brute force.
Cylon impregnation
and reproduction.
Multiple models.
Suicide bombings.
Assault on
natural resources.
REPORTER: Speculation
continues that Galactica
is harboring a Cylon agent.
Eyewitnesses claim
to have seen one of
the known Cylon models
moving in and out
of Galactica's brig.
Admiral Adama
has made no comment
on this situation.
We will continue...
How the hell did this
get out to the press?
ROSLlN: I'm surprised
it didn't happen sooner.
I'm told you've been
meeting with her regularly,
allowing her to interact
with members of your crew.
She's a military asset
providing us with
vital strategic intelligence.
While we pray that
she's not somehow
colluding with other Cylons.
If I felt for one second
that she posed some kind
of a threat to this Fleet,
I'd pull the trigger
on her myself.
I think the Fleet
may need to hear that,
Admiral.
Even more,
they need to believe it.
Someone took their vitamin
this morning.
Yeah, I don't know
what got into me.
No, you're right.
Keeping Sharon Valerii alive,
allowing her pregnancy
to continue,
there is no road map
for any of this.
Somebody, somebody
has got to keep asking
the hard questions.
I agree.
I want to stay ahead of this.
Acknowledge
the Cylon's existence
and then make
some kind of case for her
to stay aboard Galactica.
I don't think
that's going to work.
What? Why?
I think you need
to trust the people.
Use the press,
tell them the truth.
I mean,
we barely know anything
about the Cylons,
and until we learn more,
we're not gonna destroy
the only source
of information
that we have. Period.
Good. That simple, huh?
Well...
Could l...
Could I have a minute?
Sure. Important?
You were saying
about the hard questions.
I know it's just
my Debate Team ring,
but it's the best I could do.
This really isn't
how I planned it.
Anyway...
Billy...
I love you.
I've loved you
since the first day
I met you.
I mean, you were
half-naked, granted.
I know that I kind of
blind-sided you with this,
okay?
I mean, it doesn't
have to be tomorrow.
We can take our time.
Billy, I can't marry you.
I don't know
how else to say it.
I'm sorry.
He pulled out that ring
and it was like
an electric shock.
I could barely say anything.
Well, maybe you're regretting
that you didn't say yes.
No. No.
I don't know what to make
of me and Billy,
but I know
I can't marry him.
Then again,
I don't know what to make
of you and me, either.
(BOTH GASPlNG)
Excuse me.
Yeah, sure thing.
Hey, two more.
Coming right up.
Ellen.
It's good to see you.
It's good to see you,
Captain.
Dee.
Billy.
Didn't know you were
coming down here.
I grabbed
a two-day rotation.
I thought I'd grab
some R and R.
I'm on business, as usual.
Captain Adama.
Oh, I really am an idiot,
aren't l?
No, Billy...
Don't.
Don't bother.
Can you give us a minute?
No, you know what?
Have a seat, Captain.
Be my guest.
Billy, I'm sorry.
I thought, if anything,
we were honest
with each other.
But you knew you were gonna
be here with him today,
and you let me propose to you.
I didn't...
I know that giving you
the ring was stupid.
That's fine.
And maybe this wasn't
gonna work out between us.
But this...
You should've told me
about this.
Oh, it's hard, you know,
to choose the people
we fall in love with.
To love only
one person at a time.
People like us
are more complicated.
Us?
I'm sorry.
I'm here with friends.
Ellen,
you're a regular here, right?
You ever see
that woman before,
in the corner?
No. Only when I came in.
And wondered when they were
gonna start enforcing
a dress code.
Ellen, the bathroom's
over here.
Are you serious?
Let's go.
Lee Adama, you amaze me.
This is it now.
You ready?
Yes.
We're with you.
Do it!
(DOOR ALARM BLARlNG)
(GUN FlRlNG)
(PEOPLE SCREAMlNG)
Everybody by the bar!
Now! Move.
You, you!
Up against the bar!
Oh, my Gods!
Three men, one woman,
all armed.
Is it true? The Fleet
knows I'm on Galactica?
I'm interested
in navigational weaknesses.
Wormholes,
dark matter blind spots.
Likely ambushes.
I would avoid these
pulsar pointers because of
dradis interference.
If I was gonna
plan an ambush,
I'd do it there.
It depends, Admiral.
They adapt
to your every move.
Every move triggers
a countermove.
Adapt. That's what
you're good at, right?
Why won't you answer
my question?
Does the Fleet know
I'm on Galactica?
(BOOMER MOANlNG)
It's the baby.
She's kicking.
The Fleet knows.
That'll be all for today.
Guards.
You know, if people knew
how much you've relied
on that thing's
so-called intelligence,
they'd be scared
out of their wits.
What about you, Saul?
Are you afraid of her?
You know, the truth is
I don't like the way
it's gotten under your skin.
What are you doing?
The pressure hatch
can withstand
explosive decompression.
The only way help's getting in
is with a raft
of high explosives.
Or we could just
let these clowns
open the pressure door for us.
There's bound to be
a security force
on its way soon.
Open the door for us?
Why would they do that?
Give me your drink.
Let me talk to them.
The ice.
I need the dry ice.
Okay, stay calm.
(DOOR CLOSlNG)
Ellen!
ELLEN: Please don't shoot!
Who are you?
Ellen Tigh.
VlNSON:
Get over here now. Move!
We are not criminals.
We are members of the Fleet,
just like you.
My husband's
XO of Galactica.
You've just made
the worst mistakes
of your life.
Colonel Tigh, Admiral,
you need to hear this.
ELLEN: Saul.
Ellen. What's wrong?
They're holding us hostage.
They're threatening
to kill us!
My name is Sesha Abinell.
I have seized control
of the Cloud 9 lounge
and held the people in it
hostage.
What do you want?
What do I want?
This is not about what I want.
The Colonial Fleet has become
a Cylon-occupied territory.
You are working in collusion
with a Cylon agent.
The very same model
of the Cylon
that tried to murder you,
Admiral Adama,
on your own ship.
We want Sharon Valerii.
You have two hours.
Get me everything you can
on Sesha Abinell.
Yes, sir.
GAETA: Sesha Abinell.
Fleet records indicate
she's the widow
of a Ray Abinell.
He was a casualty aboard
the Greenleaf freighter
when the Cylons hit it
about 10 weeks ago.
Widow.
Who do we have
aboard Cloud 9?
Rotation schedule shows
Captain Adama,
half a Marine squad,
and Starbuck's already there
on R and R.
Get me Starbuck right away.
Yes, sir.
Hell, one of you beauties
has got to be an O2 sensor.
And I'm guessing it's you.
Take a sip of carbon dioxide.
There was another guy
at the bar.
Check the back.
We don't want
any more mistakes.
Kern,
there's an awful lot
of military types here.
And that's why we're here.
To get Galactica's attention,
remember?
Page, you go.
No problem.
(GROANS)
Good to see you, Gunny.
I'm gonna need
some of those gorillas
you call Marines.
Most of my gorillas
are already here, sir.
Just trying to
cop a little R and R.
STARBUCK: Tell me about it.
All right,
here's what we know.
We got an
unknown number of shooters,
at least 20 hostages,
and about a 90-minute window
before they start
throwing out bodies.
You got a plan, sir?
Lock and load.
Let's figure out the rest
as we go along.
Put your weapon down!
Tell them.
He says he's Captain Adama
from the Galactica.
He just wants to talk.
Talk, that's it.
Just talk.
SESHA: They're together.
(PEOPLE GASPlNG)
Put it down or she dies.
Hey! She dies,
he dies. You get it?
The difference is,
you won't do it.
He will.
Okay?
(EXCLAlMlNG)
We all have someone
we care about.
It's his son.
He's not gonna
choose the Cylon over his son.
VlNSON:
Get in line with the others.
(BEEPlNG)
(PEOPLE MURMURlNG)
The CO2
is through the roof.
They're trying
to suffocate us.
What is this, a trap?
There's a reason you don't
just start shooting
on a spaceship.
You probably nicked a line.
Why don't you let me
talk to the Admiral,
see if we can't
find a way out of this?
I've got two strike teams
inbound to you.
ETA ten minutes.
We'll have
plenty of firepower,
so that's good,
but I'm concerned
with limited access points.
Admiral,
it's Abinell.
ADAMA: Keep Starbuck
on the line with us.
Adama.
We're losing oxygen.
If it's not restored,
the hostages die.
Then you all die,
because this is over.
Not till the Cylon's dead.
I'm willing to die
to see this through.
Are you willing
to risk your son's life?
Son of a bitch.
Suddenly, you're listening.
Gods damn it!
Give her what she wants!
Give her the Cylon!
You're all alone on this,
Admiral.
I'm not gonna sacrifice
a military asset
on your altar of revenge.
What are you talking about?
This isn't...
You said this was about
us being played by the Cylons,
but it isn't. It's about
the loss of your husband,
and I understand that.
It's about you
wanting to strike back,
and I understand that, too.
But we've all lost people
that we care about,
and we learn to live with it.
I am sure
you are aware, Admiral,
of the concrete evidence
that Caprica's defenses
were compromised
by a Cylon agent
who infiltrated
the Ministry of Defense
on the eve of the attacks.
People look for
complicated answers when
something terrible happens.
Maybe we were just
caught by surprise
and were beaten,
and maybe we have to learn
to live with that.
And maybe you are
just missing the point.
You were infiltrated.
You, the military.
And you are being
infiltrated again, right now.
You can sit there and pretend
you know what you're doing,
but you do not.
You are being played.
And the rest of us
do not want to go down
with your ship.
I want this air system
restored right now.
One person comes in alone,
fixes it, leaves.
Anything goes wrong,
somebody gets hurt,
it's on your head.
Keep a direct line open
to Cloud 9.
What do we do?
We repair the air system.
Saul, we can't
give her Sharon.
I hope you know that,
right?
I know that.
We can't start
dealing with the terrorists.
We start now,
it'll open the floodgates,
and it'll never stop.
But, by the way,
it's not Sharon.
It's a frakking Cylon.
You don't think I know that?
I think there's part of you
that looks into
that thing's eyes
and still sees that young girl
that reported aboard
two years ago
as a rook pilot.
Well, it's not.
It never was.
Bill, it's a machine.
Admiral,
it's Captain Thrace.
Sitrep.
STARBUCK: I had one of
the Cloud 9 techs
double-check
the oxygen feed in there.
There's nothing wrong
with the air.
ADAMA: Could be a glitch.
Or maybe someone screwed
with one of the CO2 sensors
in the bar.
Lee? Why?
Maybe he's given us
an opening.
If I can get someone inside,
get a clear idea
of what we're dealing with...
Kara, this is a recon mission.
Get someone to volunteer.
Then you assess the situation,
and then
get the hell out of there.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
I'm here to repair
the O2 line.
Captain,
what are you doing?
Volunteering.
Let me see that.
(KNOCKlNG ON DOOR)
SESHA: Close the hatch.
Search her.
You may not want to do that.
You're running out of air
in here.
Looks clean.
Do your job.
Cover her.
VlNSON: Wait a minute.
Turn around, slowly.
Check the box again.
(GUNS FlRlNG)
(PEOPLE CLAMORlNG)
MARlNE:
We're hot! Let's go! Hurry!
Get down! Get down!
(PEOPLE SCREAMlNG)
We gotta get out now!
Come on!
(GUNS FlRlNG)
(WOMAN SCREAMlNG)
(WOMAN SOBBlNG)
(GASPlNG)
DUALLA: Billy, Billy.
I need shirts, towels,
anything I can use
as a bandage.
Billy!
VlNSON:
Nobody said you could move.
You still want the Cylon?
Do you?
Because
if the Admiral's son dies,
you're not gonna get a deal.
You get that?
If he dies, you're not
gonna get what you want.
He's right. Let him go.
Sir, it's Starbuck.
We got a report
of gunshots.
What's happening?
My cover was blown.
I had to move. I'm sorry.
ADAMA: Any casualties?
Two Marines, probably KlA,
at least one of the gunmen,
and Lee.
It was crazy in there,
confused, and he got hit.
How bad?
I don't know.
Stand by.
Hold your position.
Make no move
unless you hear from me.
It was friendly fire.
Lee got hit by friendly fire.
I think it was me.
You have your orders.
DUALLA: I can't stop
the bleeding.
What can I do?
I can't stop the bleeding.
I gotta stop the bleeding.
I can't tell
if it hit an artery.
Lee, don't leave me.
Lee. Lee, don't leave me,
okay?
Please.
Hey.
He's gonna be okay.
Just hang in there.
Come on.
(SOBBlNG) Stay with me.
Stay with me, Lee.
Stay with me.
Are you playing with us?
Are you playing with me?
I've saved the ship,
saved you,
how many times now?
Five? Six?
You just can't believe
I'm not playing against you.
You know that there are
Cylons within this Fleet.
You know what they look like.
You know where to find them.
If I were to ask you,
would you tell me
who they are?
No.
That I believe.
(WHlMPERlNG)
He'll be all right.
Thanks for the concern.
She loses a husband
and suddenly the world
owes her an explanation.
He was a good man.
And he wasn't
just her husband.
He was my brother.
My brother died on Picon.
He was a good man, too.
They're all good men.
The Abinell woman
sent over a manifesto
to the press
before they took over
the bar.
It's mostly
a collection of rumor
and conspiracy theories
about Cylons
in the military
and the government.
Bunch of crap.
It's getting a lot of
attention. We gotta
get our people out of there.
You have Marines
on Cloud 9.
The pressure door to the room
has been resealed.
If we try blowing it open,
we'll need so much G4
we'd risk killing
everyone inside.
There are no options left
except for one.
No. We don't strike deals
with terrorists. We can't.
We give them Sharon Valerii,
we're inviting terrorism,
and we weaken
our position permanently.
You know that.
Gentlemen,
everyone in that room
is someone's son,
someone's wife,
someone's mother.
Billy is the closest thing
that I have to family
left in this world.
And if you don't think
that that confuses things
emotionally for me...
Let's not be naive.
What if they're right?
What if Sharon has been
playing us all,
plotting our destruction
with every passing day?
What if the terrorists
are right?
This isn't about Sharon.
It's about something
much bigger than that.
It's about
the long-term survival.
It's about the way
we conduct ourselves
in all of this.
Sir, it's Abinell
on the line.
How's my son?
Alive, but my friend is dead.
So are two of your soldiers.
And your son's dying.
You know, I thought
a long time about this.
About what I'd do.
About how far I'd go.
And I honestly did not know
until this moment...
Two.
What? What?
Get on your feet.
What are you going to do?
Saul! Give them
what they want!
It's just a machine!
WOMAN: Oh, no. Oh, no. No!
They're gonna kill her.
Hold your fire.
I'm giving you the Cylon,
but she won't be alive.
What does that mean?
That is not the deal.
It means that
you've convinced me
that we may have been played.
And if that be the case,
and she's been
playing with me,
then I can't take
any more chances.
So you make up your mind.
If you want Sharon Valerii,
you can have her,
but on my terms.
I give you the body,
you give me the hostages.
Done.
Cut the wire.
It's good.
MARlNE 1 : Coast looks clear.
Admiral.
Let me help, please.
Let me take it from here.
Let's go.
DUALLA:
Stop looking at him, Billy.
I can see you watching him.
I know you think
you can get that gun.
I'm only thinking
in case something happens.
No. You're not a soldier.
You're not trained for that.
You've got nothing to prove.
I know.
They're right outside.
We open up,
they'll give us the body.
Okay.
VlNSON: We're opening
the door.
But if anything goes wrong,
we start killing hostages.
Do it.
It's over.
Wait.
This isn't right.
This one's been dead
for weeks.
Their Cylon is still alive.
Kill the girlfriend.
(GUN FlRlNG)
(PEOPLE EXCLAlMlNG)
MARlNE 1: Down! Report!
MARlNE 2:
We're contained!
All clear!
MARlNE 1: All right,
we're all clear.
Grab this tight!
DUALLA: I need help over here!
MARlNE 3: Bring in
the ER team.
MARlNE 2: Medic,
get in here now!
Medic!
Far side of the room.
Right over there.
Lee.
Lee, can you hear me? Lee!
MEDlC 1: Blood pressure.
MEDlC 2: Right.
Can you hear me, Lee?
Come on, Son.
Come on, hurry up!
MEDlC 1: BP's weak
and threading.
(APOLLO MOANlNG)
That's good.
(SOBBlNG) Billy. Billy.
Billy.
ROSLlN:
Is this what you gave them?
It was a calculated risk.
It wasn't worth it.
(SNlFFLlNG)
Oh, dear.
There, that's better.
That's better.
He was so young.
(GASPS)
DUALLA: Hey.
Hey.
What is it?
Nothing.
When you're feeling better,
we can talk.
It was a hell of a vacation.
Yeah.
Lee?
Lee, you can't leave.
You have to stay.
You have to really stay.
You understand?
It's okay.
I'll be here
when you wake up.
I'll be right here.