NARRATOR: Previously on
Battlestar Galactica.
Citizens!
I give you
your new vice-president,
Dr. Gaius Baltar.
(ALL APPLAUDlNG)
You're the father of my child
and nothing is ever
gonna change that.
I know a place
where you can stay
where you will be safe.
How much time do I have?
Weeks. A month at the outside
Unless the cancer
goes to your brain.
If that happens...
(DOOR SLAMMlNG)
I'm afraid
the tests are positive.
The mass is malignant.
It's advanced
well beyond the left breast.
DOCTOR: I'm afraid
the tests are positive.
Ms. Roslin,
the surgery, of course,
will remove the mass.
(MEN CHATTERlNG)
STANS: Secretary Roslin?
Yes?
Naylin Stans,
from the Education Alliance.
You said you wanted to talk.
Yes.
I'm sorry, Mr. Stans.
STANS: Have to admit
I was surprised
to get your message.
ROSLlN: The President
was surprised I sent it.
Once our chief negotiator
got a billy-club to the head,
we figured Adar's government
had written us off
as a lost cause.
I was a teacher long before
I was Secretary of Education.
And causes are only lost
when we give up.
(GASPlNG)
Madam President,
can you hear me?
COTTLE: Let's make her
as comfortable as we can.
(CARDlOGRAPH BEEPlNG)
Oh, gods...
(GROANlNG)
STARBUCK: (ON RADlO)
Starbuck, zero four niner.
CAP is away.
Galactica, roger that.
Zero four niner.
Safe flight.
Safe
and 20 frakking minutes late.
Did you have a rough night,
Starbuck?
STARBUCK: (ON RADlO)
You're way out of line.
Just follow my lead
and save the attitude
for someone who cares.
KAT: Kat, six seven zero.
Roger that.
Request permission
to clear guns.
STARBUCK: Roger that, Kat.
Clear your throat.
Damn it!
Weapons malfunction!
Galactica.
Kat! Are you good?
I'm good, I'm good.
What the hell just happened?
STARBUCK:
Your port gun's blown.
Just keep it steady.
We're heading home.
Galactica, this is Starbuck.
I'm declaring an emergency.
We've got two bent birds,
requesting priority clearance
to land.
LSO: (ON RADlO)
Starbuck, Galactica.
Flight deck is yours.
Why don't you just shoot us
in the locker room, Chief?
Save the wear and tear
on the ships.
Kat's guns are clean.
I checked them myself.
Yeah, well,
I don't believe in accidents.
Chief,
something's not right.
The weight's off.
It's too light.
I found three more
just like it, mixed in
with the regular rounds.
The casing's been weakened.
It falls apart in the barrel,
the next one hits it, bang!
She's lucky
she didn't lose
her whole wing.
One bad round's a fluke.
More than one is sabotage.
Pull them all!
CREWMAN: All right,
you heard the Chief!
Let's pull them all! Let's go!
ADAMA: How is
the President doing, Doc?
She's dying,
and she knows it.
I offered her a shot of morpha
to ease the pain,
but she wouldn't hear of it.
The tests are positive.
ROSLlN: They're teachers
not terrorists.
Mr. President,
we should at least speak
with the strikers
before sending in
the troops.
They're teachers
not terrorists.
They're acting like thugs.
Their last demonstration
put two policemen
in the hospital.
Six of them
have chained themselves
outside the Hall of Education.
As far as I'm concerned,
they're criminals.
Their pay is sub-standard,
their schools
are falling apart,
and this strike action
has been gaining momentum
for months and you know that.
I don't understand
why we're not
at least talking to them.
One of the most
interesting things
about being president
is that you don't have to
explain yourself to anyone.
You've already set
a meeting with Stans,
haven't you?
Obviously only if you approve,
Mr. President.
BALTAR: She's really in no
good state to do anything,
Iet alone to conduct
any Government business.
Don't talk about me
as if I'm not here.
There'll be plenty of time
for that soon enough.
(ROSLlN SNlCKERlNG)
Billy, could you...
Of course.
Gentlemen, I called you here
to discuss the Cylon.
Dr. Cottle, would you...
Would you please tell them
what you told me this morning?
I'm no expert in genetics,
but I can read a blood test.
That Cylon fetus
is showing
some very peculiar
genetic abnormalities.
I haven't seen any of this
on your report, Doctor.
No, well,
as Dr. Cottle says,
he's not an expert and I am.
I've been through the tests
and I wouldn't say that there
was anything conclusive.
I didn't say conclusive,
just damned odd.
Right.
BALTAR: Madam President?
As you know,
the Sharon Cylon
is of considerable
tactical value
to the fleet and...
Perhaps you've gotten
too close to your subject,
Doctor.
This is difficult,
so I'm gonna cut right to it.
Allowing this thing to be born
could have frightening
consequences.
For the security
of this fleet,
I believe the Cylon pregnancy
must be terminated
before it is too late.
Madam President,
I'd like...
I thought you of all people
would understand, Admiral.
BALTAR: Madam President,
I don't understand.
This makes no sense.
One of the interesting things
about being president
is you don't have to
explain yourself to anyone.
Thank you, gentlemen,
I'm a little tired.
Gentlemen?
I don't want to seem alarmist,
but I am perturbed.
I think that
the President's illness
is affecting her judgment.
Especially when it
comes to the subject of...
ADAMA: She seemed
reasonably coherent to me.
Well, then I'll have to appeal
to you on scientific grounds.
Destroying this child
would seriously impact
my studies
of the Cylon subspecies.
The President made the call.
I'm backing her.
With all due respect,
the President made the call
based on evidence
presented by Dr. Cottle
and he...
Pull yourself together.
You're about to become
President of the Colonies.
You're gonna be asked
to make
some very hard decisions.
Act like you can handle it.
Gods.
Where have you been?
Where have I been?
I never left you, Gaius.
All right, yeah.
Yeah, metaphorically speaking.
It's just it was weeks ago
and l...
I'm sure you've suffered
mightily in my absence.
You know, jealousy's
a really ugly emotion.
What is this
lingering controversy
over my affair
with your
three dimensional duplicate?
I'm not jealous,
I'm concerned.
Oh, yeah? Concerned?
About what?
Our child!
You're concerned?
Well, for your information,
the President
intends to kill it!
Once Roslin's gone,
you'll be President.
You can use your new authority
to save our child.
Yeah, yeah. That's good.
Did you see the way
Adama looked at me?
The contempt on his face?
I will be the President,
all right,
but without military support
I might as well be
an anointed dogcatcher.
Yes, well,
you have your own resources,
if you'd use them.
What?
You don't know what I mean?
No, I don't know
what you mean.
The nuclear device.
The one Adama
provided for your research.
There is one way.
NO. 6: I didn't wanna
have to ask...
I didn't wanna have
to ask you for this.
NO. 6: But what
I really need...
But what I really need
to complete the project...
Is a nuclear warhead.
Is a nuclear
warhead.
You're totally insane.
I'm trying to help you,
you idiot.
If Adama remains committed
to the destruction
of our child,
it may be
our only hope.
There's no easy way
to say this.
It's about the Cylon.
The President has decided
that her pregnancy
will be terminated.
What?
Why?
Doc Cottle
discovered some anomalies
in the fetal blood work.
Isn't that expected?
Maybe.
But the President
believes
that to allow the baby
to come to full term,
it constitutes
an unacceptable risk
to the fleet.
I don't understand.
Sharon's only helped us
since she came back
from Caprica.
She even turned on her own.
To save her life.
Don't mistake
the will to live
for genuine compassion,
Lieutenant.
She's still the enemy.
Does she know?
Not yet.
Then I should be the one
to tell her.
If that's all, sir.
Helo.
I don't expect you
to agree to the decision,
but I need you
to accept it.
We're talking about
my child, sir.
Part of me.
But I guess
it's easier to kill
when you call it a Cylon.
Dismissed.
So you're saying
someone's been tampering
with our ammunition?
Shells don't
unload themselves.
What's this I hear
about you ordering
both Galactica
and Pegasus fighters
to stand down?
The price you pay
for reinstating me as CAG,
sir.
Maybe that was a mistake.
Maybe I don't give a damn
what you think, sir.
Take it easy,
both of you.
The fact is
we've been sharing stores
between the ships.
And nobody flies combat
until our ammo supplies
check out.
Leaving us defenseless
if the Cylons
decide to pick a fight.
We were defenseless
before this.
We just didn't know about it.
ADAMA: Lee,
find out who did this.
(MACHlNES BUZZlNG)
APOLLO: All right.
Excuse me,
I'm looking for
Asha Janik.
Asha? She's there.
APOLLO: Let's do this quietly.
APOLLO: Asha Janik?
Captain Adama.
I have a message
for your father.
They may take me...
All right, stop her!
...but I'm one of many!
We have declared war
against Galactica's
army of death!
MAN: Let's go.
The Cylons
aren't our true enemy,
it's the military
that refuses to negotiate!
ASHA: All we want is peace!
Demand peace!
So much for being discreet,
huh?
ADAMA: We found
these pamphlets
in Janik's quarters.
Some kind of a manifesto.
"Demand peace"
from the Cylons?
Who the hell are these people?
Cylon sympathizers.
I just had no idea
they were this organized.
I want to know
how she got aboard my ship.
The hangar deck's
short-staffed.
We've been forced
to import civilians to handle
some of the grunt work.
Apparently she's...
She's a Picon,
worked maintenance
on the Greenleaf,
no known criminal
affiliations.
Until now.
Now listen to this,
"Do not be afraid.
We are not terrorists,
but we will not sit back
"while Adama's war machine
continues to press us
"into cruel
and futile conflict."
Gods damn it.
Well, her demonstration's
worked.
The news is already spreading
across the fleet.
I know.
We were contacted by a person
claiming to speak
for the subversives,
demanding a meeting
on the Galactica.
Well, they've got stones,
I'll give them that.
ADAMA: Well, I've agreed.
What?
We're not negotiating.
I just wanna know
what we're up against.
(GASPlNG)
(MOANlNG)
(DISTORTED TALKING)
STANS: Considering the stakes,
you don't seem
particularly engaged.
The stakes
are what we decide
to make them, Mr. Stans.
If the President uses troops
to enforce
his back-to-work order,
people will get hurt.
Even die.
Some causes
are worth dying for.
Not this one.
(GASPlNG)
DOCTOR: The mass is malignant.
Doctor...
(GASPlNG)
Admiral.
I am Royan Jahee.
You have a unique way
of welcoming visitors
to your ship.
TlGH: Visitor my ass.
We shoot people like you
for treason.
Colonel, I'm only
an interested party,
trying to prevent
more bloodshed.
I deplore what happened
aboard your Vipers.
How many sympathizers
do we have
aboard this fleet?
If you're trying
to crush an organization,
you can stop now.
The people in this movement
are following an idea,
not a leader.
What the hell do they want?
Peace with the Cylon.
You want us to surrender.
They attacked us.
Only after
we'd enslaved them!
You call yourselves
military men, strategists!
Explain to me
how our current course
of attack and retreat
Ieads to victory!
You can play
innocent bystander,
but I think you know more
than you're telling us.
Either way,
you're a danger to this fleet.
Admiral, arresting me
isn't going to stop
any of this.
Maybe not,
but it's a start.
Take him away.
All right,
get your rubber gloves on.
This is everything from
the Janik woman's quarters.
Somehow the Admiral thinks
looking through this crap
is gonna tell us
something new about
their so-called movement.
So, um,
I haven't seen much of you
since your spacewalk.
APOLLO: Hold it.
What's this?
What's a deckhand need
with a portable
library reader?
The Daru Mozu.
A Tylium refinery.
And Janik's
used to explosives.
This is the CAG.
Get me a TAC team ready.
Right now.
BOOMER: (ON TELEPHONE)
I don't understand.
Why are they doing this now?
I don't know.
The Admiral said
they found something
in the baby's blood.
Somehow President Roslin
considers it
a threat to the fleet.
It can't just be that.
I've done nothing
but help them
since I've come here.
I've held back my anger.
I've tried to show them
that Cylons
are not all the same.
That we're not all murderers.
Deep down,
I think they're still
afraid of you.
Yeah.
Afraid.
They wanna be afraid
of something?
Yeah? Just let them come.
Let them!
Let them just try
to take my baby!
(GRUNTlNG)
Let them try to take my baby.
Sharon, stop!
(SCREAMlNG)
Sharon, please, don't do this.
Please!
(YELLlNG)
HELO: Listen to me.
Listen to me.
HELO: Sharon, look at me.
GUARD: Let's go.
Hey! Easy!
Easy!
When we land, move fast.
We're looking for
explosive devices
set near the Daru's FTL drive.
Captain, I'm getting something
on the wireless.
I think it's coming
from the Daru Mozu.
WOMAN: (ON RADlO) None of us
wants to die,
but the fighting must end.
If my sacrifice
sends a signal to the Cylon
that brings peace,
then it was worth it.
I do this for my children
and for the children that will
follow them, gods willing.
Demand peace.
Pull out!
Pull out! Pull out!
(MACHlNE BEEPlNG)
People are dead.
I grieve for them, Admiral.
And I assure you
the Tylium ship's just a taste
of what's in store
unless someone
starts listening!
(GROANlNG)
You listen,
and you listen well.
I don't care
if I have to interrogate
every civilian
onboard this fleet.
This is gonna stop.
Do you understand?
(GROANlNG) Yes.
BlLLY: Mr. Vice President,
President Roslin insisted
on your taking the tour.
She'd like the transition
to go as smoothly
as possible.
BALTAR: What are these?
Cylon agent suspects, sir.
That number
means everything to her.
It represents hope.
It's our future.
Yes. Yes.
Being the President is
a lot of responsibility.
It's tradition
for outgoing Presidents
to leave a letter
for their successor.
It's usually opened
on the first day
of the new term.
But the next few days
are likely to prove
hectic, so...
Well, let's just pray
that she gets better.
Let's.
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
Excuse me.
Yes.
Mr. Vice President.
Hello?
Yes.
I understand.
Thank you.
(KNOCKlNG ON DOOR)
I was told I might meet
an old friend here.
GlNA: It's good to see you,
Gaius.
So you've become a member
of the peace movement?
Well, despite
what you may think,
I've always abhorred violence.
Would you excuse us, please?
Do they have any idea
what you are?
Of course not.
Even their dedication
has limits.
I've missed you.
You look amazing.
I can't believe
how real you are.
What are you doing?
I haven't stopped
thinking about you
since the second
I left the Pegasus.
No.
I can't get you
out of my head.
Don't do this now.
Not yet.
I can't help myself.
I can't.
Gaius.
(GRUNTlNG)
I'm sorry.
No.
I'm sorry. I'm just...
I'm not ready.
So is there any reason
in particular
for inviting me around here?
Because you saved me.
Let me save you.
Here we go again.
What are you talking about?
You must sense it.
Gaius, the fleet's crumbling.
People are turning
on each other.
There are serious misgivings
about the military.
When you're President,
you can use the office
to turn them against Adama,
paving the way
for the Cylons to save us.
I would love to be with you
always, but...
I know it's hard,
but it's the only way.
No.
I am not who you think I am,
and I will not be responsible
for the destruction
of mankind.
If we would have caught it
sooner,
maybe we could have done more.
ADAR: Laura.
I didn't like the way
we left things this morning.
Richard...
I know.
You've been thinking
this is a mistake
for a while now.
I just met with Stans.
The Education Alliance
is going to back off.
Back off?
Laura, what did you give them?
I made them a promise
that we would seriously
hear out their grievances,
Richard.
I thought you'd be happy
they're going back to work.
Laura,
you've put me
in a very awkward position.
I don't see how.
Both sides gave ground.
It's not just
about your teachers.
It's the next strike
I'm worried about.
You just showed them
that if they hold out
long enough,
this administration will cave.
You expected me to fail.
I expected you
to hold the line.
This doesn't have to be
the end of the world.
You can stay on
in an advisory capacity.
Gods know we need your ideas.
You're asking me to resign?
I don't have any choice.
This isn't about
you and me anymore.
You're right, it's not.
You were willing
to attack those people,
and up until a few hours ago,
I was prepared to let you.
I am on my way
to the Galactica to
represent this administration.
When I return,
if you still want my job,
be prepared to fight.
When I return,
if you still want my job,
be prepared to fight.
Notify the Admiral.
(FLATLlNlNG)
This is Admiral Adama.
As you know, President Roslin
has been aboard Galactica
for the last few days.
She's a fighter.
But as of this moment,
her prognosis is grave.
I know that many of you
believe in
the power of prayer.
If that is your way,
then I urge you
to pray for our President.
As for the others,
I hope you will join me
in keeping her
in our thoughts.
Admiral, please don't do this.
Stand down, everyone.
Give me room.
Think about what you're doing,
Helo.
You're a soldier.
I'm a father, like you.
Please, sir,
give me a Raptor.
Let me take her off the ship.
I'll get her away
from the fleet.
I can't do that, son.
BALTAR: Admiral! Admiral!
Admiral!
Doctor, get the hell
out of here!
I must talk to you
concerning the Cylon child.
It seems I may have been
wrong,
very wrong,
when I said that
Dr. Cottle misinterpreted
the fetal blood work.
BALTAR: You see,
I had another look
at those samples
and I discovered something
quite intriguing.
Understand, Cylon blood
is virtually impossible
to differentiate from our own.
That being said,
obviously it has to be
slightly different
because the Cylon
is not human.
If our blood
Iooks like this,
for example,
and the Cylon's blood
looks like this,
then it's fair to assume
that the Cylon-human
is carrying an amalgam.
Is this a theory or fact?
The Cylon's fetus
contains no antigens,
it has no blood type.
That's what Dr. Cottle
was talking about when he said
it was damned odd.
Except it's not damned odd,
it's astonishing.
Now, knowing, as we do,
that the Cylons are built
slightly better to endure
than their human counterparts,
I wondered, could the Cylon
blood also be blessed,
shall we say blessed,
with a heightened resistance
to disease?
So
I applied a sample
of Sharon's fetal blood
to some cancer cells
I took from the President.
What am I looking at?
Nothing.
That's the whole point.
The cancer was gone
and it was gone
within a matter of hours.
Are you saying
you've found a cure
for the President's cancer?
Well, it's untried.
It's obviously untried
and therefore
extremely dangerous.
But, yes,
it's possible.
If you abort
Sharon's fetus now,
you'll never know.
Now, you may feel
a sharp pain.
Sharon, it's okay.
It's gonna be all right.
I don't like
what you're doing.
I think it's unnatural
and damned dangerous.
Yes, well,
given the patient's
current condition,
I am not sure
that I see the downside.
Maybe it's just her time.
Then for once
perhaps I am
the beacon of hope
around here.
It's all right.
Everything's gonna be okay.
I'm right here with you,
Sharon.
If you wanna settle this,
your people have to disengage.
No more civil disobedience,
no more acts of violence.
I want our students
back in school.
Done.
I'm glad you called,
Madam Secretary.
Me, too.
DOCTOR: I'm afraid the tests
are positive.
The mass is malignant.
(RAPlD BEEPlNG)
BlLLY: What's happening?
(ALL CLAMORlNG)
She's convulsing!
Nurse, get me 10cc's of...
COTTLE: Help me get her
on her side.
(GASPlNG)
Nurse! Nurse!
(ROSLlN GASPlNG)
(CARDlOGRAPH FLATLlNlNG)
No, hold it.
(RHYTHMlC BEEPlNG)
I'll be damned.
BALTAR: Madam President?
Dr. Baltar.
It's so very good to see you.
No, no, no. Don't. Don't move.
Don't move.
(ROSLlN GRUNTlNG)
BlLLY: Madam President.
How's she doing, Doctor?
I've never seen
anything like it.
It'll be a while before
she's 100%,
but the scans are clear.
The cancer's gone.
Are you sure?
It's gone.
Thank you.
Admiral.
You seem better.
Much.
Are you still
holding the spokesman
from the new faction
in the brig?
Yes.
Would you take me to him,
please?
Certainly.
Thank you.
I'll wait for you
to get dressed.
JAHEE: President Roslin.
Mr. Jahee, isn't it?
I thought it was time
we met.
Would you open the door,
please?
Do it.
All these people want
is to be heard.
A member of your group
nearly destroyed
our Tylium refinery.
Before we can even
begin to talk,
I need your personal assurance
that there will be
no more attacks.
As I told the Admiral,
I've had no direct contact
with anyone.
Genuine negotiations
require trust.
Do not lie to me.
I'll talk to my people.
Make them understand.
Excellent.
Then I'll listen,
maybe even act.
But if you renege,
I'll insist the Admiral
hunt you and your friends down
without mercy.
NO. 6:
You seem very content.
Sharon's child is safe.
Adama and Roslin have agreed
that more study
is required before any
drastic measures are taken.
Yes, but by saving Roslin,
you've denied yourself
your rightful place
of leadership.
There are many aspects
of you, Gaius,
I will never understand.
You wouldn't.
And neither, would I suspect,
your corporeal counterpart.
Do you love her?
What is that?
The note
that Roslin wrote me.
To be opened
upon the event of her death.
"President Baltar,
I offer my sincere
congratulations.
"l say that knowing
we've had our differences
"and that you take office
despite my many reservations.
"You may be
the most brilliant person
I've ever met,
"but your intelligence
is unleavened by compassion.
"You must be reminded of
your ethical responsibilities
"and challenged
to rise above
your own selfish needs.
"l don't write this
to hurt you, but to beg you
to open your heart.
"Understand that
the people in the fleet
look to you
"not only for leadership
but for solace.
"Justice.
"Find a way
to give them that,
"and you will be
a great leader.
"Laura Roslin."
BALTAR: And after all
I've done for the fleet.
And after all
I've done for her.
Roslin's never trusted you.
She's undermined you
at every turn, and now...
So now we know
she's never gonna trust me.
This is not
a political struggle anymore,
Gaius.
This is quite literally
life and death.
(DOOR OPENlNG)
The President assured me
that as long as there are
no further acts of violence,
she's willing
to bring our concerns
to the Quorum
and Admiral Adama.
She's trying to buy time.
She'll never be open
to negotiating
with the Cylons.
I disagree.
I think we made
real progress today
and so does
the Vice-President.
Baltar?
Yes.
Just before I left,
he asked to meet with me.
He encouraged patience
while he works with Roslin
from within,
and he offered
the contents of this case
as proof of his sincerity.
What's in it?
I don't know.
He said
that you should be the one
to open it.