Everything is shot on
digital now, you know.
Yeah, I'm equipped.
Nice stuff.
Oh, I like this one.
- What lens did you use?
- Twenty-four F8.
- What shutter speed?
- One twenty-five.
Okay, lose the kicker.
Let the shadow play there.
- Impressive.
- So does that mean I got the job?
Based on your portfolio, yes.
Based on your résumé, no.
Took a detour from
shutterbugging, did you?
Mr. Corso, I've changed careers,
I'm not hiding that.
But with all due respect, if you like
my work that should be enough.
I mean you're hiring me,
not my résumé.
You want a shot?
Get me a better one
of Maggie Murphy.
She's gonna be featured
in our St. Patty's Day issue.
Something about being the
unluckiest woman in San Francisco.
And she's Irish.
Down where they do the writing,
they call that irony.
Address is on the back.
Up until three months ago,
she was like a saint, helping the
homeless, volunteering, charity.
Then, like, overnight,
everything started going bad for her.
Real bad.
I want what you have in here, Prue.
Artistic, soulful, poignant.
I want to see the inner Maggie
in your photograph.
And I want to see it by 5:00 today.
Or don't bother coming back.
Thank you.
What am I doing?
This isn't me, this...
Yes, it is. It's all my fault.
The car accident.
The fire. My brother's death.
I hurt the ones I love.
I have to stop it.
Has to stop.
I don't deserve to live.
This is who I really am.
Cursed.
I'm cursed.
Hey, look up there!
Oh, my God, she's gonna jump!
Maggie?
Maggie, no!
Maggie.
Wait, don't.
Where did you come from?
How do you know me?
It doesn't matter. Just step away
from the ledge and take my hand.
Stay away from me.
Maggie, please, I can help you.
Nobody can help me.
Maggie, this isn't the answer.
All I wanted to do is help people.
Now all I do is hurt them.
Maggie!
Let me go. Please.
I can't hold on much longer.
No.
Bring it over here.
Wait. Wait.
Well, of all the luck.
Just stay still, ma'am.
Hey.
I thought you had inventory
at the club.
I do.
So then what are you doing here?
Trying to figure out what to tell Dan.
About what, honey?
Leo.
Oh, that. You're not actually writing
him a Dear John letter, are you?
No, of course not. He deserves
more than that, a lot more. But...
It's just hard.
I mean, I don't want to hurt him.
Dan's a great guy,
and he's been really good to me.
And we've never really had
any huge problems.
No, I mean, the only huge problem
is that you really love Leo,
and he loves you,
and he gave up immortality for you.
I know, which is obviously good for us.
But lately, he seems a bit restless.
You're thinking too much again.
Stop trying to predict the future,
all right? That's my job.
Just follow your heart, honey.
Good things will happen.
What would I do without you?
Oh, suffer endlessly, no doubt.
Thank you.
All right, I'm going to the club.
- Love you.
- I love you too.
- Miss Murphy?
- I can't go in there.
You don't really have a choice.
Am I being arrested?
No, but there's some paperwork
we have to get started.
Are there guns in there?
It's a police station.
They might go off.
Things like that happen around me,
and I don't want anybody
to get hurt.
I'm more concerned
about you hurting yourself.
Come on.
- Nothing's gonna happen.
- You don't understand.
Trust me.
We're only here to help you.
You can't help me.
Nobody can.
We're gonna find
somebody who can.
First, you have to answer a few
questions about what happened today.
I don't know what happened.
It was like a bad dream,
only it wasn't.
Voices in my head...
...and everything spinning.
Is there somebody you wanna call?
Family, friends?
No, no, no. Keep them away from me.
They're safer there.
I shouldn't even be here.
I shouldn't be alive, and if it
hadn't been for that angel...
- Excuse me?
- She just appeared.
Out of thin air
when I was on the rooftop.
She reached out her hand, and then
when I was falling, it was like...
Something slowed me down,
like she guided me to that awning.
- The angel?
- Yes, she saved me.
Help me out here.
What exactly
did this woman look like?
So how'd it go?
- What?
- The interview. Did you get the job?
Yeah, I did.
- Prue, are you okay?
- The woman that I am supposed
to photograph,
when I got to her apartment,
she was on the roof, ready to jump.
- Oh, my God. She didn't...
- Yeah, actually she did.
Luckily, I was able to break her fall
with my powers, but just barely.
So lucky you got there in time.
Yeah, but I keep thinking
if I had been a minute later,
it would have been too late.
But you weren't. You were
supposed to be there in time.
You were supposed to save
that girl's life, I believe that.
- Hello?
- Hi, Prue.
You weren't outside 413 N. Fergis Ave
this morning, were you?
Why?
I got a Maggie Murphy here.
She claims that she was saved
by some angel this morning.
An angel that, by her description,
bears no resemblance to Della Reese.
- But does resemble me.
- Yeah, bingo.
Everybody around here thinks she's
nuts. Wish I could tell them otherwise.
Hey, what's on this roll?
Just some old photographs.
- Darryl, is Maggie all right?
- It's not for me to say.
We have to send her over to Psych
for a mandatory 72-hour stay.
I'm so sorry.
Poor woman. It's like she's
snakebit or something.
Listen, Prue,
you'd better steer clear of here
so she doesn't ID you.
I'll keep you posted, okay? Bye.
- Where are you going?
- I'm gonna go see Maggie.
Something tells me that I may have
stopped her, but I didn't save her.
I'll come with you. Maybe something
from my psych class could be of use.
Cool, thanks.
That can't be right.
How many swizzle sticks?
Who's counting?
I don't know. A lot.
You think you might
have over-ordered?
- No, they over-shipped.
- Here.
It's my fault.
- What?
- Nothing.
Piper, are you mad at me?
No, don't be ridiculous.
Why would I be mad at you?
I don't know, that's why I'm asking.
What is it?
It's just...
It's Dan.
Never mind, sorry I asked.
And he's going to be...
He's going to be very upset
when he finds out...
...you're the one that I really love.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- No, wait, we can't do this.
- But you just said that...
I know, but I really need
to talk to Dan first.
So count.
- Count.
Count.
Brought you some coffee.
- Thanks.
- I'll take it from here. Thanks.
Okay.
I saw her, you know?
The angel, she saved me.
I believe you, Maggie. Really, I do.
- Here.
- Thanks.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- I'm okay.
I'm just gonna wipe this off.
Maybe you should
just stay away from me.
People get hurt.
All right, that's her.
Any idea what you're gonna say
to her about the whole angel thing?
I'm not really worried about that.
I'm worried about her.
I've been thinking
maybe I can write a spell.
- A spell for what?
- Help put good luck back in her life.
That's sweet, but you know you can't
keep using your powers to save her.
I know. Maybe it'll help her
turn things around,
make her see that life's worth living.
Thanks a lot.
Okay, you see?
All right, I'll need your help.
How do I do this?
You don't need my help.
It's your connection.
It just has to come from the heart.
All right. Here it goes.
From this moment on
Your pain is erased
Your bad luck as well
Enjoy your good luck, Maggie
You're free from this hell
Thanks.
Did I just do that? I mean, help you?
Looks like
her luck's changing already.
Yeah. Have a seat.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Let's get out of here.
Not so fast.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, just a chill.
I gotta tell you, for your first spell,
you packed quite a punch.
Well, you told me to speak
from the heart. I did.
Still, it took me a few times
before my first spell actually worked.
Really?
Well, must be my lucky day.
Phoebe? Phoebe.
Your turn to be cursed, witch.
Piper, I'm going crazy here.
- We're almost done.
- That's not what I mean.
Look, you can't come in here
and tell me what you told me
and expect me to act
like nothing's changed.
- Everything's changed.
- I know. Believe me, I know.
But Dan is out of town,
and until he comes back...
When? When is he coming back?
Next Thursday.
A week? Oh, God.
Can you call him or something?
Never mind, that's not right.
It's just... You know, I've been waiting
for this, for us, for so long.
And I just...
I don't wanna wait any longer.
- Piper, you there?
- Prue?
What...? What happened?
We got in a car accident.
I wasn't looking.
- You guys okay?
- We're fine.
- Phoebe's got a concussion.
- A mild one.
Still, the doctor said that,
you know, you should...
The doctor? You went
to the hospital? Phoebe, you...
I'm fine, really.
I just have a little headache.
We've got some aspirin
around here somewhere.
- Phoebe, I'm so sorry.
- Prue, it's okay, it was an accident.
It wasn't your fault.
Yeah, but you know what, I should
have been looking. I always look first.
At least I didn't put you
in the hospital this time.
Your lipstick's smeared.
It is?
- Don't worry about it, I got it. I got it.
- Okay. I am such a klutz.
I can't seem to do anything
right all of a sudden.
Do you think that that spell
backfired on me?
- Not possible, no personal gain.
- What spell?
Hello.
Yeah, Mr. Corso, there was a
problem with the photograph.
Prue got this gig photographing
this girl named Maggie Murphy.
The unlucky Maggie Murphy?
- I'm sorry. Is there anything...?
- I saw a piece on her on TV.
Well, she's not unlucky anymore.
Prue cast a spell
to turn her luck around
after she saved her
from jumping off a roof.
- What?
- Yeah, pretty scary, huh?
- That's more than scary.
- I understand.
- It got to Prue too. Big time.
- Okay. Goodbye.
All right, Mr. Corso said if I don't
get that photograph of Maggie,
I can kiss my career goodbye.
Like that's what I wanna do right now.
Well, it's a good excuse
to go check up on her.
Yeah, I'm just gonna stop by
the house, pick up my things...
It's okay.
I'll drive because you didn't
get collision on the rental.
- Here, you want the keys?
- Yes.
Here.
Thank you.
What? I'll clean it up.
No, it's not that. I was just thinking
about Maggie Murphy.
What about her?
It's just that she was doing all
these good things in her life,
and then, all of a sudden,
her own life goes to hell.
- So what?
- I don't know.
What if, you know, all these accidents
in her life weren't actually accidents?
I mean, what if something
was trying to make her jump?
Something like...?
Like a darklighter, maybe.
It's okay, Mrs. Sidelman.
Let's just get you out
into the sunlight
and let you see
what's going on in the world, okay?
That's it. You're doing fine.
Maggie has made
a remarkable turnaround.
Severely depressed this morning,
now, suddenly, she's smiling,
laughing, helping others.
However, I'm afraid her recovery
is only temporary.
Why do you say that?
Once you've been on that ledge,
Miss Halliwell,
you can never forget it.
That deep, dark place
never goes away.
It haunts you, beckons you back.
- That's not true.
- Oh, are you a psychiatrist?
No, but I still don't think
that that's true.
Lots of people
recover from depression.
Not people in Maggie's
rather unique situation.
She still feels responsible for all
of the tragedies in her family's life.
That pain doesn't just...
...magically go away.
- May we see her?
- Of course.
- You're doing great.
- Thank you.
I'll be right back, okay?
- You'll be fine.
- Okay.
I hoped you'd come
so I could thank you.
And ask you...
I have so many questions.
Maggie, I think that you may have
the wrong idea about me.
You saved my life.
There was so much going on this
morning. It was really confusing,
- there were so many people.
- That doesn't change what you did.
Who are you?
My name is Prue.
- This is my sister Phoebe.
- Hi, Maggie.
- Two angels.
- Oh, no, I'm just a student.
Maggie, how are you feeling?
Better, I hope.
Honestly?
I feel great. I couldn't be happier.
- Even though you're here?
- I'm alive.
And more importantly,
I feel alive again.
I'm able to give.
I'm able to help people.
I haven't been able
to do that for a while.
That's really sweet.
Are you a photographer?
Yeah. Sort of...
Yes, she is.
She's working for 415 Magazine.
Oh, yeah,
they're doing an article on me.
Is that why you were at my place
this morning, to take my picture?
Yeah. But believe me,
that was the last thing on my mind.
No, no, no. It's fine.
Maybe the article will help others.
Help them realize
not to give up either.
Where do you want me?
I guess here is fine.
Here you go.
I just can't get over how
everything's changed suddenly.
I mean, I know I'm stuck here
for a while,
but I feel like a 1000-pound weight's
been lifted off me.
I feel like my old self again.
Maggie, I'm taking
a psychology class in school,
and I was wondering
if I could ask you a question.
Sure, anything.
I was wondering why you...
How...?
- How did I get on the ledge?
- Yeah.
I really don't know, actually.
All I know is
I just wanted it all to stop.
You wanted what to stop?
The voice in my head that kept
telling me I was hurting people,
not helping them. That I was causing
pain and trouble wherever I went.
That it was all my fault.
It's like...
...I was...
...cursed.
Maybe you were cursed.
I'm sorry, what was...?
Prue?
I have to go get these
to the magazine right away.
- Did you just hear what she said?
- Yeah, look, can you take a cab
- and take that home for me?
- Why don't I drive you?
No, it's fine.
- Bye, Maggie.
- Bye.
There's a whole section in here
on darklighters somewhere.
Somebody should
really index this thing.
Are you sure about this?
Piper, I've been a whitelighter
for over 50 years.
Okay.
It's just Prue's in trouble.
Maybe that's her.
- Hello, Prue?
- No, it's me, Dan.
- Dan. Hi.
- You miss me?
- No.
- Really?
I was talking to the cat.
Are you in New York?
Yeah, I'm in my hotel room.
So, what are you doing?
Just reading.
- How was your flight?
- It was fine.
Hey, listen, maybe it's
just my imagination,
but I sensed a little...
...something going on.
Or not going on at all,
if that makes any sense.
Everything's fine.
So that feeling that you had
something important to tell me
but didn't want to ruin my trip,
that's just all in my head?
Piper?
I'm sorry. I'm just...
I'm a little distracted here.
Can we talk when you get home?
Right. Hey, listen, you know what,
you don't have to worry about
picking me up at the airport.
I'll just catch a cab back to my place,
maybe we can go out to dinner.
Great.
Okay. I'll see you soon.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
I'm sorry. It's difficult.
I am going to break up with him, but I
can't do it when he's 3000 miles away.
I have to be fair to him.
I understand that totally. I really do.
You know, I'm glad
that you're the kind of person
that would give him
that kind of respect.
Thank you.
Now, here's what I'm
really worried about.
Read this.
You've got to be kidding.
I don't understand. I checked it
in my camera myself. It was fine.
What am I supposed to print
with the article?
What am I supposed to do, huh?
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
I gave you a chance.
I believed in you.
And this is what I get?
- You're a fraud.
- Wait a second, look...
No, you look. Lady, you're fired.
No, you're worse than fired. I will
make sure nobody hires you again.
Now, go on, get out.
Go screw up somebody else's life.
Wait. I can handle this.
Everything's gonna be fine.
No, it's not. He's right.
I'm a fraud.
- I only hurt people.
- No.
It's all my fault. I'm responsible.
- Hi.
- Phoebe, where's Prue?
- Probably at the magazine, why?
- There may be a darklighter after her.
- We need to find her fast.
- What?
Was the car wreck right after
Prue cast the spell on Maggie?
- Yeah, why?
- A darklighter
- must have seen her cast it.
- Why isn't this going through?
- Maggie thought that she was cursed.
- She probably was,
until Prue turned her luck around.
See, there's a certain
type of darklighter
that drives future whitelighters
to commit suicide.
- What do you mean?
- The only way to keep
a whitelighter from becoming one
is to have them take their own life.
To lose their souls forever.
They curse them. They bring
their victims self-doubt,
bad luck, the kind
that hurts other people.
Then reinforce that by
preying on their thoughts,
make them think they're
responsible for all the pain
when they're actually not.
- That's not suicide, that's murder.
- Well, not technically.
They never actually push their victims,
they just always compel them to jump.
So Prue didn't save Maggie from
herself, Prue saved Maggie from him.
What is wrong with her phone?
And that's why the darklighter
is after Prue.
If he destroys Prue,
he destroys the good-luck spell
and leaves Maggie unprotected.
Well, he's not gonna get to Prue.
- I don't care what he tries.
- Phoebe, he knows her thoughts.
He can make her think
anything he wants her to.
Piper, this is Prue that we're
talking about, okay? She is so...
She wouldn't even think of...
- What?
- You guys are right.
We have to get to Prue.
The cellular subscriber you are trying
to reach is not in the calling area.
The cellular subscriber is too
in the calling area. Damn it.
Try calling the magazine.
I already did. They said
she left a half an hour ago.
Okay, then. Keep trying her cell.
Are you sure your vision
was of the past and not the future?
- Positive.
- Could you tell how old she was?
Around 20.
It was the same time
that we had that other accident.
What happened?
Prue was driving,
and she ran a red light.
- We didn't hear the other car honk.
- Phoebe was the only one hurt.
She was in the hospital for over a
week. It scared the hell out of us.
- And Prue never forgave herself.
- It was a really rough time for her.
- For all of us, actually.
- Why?
Well, Phoebe and I
were teenagers
and Grams was
extremely overprotective.
But she was hardest on Prue.
She made Prue take care of us.
She didn't let Prue go away to school.
She wanted to go back East
to be a photojournalist.
But Grams knew that we were
going to become witches,
and she wasn't gonna let
anything jeopardize that.
Still, you know what, I don't
care what was happening,
- Prue would never even consider...
- I know, but you saw her.
Okay, what I saw
was Prue taking a picture,
and she was very sad,
but that doesn't mean
that she was actually gonna jump.
Yeah, but the darklighter will make
her think that she was going to.
He'll mess with her head and try and
take her back to that same dark place.
Then he'll say whatever he has to
and make her do something
she would never otherwise do.
Okay, so if we can't find Prue,
how do we find the darklighter?
You can't without a whitelighter.
They sense each other.
- Prue?
- Hey, Pheebs.
- Is it her?
- Yeah.
- Where are you?
- I don't really know,
but I can't start my car,
and this day just really sucks.
None of what's happened today
has anything to do with...
- Hello?
- Prue, can you hear me?
Barely.
Look, I lost my job, and can you guys
just please come and get me?
- Tell her about the darklighter.
- I'm trying. Prue?
Phoebe, I can't hear you.
Hello?
Damn it.
I lost her.
Okay, what do we do?
We have to find her.
- Well, where do we start?
- We start at the magazine.
Backtrack from the magazine.
That's where she was last.
She could be anywhere.
How about the Book of Shadows?
You could try scrying.
I don't think
we have the time for that.
Well, maybe we need a little luck.
A little good luck.
- Maggie?
- We need a map.
Okay, I'll meet you at the car.
- All right, I'm going with you.
- No, somebody has to stay here
- in case she comes back.
- Piper...
If we find her,
the darklighter will be there too.
And if he recognizes you...
Piper, I hate this, all right. I hate
not being able to look after you guys.
I know.
I'm sorry. I know.
What's happening to me?
What's the matter with me?
I gotta keep moving. Keep walking.
I've been in this dark place before.
I remember.
No one can help me. I'm all alone.
Keep walking. Yes, keep walking.
Okay, Prue, keep it together.
This isn't me. I'm a good person.
I do good things.
Are you okay?
Oh, God.
- Are you all right? Are you all right?
- My leg.
I almost got him killed. Just like
how I almost got Phoebe killed.
Run. Run.
Gin. That's great, Mrs. Sidelman.
- Maggie. Hi. Remember me?
- Of course.
We need your help finding Prue.
- Prue?
- Your angel.
She's in trouble. Big trouble.
- The kind of trouble you can relate to.
- What can I do?
We need you to point anywhere
on this map.
We need a little of your luck.
- But I don't understand how that...
- Please. It'll help, trust me.
Here.
It's close by.
Thank you.
It's okay.
No need to be afraid.
I know what needs to be done.
It's the best thing.
The best thing for everyone.
It's something I should have done
a long time ago.
Jump.
That's it.
That's right. That's the only way.
That's the only way
to save the ones I love.
I should have done it before.
Eight years ago.
But I didn't want to.
But if I had, loved ones
would still be alive today.
Like Andy.
I'm responsible for Andy.
Andy.
It's all my fault.
Jump.
There's gotta be something in here.
Damn it.
I can't just sit back and do nothing.
Think, think.
Give me my powers back.
I want my powers back.
I want my powers back!
I want them back now!
God...
I can't keep being mortal
if this is the cost.
No, I don't want to lose Piper.
But not at the expense
of losing one of her sisters.
Now, this is my calling.
You have to let me help.
You have to give me my wings back.
- Are you sure this is right?
- This is where Maggie pointed to.
- But she's not here.
- She's gotta be here somewhere.
Oh, my God. Phoebe.
Prue!
- Wait, we can drive there.
- No, there's no time. Come on.
Prue. Get away from the railing!
- Prue!
Prue, this isn't you.
A darklighter is making you do this!
- I'm all alone.
- Alone.
He tried to kill Maggie,
and he's trying to kill you.
He put a spell on you,
just like he did with Maggie.
There is no darklighter. It's only me.
- Just me.
- I have to do this.
- Prue!
- Prue! You're stronger than he is.
Jump, damn it.
- Hurry up.
- I'm stronger.
End it before I hurt them again.
Prue. You have to believe us.
- He's there, Prue.
- Turn around, Prue!
- It's true.
- How did you...?
You bastard.
How dare you hurt people this way.
It's a gift.
You'll jump for me, sooner or later.
I haven't lost anyone yet.
- You lost two today.
- Perhaps.
But remember, you can't stop me.
Leo?
- You all right?
- Yeah, I think so.
I gotta go. Now.
Well, the bridge
hasn't changed much, has it?
- But you sure have.
- Well, we all have, for the better.
Prue, Phoebe
and I were wondering...
What?
Why I was on this bridge eight years
ago? Why I took this picture?
- Well, yeah.
- I don't know.
I guess I was
just in a really bad place then.
Anyway, I was out scouting for a shot,
and I found myself on that bridge.
And I just wanted to take a picture
of it to remind myself
of that particular moment
and how I was feeling.
- But you weren't gonna...?
- No.
No, I would never, ever do that.
But why didn't you develop it?
I mean, until now?
I guess I just wasn't ready
to relive that pain.
But now I am.
Especially since a demon
tried to take advantage of it.
But that was then.
And...
...this.
This is now.
What's this?
Hi, it's me. I'm a
professional photographer. Look.
- I'll get it.
- Wait.
What if it's Dan?
What if he's back from his trip early?
Well, then I have to tell him the truth.
Just because Leo has his wings back
doesn't change anything.
- Honey, that's awesome.
- I know.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Thank you.
Leo? You rang the bell?
Yeah, I wasn't sure how you'd feel
about me orbing in.
I'd feel okay.
But I just wanted to let you know
that this wasn't their idea.
It was mine. And it's not something
that I wanted to do, it's just...
Leo.
I meant what I said,
and I've thought about this a lot.
Whitelighter or not, we can
find a way to make this work.
- Somehow, some way.
- I'm gonna hold you to that.
You do that.