Painting of a Gothic castle,
artist unknown, circa 1920s.
Oil on canvas, 20-by-28. Miss Franklin,
where did you say you got this?
I inherited it a few months ago. But
it's been in my family for generations.
The composition is so unusual.
The artist used pure colour straight
from the tube and then varnished
- each layer over and...
- I'm sorry for interrupting.
But do I really need to be here?
No, of course not. It's just that most
people prefer to be at an appraisal,
especially when they plan
on selling the piece.
- It's just that I'm kind of in a hurry.
- Say no more.
Just sign at the bottom,
and you are free to go.
Thank you. So how long
do you think it'll take to sell it?
Well, I'll need to see ownership
records before I can do anything.
I'll send you everything I have.
So is that all then?
No, since you definitely wanna sell
the piece,
I'll need to confirm its authenticity,
its physical condition.
So if you'll just sign at the bottom,
that will let us go ahead
and x-ray the piece.
Done.
Anything else?
Well, yes, Miss Franklin. I would really
like the time to research this.
That way I can get you the best price.
Look, I appreciate
your professionalism. I really do.
But I'm not interested in getting
the best price.
I just want you to sell that painting
as soon as you can, all right?
- Good night, Miss Halliwell.
- Good night.
Piper, it was an accident.
It's not like I borrowed Prue's car
- so I could drive it into a pole.
- How bad's the damage?
Not bad, but maybe expensive,
which is why I need a favour.
If you're calling to borrow money,
I don't have any.
No, it's not about money.
It's just... I don't want you to tell Prue.
She's been so supportive,
and I don't wanna lose her trust again.
- You mean you haven't told her?
- Well, not yet, but I have a plan.
Phoebe, you have to tell her.
It's her car, and you don't have
the money to fix it.
But I will have the money to fix it.
I'm at this company called
Web San Francisco. It's
an interactive network on the Internet.
And I faxed them my résumé
this morning,
and they wanna meet
with me tonight.
I've gotta go, but I don't wanna
be in the middle of this.
- Just tell her, okay?
- If I don't get the job, I will tell her.
Hello, I'm Phoebe Halliwell.
I have an appointment.
Thanks.
All these people, they're here
for the interview too, aren't they?
Well, you won't have any trouble
with this if you figured that out.
It's an aptitude test.
You can finish it at home.
Great. Great.
So you won a fellowship from
the National Science Foundation?
When I was at Harvard, yeah.
How'd you know?
I saw it on your résumé.
I was cum laude also.
Except I was
a Ford Foundation scholar.
So then you must have gone
to Stanford?
Stanford? I went to Stanford.
Intimidating, isn't it?
The Good Will Huntings
or this aptitude test?
Oh, who cares about linear algebra or
differential? And that test is a snap.
I mean, in this day and age,
who can't write
in the HTML and numeric
languages, right?
Right.
Yeah, that's... That's for you.
What?
At first I just thought that it was a
reflection off of something in the room.
But then when I moved closer,
I saw a man
inside the painting, in the castle.
Right, but the moment I saw him,
he backed away from the window.
And then there was this strange glow
that went past the window again.
It was just so...
- Piper?
- What?
- We were talking?
- I know, about a man in a painting.
Listen to this one. "Hallway
near club entrance too narrow."
I thought that we had discussed
your code violations.
Well, I keep finding more.
The plumbing, the electrical,
the heating.
- It... None of it is up to code.
- Stop.
- You're obsessing.
- Well, it runs in the family.
I don't obsess.
I think intensely.
Anyway, I can't really help it.
I mean, we've seen so many bizarre
things, why not a man in a painting?
At least he's safe
from building inspectors.
I can't imagine
that castle's up to code.
I'm sorry, but I couldn't find anything
in the Book of Shadows about people
who may be trapped inside paintings.
I looked everywhere.
Hey, you were asleep by the time
I got home. How did your interview go?
It went fine.
Actually, it's still going. I have
to finish this take-home aptitude test,
which I actually think
I will start right now.
So I will see you guys later.
- Phoebe?
- What?
Aren't you forgetting something?
My car keys?
They'd be with your car...
...which is at the body shop,
having an estimate.
- An estimate?
- Yeah, I bumped...
No, actually I backed your car
into a pole last night.
A pole?
You hit a pole?
Yeah, you don't even have to say it.
I know what you're thinking.
How could I be so irresponsible?
How could I be so stupid?
Okay, irresponsible, yes. Stupid,
no way. Where is that coming from?
It's coming from the fact
that I'm the youngest sister,
the one who always makes mistakes,
the one who always causes problems.
I mean, if anybody were gonna back
your car into a pole
and not tell you right away,
it'd be me, right?
- I think I'll just be going now.
- See? Even the middle sister,
the one that's supposed to stay neutral
when it comes to family problems,
- checks out on this one.
- Yes, you're right. You're on your own.
Well, leave me out of it too.
I don't wanna argue with you.
- I just wanna find a cab.
- Well, whatever it costs,
I will pay for the damages.
And whatever the cab costs,
I will pay for that too.
- What just happened here?
- I don't know anything about anything.
- I'm gonna go see Dan.
- Piper!
Just forget about the car.
What about the man in the painting?
Well, unless he's real and screaming
for help, forget about him.
We shouldn't go looking for trouble.
We have enough around here.
I'm going next door.
- Dan.
- Good morning.
- I'm sorry to bother you.
- No, you're not bothering me, unless
- you refuse to hand over my paper.
- Oh, all yours.
- Thanks. You wanna come in?
- No, no, really,
I just stopped by to ask a quick favour.
My club received a visit
- from the DBI last night...
- And you got code violations.
I have the War and Peace
of code violations.
And you were thinking what?
Neighbour Dan, he's in construction,
- maybe he could help, huh?
- Of course I'd pay you something.
- Uncle Dan, I'm late. Oh, hey, Piper.
- Hi, Jenny.
See you later, Uncle Dan.
And don't forget your promise.
Okay, then, I'll tell you what I can do.
I'll check out the code violations,
see how serious they really are
if you will help me with the promise
- I made Jenny.
- Deal. Wait, what's the promise?
She needs help with a paper. It's...
It's for bio class. You know, something
- with the human reproductive system.
- Oh, you mean sex.
It's just way too awkward for me
to talk to my niece about.
Yeah. Sure, not to worry,
I have plenty of experience.
- Really? With sex?
- No, I mean, talking about it.
Yeah.
So was there a problem
with any
of the ownership records
that I sent over?
No, everything's in order.
Then I'm not sure why you wanted
to meet with me.
Look, Miss Franklin, I know that you
don't really wanna be here,
so I'll just be perfectly honest. There is
something strange about that painting.
- Have you seen him?
- Him?
- That's how it all starts, you know.
- What do you mean?
At first, you see him...
...the man inside the painting.
At least you think you see him,
but he just... He disappears so fast.
And you start to think about it, but
it doesn't make any sense. I mean,
how could a man be inside a painting?
And then you see him again.
This time longer.
And now you're sure.
So you think that the painting
is haunted by a ghost?
Oh, no, no,
I think he's definitely alive.
I think he's trapped inside.
- Do you know who he is?
- No, I have no idea.
Nobody does.
Look, all I know is that
if I don't get rid of that painting,
I'm gonna end up just like everybody
else in my family who ever owned it.
- I'm gonna be completely insane.
- Miss Franklin...
No, you've only seen the beginning,
Miss Halliwell.
Just trust me when I tell you
it's only gonna get worse.
Spirits send the words from all...
It's me. Can I come in?
Piper, I really just wanna be alone
right now.
I won't stay long, promise.
All right, just give me a sec.
Okay, you can come in now.
I just wanted to tell you
the body shop called.
Yeah, I know, I heard the message,
1,200 bucks.
- Did you tell Prue?
- I didn't have to. She already knew.
She called the body shop herself.
That's why I have got
to get this job, Piper.
It's the only way that I could pay
for the damages.
The only way I can make
things right.
All the more reason
you just should've told her.
Okay, well, maybe a smarter person
would've figured that out.
Then again, a smart person wouldn't
have backed the car into a pole.
A smart person would've realized
that it was a $1,200 pole.
That's because smart people don't do
stupid things, only stupid people do.
- Phoebe, I didn't mean to upset you.
- I know.
- Maybe we should just talk later.
- Okay.
- You sure you're gonna be okay?
- Yeah. Why?
Phoebe, I know you think getting
this job is the answer, but please,
- just don't do anything...
- What, stupid?
No, just don't do
anything I wouldn't do.
Don't worry, I won't.
You would never cast a smart spell.
Okay.
For 24 hours, from 7 to 7,
I will understand all meaning
of the words from here to heaven.
Spirits, send the words
From all across the land
Allow me to absorb them
Through the touch of either hand
For 24 hours, from 7 to 7
I will understand all meaning
Of the words from here to heaven
Oh, and P.S., there will be
no personal gain.
Abaca, strong fibre obtained
from a banana leaf.
Zygote, a cell formed
by the union of two gametes.
Cool.
- Hey, Joe, that was fast.
- No line at the x-ray machine.
So did the x-ray confirm
its authenticity?
It did a lot more than that.
Check out the x-ray.
It's got definitive underwriting
on the canvas.
- It has a pentimento?
- Yeah, I couldn't believe it either.
But you can see it on the x-ray.
The text is in Latin.
I've never seen
anything like it before.
"Absolvo, amitto, amplus, brevis."
- To free what is lost say these words.
- Wow, you speak Latin?
- Yes. Good night, Joe.
- Okay.
Well, why don't I just return
the painting to the vault,
say, tomorrow.
- Good idea.
- Okay.
"Help."
Okay.
"Semper mea." Mine forever.
Absolvo amitto amplus brevis.
Semper mea.
Oh, no.
Who's there?
- Quick, follow me!
- What?
This way. Ladies first.
I see you read Latin too.
Okay, what has happened?
Where am I?
- You're in the castle.
- Where is that?
- Inside a painting.
- I'm trapped inside a painting?
Yes, and if you don't get to
that bookcase, you're dead.
Who are you?
My name's Malcolm, and you were
supposed to help me, not join me.
Who are you anyway?
My name is Prue,
and I was helping you.
- You were supposed to come out.
- Great, now we're both trapped. Hurry!
What the hell? What are you?
How'd you do that?
Oh, okay, never mind. We're gonna
get killed. Will you hurry up?
Hi, Phoebe.
You're up early. What's up?
Oh, the Dow Jones, housing prices
and the space shuttle Discovery.
Read the paper.
- Have you seen Prue this morning?
- Not yet.
Oh, Dan just called, said he'd
meet you at the club at noon.
Okay.
- Did you hear her come in last night?
- Nope.
This is really strange.
Cat hasn't been fed,
no coffee's been made.
And Prue definitely
didn't pack a lunch.
Well, maybe she's still asleep.
No, I checked her room.
Her bed hasn't been slept in.
Maybe she didn't come home
from the office last night.
No, it's her voice mail.
What if Prue is right
about the painting?
What if something's happened?
First off, 63 percent of all adults
believed to be missing show up
within 24 hours.
An auto accident is unlikely,
1.2 percent.
Even less likely
for work-related accidents.
Factor in her good health,
a life expectancy of 78.5 years,
add her defensive powers
of telekinesis,
and we are looking at the odds of...
...less than 4.1 percent. No, actually,
make that less than 3.3 percent.
I forgot that the Book of Shadows
had zip on evil artwork.
- What's wrong with you?
- Nothing.
No, you are like
Ask-Rain-Man. Com.
You haven't been
in the Book of Shadows, have you?
- No. Why would I do that?
- All right, I don't have time for this.
I'm gonna go to Buckland's.
Well, what about Dan? You're
supposed to meet him at the club.
- Damn it.
- Do you like him?
Is that the vibe that I am getting
right now?
No, don't be ridiculous.
Do me a favour and go in my place.
And then you can give me
all the details later.
- Like what he was wearing?
- No.
You can't just stand there another
12 hours and not let me help you.
- You're hurt.
- Stay where you are. I hate witches.
How many times do I have to tell you
that I'm a good witch?
Although, if you make me say
that again, I just may hurt you.
- Look, I was trying to save you.
- Well, you did a great job.
The last thing that I expected
was to get stuck here.
So I guess your powers can't get us
out then, huh?
No, I can't just lift us
from another world.
So if we're gonna get out,
we're gonna have to work together.
Just let me help you.
I won't turn you into a toad.
I promise.
Thank you.
May I?
Doesn't look too bad.
At least the bleeding has...
So why do you hate witches so much?
It's how I got trapped in here.
The artist that painted this was a witch.
She was my girlfriend.
- You dated a witch?
- What, you've never dated a mortal?
I wonder.
Oh, sorry.
- Go on.
- Fine.
Nell and I, we broke up,
and she wrote a curse in Latin.
To free what is lost.
Right, and she painted the castle
over it, made sure I got the painting.
It was the only way she could
trick me and trap me inside.
- It worked.
- So how did you see the underwriting?
- Same way as you probably.
- An x-ray.
Well, you must have really
pissed Nell off.
Well, that would explain why I haven't
aged since I got here and the fireballs.
How long have you been running
from them?
- What year is it?
- 1999.
It's been 70 years.
Wait a second. You've been stuck
here trying to get out for 70 years?
It's not the typical life
of an art historian, is it?
Well, I won't be here that long.
I mean, I have two sisters,
and we all have powers.
If anybody can find a way out, it's us.
- Dan, sorry to keep you waiting.
- I didn't realize you were late.
Oh, 11 minutes, 23.4 seconds,
to be exact. Those the code violations?
That and the DBI's codebook
of minimum safety requirements.
Okay, then we're all set. I think you'll
find me pretty knowledgeable
about all areas of construction.
- What about Piper?
- Oh, something came up.
She can't be here. Sorry, buddy.
Prue?
"Absolvo, amitto, amplus, brevis."
Oh, hey, Piper.
Joe Lyons? We met at a wine
auction a few months ago?
Prue around?
She's... She's somewhere.
Well, I won't get in your way.
Just need to pick up the painting.
- Oh, forgive me, Joe.
- For what?
For that.
That's your plan? Are you crazy?
My sisters will realize I'm missing
soon. I have to let them know
- where I am and warn them.
- You'll die.
I don't have any other choice.
Otherwise, my sisters could make
the same mistake I did and get sucked
into this painting. Okay, corner, now.
- And how will seeing your name...?
- And the name Nell.
Yes, written on the window
prevent that?
Okay, my sisters
will think that it's a clue.
They'll look up the name Nell
in our Book of Shadows,
and hopefully, they'll find a solution.
Are you ready? Go.
Okay, tell me how you write "help"
on the window
without getting creamed
by a fireball.
- You don't know how to do it?
- You're the expert.
Are you crazy? It took me years
to get those messages written.
And I have the scars to prove it.
What about your powers?
All right, fine. I'll deflect fireballs,
you write the names.
Be careful near the window.
Why?
What's wrong with the window?
Okay, okay, what is happening?
The painting, it's being moved.
And it's moving fast.
- Get back to the chamber.
- No way, I'm going to that window.
It's too dangerous.
We gotta get out of here.
Hold the elevator, please.
I really wanted to get my name
and Nell's on that window.
And you can as soon as the painting's
stopped moving. Just stay low.
- What?
- Nothing, I was just... Never mind.
- No, what?
- Well, I always hoped
someone would get my SOS. I just...
I just never thought
it would be a woman.
What, a woman can't rescue a man?
- I'm still waiting.
- Yeah, well, keep waiting, pal.
Bookcase!
Hello, this is Phoebe Halliwell,
and I'd like to set up an appointment
to return my aptitude test.
By 5 tomorrow? Great. Bye.
Oh, Piper, good news.
I spoke to Dan. He will have
your estimate ready by tomorrow.
We got bigger problems
than code violations.
- Prue wasn't at Buckland's?
- No.
But it was clearly the last place
she was before she disappeared.
- I take it you haven't heard from her?
- Not a word. Okay, now I'm worried.
Check out this x-ray I found
in her office.
I think it may have something to do
with her disappearing.
And we don't have a lot of time either.
It won't be long before everyone
at Buckland's realizes she is gone
and the painting is gone.
Oh, the final match.
- Primarily concerned
with blood and...?
- Haematology.
Yes. Oona Chaplin,
the wife of Charlie Chaplin,
was the daughter of what famous...?
- Eugene O'Neill.
- O'Neill.
Yes. What country now occupies the
peninsula once known as Asia Minor?
- Turkey.
Yes. Basketball player turned poli...
How is it that you know
all the answers?
What? I could know about medicine,
American playwrights
and that Asia Minor
is now called Turkey.
No, you couldn't.
You have cast a spell, haven't you?
I wanted to be able
to get Prue's car fixed.
And this job was the only way
that I could do it.
Phoebe, what kind of spell?
All I had to do was ace an aptitude test,
which, by the way, I'm sure I have.
- Phoebe!
- Okay.
It's a smart spell. And before
you freak out, it's only temporary.
It'll be over by 7:00 tonight.
It doesn't matter when it ends.
We're not allowed to cast
personal-gain spells. You know that.
Yeah, I do know that, but it's not.
I even put that in myself,
no personal gain.
There will be consequences.
There always are.
I don't care. It's worth it.
Piper, you weren't
at that job interview,
surrounded
by all those college graduates.
You don't know how good it feels
to be really smart.
Smart people are respected,
taken seriously. And really smart
women, forget about it.
Then again, you probably
do know what I'm talking about.
- You have a four-year degree.
- So what?
Phoebe, I will never have the kind of
smarts you have, no matter what I do.
But, you, you can go back to college.
Say you did get this job.
What would happen to it the moment
your smart spell ended?
I thought I'd worry about that later.
Wait. What does this mean?
"Absolvo, amitto, amplus, brevis.
Semper mea"?
Phoebe, help!
- Piper, no!
- Phoebe!
Piper?
What the hell is happening?
Where are we?
All right, hurry, just get
to the bookcase fast.
Watch out!
Don't tell me she's the sister witch
who was gonna save us.
I don't wanna live forever
and spend the rest of my life
trapped in a painting hanging
on some wall wearing a broken shoe.
Well, neither do I,
but there is a solution.
You call that a solution,
braving endless fireballs
to get a message to Phoebe?
Okay, so it doesn't take
a rocket scientist to figure out
that this situation is pretty bad.
No, but it may just take a rocket
scientist to get us out of here: Phoebe.
- Another witch sister?
- Not just any witch, a super witch.
- She's a genius.
- Piper, I don't really think
that you're helping the situation.
No, I mean it. She's a walking
brain trust. An Einstein with cleavage.
She cast a spell on herself, Prue,
a smart spell.
- What?
- Can she save us?
Forget the details, Prue.
Just know that
if anybody can get us out of here,
it's Phoebe.
We need to get back
to that living room,
- get Nell's name on that window...
- Piper, wait.
No, we can't wait. It's only temporary.
The spell ends at 7 tonight.
Come on, come on,
there's got to be something.
- Who is it?
- It's Jenny.
Unless it's a huge 911, sweetie,
you're gonna have to come back later.
If we get out of here alive,
you owe me a new pair of shoes.
If we get out of here alive, I'll buy you
the purse to match. Piper, left!
Look, forget the shoes. The next time
you get a supernatural SOS...
I'll take your advice and just ignore it.
- Be careful near the window!
- What's wrong with the window?
Blades.
- Are you okay?
- For now.
But I can't reach the window, because
if I lean forward, I am slice and diced.
Okay.
Piper, hurry.
Don't forget to write her name
backward
so Phoebe can read it
from the outside.
Come on.
Good thing she had a short name.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
The human reproductive system?
Wait. And your uncle wanted
Piper to help you out with this?
Yeah, but I was too embarrassed to tell
him that I already know about sex.
So I figured we could just hang out
and watch some television.
Hey, what's that?
Jenny, will you go in there
and grab me a pen, please?
- Nell?
- Is something wrong?
I'm not sure. Okay.
The 23 chromosomes that make up
the human genome system
within the cell...
It's too complicated. Okay.
- Okey-dokey, you're all set.
- But...
Bye, Jenny.
Nell, Nell, find me Nell
Whoa, I am one super-smart witch.
Okay, what do we have here?
Latin. "In the 1920s,
a witch named Nell
tricked a powerful warlock
into a painting
with a hidden spell that only his power
of x-ray vision could see."
Okay, I'm getting tired of talking
to myself. How do I get my sisters out?
"Verva omnes liberant."
Words free us all.
"These words will free anyone trapped
inside the painting."
Okay, but how do I get the words
inside without getting trapped
inside the painting myself?
No, I couldn't.
So maybe we should take shifts
waiting for Phoebe
outside the bookcase.
I mean, we've been
pretty safe there so far.
- I'll take the first shift.
- I had a feeling you would.
What? What is it? What's wrong?
I've been thinking about that witch
who cursed Malcolm into the painting.
I mean, it takes a lot of time and a high
level of magic to create this world.
Seems like an awfully big spell
just to get revenge over a bad breakup.
- I agree.
- And it was almost impossible for us,
the Charmed Ones no less,
to get that message on the window.
Yet Malcolm, an art historian
with absolutely no powers,
was able to escape fireballs
and those blades
to get his message on the window.
I mean, I don't know, Piper, it just...
Something weird about all of this.
Here, kitty, kitty.
What do we have here?
- It is Kit.
- What is she doing here?
- Prue, look.
- Verva omnes...
Piper, freeze him.
You're too late. But you were right,
your sister Phoebe is one smart witch.
Blinking allows me to be one place
one moment and another the next.
Piper, look out.
Liberant!
I thought he was an innocent.
I thought he needed help.
I'm not talking to you, forever.
Thanks for freeing me, witch.
Seventy years is a long time.
Seventy years?
- You're a warlock, aren't you?
- Your sisters were right.
You are a smart witch.
- Where are they?
- With the cat.
The one with no collar.
That was interesting.
That was smart.
Too smart for your own good.
So that woman who brought Prue
the painting, she's a warlock too?
Jane's my lover. She's been trying
to get me out for years.
She needed to find
the Charmed Ones, you.
- It took her 70 years to do that.
- We haven't been around that long.
I read a Jeet Kune Do manual
earlier today.
I think that makes me a black belt.
Actually, make that a seventh-degree
black belt. I'm a master.
Not for long you're not.
We'll see how powerful you are,
how smart you are
- when your spell ends at 7.
- How do you know about that?
Tick-tock, Phoebe. Tick-tock.
- Malcolm.
- Jane.
I thought I'd never seen you again.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Not yet, not yet. I have
a little present for you.
Oh, you do? Where is it?
It's inside the house.
Something you've always wanted.
- And what would that be?
- The power of premonition.
- And what would you get?
- Revenge and two more powers.
Even if Phoebe is alive,
she may not be for long.
Maybe she can figure out a way
to save herself before he finds her.
Yeah, well, she better do it quick.
It's almost 7.
Although, if anybody can do it,
Phoebe can.
Yeah, even without the smart spell.
I mean, putting that message
on Kit's collar,
that's very Phoebe.
I would have never thought of it.
Neither would I. It was a great plan.
If we get out of here, I'm gonna buy
her a new pair of shoes.
I'll buy her the purse to match.
Now, the spell,
it was three words in Latin.
Question is, which three?
Oh, no. Come on, come on.
Okay, it's on the tip of my tongue.
Verva omnes... Something.
Verva omnes... Liber... Liber...
Liberace!
No, it can't be Liberace.
Oh, no.
It's in Latin. The spell is over,
and I don't understand
Latin anymore.
I told you I'd be back.
Hello, Phoebe.
- Say goodbye to your family.
- No!
"Absolvo, amitto, amplus, brevis.
Semper mea."
No!
- The house is on fire?
- No, not the house, the painting.
It's gotta be Malcolm's doing.
He must be at the manor.
- Phoebe, you're alive.
- Yeah. Let's keep it that way.
Malcolm?
- And Jane.
- She's a warlock.
You stupid witch.
Now you and your sisters
are gonna end up burning to death.
Looking for this?
Freeze them.
Where's Kit?
There she is, there she is.
Okay. Oh, I can't believe
we almost forgot her.
Verva omnes liberant!
You know, I didn't want them to die.
I just wanted them trapped
in that house forever.
Bright side, you won't have
to worry about any complaints
- from the owner of the painting.
- And you'll never have to worry
about anyone else getting
a supernatural mayday from it.
Yeah, well, thanks for getting ours,
Phoebe.
How did you get the collar
from Malcolm?
Oh, I used a very complex,
very different kind of smarts.
- You picked his pocket.
- I picked his pocket.
- Phoebe.
- What? He was a warlock.
Smartest thing I've ever done.
A new heating and cooling system,
retrofitting, imported pre-stressed
l-beams, architectural flooring.
Your estimate requires a quarter
of a million dollars and a crew of 75.
I tell you,
I'm not feeling real guilty
about not helping Jenny
with that paper.
Well, actually,
those were Phoebe's suggestions.
Phoebe. Can you fix it cheap
and fix it quick?
In a couple of days, sure.
Great, you're hired.
You can take that with you.
- Hey, Prue.
- Hey.
- Phoebe.
- You got a minute?
- Yeah.
- Is it about Piper?
- No, it's actually about Jenny's paper.
You know, I wasn't really myself
that day. Is there a problem?
No, it's not due till Friday,
but I really appreciate your help.
- I think...
- Yeah, okay.
I'd really appreciate if Jenny could do
her own work, in her handwriting,
using her own smarts,
if you know what I mean.
L... I certainly do. All right.
You don't wanna know.
You know, this whole smart spell thing,
it really just made me realize
that there's a lot of cool information
out there.
- I agree.
- And who knows,
maybe I will go back to college,
take some night classes.
- I'm a smart girl, I'll figure it out.
- Yes, you will.
Just don't lose that common sense.
We may need it to save the day again.
- What are we talking about?
- Right now, the job
- that I will not be getting.
- Smart move, Pheebs.
- Now open your present.
- Okay.
Wait, you guys got me shoes
and a purse?
Very smart-looking,
wouldn't you say, Piper?
- Pure genius, Prue.
- Enough with that already.
Okay, you wanna explain this?
Okay, well, that's Piper,
and that's Dan.
I see.