All right, Jessup, let's go.
- Where?
- Downtown. Evidentiary hearing.
My hearing?
It's not supposed to be until next week.
Got moved up.
- Open up Bane Jessup.
- Opening up Jessup.
I've never seen you guys before.
Hey, look, it's your hearing,
you don't wanna go, fine.
Garbage in, garbage out, huh?
Litvack sent you, didn't he?
Hey. Hey.
Stop.
Hey, what's going on here?
Leo's mortal now and everything,
but for how long?
I mean, how do I know he won't
want his wings back some day?
And then there's Dan,
who is still great and normal.
- Which is good considering I'm not.
- Twenty-eight minutes, 33 seconds.
Really? We ran that long?
No, I'm timing how long
you've been comparing Leo and Dan.
I haven't been comparing,
I've just been talking.
Non-stop.
Well, so, you're my sister,
I have a problem,
the least you could be
is more understanding.
Piper, I am understanding.
You're in love with two guys
who both love you.
I get it. Totally.
But what I don't get
is why you won't let me help you.
Help me? What are you gonna do?
Take one of them off my hands?
That's not an option.
Look, you're stuck.
You don't wanna string them along,
but you can't make a choice.
You need help, assistance, a sign.
- A sign?
- A spell.
One that will point the magical arrow
in the direction of your true love
and end the great debate
once and for all.
Like that doesn't have personal gain
tattooed across its forehead.
Not necessarily.
I've been working on my spells.
I think I can write one for you
that's consequence free.
It's all in the wording.
- No. I can't.
- Why not?
Because I can't expect magic
to solve my personal problems.
But that's the beauty.
You don't have to. I'll do it for you.
Hey, when did
my camera equipment get here?
Oh, about an hour ago. I didn't wanna
wake you. Is everything there?
Yeah, it looks like it.
Jeez, Prue,
think you bought enough stuff?
Yeah, I know. It's a lot.
But so much of photography
has gone digital now
that if I wanna seriously pursue it,
I have to have the right equipment.
Wait, you're thinking of becoming
a professional photographer?
Yeah. Why, you don't think
that I should?
No, no, I mean, I think it's great
if it's what you wanna do, it's just...
It's just what?
Well, isn't photography just
a really dicey profession moneywise?
You know, all I'm saying
is that, how many women professional
photographers do you know?
I know, and that is
a totally fair question,
one that I've been
wrestling with a lot lately.
Like, ever since I quit my job.
Prue, you dreamt of winning the
Pulitzer in photography back in college.
You never wanted to work in
the museum or at the auction house.
That's something you did for us
so we could keep the house.
So now it is your turn
to follow your dreams.
Hey, maybe finding out you were
a photographer in your last life
is some kind of sign.
Speaking of signs.
No. Wait. No.
Portrait of a dreamer.
Phoebe, you're not in there
writing a spell for me, are you?
No. I'm in the bathroom.
Who writes spells in the bathroom?
I'll be right out.
Okay.
I beseech all powers above
Send a sign to frame my sister's heart
One that will lead her to her love
Hello, Prue.
- Well?
- Nothing.
Okay, we have to keep trying
till you do get a premonition.
We have to figure out
what happened to Prue.
Piper, that crack that I made
about her becoming a photographer,
I don't want that to be the last thing
I say to her.
Phoebe, you're overreacting.
That is my department.
All you have to do
is relax and concentrate.
Here. Try the rag again.
I got bad news and I got worse news.
Which do you want first?
Phoebe.
Does this have anything
to do with Prue?
Unless she helped Bane Jessup
escape from county jail, no.
Bane Jessup, why does
that name sound familiar?
Because he's the guy
our favourite demon
hired to eighty-six us, remember?
- The one we thought Prue liked?
- Yes.
When did he escape?
This morning. We've already launched
a full-scale manhunt to...
What is it? What's wrong?
Prue is missing. We think
she may have been kidnapped.
And we found this by the back door.
Chloroform.
We would've called you, but we didn't
know who or what had taken her.
Be a pretty big coincidence
if it wasn't Bane,
especially since you guys
are responsible for putting him in jail.
Yeah, but why take just Prue?
Why not all of us?
Well, maybe he's trying to lure us.
Maybe another demon
hired him to trap us.
Which might explain this.
I found it when we swept
the prison lot this morning.
It's actually the reason
why I came over.
I wanted to see
if it looked familiar to you.
Well, it's definitely demonic.
Do you mind if we keep this
so we can figure out
what demon we're dealing with?
I can't exactly turn that in
to evidence inventory.
Look, I gotta go.
Let me know if you find out anything.
I think that your chances of
finding Bane are bigger than ours now.
Yeah. And could you maybe
keep this quiet,
because the bigger this thing gets,
the more danger she's...
I know. Look, I'll keep it as quiet
as I can, for as long as I can.
Thanks.
Hi there. Gotta sign.
It's for Piper, Piper Halliwell?
Can I see that?
Leonardo's Boutique.
Bodega Bay, California.
Yeah, Dan and I were there,
ordered some earrings. Thank you.
The deliveryman said he "gotta sign."
Leonardo's Boutique in Bodega Bay.
Leo, short for Leonardo.
Bodega Bay, where Dan is from.
Don't act blonde.
You cast that spell, didn't you?
- Yes, I did.
- When I specifically asked you not to.
- And at a time like this.
- I was just trying to help, Piper.
- And it was before Prue disappeared.
- You, this, Book of Shadows, go.
- What? What did you see?
- Prue, bound and gagged.
And with Bane.
- Don't scream.
- Why not?
Because if you do,
we won't be able to talk.
Besides, it won't help. The nearest
neighbour is about six miles away.
Why not take off the blindfold?
What are you afraid of?
Are you kidding? I've seen you use
your powers before. On me.
All right, if you try anything,
the blindfold goes back on.
What do you want?
Your help. To save my life.
Well, most people ask for it,
they don't kidnap for it.
I'm not most people.
Neither are you.
What makes you think
that I'll help you?
I don't.
But without you and your sisters,
I don't stand a chance
against this particular demon.
Yeah, well, from where I'm sitting
that's a good thing.
He tried to have me killed today, Prue.
I got lucky and barely escaped.
And he's gonna keep trying.
Why would he bother?
You're a mortal.
A mortal that knows about demons.
He doesn't like that.
Litvack, that's what they call him.
Where are we?
This yours?
It was going to be,
before you came along,
cut me off from my dreams.
Because you tried to kill me.
Well, that was before
I got to know you.
You don't strike me as a dreamer.
Well, there's a lot about me
you don't know.
A few things that you need
to learn about me too.
Like how I will never
put my sisters in danger.
So you can forget about
any of us helping you.
Sooner or later,
you're gonna have to trust me, Prue.
About freaking time.
What took you so long?
- We had a little problem.
- Problem? What problem?
Where's your partner?
Do not tell me
that you screwed this up.
that Bane Jessup is still alive.
How is that even possible?
He's a lousy mortal.
How hard can it be?
He's smart. He wasn't surprised
we were coming for him.
Of course not, you idiot.
That's why we wanted him offed.
Because he knows about us.
Oh, jeez, think, think, think.
What are we gonna tell Litvack?
You're going to tell me how you plan
to rectify this little problem,
is how I believe you phrased it.
On your knees.
I saw what you saw.
How he used you to kill the other,
how he got away.
- How you lost the weapon.
- Wait, wait, wait. What?
You lost the weapon?
The guards were coming,
I had to run.
To find a mortal,
all you need to do is follow his dreams.
That's where they always escape to.
Do you understand me?
He'll find Jessup. I swear.
No.
You will.
And then you'll find the weapon.
No loose ends.
We couldn't find it
in the Book of Shadows anywhere.
- It's a weapon.
- Are you kidding me? It's a weapon?
One that can only be activated
by a demon.
From what I remember, it's handed out
by a specific upper-level demon
to those who work for him.
- What do you mean upper-level?
- There's a hierarchy of demons.
They try to work their way up
by destroying good, promoting evil.
Whoever issued this particular weapon
is very important.
- You mean dangerous. Any idea who?
- No.
All right, well, this weapon may be
the only way to find Prue.
I'm back to the Book.
I'll be right there.
Thanks for coming over
so quickly, Leo,
and your offer
to take care of the club.
Is there anything else you need?
I don't know. I can't do anything
but think about Prue right now.
Remember, you know
the most important thing.
Phoebe's premonition proves
that Prue is still alive.
I know. But for how long?
I mean, what if we can't get to her?
What if she's hurt?
I wish I could do more...
...because I can't help, but remember
all the times that I could.
I don't think you understand.
As long as you're here with me,
your life is on the line too, you know.
- I can take care of myself.
- Not against Litvack.
You have a fighting chance
with your sisters,
but as long as you're alone,
you're as powerless as I am.
Even if you can't trust me,
you can trust that.
I told you I'm not getting
my sisters involved.
All right, fine. Your sisters
came looking for you once before,
they'll come looking again.
Not if I can help it.
A weapon issued
by level-two demons?
But it doesn't say
which level-two demon.
- I love it when it does that.
- "Mariners"?
Well, they're not demons,
they're sea fairies.
That's because it has nothing to do
with Prue, Phoebe, it's a sign.
Dan was a baseball player
for the Seattle Mariners.
No one feels worse
than I do right now.
Prue, you're okay, thank God.
Yeah, but Bane Jessup,
he kidnapped me.
We know. Where are you?
- You can't find me.
- What do you mean?
It's a trap, just stay away,
don't look for me.
- What? Wait. Wait, Prue.
- Wait. Hello?
Hey, are you all right?
I thought you passed out
or something.
Feeling guilty?
That's a good sign.
Means that you have a conscience.
What are you doing?
- I'm letting you go.
- Just like that?
I never wanted to hurt you, Prue.
I only wanted your help.
But you can't help me
if you don't trust me.
And you're in danger
as long as you're here.
There's a market
a mile down the road.
You'll never see me again,
I promise.
Told you I never wanted to hurt you.
You just saved my life.
You think you can trust me now?
- Tell me you're kidding.
- It's all over the news.
We called as soon as we saw
the first broadcast. Look.
I'm reporting live
from the county jail,
where an inmate escaped
earlier this morning.
A massive manhunt has been
launched to find the escapee,
a man by the name of Bane Jessup
who was awaiting trial
for racketeering,
money laundering
and embezzlement.
So much for keeping things quiet.
This is a nightmare.
- Welcome to our world.
- You want some aspirin?
What I want is Prue safe,
Bane put in jail,
and nobody hurt by any...
- Do you know what that is yet?
- We're still looking.
We do know
that Bane definitely kidnapped Prue.
- Has he made contact with you?
- No, but she has.
It's a long story, but she's okay.
She said not to come looking for her.
She said it was a trap.
Did she say what kind?
Maybe this will help.
It's the DA's file on Bane.
It's all the information
they pulled together for his trials.
It's everything I could copy
before I got your phone call.
Hello?
Really?
It's someone calling
for a Leonora Watkins.
Leonora Watkins. Isn't that weird?
You have the wrong number.
Anyway, we believe
that Bane is holed up somewhere.
Maybe there's something in there
that can tell you where.
So, what the hell is he doing?
Oh, God,
I hope he's not hurting her.
Prue.
If I'm gonna clean the wound,
then I have to stop the bleeding,
I'm sorry.
Do you even know
what you're doing?
No, not really. But right now
I'm the only choice that you've got.
- So just try and hold still.
- That's easy for you to say.
You don't have a set of fingernails
clawing into your body.
Yeah, well, I'm almost done,
put this in your mouth or something.
Forget about me, go home
before Litvack's man comes back.
I told you, he's gone.
Probably ran right back to Litvack.
So now he knows about you too.
All the more reason to leave.
Yeah, well, as much
as I would like to, I can't.
Not until I know that you're okay.
Besides, it's probably better
just to stay put.
I mean, now that we've been sighted,
they'll expect for us to take off.
Speaking of things
that need to be taken off,
your pants.
- Excuse me?
- Well, I need to get to the wound.
Forget it.
Okay, you know what?
It's just gonna get infected.
So you can either
take your pants off on your own,
or I can always do it by force.
I'm getting nowhere and everywhere.
How about you, any luck?
I'll give Bane this, he works hard.
Tax evasion, racketeering.
Pick a crime, any crime.
I feel like we're looking right at
the answer, we're just not seeing it.
Got good taste too.
There's a whole
money-laundering indictment here
based on a real-estate development.
Exclusive custom homes.
They're really gorgeous.
Check out the brochure.
Mariner's Bluff.
I'm sure the sea fairies
will be very happy here.
What did you say?
Phoebe, what exactly
did your spell say?
"I beseech all powers above
Send a sign to free my sister's heart
One that will lead her to her love"
Why?
Because the Book of Shadows
specifically opened
to the Mariner section.
What if the signs we're getting
have nothing to do with Dan and Leo
and everything to do with Prue?
Where is Mariner's Bluff?
Bodega Bay.
Leonardo's Boutique of Bodega Bay.
- Piper, I think you're right.
- Okay, so, what were the clues?
Mariners, Bodega Bay,
Leonora Watkins.
Watkins Road exit.
So we've almost found her.
All we need is an address.
What's this?
- Let's see.
- Are the lots numbered?
In an exhibition game last night,
the Mariners lost to the Angels,
8 to 7.
In other news, Sammy Sosa...
Okay, now we're back to Dan and Leo.
Mariners, Angels.
No, Phoebe, "8 to 7."
Lot 827?
Yes, there's an 827
at the top of the hill.
I'll drive, you navigate.
Prue, why are you still here?
Because...
...I believe you.
Well, thank you. It's been a long time
since someone believed in me.
Maybe that's because
you stopped believing in yourself.
You know,
I haven't always been like this.
The wrong side of the law,
always looking over my shoulder.
I had dreams once.
Big dreams.
It's not too late to change, you know.
Well, it's too late for me.
But not for you.
So you should definitely go.
So you can still have your dreams.
- Easier said than done.
- What do you mean?
I don't know.
I've just been thinking lately that
maybe dreams are just that, dreams.
I don't believe that.
I'm sorry.
I'm not.
Interesting.
I know. I screwed up.
Oblivion, right?
This is different.
You weren't just up against a mortal.
From what I saw,
you were also up against a witch.
No excuse.
Hundreds of witches out there,
I should be able
to handle one by myself.
This was different.
Powerful. Very powerful.
Take me to
this mortal's dream house.
Why? They gotta be
long gone by now.
But their essence remains.
I'll need to tap into it
if I expect to reach their minds.
Reach their minds? To what end?
Theirs.
The Source likes it
when I feed him witches.
That's how I got to where I am.
Prue?
The view is amazing.
It's not as good as mine.
I thought maybe you left.
No, I just couldn't really find
all of my clothes.
Look, I'll help you with Litvack.
You just have to promise me that you'll
turn yourself back in when it's all over.
Bane.
You know, I was thinking maybe this,
us, doesn't have to end.
That maybe we can go somewhere
where we could be together,
get away from all this.
What do you say?
I would say that you're beginning
to strike me as a dreamer.
Bane.
- Oh, my God.
- What are you guys doing here?
We're rescuing you
from the tall, dark and naked man.
- I told you to stay away.
- Yeah, now I know why. He is yummy.
I don't believe this.
We've been frantic,
worried sick about you,
thinking you've been kidnapped...
Yeah, I was.
Panties.
Thanks. Look, you guys
have really got this all...
...wrong.
- Yeah, we know, it's a trap.
A tall, dark and naked trap.
All right, how did you two
find me anyway?
We'll explain that later.
We really need to be going now
because there's a demon behind this.
Yeah, Litvack.
Wait, how did you know?
We have the weapon he used
to break Bane out of jail.
No, no, no. He tried to kill Bane in jail,
not break him out.
Or so Bane says.
I believe him, because one of the
guys came here and tried to kill me.
- All the more reason we should go.
- Fine, then just unfreeze him.
You want us to bring him along?
Well, yeah. I mean,
I told him that I would help him.
I can't leave him here when everything
I need to do is clearly at the manor.
- Oh, hello.
- Hello.
Nice to see you again.
Why don't you put some clothes on?
Listen, you guys have any peroxide
and stuff? I think I should clean this up.
Yeah, upstairs bathroom,
medicine cabinet.
All right, thanks.
First, I'd like to tell you
how relieved I am you're okay.
Me too.
And second, I'd like to tell you that
you have completely lost your mind.
Completely lost your mind.
Okay. We have a demon to vanquish.
You really wanna help him?
Piper, past aside,
I know an innocent when I see one.
And I trust him.
- Prue...
- Phoebe, I'm going to help him.
Think about this,
how well do you really know him?
Regardless,
Litvack has to be vanquished
whether Bane is on our side or not.
It would be nice to know that
ahead of time. Minimize the surprises.
You really wanna minimize them?
Help me find Litvack
in the Book of Shadows.
Hello, Bane. It's telepathic connection.
I'm only in your mind.
How did you find me?
Your essence.
This dream house of yours
reeks of it.
It's a beautiful place. Too bad
you won't live long enough to enjoy it.
- You don't scare me.
- Sure I do. I scare everybody.
For good reason.
By the way,
your essence isn't the only one
I sense here.
You bedded a witch.
And not just any witch,
one of the Charmed Ones.
My offer is simple.
Your life in exchange for theirs.
Screw you, Litvack.
You can't hide from me.
I can keep sending demons
after you for eternity,
till one of them finally gets you.
You know me, Bane,
better than you wish you did.
I'm evil, just like you are.
And you can't change that
no matter what you do,
or who you sleep with.
It's who you are.
Bring me the witches,
and then bring me back
my weapon,
and I'll give you all your dreams.
Bane, are you in there?
Yeah. Yeah. I'll be right out.
Hi.
I thought that you had
skipped out on me or something.
No, I was just washing up.
So is he gonna do it or not?
I found Litvack in the Book,
but there's nothing
about how to vanquish him.
Maybe that means there isn't a way.
Where there's a demon,
there's a way.
Our jewellery better still be
where it's supposed to be.
- We need to focus on Litvack.
- Do we?
I mean, aside from the fact there's
nothing in the Book that can help us,
maybe we should
just let bad enough alone.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm talking about our lives.
As in, saving them.
This demon has powers
we don't know about.
Why go up against him unprepared?
What's the rush?
He doesn't know about us
or anything.
Sure he does.
I mean, the demon he sent after us
saw Prue's power, right?
You know he told Litvack.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean
that he knows about all three of us.
Look, all I'm saying
is he knows enough.
You don't go after him,
he comes after you.
- How can you be sure?
- Because I know him, that's why.
Better than I wish I did.
Okay, still doesn't help us
vanquish him.
I just wish we knew
what his other powers were.
- You don't know what they are?
- No idea.
You still have that weapon, right?
- Why?
- Might be your only hope.
I thought only another demon
could activate it.
I got one to activate it before,
maybe I could do it again.
Yeah, he's right. That's how
he took out the demon guard.
So he says.
- Do you think I'm lying?
- What do you think?
I think I don't like
your implications, lady.
I'm in this mess because Litvack
tried to off me, remember?
You don't trust me, fine.
I don't care.
But trust this, I've had it
with all this supernatural crap,
and I'll do anything I have to
to get out from underneath it.
- That's what worries me.
- Okay, you know what? I trust him.
And, please, I'm just asking
you guys to trust me.
If we're going to get Litvack, then
we're gonna have to work together.
With Bane.
Otherwise, we're all gonna be dead.
Okay, Phoebe,
let's go get that weapon. Come on.
- I don't really know what to say.
- You don't have to say anything.
I'll be right back.
We're on our way.
He lives in a cemetery? How cliché.
Well, at least it's not
a warehouse again.
Do we really think this is a good idea?
We don't really have a plan.
Yeah, sure we do. Bane goes in,
we follow, you freeze Litvack,
we put the weapon in his hand,
turn it on him.
- I mean, it's pretty simple.
- Still.
Maybe you should
give me that weapon.
Oh, I don't think so.
Listen, the guy wants me dead,
remember?
The only way for me to stay alive
long enough for our plan to work
is to show him good faith.
Double-crossing us shows some
pretty good faith too, don't you think?
Pheebs, we've been through this.
Yeah, well,
it doesn't change my mind, Prue.
All right, give it to him.
We're either doing this or not.
Thank you.
You guys wait at the base of the steps
for my signal.
Trust me.
I hope we're not making
a huge mistake.
Hello, Litvack.
Well, well.
I was wondering when
you were gonna show.
Before you kill me...
It's all right.
I wanted to give you something,
hoping you would spare me.
I'm afraid it's gonna take
much more than this.
Now.
- That was easy.
- A little too easy.
Let's just get this over with.
He didn't freeze. He...
He didn't freeze.
I'm immune
to the parlour tricks of witches.
What's the matter?
Bane didn't tell you about that power?
He said he didn't know.
He knew.
He just didn't tell you.
He showed his true colours.
His true evil colours.
Prue, I just want you to know,
I am really pissed at you.
No, no, wait. Something isn't right.
This is gonna please The Source.
Piper, unfreeze Bane.
- Hurry.
- What?
Tell The Source that we said hi.
Traitor.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
What just happened here?
Bane just saved our lives
is what happened.
Are you saying this was
all part of the plan,
to make it look like
you were double-crossing us?
I had to. If I would've told you
about his power,
you would have come up
with a different plan of attack.
And Litvack would have known it.
He's telepathic, remember.
So you had to believe
I double-crossed you,
so he'd believe it too.
How did you know
Prue would figure it out in time?
We trust each other.
It's strange, isn't it,
being back where we started?
What is stranger to me
is that I'm still here.
I know.
It was really good of you
to call Morris.
I have to go back,
it's the right thing to do.
Much as I'd prefer not to.
Listen, I don't know
how much time we have so...
...I really want to apologize.
- Don't.
I'm not sorry at all.
This is really the awkward part,
you know?
- Tell me about it.
- Well, next time I'll call first, huh?
Thank you for saving my life.
Thank you for changing mine.
What can I get for you?
So who do you think is The Source
that Litvack was talking about?
I don't wanna know.
And, boy, did we read Bane wrong.
Not surprising.
We read all the signs wrong.
- Hey.
How'd it go?
Well, the cops came
and took him away a little while ago,
so everything's back as it should be.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. He thanked me
for changing his life.
You must have been a really good...
- Influence on him.
- Yes, well, the influence was mutual.
So how did you guys find me anyway?
I cast a little spell
to help Piper find her love.
It was supposed to help her decide
between Dan and Leo.
But it led us to you.
Naked, I might add.
I want you to know
I tried to stop her.
Yeah, and you probably would've too,
if you weren't busy getting kidnapped.
Yeah. So, what was the outcome?
Dan or Leo?
I never needed a sign
to tell me where my heart lies.