Previously...
Principal Hobson just called
and Juanita got accepted to Oakridge.
- There was acceptance...
- I like the blunt Ana
- more than the cute Ana.
- So you think I'm cute?
- A plea...
- Let me help you, or I am...
Or you won't get into heaven?
- A breakdown...
- Did you stab yourself?
I have to get to Mike!
And a confrontation.
I don't know how you feel,
because you never talk about it!
We lost a kid.
How can saying this out loud be helpful?
If you want to throw
a successful dinner party,
there are certain rules
that must be followed.
If the good silver is used,
it must be polished.
If music is played,
the volume should be low.
If the guests bring wine,
it must be served.
And if the evening is
to be truly successful...
There must be a toast.
To Lee. This dinner
has been a total triumph.
And it's not over yet.
I made a fruit tart for dessert.
And in case any of you are diabetic,
let me just say...
it was nice knowing you.
No. Seriously,
this is how we lost his cousin.
Bob, where's the whipped cream?
I totally forgot. I was on my phone
and I drove right past the store.
Of course,
'cause it's something that I needed.
I was working all day.
If it was that important,
why didn't you just get it?
I work, too.
Selling houses is work.
House.
He's sold one house in six months.
Attacking.
What's that?
My feelings journal.
Lee and I are seeing this counselor.
She has us write down our negative
feelings to discuss in our sessions.
Seems like you got
a lot of feelings there.
That's volume three,
with an entire chapter about me
forgetting to put down the toilet seat.
I thought that would be the one
advantage with two guys living together.
You'd think.
The good news is
that you're getting help.
We should think about that.
- What?
- You know, to help us with our stuff.
Can we talk about our stuff later?
We could, but you won't.
She never wants to talk.
You know how I feel about therapy.
It's for weak, indulgent...
Straight people.
You guys totally make it work.
I used to feel the same way.
But this lady, she's really great.
Volume three?
Can't we give it a try?
I don't need someone
telling me how I feel.
So could we just drop it?
And the number one rule
for a successful dinner party?
After dessert, let's karaoke!
Keep discussion of your marriage
to an absolute minimum.
CREDITS
Synch: Wisteria Team
Transcript: Addic7ed
Dr. Brent Avedon was
the head of psychology
at the Fairview health center.
He spent his days treating
antisocial adolescents,
delusional dowagers...
And bipolar businessmen.
But lately,
his most interesting patient
was a housewife
who'd had a nervous breakdown.
I was just so lonely.
And then one day,
along came this wonderful man...
A man who made me laugh,
who gave me hope again...
And who turned out
to be in love with someone else.
So I went back to being lonely.
Only it was worse now because...
He wasn't really gone.
He was across the street,
holding her hand,
laughing with her.
So one day...
I pretended,
just for a second...
that it
wasn't her hand he was holding.
It was mine.
And that's
how the fantasies started?
When I was hurting,
I would let myself imagine
that he was there with me.
But then those moments started to...
mean more to me than what was real.
So...
I just let myself have them.
I let them take over.
What about now? Do you
feel that the medication is helping you?
I certainly
have a firmer grasp on reality now.
I can see things,
for the first time in a long while,
very clearly.
That's great.
Not really.
Because now
I can see what I've done to my life.
And...
How I've ruined it.
Orson, it's time for
me to give you your bath.
Not now.
You haven't bathed in over a week.
I don't want
to do this any more than you do,
- but frankly, you're getting ripe.
- I said I don't want a bath.
It's not about what you want anymore.
It's a matter of preserving the drapes.
To have another
human being bathe me is humiliating.
Here.
- What's this?
- A list of things I need at the store.
I just went to the store
for you an hour ago. Can't it wait?
I need these items immediately.
It's urgent.
How are cornnuts urgent?
I'm sorry, Bree.
I just thought
that since you played a major part
in putting me in this chair,
you'd want to play a small part
in making my new life tolerable.
Give me the list.
Better yet, leave
it on the table and then back away.
Hey, teach.
I just dropped off
Juanita for her first day.
She's a little nervous.
She's gonna love it here.
The teachers are great.
- What animal is she?
- Excuse me?
They test the kids and they place
them in groups according to their level.
In math, there's leopards,
chipmunks, giraffes.
It should be in her folder.
She's a leopard.
What's M.J.?
He's a giraffe.
So...
Which is the advanced group?
No one knows.
They won't even tell me.
Principal Hobson feels
that if the parents find out,
they'll freak and
get all competitive.
That's crazy.
- Who cares?
- Exactly.
Leopards are the morons,
aren't they?
- I didn't say that.
- Yeah, you did.
When I asked about M.J.,
you were like, "He's a giraffe!"
And I said Juanita was a leopard,
and you were like, "Oh."
You're just jumping to conclusions.
You know something.
Spill it!
I don't know for sure,
But I teach these kids,
and it's pretty obvious.
We were making paper globes
This...
is Rachel Miller.
Damn, that's good.
She's a giraffe.
And this is Wendy Benson.
Chipmunk.
And this one was
made by Adam Hunter...
A leopard.
It looks like an
actual leopard made it.
There's nothing wrong with being
a leopard. They're very important.
They move the cafeteria tables,
excellent door holders.
This isn't fair.
We have a saying around here.
"It's the pace, not the race."
I know my daughter.
She is all giraffe.
I'm gonna go talk to the principal.
You don't push. You...
Sorry. My daughter wasn't
here to hold it for me.
Dinner's ready. Go wash up.
What is that?
It's nothing.
It's personal.
- Personal?
- Yes.
And I think it's important that
we respect each other's boundaries.
This morning, you walked in and sat
on the toilet while I shaved my legs.
We have no boundaries.
- Attacking.
- What?
You sound just like Bob and...
- Is that a feelings journal?
- If you must know, yes, it is.
I started seeing their therapist.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Because I wanted to talk to someone,
and I didn't need your ridicule.
Are you talking about the baby?
It started out about that.
But now we're on to,
other things.
Other things? You mean like me?
I might've mentioned
you once or twice.
Once or twice?
I bet if we downed a shot every
time we read the name "Lynette,"
we'd be hammered by page two.
- Let me see that.
- No way.
But if your're really
interested in what's in here,
you can always join me in therapy.
Like hell.
Fine.
Then I guess you'll just
have to wait for the movie.
Here we go.
Thanks again for having me.
This all looks delicious.
It's your first night over. I wanted to
make you a traditional Italian meal...
Rigatoni with sausage,
chicken parmesan.
Just salad would be great.
Screw the salad.
That came out of a bag.
This rigatoni came from my heart.
To be honest, I don't eat carbs.
But you'll make an exception 'cause I've
been sweatin' over the stove all day.
Let it go.
She's watching her weight.
Her weight?
If I put the AC on high,
it'll blow her across the room.
I just have to be careful.
As soon as a graduate,
I'm going to NY to be a model.
No college?
Are you kidding?
And miss my prime modeling years?
I think it's great.
It takes guts to follow a dream.
It's great,
but it'd be nice to have something other
than the porn to fall back on.
I'm not saying that's gonna happen.
But a lot of models do end up that way.
I know it's risky,
but I'm really passionate about this.
And the best way
to be successful in life
is to do what you're
passionate about.
That's why I keep telling
Danny to pursue his poetry.
Poetry?
- It's amazing, right?
- I wouldn't know.
I'm too busy cooking
food nobody's gonna eat.
Why didn't you ever
show me your poetry?
- It's no big deal.
- Danny, it's great.
I keep telling him he should come to New
York with me to focus on his writing.
A model and a poet.
So while you're doin' porn,
he can make the dialogue rhyme.
This is why I don't tell her stuff.
I'm sorry.
I was just trying to make a joke.
Let's get back to dinner.
No. I'm good.
Carbs.
I'll be out running errands today,
so you'll have to let the physical
therapist in when she arrives.
What's wrong?
There's no strawberries.
You know I like strawberries
with my waffles.
I am sorry.
They're right here. There you go.
Strawberries.
Enjoy.
I need whipped cream.
Unless you think the strawberries
are gonna magically
stick to the waffles by themselves.
Not so fast.
Say "Please."
I will not.
Give me my breakfast.
I am happy to do whatever you ask,
but I will not treated like a slave.
Now say "Please."
Now that I look at your waffle,
I understand
why you're so eager to have it.
You know the magic word.
It has six letters.
I know one that has three.
If you don't give me that,
I'm gonna shove that fork up it.
You can have it when
you're ready to be polite.
Mr. Hobson,
my daughter is incredibly bright.
I just need to know if
she's in the advanced classes.
You know that we have
a policy not to disclose that.
You don't have to say anything.
Blink when I mention the smart group.
- Leopard.
- Mrs. Solis...
Wait, was that a blink or a twitch?
I can't tell. You seem very nervous.
See, this is exactly
why we don't tell the parents.
They start behaving irrationally.
Stop trying to read things
on my desk upside-down.
What's the big deal? I just need to know
if my daughter's gonna succeed in life.
She's 7.
I suggest that you stop prying
and just be proud of her
no matter what group she's in.
I am proud of her, and I don't pry.
By the way,
enjoy your colonoscopy on the 16th.
Mom. What are you doing here?
I was having a nice get-to-know-you chat
with the principal.
Who are your friends?
This is Wendy and Rachel.
We're in math together.
Wait a minute.
I think I saw your art projects.
Wendy, you're a chipmunk, right?
And, Rachel, you're a giraffe?
You know what I would love to do?
Is take a picture with Juanita
and her friends.
And you know what
would be really cute?
Is if you hold up
your math homework.
Got it.
But I wasn't smiling.
It's a tough world out there.
Not much to smile about.
Have a great day!
Your mom's weird.
You have no idea.
I'm letting myself in.
Time for your therapy.
Help me!
Help.
Dear lord!
What happened?
Joyce.
I was trying to get those waffles,
And I fell out of my chair.
What are they doing up there?
Starving him?
That's ridiculous.
Really? So you don't torment
him by putting food out of his reach?
You kinda had to be there for that.
Can someone please
get me a piece of bread?
For god sakes! Stop that!
Please hit me in the legs this time.
There's no feeling there.
Mrs. Hodge, may I speak
to you privately for a moment?
You have to believe me.
I would never hit my husband.
I sensed him being
a little dramatic.
But withholding food?
The whole thing started because
he refused to say please...
Which I know sounds rather petty,
but you have to understand.
He has been impossible lately.
The man is facing
life in a wheelchair.
He's mad at the world, unfortunately,
he's taking it out on you.
I know this is not easy.
But until he comes to accept this,
you're gonna have to figure
out how to be more patient.
And if you can't,
it's my obligation to report it.
And give the man a bath.
Physical therapy
shouldn't require gloves.
You weren't home when they tried
to deliver this, so I signed for it.
We saw an ad for...
Honest to god, don't need to know.
Good.
Looks like somebody
got a new girlfriend.
Not for long.
I do not approve.
You don't approve, and she's got a body
that would make the pope walk
through a sliding glass door.
Gosh, who's gonna win?
He is my kid.
If I don't think she is good for him,
I will do whatever I have to do.
Which will drive him
towards her and away from you.
I know what it's like when
a mom hates the hottie her son loves.
Bob's mom hated me.
- I always thought that Bob was--
- The point is,
she overplayed her hand
and made Bob choose between us.
The long story short,
I'm cuddling up with Bob every night.
And where's mama? Nursing home.
How'd she get there? Don't know.
Can't remember.
It's just...
I don't know this girl.
I don't know if I can trust her.
Then you better get to know her.
I'd hate to see you lose your son
cause you're afraid to share him.
Get outta here.
Carlos, did you get
the pictures I sent you?
You're as beautiful as the day we met.
Time hasn't touched you at all.
Not of me, of the math homework.
- What?
- Here.
This assignment looks easy,
doesn't it?
Pretty basic, yeah.
And look at this one
with the multiplication,
little more complicated, right?
I guess.
And this one...
Word problems. Fractions.
- This is the hardest one, isn't it?
- Looks like it. So?
This is the leopard's homework.
That cleared that up.
No. Don't you get it?
Our daughter is a leopard.
She's in the advanced class.
Good for her.
Poor Susan.
Yeah? Why?
Well, she was convinced
that MJ's brilliant,
and it turns out he's
in the slow group.
I'd hate for her to find out.
- Gaby, you are not telling her.
- Why not?
She didn't have any trouble telling
me she thought Juanita was one
- thermos short of a lunch box.
- She said that?
With her tone.
We've had enough drama with
the neighbors lately, so just drop it.
Fine, I'll drop it.
But just so you know,
I like you better when you're reading
the newspaper pretending to listen.
Sure, take whatever you need.
What are you doing here?
I told them I don't
want any visitors.
Who says I'm visiting?
Maybe I'm bonkers, too.
Gonna eat the applesauce?
Remember when my gout flared
up and I couldn't walk?
And you used to come over to see me?
I figured I owe ya.
Debt paid. Goodbye.
I see you got your
charming personality back.
So... when are you gonna
be coming back home?
What makes you think
I would ever come back?
After what I did to those
people? No. They hate me.
Take it from the reigning
odd duck on the Lane,
nobody cares about
all that silly stuff.
You're right. Bree and I
can just laugh, laugh, laugh
about silly me nearly
destroying her business.
And I'll tell Susan that I was just
joshing about trying to wreck
her marriage.
And I'll bet Mike is still chuckling
about me getting him thrown in jail.
Will you listen?
Kathy, I'm serious.
I'm willing to bet there's more
forgiveness there than you imagine.
- In that case, you know what?
- What?
Maybe you are bonkers.
Look who's here.
- Hey, Susan. What's up?
- I was going through some of MJ's stuff
and I found these math
workbooks from last year.
I thought Juanita
would find them helpful.
Well...
Thank you.
No problem. I thought
it might help her catch up.
Catch up?
You know, from when
she was out of school.
She was never out of school,
I was homeschooling her.
And I know you did
the best you could.
But now she has
professional teachers,
and I bet she's gonna
catch up to MJ in no time.
Get her.
By the way, did you hear?
Leopards are the advanced students.
What?
It's true. Chipmunks are average.
And giraffes...
well, those cafeteria tables
aren't gonna move themselves.
How do you know this?
I got a copy of each group's homework.
Trust me. I cracked the code.
So that means
that MJ's not in the...
But you said it yourself...
it's no big deal.
"It's the pace,
not the race," right?
Right.
And please, don't
say anything to anyone.
You know how competitive
some parents can get.
All too well.
I'm finished. Can I have
my milk and cookies now?
Sure, sweetie.
You have some pasta stuck to
the right side of your face.
No, sweetie. Your right.
Never mind.
Mike, can you help
me take out the trash?
Sure.
Never mind that.
Okay, so he's a giraffe.
You know, there's nothing
wrong with being average.
Chipmunks are average.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Leopards, chipmunks, giraffes.
I love him so much, Mike.
What if he's...
Slow?
He's not slow.
He's a smart, inquisitive,
bright little boy.
He's got his hand
stuck in the glass.
Come on, buddy.
Come on.
Just... just hold the glass.
Pull with the other hand.
You can do it.
Come on, MJ.
See? You were worried about nothing.
You're right.
He's heading toward
the toaster with a fork!
- I'm heading out.
- Okay. Mwah. Wanna grab lunch today?
Maybe tomorrow. I have a thing.
If you mean therapy,
why not just say "therapy"?
I just didn't want to get
into a fight. That's all.
Won't you need this?
Right. Thanks.
Don't you wanna know if I read it?
I'd know if you read it.
Excuse me. Are you
waiting for dr. Graham?
- Don't tell me she double-booked again.
- Oh, no. I don't have an appointment.
But I really need to talk to her,
so can I have yours?
I don't know. I really
need to talk to her, too.
Seriously? Because I was
looking at you thinking,
what is he doing here?
That guy's really got it together.
Thanks. But I'm been having
a pretty hard time lately.
- I'll give you 200 bucks.
- Cash?
20's okay?
What were you going
to talk to her about?
I'm starting to feel
the urge to gamble again.
Thanks.
Mr. Jameson?
He had to go, but he said I
could have his appointment.
I'm sorry, but it
doesn't work like that.
If you're interested
in becoming a patient...
I'm not. I am Mrs. Tom Scavo.
Yep, that's what I thought.
Well, I don't blame you
for reacting like that.
I can only imagine the stories
Tom's been reading to you
from his big book of wah!
So... here I am,
Tom Scavo's bitch of
a wife, in the flesh.
Why do you put it like that?
I don't know specifically
what word he uses.
I'm just...
picking the one
that seems the most likely.
So you think your husband
describes you as a bitch?
- Doesn't he?
- What Tom says in this room is private.
Which means yes?
Well, obviously, it does to you.
I'm just wondering
why that might be.
Oh, I see what you're trying to do,
but I did not come here for therapy.
I came here to defend myself.
There's two sides to every story.
So you're not a bitch?
Not all the time, no.
But sometimes?
I just...
need...
want...
to feel like I'm in control,
and when I don't, that makes me mad.
Maybe I'm mad a lot
because I don't know if you've noticed,
but you can't control
what happens in life.
Like your baby dying?
I'm going to sit down, but only...
Because I'm tired.
Unless you need to go or something.
No. I don't need to go anywhere.
How was your day?
- Is that a...
- Yep.
Looks like we'll be
going to therapy together.
Really?
That is great news.
Thank you.
W... where's dinner?
I mean, you were home all day.
- What are you writing?
- You'll find out, Tuesday at 12:30.
Colleen! Can I talk to you?
Uh, I've got parent-teacher conferences,
but not for a few minutes. What's up?
It's about M.J. How is he
doing in your math class?
Oh, he's such a joy.
You just did the "he's such
a joy" with the head tilt.
I give that one to parents all the time
when I think their kid is driftwood.
No, seriously, M.J.'s doing great.
Oh, really? Well, if
he's doing so great...
Why is he a giraffe?
- What?
- He should be a leopard.
- They're the advanced students.
- You don't know that.
I do now.
Gaby Solis broke the code.
What?
That's right. Giraffes
are the slow learners,
- and you know it.
- Giraffes are the slow learners?
No, no, no, Mrs.
Chapman. No one said that.
Why don't you wait
for me in my classroom?
Gabrielle Solis figured out the code
leopards, chipmunks, giraffes.
Jenny, we got the code!
Leopards are the smart ones!
- Now look at what you've done.
- M.J. is here. He's a leopard.
Get used to it.
Where have you been?
I needed to close the door.
Oh, uh, well, I thought a
little fresh air would be nice.
Hmm, it isn't.
Well, as the person
who has to share a house
with the person who won't take
a bath, I need the fresh air.
I don't care. Close it.
I know that you are angry
at the world right now.
What happened to
you is unimaginable,
and I am gonna do whatever I
can to help you through this.
And all I ask in return is that you
treat me with a little bit of courtesy,
and that includes
using the word "please."
Why the sudden interest
in etiquette, Bree?
I mean, I don't recall you saying
"please" before you cheated on me.
This conversation is
over. The door stays open.
- I want it closed.
- No. You stink.
- And you're a whore!
- Here's the difference...
I can get clean.
Yes, you can.
What are you doing?
What is going on?
I'm not even dressed.
What is that? What... what
is that? What's going on?
Bree, stop.
You wouldn't.
Okay, Bree, stop it.
Stop. Bree.
If only there was a word you
could use to get me to stop,
- like "please".
- I'm calling Joyce.
- Say "please"!
- Go to hell!
Why can't you just say
it? It's easy. Please.
Please, please! Please stop it!
Please roll me over. Please
help me off the toilet.
Please, please, please!
That's the life I'm facing now,
having to ask people
for help for everything.
Do you know how hard that is?!
Every morning I wake up at 5:00. You
get upt 6:30. For an hour and a half,
I lie, staring
at the bedroom door,
fantasizing about how
lovely it would be...
how excruciatingly
to get up and make myself
a cup of tea one last time.
No "please."
Just hot water and tea.
I'm so sorry.
Forgive me.
Please.
- What are you in for?
- Eating paste.
- What animal group are you?
- Giraffe.
Damn.
Joey Murphy.
I'll be with you two in a moment.
Sorry for getting you in trouble.
It's my own fault.
I got carried away.
Me, too.
It was just so important to
me that Juanita was doing well.
I know.
No, I don't think you do.
My kids are my calling card.
They're what I have
to show for myself.
I don't have a career,
Susan. My kids are my job.
And if they succeed or not...
it's because of how I raise them.
Well, at least you get
to raise them.
Ever since I took this job,
I feel like I'm never with M.J.
I constantly worry. Am
I there enough for him?
Am I letting him down?
You don't have anything
to worry about.
M.J.'s a fantastic kid.
Well, so is Juanita.
Their moms are competitive nuts.
This has been so ridiculous.
Leopards and giraffes and chipmunks
I mean, who created this crazy system?
You know, reading class is just as bad.
There's otters, penguins and seals.
Yeah, Juanita's an otter.
I mean, what does an otter have
to do with learning how to read?
Juanita's an otter?
- Why? What's M.J.?
- Penguin.
This is pretty. What do you think?
I think maybe I'd buy
it for my grandma...
If I hated her.
You're so funny.
So... as much fun as
we're having here,
- why are we doing this?
- We are getting to know each other.
You know me, and you don't like me.
It's not that I don't like you.
It's just, I don't think
you're good for Danny.
Why? Because I wouldn't
eat your pasta?
Rigatoni.
And no.
It's because you are a
good-time girl out to have fun.
I don't blame you. You're young,
beautiful. You're supposed to have fun.
But Danny has been through a lot,
and he needs someone who
is not gonna hurt him.
I know Danny has been
through rough stuff.
When he lashes out
and gets all defensive,
trying to protect himself?
I get it,
because I used to do it, too.
It's the thing that
made me like him.
I know how he feels,
and it's not fun at all.
I don't care if you like me
and I don't care if
you hate how I dress,
but I am not gona hurt Danny.
How can I be sure of that?
You can't.
But it doesn't matter, 'cause...
I'm not going anywhere.
What are you doing back here?
I've been thinking about
what you said last time.
The more I thought about it,
the more it pissed me off.
Why is that?
The people on that street have
been your friends for years.
You really think we
would dump your ass
just 'cause you went off
the deep end for some months?
I appreciate you coming here.
I do.
But after everything I did,
I don't see how anyone
could forgive me.
Well, we're not
saying it'll be easy.
But we'll give it a try.
I told them how much
better you were doing,
but they couldn't
take my word for it,
so they had to see for themselves.
In our darkest moments,
we all need someone who will listen.
Some turn to friendly professionals.
A few rely on those
who are older and wiser.
Others seek out
someone who knows what
they're going through.
But for most of us,
nothing is quite so therapeutic
as a good long talk
with a few old friends.