Previously on Desperate Housewives...
Victor made himself
perfectly clear.
Whenever I've truly
wanted something,
I've always gotten it.
Bree needed to get away.
We're finally taking our honeymoon.
Susan couldn't wait to
pop the question.
Will you marry me?
Lynette received shocking news.
You can see this...
It could be lymphoma.
Why are you so reluctant
to make a commitment to me?
Because I'm not in love with you.
And Edie...
What if we tried to have a baby?
engaged in a dangerous deception.
When Gabrielle Solis agreed to
marry Victor Lang,
she was determined to have
a very traditional wedding.
She was even more determined
to be a very traditional bride.
To that end,
the handkerchief in
her cleavage was borrowed,
the garter on her leg was blue,
and the diamonds on
her ears were old.
But sadly for Gabrielle,
something was missing,
and she was about
to throw a traditional fit.
It is after 3:00! Where the hell is Bree
with my "something new"?!
I know her plane landed on time.
She'll probably be here any second.
God, I should have my head examined
for even agreeing to this.
Who the hell cares about
swiss jewelry anyway?
Gaby, Bree went out of her way
to buy you that bracelet.
And, of course, it's the hottest
day of the year.
All the guests are out
there sweating like pigs.
God, at this rate,
my reception's gonna look like
the finish line of
the Boston marathon.
If you're that freaked out, just get
married without the bracelet.
Are you out of your mind?!
I can't get married without
my "something new."
I have an idea.
I just got a lipstick yesterday.
You could wear that.
I just paid a makeup artist
500 bucks to do my face.
Do you really think
I wanna march down
the aisle looking like
just ate a popsicle?
Okay, it's your big day,
so I'm gonna let that slide.
God, it is 10 after,
and Bree is never late!
Where can she be?
All right, that's it.
After I finish "tszujing" my hair,
tell the preacher it's showtime.
I can't believe my wedding's already
ruined, and it hasn't even started.
Hey, I'm starting to get
worried about Bree.
Maybe we should call.
I'm calling her cell.
It's ringing.
Hello, ladies.
Is that Bree? She better not
have come empty-handed!
I didn't.
As promised, Bree had arrived
with something new.
Holy crap!
And she also...
brought the bracelet.
Transcript:
swsub.com
Synchro:
YST
Season 03 Episode 23
"Getting Married Today"
Three Days Earlier
Family...
there is nothing more important.
They're the ones we want to laugh
with during the good times...
And the ones we need
to console us during the bad.
And even though the time comes
when they have to leave us,
their voices still linger
in our minds.
And sometimes we can't help
but listen.
A tangled web...
That's what you're weaving.
Beat it, mother.
You really think this little scheme
of yours is gonna work?
Of course it will.
Look at him.
He's practically in love
with me already.
That's because he thinks
you're gonna give him a baby.
Wait till he finds out
you're still on the pill.
Shut up, would you?!
I just thank the good lord
your father didn't live to see this.
Well, neither did you.
You died alone in a trailer park
watching game shows.
And why should I listen to you?
'cause I know
what's waiting for you, missy.
This one's gonna leave
you like all the others.
You're going to end up old and alone,
just like I did.
Down here, babe!
I'm making you a fruit smoothie.
Chicken or fish?
What?
I haven't gotten
your reply card back yet.
So chicken or fish?
Right, your wedding.
I can't go.
- Why not?
- I'm a jinx.
I went to your last wedding,
and look how that turned out.
Come on, Gaby. We both know
it'd be weird if I went.
Okay, maybe a little, but
it'll be weirder if you don't.
Excuse me?
Look, everyone knows
you're living with Edie.
If she shows up alone, people will
think I asked her not to bring you,
like it bugs me that
you guys are together.
But it does bug you. You hit
the roof when you found out.
Which is why I have to show
people that I'm okay with it.
Please, just consider it
my wedding gift.
But I'm skipping the ceremony.
What?!
And just go to the reception?
You can't do that.
I don't want to make a scene.
You'll vow, "till death do us part,"
I'll bust out laughing,
people will stare...
Reception starts at 4:00.
I'm thinking a chocolate fountain
would be
a cool centerpiece
to a dessert buffet.
Dessert buffet?
We're having a wedding cake, right?
Isn't that dessert?
Yeah, but you have
to give people a choice.
Don't you think a chocolate
fountain would be elegant?
I don't know... you,
a big white dress, melted chocolate.
Am I the only one
hearing alarm bells?
Fine, we'll skip the chocolate.
How about a champagne fountain?
I know! Maybe we can make the champagne
flow through the ice sculpture.
Don't you think we might be
going a little over-the-top?
These are all fairly standard
wedding features.
Now you name one thing
that you think
is going over-the-top.
How about the dove wrangler?
The doves are not going
to release themselves.
Do we really need 40 of 'em?
Okay, I know that
you think I'being silly,
but all of our friends went
to Bree's wedding,
and now they're going to Gaby's.
Two months from now, do we really
want them thinking our wasn't as nice?
It seems to me our friends wouldn't be
there to make petty comparisons.
They'd be there to celebrate our love.
You would think that, but no.
Come on. This is something that
we have both
looked forward to for so long.
Don't you want it to be perfect?
I guess.
About the doves, though...
What?
You in a wedding gown,
40 birds circling overhead?
Again, not liking those odds.
It's not as bad as it sounds.
It's Hodgkin's lymphoma, and
apparently, if you're going to get
lymphoma, that's the kind you want.
Hey, you wanna hold it
down up there, kids?
I'm trying to talk to your
aunt Lucy! Thank you!
Anyway, I know I said that we would
come and visit you this june,
but I'll be a little woozy and...
bald from the chemo, so...
Thanks for understanding.
One more thing...
Our insurance policy has
a really high deductible,
so we are strapped financially,
and I was wondering
if maybe you and Dave
might be able to...
Really?
No, I am not asking mom.
She doesn't know about any of this,
so don't you tell her, okay?
We'll be fine. I love you. Bye.
I take it that's a "no" on the loan?
Dave lost his job at the plant,
and he is now handing out flyers
at a chicken restaurant, and...
Prepare to wince...
there is a chicken suit involved.
So where are we
gonna find this $10,000?
You leave that to me.
I want you to focus on getting better.
- But, honey...
- I will find it.
Meanwhile, we'll make some
sacrifices around here.
My tennis club membership
is up this month.
I'm not renewing.
Should you even be playing tennis
after your back surgery?
Probably not.
Well, in that spirit,
as soon as I start chemo,
I will be giving up shampoo.
Okay, thanks.
Taxi's here.
Are you sure you're
ready to go back?
We could wait another week.
And miss Gaby's wedding?
No, I'll be fine.
Is this the dress you were
thinking for the ceremony?
- Yes.
- Good.
I'll fold it in tissue
so it doesn't wrinkle.
Darling, I don't deserve you.
Come on.
We agreed...
no more tears.
I'm so sorry to be putting
you through this.
I wouldn't blame you if you ran like
hell and never looked back.
Stop.
I'm going to raise this child and
love it as if it were my own.
Now let's see a smile.
I'm glad you could
join us, Milton.
It's good to get to know
you before the wedding.
Thank you.
You know, I must say,
all these months, I thought Victor
was exaggerating about you.
But he hasn't done you justice.
You, my dear, are
a flawless beauty.
I'm hardly flawless.
I'm sure I have a blemish
hidden away somewhere.
Now that's a search I would relish.
She is way out of
your league, dad.
Honey, he's a multimillionaire.
He runs my league.
By the way, Victor, I ran into
Keith Perkinson last week.
And how is the venerable
state chairman?
Impressed with you.
He liked the way you ran
your moral campaign,
said if you keep your
numbers up, he might
consider supporting you
in the next Governor's race.
Really?
What's so funny?
You gotta be kidding, right?
I mean, we just finished a campaign.
You're not about to put me
through another one.
But I thought you loved campaigning.
God, no.
It's a complete snore.
Pasting a smile on
my face while
you say the same speech
for the 50th time?
But you were a natural.
People loved you.
Well, the feeling wasn't mutual.
You think I enjoyed sipping tea
with these frumpy matrons
who wore loud,
probably end pantsuits?
You know how many times
I just wanted to scream,
"Vote for my husband,
you color-blind cow!"?
I think you've discovered something
very important
about democracy, my dear...
The nation is full of fools,
and everyone gets a vote.
They're not gonna get us again.
I made nice with Fairview.
I'm not about to suck up
to the whole damn state.
What are you doing?
Some guy out in mount pleasant's
got a cracked water heater.
It's 3:00 in the morning.
I started advertising as
a 24-hour plumber.
After midnight, I get triple time.
Okay, that's crazy.
You can't work round the clock.
It's not healthy.
This is the third night
I've worked this week.
I'm fine so far.
You've been sneaking out
while I've been asleep?
What are you, ninja plumber?
It's just for a little while,
earn some extra money.
Is this about the wedding?
We agreed we want it to be nice.
But we didn't agree on this.
Maybe I can scale
things back a bit.
How?
Have a ginger ale fountain?
Make paper doves
and hope it's windy?
Okay, seriously, you don't
have to kill yourself.
I could max out my credit card.
Is that really how you want
to start our life together...
in debt?
No, I wanna start out happy.
But clearly, you're upset,
and I don't know why.
I'm not Ian.
I can't afford to move
you into a mansion
or fly you off to Paris,
but I'll be damned
if I don't give you
the same dream wedding
he would have given you.
I'll see you in the morning.
I'm drawing pictures of trees.
Where the hell do you get off
having cancer and
not telling me about it?!
Mom...
How do you think
you could handle
this without me?
Stella?
There's my Tommy boy!
Come here!
God.
Listen, be a love, will you, honey,
and get my bags from the cab?
Bags? She's staying?
And do not tip the driver.
SOB wouldn't let me smoke.
Jeez, Lynette, I didn't know you
opened a day care center.
Hey, kids, grandma's here.
Okay, what did you
tell them about me?
It's been five years, mom.
They don't rember you.
Well, they'll remember me
this time. I brought presents.
Cool!
For you,
and... you,
and you.
These are baby toys.
We're too old to play with these.
I'm too old to remember what the hell
6-year-olds like to play with.
We're 8.
What do I care?
Just say thank you.
Thank you.
Who's the pretty thing?
Your girlfriend?
She's my sister!
Is that Tom's little b-a-s-t-a...
Okay, kids, time to get your toys
and let's play upstairs.
Come on, Penny.
Come on, sweetie.
Let's go, everybody.
Listen, mom, I really appreciate
you coming to help,
but as you can see,
I'm perfectly fine.
For now.
Now how you gonna handle
that mob when
you're flat on
your ass from chemo?
I'll manage.
You got through breast cancer while
raising the three of us alone.
I was not alone.
I had you.
Lynette was all of 13, and
she still looked after her sisters,
cleaned the house,
cooked the meals,
and I was curled up in
a ball, puking my guts out.
Well, that's what you get when
you mix chemo and vodka gimlets.
You can goad me
all you like, Lynette.
I did not come here to fight.
Now trust me, Cookie,
I have memorized the whole
catalog of subjects
you and I can no longer
discuss, and if that means
that we have to talk about
the weather for three months,
then fine.
But I am staying.
Now...
If you'll excuse me, I have to go
kick a child out of its room.
Okay.
Legs up!
You wanna do it again?
I've been doing a lot of research,
and gravity helps facilitate
the sperm reaching the eggs.
So... heave-ho!
Could we try a little light spooning
before you hang me up
like a side of beef?
Edie, we're trying to have a baby.
Well, could we be
a little less clinical?
Maybe let nature take its course?
Nature is not on our side anymore.
Look, you're no spring chicken, and
those eggs aren't exactly farm-fresh.
Stop referring
to me as poultry.
Sorry. Can we just try this?
It's only for 30 minutes.
30 minutes?!
I am not staying
in this position
for a half an hour
Listen, I know that
this requires some work,
but it will all be worth it when
we have our beautiful, beautiful baby.
Right?
Right.
I guess I could...
make some sacrifices.
That's my girl.
Can I get you anything?
I'd kill for a beer.
- Sorry. No alcohol.
- What?!
For how long?
Just until the baby's born.
And you stop nursing.
Don't worry. I'll get you
a nice herbal tea.
It's just for a few months
while you're in treatment.
We're gonna have to find
someone to watch the kids.
I am not leaving that woman
in charge of our children.
In three months, the twins
will be chain-smoking, and
Penny will be an alcoholic.
We can manage.
We've got Mccluskey.
She costs money...
money that we won't have
if we're paying someone
to replace you at work.
You said not to worry about money,
that you'd find it somewhere.
I did.
What, someone loaned us $10,000?
No, gave us,
and we can't thank her
by kicking her out.
No! Tom, you didn't
ask my mother?!
Didn't have to. She knew that
you hit up Lucy, so she offered.
We're giving it back.
No, we can't afford to.
You don't know half
the stuff she did to us.
She would get drunk
and smack us around.
She would meet some
new guy and then drop us off
at her sister's for a week
because he wasn't into kids.
So she was a crappy mom.
You said yourself that
she has mellowed.
Now she wants to make amends.
If you would just try
to understand...
I think that I've been pretty
understanding lately.
What's that supposed to mean?
I think you know.
Great, so in the middle of
everything I'm dealing with,
you're gonna throw
Rick in my face.
When someone we love hurts us,
if we still love them,
we deal with it and
we move on.
If I can do it, so can you.
So forgiving my mother...
That's my penance?
I think it is.
I thought you said
we weren't supposed to spend
the night before
the wedding together.
I was trying to respect tradition...
But I got horny.
I guess we'll just have to start
the honeymoon early, won't we?
Let me get rid of this stuff.
What are you working
on so late?
Nothing.
Polling data?
Why are you polling?
The election's over.
It's just a little research.
God, you look hot.
Is this about running for Governor?
Because I told you
how I feel about that.
My dad just set up a little...
Exploratory committee.
It's no big deal.
Well, let's explore it now.
Nope, not gonna happen.
Victor, ever since we met,
it's been photo ops and
fund-raisers,
and I'm sick of it.
I'm a politician.
Do you think I want my career
to begin and end
in the suburbs?
Fairview is my home,
and I don't want to leave it.
And you can't make this decision
without me. I'm gonna be your wife.
Exactly, not my career adviser.
- So I don't even get a vote?
- Not if it's a veto.
Look, no!
I already married a man
who put his career before me,
and I swore I wasn't gonna do it again.
I swore I would not let
a stupid woman hold me back.
That did not come out
the way I wanted it to.
I'm sorry.
I'm sor...
I'm really sorry.
I've just been under
a lot of pressure lately.
Here's one less thing
you have to worry about...
our wedding.
You can't cancel the wedding.
It's too late.
As far as I'm concerned,
it's just in the nick of time.
Good morning, Gaby.
God, Milton, the newspaper's
not even here yet.
I'm sorry it's so early.
I just...
came to apologize.
Why? What happened
wasn't your fault.
That's not exactly the case.
Is that coffee I smell?
You only bolted because
Victor wants to be Governor.
He only wants to be
Governor because of me.
You only suggested it.
You can't make him go
after something
he doesn't want.
The hell I can't.
Ever since he was a kid,
Victor's been killing himself
trying to live up to
his big shot father.
He's desperate for my approval.
Why?
I suppose because
he's never gotten it.
Everything he does...
even becoming mayor...
I'm let him know that
it's not quite enough.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm right to push.
That's why he's so successful.
So what are you saying,
I should marry Victor because
you're a with holding father?
No, I just want you to understand
why he does what he does.
Fine. I get it.
But why would I want
a husband who values
his father's opinion
more than mine?
Well, he doesn't really care
much what I think anymore.
After you left last night,
he called me and...
What's the phrase?
"tore me a new one"?
He did?
He said because of me,
he'd lost the best thing
that had ever
happened to him,
and if he coul't win you back,
I could take my money
and buy a new son,
because I was never gonna
be hearing from him again.
He blew off $80 million?
If he cares about me
so damn much,
why am I not hearing
this from him?
I think you're about to.
Is there a back way out of here?
Aren't you gonna be late
for Gaby's wedding?
Weddings are boring.
I like to sneak in at the end,
look teary-eyed and
pretend I was there
the whole time.
I am gonna see you
at the reception.
Hi, Danny.
Carlos, the paperboy's here.
Could you pay him?
Come on in.
Hey, here you go, Danny.
looks like I'm a little short.
Can I catch you later?
Okay. Hold on.
My God.
What's that?
It's birth control pills.
I'm gonna need cash.
Welcome home!
I have missed you, sweetheart!
Here, allow me.
Hello there, Julie.
You guys are back!
Somebody's... blonder.
Yeah, my mom hates it, too.
So where's Danielle?
While we were in switzerland,
she ran across this boarding school,
and she fell in love with it
and just insisted
that we let her spend
a year abroad.
She must be having
a really good time.
She hasn't returned any
of my phone calls.
You know, her school's
up in the mountains, and...
and her cell phone
reception is kind of funky.
She hasn't answered
my e-mails, either.
Well, I am gonna call
her tonight and
have a little talk with her
about common courtesy, and
I'm sure that you will get an e-mail
first thing tomorrow morning.
We should go. I've got to get that
bracelet to Gaby before the wedding.
I'll see you guys there. Bye.
Well, that was uncomfortable.
You have no idea. Everyone's
been asking questions.
This might not be
as easy as we'd hoped.
There. Now you have
something new.
So how do I look?
You are now officially the most
beautiful bride that ever lived.
Until your wedding,
of course.
Nice save.
It means so much to me that
we're all here together right now.
And... break!
Love you.
We are gathered here
today to join together
Victor Lang and Gabrielle Marquez
in matrimony...
an honorable estate not
to be entered in lightly,
but reverently and soberly.
This is a lifetime union...
One based on love,
honor and trust...
You wanna be
my new best friend?
Premium scotch.
Keep it coming.
You are promising not
only to give of yourself,
but also to accept each other,
promising not only
to love for today, but to extend
that love to include...
I thought you weren't
coming until after...
Save it.
Okay, look, I can explain...
Don't bother!
Your lies were more
convincing when I cared.
Victor, do you take Gabrielle...
...in good times and bad...
You've got to understand.
I do wanna have a baby with you,
just not yet. I...
I just... I wanted to give you a chance
to fall in love with me first.
I don't believe you, and
I will never trust you again!
What was I supposed to do?
You backed me into a corner,
and you were gonna
bail on us,
and I was just trying
to save what we had.
Don't leave me.
Please just talk to me.
I am done with you.
Ladies a gentlemen,
I present to you
Mr. and Mrs. Victor Lang.
I'm sorry!
Enjoy the wedding?
Nice. Very classy.
Although what the hell was that
brouhaha between Carlos and Edie?
I don't know and I don't care.
Today, I'm so filled with love,
I can forgive anyone anything.
But if you do see
them again, call security.
So we're in Zurich, and
I sick after breakfast
for the third morning in a row.
And I thought to myself,
dear God, I hope I have not developed
an allergy to chocolate brioche.
Life just wouldn't be worth living.
So I said, that's it.
We're seeing a doctor.
Well, you could've knocked us
over that feather when
he said she was already
two months pregnant.
I think it's so great, and
we could not be happier for you.
- When's your due date?
- Not until the early fall,
but enough about me.
This is your day...
You and Victor... who,
by the way, I have not met yet.
My gosh, that's right.
Okay, you stay here.
I'm gonna go grab him.
It is so good to be back.
I can't believe how much
is happening. I mean,
you and Gaby getting
married, and
and I'm having a baby.
What's going on
with you, Lynette?
Nothing.
Same old, same old.
Really? Is everything
okay, sweetie?
'cause you haven't quite seemed
yourself the last couple weeks.
I'm fine.
Everything's just fine.
I'll tell you this much...
I'm exhausted.
I'll be glad when
this day is over.
Well, it was all worth it.
Marrying Gaby is the smartest
thing you've ever done.
With her bringing
in the latino vote,
the Governor's mansion's
as good as yours.
Well, that's assuming
I can change her mind.
I had to make certain concessions
just to get her down the aisle.
You're the husband now.
The rules have changed.
Be nice, buy her
a few pretty things.
Trust me, you'll be able
to tame that little Spitfire.
I'm not too worried. I've always
been able to manage my assets.
Did you find him?
No, I'm still looking,
but I'll let you know.
Movie's over.
And may I add... amen.
Go out and play.
Go on, go on. Out!
They're just gonna go play guns.
Can I watch another movie?
Lynette said one was the limit,
and she'll be home soon.
No, she won't.
When ever they go out
to a party,
they always come home
at least an hour later
than they say they will.
Aren't you an observant
little monkey?
Tell me, sweetie...
would you know anything
about a man named Rick?
I know Rick.
My daddy and Lynette had
a big fight about him.
Really?
Sounds like there's maybe
a little story there.
If I tell you,
could I watch a really
good grown-up movie?
If it's a really
good grown-up story.
Okay, I got you some
appetizers to tide you over.
We have mini quiches and
beef satay and
something called "crystal coast
shrimp with grits,"
but it's mostly just grits 'cause
I ate all the shrimp on my way over.
Reverend, that was such
a beautiful ceremony.
Really, just heartfelt and
moving... the whole package.
Why, thank you.
It was really impressive.
So what are you doing tonight?
Didn't know you were in here.
I got a little thirsty.
I can see that.
Gaby, I am sorry if
I ruined your wedding.
But if it's any consolation,
I also ruined my life.
What are you talking about?
A couple years ago,
I was totally happy.
I had a home, you, a great career.
And I don't understand
how I let it all go to hell.
And now here I am,
back at square one.
I really blew it.
What am I doing?
I shouldn't be dumping this
on you. It's your wedding day.
Go to Victor.
I'm gonna stay right here...
Well,
I don't know how you did it.
The kids are asleep,
and the cough syrup
hasn't been touched.
Boy, you're just waiting for
an excuse to give me the boot.
Well, if history's any indicator,
I won't have to wait long.
So you don't think
people can change?
I think at a certain point,
people just are
who they are.
Well, I think people can change.
Now take you.
You were the perfect wife and mom...
Then along came Rick.
- How did you...
- Come on, Lynette.
You kids were young when
I was sneaking around on Glen,
but you knew
something was up.
You heard about this from my kids?
Just the girl,
and all she knows is that
daddy got mad
because Rick "liked" you.
Nothing happened
between me and Rick.
Yes, he came on to me,
but unlike you,
I controlled myself.
Well, you had Tom
to come home to.
I had your stepfather.
Hey, Glen may have
bored you, but the years
we had a father in that house
were the happiest in my life.
You didn't care about that,
though, did you?
You just drove him away.
And you couldn't wait
to pay me back.
Do you remember what
you said the next year
when I got sick?
No I don't.
Liar.
You said I earned it.
It was God's punishment.
How are you feeling now, Lynette?
You think you're being punished?
How can you say that?
You were so sanctimonious.
You could not imagine
what sort of woman
could do that kind of thing.
Not so hard
to imagine now, is it?
Stop comparing us.
I never did what you did.
No, you just wanted to.
You're leaving tomorrow.
I don't want your money.
I don't want you imy house.
You are sick, Lynette.
You think you know
what you're in for
'cause you watched
me go through it?
Watching it is nothing.
You are going to feel
worse than you thought
a person could feel,
and I'll be holding your hand
through every damn minute.
You can't stay if
I don't want you here.
You can fight me or
you can fight the cancer.
Trust me,
you won't have
the strength to do both.
Hi, Julie, it's me, Danielle!
Sorry I didn't write you.
My new school is
Switzerland is AWESOME.
Do young people
still say "awesome"?
Not so much.
Try "off the hook."
"Off the hook"?
That doesn't even make sense.
Fine, ty in "groovy".
See if I care.
Hello? Hodge residence.
Hi, Danielle. Listen, I am sending
Julie Mayer an e-mail from you.
Now would you say that
your school was "off the hook"?
No. I would say it was sucky
or crappy or
a freaking nightmare.
Look, if you're gonna start complaining,
I'm going to hang up.
Mom, you have got
to talk to the nuns.
They are so harsh with me, and
they have all these stupid rules.
Well, perhaps if some of
those rules had been in place
when you took up
with Edie's nephew,
you might not be
in this little pickle.
Mom, please, I just
wanna come home.
Look, I am gonna say
this one last time.
You are gonna stay put
until that baby is born.
Now don't forget,
we're driving up this weekend,
and I am bringing your favorite...
Lemon squares, and...
Darling...
Can I draw you a bath?
That would be lovely.
Would you give me
a hand, please?
Here we go.
It's almost time for
the 6 month size.
Don't remind me.
No. No, it's no problem.
I can fix that for you.
Just give me your name
and address.
I'm Mrs. Emmeline Walcott,
and I'm at 42 old mill road.
I gotta stop and pick up
a Douglas valve,
But I should be there
in 45 minutes tops.
I hate to see you drive
when you're this tired.
There's some iced coffee
in the fridge.
I'll be fine.
See you when I get back.
You were great.
Did y'all ever doubt I would be?
Just hurry up and get dressed.
We only have 45 minutes.
Are you Mike?
I'm looking for a
Mrs. Walcott's house.
You've come to the right place.
Here, put this on.
Wear me.
Love, Susan.
You mind telling me
what Susan's up to?
Ask her yourself.
Are you sure about this?
I don't want you to look back and
regret not having
your perfect wedding.
Well, I don't know if
you've noticed, but my idea
of the perfect wedding
keeps changing.
One day, I want white roses,
and then I want lies, and
and first, I want a harpist,
and then a string quartet.
Only one thing stays constant...
And I'm looking at him.
Why would I need anything else
to make my wedding perfect?
Well, who knew down sizing
could be so romantic?
Mrs. Walcott, I presume?
That's right, sugar.
You might wanna check that
breast pocket of your suit.
And just so you know,
you'll be paying for those
and the lights and
the flowers.
I've never seen you
look so beautiful.
You clean up pretty good
yourself.
Are we ready?
Are you kidding? They've been dragging
this thing out for three years.
We are gathered here today
to join together Mike Delfino and
Susan Mayer in matrimony,
an honorable estate not
to be entered into lightly,
but reverently and soberly...
Family...
there is nothing more important.
They're the ones who show up
when we're in trouble...
the ones who push us to succeed...
the ones who help
keep our secrets.
But what of those who have
no family to rely on?
To My Beloved Carlos.
What happens
to those poor souls...
who have no loved
ones to help them
in their hour of need?
Well...
most learn to walk life's road
by themselves.
But a sad few of us...
simply...
stop trying.
_/Yellow Sub\_
contact@yellowsubteam.com