PREVIOLY ON...
IT MEANS A LOT TO HER
TO FEEL INCLUDED.
SOMETIMES DARK CLOUDS
HAVE SILVER LININGS...
(Susan)
HE SORT OF ASKED ME OUT.
IT'S OKAY WITH YOU
IF I GO OUT WITH HIM?
SOMETIMES THEY DON'T.
ONCE THAT BABY COMES,
I'M GONNA BE STUCK
RAISING A CHILD ALONE.
WHEN IT COMES TO LIFE
ON WISTERIA LANE...
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
THINGS THAT SEEM
TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE...
DOES SHE KNOW
YOU KILLED YOUR WIFE?
USUALLY TURN OUT...
GET AWAY FROM HIM NOW
WHILE YOU CAN.
TO BE DEADLY.
www.1000fr.com Present
Sync:FRM@¾ÆÄÒ·¹´ü
(Mary Alice)
BRIDES ARE SENSITIVE CREATURES,
AND NO ONE KNOWS THIS BETTER
THAN THE BRIDESMAIDS
WHO HAVE TO DEAL WITH THEM.
WELL, I THINK
A 10-FOOT TRAIN IS GREAT,
BUT A SHORTER ONE
WOULD BE JUST AS NICE,
AND YOU WOULDN'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT PEOPLE TRIPPING ON IT.
PERSONALLY,
I LOVE SMOKED RABBIT,
BUT FOR A SURE CROWD-PLEASER,
YOU CAN'T BEAT CHICKEN.
UH, SURE, WHO DOESN'T LOVE
A STRING QUARTET?
BUT IF YOU GOT A BAND,
MAYBE PEOPLE COULD DANCE,
AS OPPOSED TO SWAY.
BUT THE ONE AREA
WHERE A BRIDESMAID'S TACT
IS MOST REQUIRED
INVOLVES THE DRESS...
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SHSHE'S REQUIRED TO WEAR.
WELL, UM...
I'M NOT SURE THAT I'VE EVER
SEEN THIS SHADE OF GREEN BEFORE.
YEAH, DON'T YOU THINK IT'LL BE
GORGEOUS WITH MY COLORING?
YES, IT WOULD
LOOK PERFECT.
FOR SOMEONE
WITH YOUR COLORING.
I MEAN, I WAS CKY
TO FIND THESE--
NOT EASY PUTTING
A WEDDING TOGETHER IN TWO WEEKS.
THEN WHY THE RUSH?
YEAH, BREE,
I'D HAVE THOUGHT OF YOU
AS A PERSON WHO WANTS
TIME TO PLAN.
WELL, ORSON AND I
TALKED ABOUT IT,
AND WE JUST FEEL AT OUR AGE,
IT'S SILLY TO WAIT.
AND WITH YOUR HELP,
I'M SURE WE CAN GET IT ALL DONE.
WELL, WE ARE HAPPY
OH, UH, THAT REMINDS ME.
I HAVE TO GET A COPY
OF THE SEATING CHART FOR YOU.
GABY, YOU ARE IN CHARGE
OF THE CENTERPIECES.
AND DON'T WORRY, SUSAN.
I WILL THINKF A JOB FOR YOU.
HERE'S A JOB. HOW ABOUT
TALKING YOU OUT OF MARRYING
A HOMICIDAL DENTIST?
SUSAN, WE DON'T KNOW THAT!
ALL WE HAVE IS SOME
CRAZY WOMAN'S ACCUSATIONS.
HIS WIFE VANISHED,
AND HE DIDN'T EVEN TELL BREE.
HOW MUCH MORE PROOF
DO YOU NEED?
HE SAYS HE'S INNOCENT.
SHE BELIEVES HIM.
IF WE SAY WE DON'T,
SHE'LL JUST END UP HATING US.
WELL, I'M SORRY. I CANNOT
SIT HERE ON MY KEY LIME ASS
AND WATCH BREE MAKE
THE WORST MISTAKE OF HER LIFE!
(Bree) AHEM!
AND WHAT MISTAKE WOULD THAT BE?
WELL...
UM...
HONESTLY...
YES, A BRIDESMAID CAN QUESTION
MANY OF THE BRIDE'S CHOICES.
THESE DRESSES ARE HIDEOUS.
BUT THE GROOM
ISN'T ONE OF THEM.
**
Captioning provided by
Touchstone Television, ABC, Inc.
and brought to you by Ford--
Every day, someone somewhere
makes a bold move.
There's a car company
for people like that.
Captioned by
Closed Captioning Services, Inc.
THE PERFECT COUPLE...
WE'VE ALL MET THEM,
HAVEN'T WE?
THAT MAN AND WOMAN
SO CLEARLY MADE FOR EACH OTHER,
WE FEEL CERTAIN THEY'RE
ON THE ROAD TO HAPPINESS.
BUT THAT ROAD
HAS MANY DETOURS,
AND EVEN PERFECT COUPLES
CAN FIND THEMSELVES...
AT A DEAD END.
(Carlos) YOU WANT WHAT?!
YOU HEARD ME.
AND I WANT THE BEDROOM STEREO.
I WANT THE MARBLE CONSOLE
AND THAT PAINTING
OF ST. AUGUSTINE.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO HE IS.
I KNOW HE MATCHES
THE DRAPES.
PEOPLE, CAN WE FOCUS HERE?
AND I WANT
MY PEARL NECKLACE BACK.
DON'T THINK I DIDN'T NOTICE
THAT YOU SWIPED IT.
THAT WAS MY MAMá'S
I THINK IT BELONGS
IN MY FAMILY.
THERE WAS A TIME
I BELONGED IN YOUR FAMILY,
AND YOU GOT OVER THAT.
STOP EATING MY FRIES!
I'M HUNGRY.
YOU KNOW
WHAT THE DOCTOR SAID.
YOU SHOULD SEE HIS CHOLESTEROL.
THIS MAN BLEEDS BAKING GREASE.
ENOUGH!
YOU TWO ARE GONNA HAVE TO FIND
A WAY TO DEAL WITH EACH OTHER,
BECAUSE YOU ARE ABOUT TO BRING
A CHILD INTO THIS WORLD.
AND DIVORCED OR NOT,
ONCE THAT CHILD ARRIVES,
YOU WILL BE BOUND TOGETHER
FOR AS LONG AS YOU LIVE.
WELL, IN THAT CASE...
HAVE SOME MORE FRIES.
I'LL PICK KAYLA UP
ON SUNDAY.
WHENEVER. JUST GO.
YOU AND TURK HAVE A GREAT TIME.
OH, TRUST ME, WE WILL.
THE MAN IS A JACKHAMMER.
AH.
BYE, TOM.
BYE.
SEE YOU SUNDAY!
WHERE IS SHE GOIN'?
SHE AND TURK
ARE GOING DOWN TO THE RIVER
FOR THE WEEKEND.
THAT'S TURK?
THAT'S THE NEW BOYFRIEND?
UNH-UNH, NO.
HEY, HEY, HEY, TOM, PLEASE.
I DON'T WANT MY DAUGHTER HANGING
AROUND WITH A GUY LIKE THAT.
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN MET HIM.
HE COULD BE THE SWEETEST MAN
IN THE WORLD.
(squeals)
HA HA! OOH.
MORE IMPORTANTLY, EVER SINCE
HE ENTERED THE PICTURE,
SQUEAKY FROMME
IS NEVER AROUND.
IT HAS BEEN BLISS.
I HAVEN'T MADE THIS FACE...
IN A WEEK.
IF YOU RUIN THIS,
SO HELP ME, I WILL HURT YOU.
JUST LOOK AT HIM.
LOOK AT HIM, PLEASE.
I SWEAR,
THAT IS A CHILD'S SKULL
HANGING FROM
HIS REARVIEW MIRROR.
DOESN'T THAT CONCERN YOU?
NO, I'M GOOD.
COULD BE A MONKEY.
UH, I THINK
I WILL HAVE THE...
MESCLUN SALAD.
THAT'S IT?
THAT'S ALL YOU'RE HAVING?
(whispering) WELL,
ALL THE FOOD IS VERY EXPENSIVE.
YOU DON'T NEED TO WHISPER.
THE WAITER KNOWS
THEY'RE ROBBING US BLIND.
YOU CAN HAVE
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
IN THAT CASE,
I'LL HAVE THE LOBSTER BISQUE
AND THE VEAL
WITH THE BLACK TRUFFLES.
IS THAT OKAY?
YEAH, THAT'S FINE.
I'LL JUST HAVE JANE MOVED
TO THE V.A. HOSPITAL.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M KIDDING. IT'S FINE.
I'LL HAVE
WHAT SHE'S HAVING.
OF COURSE. THANK YOU.
GOD, I LOVE
SEEING YOU LAUGH.
OH, WELL,
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE I'VE BEEN IN THE MOOD TO.
THANK YOU.
OH, DEAR GOD!
DID I SQUEEZE TOO HARD?
NO,
IT'S MY WIFE'S PARENTS.
OH! OH, WOW!
OH, IS THIS
GONNA BE AWKWARD?
NO, NO, NO, NOT UNLESS,
OF COURSE, THEY SEE US.
(man) IAN?
AWKWARD.
JEFF, RENEE,
WHAT A DELIGHTFUL SURPRISE.
(chuckles)
IT'S SO GOOD
TO SEE YOU, DEAR.
HELLO. I'M RENEE,
AND THIS MY HUSBAND JEFF.
SUSAN MAYER.
UH, DOCTOR...
DR. SUSAN MAYER--SHE'S NEW
TO JANE'S NEUROLOGY TEAM.
OH!
I JUST ASSUMED YOU WORKED
IN IAN'S PUBLISHING HOUSE.
WELL, YES, AND HOW--W NICE
THAT WOULD'VE BEEN, HUH?
UM, BUT, NO, NO,
I'M A...
A BRAIN SPECIALIST.
WELL, DR. MAYER,
MAYBE I CAN ASK YOU,
OUR DAUGHTER'S MOST RECENT
E.E.G. SHOWED BRAIN SPIKES,
BUT IT DIDN'T CHANGE
THE SCORE
ON THE GLASGOW SCALE.
WHY IS THAT?
WHAT AN EXCELLENT QUESTION.
AND THIS IS THE, UH...
SPINAL CORD.
UH-HUH.
AND IT, OF COURSE,
ATTACHES TO THE BRAIN.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
DUMB IT DOWN FOR US, DOCTOR.
WE'VE BEEN DEALING
WITH JANE'S CONDITION FOR YEARS.
OH, GOOD. UM, WELL,
THEN LET'S--LET'S GET TECHNICAL.
UH, LET'S GIVE
DR. MAYER THE NIGHT OFF.
SHE WAS IN SURGERY
FOR TEN HOURS TODAY
PERFORMING A CRANIOTOMY.
THAT'S EXACTLY THE PROCEDURE
JANE HAD. HOW'D IT GO?
UH, WELL, IT JUST--
WOW!
I HEAR MY--
MY PHONE VIBRATING.
UM, HELLO, UH, DR. MAYER.
YEAH, WHAT?
YOU SAY THAT
HIS BRAIN SHUT OFF?
OH, WELL,
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
UM, STAT. I'M SORRY.
(chuckles nervously) DUTY CALLS.
ORSON?
I MOVED THE FURNITURE BACK!
GOOD LORD, BREE,
NOT AGAIN.
(jazz music playing)
DON'T YOU WANT
OUR FIRST DANCE TO BE PERFECT?
THERE'LL BE 200 PEOPLE
STARING AT US.
YOU KNOW, BREE...
SINCE THAT INCIDENT
AT OUR ENGAGEMENT PARTY,
THERE'S BEEN A LOT
OF DARK TALK ABOUT ME.
WELL, I DON'T PAY ATTENTION
TO GOSSIP.
I'M JUST SAYING I WOULD
UNDERSTAND IF YOU HAD
SECOND THOUGHTS ABOUT MARRYING
A MAN WHO'S UNDER A CLOUD.
WELL, NO ONE WHO KNOWS YOU
COULD SERIOUSLY BELIEVE
THAT YOU COULD HURT
A WOMAN.
STRANGERS MAY TALK,
BUT I KNOW THE TRUTH.
REALLY?
MEN HAVE LIED
TO ME BEFORE.
BELIEVE ME,
THAT'LL NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
SO YOU TRUST ME
COMPLETELY?
CLEARLY, I DO.
THE BODY IS UNUSUALLY
WELL-PRESERVED
BECAUSE IT WAS BURIED
IN CLAY.
DO WE HAVE
A CAUSE OF DEATH?
BLUNT FORCE TRAUMA
TO THE HEAD.
I WANT YOU TO PULL
ALL THE MISSING PERSONS REPORTS,
CROSS-CHECK AGAINST
HER HEIGHT, AGE AND WEIGHT.
I'M ALSO RUNNING
A D.N.A. PANEL
SINCE WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO USE HER DENTAL RECORDS.
WHY NOT?
WHOEVER KILLED HER
PULLED OUT ALL HER TEETH.
NORA? WHAT ARE YOU DOING BACK?
ARE YOU OKAY?
SHUT THE DOOR!
OKAY.
I DON'T WANT KAYLA
TO FIND ME LIKE THIS.
WHAT'S WRONG?
TURK AND I HAD A FIGHT.
WHAT? NO! NO, NO, NO!
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT HAPPENED IS,
TURK IS AN ASS!
ON THE WAY TO THE RIVER,
WE STOPPED OFF AT THIS BAR.
AND WE WERE AYING POOL,
AND I GOT A LITTLE BITCHY
WITH ONE OF THE WAITRESSES.
WHO CARES, RIGHT?
I MEAN, WHO CARES? IT'S A BAR,
AND WE ALL DO IT, RIGHT?
R-RIGHT.
SO HE TELLS ME
TO WATCH MY MOUTH.
AND I'M LIKE, WHOA!
GET A LOAD
OF MR. TWO STRIKES
TRYING TO TELL ME
HOW TO ACT IN PUBLIC.
AND THEN HE CALLED ME
A WHORE.
WE'RE DONE.
OKAY, WHOA! WHOA!
TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
YOU DON'T BREAK UP
WITH A GUY
BECAUSE IN A WEAK MOMENT
HE CALLS YOU A WHORE.
AND THEN ON THE WAY OUT,
HE THREATENED TO HIT ME.
OKAY, BUT HE DIDN'T. HE DIDN'T.
AND, YOU KNOW, UNTIL--
OH, JEEZ, LYNETTE,
WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON?!
I'M ON THE SIDE OF LOVE.
YOU GUYS SEEM LIKE
SUCH A PERFECT COUPLE.
I KNOW.
I JUST--I-I...
YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T WANNA
THROW THAT ALL AWAY
'CAUSE OF A LITTLE FIGHT
WITH NO HITTING.
(sniffles loudly)
NO. IT'S OVER.
I JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH TURK'S PAROLE OFFICER,
AND I WAS LIKE, "GUESS WHO AIN'T
IN NEVADA NO MORE?" CLICK.
(sobbing)
I THINK I'M GONNA
HAVE TO STAY HERE TONIGHT.
(rattling in distance)
(door opens in distance)
(rustling in bushes)
(loud rattling)
(grunting)
FREEZE!
AUSTIN?
HEY, AUNT EDIE.
ANYWAY...
MOM JUST GOT BACK
FROM HER CRUISE TO JAMAICA
WITH NEW BOOBS
AND A 24-YEAR-OLD CABIN BOY.
OOH.
NEEDLESS TO SAY,
ME AND MR. "CAN I GET YOU
SOME MORE HOT TOWELS?"--
WE DIDN'T EXACTLY HIT IT OFF.
SO AFTER I BROKE HIS NOSE,
I, UH, FIGURED IT WAS
A GREAT TIME TO COME VISIT
MY FAVORITE AUNT.
YOUR MOM ALWAYS DID HAVE
LOUSY TASTE IN MEN.
SO, UH, I FIGURED
I'D CRASH HERE FOR THE NIGHT.
THEN HITCH DOWN
TO MEXICO--
HANG OUT, PARTY.
YEAH, I'M THINKING, LIKE,
NO WAY IN HELL.
YOU'RE GONNA
STAY HERE WITH ME
UNTIL THINGS BLOW OVER
WITH YOUR MOM, OKAY?
COOL. THANKS.
OH, WAIT,
YOU'RE 18, RIGHT?
WELL,
THAT'S WHAT MY I.D. SAYS.
YEAH, MINE, TOO.
HEY, YOU ARE SUPPOSED TO BE
ON BED REST!
I'M BORED.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU TRY
PUTTING ON A PAIR OF PANTS?
THAT SHOULD KILL
A COUPLE OF HOURS.
(doorbell rings)
HEY, BABE.
HEY, WHAT IS SHE DOING
OUT OF BED?
THAT CAN'T BE
GOOD FOR HER.
OR THE STAIRS.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
THE MEDIATOR WAS RIGHT.
A MONTH FROM NOW WE'RE NOT JUST
GONNA BE CARLOS AND GABY.
WE'RE GONNA BE MOM AND DAD,
AND I DON'T WANNA BE AT WAR
WITH THE MOTHER OF MY CHILD,
SO, HERE.
YOUR MAMá'S PEARLS?
CARLOS...
THANK YOU.
AND?
AND WHAT?
WOULDN'T YOU LIKE TO MAKE
SOME RECIPROCAL GESTURE?
FINE. YOU CAN COME TO BREE'S
WEDDING RECEPTION AS MY GUEST.
THANKS. WHERE IS IT?
HERE.
HERE?
YOU'RE THROWING
THE... RECEPTION?
YEAH, IT'S OUR WEDDING PRESENT
TO BREE.
SO I GIVE YOU
A PRICELESS FAMILY HEIRLOOM,
AND IN RETURN, YOU INVITE ME
TO A PARTY AT MY HOUSE
THAT I'M PAYING FOR?
WELL, WHAT KIND OF GESTURE
DID YOU HAVE IN MIND?
(scoffs)
MMM.
THINGS I'LL DO
FOR JEWELRY.
SUSAN, I AM SO SORRY.
DR. MAYER?
PANIC. PURE PANIC.
HERE. THESE ARE FOR RUINING
OUR FIRST DATE.
SHH!
NOT IN FRONT OF MIKE!
OH, LOOK, MIKE,
IAN BROUGHT YOU FLOWERS.
I'LL JUST GO PUT THEM
IN SOME WATER.
LOOK, I-I WAS JUST TRYING
TO PROTECT JANE'S PARENTS.
OH, PLEASE.
THEY STILL HAVEN'T
ACCEPTED THE FACT
THAT--THAT JANE
ISN'T GOING TO WAKE UP.
IF THEY KNEW
THAT WE WERE ON A DATE,
THAT I WAS TRYING TO MOVE ON,
WELL, IT WOULD DEVASTATE THEM.
THAT'S A REALLY
LOVELY EXCUSE,
BUT IT ISN'T
THE WHOLE STORY, IS IT?
EXCUSE ME?
A PART OF YOU FEELS
THAT YOU'RE CHEATING ON HER.
NO!
WELL, PERHAPS A SMALL PART,
BUT THAT--THAT DOESN'T MEAN--
IT'S ALL RIGHT,
'CAUSE I FEEL GUILTY, TOO.
THAT--THAT'S WHY WE SHOULD
JUST STOP IS RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE IT'S
ALL WAY TOO COMPLICATED,
AND I-I THINK
WE'D BOTH BE HAPPIER
IF WE JUST WENT BACK
TO BEING FRIENDS.
WELL, I-I DON'T THINK
I CAN DO THAT.
THE--THE TRUTH IS,
I HAVEN'T THOUGHT OF YOU
AS JUST A FRIEND
FOR SOME TIME NOW.
MAYBE I SHOULDN'T HAVE
LET MYSELF FEEL THAT WAY,
BUT--BUT I HAVE.
AND I CAN'T GO BACK.
I'M SORRY.
WELL, IF WE CAN'T
BE FRIENDS...
THEN I GUESS
WE'LL BE NOTHING.
(rap music playing loudly
in distance)
(music volume increases)
(rap music
continues playing loudly)
(decreases volume)
HEY, LEAVE THAT ALONE.
SORRY, I WAS JUST...
TURNING IT DOWN.
WHAT, YOU'RE NOT
A MUSIC FAN?
SURE, IT'S JUST, UM...
GOT ANYTHING WHERE
A PIMP ISN'T BEATING H HO?
(chuckles)
I'M AUSTIN,
EDIE BRITT'S NEPHEW.
OH. (chuckles)
I'M JULIE,
SUSAN MAYER'S DAUGHTER.
OH.
ANYWAY, UM, I WAS TRYING
TO DO MY HOMEWORK, SO...
ON A SATURDAY?
WELL, MAKE SURE
AND TAKE REGULAR BREAKS
AND STOP
FOR A SENSIBLE DINNER.
JUST KEEP IT DOWN.
YOU HAD IT REALLY LOUD.
THAT'S H I LIKE IT.
HOW DO YOU LIKE IT?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE NOT THAT HOT.
HEY, WHATCHA DOING?
OH, I'M WORKING ON
A SEATING CHART--MWAH!
FOR BREE'S WEDDING.
NORA? WHO INVITED HER?
I DID. WE NEED TO FIND HER
ANOTHER BOYFRIEND,
AND WEDDINGS
ARE CRAWLING WITH SINGLE MEN.
HEY, I HOPE
YOU'RE NOT SEATING HER
NEXT TO ANY OF MY FRIENDS.
HEY, SACRIFICES
MUST BE MADE, TOM.
NO, JERRY RAWLINGS!
NOT JERRY RAWLINGS!
YES!
SHE GETS HER PSYCHO HOOKS
INTO JERRY RAWLINGS,
HE WILL NEVER
SPEAK TO ME AGAIN.
OH, THERE ARE OTHER UROLOGISTS
IN THE WORLD.
GO BACK TO THAT OTHER GUY.
THE ONE
WITH THE COLD HANDS?
OH, IT'S ONCE A YEAR.
SUCK IT UP.
GET A GRIP, LYNETTE.
"GET A GRIP"?!
I AM HANGING ON
FOR DEAR LIFE HERE.
YOU ARE THE ONE THAT BROUGHT
THIS LITTLE PROBLEM
INTO OUR FAMILY,
AND THE ONLY THING
I SHOULD BE HEARING FROM YOU IS,
"HOW CAN I HELP?"
I AM ALSO PUTTING
STEVE HANSON AT HER TABLE,
SO YOU MIGHT WANT
TO START SHOPPING AROUND
FOR A NEW GOLF BUDDY.
GET A GRIP.
(cans rattling)
(chuckles)
HI.
MY NAME IS SUSAN MAYER.
YOUR NEIGHBOR TOLD ME
I COULD FIND YOU HERE.
YEAH?
WELL, I WAS
AT MY FRIEND
BREE'S ENGAGEMENT PARTY
THE OTHER NIGHT--
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU CAME IN
AND YOU DID THAT WHOLE
"ORSON KILLED HIS WIFE"
THING?
I WAS JUST WONDERING
IF YOU COULD ELABORATE.
HE KILLED HER.
WHAT ELSE DO YOU NEED TO KNOW?
WELL,
WHAT MAKES YOU SO SURE?
DO YOU HAVE ANY PROOF?
LOOK, I CAN'T TALK NOW.
I GET OFF AT 6:00.
MY FRIEND IS MARRYING THAT MAN
IN TWO HOURS. PLEASE?
OKAY, I-I NEED, UM,
$10 IN UNROLLED PENNIES,
AND I NEED
TO SEE YOU COUNT IT,
'CAUSE LAST TIME
YOU STIFFED ME.
AFTER ALMA DISAPPEARED,
THE POLICE CAME
AND SEARCHED THE HOUSE.
THE POLICE?
WHAT DID THEY FIND?
NOTHING.
AND THAT'S BAD WHY?
DON'T YOU GET IT?
WHEN THE POLICE SHOWED UP,
ORSON HAD SCRUBBED EVERY INCH
OF THE PLACE CLEAN WITH BLEACH.
NO FINGERPRINTS,
NO SKIN CELLS, NO D.N.A.
IT WAS LIKE
ALMA HAD NEVER EXISTED.
WHO CLEANS
A HOUSE LIKE THAT
UNLESS HE HAS
SOMETHING TO HIDE?
SO WHEN I LEFT THE BANK,
I CALLED THE DETECTIVE
THAT WORKED THE CASE,
AND HE SAID THAT THE ONLY REASON
ORSON WAS NEVER CHARGED
SO HE WAS
AN ACTUAL SUSPECT?
HE WAS THE ONLY SUSPECT.
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
WELL, YOU KNOW
WHAT WE HAVE TO DO.
THAT WAS CLOSE.
THE FLORIST PUT THREE MUMS
IN MY BRIDAL BOUQUET,
BUT NOT TO WORRY.
CRISIS AVERTED.
BREE... WE HAVE TO TALK.
AH, REVEREND.
ANY WORD
OM THE BRIDAL PARTY?
THEY'RE STILL
IN THE BRIDE'S ROOM.
YOU KNOW WOMEN.
THEY'RE PROBABLY IN THERE
FUSSING ABOUT MASCARA AND BLUSH.
HE DID NOT HACK HER UP
AND DISSOLVE THE PIECES IN ACID!
I SAID IT WAS A THEORY.
THE POINT IS,
ALMA DISAPPEARED UNDER
VERY SUSPICIOUS CIRCUMSTANCES.
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
I'M GETTING MARRIED NOW.
THIS IS YOUR DAY. YOU CAN PUSH
THE CEREMONY BACK AN HOUR.
NOW GET THAT DETECTIVE
ON THE PHONE,
TALK THINGS OUT WITH ORSON.
I CAN'T TALK TO ORSON.
IT'S BAD LUCK
FOR THE GROOM TO SEE
THE BRIDE BEFORE THE WEDDING.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S REALLY BAD LUCK?
MARRYING A WIFE-KILLER.
IF THE THREE OF YOU
DON'T DROP THIS RIGHNOW,
I WILL NEVER FORGIVE YOU.
BREE, WE ARE JUST DOING THIS
BECAUSE WE LOVE YOU.
BUT...
IF YOU CAN
HONESTLY TELL US
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE
THE SLIGHTEST DOUBT...
NONE WHATSOEVER.
HMM.
(Mendelssohn's "Wedding March"
playing)
DEARLY BELOVED,
WE ARE GATHERED HERE TOGETHER
IN THE SIGHT OF GOD
TO JOIN THIS MAN AND WOMAN
IN HOLY--
EXCUSE ME?
COULD YOU GIVE US
JUST A SECOND?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
I JUST NEED A MOMENT.
(guests murmuring)
BEFORE WE DO THIS,
THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO ASK YOU.
WHAT?
DID YOU KILL YOUR WIFE?
SUSAN TALKED
TO THAT CAROLYN WOMAN.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME THATTHE POLIC
BECAUSE IT'S EMBARRASSING,
AND THEY DIDN'T FIND ANYTHING.
IS THAT BECAUSE YOU SCRUBBED
THE HOUSE SO THOROUGHLY?
WHEN I'M UPSET, I CLEAN.
FOR GOD'S SAKE, BREE,
I SWEAR TO YOU
I DID NOT KILL MY WIFE.
OKAY.
PROCEED.
DEARLY BELOVED,
WE ARE GATHERED HERE TOGETHER
IN THE SIGHT OF GOD
TO JOIN THIS MAN AND WOMAN
IN HOLY MATRIMONY,
WHICH IS
AN HONORABLE ESTATE...
HEY!
LOOK AT YOU, MISS POPULAR!
SO ARE YOU HAVING
A GOOD TIME OVER THERE?
AS IF,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT IDIOT
STUCK ME AT THAT TABLE,
BUT EVERY GUY OVER THERE
IS JUST A BORING STIFF.
ALL OF THEM?
WHAT ABOUT... JERRY?
JERRY'S FUN.
YOU MEAN MR. FATTY HAIR PLUGS?
OH, YEAH, HE'S A BLAST.
(imitates gunshot)
UM, HOW ABOUT STEVE?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HEAR HIS FAMILY HAS MONEY.
WELL, THEN MAYBE
THEY COULD ALL CHIP IN
AND BUY HIM
SOME DEODORANT.
I'M THROUGH
WITH THOSE LOSERS.
I'M GONNA STAY
RIGHT HERE WITH YOU.
ARE YOU GONNA EAT THAT?
(gasps) HEY, LOOK AT YOU!
(sighs)
GOD, I HATE WEARING A TUX.
ON MY WAY IN, BREE'S AUNT FERN
ASKED ME TO PARK THE CAR.
SHE'S GOT GLAUCOMA.
TO HER, YOU'RE NOTHING
BUT A HISPANIC BLUR.
(chuckles)
LET ME FIX YOUR TIE.
HEY, YOU'RE WEARING
MAM?S PEARLS.
YEAH.
OH!
HEY, JULIE!
HAVE YOU MET
MY NEPHEW AUSTIN?
YEAH, WE'VE MET.
I JUST DIDN'T RECOGNIZE HIM
WITH HIS SHIRT ON.
SHE COULDN'T
TAKE HER EYES OFF MY ABS.
I FELT VIOLATED.
HI, EDIE.
NICE PARTY, HUH?
IT WAS.
PERFECT.
WELL, IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU TWO
GETTING ALONG AGAIN.
WE'VE SORT OF
TURNED A CORNER.
REALLY?
DOES THAT MEAN YOU'RE GONNA
BE GETTING BACK TOGETHER?
MAYBE.
GOD, NO!
WOW, IS THAT SHRIMP?
WHAT WOULD MAKE YOU THINK
I WOULD EVEN CONSIDER
TAKING YOU BACK?
WELL, YOU INVITED ME
TO BE YOUR DATE.
"GUEST," CARLOS.
I SAID "GUEST."
COME ON, YOU'VE BEEN FLIRTING
WITH ME SINCE I CAME IN--
"HERE, BABY,
LET ME FIX YOUR TIE."
I MEAN, FOR A WOMAN
WHO'S NOT INTERESTED,
YOU SURE ARE SENDING
SOME MIXED SIGNALS.
YOU WANT A CLEAR SIGNAL?HOW'S
(band playing jazz music)
IAN!
SUSAN!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WELL, MY--MY COUSIN IS--IS
DR. HODGES' DENTAL HYGIENIST,
AND HER HUSBAND--
HE--HE COULDN'T JOIN US
SINCE HE'D COME DOWN
WITH A SPOT OF IMPETIGO,
SO SHE CALLED ME,
KNOWING HOW MUCH I LOVE
A GOOD GARTER TOSS, AND SO--
IAN.
YES, I-I'M SUCH
A TERRIBLE LIAR.
I MEAN, IMPETIGO--
WHERE DID THAT COME FROM?
HMM.
SO WHAT ARE YOU REALLY
DOING HERE?
(sighs) LOOK...
I CAN'T STOP
THINKING ABOUT US,
ABOUT HOW GREAT
WE COULD BE TOGETHER,
AND I THINK
YOU'RE MAKING A MISTAKE.
IAN--
SUSAN, PLEASE DON'T GO.
CAN'T WE AT LEAST
TALK ABOUT THIS?
I CAN'T, 'CAUSE I HAVE...
BRIDESMAID STUFF.
HI THERE.
I JUST WANTED TO SAY
YOU'RE DOING A GREAT JOB...
TAD. (chuckles)
THAT'S, UM, THAT'S SUCH
A MASCULINE NAME.
MY BOYFRIEND
SEEMS TO LIKE IT.
OKAY, HERE'S THE DRILL.
MY EX IS HERE,
AND I WANNA PISS HIM OFF,
SO JUST ACT LIKE
YOU'RE ALL HOT FOR ME,
AND THERE'S A 100 BUCK TIP
IN IT FOR YOU.
RIGHT.
UH, SO SHOULD I...
CUP YOUR BOOB?
NO, I'LL DRIVE.
(laughing loudly)
OH!
TEQUILA, STRAIGHT.
HEY, ARE THERE ANY DECENT
SINGLE WOMEN ATHIS WEDDING?
NOT THAT I'VE SEEN.
AH, DAMN IT. NOT A ONE.
HEY, CARLOS.
YOU SHOULD COME OVER
TO OUR TABLE.
THAT'S WHERE
ALL THE HOTTIES ARE.
HEY, EVERYONE!
I'D SAY IT IS TIME THAT
WE GET BREE AND ORSON UP HERE
FOR THEIR FIRST DANCE
AS A MARRIED COUPLE.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
I GIVE YOU
MR. AND MRS. ORSON HODGE!
ORSON,
YOU LOOK SO SERIOUS.
I'M TRYING TO REMEMBER
MY STEPS.
YOU'RE UPSET, AREN'T YOU?
YOU'RE STILL THINKING ABOUT
WHAT I SAID AT THE CHURCH.
WHICH PART, DARLING--
THE "I DO" PART,
OR THE "DID YOU
KILL YOUR WIFE?" PART?
I'M SORRY,
BUT I HAD TO ASK.
THAT'S MY POINT.
YOU HAD TO ASK.
(up-tempo jazz music playing)
(squealing)
YOU ARE GONNA
ROT IN HELL FOR THIS.
HEY, I JUST BROUGHT
TWO LOST SOULS TOGETHER.
OKAY, HOW ABOUT THIS?
HE CHEATED ON MY FRIEND.
HE DESERVES EVERY BIT OF...
(singsong voice) CRAZY
SHE'S GONNA
RAIN DOWN ON HIM.
HELL... ROT... YOU.
(slow jazz music playing)
WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
ROUNDING SECOND
AND HEADING FOR THIRD.
UH-OH.
CARLOS!
OH, HEY, GABY.
LOOK, I MADE A NEW FRIEND.
YES, I'VE BEEN WATCHING YOU
MAKE YOUR NEW FRIEND,
AND IT'S DISGUSTING!
DO YOU MIND?
WE'RE TRYING TO DANCE HERE.
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU,
ANYWAY,
AND WHY THE HELL
ARE YOU AT THIS WEDDING?!
THIS IS NOT
GONNA END WELL.
THEY'RE JUST TWO RANDOM PEOPLE
WHO MET AT A WEDDING.
CAN'T PIN IT ON .
IT WAS HER!
LYNETTE SCAVO,
I WANNA TALK TO YOU!
I'LL SEE YOU AT HOME.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
I DIDN'T INVITE YOU HERE
TO EMBARRASS ME
IN FRONT OF MY FRIENDS.
OH, NO, YOU JUST
WANTED ME TO WATCH
WHILE YOU SUCKED THE ZITS
OFF SOME TEENAGE WAITER!
THAT'S IT.
I TAKE MY INVITATION BACK.
YOU ARE NO LONGER WELCOME
IN MY HOUSE.
FINE, I'LL GO!
JUST GIVE ME BACK THE PEARLS.
NO!
GABY.
CARLOS, NO!
THEY WERE MY MAM?S!
NO! (gasps)
NOW LOOK WHAT YOU'VE DONE!
MRS. SOLIS!
NO, CARLOS!
HEY, GIVE ME THAT!
GIVE ME THOSE!
PARDON ME. EXCUSE ME.
GET AWAY! THOSE ARE MINE!
NO, THE HELL THEY ARE!
MRS. SOLIS?
NOT NOW, XIAO-MEI!
MRS. SOLIS!
OH, FOR GOD SAKES, WHAT?!
(liquid splashes)
(guests gasp)
(woman) ARE YOU KIDDING?
I THINK MAYBE IT'S TIME.
AND I WISH YOU BOTH
A LIFETIME OF HAPPINESS.
(rim shot, applause)
WOW.
THAT WAS BEAUTIFUL, AUNT FERN.
THANK YOU.
HEY, THEY MOPPED UP
ALL THE AMNIOTIC FLUID,
SO WE SHOULD FEEL SAFE
START THE CONGA LINE!
(piano starts playing)
ACTUALLY, I'D--I'D LIKE
TO SAY A FEW WORDS.
(piano stops playing)
BREE, ORSON,
YOUR LOVE
IS AN INSPIRATION TO US ALL.
THAT'S VERY SWEET.
HMM.
HOW DO YOU KNOW HIM?
I THOUGHT
HE WAS ON YOUR SIDE.
MNH-MNH.
WELL, I KNOW
THIS IS A SECOND WEDDING
FOR BOTH OF YOU,
AND I THINK YOU'RE JOLLY BRAVE.
SO OFTEN, PEOPLE FIND EXCUSES
NOT TO FALL IN LOVE AGAIN.
THEY'RE--THEY'RE AFRAID.
BUT IT'S RARE TO FIND SOMEBODY
THAT YOU CONNECT WITH,
SO WHEN YOU DO,
YOU HAVE TO FOLLOW YOUR HEART.
BREE, ORSON,
I SALUTE YOU.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
THE MUSIC CRANKING AND THE--
WAIT, ACTUALLY, TOM,
COULD YOU JUST HANG ON A SECOND?
UH, I-I ALSO WOULD LIKE
TO SAY A FEW WORDS.
TO BREE AND ORSON, UH, YES,
WHAT COULD BE BETTER
THAN A SECOND LOVE?
AND THIS TIME YOU ENTER INTO IT
A LITTLE OLDER, LITTLE WISER,
BUT ALSO--
AND THIS IS KEY--UH...
WITH A BIT OF CAUTION.
BECAUSE...
WHILE LOVE CAN BE SPONTANEOUS
AND WONDERFUL,
IT CAN ALSO BE SELFISH.
AND SOMETIMES
THE BEST THING YOU CAN DO
IS JUST TO WALK AWAY.
UH... I--NOT YOU TWO.
I MEAN, YOU TWO CRAZKIDS
ARE GREAT. (laughs)
CONGRATS, YEAH.
WELL, THEN, LET'S--
HANG ON. I'D LIKE
TO RESPOND TO THAT TOAST.
BREE, ORSON,
SOMETIMES WALKING AWAY
CAN SEEM THE BEST CHOICE.
IT'S--IT'S CERTAINLY
THE SAFEST.
BUT... BUT WHAT DO YOU DO
WHEN YOU FIND SOMEONE
WHO MAKES YOU FEEL JOY
WHEN YOU THOUGHT
YOU NEVER WOULD AGAIN?
DO YOU--
DO YOU JUST LET THEM GO?
NO.
NO, I CAN'T DO THAT.
(microphone feedback squeaks)
YOU--YOU WANNA...
NO.
I'M GO.
ALL RIGHT THEN, LET'S DANCE!
**
WELL, I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
NEED A CHANGE OF CLOTHES.
YOU'RE STILL
MAD AT ME, HUH?
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING,
SETTING CARLOS UP WITH SKANK?!
I'M SORRY.
I WAS DESPERATE.
I HAD A LITTLE TOO MUCH
TO DRINK.
AND YOU
ARE DIVORCING CARLOS...
NO, LYNETTE,
CARLOS WL NEVER BE FAIR GAME.
YOU KNOW THE RULES.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU ARE RIGHT. YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S JUST...
WHAT?
I'M SO UNHAPPY.
EVER SINCE THAT WOMAN
PUSHED HER WAY INTO OUR LIVES,
I-I CAN'T EVEN
WO UP A SMILE.
AND THE MORE SHE PUSHES,
THE MORE I RESENT TOM--
TOM, FOR SOMETHING HE DID
12 YEARS AGO.
AND I'M AFRAID
IF I CAN'T FIX...
THIS, THAT...
THE ANGER IS JUST GONNA
FESTER UNTIL...
LYNETTE, LISTEN TO ME--
YOU AND TOM
WILL SURVIVE THIS.
NO, SERIOUSLY, GABY,
I AM SO TIRED
OF PRETENDING TO SMILE.
YOU AND TOM...
WILL SURVIVE THIS.
YEAH?
HOW CAN YOU BE SO SURE?
BECAUSE SOME MARRIAGES
WERE BUILT TO LAST...
AND SOME AREN'T.
TRUST ME,
I KNOW THE DIFFERENCE.
(applause)
(both chuckle)
I'M LOOKING
FOR BREE VAN DE KAMP.
RIGHT OVER THERE.
COULD YOU EXCUSE ME
FOR JUST A MINUTE?
MM-HMM.
ORSON, CONGRATULATIONS.
EXCUSE ME.
ARE YOU MRS. VAN DE KAMP?
IT'S HODGE NOW.
YES, I'M TERRIBLY SORRY
TO BARGE IN LIKE THIS,
BUT WE NEED YOUR HUSBAND
TO COME DOWN TO THE MORGUE.
WE MAY HAVE FOUND
HIS WIFE'S BODY.
(grunting)
PUSH, XIAO-MEI. PUSH.
(groaning)
OKAY, OKAY.
DEEP BREATHS NOW.
YOU'RE GETTING CLOSE.
IT'S TIME! I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING!
I THINK I'M GONNA CRY.
CARLOS,
I AM SO SORRY ABOUT THE--
YEAH, I--ME, TOO. ME, TOO.
I WAS WAY OUT OF LINE.
I FORGIVE YOU. IT'S WORTH IT
WHEN YOU EXPERIENCE
A MOMENT
AS BEAUTIFUL AS THIS.
(grunting)
OKAY,
I CAN SEE THE HEAD NOW.
OH, GET THE CAMERA!
GET THE CAMERA!
(grunting)
OH!
(Gaby) OH, MY GOD!
(baby crying)
OH, MAN,
I GOTTA GET THE COLOR FIXED
ON THIS THING.
HOW COULD THIS
HA HAPPENED?
WHAT KIND OF HALF-ASS FERTILITY
CLINIC ARE YOU RUNNING?
UH, PRIOR TO IMPLANTATION,
OUR EMBRYO WAS ACCIDENTALLY
SWITCHED WITH ANOTHER CLIENT'S.
SO IF WE GOT THEIRS
AND THEY GOT OURS,
THEN--THEN IT'S POSSIBLE...
NO, I'M AFRAID
YOUR EMBRYO DIDN'T TAKE.
AGAIN, ON BEHALF OF THE CLINIC,
I AM SO SORRY.
IT'S RARE,
BUT THESE THINGS DO HAPPEN.
EXCUSE ME.
YOU SCREW UP OUR LIVES,
AND THE BEST YOU CAN DO IS,
"THAT'S THE WAY
THE COOKIE CRUMBLES"?!
AND WHO IS THIS GUY?
WHY IS HE WRITING DOWN
EVERYTHING I SAY?
THIS IS MR. DARBY,
OUR ATTORNEY.
WE THOUGHT IT WISE
TO HAVE HIM PRESENT.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
WOULD'VE BEEN WISE?
STICKING THE RIGHT BABY
IN THE RIGHT BELLY!
MRS. SOLIS, PLEASE.
THAT'S NOT ALMA.
ARE YOU SURE?
ABSOLUTELY.
THANK GOD.
CAROLYN.
WHAT IS SHE DOING HERE?
YOU DIDN'T HONESTLY THINK
THEY'D TAKE YOUR WORD
FOR IT, DID YOU?
IT'S NOT HER.
WELL, THAT'S IT THEN.
SORRY FOR WASTING YOUR TIME.
THIS MEANS NOTHING.
I'M TELLING YOU,
THAT MAN IS AS GUILTY  SIN!
WE KNOW WHAT YOU THINK.
NOW WOULD YOU PLEASE
LEAVE US ALONE?
HE'S A COLD-BLOODED KILLER.
HE'S KIND AND DECENT,
AND NOTHING YOU COULD SAY
WILL EVER MAKE ME
DOUBT HIM AGAIN.
NOW PLEASE GO.
YOU DESERVE HIM.
DARLING, I AM SO SORRY
YOU HAD TO ENDURE THAT.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M FINE. LET'S JUST GO BACK
TO OUR GUESTS
AND FORGET ANY OF THIS
EVER HAPPENED.
ALL RIGHT.
TU ME MANQUES, MONIQUE.
WELL...
YEAH.
Welcome to www.1000fr.com