Previously
on Desperate Housewives...
Your ex-husband was
part owner in a business.
Susan came into
an inheritance.
Who do I speak to about selling
my share of herpes on parade?
Lynette acquiesced...
- Looks like we'll be going to therapy.
- That is great news! Thank you.
As soon as I graduate high school,
I'm going to New York to be a model.
Angie's concerns
made her more protective.
You know I've always felt bad
about the way we've had to raise you,
- being on the run and all.
- The door stays open.
- I want it closed.
- You stink.
And you're a whore! Here's
the difference. I can get clean.
- Stop!
- Say "please".
- And Orson expressed his feelings.
- Please!
That's the life I'm facing now.
Having to ask people for help,
for everything.
Do you know how hard that is?!
Orson Hodge was smiling again,
and it was starting to worry
his wife.
You see, since his accident,
Bree Hodge had grown accustomed
to her husband's severe mood swings.
She had grown used to
his unexpected rage...
His sudden anguish...
His deep depression.
But lately,
an odd tranquility
had settled over Orson,
and his wife had the feeling
something was terribly wrong.
Sadly,
she was right.
What's going on here?
Just thought I'd give away
some things I don't need anymore.
You got these in 8 and half?
Sorry, Roy. Just carry men's sizes.
I can understand why you might want
to give away your sporting equipment,
but why would you give away
your books and your CDs?
And for God sakes, you can
still use your headphones.
These are amazing!
Give me those.
What is wrong with you people?
Don't you realize
you're taking advantage
of a man who is
emotionally distraught?
He seemed to be in a great mood.
Until lady sunshine walked in.
Sorry, we assumed
you had talked about it.
We didn't. That doesn't excuse the fact
that you're acting like vultures.
It's a good thing I came home,
or you'd be picking through his closet.
You know what, guys? We should go.
And please leave
your plunder behind.
Come on. At my age,
it's just a short-term loan.
What has gotten into you?
I'm sorry, darling.
I had no intention of upsetting you.
Keep my things, give them away.
Ultimately, it doesn't matter.
Yes, Orson Hodge was smiling again
and Bree would soon learn
the reason why.
You see, her husband...
had decided to kill himself.
Par la Wisteria Team:
MiniBen314, Jayson.Sosweet
www.wisteria-team.fr
www.sous-titres.eu
In this never-ending drama
we call life,
everyone has a part to play.
Some are cast as romantic leads.
Others end up playing the victim.
And a few provide comic relief.
But if the drama is to be
really compelling,
there must be a hero...
and a villain.
Hey, Mrs. Kinsky.
Look who's here!
The garbage police.
I hate to bug you, but you're still not
separating your glass and your plastics.
The city passed
that ordinance, remember?
How I envy you...
Young, pretty,
able to crouch
for hours behind a bush,
waiting for a neighbor
to dump her trash.
Maybe you don't get
how easy it is to recycle.
I get it.
I just don't want to do it.
I've been throwing styrofoam into
the trash since before you were born,
and the sky is still blue
and the grass is still green.
Maybe now, but what will it be
like for our grandchildren?
My son is shooting blanks,
and my daughter likes the ladies.
Grandkids are
the least of my concerns.
So you don't care
about our planet at all?
By the time
it's a problem, I'll be long gone.
Let the cockroaches
and the robots fight over it.
What was that all about?
- What do you think?
- Come on.
One old crank
doesn't want to recycle.
You don't care about that stuff
anymore, remember?
- Of course I still care.
- Yeah, fine. You can care.
Don't be blowing our cover.
So what am I supposed to do? Stand
back and watch her defile our planet?
That's exactly what
you're supposed to do.
"Sometimes you chain
yourself to the tree,
and sometimes you go after
the guy with the saw."
That's what Patrick used to say.
We don't talk about Patrick anymore.
- I'm just saying.
- So am I.
So the lawyer says
you sign right here,
and you are officially bought
out of the strip club business.
Let's hope I don't get
my share in singles.
And here's a little something
to remember us by.
"Lap dancing...
It's a grind."
I will be sure to wear this on the
next field trip I take with my students.
- Thanks, Jimbo.
- Good luck.
You, too.
- Bye, Mrs. D.
- Take care, Robin.
"Moby Dick"?
It's not what you think.
It's about a whale.
Yes, I know. It's a classic.
I saw an article about a hundred
books you should read before dying,
and I thought,
with all the high cholesterol
in my family, I better get crackin'.
Good for you.
So what are you gonna do now?
This was never really my job.
I'm actually a teacher.
Really?
That is so cool.
I thought about being a teacher.
I went a couple semesters,
but then my family had
some money problems, and,
nine years later,
I'm still wearing tassels.
Robin, you're being requested
in the VIP lounge.
- Good luck with those hundred books.
- Thank you.
Not this guy again.
I keep telling him to keep
the tips and buy himself a toothbrush.
Robin, wait.
You don't have to keep doing
this if it makes you unhappy.
I've got bills to pay, Mrs. Delfino.
I know, but you don't
have to work here.
You could do anything you want.
That's easy to say.
I mean it.
It is never too late
to change your life.
Robin, now.
Thank you.
You're taking that with you?
When customers get grabby, I like
to have something to whack'em with.
I almost killed a guy with
"War and peace".
So, I'm driving.
- This guys pulls out in front of me.
- Cuts him off.
- I was a little pissed.
- You were furious.
But at the stoplight, when I start to
tell the guy off, Tom lays over and says
"Sorry. No big deal.
She's just having a bad day."
You didn't have to
take the guy's head off.
- She flipped him the bird.
- I was sticking up for you!
Yes, but Tom was driving.
Whether he chose to ignore it
or try to run the man
of the road, it's his decision.
Let him be in the
driver's seat sometimes,
literally and figuratively.
Bringing the score to Tom 4
and controlling bitch 0.
There's no scoreboard
in this room. You know that.
I think you both did
some great work today.
- Next Tuesday, same time?
- Thanks, doctor.
It felt really great.
Yeah, great.
I always feel so much better
when we get out of there.
- I bet you do.
- Don't you?
I really think she got this working.
Yeah, I think she's got this working
and this is getting beat up.
- Don't feel like that.
- It's true. She always sides with you.
I want a second opinion.
Maybe we should think about
seeing another therapist.
When we started, you loved her.
Yeah, and when we started,
I loved you, too.
Things change. Let's go.
Hold on.
I think I left my keys.
I can't.
I have dress rehearsal tonight.
Talk to you later.
- I'm sorry. I forgot my keys.
- That's okay.
I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
Did you say you had dress rehearsal?
That. Yes, I'm sort of in a little
play that runs this weekend.
Really?
You're an actor, too?
I dabbled in college.
I have a bit of a gift,
so I try to keep it alive.
What's the play?
We'd love to come see it.
"Antony and Cleopatra." But it's
just a community production.
I would never force you
to sit through it.
- If you don't want us to come...
- Here's a flyer. Matinees are half-off.
I need Ana to watch the girls
while I run to the store
and big shock,
she's not answering her cell.
No problem. Come on in.
They're just up in Danny's room.
Gaby's here!
So they're in Danny's room?
They were listening to music, it was
so loud I made'em shut the door.
So they're by themselves...
with the door shut?
Just a couple of teenagers
alone with their genitals?
Get your ass down here!
What's the big deal? They're
just hanging out in Danny's room.
With a mattress. Why don't you crack
a bottle of champagne on Ana's pelvis
and wish Danny a bon voyage?
Ana! Now!
Hold on. I'm coming.
I'm sure she meant she's on her way.
What's going on?
I have to run.
I need you to watch the girls.
That's it? Jeez, I thought
the house was on fire.
Let me grab my stuff.
So...
you worried they might be doing it?
Yeah. What I don't get is
why you're not worried.
They're healthy, red-blooded kids.
They're gonna do what they're gonna do.
So we say nothing
and just fluff their pillows?
We make sure they don't
do anything stupid.
Have you gotten Ana birth control?
I make her spend time with Juanita and
Celia. I was hoping that would do it.
Come on, Gaby.
You have to talk to her
about safe sex, condoms.
She's only 17.
She's too young!
How old were you
when you first did it?
Ana, hurry up!
Gotta hit the pharmacy, too!
I didn't hear you come in.
"Dearest Bree,
I will always love you,
"but the will to fight on has left me,
so I've chosen to...
exit life on my own terms."
Is this a suicide note?
It's really more
of a suicide rough draft.
I didn't mean for you
to find out this way. But,
now that you know,
- we can discuss it like adults.
- There is nothing to discuss.
This is obviously
the depression talking.
We will get you some medication.
There's no need for you
to feel badly about this.
I've had a good life.
Let me go.
I will do no such thing.
I forbid this. Do you hear me?
You will not be killing yourself.
I will remove every knife,
rope and pill from this house,
and if I have to, I will be
with you 24 hours a day.
Being bored to death
wasn't how I was planning to go, but,
we can try it your way.
I'll give you some time
to adjust to this.
But understand me.
It's going to happen.
- What's with the condoms?
- Calm down. They're not for you.
Just what every man wants
to hear from his wife.
So?
Okay, hear me out. You know
how Ana is dating Danny Bolen?
- I'm gonna kill him.
- We have to be realistic.
- With my bare hands.
- They're not gonna listen to reason.
And bury him under the porch.
What choice do we have?
They're two teenagers
who are getting seriously involved.
- Isn't it better to be safe than sorry?
- Its like giving them our blessing.
That's how I felt first, but like Angie
said, nature's gonna take its course.
Easy for her to say.
She's got the boy.
What if the condom breaks?
What if he forgets to put it on?
If he knocks Ana up,
who's gonna end up raising the kid?
God, that'd be awful.
Getting up for those 3:00 AM feedings
after you've worked all day?
Not me. You.
You'll end up
taking care of the baby.
You better convince her to keep her legs
crossed til she's outta this house.
Wait. How is this my problem?
She's your trampy niece.
Because if she gets pregnant,
I'll be in prison for killing
what's buried underneath the porch.
Mrs. D.!
I hope you don't mind
me just showing up, but
I thought about what you said,
and you were right.
It's never too late
to change your life, so,
- I quit Double D's.
- You did?
I was pretty scared at first, but now
I think it's the best thing I ever did.
That's great.
I never would've had the guts without
talking to you. You're my role model.
Really?
That's sweet.
My old role model was Candi,
down at the club, but she OD'd.
I will try to do Candi proud.
Good for you, Robin.
I know change
takes a lot of courage.
It sure does.
So what do I do now?
You know...
What's my next move?
Where do I work now?
I'm sorry.
You quit without having
anything else lined up?
I know it was a little hasty, but
you said I could do whatever I wanted.
You sounded so sure.
You're still sure, right?
I'm very sure.
The world is your oyster.
You have saved up, right?
She stripped for nine years
and didn't put anything away?
Apparently there was a boob job
and a bad relationship
and the rising cost of glitter.
- I have to find a way to help her.
- And why is this your responsibility?
Because I'm the one
that told her to quit.
I didn't think she'd listen.
No one listens to me.
I keep telling you how much
I hate that shirt, and there it is.
We'll help her.
What do you have in mind?
We need to find her a job.
What can she do?
Does she have skills
that don't involve picking up
a dollar without using her hands?
Why are you so sad?
I need a job,
and I don't have any skills.
You're so pretty.
You could be a princess.
Look.
MJ is so smitten with her.
He's a guy.
And she's good with kids.
That's it.
They've been looking for an assistant
art teacher down at the school.
She always wanted
to do something like that.
You think she can handle it?
We glue macaroni to shoeboxes.
It's not the hardest job in the world.
How come when I say that,
you give me that look?
And there it is again.
Thanks for cheering me up, MJ.
You're so sweet.
You can give me a bath
if you want to.
- You scared the crap out of me.
- Where's Orson?
- You're supposed to be watching him.
- Don't worry.
I stuck him in the laundry room
and put a broom through his spokes.
Can we please cross Roy off
the suicide watch list?
You're alive. My job's done here.
Where have you been? You were
supposed to be back an hour ago.
I am sorry, but I had to stop
and pick up our guests.
What guests?
Orson, meet Chris and Ron.
I know you won't listen to me,
but you might listen to them,
- since you have something in common.
- Really?
Are you Gilbert and
Sullivan fans, too?
Sense of humor.
That's very important.
I know there's no reason to go
on living, because you're paralyzed...
So you thought, "hey!"
"You know what might cheer him
up? Two more paralyzed guys."
Please. Just hear them out.
If you'll excuse me,
I'm going to make some tea.
So your wife tells us
you in a pretty negative place.
- That's to be expected but eventually,
- I know you mean well,
but I don't need
a handicapped pep talk.
We're not handicapped.
We're handi-capable.
Oh, Lord!
We play basketball, dance,
we make love.
And I hope
you're very happy together.
I, unfortunately, don't have
someone to join me on this journey.
You have a wife
who clearly loves you.
Paralyzed and blind. You must always be
the first one to board the plane.
We know what you're going through.
A lot of us feel unloved after
something like this happens.
You don't understand.
My wife stays with me solely
out of obligation.
- How could you say such a thing?
- It's true, isn't it?
You feel guilty because
I never would've been hit by that plane
if I hadn't gotten in
a fist-fight with your lover.
This is the thanks I get?
I have bent over backwards
to make your life easier.
I should just let you hang yourself.
Don't we have
a basketball game at 2:00?
Can you be honest for one moment?
You don't love me.
Yeah, we should go.
- Please stay. I've made tea.
- See?
You can't deny it.
Go ahead, Bree. Correct me.
Say you love me.
I...
care very deeply for you.
That's what I thought.
I'm feeling
a little upset right now.
Would you mind
rolling yourselves out?
Ana, let me ask you something.
Are you happy?
Why?
Well, Carlos and I
want you to be happy.
Over the last few months, we've come
to thing of you as our own daughter.
Really?
In fact, your uncle
thinks it's about time you
and I had that little talk...
about the birds and the bees.
That's how I feel,
so we're not gonna be doing that.
- Instead I'm gonna write you a check.
- A check?
A check big enough to cover one
whole year of modeling school...
and to rent a decent-size apartment...
in New York.
Okay, what's the catch?
That's so cute that
you think there's a catch.
- This isn't signed.
- That's the catch.
I will sign it once you graduate
high school without having had sex
or more sex, as the case may be.
Are you serious?
Ana, I could talk to you about morality
or saving yourself for marriage
or statistics about STDs,
But I think you're the kind of girl
who responds to cold, hard cash.
You know me well.
So do we hava deal?
Are you gonna be a successful
model with a nice apartment
or a teenage mom with no future?
Well...
When you put it like that...
Good girl.
And to answer your earlier question,
I'm now very happy.
I can't believe
I let you talk me into this.
Three hours of Shakespeare
for a woman who has to pee
every 20 minutes.
Dr. Graham's been so supportive of us.
Can't we be supportive of her?
This isn't about support.
This is about
little Tommy teacher's pet
wanting a gold star
for butt-kissing.
That's not true.
Nay, but this dotage...
Please.
You brought her a
40 dollar box of chocolates.
Last mother's day, you threw me a bagel
and called it breakfast in bed.
Admit it. You just have
a problem with her
because you hate it when
someone points out your flaws.
That's not true. I can take
constructive criticism justine.
- You're being a little loud.
- Sorry.
See? I can take
constructive criticism.
- You're still talking.
- You're still annoying. Relax.
She's making her entrance.
Grates me... the sum.
Nay! Hear them, Antony!
Fluvia Perchance is angry.
Or... who knows?
If the beard...
If the scarce-bearded Caesar
hath not sent you
his powerful mandate...
"Do this or this.
Take in that kingdom
and enfranchise that.
Perform it.
Or else we damn thee."
How was the play?
Lincoln had a better time
at the theater.
Really? So how bad was it?
You remember how horrible your
second grade arbor day play was?
But at least we were drunk for that.
Honestly,
how did Dr. Graham get that part?
Is she sleeping with the director?
Sleeping with, bathing, donating
a kidney... It's still not enough.
I just hope that I can erase this
from my memory before our next session.
Are you kidding?
We're not seeing her again.
Why not?
We're not going
to continue to take life lessons
from a woman who burped
during her death scene.
That has nothing to do
with her skills as a therapist.
Really? Did she not tell you
she has a "gift" for acting?
Well, I can't trust
the judgment of someone
with absolutely no self-awareness.
We're not going back.
This is an excuse.
You have been looking
for a reason to dump her
ever since our last session.
Tom, I learned two things tonight...
Dr. Graham has no insight
into real human behavior, and,
there are 428 tiles
on the ceiling of that theater.
Say what you want.
We are going to our next session.
And, by the way,
It was 429.
Robin Gallagher, teaching assistant,
reporting for duty.
- Look at you!
- I wanted to look professional.
Do you like the glasses?
I don't even need them.
You look great.
That's a beautiful suit.
Thanks. It is so nice
to wear work clothes
that don't rip away
to reveal crotchless panties.
Yeah, you're preaching to the choir.
So, I'm just gonna get
the kids started painting.
And why don't you hang those
globes that we made last week?
Can I say something?
You really took a chance on me. No one's
ever done that for me before, so,
thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm really glad you're here.
Careful.
Never let the kids see you cry.
If they sense weakness, you're done.
Sorry we're late.
Forgot his backpack.
That's okay, Mr. Linwood. Come on,
Kyle. Let's get you painting.
Who's that?
That's my new teaching
assistant, Miss Gallagher.
No, Bobby. That's not
how we use pipe cleaners!
I'm sorry.
Do we know each other?
I don't think so.
Are you sure?
You look so familiar.
I guess I just have
one of those faces.
What did you want to see me about?
You are aware, aren't you,
that as a private school,
we depend on the financial
support of our more
affluent parent donors?
I am aware of that.
Good.
Because I just got a call
from Kyle Linwood's father,
a major donor.
Is it true that your assistant
can break a 5 dollars
by shaking out her underwear?
- I don't want to take a bath!
- Well, that's too bad.
It's time to give the Earth
back some of its dirt. Go!
I'm gonna be upstairs for a bit.
What are you guys up to tonight?
We're just gonna stay home
and study.
Good girl.
Why are you getting me all worked up?
I thought you made your aunt a promise.
I promised her I wouldn't have sex.
I didn't promise you wouldn't.
Fine! I'll sort it myself!
- Don't freak out, okay?
- What the hell are you doing?
- I'm sorry. This won't happen again.
- It's no big deal.
You think you can come into
my house and do this?!
Answer me!
Answer me! Answer me!
I catch you near her again,
I will kick your ass, boy.
Let go of him!
You know what I caught
your son doing in my house?
- I don't care.
- Carlos, what is going on?!
I said let go!
Angie, what the hell?!
- Wait for me outside.
- Ma, please don't.
Outside!
Look, I came in and
found him on top of her.
I don't care. He's my kid.
You ever touch him again, you're dead.
I see you tried to separate
my glass and plastic.
Suck it, Earth!
Come on, ma. Let's go.
So maybe you shouldn't just think
about what you want to say
But about how you say it,
so Tom can hear you.
That's... a theory.
Is something bothering you?
It's the pregnancy.
This morning she got mad at me
over the way I drank my orange juice.
Is that all?
You know you're in a safe place here.
We can tell each other anything.
Since this is a safe place...
Tom and I saw your play
the other night.
You did? Well, why didn't you
come backstage and say hello?
Well, the truth is, I didn't
know what to say, because...
I didn't really like it.
I know.
Our Antony was dreadful.
You weren't the only one
who thought so.
Actually, I was talking about you.
You were...
really not very good,
and now I've sort of lost confidence
in you as a therapist.
Do you want to elaborate?
No. I think I said
what I needed to say.
See, this is the same thing
in your marriage.
You criticize Tom,
but you won't be specific. It's...
sort of the coward's way out.
Coward?
You sucked.
You were really, really bad.
Three words...
Stink, stank, stunk.
Specific enough?
Good for you, Lynette.
I commend you for your honesty.
Although, the Fairview Herald
had a different take.
They found my Cleopatra
"incandescent."
You actually believe that? See,
this is why we can't see her anymore.
You haven't weighed in yet.
What did you think?
I thought you were great.
What? Liar!
You said you've seen seals
playing horns that put on a better show.
There's no need to bully him
into agreeing with you.
I wouldn't have to bully him
if he would man up for once.
You're attacking.
Of course. Because I'm always
the bad cop, he's always the good cop.
Could you just once
not be such a wuss?
Damn right I'm the good cop.
Someone has to be,
because
bad cop-bad cop doesn't work.
I grew up in that house,
and it doesn't work.
That is not it.
You like me being the bad guy.
That way you can always be
the good guy. But guess what?
I'd love to be the good guy
once in a while, but I can't,
because when things get hard or
a difficult decision has to get made,
You run from confrontation,
and if I don't
step into the void,
things grind to a halt.
Because I got news for you...
Good cop-good cop doesn't work either!
You're right.
Really?
I like to be liked,
and because of that,
A lot of the ugly stuff
I defer to you.
And I'm sorry.
Your performance was
aggressively bad.
At one point during the second act,
I started to choke on a mint
and thought about not fighting it.
Thank you.
Well, this was quite a breakthrough.
And you're right.
You're a wonderful therapist.
Thank you, Lynette.
Now, both of you, get
the hell out of my office.
So we catch her son
on top of our niece,
- and we have to apologize?
- No, we have to apologize
because you almost put
her son's head through a wall.
When are you gonna learn
violence is not the answer?
I shouldn't have to tell you this!
You know better!
We've been doing it for 19 years.
You're smarter than this!
This is not the first time
we've had this conversation.
I feel like I'm talking
to a wall here, huh?
What is going on here?
What the hell is wrong with you?!
He's ripping Danny a new one.
- Damn it! Angie!
- Okay, Nick, just leave me
- alone!
- No... You are getting sloppy.
- We should go.
- Yeah, we should.
First you get into it with that
crazy lady about her recycling,
which I told you not to do.
And then guess what?
She comes over this morning
and she's thinking about suing us.
- I lost my cool.
- Get it back!
Cause this rock we are hiding under
is not that big, and if people
start poking around, we're done.
And then, bam! He fires her
for something she used to do.
It's so hypocritical. I mean,
why not get mad at the kid's father?
He obviously goes to Double D's.
I just hope I didn't get you into
any trouble, Mrs. D. I feel awful.
No. This is not your fault.
When I'm sad,
my mom gives me a big hug.
Down, Tiger.
What am I gonna do?
I have no money for rent.
I'm just gonna end up homeless.
You know, maybe I should go
and beg for my old job back.
No. You can't do that.
Quitting that place took a lot of guts.
How do you feel about
letting her move in here?
Julie's gone. We have her empty room.
It's just until she gets on her feet.
You're asking if I'm okay
with letting a stripper live with us?
- I'm gonna go with no.
- Why not?
I have no idea. I'm just really
sure this is a trick question.
She's a nice girl, and she's in trouble.
You know, I think of myself
as a good person
who cares about others, and,
how often do I actually
get to walk the walk?
This is an opportunity
to really help someone.
I want to do it.
Okay, let's go make ex-stripper
and a little boy very happy.
What's this for?
The Lackeys' 50th anniversary party.
Don't you remember?
I'm sorry. I thought
I'd be dead by now,
so I wasn't paying much attention
to our social calendar.
Well, regardless, you're going.
And if you're still around next Saturday
we've got brunch with my family.
Well, now you're just daring me.
Walter is about to make a toast.
Don't you want to hear it?
A speech about the joys
of wedded bliss?
Pass.
Walter and Shirley are about
to dance to a song
that was played at their wedding.
But before they do,
Walter would like
to say a few words.
I want to thank you all for coming.
50 years...
Would it hardly seems possible.
And now I'm not gonna lie to you
and say it's always been easy.
I mean, we've had
our share of tragedy and
we've said a few things
we wish we could take back.
But for the most part,
we've been lucky,
because no matter how old we get,
we've always been able to remember
what made us fall in love
in the first place, right, hon?
Stop!
Don't you dare throw yourself
in that pool!
I want to die.
Why can't you let me?
Because I want this, too.
I want a party like this someday
to celebrate our life together.
What is there about
our life to celebrate?
Look at Walter and Shirley in there.
I was watching them dance
with such passion in their eyes,
but I know they haven't
always been like that.
They've had their rough times,
too, but they stuck it out.
Because they're in love.
I asked you if you loved me,
and you couldn't answer.
Fine. I'll answer you now.
I loved you once.
Can I love you again?
I don't know.
But I...
would like to recapture
whatonce had.
And how can we do that
if you're not here?
So... I'm asking you...
Please stay.
In this never-ending
drama we call life,
everyone has a part to play.
Some are cast as romantic leads.
Others end up being the victim.
And a few always
provide comic relief.
And then
there are those
who end up playing the hero...
Especially if they feel
there's a villain...
who lives just across the street.