Well, I was driving
my car one night...
I crashed into
a utility pole.
And then to add
insult to injury,
I was electrocuted.
What can I say?
It was one of those days.
All my neighbors
heard it happen,
so they quickly left
their microwaved burritos...
and their expensive jars
of moisturizer...
and their racy
pay-per-view movies...
and they hurried outside,
excited to see
what all the ruckus was about.
But then,
when they saw it was me,
this weird thing happened.
For a moment,
no one moved or said anything.
They just stared.
And then...
Oh, my God.
All hell broke loose.
Does anybody know C.P.R.?
There's been an accident.
Edie!
Can you hear me?
Yes, everyone suddenly
became very concerned,
which was touching,
but ultimately pointless.
Moments before the ambulance
finally arrived,
I heard someone whisper...
Don't worry, Edie.
You're gonna get through this.
You're gonna be just fine.
Susan Mayer--wrong again.
Two seconds later, it happened.
With all of my neighbors
surrounding me,
I took my last breath.
The good news?
I died just like I lived--
as the complete
and utter center of attention.
Two days after I kicked
the proverbial bucket,
my husband asked my neighbors
to do me a favor.
You could tell
from the looks on their faces
It wasn't something
they... wanted to do,
But... they agreed to do it
anyway.
So the next day,
they piled into a car
with two thermoses filled
with coffee,
a basket filled
with baked goods
and an urn that was filled
with... me.
I hate
that we have to do this.
So you've said.
I mean, it really is the kind
of thing a relative should do.
Maybe it is, but we're
in the car, on our way there,
so stop your bitching.
Well, can you at
least put the radio on?
I won't feel like bitching if I
can sing along to something.
If you start singing,
I'll start bitching,
and you don't want that.
It's a 4-hour drive.
We have to do something
to pass the time.
Here's a thought.
Why don't we talk about Edie?
And say what?
I don't know, but she is
the reason we're on this trip.
Uh, maybe we could share
memories or tell stories.
Mm. Why don't you start
with the time
she tried to steal
your comatose boyfriend?
That was fun.
- Okay, I was thinking
of stories that put Edie
in a positive light.
And after that five minutes
is up, then what do we do?
The woman is dead, people.
Let's honor her memory.
Well, I'm all for saying
a few nice things...
but you were
never really friends.
You and Edie clashed
right from the start.
Yeah.
That's what everybody thinks.
But the the first time we met,
it seemed like we'd end up
being the best of friends.
Oh, that's disgusting.
No, it's okay.
It landed
on the detergent box.
Here.
You go buy yourself
a fresh doughnut
or booze, crack,
whatever eases the pain.
Just move it along.
Uh, you think I'm homeless.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, I live here.
I-I can prove it.
I know exactly
what's in this garbage bag.
Um, empty carton of eggs,
coffee grinds,
shampoo bottle...
Wart removal cream?
You're right. I'm homeless.
Susan Mayer. Oh.
It's all cleared up.
Mm. Edie Britt. I just
moved in down the street.
Oh, yeah.
I saw the moving van. Welcome.
Thanks.
So is it just you,
or do you have a family?
I have a son.
He lives with his dad.
It's a long story. I'll tell you
one day over a margarita.
You wanna invite me in
for a margarita?
How about coffee?
I just put on a pot.
Great.
You can fill me in on all
of the neighborhood gossip,
starting with the redhead
across the street
with the muffin basket.
That's a robot, right?
Funny and likes to gossip.
We're gonna get along just fine.
- Yes, we are.
Wait. Stop.
Could we just rest
for a second?
We've only gone four blocks.
Okay, I lied.
I hate running.
Well, why didn't you
say something?
We've been doing this for a week.
Because we were
starting to become friends,
and you like to run,
and I like to...
sit and...
one of us had to give.
Hi, Susan!
- Oh, hi, Helen, Ed.
I would have introduced you,
but once Helen starts talking,
she doesn't shut up.
Right. Ed told me that.
- Oh, you met Ed?
Oh, yeah. I've gotten
to know him quite well.
Yeah?
We're kinda...
doing it.
Doing what?
It.
Ed is married.
Yeah, I'm a naughty girl.
No, you're being immoral.
You're committing adultery.
Actually, Ed's committing
adultery. I'm just getting laid.
You know,
forget I ever mentioned it.
I can't forget
something like this.
Helen is my very good friend.
- I thought you just said that she was--
She is annoying, and I hide
when she knocks on my door,
but she does not deserve for you
to be wrecking her marriage.
Where are you going?
Home.
Oh, so you're not
gonna be my friend anymore?
I don't think so.
I thought
you didn't like running.
Well, it depends
on what I'm running away from!
Hi. I'm the whore
that lives down the street.
Could I borrow
a cup of condoms?
A cup? Are you sure
that'll be enough?
Look, I know
that you don't like me,
but I am here
to do you a favor anyway.
I was out to dinner
last night,
and I saw your husband
with another woman.
Really?
I feel bad saying it,
but if I were in your shoes,
I would want to know.
You're welcome.
Oh, I get it.
So you feel I judged you,
and for revenge,
you're trying to make me
insecure about my marriage.
If I wanted revenge,
I would have joined them
and made it a threesome.
You know,
Karl would never cheat,
And the woman he was with--
Brandi, his secretary,
and he took her out
for her birthday.
Oh, the old
"I'm taking my secretary
out for her birthday"
routine.
Hmm. Nice tip of the hat
to the classics.
Okay, well,
since you're on this moral roll,
why don't we walk
over to Helen's?
and I will introduce you.
We can have some tea,
And then you two
could swap stories
about
Ed's favorite positions.
What I do and what Brandi's
doing is completely different.
How?
I'm not looking to break up
anyone's marriage.
I'm in it for a little fun,
some free meals
and to help an unhappy man
through his midlife crisis.
Wow. You're just a giver.
Fine.
Use all of your energy
judging me
and ignore the real problem.
But let me
tell you something.
This is my area of expertise,
and I saw the look
in that woman's eyes.
She's not in it for the free
meals. She's in it for keeps.
You should leave now.
You know, Susan,
I'm trying
to help my neighbor out.
I thought it was
the moral thing to do.
Three weeks later,
I found Brandi's bra
in Karl's glove compartment,
and, well, you know the rest.
Say what you want about Edie,
she really understood men.
I should hope so.
After all those years of research...
I can't help thinking about
all the times Edie and I
sniped at each other.
We could have been
good friends.
Well, if she knew what
you're about to do for her,
she'd forgive you
for everything.
Okay, my hour's up.
Someone else hold Edie now.
Mm.
- I'll take her.
Kinda looks like cat litter.
Lynette, don't look at Edie.
Or what, I'll turn to stone?
She's all rough and gritty.
Uh, Gaby, before we learn
what Edie tastes like...
I got it.
I think a little more reverence
for the dead is in order.
Oh, please.
We're talking about Edie.
A little more irreverence
is what we need.
Give it.
Do you guys remember when you
took turns driving me to chemo?
Well,
none of you did it like Edie.
Hey, Lynette.
Hey.
How you feelin'?
Eh, same.
Well, here's the DVD
you asked for.
Thanks. I'll watch it during
chemo if I'm not too tired.
Here we go.
Oh, hi, Edie.
Hi. Ugh. What is that?
It's a health shake
of fermented brown rice,
and for her entrée,
a salad of radish,
burdock root and Bok Choy.
Mmm. What's for dessert,
waterboarding?
Thanks.
I can't get comfortable.
Could you fluff my pillows?
- Of course.
Well, I've got errands to run,
and I'll be back to
drive you to chemo.
Before you go, would
you put my socks back on?
My feet are cold again.
Oh, of course.
Katherine,
you have got stuff to do.
Why don't I take her
to chemo?
It's fine.
Okay.
See you tomorrow then.
Bye.
Okay, where's your coat?
Why? Chemo's not until 5:00.
Yeah, I've gotta make
a little stop on the way.
Edie!
- Whoo!
Been here before?
A couple of times.
You're gonna love it. Hey!
Love it? I have cancer.
I probably shouldn't even use
the ladies' room in this place.
Oh, there isn't a ladies' room,
so that's not a problem.
Um, I...
Edie, I have chemo
in half an hour.
Fine. Then we better start drinking.
- I'm not supposed to drink.
And they're not supposed to do
tattoos in the kitchen,
but I have a bald eagle
on my ass that says otherwise.
Two tequila shooters!
Hey, Edie!
Reggie! Oh, I thought
you were in Florida.
Nah. That was just a body
they identified as me.
Oh. Reggie,
this is my friend Lynette.
I'm trying to cheer her up
a little.
Right on.
You wanna shoot some stick?
Uh...
No, thanks.
Oh, come on.
You can totally take him.
No, I can't. Uh, see?
Cancer.
Oh. No sweat.
I'll play you one-handed.
Can you excuse us
for one second?
I need to go to chemo. I have--
- Cancer. Yeah, I heard.
And what do you want
from me?
I want you to fluff
your own pillows.
You need to start
fighting this thing.
I'm doing the best I can.
Oh, not even close.
Hell, Lynette, you--you are
the strongest person I know.
You're even stronger than me,
and that's saying something.
Now...
I may be a little out of line
bringing you here,
But you need to remember
who you are.
Screw cancer.
You are Lynette Scavo.
Two tequilas.
Now... where's that
one-armed friend of yours?
I'm--wanna shoot some stick.
Wow. It sounds like she gave you
just what you needed.
Good for Edie.
- She never let me forget it either.
She always insisted
it was the tequila shooters
that killed the cancer.
Oh, what the hell is that?
Oh, not now. We have a flat.
Maybe it's a sign we're not
supposed to do this today.
Nice try.
We don't have time for this.
Anybody know
how to change a tire?
You want to hand me that cross wrench?
- Do you wanna tell me what that is?
It's the T-shaped dealie
I'm gonna whack you with
if you don't hand it over.
You know,
Edie used to live around here
when she moved away
from Wisteria Lane.
You mean when you gals gave her the boot.
- Less yakkin', more jackin'.
Bree, how did you know
where she lived?
Um, I ran into her once,
unexpectedly...
in a place
I never thought I'd be.
Bree Hodge.
Follow me.
I'll get you situated,
and I'll bring
your husband in.
Is that the visitors' room?
Yeah. Why?
You don't happen to have
a private room, do you?
You mean, like an upgrade,
something with a couch
and softer lighting?
That would be lovely.
Oh.
You were being sarcastic.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you ready to--
Oh, not, uh, just yet.
It's not a bad idea,
having an upgrade available.
I bet that's a perk people
would be willing to pay for.
Ma'am, it's a prison.
The only perk we offer is
a cavity search.
Um...
To be honest,
I-I'm not feeling up to this.
I'm gonna have
to come back another day.
Fine. He's got another visitor
scheduled anyway,
so I don't even have to
tell him you were here.
Another visitor? Who?
Some lady.
She visits him every week.
Every week?
What's her name?
I can't give you that.
If she's visiting my husband,
I think I have a right to know.
Ma'am, I'm sorry,
but I cannot give you her name.
Really?
Because I would consider that
a perk worth paying for.
Well, well.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see you.
And you didn't
bring muffins?
It isn't
that kind of visit.
No muffins, no small talk.
Should I be scared
or grateful?
I stopped by
the prison today.
The guard tells me
you've been visiting Orson--
Sometimes twice a week,
she said.
Oh. Who knew lady prison guards
could be so chatty?
What are you up to, Edie?
I'm not up to anything,
you redheaded ice cube.
He's 15 minutes away.
And quite frankly,
I feel sorry for him.
After all, I know what it's like
to be exiled from suburbia.
So you're not...
Trying to start up something?
He's in jail.
My boobs are impressive,
but they can't bend iron bars.
Well...
Thank you for...
checking in on him
and for answering
my question.
I have a question.
Why aren't you visiting him?
Oh, well,
my schedule is just unreal,
what with the catering company
and looking after Benjamin.
Yeah, well, we're all busy.
Come on.
Why haven't you
been to see him?
That jail is...
it's disgusting.
All those men in cages,
like animals.
Even to step foot in that place
is humiliating.
That man
went to jail for you.
Do you have any idea
how much he must love you?
I do.
Then why can't you suck it up
once a month and go and say hi?
Try to help him get through
this living nightmare.
Why can't you do that?
Now as I think about it,
don't visit him.
He can do so much better
than you.
So... how are you doing?
How do you think?
You're right.
I shouldn't have asked.
I know it's horrible here.
How would you know?
You've never been.
You have every right
to hate me.
There's no need
to be melodramatic.
I meant for asking you
to come here,
for insisting
you turn yourself in.
Oh.
Now that I see this place,
I don't know what I was thinking.
You were thinking
I needed to take responsibility
for what I did,
and you were right.
But still, asking you to make
this sacrifice and not...
ever...
coming to see you...
How can you ever forgive me?
Just be there
when I get out.
I never told you about that
because... I was embarrassed.
Yeah, Edie Britt shamed you
into being a better human being.
That is embarrassing.
All right, ladies,
we're ready to ride.
Good. We got some ground
to make up.
I was hoping we would be able
to get there before dark.
How do you think he'll
react when we tell him?
How do you think?
I never thought Edie
would be cremated.
I figured she'd wanna be
pumped full of chemicals
and preserved.
Isn't that what she did
for the last 15 years?
My theory--
Edie knew if she was buried,
her true date of birth
would be carved into a tombstone
for all the world to see.
You really think
she spent a lot of time
thinking about her death?
Yeah, I do.
I spent a night with her
right after Carlos
and I got divorced.
Is this too red? I think
I need something pinker.
It's fine. Hurry up.
I want to get to the club while
this bikini wax is still fresh.
This is gonna be fun.
I can't believe we've never
gone out on the town together.
Well, we've never been single
together before.
Oh, I feel so sorry for all
those other girls in the bar.
Oh, so do I.
To be fair, we should
probably walk in backwards.
Oh, no, that won't work.
We're an unstoppable team.
Mm, the hottest chicks
on Wisteria Lane.
Oh, be nice.
There are lots of
attractive women on the street.
Like who?
How about Bree?
Uh, with that hair color,
you could stick
a red nose on her,
and she could join
the circus.
Lynette's beautiful.
Mm, for a baby factory.
And Susan?
- We're the hottest, okay?
Wow.
Too much?
No, it's great.
All right.
Come on. Let's go.
Wow! You were right
about this place.
Told ya. A lot of hotties,
very few "notties."
Ooh.
Ladies, this is
from the gentleman
at the end of the bar.
Oh, and I just sat down.
Well,
that's a personal best.
Actually, the drink's for her.
Oh.
Oh!
- It's pretty dark in here.
He probably didn't get
a good look at me.
Oh, Edie,
don't take it personally.
We're just different types.
You're right. Some like
tall, blonde and sexy,
And some men like...
that.
Now, now, Edie.
Don't be snarky.
We're both hot, remember?
Although, apparently,
I'm just a little bit hotter.
Well,
one guy might think so.
One guy
who's evidently intimidated
by full-sized
womanly breasts.
Hmm. Yes, I guess I am
a little on the small side.
That's the drawback
to having ones that are real.
What are you talking about?
These are real.
Oh, Edie, come on.
When you jump up and down,
the room moves more
than your boobs.
Well, someone obviously has
a chip on her shoulder.
I'd reach down
and knock it off,
but I can't go down that low.
Okay, you really think
you're hotter an me?
Let's just say that I have more
of what men want.
Yeah? Well, I have a vodka soda
here that says otherwise.
Ooh! So he bought you
one drink--
A well drink, I might add.
Well, it's one more
than you got.
Are you saying that I can't get
a man to buy me a cocktail?
Sure, you can,
just not as many as me.
One hour.
Whoever gets the most
swizzle sticks by the end wins.
See ya in an hour, loser.
# I know what boys
like, we know what guys want #
# I know what boys like,
we know what guys like #
# I make them want me #
# I like to tease them #
# they want to touch me #
# I never let them #
# I know what boys like #
# we know what guys want #
# boys like #
# boys like me #
# sucker #
# I know what boys like #
# we know what guys want #
# na-na na-na na #
Count 'em and weep, Solis.
Well,
I guess I could do that.
Or I could do this.
Ah.
I should make
some kind of speech.
But I think it's enough. We both
know I crushed you, right?
Now if you'll excuse me,
swizzle stick number 17
has a yacht and giant feet.
Whoo-hoo!
What the hell
were you thinking,
abandoning me
at a singles bar?
I'm sorry.
I just needed to be
by myself for while.
Why?
Don't tell me
you're depressed
because you lost
some stupid game.
I'm not depressed.
I'm surprised.
It's going by so quickly.
What is?
My youth.
The harder I try
to hold on to it,
the more it just...
slips through my fingers.
And all the makeup
and dim lighting in the world
can't seem to stop it.
Oh, please.
You're gorgeous.
And you are going
to stay that way forever.
Hmm.
That's the tricky part.
I'm not gonna be old.
What?
Ever since I was a child,
I've known that I was
never gonna see 50.
Oh, that's ridiculous.
No, it's true.
As far back
as I can remember,
a voice in my head said,
"live it up today,
'cause you're not gonna have
a lot of tomorrows."
You do realize
there's medication designed
to get rid of those voices?
It's not a bad thing,
Gaby.
It's actually a gift.
I...
appreciate my life
in a way
that most people don't.
I just didn't expect it
to go by this fast.
That's all.
Well, you know what?
I have a voice inside my head
that says you're wrong.
It tells me
that 50 years from now,
you and I will still be
wearing dresses too tight
and walking in heels too high
and going to bars
where we'll meet old geezers
who'll buy us drinks
with the last of
their Social Security checks.
If you say so.
Now come on.
Let's go to my house.
Let's pop open a bottle of wine
and toast to our future.
Why not?
Isn't that weird?
She knew
she was gonna die young.
What do you mean, you two were
the hottest chicks on the lane?
She called me
a baby factory?
Yeah, Gaby, in hindsight,
maybe you shouldn't have
told that part of the story.
Oh, pfft.
I think we're here.
So are we ready for this?
I don't know.
Can you ever be ready to tell
a boy that his mother is dead?
Hey, Travers.
Remember us?
Sure.
Wow. You brought
the whole neighborhood with you.
Did my mom come with you?
We brought you
some muffins.
You can share them
with your roommates
or maybe a favorite teacher.
What's going on?
Is my mom in trouble
or something?
Come here.
I'm afraid
we have some bad news.
Your mom was
in a very serious accident,
and I am so sorry...
but she passed away.
She died?
When?
A couple of days ago.
We've been trying
to get in touch with your dad,
but he's still
out of the country.
And your mom's new husband's
never met you,
so he thought it would be best
if we told you.
Wow.
If you'd like,
we could give you a moment.
No.
I'm okay.
Well, I have a class.
Uh, I'm sure the school
will understand
if you need
to miss a few days.
I don't need to do that.
I mean, I'm sorry she's dead,
but we weren't very close.
Still, she was your mother.
Technically.
But not a very good one.
Look, Travers,
we're all moms here.
We've all made mistakes
with our kids,
and what we count on is
when they grow up,
they'll forgive us.
- My mom didn't even try to raise me.
I mean, she just handed me
to my father and walked away.
How do you expect me
to forgive that?
Look, I'm sorry.
I don't mean to be rude,
but I'm gonna be late.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wait a second.
Travers, you need to know
something about your mom,
and I'm gonna tell you.
Now sit down.
I'd only known your mom
about a year
when she came over to my house
this one day.
Hey, Karen!
Your porch light's on.
Whoa. Sitting in your bathrobe
drinking,
and you didn't call me?
I kinda wanted to be alone.
Why?
It's the anniversary
of my son's death.
Ohh.
I'm sorry.
Every year
I think it'll get easier,
and it never does.
Nothing worse
than losing a child.
In a way, you're kinda lucky
you don't have any.
Actually, I do.
What?
Mm, I have a son.
You lived here a year.
How do I not know this?
Because he lives
with his father.
When I got divorced,
I gave him full custody,
so I kinda know
how you feel.
I mean,
we've both lost kids.
No.
I lost a kid.
You gave yours away.
And you have the nerve
to tell me you know how I feel?
I gave him up because
I wanted to protect him.
From who?
From me.
You know, I tried to be
a good mom. I really did.
But I know myself.
And if he...
if he was
gonna grow up normal,
he needed to get away
from me.
What a cop-out.
I think
you're just being selfish.
You know, trust me, Karen,
there is nothing
that you could say
to make me think less
about myself than I already do.
But if it gives him
a chance, it's worth it.
Aren't you afraid
he's gonna hate you?
I love him enough
to let him hate me.
Well, I hope you're not
making a big mistake.
Well...
me, too.
So I'm not defending
everything she did, Travers,
but you have to know,
she loved you,
more than you can imagine.
I really need
to get to class.
Bup, bup, bup.
I believe I called shotgun.
God,
she is so good at that.
She should be.
She's been doing it
since she rode shotgun
on an actual stagecoach.
Hey. Hey.
I realized...
I never thanked you
for coming all the way out here
just to tell me.
That was really cool of you.
We felt we owed it
to your mom.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe we forgot.
What?
We, uh...
Also came to give you
your mom's ashes.
We thought you might
wanna scatter them somewhere.
Unless that's a little...
weird for you.
Why don't you guys take 'em?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
You were her best friends.
I'm sure you could think
of the perfect place to put her.
Okay, we're here.
Guys...
wake up.
Guys?
We're home. Get out.
Lord, Lynette. You nearly
gave me a heart attack.
Yeah, I'd like to see Edie
again, but not tonight.
Oh, I think my leg's asleep.
Actually, that's my leg.
Get your hand off.
Lynette, thank you again
for driving.
You bet.
- Hold it.
We still gotta figure out where
we're gonna spread the ashes.
Now it's gotta be someplace
that was meaningful to Edie.
Well, Edie once told me she lost
her virginity in a cow pasture.
If we can
find that exact field...
we'd find a lot
of traumatized cows.
Do we really need to do
this tonight? They're ashes.
It's not like
they're gonna go bad.
Fine. We'll talk tomorrow.
Oh, Edie, what are
we gonna do with you?
Subtle as always, I see.
This was a wonderful idea,
Karen.
It wasn't exactly mine. Now be
careful. You're spilling Edie.
Urn is empty.
Let's do it.
Shouldn't we say something
first?
Like what?
I don't know.
A few words describing
how we felt about her?
I don't think Edie would want us
to get all sappy.
Well, I think if we're quick
about it, she'd be fine.
Mm.
Here's a thought--
We all say one word that sums up
what we thought of her.
And then we dump her?
- Then we dump her.
Just one word. This is hard.
Mm.
Okay, I got one.
I'll go first.
Edie Britt was sexy.
Perceptive.
Strong.
Beautiful.
- Mm-hmm.
I need four words.
Ay.
Okay. I want to do Edie justice,
and for that to happen,
I need four words, okay?
Edie would so not be surprised
you're ruining this moment.
Go ahead, Susan. What are
your four words for Edie?
One of a kind.
Now it's time.
And that is
how Wisteria Lane came to be
my final resting place.
My ashes were spread over grass
I had once walked on...
beneath trees that had
once given me shade...
on top of roses
I once admired...
and beside fences
I once gossiped over.
And after my friends had
finished saying good-bye,
a wind came along and took what
was left of me into the air.
As I looked down on the world,
I began to let go of it.
I let go of white picket fences
and cars in driveways,
coffee cups
and vacuum cleaners.
I let go of all those things
which seem so ordinary,
but when you put them together,
they make up a life...
a life
that really was one of a kind.
I'll tell you something--
It's not hard to die
when you know you have lived,
and I did.
Oh, how I lived.
Subtitles by LeapinLar