Previously
on Desperate Housewives...
This thief was trying
to steal your truck!
You're the guy who's four months
behind on his payments?
Mike reluctantly borrowed
money from Carlos.
Tell me how much you need.
Andrew did his homework.
I made a few calls.
Turns out the golden child
never got his degree.
I left school when the doctor
told me my mother was terminal.
I can save you a phone call
and bring in her death certificate.
That's okay.
The worst mistake I ever made
in my life was having you!
A killer...
Got an invitation.
We would like it if you
would move in with us.
And Angie revealed her past.
I got involved with a really
bad guy... Danny's father.
Many years ago,
a terrorist fell in
love with a woman.
This woman believed in the terrorist
and his cause...
Until an undercover Agent showed up,
determined to stop them.
The terrorist wanted to attack
those he felt
were hurting the planet,
so he got the woman
to help him build a bomb.
But something went wrong,
and someone was killed.
The terrorist didn't care.
He said it was unavoidable.
The woman wanted to turn herself in,
but she was pregnant.
So the Agent convinced her
to run away with him,
and he'd raise the child as his own.
So they escaped from the terrorist,
hoping and praying
he would never find them.
Unfortunately...
he did.
If it isn't double
cappuccino, extra hot.
You know me so well.
Just made chocolate scones.
Interested?
What the hell...
Might as well live dangerously.
- So, how's the novel comin'?
- Almost done.
Endings are a bitch.
I really need
to surprise my audience.
I know you're my dad...
but you still gotta close
the door when you come in.
Sorry.
I was gonna ask you somethin'.
You wanna join
your old man for a run tonight?
Dad, you don't run. You jog.
And no.
Come on. I'll be going by the park.
It'll be real pretty.
I'm working Eddie's shift tonight.
I'm gonna be here late.
But I am proud of you.
Keep it up.
Thanks, coach.
See you at home.
That's your dad?
I should have introduced you.
You'd like him.
I bet I would.
- So he's a runner?
- Every night, even when he's sick.
You can't stop him.
He's pretty inspiring.
Inspiring?
Don't guys your age
usually hate their dads?
We've had our issues.
But my dad's sacrificed
a lot for me.
I figure this is how I pay him back.
You're right.
Payback's really important.
- All right, back in a bit.
- How long are you gonna be?
Just long enough to get
a little sweaty.
You be careful.
It took the terrorist 20 years
to find the people
who had betrayed him.
What the...
And his plan for revenge...
was just getting started.
Synch: Wisteria Team
Transcript: Addic7ed
www.wisteria-team.fr
www.sous-titres.eu
Our mothers tell us
to beware of mysterious men.
Don't talk to them in the park.
Don't take their candy.
Don't get into their cars.
And whatever you do...
Don't let them into the house.
But what do we do when mother
has already invited them in?
Eddie, what have you done?
I saw you were running low on supplies,
so I went to the store for you.
You didn't need to do that.
You're cool enough to take me in.
I gotta earn my keep somehow.
I bought fresh vegetables.
Now you're just
trying to make me cry.
Is that the laundry? I'll get that.
That's okay. It's Porter's turn.
I can't, mom. I'm late.
You can spare five minutes
to put clothes in the dryer.
I can't. Jeremy and Dave
are waiting to take me to the mall.
You are not leaving wet
clothes in that washer.
Mom, chill. It's water.
Don't talk to your mother like that.
That's my ride. I gotta go.
After the laundry.
What a bitch.
- Tell her you're sorry.
- Get off me!
Apologize!
- He shouldn't talk to you like that!
- I'm sure he's very sorry.
Stop it! Stop! Let him up.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
Go join your friends.
Go on.
I'm sorry.
I just can't watch
you be disrespected.
I'll take care of the laundry.
- Hey, Carlos. Here's the money...
- for the church raffle!
Thanks, Mike! Now sister Mary
can finally replace her wooden...
Gaby's home.
Sorry. I just wanted to bring you
the first payment for the loan.
- Thanks again. You really saved my ass.
- No problem.
Just so you know, I'm making a lot of
cutbacks so I can pay you back quicker,
no vacations, basic cable.
I even convinced MJ
that Mrs. McCluskey's house
is summer camp.
Don't go crazy.
Just pay it back when you can.
- Let's make sure Gaby doesn't find out.
- So she can tell Susan?
- No problem.
- I gotta get going.
And give my best to sister Carrie.
Mary.
I know, right?
It's the middle of the afternoon.
What are you doing?
Why don't you come
upstairs and find out?
- No, thanks. I can't afford it.
- What?
Every time you
offer me afternoon sex,
it's because you want something,
and it is not afternoon sex.
All right, fine. Check this out.
Where were you even hiding this?
That is a ski chalet in Aspen.
It's for sale, and I want it.
- Sorry, hon, not gonna happen.
- That was just my opening offer.
What if I see your afternoon sex
and raise you...
honeymoon sex?
I can't. All of our cash
is tied up in a business deal.
- What kind of deal?
- You don't want me to bore you
- with the details.
- Half that money is mine. Bore me.
This conversation is over.
Now if you're interested
in going upstairs
and making love to your husband
simply because you...
Like it?
I've been practicing all day.
Why is there a
big-ass piano in our house?
Actually, big-ass
stopped making pianos.
This is a Yamaha.
So I'm...
curious...
How much did this thing cost?
It was free.
You remember dear, sweet,
98-year-old aunt Regina?
The one you called
"the crypt keeper"?
That was okay when she was alive.
Now she's a dead lady giving us
really cool stuff, so a little respect?
Okay.
As long as it was free.
But as far as Gaby's concerned,
it cost 30 grand.
What? Why?
I love Gaby, but for years,
she has been flaunting how much
they spend on her house
and her car and her jewelry.
And this
is my turn to flaunt,
and I can't flaunt
with a free piano.
Don't stoop to her level.
You're better than that.
No, I'm really not.
I'm not kidding. You're not telling
Gaby we paid for this piano.
Please. This is my chance.
My aunt had a stroke while driving!
When am I ever
gonna get that lucky again?
You're not gonna believe this.
They're out of cilantro.
How can a market be out of cilantro?
I don't know, but I told that clerk
she should hang her head in shame.
As well you should.
- What else do we need?
- Let's head over to the kosher aisle.
I need a few items
for the Schwartzman Bar Mitzvah.
We need baking soda. I'll get it.
- Please. Not now.
- What are you even doing here?
I lost my job.
I had to work someplace.
You already got the baking soda.
I would lose my head
if it wasn't screwed on.
Who's that woman?
Nobody. Someone I used to know.
Is everything all right?
I was telling her that
it doesn't make sense
for a store this big to
run out of a major herb.
- We should check out Hudson's market.
- That's downtown.
We need cilantro, don't we?
Come on.
You brought me flowers.
I wanted to get you
a T-shirt that said, "I'm a moron
who wears dark clothes when I run
at night," but the gift shop was out.
Who did this to you?
Did you see 'em?
What kind of person hits
you and then just drives away?
Maybe the kind of person
who wanted to hit me.
Wait. You said you didn't see them.
I didn't, but, Ange,
I'm telling you, this guy...
he drives past me,
he turns around and
swerves right into me.
- Where's Danny?
- He fell asleep in the waiting room.
We've been here all night.
You want me to get him?
I need you guys to go home,
grab the IDs,
some money, whatever
you can stuff in a couple of bags.
But you're not exactly
travel-ready, Nick.
- Absolutely not.
- The place we talked about,
near Carbondale.
Just for a few weeks.
Not without you.
I'll send Danny.
But you and me...
- this is as far as we run.
- What if it is Patrick?
What are we gonna do?
We've been asking that
question for 20 years.
I guess now we're gonna find out.
Can I talk to you a minute?
Sure.
It's about what
happened with Porter.
- Are you mad? You're mad.
- No, I'm not.
You want me to leave.
No, I just want to talk.
You looked like
you really wanted to hurt him,
and I kind of need to know
what that's about.
Your family doesn't seem
to care how much you help them.
You're a great mom,
and they just push you around.
It made me angry.
Yes, I saw that.
And sometimes my family
can be unappreciative.
But what happened today
can never happen again.
I know.
Listen, I grew up
with an alcoholic mother.
I know what it like to be
angry all the time.
But when I was your age,
I had to find a way...
to control myself.
How did you do that?
A lot of help.
One thing... I had a great
counselor at school,
and she taught me
that whenever I was
about to lose it,
that I should do this...
One.
Two.
Three.
That really works?
It really does.
It gives you a chance
to step back,
feel like you're in control.
You should try it next time.
You'll see.
I'm really sorry about what I did.
It's fine.
Just don't ever do it again.
But thank you for wanting to.
Come on, Larry. You're my business
manager too.
I am not leaving this
office until you tell me
what Carlos is doing
with my ski house money.
Gaby, you're putting me in
an uncomfortable position.
- You should talk to Carlos.
- I did!
I offered myself in a very uncomfortable
position, and he still said no.
I'm sorry, but Carlos
swore me to secrecy.
Please respect that.
You're right. I'm sorry.
- No hard feelings.
- Of course not.
What are you doing?
I don't want to be a liar.
When I go home,
and I'm in tears and Carlos asks me
why, and I say you grabbed my ass,
I want to be telling the truth.
Well played.
Carlos gave $50, 000
to one of your neighbors.
What?! Who?!
A Mike Delfino. Apparently,
his business is in big trouble.
Mike's wife is one of my closest
friends, and she never said a word.
- Poor thing.
- Please don't tell Carlos I told you.
Of course.
I should get going.
- Do you have parking validation?
- Those are only for employees.
Okay, you could take mine.
Hotel, food, incidentals...
$300.
You can order pay per view.
I don't even care if you buy beer.
Just stay in your room
as much as you can.
This is stupid. It's been 20 years.
Have you actually seen or heard
from this Patrick Logan guy?
Do you know for a fact
that he's even still alive?
- I'm not gonna debate this with you.
- If he started this group you were in,
then isn't he on the run, too? He's got
bigger problems than getting revenge.
Just humor me.
Because if I'm wrong,
all I am is wrong.
But if I'm not...
Please. Just humor me.
I saw you the other day,
talking to my friend Sam.
I'm Bree, by the way.
I know who you are.
This is none of my business,
but I noticed that there was some
tension between you two.
You could say that.
Well, I hope everything is okay.
What is it you want?
I don't know. There was just
something so odd about that...
encounter.
I don't understand why
he would talk to a friend like that.
Maybe that's because
I'm not his friend.
I'm his mother.
My manager said I could
take a break early.
You've got five minutes.
Are you aware that Sam goes around
telling people that you're...
dead.
- Yes, I heard.
- Why would he do that?
He's a complicated boy.
Did Sam tell you who his father was?
He told me about your
relationship with my... husband,
if that's what you're referring to.
Did he also mention
the letter that Rex sent to me?
What letter?
It was after you were married.
Rex had just started
his practice, and,
apparently,
the money was pouring in.
Rex wrote
and told me
he could give Sam a better life.
He then asked for full-time custody.
I'm guessing he never told you that.
Must have slipped his mind.
I politely declined his offer.
And did Sam... know about this?
Not until a few months ago,
when he found the letter.
And when he realized that he
could have lived all those years
with his dad in a fancy house...
He... was beyond livid.
Even so, how could he go around
pretending that you're dead?
Like I said...
He's a complicated boy.
I just got back from the supermarket
and realized I bought way too much.
I'm afraid some of it's gonna go bad,
so I thought, who could I give this to?
And I randomly thought of you.
You're afraid that canned peaches
and condensed milk are going to go bad?
Well, it's just, my
cupboards are cluttered,
and you'd be doing me a huge favor.
Thanks.
As long as you're here,
I want to show you something.
We just got it.
MJ is gonna take lessons.
You sure you don't want to
start him off with,
say, a used upright?
No way.
Me wan-ny, me like-y, me get-ty.
May I ask how much this cost-y?
Well, Mike doesn't like
me throwing around numbers,
but let's just say
your jaw would drop...
30,000 times.
- Wha...
- That's one.
This is none of my business, but,
is this really the best time
to buy something this expensive?
I mean, didn't Mike just
have his truck repossessed?
Things finally turned around.
He got a big cash infusion.
You don't say.
Anyway, I know you
guys don't have a piano, so,
if you ever want the girls
to take lessons...
Well, thank you. I gotta go.
Enjoy your peaches.
You owe me $50,000.
- What?
- For your information,
Mike's "big cash infusion"
cost me my ski house.
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb. Carlos loaned Mike
the 50 grand, and you know it!
Why are you looking
like you don't know it?
He told me...
business picked up.
He lied, just like Carlos lied to me
about where our money went,
which you went and spent on a piano.
No, I didn't...
I inherited it.
I was trying to make you jealous.
Honey, given different circumstances,
that so would have worked.
This is unbelievable.
I have the money from the strip club
sitting in the bank,
and Mike would rather
borrow it from you guys?
I'm about to screech at my husband.
You might want to stand back.
I have a better idea.
There you are.
- How was the flight?
- Horrible.
It was delayed, there was turbulence,
they ran out of food,
and I'm not seeing a plate
covered with tinfoil here.
There was one, but one of our
50 children must have inhaled it.
Damn it!
- Okay, calm down.
- Lynette, no. I'm hungry.
You know, when you were working,
I always had food waiting for you.
That's right. You were very
considerate in your eighth month.
I'm sorry. I keep forgetting,
you're the only person
- who's ever been pregnant before.
- Relax. Relax.
We'll just order a pizza.
And wait an hour?
Forget it. I'll fend for myself.
Six, seven,
eight, nine...
It's okay. I'm fine.
There's nothing in here.
- You didn't go to the store today?
- 16... 17...
- You might wanna take it down a notch.
- I have been in three cities
in two days. You'd think you'd find
the time to go to the market.
- 21, 22...
- What the hell is he doing?
Eddie, it's okay.
- 23, 24, 25, 26, 27...
- Tell him to stick a sock in it.
You need to kiss me. Here.
Okay, there. We're good.
We're good. He loves me.
He loves me.
We'll talk about it later.
So Eddie attacked our son?
Okay, I'd use "attack"
but with a small "a".
Okay, that's it. I want him out,
and that's with a big "O".
Look, Eddie is not some
exchange student from France.
He comes from an abusive home.
We have to accept he has some...
baggage.
So I have to wonder if he's gonna punch
me any time I raise my voice to you?
I am not sending him back
to live with that woman, Tom.
How about therapy? That might help.
Now we're gonna pay for his therapy?
Okay, here's a thought.
How about we all stop yelling at me?
What a concept...
Be nice to Lynette.
Fine.
We'll try the therapy.
All these weeks, Sam has been going on
about how his mother was dead,
and the whole time, she has been
at Howe's market, in a smock,
stacking cans.
I guess my instincts about Sam
were right, wouldn't you say?
What did I say about gloating?
Something. I wasn't listening.
I was thinking about how right I was.
- Okay, I'll stop. I know you're upset.
- You have no idea.
When Sam first showed up, I felt
like I got a little piece of Rex back.
It was wonderful.
But this has forced me
to remember that
Rex was a liar, too.
Sorry. Am I interrupting something?
Orson, would you please excuse us?
Of course.
Everything all right?
Actually, Sam...
Wait, wait. Still here.
I went back
to the supermarket today.
I take it you met my mother.
Why did you say she was dead?
She is dead... to me.
So you admit that you lied?
Did she tell you
I found a letter my father wrote,
begging her
to let me come live with him?
That's hardly an excuse.
I was 4.
He said he could give me all
the advantages she couldn't,
but she wouldn't let him.
She loved you. She
wanted you by her side...
She should have wanted more for me!
Andrew got bicycles for Christmas
and TVs for his birthday.
I had to sit in a trailer and
do my homework with mittens on
because my mom couldn't
afford to pay the heating bill.
If she had loved me, she would have let
me live the life that I was entitled to!
I'm...
going to...
talk to the... Schwartzmans
about their Bar Mitzvah.
If you want to go over the
menu later, let me know.
- How'd it go?
- Kind of weird, but it was okay.
I think you did very
good work today, Eddie.
Now the restroom is down the hall,
second door on the right.
I'll be here.
So you said "good work".
Does that mean it went well?
That means Eddie's got some issues,
and it's going to take
time to work through them.
Okay... how much more
time at $130 an hour?
Well, it would go a lot faster
if we could get his mother in here,
but he seems to think there's
no way she'd agree to that.
Really? If you think it'll help,
I can get her in here.
That would be great.
Okay, and then...
and then
everything will be okay, right?
Let's just get the mother in here.
Barbara?
It's Lynette Scavo.
Barbara,
we need to talk about Eddie.
Are you looking
for Barbara Orlofsky?
- Yeah. Do you know where she is?
- No. Nobody's seen her for days,
and her car's still there.
It's weird.
There's this crazy rumor going around
that you've got something for me.
Just an apology.
Well, as long as it comes
with one of your muffins,
I may just accept it.
Orson told me about Sam.
You were right from the start.
I never should have trusted him.
I don't even need the muffin now.
Now that that's settled,
what are we gonna do about Sam?
That's easy. We get rid of him.
I don't think
it's gonna be that simple.
Why not?
I saw a side to him last night
that I've never seen before, and,
to be perfectly honest...
I'm afraid of him.
Hi, Susan! Thanks for
having us over for dinner.
Well, actually,
dinner was just an excuse.
I wanted to show you something.
You bought a piano?
And I wanted you
to be the first to see it.
That looks... pricey.
$30,000,
plus delivery and tax
and a biannual tuning fee.
But Mike's on his way down.
Do me a favor.
Don't let on
you know how much it cost.
- Why not?
- He thinks it's ostentatious,
and he's a little embarrassed.
In fact, he keeps telling everyone
that I inherited it from my aunt,
so just go with it.
Hey, guys. Sorry I'm late.
That's okay, honey.
I'm gonna check on dinner.
We're gonna check on dinner.
Dude, we need to talk.
A piano?
Don't worry about it, we didn't buy it.
Susan inherited it from her dead aunt.
Without even blinking.
Would anyone mind
helping me set the table?
- Carlos will do it.
- Great.
And, Mike, maybe you and Gaby
can get the wine.
So you and Carlos have any big plans
for the summer? You taking any trips?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Look, if you need to talk...
Susan's in the other room.
I think Carlos is having an affair.
What? Why would you think that?
Because he's been acting
really secretive lately.
And I went to talk to
our business manager,
and I discovered $50, 000
was missing from our account.
Well, I'm sure
there's a good explanation.
Yeah, there is.
It's called fancy dresses and
hotel rooms for some bimbo.
No, no, no. I am sure
that you've got that all wrong.
Wait a minute.
Are you covering for him?
Because I stole his cell phone
to see who he was talking to,
and he called your house,
like, a hundred times.
- He hasn't been talking to me.
- Really?
Well, the next time
he's not talking to you,
you might want to give him
the name of your divorce lawyer.
I'm so glad you guys were free tonight.
We've been wanting to do this for...
- What's wrong?
- My earring. It's missing. Damn it!
- I just got them today.
- I'm sure it's somewhere.
Here it is.
That would have been
3 grand out the window.
- You bought $3,000 earrings?
- Of course not.
Mike did.
He's so generous,
especially now that we're loaded again.
You know, Carlos,
I never noticed before...
you have a really veiny forehead.
- Buddy, we got a bit of a problem.
- No kidding.
Wait, you know?
Did Gaby say something?
No. I heard it all from Susan.
Well, it's not surprising, the way those
two talk, but luckily, it's not true.
Come on, Mike. Let's stop the lies.
It is true, we both know it.
- It is?
- Don't act surprised.
God, this whole thing was a mistake.
I never should've written that check.
You paid for it?
Oh, man.
Dinner is ready.
- Everything smells so good.
- Thanks.
You want some meatballs, Carlos?
I've got two nice,
big ones for you right here.
Nope. I'm fine.
I saw that.
Saw what?
You leering at Susan's breasts.
I was looking at the pasta.
Susan's breasts
- just happened to be hovering nearby.
- Gaby, leave Carlos alone.
Oh, my God. It's you.
- Excuse me?
- You're the one
- Carlos is having an affair with.
- What?
What?
Makes perfect sense. That's why
there were all those phone calls
- to this house from his cell phone.
- You looked at my cell phone?
Yes, and thank God I did.
Whore!
Shamelessly shoving your meatballs
in my husband's face.
There was no shoving.
Sometimes they spontaneously heave.
Have you lost your mind?
I am not having an affair with Susan.
Mike, you believe me, right?
Yeah... I guess.
It's just... why are you
calling over here all the time?
I'm not! I always call your cell!
Susan, say something.
Forget it, Carlos.
We might as well confess.
Confess what?!
You wouldn't take my money
when you were in trouble, and,
well, I've always known
that Carlos had a thing for me, so,
I told him that I would sleep with him
if he would loan you money.
You son of a bitch!
I didn't touch her. All I did was help
a friend who screwed me over buying
diamond earrings and grand pianos.
I told you, the piano was a gift
from Susan's aunt!
You bought diamond earrings?
With the $50, 000
that you borrowed from Carlos.
You know?
So you two were just...
Screwing with you, yes.
So tell me, Mike,
do you feel betrayed, humiliated?
Good. Because I only did this
to show you what it feels like
when the person that
is supposed to love you the most
lies to you.
I just did it
cause I want a ski chalet.
I just keep trying
to think what I can say
so you'll know how sorry I am.
Well, I do know,
and I'm not looking
for another apology.
What I am looking for is your word
that you will never
freeze me out like this again.
I swear.
Good.
So is this everything?
You sure you don't want me
to walk you through it?
I just want to get a sense
of where we stand.
If I have any questions,
I'll ask you later.
Why are they putting
you in a coma on purpose?
Your brain seems fine. It's not
like you think you're Napoléon.
You don't think
you're Napoléon, do you?
There was some swelling
when they brought me in. Now it's...
pushing against my skull.
They say this is gonna relieve it.
- So how long are you gonna be out?
- A couple of days.
And you know where you're gonna be?
With Danny.
Actually, I was thinking
about bringing him back.
No way.
It's been three days.
Nothing's happened.
I'm starting to think
you were wrong.
We're not taking any chances.
You know what? If I gotta drive you
out of town myself, I'm gonna do it.
If it'll keep you
from killing yourself,
I will go stay with Danny.
Thank you.
You're easy to get along with,
you know that?
You don't seem surprised to see me.
Don't bother running upstairs.
I already found your gun.
Come on.
After all this time, there's gotta be
something you want to say to me.
Go to hell.
Couldn't you come up with
something more original than that?
I guess all this suburban living
forces you to think in clichés.
So it was you.
You ran over Nick.
Would you believe me
if I told you it was an accident?
I sent Danny away.
You will never find him.
That's okay.
We're not that close,
seeing as how you stole him from me.
Are you gonna kill me?
I need you alive.
You are gonna do me a favor.
What kind of favor?
Can we discuss it in the morning?
I've had an exhausting couple of days,
what with searching your house
for firearms and running down
Dudley douche bag.
So...
- which way to the guest room?
- You think I'm gonna let you stay here?
How are you gonna stop me?
If you call the cops,
they'll arrest you and lover boy.
Aren't you afraid
I'll kill you in your sleep?
If the last 20 years
have taught us anything,
it's that you're not
comfortable killing people.
And if you decide to run away,
just make sure you stop by the hospital
and say good-bye to Nick, because,
he won't be around much longer
after you've gone.
Patrick, please, don't hurt him.
Just do what I tell you, baby,
and I'll let you both live.
Mysterious men...
they make promises
they have no intention of keeping.
They tell lies
to get what they want.
They may be more dangerous
than they seem.
Yes,
our mothers told us we cannot trust
the men we don't know.
And those we do know?
Well,
we can't always trust them either.