-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
lost 第4季第11集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：个人id 校对：个人id
时间轴：jimmyvan
* everyday,
it's a-gettin' closer *
* goin' faster
than a roller coaster *
* love like yours
will surely come my way *
* a-hey, a-hey, hey
* everyday,
it's a-gettin' faster *
* everyone said,
"go ahead and ask her" *
* love like yours will...
where do you think you're going?
out.
with who?
him?
yes, and you can't stop me.
i'm in love.
he's twice your age,
emily.
so what, mom?
are you jealous?
emily, wait a minute.
emily, listen to me!
emily!
get back here, young lady,
right now!
you can't stop me! i love him!
emily! emily-
aah!
honey?
honey, can you hear me?
that's good.
d y antrstay awake now.
must be internal.
keep it steady. out of the way. pulse!
she's bleeding. her heartbeat's
dropping fast. i'm pregnant.
what? what did you say?
i'm pregnant.
i'm five-
i'm almost six months.
she-she's pregnant.
get the clamps ready.
that's it, emily. good girl.
baby's crowning.
she's crowning.
dilated and ready to go.
here we go. that's it.
okay, sweetheart.
all right, there you go.
wrap you up nice and warm.
we'll just take you
over here now.
margaret, would you put him in
for me, please?
my baby.
it's a boy, honey.
he's okay for now.
he's just real early.
can i hold him?
i'm sorry, sweetheart.
he's just too little.
we have to take him away now.
but...
name-name him john.
please!
his name is john!
who builds a cabin in
the middle of the jungle anyway?
that's a good question.
so? how about answering it?
i don't know.
and why are
we even going there?
because hopefully,
the man who lives in the cabin
can tell us what to do
about the people
who are trying to kill us.
we've been walking all day.
are we gonna get there soon?
how long?
i don't know.
i've been following him.
what? what do you mean,
you've been following him?
i'm not even in front. i have
no idea where the cabin is.
hugo's the last one who saw it.
oh, this is just awesome.
what do you think
we should do, john?
we're making camp.
what?
here in the dark
with the monster and... him?
well,
the rest will do us good.
dude, what's gonna happen when
those freighter guys come back?
i don't know...
yet.
desmond.
the helicopter's here.
all right,
get him on the litter.
careful with him!
get him down over there.
be careful.
okay, guys, unload it.
come on. pick it up.
pick it up. let's go.
what did this to him?
a black pillar of smoke
threw him 50 feet in the air...
ripped his guts out.
what?
i need you to tell me
exactly how many people
are on that island and where
every single one of them is.
and why would i do that?
keamy!
what the hell do you think you're
doing, mate? you gave me up.
what? linus knew who
i was. he knew my name.
he knew everything about me.
no, i'm not the one
who gave you up.
then who did?
aah! oh! oh!
ohh!
do you know who i am?
what?
my name.
do you know my name?
keamy.
martin keamy.
did you give it to him?
who? benjamin linus
- did you give him my name?
yeah.
wait. wait!
martin, no!
martin, we need him.
he's the only one
who can fix the engines.
and what makes you
so sure about that?
because he's the one
who broke them.
hello there.
who are you?
i'm horace. whew!
and what are you
doing out here?
oh, building a place-
a little getaway
for me and the missus.
no, i mean,
sometimes you need a break
from the d.i., you know?
the dharma initiative?
i'm not making any sense,
am i?
no.
that's probably because
i've been dead for 12 years.
hello there.
you gotta find me, john.
you gotta find me.
and when you do,
you'll find him.
who?
jacob.
he's been waiting for you
a real long time, man.
i'm horace.
godspeed, john.
hugo.
mallomars.
wake up, hugo.
hmm? huh? what?
time to get up.
we're gonna get going.
i thought we didn't know where
we're going, dude. we do now.
hmm.
i used to have dreams.
dr. miller, dr. miller,
please call the switchboard.
hi, emily.
mrs. locke,
it's good to see you.
how is he? he's amazing.
he's the youngest preemie
to ever survive in this hospital.
he's had infections,
pneumonia, you name it.
and every time,
he knocked them out.
he is a fighter,
your little john.
that's wonderful.
the other girls say
he's a miracle baby.
and today, we're gonna
take him out of the incubator
so you can hold him
for the very first time.
i...
i can't do this.
i'm sorry. i can't!
so who do i talk to
about adoption?
you can't smoke in here,
mrs. locke.
oh. of course.
i'm sorry.
is that the father?
i, uh...
i don't know who that is.
can i ask you somethin'?
sure.
why am i here, man?
you're here
because you can see the cabin,
and that makes you special.
well, i have a theory
as to why we're the only ones who
can see it. i'd love to hear it.
i think we can see it
'cause we're the craziest.
so how'd you figure out
where it was, dude?
i didn't. we're not
going to the cabin.
we're gonna make
a pit stop first.
pit stop? where?
you ever wonder what happened
to the dharma initiative, hugo?
there must have been
at least a hundred of 'em
living on this island-
manning the stations,
building those homes,
making all that ranch dressing
that you like.
and then one day,
they're all gone.
they just disappeared.
you want to know
where we're going?
we're going to see them.
whoa.
what happened to 'em?
he did.
hello!
that game's stupid.
he's right in here.
come on in.
melissa, stop that!
come on now.
take your brother
in the kitchen.
there's someone here
who wants to see john.
it is coming down
like cats and dogs out there.
this nice gentleman
wants to talk to you, john.
so i want you on
your best behavior. understand?
he's all yours.
you like backgammon?
yeah?
you seem to have
a pretty good sense of the game.
i'm richard, john.
i run a school
for kids who are...
extremely special,
and i have reason to believe
that you might be one of them.
mind if i show you
a couple of really neat things?
did you draw that, john?
i want you
to look at these things...
and think about 'em.
okay, now tell me, john,
which of these things
belong to you?
t- to keep?
no, no, john.
which of these things
belong to you already?
are you sure the knife
belongs to you, john?
you sure about that?
well, it doesn't.
how did he do?
i'm afraid john isn't
quite ready for our school.
i'm sorry
i've wasted your time.
what did you do?
what's he doing down there?
so...
this is where you shot locke
and left him for dead, huh?
yes, hugo, i was standing
right where you are now
when i pulled the trigger.
should have realized at the time
that it was pointless,
but... i really
wasn't thinking clearly.
is that why you killed
all these people, too?
i didn't kill them.
well, if the others didn't
wipe out the dharma initiative-
they did wipe them out, hugo,
but it wasn't my decision.
then whose was it?
their leader's.
but i thought
you were their leader.
not always.
the cabin?
he was building it.
did you find
what you were looking for?
yes, hugo. i believe i did.
i need your key.
what?
captain.
mayhew just died. doc couldn't
do anything for him.
the crew's
asking a lot of questions
about what happened to you guys over there.
you tell the crew that i'm dealing with it.
then you can go gas up
the chopper, frank.
we're going back.
going back? what the hell for?
gas up the chopper, frank.
okay.
listen, martin.
while you were gone, there was
some sort of a sickness. mm-hmm.
the crew-
they've been exhibiting
some very strange behavior.
regina threw herself overboard,
for god sake.
now i would be derelict
in my duty
if i didn't point out
that this might be exactly what's
happening to you. i appreciate your concern.
give me your key.
that's not the protocol-
thank you.
the reason there are two keys
is we're only supposed
to open the safe together.
you're here, aren't you?
what is that?
it's the secondary protocol.
what does it say?
it says where linus is going.
how would
mr. widmore know that?
'cause he's a very smart man,
and if linus knows that
we're gonna torch the island,
there's only one place
that he can go.
what do you mean,
"torch the island"?
that was not the agreement.
i agreed to ferry you here
for an extraction mission.
fix my gun.
the injured man...
there was no gunshot.
what do you think
happened to him?
i don't know.
but when they go back,
they'll be certain it doesn't happen again.
omar!
keamy wants you in the armory.
he said i wasn't supposed to let
those two out of my sight.
i'll watch them. go.
there's a pantry
below our galley
with enough room for two men.
i've left you a supply of food and water.
you need to go there. michael-is he dead?
no, but not for lack of bloody trying,
which is precisely why
you two need to be hiding before
keamy comes back on this deck.
hiding is pointless.
give us your zodiac raft
so we can start ferrying people
back here from the beach.
the only way
to save our lives
is to get our people
off that island.
meet me behind the container
in ten minutes.
the boat will be in the water.
cabin's here.
i came from over there.
up the coast.
here you go.
drink up, dude.
digging through dead bodies
takes it out of you.
it's gonna be dark soon,
hugo.
if you head that way,
you'll hit the coast,
and all you have to do
is take it north until you
reach our beach. uh, what?
i forced you to come with us at
gunpoint, and i'm sorry, hugo,
but i was led to believe that we
needed you to find this place.
oh, i get it.
now you got your magic map,
you don't- you don't need me anymore.
i'm offering you a chance to leave.
i don't want to put you
in harm's way against your will.
and you think walking
through the jungle
at night by myself is gonna be any safer?
i'm not sure it is.
i think
i'll stick with you guys.
this way?
what?
he actually thinks
staying was his idea.
not bad, john.
not bad at all.
i'm not you.
you're certainly not.
somebody, let me out!
please let me out.
please, somebody, let me-
john, you okay?
i'm fine. i'm fine.
get to class, ladies.
tardy bell just rang.
john, you're bleeding.
come on.
let's go to the nurse's office.
you wanna talk about it?
no.
i know you're probably upset right now,
but i do have some exciting news for you.
i got a call from portland recently.
there's a company up there
doing some very exciting things
in chemistry and new technologies.
they're called mittelos laboratories.
i spoke with a dr. alpert.
he's very interested
in finding young, bright minds
to enter
in these new fields of science.
they want you to go
to their camp this summer.
science camp?
yes.
don't you understand
that things like science camp
are the reason why
i get stuffed into lockers?
john, this is a great opportunity.
how do they even know about me?
well, they must have sent a rep
to the science fair-
your display at costa mesa.
i'm not a scientist!
i like boxing and fishing and cars.
i like sports!
i'm gonna tell you something-
something i wish someone
had told me at your age.
you might not want to be
that guy in the labs
surrounded by test tubes
and beakers,
but that's who you are,
john.
you can't be the prom king.
you can't be
the quarterback.
you can't be a superhero.
don't tell me
what i can't do.
why didn't you tell me?
tell you what?
that you're a survivor of 815.
aah!
'cause you
wouldn't have believed me.
you didn't think
i'd believe you?
i tell you that i'm one of
the only people in the world
that think that that plane
on the bottom of the ocean
is a hoax,
and you didn't think i'd believe you?
i didn't know if i could trust you.
your boss put that plane there.
man, i thought
i was mr. conspiracy,
but you got me beat there.
listen to me.
you can't fly that guy back-keamy.
you let me worry about keamy,
all right? you can't fly him back!
he is gonna kill
everyone on that island.
everyone.
and you don't want that
on your conscience, man.
trust me.
hey, boss.
just getting him
down to the engine room.
stay on a heading
of exactly 3-0-5.
faraday says that's the only
safe way to and from the boat.
what will you tell keamy if he
notices the zodiac is missing?
i'll tell him you stole it.
now go.
desmond.
i can't go with you.
why not?
i've been on that island
for three years.
i'm never setting foot on it again...
not when
penny's coming for me.
i'll be back with the first
group as soon as i can.
stay on that bearing, yeah?
i will.
you need to go now.
it should be about 200 yards this way.
you sure it's gonna be there, john?
i'm sorry?
the cabin-
what if it's moved again?
it hasn't moved
because i was told
that this is where it would be.
i was told
a lot of things, too-
that i was chosen,
that i was special.
i end up
with a tumor on my spine
and my daughter's blood
all over my hands.
i'm sorry those things
happened to you, ben.
those things
had to happen to me.
that was my destiny.
but you'll understand
soon enough
that there are consequences
to being chosen...
because, destiny, john,
is a fickle bitch.
guys?
cabin.
okay, okay, okay.
good job, man.
good job, john. okay,
we'll try it some more tomorrow.
he's all yours. come on up.
it's all right. come on.
don't give up, mr. locke.
excuse me?
i'm just saying,
don't give up.
anything's possible.
you should read my file.
my spine was crushed.
there's a 98% chance i'll never
get any feeling back in my legs.
so i don't know
why i'm even trying to-
as a matter of fact,
i did read your file.
you survived falling
eight stories out of a building.
that's a miracle, mr. locke.
let me ask you something.
do you believe in miracles?
no. i don't believe in miracles.
you should.
i had one happen to me.
hey, look. i just want
to go back to my room.
you know what you need,
mr. locke?
you need to go on a walkabout.
wha-what's a walkabout?
it's a journey of self-discovery.
you go out
into the australian outback
with nothing more than a knife
and your wits.
i can't "walkabout" anything.
in case you haven't noticed,
i'm a cripple.
is that what you are,
mr. locke?
i went on my walkabout
convinced i was one thing,
but i came back another.
i found out what i was made of,
who i was.
and here you are,
an orderly.
oh, i'm a lot more
than just an orderly, john.
when you're ready,
mr. locke...
you'll listen
to what i'm saying.
and then when you and me
run into each other again...
you'll owe me one.
hey, doc.
wanna hear something weird?
yeah, sure.
you know that morse code message
that i got from the beach?
it said that the doctor
washed up on the shore
with his throat slit.
but i'm the doctor.
crazy, right?
everything here?
yes, sir.
good. get it packed up.
what are you gonna do
with all that?
fire her up, frank.
mr. keamy, i was hired
to fly scientists.
get your ass in the cockpit
and fire up the chopper, frank.
i'm not taking you.
i'll kill you, frank.
yeah, well, you do that,
you'll never get back to the island
'cause i'm the only pilot you got.
sorry, doc.
that change anything, frank?
huh?
another 30 seconds goes by
and someone else's turn-
i fixed your gun.
now stand down, martin,
or i will fire.
i don't think you want
to do that, captain.
what's that on his arm?
hey!
what'll it be, frank?
we're flying.
come on.
let's go, boys. come on!
get the rest of the weapons onboard,
and let's go. let's go! let's get out of here.
let's move out.
thanks, captain.
come on! come on!
come on! come on! let's go!
hey!
what did i say to you?
you told me not to leave my tent.
i was hungry.
jack, you have to rest.
you can't run around.
i know that it is hard
for you to ask for help,
but if you tear
your stitches...
okay. okay. i got it.
doctors make the worst patients.
jack!
i think they want us to follow 'em.
all right. let's do this.
i'm not going in there
with you.
what?
the island wanted me to get sick,
and it wanted you to get well.
my time is over, john.
it's yours now.
yeah, i'm cool
with you going in alone, too.
good luck, john.
are you jacob?
no.
but i can speak
on his behalf.
well, who are you?
i'm christian.
you know why i'm here?
yeah, sure.
do you?
i'm here...
because i was chosen to be.
that's absolutely right.
claire?
hi, john.
what are you doing here?
don't worry. i'm fine.
i'm with him.
wh-
where's the baby?
the baby's where
he's supposed to be,
and that's not here.
it's probably best
that you don't tell anyone
that you saw her.
why? why is she-
we don't have time for this.
the people from the boat
are already on their way back,
and once they get here,
all of these questions
won't matter one bit.
so why don't you ask the one
question that does matter?
how do i save the island?
did he tell you
what we're supposed to do?
he did.
well?
he wants us
to move the island.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入