previously on "lost"...
how did you know my father?
He came to see his daughter.
My daughter was on your plane.
Her name was claire.
We're here to geta blood sample
from you and one from your son aaron.
Why?
To determine your
relationshipto the child.
where you going, mommy?
We're going on vacation, baby.
Wait, you're in L.A.?
Of course I can meet, yeah.
Hello, kate.
you okay?
Get me to the car.
- sayid, you've been attacked.
- Where's hurley?
The only wayto save the island,
john, is to get your people back here.
How? How am isupposed to do that?
- what?
- You've...
do you knowwhat's happening to me?
Charlotte? Charlotte?
Oh, you don't haveto whisper.
When he's out, he's out.
at least one of uscan sleep.
It's gonna takemore than two nights for
me to get usedto sleeping in a normal bed.
What are we gonna doabout him?
About aaron.
I don't know.
I've been thinking a lotabout him.
Did you know that clairewas flying
to L.A. To give him up for adoption?
No. No, I didn'T.
I think we should sayhe's mine.
What?
We could say that I wassix months
pregnant when I was arrested
and that I ge birth to himon the
island. No one would ever know.
Kate, no. You don't have to...
there's other waystoo this.
After everyone we've
lost--michael, jin, sawyer...
I can't lose him, too.
Sawyer's not dead.
No. But he's gone.
Good night, jack.
Kate...
if we're gonna be safe, if we're gonna
protectthe people that we left behind,
tomorrow morning, I'm gonna
haveto convince everyone to lie.
If it's just me,they're
never gonna go for it.
So I'm gonnaturn to you first.
Are you with me?
I have always been with you.
THREE YEARS LATER
how does it fit?
It's perfect. Thank you for the loaner.
Looks great on you.
are you sure you want to do this?
it was your idea.
Mommy!
Aaron, honey, mommy's
gonnarun out and do an errand.
I'll be right back. Okay?
And then we can go home.
don't worryabout us, kate.
There's candy in the minibarand
a hundred channels on tv.
We're going to bejust fine here.
Sun...
I don't know what I
would'vedone if you weren't here.
Thank you.
It's what any friendwould do.
Okay, well,I will be back soon.
Okay, you be good for sun. Okay, honey?
Good luck.
delivery for you, ms. Kwon.
Thank you.
I'll be right back, honey.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ßÇÈâÈâ »ð¼ý¼ý
LOST
Season05 Episode04
Charlotte?
What the hell's wrong with her?
She's been out for ten minutes.
Stop shouting, james.
Hey, man.
Thank you.
If there's something that you want to
tell me, daniel, now would be a good time.
I'm not sure what you mean exactly.
She's asking if you know why
your girlfriend had a seizure.
Give us some space, would you?
She's like this 'cause
the sky keeps lighting up.
He knew this would happen and
he didn't say squat about it.
James... go away.
did you know that this would happen?
I thought... I thought it might.
I think it's neurological.
Our brains have an internal
clock, a sense of time.
The flashes... throw the clock off.
It's like really bad jet lag.
Really bad jet lag doesn't
make you hemorrhage, daniel.
You wanna tell me why it isn't
happening to the rest of us?
I don't know.
But thank god it's not.
thank you for waiting.
Did my assistant offer
you something to drink?
Um, yes. I'm fine, thank you.
Good. Please, ms. Austen, sit.
So... how can I help you?
mr. Norton, when you came to mhouse looking
for blood samples from me and my son,
I asked you who your client was...
- and I said I couldn't tell you.
- Yeah.
I'm here to offer you a deal.
I'll give you the blood samples, but
first, I wanna talk to your client.
Considering what you're asking
for, that's more than reasonable.
Well, I am, uh, seeing my client later today,
and I will be sure to pass along your offer.
But I am pretty sure of what
the answer's gonna be-- no.
And the reason, of course, is that you're in
no position to be making any kind of deals,
and we both know it.
I have a signed court order compelling you to
let us confirm that you're the child's mother.
I could send the sheriff over there today and
make you do it, but my client insists that we...
handle the exchange of custody quietly.
What do you mean "exchange of custody"?
You know exactly what I mean.
No, I...mr. Norton,
I just wanna know who
is doing this to me.
You did this to yourself.
Now it is time you prepare
yourself, ms. Austen.
You are going to lose the boy.
We have to go back to the orchid.
Excuse me?
The orchid.
That's where all this started.
Maybe it's where it'll all stop.
That greenhouse is a long ways away.
You said you had a zodiac
raft back at the beach.
We could take that, cut around the horn of
the island, be at the orchid in half the time.
And let me guess. You know exactly
what to do when we get there.
No, not exactly at all, but I know
that ben used it to leave the island.
And if I can do the same
thing, I believe I can save us.
And how you gonna do that?
This is all happeningbecause they left.
I think it'll stopif
I can bring them back.
- Bring who back?
- Jack, sun, sayid,hugo, kate.
The boat blew up, and that
chopper was probably on it.
They're not dead, james.
Says who?
That doesn't matter.
All that mattersis
they've gotta come back.
I have to make them come back...
even if it kills me.
Don't you want 'emto come back, james?
Don't you want her to ce back?
It doesn't matterwhat I want.
She's waking up!
Are you okay?
- Who are you?
- It's me.
It's daniel.
Daniel.
oh, my head.
what happened?
There was another flash. You passed out.
How do you feel?
A bit dizzy, but...
- I'm fine.
- Good.
hooray. Everything's back to normal.
Now what?
I'll tell you "now what."
We're going to the orchid.
Oncologist on call to the I.C.U.
Dilation's almostback to normal.
Good. Now take this I.V.
Out of my arm, and let's go.
Sayid, you were unconsciousfor 42 hours.
You had the equivalent of threedoses
of horse tranquilizer in your system.
If you sent that man to hurley'shouse,
- we have to leave now.
- You need to relax.
Ben is not gonna hurt hurley.
Ben is on our side.
The only side he's onis his own.
Dr. Shephard?
I'm dr. Ariza,director
of clinical services.
A word with you, please?
I'll be right back.
What do you thinkyou are doing here?
I was treating a patient. I
apologize. It was an emergency.
you were suspendedon
charges of substance abuse.
Emergency or not, dr. Shephard,
you have no business being here.
I understand, and I take full
responsibilityfor my actions.
No, doctor. The hospital takes full
responsibility for your actions,
and that makes usliable for them.
excuse me.
- Hello?
- jack? It's me.
Hurley.
Hey, did sayid get to you?
Did my dad drop him off?
- Yes. He did.Hurley,
where are-- - is he okay?
- He's fine.
- Awesome.
Hurley, where are you?
Dude, I'm totally cool.
I'm in L.A.County lockup.
Oh, and tell sayidI did
exactly what he said.
I'm totally safe. Ben's
never gonna get me now.
What are you talking
about, hurley? Wait!Wait--
good. You're here. How's sayid?
How you doing today, sir?
Got your meds for you.
Sorry, I think you havethe wrong room.
Nope. Room 133, right?
Got the orders right
here. But don't worry.
I won't have togive you an injection.
Put thisright in your I. V. Line.
who are you? Who are you working for?
okay, talk, talk.
Address--it's
in my pocket.
hello, sayid.
What happened?
Do we know anyonewho
lives at 42 panorama crest?
That's kate's address.
hello?
Kate? It's jack. Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Where are you right
now? Are you at home?
what?
Listen, I'll explain everythingonce
you're out, but you've gotta get aaron--
look, I'm not at home, okay? I'M...
aaron is at a hotelwith sun.
Sun? Sun's in L.A.?
Yeah, she's here on business.
Listen, jack, this
isreally not a good time.
I'm so sorry that I
evenpicked up the phone.
kate, do not hang up on me.
Please listen. Lisn, uh...
will you tell me where
you are? I need to see you?
Kate, please.
I'm downtown. Wilshire and olive.
Okay. All right. I'm on my way.
She's not at home, but I'm
gonnago to her right now.
Good. I'll go deal with hugo.
Sorry, ben.
I'm not letting youget
anywhere near him.
You have friends in trouble.
Let's get them to safety and
save the dirty linenfor later.
I'll drive.
After you get kate, meet us
atthe long beach marina, slip 23.
And, jack... hurry.
We're running out of time.
hey, locke? What are
you gonnasay to her?
Sorry?
Kate. What are you gonna say
to herto get her to come back?
I haven'tfigured that out yet.
Well, let metell you something.
She was pretty excited to hop on that
chopperand get the hell out of here.
What the hell is that?
Whatever it is,we
better stay clear of it.
Beach is this way.
Now you wanna takethe scenic route?
John... do you know when we are?
We need to keep moving.
How's your headache?
Better.
Nothing like sore feet to
takeyour mind off your head, eh?
well, don't worry.Once
we get to the beach,
we're gonna take the zodiac around
the other sideof the island and rest.
You're sweet, but you don't
needto baby me. I'm fine.
You okay?
I'm peachy.
Now what?
nobody move.
- james!
- I got this.
it knows I don't want it,and
I was gonna give it away.
Babies know that stuff.
Okay, no, no, hang on. Listen, listen.
Do you want this baby?
Do you want itto be safe and healthy?
you're not alone in this. We are all
here for you. This baby is all of ours.
But I need you to push.
Okay?
one, two, three... push!
come on, claire! Push!
Okay! He's coming!
push! Push! Push! Push!
james?
What happened?
Did you see somethingout here, james?
Don't matter.
It's gone now.
you shaved your beard.
Yeah.
Just needed a change.
Look,jack,uh...
I don't know why you called,but I
can't be dealingwith this right now.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Just...
can you just go?
Why don't you just tell me?
Jack,please,just go.
Kate,please,tell me.
somebody wants aaron.
What?
There's a lawyer in there.
His clients--they
know we're lying.
They know I'm not his mom,and
they're gonna take him away.
Who's gonna take him away?
What--what
are you doing?
Look,I gotta go,all right?
Get in or don'T.
You ready to tell mewho
you saw back there?
Already told you.
It was nothin'.
You and I both know when
wwerebefore the flash,james.
So who was it you
saw?Charlie?Shannon?Yourself?
And how is it that you knew
when we were,johnny boy?
That light in the sky--it
wasfrom the hatch,wasn't it?
The night that boone died...
I went out there and started
pounding on itas hard as I could.
I was...
confused...
scared.
Babbling like an idiot,asking,why
was all thishappening to me?
Did you get an answer?
Light came on,shot up into the sky.
At the time,I thoughtit meant something.
- Did it?
- No.
It was just a light.
So why'd youturn us around then?
Don't you wannago back there?
Why would I wanna do that?
So you could tell yourselfto do things
different,save yourselfa world of pain.
No,I needed that painto
get to where I am now.
I just got a nosebleed.
What?
When?
Let's just notfreak out the others,okay?
Just tell me...
why--why
her?Why me?
I don't know.
Uh,I think it mighthave something
to do with duration of exposure.
You know,the amount of
timeyou'vepent on the island.
Doesn't make any sense.
Those yahooshave been here for months.
I've never been here
before two weeks ago.
Are you sure about that?
hello?
the camp's bac finally.
Anybody for a dharma beer?
Hello?
Anybody here?
Rose?Bernard?
I wonder how long agothis happened.
Son of a bitch!
What is it?
It's vincent'S.
Yeah?Well,where's the rest of the dog?
Where's the restof our people?
The zodiac's gone,too.
Maybe your peopletook the boat.
Why the hellwould they do that?
To get awayfrom whoever came in those.
where did these come from?
That's a good question.
They're pretty old.
Not that old.
Let me see that.
"Adg-uh-ruh"?
Ajira.It's an airline.
It's based out of india,but
they fly everywhere.
Great.Maybe they got a flightout
of here to vegas tonight.
Who came in these?
Other others?
Don't look at me.
My question is,when
are they coming back?
Let's not wait to find out.
this plan soundeda hell of a lot
better when we weregoing by motorboat.
How far is this place?
It's around that point.
Not more than a couple hours.
oh,joy.
You all right?
I saw kate.
What?
Last night,in the jungle.
Before the last flash.
She was deliveringclaire's baby.
But that was two months ago.
Time travel's a bitch.
get down!
paddle!
I think they want their boat back!
Move!
these your people?
No!Are they yours?
Shut up and keeping paddling!
little help!
Little help!
paddle harder!
They're getting closer!
thank you,lord!
I take that back!
Everybody,paddle!
Head for the shore!
kate,just because the guy told you that he wasmeeting
his client doesn't meanthat they're here in L.A.
He could've just told you
that to--to throw you off.
Or they're in that hotelright now.
Okay.
And what if they are?
What if the personwho wants to take aaron
is sittingin that hotel room right now?
Then what?
Come on.
Come with me.
We'll--we'll go get aaron,we'll put our
heads together,and we'll figure something out.
All right.
Oh,my god.
it's claire's mother.
Wait.
What am I waiting for,jack?
Wait.I just...
- let's just think about this for a minute.
- She knows.
Maybe she doesn't know.
No,but she knows about aaron,and
that's all that matters!
t mego talk to her.
What?
If I can just explain to herwhy we did it--
maybe if I can get herto understand why...
she'll listen to me.
I can fix this,kate.
I can fix it.
Aaron is my family,too.
dr. Shephard?
Hello,ms.Littleton.
may I come in?
Of course.
you look drenched.
No,no.
No,I'm fine.
God,I haven't seen yousince
your father's funeral.
How did you even knowI was here?
I knew you were here,ms.Littleton,
because I followedyour lawyer.
Why would you do that?
I'm--I did it
because,um...
I understand thatyou
feel the need to do this.
But I need you to know that everything
that kate and ihave done--it was for aaron.
Who'S...
aaron?
I-I'm afraidI'm not following you.
Ms.Littleton,um...
what are you doing herein los angeles?
let's go.
Drive.
Then call sun and tell her to
bring aaronto the long beach marina.
We'll meet her there.
What--wh-whaare
youtalking about?
- What happened?
- Kate,we have to go now.
I'm not going anywhere
untilyotell me what just happened!
She doesn't know anything.
What?
She doesn't know.
She still thinksthat claire is dead.
she doesn't even knowthat aaron exists.
But the lawyer--she sued oceanic,and
she's in town to pick up her settlement.
What,and it's justa coincidence that her lawyer
happens to be the same one that's trying to take my son?
I don't know.
But whoever's tryingto take aaron...
it's not her.
Then who is it?
Can I ask you something?
Why'd you take it upon
yourselfto rescue hugo?
I had to make surehurley was safe.
You can pull in over here.
mr. Linus.
Mr. Norton.
I looked into it,and they don't have
any kindof solid case against reyes.
The M.E.Said that the manfound outside
santa rosa was killed before reyes escaped.
That's very good news.
We have a prelim hearingin the morning.
The judge will neverlet it get past
that,and reyeswill be a free man.
Thank you,dan.
Anytime.
Who was that?
That's my lawyer.
Okay!
remind menever to dthat again.
Where are we?
It's hard to saytill it gets light.
we didn't get a chanceto
finish our conversation.
What conversation was that?
The one beforethey
started shooting at us,
where you were about to tell
mehow it felt to see kate again.
I wasn't aboutto tell you anything.
why don't you tell me now?
I was close enoughto touch her.
If I wanted to,I could've...
stood right upand talked to her.
Why didn't you?
What's done is done.
Juliet?
What's wrong?
oi!
Come and look at this!
It's wreckage.
Looks like it just happened.
anybody speak french?
jack,why did you call me today?
I told you.I S...
I was worried.
But why?
Why wereyou worried?
Why today?
I don'T...
right before I called
you,sayid was attacked.
And the guy that did it--your
address was in his pocket.
Sayid?
What's he doing here?
That's not importantright now.
What matters is that we getyou
and aaron someplace safe.
safe from who?
hello,kate.
it's okay.
He's with me.
He's with you?
I know this is gonnabe hard to
understand,but he's here to help us.
To help everyonethat we left behind.
We all need to be together again.
It's him.
What?
He's the one who's trying to take aaron.
No.No.
- You-- you don't understand.No,jack.-
She's right.It was me.
Sorry.
Who the helldo you think you are?
Why don't youjust stay away?
Why don't youleave me and my son alone?
Because he's not your son,kate.
robert...ça va?
no understand.
you speak english?
little.
Are you okay?
Yes.
How did you get here?
Boat.
what boat?
It's gone.
Sink.
It must've been caughtin
the same storm as ours.
Who are you?
How long you in the water?
I don't know.
How do you not know how you wound
up inthe middle of the ocean,ah?
Montand...
merci,robert.
thank you.
What is your name?
Kwon jin.
Jin.
Hello,jin.
I'm danielle.
Danielle rousseau.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
sync: »ð¼ý¼ý
proudly presents