Previously on "Lost"
- Is that Benjamin Linus?
- We need you to save his life.
If I take him,
he's not ever gonna be the same again.
He will always be one of us.
Get your ass out here right now,
or I'm gonna kill your daughter.
I stole her as a baby
from an insane woman.
She means nothing to me.
So if you want to kill her,
go ahead and do it.
This guy is dangerous.
Sun, that boat I came here on
was filled with commandos
whose only mission was to get him.
And how'd that work out for everyone?
- You know him?
- Yeah.
He's the man who killed me.
What have you done, Richard?
Calm down. Calm down.
This has nothing to do with you.
So it's true?
You actually brought
one of them to our temple?
He's just a boy, and he was dying.
Then you should've let him die.
Jacob wanted it done.
The island chooses
who the island's chooses.
You know that.
Yes. yes, of course.
What's his name?
Hello, Benjamin.
What happened?
You were injured.
How?
You don't remember?
Where am I?
You're among friends.
We're going to take care of you.
My dad. Is he here?
You'll be back to him soon enough.
No. No, I don't want to go back.
- Okay, easy. Easy.
- Oh!
I don't want to go back.
I wanna stay.
I wanna be one of you.
Just because you're living with them
doesn't mean you can't be one of us.
You should be dead, Benjamin.
But this island...
it saved your life.
Who are you?
I'm Charles.
Charles Widmore.
Ben.
Hello, Ben.
Welcome back to the land of the living.
My God.
You're alive.
Yes, I am.
I knew it.
I knew that this would happen.
Then why are you so surprised to see me?
Because it's one thing
to believe it, John.
It's another thing to see it.
Then why were you trying
to run away to the main island?
I broke the rules, John.
I came back to the island.
I was going to answer for what I'd done.
I was going back...
to be judged.
Judged?
By whom?
Well, John,
we don't even have a word for it,
but I believe you call it the monster.
Lost Season 5 Episode 12:
"Dead is Dead"
Morning.
Hello.
What's in the crate?
Just some stuff we need to get moved.
Need a hand?
No, thanks. We got it.
Okay. Have a great day.
How're you feeling, my friend?
Like someone hit me
with an oar, but I'll live.
- What do you make of him?
- I'm not sure.
What has he told you?
When you were out cold,
he was watching over you.
And he said you killed him.
I killed him?
Really?
'Cause he looks fine to me.
You know, I don't really
remember him from the plane.
- Do you?
- No, I don't.
What if...
he was already here,
before we crashed?
If he thinks I killed him,
then he's insane.
We may be dealing with a man
who's dangerously deranged.
Then the question is,
what are we gonna do about it?
Don't worry, my friend.
I have your back.
Caesar.
Pleasure to meet you, Caesar. I'm Ben.
You want me to do it?
I can do it if you want me to, Ben.
Shut up!
And stay here, Ethan.
Don't! Don't do it.
You're the one who
infected us, aren't you?!
No!
- Give me my baby.
- It's okay. It's okay, baby.
Please, don't take my Alex!
Do you want your baby to live?
Why are you taking her?
Be grateful you're still alive.
Now you listen to me.
If you try to follow me or
if you ever come looking for me,
I'll kill you.
And if you want your child to live,
every time you hear whispers,
you run the other way.
What's that?
Just something sentimental.
So this is your old office, huh?
I never pictured you
leading your people
from behind a desk.
It seems a little...
corporate.
Was there something that you needed, John?
Well, Ben, I was hoping
that you and I could talk
about the elephant in the room.
I assume you're referring
to the fact that I killed you.
Yeah.
It was the only way to get you
back to the island,
along with as many of those
who left as possible.
You do remember, John. That's why
you left in the first place,
to convince 'em to come back?
But you failed.
And the only way to bring them together
was by your death,
and you understood that.
It's why you were about to kill
yourself when I stopped you.
If all I had to do was die,
Ben, then why did you stop me?
You had critical information
that would've died with you.
And once you'd given it to me...
Well, I just didn't have time
to talk you back into hanging yourself.
So I took a shortcut.
And look at you, John.
I was right.
You're here. you're back.
So are the rest of them.
I don't know where yet exactly,
but they came. It worked.
And that's why I did it,
because it was in the best
interests of the island.
I was just hoping for an apology.
I've decided to help you, Ben.
Help me do what?
Do what you say you are
on your way to do.
Be judged.
That's not something
you want to see, John.
If everything you've done
has been in the best
interests of the island,
then I'm sure
the monster will understand.
Let's go.
- What are you doing?
- We're taking a boat.
Where?
Over to the main island.
I don't think so, my friend.
Are these your boats?
Are they yours?
Caesar, right?
I was under the impression
these were found here.
So I'm just gonna borrow one.
I'm happy to leave the other boat for you
in case you want to follow us.
"Us"?
Are you going with him?
He didn't really give me a choice.
I'm sorry, but I'm calling the shots here
and I say you are not taking anything.
What you are going to do is to sit down
and tell us how you know so much
about this island, my friend.
You're in the habit of
calling people "friends"
but I don't think you mean it.
Step away from the boat.
No, I'm not gonna
step away from the boat.
I'm gonna take it,
and you're gonna let me, my friend.
You're not taking anything.
You looking for this?
This gentleman and I are taking a boat.
Does anyone else have
a problem with that?
Consider that my apology.
Home, sweet home.
Looks like we're not the first
ones who decided to tie up here.
That would be Sun and Lapidus.
I showed 'em where the boats were,
and Sun thanked me by smashing me
on the head with a paddle.
Oh. Is she the one that hurt your arm?
I noticed you were favoring
it on the way over.
No.
Someone else hurt my arm.
You just make friends
everywhere you go, don't ya?
Well, I've found sometimes
that friends can be significantly
more dangerous than enemies, John.
Is that why you shot
an unarmed man in the chest?
The man was unarmed
because I'd stolen his gun -
the gun he was going to use to kill you.
I couldn't let that happen.
No sense in me dying twice, right?
You're welcome.
We're going to your old house, aren't we?
Yes.
It's the only place I can summon it.
The "monster."
Once it arrives,
I'll either be forgiven
or I won't.
I think you're lying.
Lying about what?
That you want to be judged
for leaving the island
and coming back
because it's against the rules.
I don't think you care about rules.
Then what do I want
to be judged for, John?
For killing your daughter.
Did you do it?
We had a... complication.
I'm sorry. Is that a... baby?
Your orders were to
exterminate that woman.
Why? she's no threat to us.
She's insane, Charles.
Besides, you didn't
tell me she had a child.
What was it I was supposed to do?
Kill it.
It's not an "it." This is a child.
You might find this difficult
to understand, Benjamin.
Every decision I've made
has been about protecting this island.
Is killing this baby what Jacob wants?
Then here she is.
You do it.
So whose idea was it
to move into these houses?
Excuse me?
Well, your people were
living in the jungle.
And then after you murdered
the Dharma folk,
you relocated here.
I just wondered if it was your idea.
Do you disapprove, John?
It just doesn't seem like something
the island would want.
You don't have the first idea
what this island wants.
Are you sure about that?
That was your house, wasn't it?
Yes, and that's Alex's room.
Well, I suppose you better go
over there and check it out.
Sun?
What are you doing here?
This used to be my house.
I saw a light turned on.
What are the two of you doing in here?
That was taken in 1977.
Are you trying to tell me that your
friends were in the Dharma Initiative?
You don't know about this?
Of course not.
Where did you get this?
Who gave this to you?
We met some crazy old man outside.
He said his name was Christian.
He told us to come in here and wait.
Wait for what?
He said if I ever wanted
to see my husband again,
I had to wait here for John Locke.
But considering he's dead,
we ain't holding our breath.
Well, you might want to look outside.
What you're saying, it's...
Impossible.
But here I am.
I don't know how,
I don't know why,
but I'm sure there's
a very good reason for it.
As long as the dead guy
says there's a reason,
well, then I guess everything's
gonna be just peachy.
And forget about the fact
that the rest of your people
are supposedly 30 years ago.
Now the only ones who are here to help us
are a murderer and a guy
who can't seem to remember
how the hell he got out of a coffin.
Sun, please,
let's just go back to the plane,
see if I can fix the radio,
and maybe we can get some help.
If you leave with him,
you'll never find your husband again.
I'm all the help you need.
Are you saying you know
how to find them?
How to find Jin?
I have some ideas.
I'm sorry to say,
but I'm leaving with or without you.
If there's any chance
of finding my husband,
then I have to stay.
All right.
For god's sake, watch your back.
How do we find Jin?
Ben has something to do first.
Isn't that right, Ben?
Yes, John. That's right.
Better get to it then.
I'll be outside.
Again, daddy! Again!
- Okay, okay.
- Wow, Alex!
Any higher, and you're gonna
fly right off the island.
The sub's about to leave.
Higher, daddy, higher!
All right.
You don't have to see him off, Ben.
Yes, Richard, I do.
Higher! Higher, daddy!
Charles!
I came to say good-bye.
No, you didn't.
You came to gloat.
No, don't act as if I wanted this.
You brought this on yourself.
Are you quite certain
you want to do this, Benjamin?
You left the island regularly.
You had a daughter with an outsider.
You broke the rules, Charles.
And what makes you think
you deserve to take what's mine?
Because I won't be selfish.
Because I'll sacrifice anything
to protect this island.
You wouldn't sacrifice Alex.
You're the one who wanted
her dead, Charles, not the island.
I hope you're right, Benjamin,
because if you aren't,
and it is the island
that wants her dead,
she'll be dead.
And one day, you'll be standing
where I'm standing now.
You'll be the one being banished,
and then you'll finally realize
that you cannot fight the inevitable.
I'll be seeing you, boy.
Where did John go?
He said he had something to do.
Did he say what it was?
No, I didn't ask.
Jack must have lied.
- Excuse me?
- About Locke being dead?
I don't know why he would,
but that's the only explanation.
Jack didn't lie.
John was dead.
Just because he was in a coffin
doesn't mean that he couldn't
have faked his dea--
Trust me. I'm sure.
So you knew this would happen to Locke
if we brought him back here?
Sun, I had no idea it would happen.
I've seen this island
do miraculous things.
I've seen it heal the sick,
but never once has it done
anything like this.
Dead is dead.
You don't get to come back from that,
not even here.
So the fact that John Locke is
walking around this island...
scares the living hell out of me.
You may want to go inside.
Why?
Because what's about to come
out of that jungle
is something I can't control.
Any luck?
It hasn't shown up yet.
Last time we didn't have
to wait this long.
It's not a train, John.
It doesn't run on a schedule.
Well, if it's not gonna
come to us, then...
I suppose we'll have to go to it.
It doesn't work that way.
I only know how to summon it.
I don't know where it actually is.
I do.
It's weird for me, too.
Excuse me?
I realize how strange this all is.
Me, here.
But I assure you, Sun,
I'm the same man I've always been.
Are you ready?
Lead the way.
Hello?
Charles? It's Benjamin.
How did you get this number?
Doesn't matter. What matters is,
I'm going back to the island today.
The island won't let you
come back, trust me.
I've spent almost 20 years
trying to return.
Well, Charles, where you failed,
I'm going to succeed.
Just as soon as I do one thing.
And what's that, Benjamin?
Kill your daughter.
In fact, I'm looking at
"Our Mutual Friend" right now.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's the name of the boat that Penny's on.
Don't you dare.
Good-bye, Charles.
May I ask you a question, John?
Shoot.
How is it that you know
where you're going?
I just know.
I mean, how does that work, exactly?
- How does what work?
- The knowing.
I mean, did it come upon you gradually,
or did you wake up one morning,
suddenly understanding the
mysteries of the universe?
- You don't like this, do you?
- What?
Having to ask questions
that you don't know the answers to,
blindly following someone
in the hopes that
they'll lead you to whatever
it is you're looking for.
No, John, I don't like it at all.
Well, now you know
what it was like to be me.
We should keep moving.
Yes, we should.
I think I know where
we're going now, John.
Do you?
It's the same place
they brought me as a child.
It's where the island healed me.
Let's hope it's as
generous this time around.
What is it?
It's the wall around our temple.
What temple?
About a half mile from here.
We built this wall to keep people
like the two of you from ever seeing it.
We're not going into your temple, Ben.
We're going under it.
After you.
I need to ask a favor of you, Sun.
If you can ever get off this island,
find Desmond Hume for me.
Tell him I said I was sorry.
Sorry for what?
He'll know.
What are you doing here?
Desmond!
Des?!
Don't move.
Not another word.
Hello, Penelope.
My name is Benjamin Linus.
I'm sorry that you're caught up
in the middle of this thing,
but your father--
My father and I have absolutely
no relationship whatsoever,
- so whatever--
- Your father is a really terrible human being.
He's responsible for the
killing of my daughter.
That's why I'm here.
Mommy!
Charlie, go back inside, babe.
Go back inside.
Please.
Please, whatever you do,
don't hurt my son.
Please don't hurt my son.
Mommy? Mommy?
Charlie, go inside!
Captain Lapidus!
You're back.
Thank God.
They found guns.
What are you talking about?
Who found guns?
Ilana and three of the others.
They said they were in charge now.
Where are they?
Ilana!
What's going on?
What lies in the shadow of the statue?
What?
Answer the question!
What lies in the shadow of the statue?
I have no idea what the--
Get everyone else.
Tell them it's time.
And tie him up.
He's coming with us.
You know, you were right.
About what?
Why I need to be judged.
When Charles Widmore's men came,
they gave me a choice.
Either leave the island
or let my daughter die.
All I had to do was walk out
of the house and go with them.
But I didn't do it.
So you were right.
John, I did kill Alex.
And now I have to answer for that.
I appreciate you showing me the way,
but I think I can take it from here.
You got it.
I'll meet you outside, if I live--
Ben!
Are you all right?
Never better.
Hang on. I'll find something
to get you out of there.
John, wait!
You didn't tell me
that she had a child.
What was it I was supposed to do?
- Kill it.
- It's not an "it." This is a child.
Higher! Again, daddy! Again!
Higher! Higher, daddy!
I hate you!
I hate your guts!
I wish you were dead.
These people.
You said they're dangerous.
More dangerous than you?
Dad, they're serious.
They killed Karl and my mother.
Please, dad.
Help me!
She's not my daughter.
She means nothing to me.
So if you wanna kill her,
go ahead and--
Daddy?
Alex.
Hi, dad.
Oh, Alex.
I'm so, so sorry.
It was all my fault.
I know.
Listen to me, you bastard!
I know that you're already
planning to kill John again,
and I want you to know that
if you so much as touch him,
I will hunt you down and destroy you.
You will listen to every word
John Locke says,
and you will follow his every order.
Do you understand?
Say it!
Say you'll follow him.
Yes, I will. I'll follow him.
I swear.
Ben?
Ben!
What happened?
It let me live.
subtitle by unknown (credits removed)
edited and synced by rogard
www.tvsubtitles.net