Previously on Lost...
There's a rental car parked out front.
Got to Sue city.
I want you to check in
at the Sage Flower motel.
Wait for me. I'll be there in the a.m.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I don't care what Jack said.
They've got him, and we have
to get him back. I owe him that.
Obviously,
the circumstances have changed.
He may not want to be rescued.
If he's shaking hands with the others,
I'm sure he has a good reason.
We came here to rescue Jack,
and that's what we're gonna do.
What are you doing here?
I came to get you.
Get outta here.
Don't hurt her!
I made a deal with them.
They're gonna let me go.
Where?
Home.
Jack, we need to go.
Hey, hold it right there!
Get your hands up! Get down!
I said get down!
What are you doing here, John?
I'm sorry, Jack.
Sorry for what?
I was just bringing you
something to eat.
Enjoy your sandwich.
Been on the road a while, huh?
How long is it gonna take?
Well, your fan belt's shot.
I'll take two days, maybe three.
Three days for a fan belt?
Welcome to Iowa.
My name is Johnny.
I'm Lucy.
All 18-karat gold.
Cheapest one in retail for 500 bucks.
Come on. Those don't look real.
I'm not buying.
What do you mean, they don't look real?
My uncle's going out of business.
If you need a lift into town,
I'm finished up here in an hour.
- I call the cops.
- Fine. Whatever. Your loss.
Is there a problem, buddy?
Yeah. Yeah, there's a problem.
I'm getting scammed here,
that's the problem.
- Look, I'm sorry.
- What do you think, I'm an idiot?
If you don't want to buy them,
don't buy them.
Those are fake necklaces,
and you're a rip-off artist.
They're real.
I call the cops.
You don't want them,
I'll find somebody else.
Hey, let me see those.
My father owns a jewelry store.
I think I can spot a fake.
How much?
60 bucks.
I'll take the one on the end.
Whatever.
Thanks.
Can I get my money back?
Why'd you help me?
Just one girl watching
another girl's back, I guess.
Or you're stranded here,
and for some reason, you didn't want
that guy calling the cops.
I'll give you a ride into town.
You buy me a drink.
What?
What are you doing?
Did they capture you?
Yes, but...
Only temporarily.
I came to say good-bye.
Good-bye?
I'm leaving with them.
What the hell is going on?
I mean, what are they doing to you?
Are you brainwashed?
Where did Jack go?
Jack didn't go anywhere, Kate.
He's gonna have
to stay behind, like you.
You can't trust them.
If they told you that
they're gonna take you home,
- they're lying...
- I don't want to go home.
I want you to know,
I made a strong case for you.
I told them
that you were a good person...
reliable, smart, honest.
And then they told me
who you were and what you had done.
Let's just say, forgiveness
isn't one of their strong suits.
Good luck.
John, where are you going?
Coming out!
Where is Jack and where is Sayid?
Have you seen Rousseau?
John, please. What's happened to you?
I'm sorry, Kate.
Subtitle: swsub.com
What the hell's wrong with you?
Don't look at me,
and pretend we're not talking.
I'm not supposed to be here.
Good. Then scram.
Dude, you need to know
that there's been some chatter.
After Paulo and Nikki and everything,
Well, tomorrow there's gonna be a vote.
A vote for what?
To decide whether or not to banish you.
Banish me?
- Where?
- Well, there was debate about that,
but the consensus was
half a mile down the beach.
Consensus?
I'm only saying this
because there may be a way to fix it--
to, like, make amends.
I don't do amends.
You might want to ask yourself
about all the good stuff that comes
from being
part of this... society.
I mean, you can't even feed yourself.
You use our latrine,
drink the water that Steve brings
every morning to the trough...
What?
You know how for 3 days, 10 h and 15 min
I ain't allowed to use nicknames?
Well, you, sir... Hugo,
are rotund,
annoying,
and you're ruining my damn view.
How's that for amends?
You're making a big mistake, dude.
Banish me...
How about you tell me your name?
- It's Lucy.
- And what's your real name?
Next time somebody asks,
you don't think about it.
- I didn't think--
- Not even for a second.
So why Lucy?
She's a saint.
I had to memorize them all
in Sunday's school,
so I figure they're probably still
rattling around my brain.
What makes a girl who went
to Sunday school scared of cops?
A few months ago,
I killed my stepfather.
I escaped from the marshal
who arrested me for it.
Why?
'cause he was a bad guy.
So...
what the hell are you doing in Iowa?
I want to talk to my mother.
You're gonna have
a really hard time doing that,
because if you did
what you just said you did,
the feds are gonna be watching her 24/7.
I'll figure something out.
- Oh, you will, huh?
- What, you want to help me?
Absolutely.
Why?
I fell in love with the wrong guy,
and then I gave him my life savings.
He conned me and embarrassed me.
He was a bad guy.
So...
I'll help you get the meeting
with your mom... Lucy,
because one of us
deserves something good.
I ain't gonna get the Korean vote...
Come on, come on!
Hey, let's do it!
Do what?
I'm ready to do it: make amends,
change the vote.
I don't wanna be banished, okay?
You happy?
Dude, you stink.
What is that, fish?
Did you try to gut one yourself?
How have you not learned that by now?
I mean, we've been here, like,
three months.
Could we just do this?
Do what?
Make nice?
Apologize for calling me
all those names.
I'm really sorry I called you "rotund."
- Really?
- You're worse than a girl.
Come on. Let's spread the love.
What the hell am I doing here?
- Why don't you tell me?
- I don't know.
I don't know either!
So, why don't you let go of my wrist?
So what the hell happened?
I was making a cup of tea.
Canister came in through the window.
So what'd you do to piss them off?
You're wasting your time.
The knife is too big.
We need something smaller.
A safety pin...
- We're going back.
- What?
They did this to us.
Why would we go back?
You say "they"
like you didn't lock me in a cage
and watch me break rocks all day.
We're going back to your village because
my friends were probably gassed,
just like us.
Your people are gone anyway.
- I saw them all pack up and leave.
- What?
Locke came to me to say good-bye.
They were taking off,
going somewhere else.
Going? Going where?
He didn't exactly tell me.
Welcome to the wonderful world
of not knowing what the hell's going on.
On the ground!
Get down! On the ground!
Let me see those hands!
Long time no see, Austen.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm just selling bibles!
Hi.
They questioned me for half an hour.
He confiscated my case.
He was asking me about
selling bibles and...
It's a good thing I know how to lie.
Yeah, now we know
what we're up against, right?
that there were six guys
waiting to take you down, Lucy
Yeah, it's okay. I'll figure it out.
Figure it out? That marshal...
I don't know what you did to him,
but if he ever gets his hands on you,
it is gonna be you or him.
Look, if you've changed your mind,
if you don't wanna help me, I get it.
No, I do wanna help you,
but if I'm lying to federal agents,
Lucy,
so that you can have
a chat with your mom...
then I at least need to know
that there's a pretty good reason.
He...
He... used to get drunk
and beat up my mom,
so I blew up his house.
I...
Made it look like an accident...
a gas leak.
Took out an insurance policy
on the house...
for her.
Set her up for life.
And then she gave me up.
Chose him over me.
So the reason
I need to talk to her is...
someone I love...
Someone who's supposed
to care about me betrayed me,
and I wanna know why.
Well...
then let's go find out.
What are you doing?
Whoever dragged us out here
left a trail.
It'll lead us back to where
we came from.
Let's go.
It's gonna rain.
Don't you think
we should wait till morning?
Why?
Why what?
Why would they handcuff you to me
and then drag us all the way
out into the jungle?
Ben has a thing for mind games.
Is that why he left you behind?
Do we really have to talk?
Nope.
Come on.
If the trail gets wet, I'll lose it.
I hope you're not dragging me
all the way back there with you for him.
- Excuse me?
- I hope you're not going back for Jack,
because I was standing right there
when he told you not to come back,
and now that you've ruined his
chance to get off the island...
You done?
I said, are you done?
I... I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
What the hell was that?
- Get up!
- You dislocated my shoulder!
Come on!
Wait! Come here.
Okay. Get down.
What the hell...
Are we safe?
You tell me.
I ain't kissing no damn baby.
Claire's, like, really influential.
If she votes for you to stay,
you're home free, dude.
Why wouldn't she vote for me?
It's not like I ever done
anything bad to her.
Nah, but you never did
anything good for her either.
And have you ever
even asked how Aaron is?
I know how he is.
He cries loud, and he smells.
You see? That's what I'm talking about.
You're sarcastic.
People don't like that.
All right.
So I go over...
And do what?
Moms love it when you show
an interest in their babies.
So go over there,
say something nice, call her "Claire".
And give her this.
I know you can do it, dude.
Hey, Claire.
Hey there... little baby...
Aaron.
Is there anything I can do for you?
No. I just came by...
to see your baby.
He's not as wrinkly
as he was a couple weeks ago.
Yeah, I... guess he's not. Thanks.
Oh, and... this is for you.
- Thank you.
- I don't like...
blankets.
Well, good night.
Good night.
Do you think it's gone?
- Are we safe?
- Are you serious?
- What?
- You've never seen that?
If you don't believe me,
you can always pull
my other shoulder out of its socket.
- I was... I wasn't trying to...
- Don't flatter yourself.
This is the fourth time
it's been dislocated.
Give me your hand.
- Why?
- 'cause I want you to pop it back in.
- No, I'm not gonna--
- You're gonna.
Right, now it feels
like there's broken glass under my skin,
and if it weren't for you,
I would be on my way home right now.
Jack told me
not to come back to protect me,
because he didn't want me to get hurt.
- Is that what you think?
- Yeah, that's what I think.
We have cameras on the cages, Kate...
all of them.
He saw you...
you and Sawyer.
The reason Jack told you
not to come back
wasn't because
he didn't want you to get hurt.
It was because you broke his heart.
So...
grab my wrist,
push up and twist.
Why do we gotta be out here
so damn early?
You asked me to help you
catch a boar.
Well, this is when they break
cover to eat.
Looks like they picked
a day to sleep in.
So what's your angle, brother?
- My angle?
- Well, you...
Haven't spoken three words to me,
and then...
suddenly you want to be
my hunting partner.
My angle...
is I got hearts and minds to change,
and politics is all about bribes.
Since money don't mean
squat on this island,
I gotta give the people
something they like...
And people like meat.
How's your shoulder?
- Awesome.
- Then let's get going.
Thank you.
You're welcome, sweetheart.
Oh, my god! I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
- No worries.
- I'm such an idiot.
It happens all the time, sweetheart.
Thank you.
Hi, mom.
What are you doing here, Katherine?
You look good.
I asked you what you were doing here.
I want to know why you
told them what I did to Wayne.
I thought maybe you came because
you wanted to say you were sorry.
I'm not sorry.
He hit you.
He treated you like a dog and you...
You can't help who you love, Katherine.
And for good or bad, I loved him.
And you burnt him alive.
You turned on the gas,
and you lit a match.
You murdered him in cold blood.
I did it for you.
What you did, you did for yourself.
I have to go back to work.
Because you are my daughter,
I'm not gonna tell the two men
sitting at the table
who've been following me
for the last month that you are here,
but I swear to god, Katie...
if I ever see you again,
the first thing I will do
is yell for help.
Good-bye.
Did he say that to you?
Sorry?
That I broke his heart.
He didn't have to.
You don't know anything about him.
I know where he was born.
I know what his parents
did for a living.
I know that he was married
and who he was married to.
I know why he got a divorce.
I know how his father died.
I know his height, his weight,
his birthday and his blood type.
What do you know about him, Kate?
Let's go.
Run.
Run!
Get up! Get up!
Run! Run! Come on!
What are you doing?
I know what happens
when you set those things off!
We will go alongside them.
We don't need to!
We can go around there-- off!
Damn it!
You're gonna want to be over here.
Kate, come on!
We don't know what it is, but we know
that it doesn't like our fences.
You had a key!
They left me behind, too.
They gassed me.
I know that you don't care,
but the people I spent
the last three years of my life with
they just left me!
I thought that maybe...
Maybe if I could make you think
that we were in it together...
Maybe I wouldn't get left behind again.
It's delicious!
Just a little Dharma A1 and paprika...
I hope you'll remember
this little barbecue
- at your meeting later.
- Oh, what meeting?
Hurley told me about the vote.
Vote? Since when
did anyone around here vote?
You son of a bitch!
There wasn't ever gonna be no vote.
But...
Wasn't it nice...
Being nice?
You tricked me into being decent?
That's gotta be the lamest con
in the history of cons!
It wasn't a con, dude.
If you're gonna be our temporary leader,
you need to do some damage control.
Leader?
What the hell are you smoking?
Jack's gone. Locke's gone.
Kate and Sayid...
You're all we got.
When Paulo and Nikki died,
we all looked to you.
Then again, you totally tried
to steal their diamonds,
but we wanted to look to you.
Look around.
You made everyone happy.
Just for today,
they can eat boar,
laugh and forget
that they're totally screwed.
And you did that for them, dude... You.
And what if I don't want
to be the leader?
Yeah, well, I don't think
Jack wanted to, either.
Sucks for you, dude.
Sayid's in one of those backyards
down there.
I'll go get him.
You should get Jack.
Jack, wake up. It's me.
What happened?
They all left.
All left?
- What?
- Because of me.
I'm so sorry.
I should've listened to you.
I never...
I wanted to come back to help you...
but you didn't need me to.
And now because of me, you can't go...
I'm so sorry.
They just...
Left?
Even Juliet?
No, they left her, too.
Why?
You know her better than I do.
Now what?
Now...
Now we go back.
- Thanks for everything, Cassidy.
- You got it.
So... this guy who ripped you off...
You wanna give me his name,
tell me where I can find him?
You almost got arrested for me, Cassidy.
I wanna help you.
I'm pregnant.
It's his. The baby's his,
and I still love him.
So call the cops. Have him locked up.
Will you ever forgive your mom
for calling the cops?
No, I won't.
Thanks, Lucy.
My name's Kate.
You okay?
Yeah. You?
I've checked all the houses.
Everyone's gone.
No weapons, no trail.
It's like 50 people
disappeared into thin air.
We should take what we can find
and head out while we still got light.
She is not coming with us.
Yes, she is.
Why?
Because they left her behind, too.