Previously on "lost"
You're the son of a
bitch who shot my kid.
Pick him up. Get him to the spring.
You're not saving him!
You're drowning him!
Your friend is dead.
Jack!
What happened?
What is it you want?
I don't have any secrets.
Why are you doing this?
You have to give your friend
this pill. What is in it?
Poison. Why would you
people wanna kill sayid?
There is a darkness growing in him.
And once it reaches his heart,
everything your friend once was
Will be gone.
What are you hiding from me?
The pill was poison.
They wanted me to kill you.
The meter doesn't stop
until you get out, pal.
Keep the change.
Sayid.
Hello, nadia.
You're here!
Where were you, uncle sayid?
I was in sydney. Where's sydney?
In australia.
You bring flowers for my wife?
I'll give them to you, if you want.
It's good to see you, sayid.
It's good to see you,
too, brother. Come.
Uncle sayid, what did you
bring us from australia?
Go look in my bag.
It's on the couch.
It's good you came, sayid.
They've missed you.
We're lucky he even showed up--
The world traveler off on
his exotic business trips.
Translating contracts
for an oil company
Is hardly exotic...
and it's painfully dull.
Thin the world
veryof dry cleaning.E
He's being modest.
Omer's just opened up a new store.
Congratulations.
I thought we talked about cell
phones at the dinner table.
Dinner is over. This is business.
Yes?
Did you get my letters?
Yes.
You never wrote back.
These are awesome! Thanks!
You're welcome.
Mommy, we found a picture
of you in uncle sayid's bag.
I want to talk to you.
I want some answers.
Answers to what?
Let's start with that machine.
You hooked me up to this thing,
You stuck needles in me,
And you called it a test.
For every man, there is a scale.
On one side of the scale,
there is good.
On the other side--Evil.
This machine tells us
How the scale is balanced.
And yours...
Tipped the wrong way.
And that's why you
tried to poison me?
Yes.
I think it would be
best if you were dead.
You think you know me,
but you don't.
I'm a good man.
So if you're trying
to kill me--Uhh!
Go.
Leave this place.
Never come back.
Are you ready?
Why does it have to me be?
I mean, you could send
sawyer or jin or...
Do it yourself.
If i could do it myself,
I wouldn't be asking you, clai.
If i go in there,
I need to know you'll
do what you said.
I want my son back.
I always do what i say.
Are you gonna hurt them?
Only the ones who won't listen.
Aah! It's me.
Calm down. What are you doing?
It's 2:30  the morning.
Sayid, i'm in trouble.
What kind of trouble?
I borrowed money to
open the second store.
But...
I didn't borrow it from the bank.
I paid the loan back,
But the man who
lent me this money--
He says i still owe him
interest every month...
For as long as i own my business.
If you need money,
i'll lend it to you--
I don't need money, sayid.
I need you to convince these
people to leave me alone.
"Convince" them? Sayid,
don't forget who you're talking to.
I know what you did in the war.
You were an interrogator
for the republican guard.
I know what kind of man you are.
If you think i'm
going to hurt someone
Just because you made a
bad business decision--
Look, this is not about me!
Our life savings-- It's all gone,
sayid. All of it.
We could lose our home.
Please.
Look... i know you
care about nadia.
If you care about us-- About her...
You will do this, sayid.
I'm sorry.
I'm not that man anymore.
What are you doing?
I'm leaving.
I've been banished.
Banished? For what?
Apparently, i'm evil.
These people say i'm
better off dead...
Which is surprising,
Considering they were the
ones who saved my life.
Well, actually,
they're not. They...
They tried to save you, but...
You were dead, man.
For two hours.
Trt me, when--When-
When you sat up,
They were just as surprised
as the rest of us.
So whatever brought you back,
it wasn't them.
Hold it.
Stop! Don't shoot her!
What are you doing here?
He wants to see you.
Speak english.
Who wants to see me?
You know who.
If he wants to see me,
then tell him to come in.
No, he wants you to go to him.
He's waiting outside
beyond the outer wall.
I'm not a fool.
If i step outside this temple...
He'll kill me.
Well, then maybe you should
send someone he won't kill.
Stop her!
Ah, that's gonna be
a little difficult.
We can't find them.
Come on!
Come with me.
I thought you wanted me to leave.
Things have changed.
Your friends-- Shephard and reyes--
Do you know where they went?
No, i don't.
Why is claire here?
And what was she talking about?
She's a confused girl,
Under the influence
of an angry man.
What man?
For years,
He has been trapped.
But now jacob's gone.
He's free.
This man will not stop
until he has destroyed
Every living thing on this island.
He is evil incarnate.
And you want me to speak to him?
No.
I want you to kill him.
He will come to you
as someone you know...
Someone who has died.
As soon as you see him...
Plunge this deep into his chest.
If you allow him to speak,
It is already too late.
Since i've been here,
I've been drowned,
beaten and tortured at your hands.
Why would i ever do
anything for you?
You said that there is
still good in your soul.
Then prove it.
How long are you staying,
uncle sayid?
Just a few more days.
I have to go to toronto...
To work.
We like it when you're here.
Yeah, and mommy likes it, too.
Okay. Be good.
Sayid!
Omer!
Is my husband going
to be all right?
We're taking him into surgery now.
He's suffered a punctured lung
and some internal bleeding.
Do you know how this happened?
E.M.T.S thinhe was mugged.
I'll come get you as
soon as he's stable.
Sayid! Where are you going?
Stay here with omer.
This wasn't a mugging, was it?
Whatever you're
thinking of doing...
Don't do it.
I don't want you to.
Please... just...
Go home.
Wait for the kids.
Make them feel safe, sayid.
Will you of that?
Hello?
Sayid?
Hello, kate.
Are you leaving?
I am not exactly sure.
What'd i miss?
Ask miles.
Thank you.
It's good to see you, too, miles.
Sawyer sent you packing, huh?
I thought about going
after him, too.
But, um, i knew he'd
just end up berating me
Until i turned
around and came back.
That pretty much what happened?
Pretty much.
Well...
Welcome back to the circus.
What's going on in here? Well,
let's see...
Oh, that australian chick's back.
Wait. What?
You know, the--The blonde-
One that had the baby.
Claire?
Right. Claire.
She just strolled in
here a couple hours ago,
Acting all weird.
Still hot, though.
Miles, where is she?
Where is she?
Hello, sayid.
Now why'd you go and do that?
You want it back?
Take it. I won't bite.
What are you?
Well, sayid, you seem to
have some idea about that,
Considering that you
stabbed me in the chest
Without even saying hello.
What did they tell you?
They said you were evil incarnate.
I feel sorry for you.
Why?
Dogen--The man who
sent you out here--
Knew that you had no
chance of killing me.
And he believed that i would
kill you if you tried.
And this wasn't the first time that
He tried to get someone else
to do it for him, was it?
No.
Then shame on you for being
talked into it so easily.
And what is it you are
trying to talk me into?
Sorry?
You haven't killed me.
Clearly, there's
something you want.
I just want you to deliver
a message, that's all.
Then why didn't you just
have claire deliver it?
Because it would mean a
lot more coming from you.
Sayid, if you'll do this for me...
What if I told you that you
could have anything you wanted?
What if I said you could have
anything in the entire world?
I would tell you that the
only thing I ever wanted
Died in my arms.
And I'll never see it again.
But what if you could?
Uh...
We had an unfortunate incident
Involving a boomerang.
My apologies.
Oh, what time did
the kids go to bed?
About two hos ago.
And what did you tell them?
Daddy had an accident,
But that he's going to be fine.
He's still recovering
from surgery, but...
He's awake now.
Did he tell you about the loan?
Look, I have money.
No.
This is omer's responsibility.
He brought this on himself.
Why didn't you want to be with me?
You carry my picture
around with you, sayid.
If you care about me,
Why did you push me
towards your brother?
For the last 12 years,
I've been trying
to wash my hands...
Of all the horrible
things I've done.
I can't be with you...
Because I don't deserve you.
What happened?
There is a man in the jungle...
About a mile south of us,
By the outer wall.
He sent me back here
to give you a message.
He wants you to know
that jacob is dead.
And because he's gone,
None of you have to
stay here any longer.
You're free.
The man that I met
Is leaving the island forever.
And those of you who
want to go with him
Should leave the
temple and join him.
You have until sundown to decide.
What happens at sundown if we stay?
You die.
Hey!
When did you get back?
Are ford and kwon with you?
Where is claire?
Okay, I need you to tell me
what I need to know before I--
I sa, where is claire?
All right. Just let go of me, okay?
You have two minutes.
...fade away
Catch a falling star and
put it in your pocket
Save it for a rainy day
For love may come and
tap you on the shoulder
Some starless night
Claire? * just in...
Claire, it's me.
Kate?
Are you okay?
I-I can't believe you're here.
Did they capture you, too?
No. No, they...
Why did they put you down here?
What happened?
They have my son, kate.
They have aaron.
They took him from me. No. No.
Claire, they don't have aaron.
I took him.
I...
What?
I took him off the island.
You were gone,
and we couldn't find you.
So...
I raised him.
And...
He is the most beautiful,
amazing little boy.
But I came back here to rescue you
So that you could be with him,
So that you guys could
be together again.
I'm not the one that needs
to be rescued, kate.
Time's up. Let's go.
No! No! Wait!
No! Wait! Wait!
You wanted to see her.
So let's go.
He's coming, kate.
He's coming,
and they can't stop him!
All right, hurry!
Everybody, calm down!
It's going to be okay.
No! No! Wait!
Hang on!
Hey!
Hey, you created a panic here.
Our people are leaving.
I was asked to deliver a message,
And that's what I did.
What your people do
now is up to them.
Cindy, just wait.
You're all safe here.
As long we stay in the temple,
he can't touch us.
You heard him. Jacob's dead.
And if it isn't safe here anymore,
We can't take that risk.
Everyone, listen!
This is a bluff!
He can't come in! He can't come in!
Hey, what happened out there?
One minute, you're banished,
The next you're telling
everyone they're gonna die.
That's the sum of it.
So are we getting out of
here or what? Not yet.
I have to return this.
Going to pick up the kids?
Excuse me?
Why don't you get in the car?
Get in, sayid.
1¿Õ°×Ê±¼äÖá
Why don't you have a seat?
Hey, you want some eggs?
I can, uh...
Make whatever you want-
fried, scrambled.
Uh, we still got that poacher?
Where's the poacher?
You want poached? 'cause I could
make you some good poached eggs.
No, thank you.
I make good eggs.
No?
All right.
Ah, bup, bup, bup, bup, ba, ba
Martin keamy.
Sayid jarrah,
but you already know that.
Uh, that, I do. Yeah.
Right.
So...
Sayid...
How's your brother doin'?
His brother got mugged
Right out front of his own store.
It was just... terrible.
Well, but at least this way,
you know,
You're still around to
take care of his family.
You do want to take care
of his family, don't you?
Yes?
You know, I can see that you're
a very... direct guy, sayid,
So I'm just gonna get to the point.
Your brother--he borrowed
some money from me,
And just like anybody
Whborrows money or
has a loan to pay,
He has to make payments.
My brother told me he's
paid you everything he owes,
But that you still want more.
Sayid, that's a lie.
You brother does owe me,
And somebody is gonna
pay me that money.
Did you put my brother
in the hospital?
Oh, you think it was me?
I didn't do that.
You know, it's a
dangerous world, sayid.
Y-you know that because
you're from iraq.
You never know when somebody's
just gonna sneak up--
Uhh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sayid...
Okay, just relax now. Shut up.
Okay. Fine.
Fine. Okay, it's done.
All right?
Y-your brother doesn't
owe me anything.
The debt's forgiven, all right?
Good? Okay?
Just relax and... forget about it.
I can't.
Uhh!
Who are you?
No english.
You let him talk to you.
I stabbed him in the chest
like you told me to.
Then I let him talk to me.
That's twice you've tried to
have someone else kill me.
You had the opportunity
to do it yourself.
Why didn't you?
I was a businessman once...
In osaka.
I worked at a bank.
I was good at my job,
Very successful.
And one friday,
I was promoted.
My associates took
me out to celebrate.
I had too much to drink.
Every friday...
I picked my son up from baseball.
He was 12.
The accident was very bad.
I survived.
But my son...
And then...
In the hospital...
A man came to me...
A man I had never met.
And he told me that
He could save my son's life,
But I would have to come
here to this island,
Where I would have a new job.
And I could never see my boy again.
Who was this man?
His name was jacob.
Jacob drives a hard bargain.
The man outside...
I take it he offered
you a similar bargain?
Yes.
It is sundown.
Will you choose to stay or go?
I'd like to stay.
Oh, my god!
What have you done?!
Do you realize what you just did?!
He was the only thing
keeping it out!
Idiot!
You just let it in!
I know.
We gotta go now.
1¿Õ°×Ê±¼äÖá
2¿Õ°×Ê±¼äÖá
This way! This way!
I have to go get claire.
×Ö Where are shephard
and reyes and ford?
Ä» Who the hell are you?
Just answer the question.
They're gone.
Everyone's gone.
I'm the only one left.
Kate and I got separated. Lapidus?
How did you... we'll
play catch-up later.
You want to live,
you better move your ass.
What about jarrah? Is he here?
Yeah, he was headed to the pool room.
I'll go get him.
Linus, wait!
All right, the rest of you,
with me. Come on.
Claire, come on! Claire,
we gotta go.
You gotta get out of there. No.
What?! You'll be much safer here.
Sayid?
Come on.
I know a way out of here.
There's still time.
Not for me.
Where's your husband?
What?! Your husband
took off yesterday.
Jin was here? He's alive?
Last I saw him, yeah.
You do hear that, right?
You got a plan or you gonna
keep staring at the wall?
Yes, I have a plan.
Everybody inside now.
* Catch a falling star
* And put it in your pocket
* Never let it fade away
* Catch a falling star
and put it in your pocket
* Save it for a rainy day
* For love may come and
tap you on your shoulder
* Some starless night
* Just in case you wanna hold her
* You'll have a
pocketful of starlight
Sync by YYeTs.
net Transcript by Addic7ed.com