Previously on Lost...
Hello, Ben.
You're alive.
Yes, I am.
You know how to find them?
- How to find Jin?
- I have some ideas.
So you knew
this would happen to Locke
if we brought him back here?
Dead is dead.
You don't get
to come back from that.
The Dharma folks at the Swan work site,
they're gonna drill into the ground
and accidentally tap
into a massive pocket of energy,
and that will cause your plane,
Oceanic 815,
to crash on this island.
I think I can negate that energy.
If I can,
then that hatch will never be built,
and your plane will land
just like it's supposed to.
And just how exactly do you plan
on destroying this energy?
I'm gonna detonate a hydrogen bomb.
Where's the bomb, Richard?
Where is it?
The hydrogen bomb that I told
your people to bury. Where is it?
Listen to me. Lower your gun,
and we'll talk. Okay?
Nobody has to get hurt here.
Just put the gun down.
I'm gonna give you three seconds.
- One...
- Don't do this.
What's he doing down there?
- Jack, he's crazy.
- Is he?
What if this is why we're here?
What if this is our one chance
to put things back
the way they're supposed to be?
- What the hell are you doing?
- They shot him! I'm gonna go help.
We have to go, Jack.
We have to go now.
Don't you move!
Don't move.
Just who the bloody hell
might you be?
DANIEL, NO MATTER WHAT,
REMEMBER I WILL ALWAYS LOVE YOU.MOTHER
What happened?
This man walked into camp
and put a gun to my head,
and Eloise... Reacted.
Where'd you find them?
Crouched in the bushes...
like rats.
Did you two come here with this man?
Put them in my tent.
Would you care to tell me, Eloise,
why the Dharma Initiative
seems to have declared war on us?
These people aren't
from the Dharma Initiative, Charles.
Then where the hell are they from?
Thirty Years Later
He's here.
I brought dinner.
Hello, Richard.
It's been a while.
It's been three years.
- What happened? Where were you?
- I'll explain on the way.
On the way where?
It's gonna be night soon.
You and I have an errand to run,
and we don't have a lot of time.
What's wrong?
Something different about you.
I have a purpose now.
What's he doing here?
He helped me get back.
Why did Locke say these were his people?
I thought they were yours.
When I left the island,
John stepped in.
He's the leader now.
Who's that man he's talking to?
His name is Richard Alpert.
He's a kind of...
Advisor.
And he has had that job
for a very, very long time.
Sun? What are you...
Were you here in 1977?
Excuse me?
These people...
Jack Shephard,
Kate Austen, Hugo Reyes.
They were here with my husband,
Jin Kwon.
Were you here?
Do you remember them?
Any of them?
Yes, I was here 30 years ago.
And I do. I remember these people.
I remember
meeting them very clearly,
because...
I watched them all die.
Subtitles:
www.sub-way.fr (1.00)
Drink of water?
Do you think it's true?
They're all dead?
I don't think we went through all this
for nothing, Sun.
I'm ready, John.
You still have
that compass I gave you?
A little rusty,
but she can still find north.
Ben, I'd appreciate it
if you'd join us.
What, John, don't you trust me
here with my former people?
Afraid I'll stage a coup?
I'm not afraid of anything
you can do anymore, Ben.
- Well, in that case, I'd love to come.
- Good.
Stay here.
We'll be back in a couple of hours.
I'll see what I can find out.
But whatever happens, Sun,
you have my word...
If there's a way for you and Jin
to be together again,
a way to save our people...
I'll find it.
Take it easy on her.
Don't talk. Understand?
Are you okay?
Before we were caught...
You said that we needed to put things
back the way they were supposed to be.
What did you mean by that?
If we can do what Faraday said...
Our plane never crashes...
Flight 815 lands in Los Angeles.
And everyone we lost
since we got here...
They'd all be alive.
And what about us?
We just go on living our life
because we've never met?
All the misery
that we've been through...
We'd just wipe it clean.
Never happened.
It was not all misery.
Enough of it was.
The man I shot...
What did he need the bomb for?
I need you to tell me
why he wanted the bomb.
I don't think
you'd believe me if I did.
When I was 17 years old,
I took a young man to the bomb.
He proceed to tell me
that if we buried it underground,
then things
would work out splendidly.
When I asked him
how he could be so sure...
He said that he was from the future.
And then he disappeared,
right in front of my eyes.
Ten minutes ago,
I shot that man in the back.
And before he died...
He told me that he...
He said he was my son.
Explain to me...
And you have my word
I will believe you.
How is this my handwriting
if I don't remember writing it?
Because you haven't written it yet.
I know this is hard to understand,
but...
what you just did...
It was an accident,
and I think that there's a way
for you to take it all back.
What?
Your son came back here
because he had figured out a way
to change things.
He doesn't have to be dead.
You don't have to have killed him.
If we do what's written
in that journal...
None of this will have happened.
Does he know
what he's talking about?
He thinks he does.
All right then,
I'll take you to the bomb.
Just...
One small issue, however.
We secured it
over 20 years ago underground.
But since that time,
it appears that someone's built
an entire village over it.
The Dharma Initiative?
However...
It appears that you two have been
passing yourselves off as members, so...
I suppose coming and going
will be relatively simple.
It might be a little bit
more complicated than that.
That woman, where is she now?
Call my lawyer.
- Stuart! What the hell are you doing?
- I'm getting answers. Where is she?
Stop! Damn it, stop.
That is an order.
I'm still in charge here.
No, you were in charge, Horace.
But if we're gonna protect our people
and all the work we're doing here,
you don't have the stomach
for what happens next.
Okay, Jim, last chance.
You tell me where she is...
Or so help me God, I will kill you.
You ready to talk now?
Nope.
Believe me, I'm gettin'
tired of this too, Jim.
So why don't you tell me
where your girlfriend took the boy?
She bring him to the hostiles?
You know where they are?
Stop, please!
You want me to stop?
Then tell me what I want to know!
Stuart, please!
We have known each other
for three years.
We are not bad people!
We are not here to hurt you!
Don't.
Whatever you tell 'em,
they ain't gonna believe you.
It's only gonna get
more people hurt.
What are we doing, man?
Beating him is pointless.
- Okay? He's not gonna talk.
- I can make him talk.
- Son of a bitch!
- Easy.
- You're a dead man, Phil.
I'm gonna kill you.
Mr. Radzinsky?
There's still no sign
of Miles or Jin.
But the recruits from last week...
I got their sub's manifest from Amy.
There were 3 last-minute add-ons.
They were the 2 people that shot at you,
Shephard and Austen,
And one guy we can't track down.
He's gotta be a part of this.
Who the hell is Hugo Reyes?
He's the fat guy.
- So what's the rescue plan?
- Rescue plan?
We're going to the beach.
Why do you think we sent you for food.
But they got Sawyer and Juliet.
And there are 30 of them,
and they all have guns.
We can only rescue ourselves,
so let's go.
We gotta do something.
Sawyer would never leave us behind.
Dr. Chang?
What are you doing here?
I could ask you the same question.
But we asked you first.
Your friend Faraday said
that you were from the future.
I need to know
if he was telling the truth.
Dude, that's ridiculous.
What year were you born?
- What year?
- 1931?
You're 46?
- Yes, I am.
- So you fought in the Korean war?
There's no such thing.
Who's the president
of the United States?
All right, dude,
we're from the future. Sorry.
It's true then?
You are my son?
Yeah, it's true.
Your friend, the physicist,
He also told me to evacuate
everyone I could off the island.
He said there was going to be
a massive accident at the Swan.
Now is that true?
He's been right
about everything so far.
If Faraday said
get people off the island...
I'd do it.
Well, then let's hope
he knows what he's doing.
Tell me something.
Why is it that this man looks...
Familiar to me?
You and Erik are coming with me.
Going with you where?
You can untie them.
And...
Would you mind giving us a moment?
- I'm taking them to the bomb.
- What?
Are you insane?
I'm worried about you.
Not in your condition.
Who is he?
The man you're asking about
is Charles Widmore.
He and Eloise are...
Let's just say
love can be complicated.
All right. Let's move out.
So, John...
You, uh, you ready to tell me
where you've been the last three years?
You really don't know?
Well, I know that on the day
that Ben here turned the wheel,
that you and I
were sitting on a log.
There was a bright light.
There was a loud noise,
and then you just...
You disappeared.
Well, Richard, you're just about to see
where I disappeared to.
And after we're finished,
I'd like you to take me to see Jacob.
That's... Not how it works, John.
Is that true, Richard?
Is this gonna be a problem?
You just got back, John.
There's no reason to rush into...
I am the leader now.
Right?
Yes, John. That's right.
Good. Then I would like you
to take me to Jacob. Can you do that?
- Yeah, of course.
- Fantastic.
Let's keep moving.
We're almost to the plane.
What plane?
It's a Beechcraft
used to smuggle heroin.
Flew out of Nigeria, crashed here.
Richard, listen very carefully
because you're only gonna have
about 3 minutes to get this right.
Get what right?
A man's about to walk
out of the jungle.
He's been shot in the leg.
You'll need this
to get the bullet out.
- Uh, I'm sorry, John. I'm not...
- Listen. This is the important part.
You're gonna need to tell him
that he has to bring everyone who left
back to the island.
And when he asks how to do that...
You tell him he's gonna have to die.
Who is that man, John?
Me.
What is happening?
What's happening
is that you're bleeding to death.
Okay, here.
I need to get the bullet out.
How did you know there was a bullet
in my leg, Richard?
- Because you told me there was, John.
- No, no. No, I didn't.
Well... You will.
This must be quite
the out-of-body experience.
Something like that.
Your timing was impeccable, John.
How did you know when to be here?
The island told me.
- Didn't it ever tell you things?
- No, John.
And it hasn't told you where Jacob is
or you wouldn't need Richard.
You've never seen him.
- What?
- Jacob.
You've never seen him, have you?
What just happened?
- Where did you go?
- To give Richard his compass back.
You want the bullet?
Keep it.
- Everything go all right?
- You seemed pretty convinced,
especially when I said
you were gonna die.
I'm certainly glad
that didn't have to happen.
Actually, Richard, it did.
We better get back to camp.
You need to evacuate the island
of all nonessential personnel
and you need to do it...
- What the hell is going on here?
- Aren't you supposed to be at the Swan?
We're supposed to break ground
in less than 20 hours.
We're under imminent threat!
If we start drilling,
there's a high probability
of a cataclysmic accident.
We are drilling and on schedule.
- Horace, you're in charge.
- He's not in charge anymore.
This is my decision,
and it's been made.
- We keep working.
- Put us on the sub.
He's right. It ain't safe.
Put the women and children on the sub
and get 'em the hell out of here.
And if you put me and Juliet
on the sub with 'em...
We'll tell you anything
you wanna know.
You okay with that, sweetheart?
Absolutely.
You want on that sub, Jim?
Draw me a map.
I wanna know exactly
where the hostiles are.
You two know how to swim?
- Why don't we just go around it?
- No, dear, we need to go in.
We have to swim under the pond
to get to the tunnels.
I'm not going.
What?
I'm gonna go back
and find everyone else.
I can't go any further with you.
Not this time.
You can't go back there now.
They know about us.
They... They tried to kill us.
And what are you trying to do?
- You're not going anywhere.
- Don't do that.
We're not used
to telling our secrets to strangers
- then just letting them saunter off.
- I don't care about your secrets.
- I just wanna leave.
- Put the gun...
- Move!
- If she wants to leave,
- she can leave!
- I said stop!
What are we doing here, Eloise?
That man just killed
one of our own people and you're acting
like it doesn't matter.
If these people are right
about what they're about to do,,
- it won't matter.
- And what are they about to do?
So you're telling me you're going
to erase the last 3 years of our lives?
- We can change things.
- I don't know if you're aware of this,
but I've already changed things.
I killed Benjamin Linus,
- and we're all still here.
- It's because you didn't kill him.
Sawyer and me took him to the Others
so they could save him.
- Why did you do that?
- Why did I do that?
Since when did shooting kids
and blowing up hydrogen bombs
become okay?
The 3 of us disappeared
off that plane and ended up here,
ended up now, because this is our chance
to change things.
And if you're wrong,
then everyone on the island dies.
- Do you understand that?
- I'm not wrong, Kate. This is it.
This is why we're here.
- This is our destiny.
- Do you know who you sound like?
Because he was crazy, too, Jack.
You said so yourself.
- Well, maybe I was wrong.
- No, you were right.
I'm going back
to find the rest of our people
because if I can't stop you,
then maybe they can.
The submarine departs in 30 minutes.
All evacuees,
please proceed to the dock.
Come now, Charlotte.
Stay with me.
This is ridiculous.
- I can help you.
- No, Lara, you can't. Go over there.
I want you to leave
- now!
- Why is he yelling at her, dude?
It's the only way
he can get her to leave.
Sorry, man.
- We'd better get moving.
- Wait a second!
It's Jim and Juliet.
Why the hell are they...
Putting them on the sub?
Don't worry.
It's gonna be okay.
Sawyer always has a plan, right?
We'll buy Microsoft.
Excuse me?
Then we'll bet the Cowboys
in the '78 Super Bowl.
We're gonna be rich.
Look, I'm sorry.
I should've listened to you
and get on this sub 3 years ago.
I'm glad you talked me out of it.
Come on, LaFleur. Get in.
Ladies first.
Good riddance.
If I don't see you the other side,
I won't blame you.
Now take a deep breath
and follow Richard under.
There's an opening in the bottom
of the rocks at the far side.
That was a lot further
than I thought it was.
Where are we?
The tunnels.
You wanna tell me how we're gonna
get a bomb out of here?
The same way we brought it in.
I assume you don't mean
through the pool.
It's a 12-foot long,
40,000-pound hydrogen bomb.
No, not through the pool.
I didn't think you'd come.
Well, if this works,
you might just save us all.
And if it doesn't? At least,
you'll put us out of our misery.
All right. Let's get started.
I'll have a tent
prepared for you, John.
- We'll get going in the morning.
- I thought we could leave right now.
Now?
I'm eager.
We can do whatever you want, but maybe
we should go to my tent and...
Is this everyone?
There's another group
at the temple, but...
If you don't mind, I'd like to talk
to everyone here now.
Of course. Be my guest.
Hello, everyone.
My name is John Locke.
I've been told that...
For some time, you all have been
accepting orders from a man named Jacob.
And yet, oddly enough, it seems
that no one has actually seen him.
Now I'm sure
there're very good reasons
why his existence and whereabouts
are secret.
I just don't know what they are.
And to be honest with you,
if there's a man
telling us what to do,
I want to know who he is.
This man, Jacob?
Can he tell us how to bring Jin
and the rest of our people back here?
Absolutely.
Richard has agreed to show us
where we need to go.
So I'm gonna go
and see Jacob right now.
And I'd like all of you
to come with me.
I'm starting to think John Locke
is gonna be trouble.
Why do you think
I tried to kill him?
We're shovin' off in two minutes.
Appreciate it
if you didn't cause us any trouble.
Wouldn't think of it, Nemo.
What are we gonna do
when we get to Ann Arbor?
- We ain't going to Ann Arbor.
- What do you mean?
These guys ain't cops.
They got no authority over us
back in the real world.
So once we dock wherever we dock...
We're free.
"Real world."
I don't even know
what that means anymore.
Hey, come here.
Whatever happens,
I got your back, remember?
I love you.
- I love you back.
- Hold on! - Don't close the hatch!
Horace wants her off the island, too.
We'll let Ann Arbor deal with them.
Actually caught her
coming back into town.
Cuff her over there with the others.
Clear the bridge.
All personnel, lay below on the double.
We're away.
Engineering, take your stations.
Boat is clear for sea.
All hands to your stations.
Prepare to dive.
Clear the bridge.
All hands below.
- Stand by main vents.
- Diving position.
Stand by on ballast tanks.
Ship has been cleared for dive. Repeat,
ship has been cleared for dive.
Stand by for dive. Ship to dive.
Clear engines two and three.
Test two and three.
I'm sure it's occurred to you
that this woman's motivation
in helping us
detonate a hydrogen bomb
is only to annihilate
the Dharma Initiative.
- Yes, but I still trust her.
- Why?
30 years from now,
she's the one who'll tell us
how to get back to the island.
And that makes you trust her?
Well...
Now what?
Beautiful day, isn't it?
Yes, so far.
Richard had some concerns
Concerns about what?
This pilgrimage to Jacob
makes him uncomfortable.
He's expressed
reservations about whether or not
you know what the hell you're doing.
I appreciate you bringing this
to my attention, Ben.
I know we got our differences
in the past, John.
But I'm here to follow you now.
So if you need Jacob to help you reunite
with your people, I'll do whatever...
I'm not interested in being reunited
with my people.
What ? You told Sun...
I know what I told her.
That's not why we're going to Jacob.
Then why are we going to Jacob?
So I can kill him.