This story begins
on September 22nd, 2004,
in Sydney, Australia,
when 324 people boarded
a plane to Los Angeles.
Hold the door!
Like any flight that day,
this was comprised of strangers...
among them, a doctor
and a fugitive,
a soldier
and a rock star,
a con man
and a lottery winner
and an estranged couple,
a single
mother-to-be...
And a man whose faith was lost.
As Oceanic flight 815
flew high over the ocean...
this group of strangers...
It's normal. Was about
to be joined together.
Don't worry.
on a mysterious Island...
This place is different.
Far from home... The pilot said we
were over a thousand miles off course.
They found themselves on a journey...
It's a place where miracles happen.
Run!
They could never have imagined.
We're not alone.
They loved... Yes, I love him!
And lost.
Charlie!
They fought... This is our Island.
And died.
Jin!
And after 108 days...
I'm one of the survivors of flight 815.
Six people found rescue.
Ladies and gentlemen, the Oceanic six.
But the Island...
vanished...
Sending the friends left behind...
Anyone?! What the hell's going on?
Flashing
through time.
We're either in the past
or we're in the future.
Three years passed,
and those who came
home... We made a mistake.
Were beckoned... I don't understand.
It wants us to come back. To return...
Ajira airways flight 316.
to undo their past...
There's a way for you to take it
all back. You think you can come here
and do whatever the hell you
want? To alter their fate...
Get in! I'm gonna
detonate a hydrogen bomb.
Help! To change...
I love you, James. No!
Their destiny. Are you with me on this?
sync and corrections
dny238 www. addic7ed. com
It was their first night on the Island.
First plane crash? What gave it away?
I can always spot the newbies.
and the survivors of Oceanic 815...
You'd think they would've come by now.
Clung to hope for rescue.
I don't know your name.
I'm Kate. Jack.
Get me a blood gas and a c-spine.
Get her up to LCU and
keep her immobilized.
Jack Shephard was a spinal surgeon...
I'm gonna fix you. Consumed by his work.
I got it all. I mean, I had it! His
heart gave out. It's nobody's fault.
Jack was also driven
by a relentless urge
to prove himself to
his father, Christian.
What are you talking about? I'm
talking about you stitching up the sacs
so this girl isn't paralyzed
for the rest of her life.
But Jack would never
get that opportunity
because his father died in Sydney...
That's him.
And it was up to Jack
to bring the body home.
On the Island, the Oceanic survivors
looked to Jack as their leader.
If we can't live together,
we're gonna die alone. You did a
good thing, taking care of everybody
and just giving them
something to count on.
Ah, hey, girl.
Kate Austen grew up in Iowa
where her mother was
married to an abusive man.
You are beautiful.
Then one night, Kate had enough.
Katherine, what did you
do? I took care of you, ma.
She became a fugitive, on the
run for years...
hey, Kate. Until she was
apprehended in Australia.
But when Oceanic 815
crashed on the Island,
Kate found a place to begin anew.
I wanna tell you what I
did. It doesn't matter, Kate.
We should all be able to
start over. On the Island,
Kate found herself drawn
to two different men...
Jack, the honorable leader
and Sawyer, the charming rogue.
Did you tell the doc about you and me?
No, but he knows.
Well, now if that's out of the way,
how about a little afternoon delight?
Freckles, wait!
You need me to make you a mix
tape? Yeah, why don't you do that.
Listen to mommy.
James Ford was just a young boy
when his father was swindled
by a man named Sawyer.
Get under the bed. Don't make
a sound. Open this door!
James' father went into a
rage and killed his wife...
Stop it! What are you doing?!
What the hell are you...
just before he killed himself.
James grew up to become a con man,
taking the name of the man
who had conned his father,
and his need for vengeance
brought him to Australia,
where he believed he'd
found the man he sought.
Sawyer.
But he was wrong.
You don't know what
you're doin', do you?
On the Island, Sawyer
often clashed with Jack.
You're just not looking
at the big picture, doc.
You're still back in
civilization. And where are you?
I'm in the wild.
And he had trouble getting along.
break it up!
Stop! We found a transceiver
but it's not working.
Can anybody help? Yes.
Let's trust this guy!
we're all in this together, man.
Let's treat each other with a
little respect. Shut up, lard-o.
Chain-smokin' jackass.
Some people have problems.
How do you know how to do all that? I
was a military communications officer.
What were you, air force?
Army? The republican guard.
yes, sir.
Before the 815 crashed,
Sayid was a torturer in Iraq.
I guess you have a new
skill set you can use.
But he was conflicted,
and he fell in love
with a woman he tortured.
This isn't a game, Nadia. And
yet you keep playing it, Sayid.
Guard!
Sayid risked his life to
give Nadia her freedom...
Take it.
Then spent his life searching for her.
We know where she is.
When he cooperated with the CIA
to overthrow a terrorist plot,
he thought he'd finally
found a way back to Nadia.
But Oceanic 815 crashed on the Island...
did anybody see that?
And that presented its
own set of challenges...
Terrific.
For this was not an ordinary Island...
Jack!
Not by any stretch of the imagination.
Dad?
And this group was a
very long way from home.
Hey! We've got a bar!
that's French! The
rescue party... it has to be.
It's a distress call.
It's been playing over
and over for 16 years.
Guys...
Where are we?
I know food's scarce...
But your shirt?
When you find the
laundromat, let me know.
for Hugo Reyes,
crashing on the Island
carried its own special burden.
I think the plane crash
might've been my fault.
Don't be daft. How could you possibly...
hey, a lot of bad stuff used
to happen whenever I was around.
(woman on TV and that makes tonight's
mega lotto jackpot drawing...
Hugo played the lottery and won
millions... 4, 8, 15, 16, 23, 42.
(Michael but misfortune followed.
I've had some bad luck, too.
Grandpa Tito died of a heart attack,
and the first house I
bought my mom burnt down.
And when his chicken franchise
was destroyed by a meteor...
he became convinced his
winnings were a curse.
welcome. After the
crash, Hugo tried to find
the brighter side of the Island.
Dudes, listen, if we're stuck here,
then just surviving's not gonna cut it.
We need some kind of relief, you know?
We need some way that we
can, you know, have fun.
The Island had a hold on
all of the survivors...
but one man was determined to
uncover its deepest mystery.
well...
this is... awkward.
John Locke met his biological father
only to learn that he was being used.
You stole my kidney? You needed a
father figure, and I needed a kidney.
Get over it.
When Locke confronted his father,
it ended in tragedy.
Aah! Aah!
He was left shattered and paralyzed,
but he eventually made
his way to Australia
with a dream of conquering the outback.
Just put me on the bus
right now. I can do this.
No, you can't.
You don't know who you're dealing with!
Don't ever tell me
what I can't do, ever!
When Oceanic 815 crashed on the Island,
John Locke rose from the wreckage
and discovered he could walk again.
This gave him faith
that they were on the
Island for a purpose.
You think we crashed on
this place by coincidence?
Each one of us was
brought here for a reason.
And who brought us
here, John? The Island.
But the survivors
were not the first people
drawn to the Island.
Teams of scientists from
the Dharma initiative
came to the Island in the 1970s.
They built research stations
in an attempt to understand
the Island's special properties.
unique electromagnetic fluctuations.
One station was
called 'The Swan'
Where a man named Desmond spent years
entering a code into a computer
to keep a massive amount of
electromagnetic energy at Bay.
system failure. System failure.
one day, Desmond
neglected to enter the code
and caused Oceanic flight
815 to crash on the Island.
The Island's original inhabitants
were not pleased to have visitors.
Goodwin, if you run you can
make that shore in an hour.
Ethan, get up there to that fuselage.
There may actually be survivors. Go!
This is not your Island.
This is our Island.
The Oceanic survivors would soon meet
the Island's original inhabitants.
They would call these people
the others. Hello, Jack.
There leader was a man
named Benjamin Linus,
and he would do anything in his power
to protect the Island. uhh!
If any of them are stupid enough
to get in your way, kill 'em.
hey, welcome
to the Island, man.
Ben Linus came to the
Island as a young boy
when his father joined
the Dharma initiative.
But it was not a pleasant experience.
I'm stuck here on this
Island... with you.
Then one day, Ben met the others.
Take me with you. You're
gonna have to be very patient.
So Ben waited,
and when he became a young man...
Good-bye, dad.
he did whatever it took
to help the others protect
the Island from outsiders
like the Dharma initiative.
You want us to go get his body?
No. Leave him out there.
Ben joined the others and
Rose to power as their leader.
He raised a daughter
and was a devoted servant to the Island.
But when John Locke
arrived, Ben felt threatened
by Locke's special
communion with the Island.
You've been here 80 days, John.
I've been here my entire life.
So how is it that you
think you know this Island
better than I do?
Though not all of the others
regarded Locke as a threat.
When word had gotten back here
that there was man with a
broken spine on the plane
who could suddenly walk again...
Well, people here began
to get very excited.
Locke joined the others
and would soon become their new leader.
But one of them wanted
desperately to leave.
I wanna go home. That's
not our agreement.
You need to stay here
until your work is finished.
we're here.
Juliet was a fertility specialist.
She was recruited by
the others to find out
why women on the Island
could not have children.
I think it happens at conception.
There's nothing I can do
about it... at least not here.
The situation appeared hopeless,
so Juliet joined the Oceanic survivors
in hopes of finding a way home.
I want to know about your research.
What happens to pregnant women?
They all die.
Sun and Jin were from
Korea...
and despite their very
different backgrounds,
they fell in love.
their wedding was joyful,
but their marriage soon darkened,
and Sun planned an escape from Jin
when the two were in Sydney.
Life on the Island
brought them closer...
You're pregnant.
And they fell in love once again.
But Sun's pregnancy put her in danger.
Your wife is very sick.
If she doesn't get off
this Island, she will die.
But there was new hope for rescue.
After nearly 90 days on the Island,
a freighter arrived off the coast.
So Jack led his group to a radio tower
to make a call for help.
I'm one of the survivors
of Oceanic flight 815.
Can you get a fix on our location?
hell, yeah, we can.
They believed they'd
finally found a way home.
A group from the freighter arrived
by helicopter. uhh!
Who are you? I'm Daniel Faraday.
I'm here to rescue you.
what's his story? Half the
stuff he says goes way over my head.
The other half goes way, way over.
Daniel Faraday was a physicist
who devoted his life to
the study of time travel.
He came to the Island
with a science team
and their pilot Frank Lapidus.
but rescuing
the Oceanic survivors
was not the primary mission.
This is Charles Widmore, the man
whose boat is parked offshore.
What does he want? Charles Widmore
wants to exploit this Island,
and he'll do everything
in his power to possess it.
Charles Widmore was a
wealthy and powerful man
who at one time was the
leader of the others.
I'll be seeing you, boy.
He was banished from the Island
and swore vengeance on Ben.
Widmore's freighter also carried
a team of mercenaries
with orders to capture Ben.
Get your ass out here right now.
I'm not coming out of this house.
And in the process...
Ben's daughter Alex was murdered.
If you wanna kill her, go
ahead and do it.
so the survivors and
the others made a deal...
Uhh! Aah!
and joined forces to
defeat the mercenaries.
The helicopter is yours.
You have a safe journey back.
So we can go off the Island?
That's it?
That's it.
He say something to tick you off, freckles?
With Widmore's mercenaries defeated,
the survivors were eager
to leave the Island.
But John Locke chose to stay
and had one request for Jack.
You have to lie about everything.
It's the only way to protect
it. It's an Island, John.
It's not an Island. It's a
place where miracles happen.
Let's go, freckles. I've
seen enough of this rock.
Jack led a group to
the freighter by chopper
as the science team
shuttled others by boat.
But the chopper was leaking fuel.
I'd feel a hell of a lot better
if we were a few hundred
pounds lighter. Hey.
So Sawyer acted quickly...
Sawyer.
And as he made his way
back to the Island...
There it is! The boat... I see it!
The chopper reached the freighter,
only to find it was
rigged with explosives.
it's Jin! Turn around!
we can't do it.
Jin!
Sawyer reached the Island...
What are you doing here?
Believing his friends were safe.
Is that our boat? It was.
Meanwhile, Locke began his new
role as leader of the others...
Welcome home.
And Ben descended to a cavern
deep below the orchid station
to move the Island
and ensure that Charles Widmore
would never find it again.
but the act of moving the Island
created a profound side effect.
Anyone?!
where's the freighter?
A minute ago, that boat
was coughing Black smoke.
Now there's just nothin'?
The Oceanic survivors and
the freighter scientists
were taken on an extraordinary journey.
Whatever Ben Linus did
down at the orchid station
dislodged us. Dislodged us from what?
Time.
they flashed through numerous
time periods on the Island.
What year is it right now? It's 1954.
during one flash...
Jin? Sawyer?
They reunited with Jin,
who was very much alive.
But the flashes... Charlotte!
Were slowly killing them.
Locke believed he knew how
to save everyone left behind.
This is all happening because they left.
We have to go back to the orchid.
excuse me?
that's where all this started.
Maybe it's where it'll all stop.
Aah!
aah!
Hello, John. I'm here to
help you the rest of the way.
Locke turned the same
wheel Ben turned...
Say hello to my son.
and the flashes stopped.
I think it's over. I think John did it.
Now what? Now we wait
for him to come back.
after John Locke turned the wheel,
Sawyer and Juliet were
left stranded in 1974.
Along with Jin and Miles, they joined
the Dharma initiative on the Island
and soon became fixtures
in the community.
Hey, Boss. Evening, Enos.
Sawyer was named head of security,
Juliet became a mechanic...
Somethin' smells good.
And the two made a life
together on the Island.
I love you. I love you, too.
Mm.
when John
Locke turned the wheel,
he was transported to
the Tunisian desert...
three years
in the future, to 2007.
He soon received help
from Charles Widmore.
All your friends who left the Island?
They've been back three years.
They've gone back to their normal
lives. I have to bring them back.
And I'm gonna do everything in
my power to help you do that.
So Locke set out
to convince his friends
to come back to the Island.
I'm not going back. The answer is no.
No, I'm not going anywhere with you.
I only need to convince one,
and if I can do that,
the rest will come.
Locke's task was difficult,
but it was about to become dangerous.
Locke's misfortune gave him one more
chance. What are you doing here?
We have to go back.
Because it's our destiny?
How many times are you
gonna say that to me?
Good-bye, John. Your father says hello.
What?
He said his name was Christian.
he died in
Australia three years ago.
I put him in the coffin! He's dead.
You leave me alone,
and you leave the rest of 'em alone!
Locke believed he had failed,
but in his despair...
Come on. Ben Linus found an
opportunity to get back to the Island
and assume his old role.
I know where we go.
There's a woman here in Los Angeles.
Eloise Hawking.
Eloise Hawking? You sure?
Yeah. Why? You know her?
Yes, John. I know her.
I'll miss you, John.
I really will.
When Widmore's freighter was destroyed,
the passengers on the chopper
had only one place to go.
Lapidus!
Fly us back to the Island!
they made their way back
just in time to see the Island...
vanish.
Where the hell's the Island? It's gone.
That's it, people! We're out of fuel!
they survived the
crash... There's a boat.
And found rescue in
the middle of the ocean.
And on board the search boat,
Jack and Kate planned the next move.
What are we gonna do about Aaron?
I don't know.
you're so good with him.
The last thing I ever thought
I'd be good at is being a mum.
You know, you should try it sometime.
Claire was 8 months pregnant
at the time of the crash,
and on her way to LA to give
her baby up for adoption.
you have a little boy.
She gave birth to Aaron
on the Island...
and soon became close with Charlie.
I didn't want you to
worry. I'll be fine, Claire.
But Charlie drowned trying to
help his friends find rescue.
and not long after,
Claire went missing...
She just walked off in
the middle of the night.
Leaving Kate to care for Aaron.
I think we should say he's mine.
After everyone we've lost,
I can't lose him, too.
Kate, if we're gonna protect
the people that we left behind,
tomorrow morning, I'm gonna
have to convince everyone to lie.
Are you with me?
I have always been with you.
And so they returned home.
Jack, Kate, Hugo, Sayid, Sun and Aaron
would come to be known
as the Oceanic six,
and to protect their
friends left behind,
they lied about their entire experience.
Is it possible there are any
other survivors from the crash
yet to be discovered? Absolutely not.
The Oceanic six tried to
adjust to a normal life,
but three years passed,
and the memories of
their friends left behind
continued to haunt them.
Jack.
Jack began seeing
visions of his dead father
and took flights over the pacific,
hoping the plane would
crash on the Island.
Can I get another one of those,
please? How about a newspaper instead?
When he read the news of Locke's death,
he was devastated.
But in Jack's greatest despair,
he formed a most unlikely
alliance. Hello, Jack.
Did he tell you that
I was off the Island?
He told me that after I left the Island,
some very bad things happened.
And he said that I had to come back.
All of you have to go back.
We're gonna have to bring him, too.
what is this place?
the Dharma
initiative called it the lamp post.
Jack and Ben met with Eloise Hawking,
who was once the leader of the others
and the only person who knew
how to get back to the Island.
There's a commercial airliner
flying from LA to Guam.
Ajira airways,
flight 3-1-6.
So that's it? No, that's not all, Jack.
Eloise explained
that Jack would need to
bring the body of John Locke
on the plane. John is going to
be a substitute of your father's.
You must be laughing your ass off,
because this is even
crazier than you are.
Rest in peace.
Kate had no intention of
going back to the Island.
Aaron? Aaron? But when
she nearly lost Aaron...
Honey, is this your mommy? She began
to doubt her decision to be his mother.
Mrs. Littleton, I'm Kate Austen.
So Kate went to Claire's mother,
who had no idea that
Claire was still alive.
I told him that you're
his grandmother...
that you'll
take care of him while I'm gone.
Where are you going?
I'm going back to find your daughter.
welcome to Ajira air.
Thank you, sir.
And so those who came home
were together once again,
each returning to the Island
for very different reasons.
It's pretty crazy, huh?
this is your
captain, Frank J. Lapidus.
Welcome aboard. Well, hello, doc.
What are you doing here, Frank?
Well, I fly this route all the time.
Sometimes I take the big
birds into new... Delhi.
Is that Sayid? And Hurley.
Wait a second. We're not
going to Guam, are we?
High over the
pacific...
a familiar feeling
swept through the plane.
Dude, you might want to
fasten your seat belt.
I have the controls.
Aah! Aah!
is that a runway?
massive instrument
failure! We're putting her down!
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
This is Ajira 3-1-6.
brace for impact.
Hey.
The Oceanic six were
back on the Island...
Frank? Sun.
Separated by two very
different time periods.
Oh, my God. What happened?!
Sun landed with the plane in 2007...
Where'd they go? they're gone.
Gone where? How would I know?
But her friends found themselves
back on the Island... 30 years
earlier.
Jin?
Dude, I can't believe it.
Oh!
easy on the ribs there,
Kong. I actually missed that.
I missed you, too, Hugo. Sawyer.
Doc.
Good to see you, Kate.
You too, James.
So what's up with you guys
and the old Dharma jumpsuits?
We're in the Dharma initiative.
It's 1977.
Uh... what?
What about everyone else from the plane?
They could still be out there.
What do you mean, everyone else?
Sayid was on the plane,
too, Lapidus and Sun.
As Jin began his search to find Sun,
Sawyer created a cover
story for the new arrivals,
y'all are gonna be the
second batch of recruits
comin' in off the sub, pullin'
into port right about now.
everybody say,
"namaste!" namaste.
30 years in the future,
sun began her search for Jin.
hello.
Who the hell are you?
My name's Christian.
I'm looking for my husband.
I'm sorry, but you have a
bit of a journey ahead of you.
Where did you get this?
Who gave this to you?
He said his name was Christian.
He said if I ever wanted
to see my husband again,
I had to wait here for John Locke. But
considering he's dead, we ain't holding our breath.
well, you might
want to look outside.
A man who looked like John
Locke was on the Island...
Morning.
Hello.
And he raised many questions.
Nobody remembers you being on the plane.
Well, I don't remember being on
it either. What do you remember?
I remember dying.
hello, Ben.
my God.
You're alive. Yes, I am.
Ben, I'd appreciate it if you'd join us.
What, John, don't you trust
me here with my former people?
I'm not afraid of anything
you can do anymore, Ben.
Ben quickly realized
there was something very
different about this man.
How is it that you
know where you're going?
He was no longer plagued by
fear and doubt... I just know.
But more in touch with
the power of the Island
than he'd ever been
before. I brought dinner.
Hello, Richard. It's been a while.
Who's that man he's talking
to? His name is Richard alpert.
He's a kind of... Advisor.
Richard alpert
had lived on the Island
for a very long time,
and he did not appear to age.
He was a devoted servant to
the Island and its leaders.
I am the leader now, right?
Yes, John, that's right.
Good. Then I would like
you to take me to Jacob.
Can you do that? Yeah, of course.
Fantastic.
we all answer to someone, John.
And whom might that
be? His name is Jacob.
The man known as Jacob
was a mystery to the Island inhabitants.
Jacob wanted it done.
Jacob talks to me, John.
No one else has ever seen him?
That's right. How convenient.
Jacob was a spiritual presence
on the Island for centuries
and has seen many people
make their way to his home.
I take it you're here 'cause of the
ship. How did they find the Island?
You'll have to ask 'em when they get here.
I don't have to ask. You brought them here.
Still trying to prove me wrong,
aren't you? You are wrong.
Am I?
Jacob's optimism
was a stark contrast to his Nemesis.
They come. They fight.
They destroy. They corrupt.
It always ends the same.
It only ends once.
Anything that happens
before that is just progress.
But the conflict with this man in Black
had rules which prevented
them from harming one another.
Do you have any idea how
badly I want to kill you?
Yes. One of these days, I'm going
to find a loophole, my friend.
Well, when you do, I'll be right here.
Jacob did not confine
himself to the Island.
Excuse me, sir? Could you help
me? What are you looking for?
He made contact with some
of the Oceanic survivors...
at critical moments in their lives...
Don't worry. Everything's
gonna be all right.
Though they had no idea who he was.
one of these yours? I guess
it just needed a little push.
Some of Jacob's visits
occurred long before
the Oceanic passengers
crashed on the Island.
I'm very sorry about your
mother and father, James.
Be good, Katie.
And for others... Oh. Sorry.
Actually, I'm only going a few blocks,
if you want to share. He provided guidance
that would eventually lead them back
to the Island. Ajira airways flight 316.
It's your choice, Hugo.
But on the Island,
Jacob remained a mystery,
and one man was very eager
to find him. For some time,
you all have been accepting
orders from a man named Jacob.
Well, I'm gonna go and see Jacob,
and I'd like all of you to come with me.
I'm starting to think John
Locke is gonna be trouble.
Why do you think I tried to kill him?
I know we've had our
differences in the past, John,
but if you need Jacob to
help you reunite your people,
then I'll do whatever... I'm not
interested in being reunited with my people.
Then why are we going to
Jacob? So I can kill him.
But in order to kill
Jacob, this man needed help.
Why do you want me to kill Jacob, John?
Because...
Despite your loyal
service to this Island,
you had to watch your
own daughter gunned down
right in front of you. And
your reward? You were banished.
And you did all this
in the name of a man
you've never even met.
So the question is, Ben,
why the hell wouldn't
you wanna kill Jacob?
But Jacob had friends
aboard the Ajira flight.
what's in the box? We
need to show it to somebody.
What for? So they'll know
who they're up against.
Ilana was a devoted follower of Jacob...
and he came to her at a critical time.
I'm here because I need your help.
Will you help me, Ilana?
Yes.
But the man who looked like Locke
finally reached his destination.
Hello, Jacob.
Well, you found your loophole.
Indeed I did.
And you have no idea
what I've gone through
to be here.
Have you met before?
In a manner of speaking.
Outside...
Ilana and her team arrived.
Don't shoot.
Richard, I'm Ilana.
I have something you need to see.
I don't understand.
If this is Locke...
Who's in there?
All the pieces were in place...
Do what I asked you to, Ben.
Leaving Ben
face-to-face...
Benjamin... With the
Island's spiritual leader.
Whatever he's told you, I want
you to understand one thing...
you have a choice.
But Jacob had neglected
Ben for far too long.
Oh... so now, after all this time,
you've decided to stop ignoring me.
Well...
they're coming.
What?
They're coming.
Let me get this straight.
All this already happened. Yes.
Then what am I gonna
say next? I don't know.
Ha! Then your theory is wrong!
Hugo attempted to comprehend
the complex laws of time travel,
and along with Jack and Kate,
he did his best to adjust to life
in the Dharma initiative of the
1970s. Why don't we carpool?
It'll help with global warming,
which hasn't happened yet,
so maybe we can prevent it.
Sawyer's cover story worked,
and they were each assigned
jobs within the community.
And don't forget to
try the dipping sauces.
They really bring out the ham. But
their arrival weighed heavily on Juliet,
who knew Sawyer's history with Kate
and believed her life with
Sawyer would never be the same.
It's over, isn't it?
What's over?
Us... playing house.
we got a
hostile inside the perimeter.
As for Sayid... Move.
He was separated from his friends
at the time of the flash,
and his arrival aroused suspicion of
the new recruits. I guess we found Sayid.
But everything on the Island... <
/i> Hey, can I get a hand with this?
Was about to change. Dan.
Hey, Miles.
what the hell
are you doing back here, Dan?
this is what
I'm doing back here.
Daniel Faraday endured the
time flashes on the Island
with the rest of the Oceanic survivors,
and during a visit to the 1950s,
he learned the others
had a hydrogen bomb.
You need to take it off
this platform and bury it.
When Faraday arrived in the 1970s,
he focused his energies on finding a way
to change the future,
and with a new Dharma
station under construction,
the timing was perfect.
The Dharma folks at
the Swan work site...
they're gonna drill into the ground
and accidentally tap into
a massive pocket of energy.
In order to contain it,
they're gonna have to
cement the entire area in, like
Chernobyl.
they're gonna spend the next 20 years
keeping that energy at
bay by pressing a button...
A button that your friend Desmond...
system failure.
Will one day fail to push,
and that will cause your
plane to crash on this Island.
I think we can change that.
Then that hatch will never be built,
and your plane will land
just like it's supposed to.
And just how exactly do you
plan on destroying this energy?
I'm gonna detonate a hydrogen bomb.
Jack was inspired.
Where's the bomb, Richard? Where is it?
and when Faraday
was shot and killed,
Jack assumed Faraday's mission. We
disappeared off that plane and ended up here
because this is our destiny.
Jack convinced the others
to take him to the bomb.
If he could prevent flight
815 from ever crashing,
he could eliminate all
the pain and suffering
the survivors endured.
Well... now what?
Using Faraday's journal as a guide,
Sayid extracted the core of the bomb.
But there was only one way to
get to the Swan site...
and that was through
the Dharma compound...
that's not good, right?
Which was already on High alert
to hunt down Sayid and the
rest of the new arrivals.
Hey!
get in.
with Jin and Hurley's help,
Jack and Sayid escaped.
I don't know where we're
going. The Swan site.
Swan it is.
Jack, what's at the Swan?
I think I found a way to
get you back to your wife.
Don't worry, dude.
Everything'll be fine when
Jack changes the future.
It's time for me to go.
Be careful. It's rigged
to explode on impact.
Sayid, this is gonna work.
Jack was ready... See
you in Los Angeles.
But before he could finish
what he started... Jack?
He needed Kate on his side.
Nothing in my life
has ever felt so right.
I just need you to believe that.
it won't shut down!
Something's pulling the
drill down. We hit the pocket!
it's about to happen.
Are you with me on this?
Yes.
Then let's go.
When Jack approached the Swan site,
he was spotted by Dharma security...
but help soon arrived.
Uhh!
Aah! put your guns down.
All right, you can
come down out now, doc!
Most believe that what's done
is done.
You cannot change fate,
no matter how hard you try.
And those who challenge what is destined
will always be met
with disappointment...
this don't look like LAX
for fate has a way...
of charting its own course.
Aah! Help! Juliet!
Help! Juliet!
aah! No!
No! aah!
Don't you leave me.
it's okay.
Don't you leave me!
I love you.
No, you don't let go. I love you, James.
No. I love you so much.
No! No, don't let go! Aah!
Juliet!
No!
But before one surrenders
to the hands of destiny...
one might consider
the power of the human spirit...
and the force that lies
in one's own free will.
Come on!
come on!
Come on, you son of a bitch!
Sync & Correction by
dny238 www. addic7ed. com