Previously, on Lost...
Beach camp's right over there.
Can you get me some clothes?
What happened to yours?
I woke up in the jungle like this.
Well, F.Y.I.,
the whole island vibrated,
Kate, Jack and Sawyer saw it, too,
right before they had bags
pulled over their heads--
Don't worry.
Locke's gonna go after them.
- He said so in his speech.
- What speech?
I'm gonna find our friends.
We're gonna find them-- all of them.
I don't know how yet, but I will.
You've got a problem with your roof.
Roof ?
3x08 - Flashes Before Your Eyes
Dude, I don't know about this.
See, you're looking at this all wrong.
He would want us to do this.
He would want us to ransack
is tent and stash?
Yeah, that's sounds exactly like Sawyer.
He stole all this.
I mean, people need food.
They need medical supplies. They need...
shocking amounts of pornography.
Desmondo!
- I need you to come with me.
- You guys find Eko?
Both of you.
What happened?
Eko is dead.
We found his body in the jungle...
buried him yesterday.
How did he died?
The island killed him.
What do you mean
"the island killed him"?
You know what it means.
With the doctor gone the camp is on edge
enough without people having to worry
about what's out here in the jungle.
They are gonna look to you two.
See how you react.
So when I tell everyone what happened,
I need you to...
help keep things calm.
Dude, you okay?
Hey, guys.
What's wrong with Desmond?
What is he doing?
There is someone else out there.
Where's Claire?
Just went for a walk.
I offered to watch the baby.
- I've got her.
- Is she okay?
- What happened?
- Stand back. just give me some room!
Get back Charlie, I know what I'm doing.
Is she breathing? She's not breathing?
Do you want me to help you?
You all right?
Cough it up.
It's all right, Charlie.
- Okay, let's get her back to the tent.
- Is she okay?
- Let me help.
- I've got her, Charlie.
Where are you going?
Hey, how did he know?
How did he know she was drowning?
I'll tell you how he knew.
That guy...
sees the future, dude.
Subtitle : www.sub-way.fr (V.1.00)
Transcript : www.swsub.com & www.ydy.com
She's beautifull.
Aye.
Thanks.
- What's her name?
- Penny...
Penelop.
How are you feeling?
Still a little shaken up.
I go to swimming almost every day and...
the undertow just grabbed me.
You know, if you hadn't...
I thought you were only gonna be
five minutes. Aaron's starving.
Yeah, um...sorry.
Anyway, I just really wanted to say...
thank you.
Thank you so much...
for being there.
It was my pleasure.
Locke doesn't know about anything
except knives and fishing.
There's nothing to know. I don't buy
this precognitive insanity rubbish.
Look, if the bearded wonder
could predict the future,
he wouldn't have ended up here,
would he?
Well, whatever happened to him,
we're gonna have to find out what it is.
You do realize he's gonna know your plan
before you even come up with it, dude.
In that case...
we're gonna have
to get him really bloody drunk.
Beautiful evening.
Aye
Say it, dude.
This morning...
I'm sorry I wasn't more... grateful.
Thank you for helping Claire not drown.
No harm done.
Excellent.
Brought a peace offering.
You know, make the truce official.
Thanks, but no.
I've spent a wee bit too much time drunk
as of late.
Too good for us, brother.
All right, that's fine.
We'll take our drink
and go somewhere else.
What kind of whiskey is that?
It's, uh... just says "Maccutcheon".
All right, then.
Let's have it.
No, the bottle, brother.
I mean,
if you've come to drink, let's drink.
Hey, let's drink.
Are all your songs about
drinking and fighting
and girls with one leg?
Well...
girls with one leg and a heart of gold.
So, Dezzie...
let me ask you something.
Anything, pal.
How'd you know Claire was drowning?
I could hear her calling for help.
Uh, no, you didn't.
You were, like, a mile away.
Well, I suppose I...
I've got good hearing.
You...
hear the lightning as well?
Excuse me?
The lightning.
Just by chance, you pitched
your little rod outside Claire's tent,
and two hours later, lightning strikes.
Thanks for the drink, pal.
I don't know what you're doing.
You'd best tell us.
You think because you turned some key,
that makes you a hero?
You're no hero, brother.
I don't know how you're doing
but I know a coward when I see one.
You don't want to know what happened
to me when I turned that key!
You don't want to know--
- You don't want to know!
- Get him off!
Wait!
I'll see you in another life, brother.
I love you, Penny.
My god.
Des, are you all right?
Stay there. Hang on.
I'm just getting ice.
Are you all right?
- Sweetie, you okay?
- What's happening?
Well, what's happening
is the result of combining ladders,
painting the ceiling and alcohol.
Are you okay? Are you nauseous?
This is my flat.
Although if you want me
to feel at home here,
you might startcalling it our flat.
How many fingers, Des?
Love, look at me.
What's wrong?
Absolutely nothing.
Here.
Let me.
- Thanks.
- Hang on.
You've got paint on your neck.
How's that concussion?
Well, my...
severe head injury is a small price to
pay for the pleasure of having...
you move into my humble...
is...
"rat trap" accurate?
Voilà.
You know you don't really need a job
from my father, Des.
It's not about the job.
I want him to respect me.
Then respect you he shall.
But if for some reason he's too daft
to see how brilliant you are,
it's not the end of the world.
What did you say?
Here you go, luv.
You all right?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
Just...
Just had a bit of a déjà vu, that's all.
Good afternoon.
I'm here to see mr. Widmore.
- And you are?
- Hume, Mr. Desmond Hume.
Hello, luv.
Got a parcel here for 8-15.
Excuse me.
What did you say?
I said, "delivery for 8-15".
Mr. Hume?
Mr.Widmore is ready for you.
Thank you.
Penny didn't tell me
you were an actor, Desmond.
No, it's actually set design
for the Royal Shakespeare Company.
Impressive.
You didn't graduate from university.
No, Sir.
I had to look after my 3 brothers
- after my father--
- Any military experience?
No, Sir.
She's beautiful...
your boat.
My foundation is sponsoring
a solo race around the world.
Something wrong?
No, Sir.
Well, Desmond, I'm going to see to it
that you have a position
in our administrative department.
Not the most glamorous duty,
but it's a start.
- I'll speak to human resources.
- With all due respect, Sir...
I haven't come here to...
interview for
a position in your company.
- You haven't?
- No, Sir.
I came here to ask
for your daughter's hand in marriage.
We've been together
two years now, and...
Pen's moving in...
and...
I love her.
Your permission would
mean everything to me.
I'm impressed, Hume.
Very noble gesture.
- You know anything about whiskey?
- No,I'm afraid not, Sir.
This is a 60-year MacCutcheon,
named after Anderson MacCutcheon,
esteemed admiral from the Royal Navy.
He retired
with more medals
than any man before or since,
moved to the Highlands
to see out his remaining years.
Admiral MacCutcheon
was a great man, Hume.
This was his crowning achievement.
This swallow
is worth more
than you could make in a month.
And to share it with you
would be a waste
and a disgrace
to the great man who made it,
because you, Hume,
will never be a great man.
Mr. Widmore...
- I know I'm not--
- What you're not...
is worthy of drinking my whiskey.
How could you ever be
worthy of my daughter?
Thank you very much. A fiver!
Thank you very much.
- I know you.
- That's fine. See you later.
- How do I know you?
- You can leave your number if you want.
How do I know you?
I don't...
- Where do I know you from?
- Look,
I don't know, but I'll remember
if I could get some help.
Hey, can I get some help?
You're Charlie.
Yeah, name's on the sign.
System failure.
- No...
- Thanks a lot.
The... It was in the hatch.
I remember seeing you. There was a...
There was a computer,
there was a button. We...
We were on an island.
We are on an island, mate.
This is England.
- No, it was real, man, I remember!
- Hey, all right.
This is why we don't do drugs.
No, this... I remember this.
This all happened before.
Today...
This happened today. This...
I remember that he said I wasn't worthy,
and then I came down
and I took off my tie,
and then I lost my tie,
and Penny said, "where was it"?
And then it started to rain!
Your thesis is a bit neat.
The wild card, Partridge,
is unpredictability.
Run the same test ten times,
you'll get ten different outcomes.
That's what makes life so wonderfully--
- Donovan!
- Case in point.
Who could have known that a drenched
Scotsman would appear in this rotunda?
- You've looked better. Not much, but...
- I need to ask you something.
By all means, do.
What do you know about time travel?
Are you bloody insane?
Just tell me if it's possible.
Which part?
The island full of mysterious hatches,
or the computer
which keeps the world from ending?
Forget you're my best mate, all right?
As a physicist, is it possible
that I've somehow managed to
go back in time and
am now living my life over again?
It's not funny, Donovan.
Penny's father berates you
for not being a great man,
and voilà, you've dreamed a future where
you push a buttonto save the world.
These things are not in my head,
brother.
I remember things.
All right, then.
What happens next?
It doesn't work like that.
I don't remember everything, just...
just bits and pieces.
How wonderfully convenient.
I remember this.
I know this song.
The jukebox...
Des, you're worrying me now.
I remember this night.
Graybridge comes back
from two goals down in
the final two minutes to win this game.
It's a bloody miracle!
And right after they win,
Jimmy Lennon's gonna come through
that door and hit the bartender
right in the head with a cricket bat,
'cause he owes him money.
- Seriously, Des-
- Watch, please.
Just watch.
He'll score the first goal right now.
Brilliant save by...
They came back.
They--they won.
Jimmy Lennon, cricket bat.
There's no such thing
as time travel, Des.
And from what I understand,
true love can be just as unlikely.
So,
if you love Penny,
stop messing about and marry her.
You smell like the pub.
That's because I was at the pub.
You didn't get the job.
What did my father say?
Your father... was lovely.
We just both agreed that I wasn't...
exactly qualified.
I say we celebrate.
I say we celebrate that fate
has spared you a miserable existence
under the employ of Widmore industries.
Let me take you out tomorrow.
Let's go for lobsters on the pier,
my treat.
I don't think my failure
to impress your father is any
occasion to celebrate.
Well, the occasion is I love you.
Why?
Why do you love me?
'Cause you're a good man.
In my experience,
they're pretty hard to come by.
Where are you?
I'm right here.
Never done this before, have you?
Is it that obvious?
I can always tell the first-timers.
Now then, may I ask your price range?
I'm not a man of means.
I hope to, you know, one day...
I have just the thing.
This won't blind any queens,
to be sure, but still,
it has the sparkle of life.
I'll take it.
I'm... sorry?
It's perfect. I'll take it.
No, you won't.
Give me the ring. Give it here.
I don't understand.
This is wrong. You don't buy the ring.
You--you have second thoughts.
You walk right out that door.
So come on. Let's have it.
I don't know what you're on about.
You don't buy the ring, Desmond.
How do you know my name?
I know your name as well as I know
that you don't ask Penny to marry you.
In fact, you break her heart.
Well, breaking her heart, of course,
is what drives you
in a few short years from now
to enter that sailing race
to prove her father wrong,
which brings you to the island
where you spend the next three years
of your life entering numbers
into the computer,
until you are forced
to turn that fail-safe key.
And if you don't do those things,
Desmond David Hume,
every single one of us is dead.
So give me that sodding ring.
You're going to be difficult
about this, I can see.
Who are you?
Do you like chestnuts?
What?
Thank you.
That man over there
is wearing red shoes.
So? What, then?
Just thought it was a bold
fashion choice worth noting.
This isn't really happening, is it?
Sorry?
I've had a concussion.
You're my subconscious.
Am I?
You're here to...
to talk me out of marrying Penny.
Well, it won't bloody work.
Oh, yes, it will.
There is no island.
There is no button.
It's madness.
I love her. She loves me.
I'm gonna spend the rest
of my life with her.
No, Desmond...
You knew that was gonna happen,
didn't you?
Then why didn't youstop it?
Why didn't you do anything?
Because it wouldn't matter.
Had I warned himabout the scaffolding,
tomorrow he'd be hit by a taxi.
If I warned himabout the taxi,
he'd fall in the shower
and break his neck.
The universe, unfortunately,
has a way of...
course-correcting.
That man was supposed to die.
That was his path.
Just as it's your path
to go to the island.
You don't do it
because you choose to, Desmond,
you do it because you're supposed to.
I'm gonna meet Penny in an hour.
I've got the ring.
She'll say yes.
I can choose whatever I want.
You may not like your path, Desmond,
but pushing that button is the only
truly great thing that you will ever do.
How much for the ring?
- Am I late?
- Right on time.
Take your photo, lovebirds?
No, thanks, mate.
Come on, something
to show the grandkids.
Come on, Des, let's do it
for all those grandkids.
You'll do it?
All righty.
Let's see what we got for you here, eh?
Ah, a beautiful desert scene.
No, not the desert?
All right.
I know. The Alps.
I love the Alps.
I hate the Alps.
Yeah, not the alps.
Here we go.
Beautiful marina scene.
- Yeah, let's do that.
- It's the one, isn't it?
All right.
Take your coat off. It's boiling.
There's palm trees.
Here we go.
An instant classic.
- Only 5 quid.
- Here we go, luv.
Here you go, mate.
Out of 20.
You're a lovely couple.
Small price to pay
for the memories, right?
I couldn't go through with it.
What was that?
I can't do this.
You can't do what?
Us.
This...
This relationship.
What are you talking about?
How can I?
I can't look after you.
I haven't got a job.
I don't have any...
I can't even afford 5
quid for a bloody photograph.
You deserve someone better.
I know what I deserve.
I chose to be with you. I love you.
Love's not enough.
Being a good man is not enough.
What's this about, Des?
Where's this coming from?
It's all happening too soon--
you moving in,
you're painting rooms,
you're changing things.
I don't even like red.
And why would you leave your flat--
your expensive flat--
Don't do that.
Don't you pretend you don't care,
and don't you dare rewrite history.
I left my expensive flat 'cause you
were too proud to live there, remember?
If you want me to go,
if you want me to leave,
then don't make this about
what I do or don't deserve...
and have the decency to admit
that you're doing this
because you're a coward.
I'm sorry.
But this...
we're not supposed to be together.
What'll it be?
Just give me a pint of your cheapest.
I'm celebratin'.
What's the occasion?
I think I've made
the biggest mistake of my life,
and the worst part is...
I'm pretty sure I've made it before.
That's what they call déjà vu, mate.
Do they now?
I had the wrong night.
I was right.
I was off by a night.
I heard the song, and then...
I remember this.
I'm not crazy!
I can still change things.
I can still change it.
Jimmy Lennon.
Where the hell's my money?
Hey, duck, brother!
Please...
let me go back.
Let me go back one more time.
I'll do it right.
I'll do it right this time.
I'm sorry, Penny.
I'll change it.
How'd you know Claire was drowning?
Well, I could hear her calling for help.
You, uh, hear the lightning as well?
Just by chance, you pitched
your little rod outside Claire's tent,
and two hours later, lightning strikes.
I don't know how you're doing
what it is you're doing,
but I know a coward when I see one.
Yeah, a coward--
You don't want to know what happened
to me when I turned that key!
- Get off!
- You don't want to know!
You don't want to know
what happened to me.
You don't want to know!
- It doesn't matter what you do.
- What the hell are you doing?
You can't change it.
No matter what you try to do,
you just can't change it.
He's wankered.
Let's get him to his tent.
All right, Des, come on.
Give me your arm.
Come on. Stand up. Stand up!
You're a good man, Charlie.
Listen, I'm sorry I tried
to strangle you, all right?
Fair play, mate. Here we go.
Sorry I called you a coward.
Ah, you're all right, pal.
You are gonna tell me
what happened to you.
When I turned that key...
my life...
flashed before my eyes,
and then I was back in the jungle,
still on this bloody island.
But those flashes, Charlie...
those flashes--
they didn't stop.
So...
you're telling me you saw a flash
of Claire drowning this morning?
That's how you knew how to save her?
I wasn't saving Claire, Charlie.
I was saving you.
This morning, you dove in after Claire.
You tried to save her, but...
you drowned.
What are you talking about?
I didn't drown.
When I saw the lightninghit the roof,
you were electrocuted.
And when you heard
Claire was in the water, you...
you drowned trying to save her.
I dove in myself,
so you never went in.
I've tried, brother.
I've tried twice to save you, but...
the universe has a way
of course-correcting,
and I can't stop it forever.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry because...
no matter what I try to do...
you're gonna die, Charlie.
Transcript: www.ydy.com
Presync: Mina Cflily
Resynchro: Guilamu/Sixe
swsub.com