Dude, they'll find out.
Not if we stick to the story.
I don't know, Jack. It could be a risk.
It's the only way.
We have to do this. they're still at it, huh?
Look, we're running out of time.
We gotta make a decision now.
So are we all okay with this?
This is a decision that will affect the rest of our lives.
I'm not taking it lightly.
Kate?
Yeah.
Sun?
- Frank?  - What?
Sorry you got dragged into this,
But we need to know that you're with us.
Whatever you guys decide, I'll just roll with.
Hurley, what about you?
I don't think we should lie, dude.
We need to protect the people that we left behind, Hurley.
- How does lying protect them?  - It protects them from Charles Widmore.
The guy hired a boatload of people to kill all of us.
He faked a plane crash. I mean, you think telling him the truth,
He's just gonna... he's gonna leave them alone?
Look, he's your dad, right?
Can't you, like... Call him off?
There's no calling my father off.
But he'll never find them. I mean, the island disappeared.
We all saw it. It's gone.
Bloop!
You think anyone's gonna believe that...
Believe any of it?
They're gonna think you're crazy.
Not if someone backs me up.
Sayid, come on.
They'll think I'm nuts if I tell the truth.
But what if we all do?
And if we can stick together, we can make them believe us.
- I don't want to spend the rest of my life lying. Do you?  - No.
But...
I don't believe we have a better choice.
I'm sorry, Hurley, but we have to lie.
You know what, dude?
I'm gonna remember this.
And someday, you're gonna need my help,
And I'm telling you right now...
You're not getting it.
Wake up, Sayid!
Sayid!
Sayid, wake up!
No, no, no, no, no! What do I do?!
What am I supposed to do?!
Okay, okay, okay.
Just stay calm.
What the hell were you thinking?
- Ana Lucia?  - You were driving like a maniac.
And why'd you pull over?
I just... I thought...
You didn't think. What if I were real?
What if a real cop stopped you?
They already have pictures of you covered in blood
- with a gun in your hand.  - Actually, it's ketchup.
We went to a-a drive-thru, and, uh...
Well, you need to pull it together.
- You've got a lot of work to do.  - I do?
Let's start with the basics. First off, you need new clothes.
Then you need to go to a safe place.
And take Sayid to somebody you trust.
- You getting all this?  - Yeah.
then get to it.
And stay away from the cops.
Do not get arrested.
Thanks, Ana Lucia.
Oh, yeah. Libby says hi.
Well...
You heard her.
- You really think that thing's gonna work? - Rose, I told you a hundred times.
Of course it's gonna work. Yes. I worked hard on it.
- It's better than rubbing two sticks together.  - Well, I heard that's what you're supposed to do with it.
- Yeah? Well, I think this is gonna work better, all right?  - Well, I think you got too much wood here in the inside.
- That's gonna smother the leaves.  - Rose, if you don't have enough wood, the leaves just burn out.
Fire? Who cares about fire?
Any minute the sky could light up,
And who the hell knows what could happen this time?
Neil, we are trying to focus on what we can control.
You are either gonna help or be quiet!
- Whose shirt is this?  - It's mine.
- Can I have it?  - What does it matter? We're all gonna be dead by sundown.
I'll take that as a "yes, " Frogurt.
- It's Neil.  - Yeah, yeah.
Still in one piece?
- As far as I can tell.  - I figured it would've disappeared
- with the rest of our stuff.  - I guess whatever we had with us when we moved
is along for the ride.
What?
Look who's back.
Welcome back, Dr. Wizard.
- I think it's Mr. Wizard.  - Shut up.
You've been gone for two hours. What the hell were you doing?
Yeah, you're absolutely right. I'm sorry.
I... left my pack in the jungle and I was coming back
And I... I just... it was a while before I realized
that I was just... Uh, I was really lost.
Well, you figure out when the sky's gonna light up again?
- I don't know.  - Well, you at least got a plan?
I think we should take the zodiac,
- Head to a shipping lane.  - No. No, no, no. We can't just sail out on any course.
For us to leave, I need to calculate a new bearing,
And, uh, to do that...
I need to determine where we are now...
Time.
And what are the rest of us supposed to do?
- I'm gonna go find us something to eat.  - And how are you planning on doing that?
Don't worry about it.
I guess we'll get the water.
Dude, wake up!
Come on. I can't do this on my own!
I promise I'll pay you back.
Wait right here.
# They're waiting for me #
# They're looking for me #
# Every single night #
# They're driving me #
# Insane #
# Those men inside #
# My brain #
Shih tzus?
I like shih tzus.
It looks like you "heart" them.
- # The dream police... #  - Rough night?
- # They come to me in my bed #  - Yeah.
Your friend's pretty wasted.
Yeah.
I know you from somewhere, don't I?
- No.  - I think I do.
- Yeah, you definitely look familiar.  - I just have one of those faces.
You're lying.
I don't believe in lying.
I remember!
You're the guy who won the lottery...
And you crashed in that plane.
- No. I must look like him.  - You're him. Hey! Buy a ticket here.
If you win, we get a commission. You're good luck.
Sorry. Wrong dude. Keep the change.
Okay.
Okay, we're outta here.
Mommy, I wanna go home.
Look at your book, baby.
Hello?
I... I can't believe it's you.
No. Hi.
How are you?
Wait, you're in L.A.?
Of course I can meet, yeah. What...
I know exactly where that is. I'll be there in half an hour.
Mommy, we are we going?
To see a friend.
You looking for your pills, Jack?
I flushed them down the toilet.
Thank you.
I was just gonna do that myself.
Yeah, I figured you were.
Going somewhere?
I'm checking out.
Where are we going?
You're going home. And find yourself a suitcase.
If there's anything in this life you want,
Pack it in there...
Because you're never coming back.
Good.
I'll pick you up in six hours.
And where will you be going?
John's casket is outside in a carpet van.
I need to move it somewhere safe.
Safe?
He's dead, isn't he?
I'll see you in six hours, Jack.
Mmm.
Previously on "expose"...
It looks like the scorpion is taking over
all the cobra's business.
you want me to work with Tsunami,
- The dragon lady of Van Nuys?  - Yeah.
I'm here to capture the scorpion,
so if you've got a problem with that, you can go work stage 3.
She's hit!
Hmm.
Hey, dad.
How's it going?
- Have you seen the news?  - No. I just got up.  - Why, are you wanted again?
Uh, yeah. Kinda.
- Is mom here?  - No, she's out shopping.  - hey, set him over.
- Oh, man, he's out.  - Is he... Breathing?
Barely. What happened?
- He got shot by a dart.  - A dart? What, were you in the zoo or something?
- No, we were at the safe house.  - The safe house?
Sayid took me there to protect me.
Then these two guys jumped down, they shot him with darts.
- And now he's... he's in a coma or something.  - Hugo, this doesn't make sense.
And what are you doing out of the mental institution?
Sayid pulled me out. I'm in danger. We both are.
Danger from who?
I'm not sure exactly.
Hello?
Mr. and Mrs. Reyes?
L.A.P.D. Can you open the gate, please?
- Just what kind of trouble are you in?  - Dad, please! Just don't tell 'em I'm here!
All right, but then you're gonna tell me the truth.
Well, give us a call if you hear anything.
You killed three people?
- No. Sayid did.  - Oh. Well, that's better.
Come on. Let's get him to the couch.
- He saved me.  - I think we should call a lawyer right now.
No, no, no. We can't go public. They're after us.
Who? Who is after you?
I don't know. Sayid knows. He can explain.
Sayid ain't explaining nothing.
We need to get him to a hospital.
Did you not hear me? People are trying to kill us.
We go to a hospital, they'll find us!
Like... like "the godfather". It's the last place you go.
Everyone knows it. They... they smother you with pillows
and make it look like an accident.
- Sayid, please wake up!  - That's not gonna work. We need a doctor.
I think I know what to do.
Mommy, mommy, can I push the button?
Sure you can, sweetie.
But we're all the way to the top, okay?
So I want you to press number 3-1. You see it?
You see it? Okay. You get it. 3-1.
Yeah! That's the one!
You pressed it! You pressed it!
Hi.
Hello, Kate.
Have a nice day.
I'll be right with you.
Hello, Ben.
If it's the porterhouse you're looking for, we're out.
No, no porterhouse.
I do, however, have something very important in my van, Jill,
And I need you to watch it for me.
- Is it what I think it is?   - It is.
He'll be safe with me.
- Have Gabriel and Jeffrey checked in yet?  - Yeah. Everything's moving right on schedule.
- How's it going with Shephard?  - He's with us.
- Really? What'd you do? Bribe him with some pills?  - Cut the man some slack.
He's been through a lot. We all have.
Right. Of course.
Sorry.
So keep him safe, Jill.
Because if you don't...
... everything we're about to do...
... won't matter at all.
Aah! Oh, you got it! You got it! You got it!
- You got it. You got it.  - All right! Finally we got...
Why did you do that?
- Because you're supposed to fan the flame, Rose.  - I thought you said you knew how to start a fire.
- And I thought you said you didn't care.  - I care about surviving.
I think you need to take a time-out, Neil.
- You'll get it, Bernard. You will.  - Yeah. All right.
Just... just try again.
Hey.
Give me one second.
I got you something.
Ooh. Hey.
I found these in the jungle.
- Look at that. Thank you.  - There was only two,
- But I thought we could both do with a bite to eat.  - Thank you very much, very much.
You all right?
I just can't seem to shake this bloody headache.
Well... I'm sure it'll pass.
No, it's not just that.
It's the weirdest thing. Earlier, I was...
I was thinking about my mom,
and all of a sudden, I... I couldn't remember her maiden name.
I mean, isn't that odd?
Don't worry about it.
Listen, all of us have been under a lot of stress. Okay?
Daniel...
Do you know what's happening to me?
Dinner!
That's great! Wow! Where'd you get that?
I found it.
What do you mean you "found" it?
It died in the jungle. I found it.
Don't worry. It's fine. It's only been dead three hours.
What?
Who's got a knife?
A knife? You need a knife?
- Oh, it's over by the cuisinart next to the stove.  - What's your problem?
My problem is, we don't have a knife.
W... we don't have anything.
And it wouldn't even matter if we did,
- Because Bernie the dentist can't even start a fire.  - Hey, ease up there, Frogurt.
It's Neil, you inbred.
And I'm not gonna ease up,
Because I'm tired and I'm hungry and I'm screwed!
- We're all screwed!  - Calm down, Neil.
- We're gonna get through this.  - How are any of us gonna get through this?!
Didn't you hear what I just said?! We can't even get fire!
Aah!
Run!
Come on! Split up! Everybody, get to the creek!
Ow! Dan!
Keep moving!
Aah! Uhh!
Uhh! Uhh!
Come on. He's dead.
Come on! You wanna be dead, too?! Come on!
There's nothing you coulda done. We gotta go now!
Dude, the cops are on a stakeout?
You just escaped from a mental institution.
There's dead bodies everywhere! Of course they're on a stakeout!
They think you're crazy enough to come back home.
So... so are you...
... crazy?
Do you think I am?
Well, either that or you're lying to me.
I'm not crazy,
and I have a really good reason why I'm lying to you.
Well...
... well, what is it?
Why is there a dead Pakistani on my couch?!
He's not dead, ma.
Well, he's not breathing.
He's not?!
It's okay, Carmen. We have a plan.
A plan? What are you talking about?
He is breathing... Kind of. Dad, we gotta go now.
Hugo, what's happening?
- Mom, please!  - No "mom, please" me! Why are you all over the news?
- Do you know what they are telling about you?  - Yeah, mom. I know.
- Look, everything's gonna make sense. I promise.  - It better!
Officers.
So how long are you in L.A.?
Just a few days.
I have some business to attend to.
But I wanted to see you.
Here it is.
Her name's Ji Yeon. Here's a baby picture.
Oh! She's beautiful.
Thank you. She's with her grandmother in Seoul.
I hope someday you get to meet her.
It would be nice to see her and Aaron play together.
Yeah.
Kate? Are you all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Are you?
Somebody knows we're lying.
What?
Some lawyers came to see me.
Who?
Two men. They came to my house.
And they asked for a blood sample.
Some kind of lawsuit.
They wanted to test to see if...
To see if Aaron's my son.
Who did these lawyers represent?
I don't know. They wouldn't tell me who their client is.
Then they're not interested in exposing the lie.
How do you know?
Because if they were, they would just do it.
They wouldn't come to you in private.
They don't care that we're lying. They just want Aaron.
But who... who would do that? We...
I don't know, but you need to take care of them.
What do you mean, take care of them?
Wouldn't you do anything you had to
in order to keep Aaron?
What kind of a person do you think I am?
Jin! Jin!
The kind of person who makes hard decisions when she has to.
You get the baby on the chopper. I'll get Jin.
Like you did on the freighter.
You told me to get on the helicopter,
- and you said you'd get Jin.  - We gotta get outta here!
Sun, I hope you don't think...
But you did what you had to do.
And if you hadn't...
we probably all would've died instead of just my husband.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I...
I don't blame you.
So...
How's Jack?
Hugo said I could trust you.
I wasn't so sure. But he swore I could, so...
Can I?
Yes. Of course.
All right.
What happened to him?
Hugo said he got hit with some dart.
Must've been some drugs or something.
- And where is Hurley right now?  - At our house, freaking out.
Let me get my car. Help me move him over.
I'm gonna have to get him to the hospital.
No. No, Hugo said that whoever did this...
- they'll come back after him.  - All due respect, Mr. Reyes, but you brought him to me,
- So I'm gonna do what I think is best for Sayid.  - All right, fine. Take him to the hospital.
But with all due respect to you, Dr. Shepherd,
- When this is over, you're gonna do something for me.  - What?
Stay away from Hugo. Whatever it is you talked him into,
something tells me
you don't have his best interests at heart.
So stay away from my son.
Hello?
Ben...
You'll never guess who just showed up
Who?
Sayid.
Who is Sayid?
I thought he was your friend.
He is my friend...
But he's also got this double life
where he does crazy ninja moves and spy stuff.
But he's a good guy.
A good guy doesn't kill three men.
A good guy doesn't kill any men.
- Mom...  - Don't "mom" me.
You are in terrible trouble, Hugo.
The news thinks you did this.
And if the news does, everyone does.
Why is this happening?
How can anybody want to hurt you?
I don't know.
Tell your mother the truth.
We lied, ma.
What do you mean you lied?
All of us... the oceanic six,
we lied about what happened after the crash.
And what did happen?
Okay.
See, we did crash,
but it was on this crazy island.
And we waited for rescue, and there wasn't any rescue.
And there was a smoke monster,
and then there were other people on the island.
We called them the others, and they started attacking us.
And we found some hatches,
and there was a button you had to push every 108 minutes or...
Well, I was never really clear on that.*
But... the others didn't have anything to do with the hatches.
That was the dharma initiative. But they were all dead.
The others killed them, and now they're trying to kill us.
And then we teamed up with the others
because some worse people were coming on a freighter.
Desmond's girlfriend's father sent them to kill us.
So we stole their helicopter
and we flew it to their freighter, but it blew up.
And we couldn't go back to the island
because it disappeared, so then we crashed into the ocean,
and we floated there for a while
until a boat came and picked us up.
And by then, there were six of us. That part was true.
But the...
but the rest of the people...
who were on the plane,
they're still on that island.
I believe you.
I don't understand you,
but I believe you.
A lot of people died, ma.
And now this bad stuff is happening because...
Well, um...
We shouldn't have lied.
Ow!
You okay?
Yeah,I'm fine. I just stepped on something.
Something jammed...
Son of a bitch.
We should keep moving.
We gotta hook up with everybody at the creek.
- It's a long creek,James. Which part?  - I don't know...the wet part.
Sorry if my plan's not up to others' stan...
Who were those people? Are they yours?
- Did they shoot the arrows?  - You want me to crawl out there and ask 'em?
You don't have to be a wiseass. I'm just trying...
Aah!
Hey!
What are you doing on our island?!
Come on.
Son of a bitch.
Come on, Sayid.
Come on.
Say...
Sayid.
It... it's... It's Jack.
Hey! Uhh!
It's okay. It's all right.
U're okay. You're all right.
Ahh.
What happened?
You're fine. You're in the hospital.
Hurley's father brought you to me.
Hurley's father?
Sayid, you've been attacked.
Where's Hurley?
He's at his parents' house.
Who's with him?
I don't know. His mother, maybe?
Does anyone else know he's there?
Aah!
Aah.
Hello,Hugo.
Aah!
Get away from me.
Get away!
Hugo,I know you're in trouble,
And I can assure you I've taken care of everything.
I have a car waiting for us out back.
The police didn't see me come in.
I can get you out of here.
No way,dude.
Sayid warned me about you.
I'm taking you to Sayid. He's with Jack.
That's why I'm here, Hugo. Jack called me.
How else would I know that they're together?
No.
You're... you're playing one of your mind games.
They would never trust you.
In their defense, I'm not an easy person to trust.
But they came around
When they realized that we all want the same thing.
And what's that?
To go back to the island.
Come with us, Hugo...
And this'll be over. You can stop hiding.
You can stop worrying about the stories and the deceptions.
If you come with me,
You won't ever have to lie again.
Please.
Let me help you.
Never, dude.
Hey! Hey,you got me!
- That's right, you got me! That's right! I'm the killer!  - Stop! Police!
- Face your back towards me! Slowly drop down to your knees!  - I'm the killer. I'm crazy.
I'm a murderer. I killed four people... Three people.
However many are dead, I killed them. I killed them.
I killed them all. J... just... just get me away from here.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything can and will be used against you in a court of law.
You have the right to speak to an attorney
- And to have one present during any questioning...  - Just get me out of here.
If you can't afford a lawyer, one will be provided for you.
I'm gonna make this quite simple for you.
You're gonna tell me what you're doing,
How many of you there are and how you got here. Let her go.
Unlessyou're answering my questions, don't speak.
- I want you to tell me everything or I'll cut off her other hand.  - What?!
- Other?  - The first one isn't negotiable.
It's just to illustrate how serious I am.
No! Hold on! Hold on! Chill out! We're not supposed to be here.
Something's happening to the island.
- There are these flashes...  - Do it!
No! Wait a second! I'll tell you whatever you want to know!
- Do it!  - No!
Uhh!
Uhh! Uhh!
James. Juliet.
Nice to see ya.
Any luck?
Yes.
Really?
Really.
What about you?
I'm having some... difficulties.
Well, you better get busy...
Because you only have 70 hours.
No, no, that's not enough time. I need at least...
What you need is irrelevant.
70 hours is what you've got.
Look, I lost Reyes tonight.
What happens if I can't get them all to come back?
Then god help us all.