Jin. Come on. Wake up, buddy.
wake up.
Sawyer.
How long have I been out?
A while.
Figured you could use the rest.
Claire and locke-- where are they?
I don't know. They said
they'd be back by sunup.
We have to get out of
here before they come back.
Easy. Whoa, whoa.
I'with locke.
That is not locke.
Yeah, I know.
Whoever he is, he says he can
get us off this damn island.
I can't leave.
Sun could be here somewhere.
Fine.
If she's here, you got my word.
We ain't leaving without her.
What's that?
They're back.
Hi.
Hi yourself.
Ahh.
wow.
Jimmy...
mmm.
You are...
Unbelievable.
Mmm.
You weren't too shabby
yourself, darlin'.
Mmm.
baby?
Yeah?
Aren't you supposed to
meet that guy at 9:00?
Yeah. So?
It's 8... 42.
Damn it!
You weren't exactly
supposed to see that.
Jimmy, what are you doing
with all that money?
This meeting is a
potential investment.
We're going 50/50.
The guy wants to see
the money upfront.
Don't worry. It won't take long.
I'll be right back.
Me and you'll go for round-- whoa.
Step away from t case.
take it easy, honey.
Here's the thing, dimples.
I can spot a con man.
I'm married to one.
So I know all about
the pigeon drop.
Oh, what? That case just
accidentally flew open?
How stupid do you think I am?
Pretty damn stupid, actually.
Excuse me?
This is a setup, lady.
There's a van sittin'
right outside.
The room is bugged.
The place is surrounded by cops.
So now you wanna put that gun down,
And we'll work something out.
They don't care about you.
They want your husband.
There's a tracer in the case.
All you had to do
Was take it back to wherever
your hubby's hiding out.
You really except me to believe
That you're working
with the police?
If this place is surrounded,
How come no one came to save you?
I don't need saving,
'cause you're gonna
do the right thing
And put that gun down.
But if you don't,
Well, then all I gotta
do is say the magic work,
And that door busts open.
You're a lousy con man.
Lafleur.
"La" What?
Police! Drophe gun!
behind your back.
Cuttin' it a little close, huh?
Only way to cut it.
put your damn clothes on, jim.
You got it, partner.
You're a cop? Surprise.
let's go. Move.
Is this where you lived?
Yeah.
What is that?
It's all I had.
all right, everybody, listen up!
Come on in. Gather 'round.
I know that everyone is tired.
It was a...
A long and traumatic
night for all of us.
And you all have got a
lot of questions, I know,
And I will make myself
available to answer them.
But right now we
need to keep moving.
We have to take advantage of
the daylight. We wanna know
What happened to the people who
stayed behind at the temple.
The black smoke killed them.
Hey.
I know that what happened
back there was really scary.
But it's over.
You're with me now,
And I promise that I'm
gonna take care of you.
Okay.
Alright, let's move out.
Sounds like you had
a hell of a night.
Yeah.
Jack, hurley, the rest of 'em--
They make it out of
the temple all right?
I saw them leaving on my way back.
What about miles?
I don't know what happened to him.
So you're with lockeow?
I ain't with anybody, kate.
Hello. Is this anthony cooper?
Hi, mr. Cooper. This is
detective james ford, l.A.P.D.
Yeah, we've discovered
some unclaimed property
That might belong to you.
Can you verify you were
in alabama in 1976?
Uh-huh.
Okay, thanks. Sorry to have
taken up your time. Bye-bye.
Can I speak with anthony cooper?
...Sti holding for you.
Sorry. I'm gonna have
to call you back.
Who's anthony cooper?
Old buddy I ran into.
Said he could hook me up with
some laker tickets. That's cool.
What, did you-
-you see him in palm springs?
What?
Palm springs?
Your trip last weekend?
Yeah. It's a blur.
Too much sunshine.
Too many mai tais.
Well, get it together,
because you got a date tonight, pal.
date with who?
Friend of mine, works
with my dad at the museum.
She's great.
Well, if she's so great,
why don't you go out with her?
Hey, I got a girlfriend.
What is your deal,im?
Do you wanna die alone?
All right, look, I go out with her,
You gonna leave me alone?
Throw in one of those laker tickets,
Hell, yes, I will.
Look, I'm already pulling
strings with this guy.
It's just, uh...
I don't know if I can
get another seat.
You know you can
tell me the truth...
About anything.
Are you lying to me, man?
Why the hell would I lie?
About a quarter mile ahead,
there's a clearing.
We'll make camp there.
Everybody fill up on water.
We might be there a couple of days.
A couple of days?
I thought you said we were
gettin' off this rock.
We are.
When?
Maybe we should talk
about this in private?
Great. Let's go.
I wish you hadn't interrupd me.
I'm sorry. I forgot my manners.
I forgive ya.
What happened back at the temple?
How'd you know to rescue
everybody from that smoke thing?
I didn't rescue them.
I'm the smoke thing.
You telling me you
killed all those people?
I gave them the opportunity
to leave peacefully,
And they didn't take it. Why not?
Because they're convinced
That they're protecting
the island from me,
When, in fact,
all I wanna do is leave.
So it's either kill or be killed.
And I don't want to be killed.
We goin' on a boat ride?
You are.
Where?
Hydra island.
What's on hydra island?
The plane. The ajira flight.
The same plane that
brought your friends back.
Unfortunately,
they didn't come alone.
And I have reaso to believe that
Some of the other passengers
mean to do us all harm.
So I want you to go over
there and do some recon.
Well, that sounds safe.
You'll be fine. Yeah? Well,
what am I supposed to do
If I run into somebody
who wants to do me harm?
I'm not worried about that.
Oh, you're not, huh?
No, because you are the
best liar I ever met.
You tell 'em whatever
you need to tell 'em
To gain their trust, find out
everything you can about them,
And then get back here.
Why exactly am I doing this again?
Why do you think, james?
We get on the plane,
we fly off this island,
And we never look back.
Come on.
yeah?
Miles, what's this
girl look like again?
She's a redhead. How many-
how many redheads do you see?
Roger that. Be nice to her--
Yeah, yeah.
Excuse me.
Would you be charlotte?
I most certainly am.
Well, it's a pleasure
to meet you, ma'am.
Thank you.
Archaeology, huh?
What's wrong with archaeology?
Nothin'.
I just figured you'd be
stuckn a room somewhere
Dusting off antiques.
no, I actually get to
travel quite a bit,
To far off and romantic places.
Really?
What, you like an indiana
jones or sethin'?
Yes. I'm exactly
like indiana jones.
You got a whip?
Maybe.
So, um, what about you?
What about me?
Why did you become a cop?
You ever seen "Bullitt
steve mcqueen flick.
No.
Well, then I won't even bore
you with an explanation.
Okay, do me a favor, james,
and don't treat me like
All the other girls who ask you.
Tell me the truth.
Well...
I guess I... Got to
a point in my life
Where I was either gonna
come a criminal or a cop.
So I chose cop.
What?
You know what.
Well, not bad, considering
we didn't have that whip.
Bring it next time.
You want some water?
Mm-hmm. Yes, please.
You mind if I borrow a t-shirt?
Help yourself.
Top drawer on the right.
Thanks.
What the hell are you doing?
Um, I was just looking foa t-shirt.
What did you see? Nothing,
just that you had-
that picture fell out,
And I was just trying to put it back.
What did you see?!
Nothing! I didn't see anything.
Get the hell out.
James, just let me explain.
Get out!
Hey.
Kate.
Do you believe locke?
What do you mean?
That he can get us off the island.
Yes, I believe him.
Sayid, are you all right?
No.
claire! Sayid!
Sayid, please! St--
What are you doing?!
She took him!
She took aaron! Claire,
you had disappeared.
Kate couldn't find you.
She did what she had to do.
She took aaron!
She can't just do that!
This is completely inappropriate.
All right?
Now... You go over there.
I'll deal with you in a minute.
Go.
You all right?
No, I'm not all right!
Hey! Stop!
No! Oh! Don't move!
please don't hurt me!
Who the hell are you?
I'm the only one left.
Excuse me, sir?
I asked you about my brother.
I told you. I'll be
with you in a minute.
Hey, uh, I'm looking
for my brother.
Uh, he was arrested at the
airport on a drug charge.
Sorry. Not my department.
Mornin', sunshine.
Come with me.
Whoa! What the hell is your--
shut up!
Is there something you
wanna tell me? What?!
Is there something
you wanna tell me?
Look, she opened the wrong drawer.
What the hell are
you talking about?
I wanna know what you
were doing in australia
When you told me you
were in palm springs.
I ran your credit card.
I know you went to sydney.
Oceanic. Round trip.
You took flight 815
back 2 days ago.
What the helare you doin'
running my credit card?
You lied to me!
're supposed to trust each other.
So, jim...
What were you doing in australia?
That's none of your damn business.
You know what?
You're right,
Because I'm not your
partner anymore.
You thirsty?
Very.
I'm sawyer.
Ahh.
I'zoe. I can't believe
there's anybody left alive.
I thought I knew
everybody on the plane.
I didn't come on this plane.
What plane did you come on?
Long story.
What the hell happened here?
What killed all those people?
I...
We--we crashed here,
And we were all just waiting for...
Someone to rescue us.
I was out collecting wood
When I heard...
Screaming.
Screaming?
When...
When I came back...
They were-- they were all dead.
I spent the last two days
dragging their bodies up here.
I didn't feel it was right to
leave them out there in the sun.
Are you alone?
No. I'm with a group of people
back on the main island.
I can take you back there.
Oh, thank god.
Trust me,
God's got nothing to do with it.
I'm sorry, kate.
Excuse me?
I have to take responsibility
for claire's behavior.
I was the one who told her
that the others had her baby.
Why would you tell her that?
Have you ever had an enemy?
Someone that you needed to hate?
Very powerful, isn't it?
Claire was devastated
without aaron.
She needed something to...
Something to keep her going, so...
I gave her something to hate.
And then when you
told her the truth,
All those feelings,
all--all that anger
That she'd been holding
on to for so long--
It had to go somewhere.
Very insightful...
Coming from a dead man.
Mm.
Well, nobody's perfect.
I'm sorry that this happened.
And I'm sure if you give her time,
Everything will be all right.
I promised before that I
would keep everyone safe,
And that means you, too, kate.
Where did sawyer go?
I'll show you.
think that thing'll still fly?
I don't know.
It'll take a bit of work
And someone who knows how to-
how to do it.
I-I take it you haven't
come across the pilot?
No, ma'am.
How many people did
you say were with you?
Couple dozen.
Did they all come on the
same plane with you?
Some, not all.
When did you crash?
Long time ago.
Do you all have guns?
I mean, whoever killed
those people back there,
They--they might come back.
Yeah, we got plenty of guns.
You wanna grab that end?
Where'd you say you were headed?
What's that?
Your flight. Where were you going?
Oh. Uh...
Guam.
What's in guam?
My boyfriend.
You're good, sweetheart,
but you ain't that good.
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
Drop it now!
Your name even zoe?
Is yours sawyer?
Down on your knees!
All right, all right. You got me.
Take me to your leader.
That island over there-
that's where I sent sawyer.
You could've just told me
That you sent him to the island
where we were locked in cages.
You didn't have to
bring me down here.
Sure, but then I wouldn't
have gotten to talk to you.
You referred to me as a dead man.
I am not a dead man.
I know what you're feeling, kate.
I know what you're going through.
How do you know that?
Because...
My mother was crazy.
A long time ago, before I...
Looked... Like this,
I had a mother, just like everyone.
She was a very disturbed woman.
And as a result of that...
I had some growing pains...
Problems that I'm still
trying to work my way through.
Problems that...
Could h-have been avoided,
Had things been different.
Why are you telling me this?
Because now... Aaron...
Has a crazy mother, too.
Get in. He's waiting for you.
It's not me I'm worried about.
I just don't know what I'd do
If anything ever
happened to you and ma.
Anyway, nothing's
gonna happen to us.
Not today, anyway.
It's the way you live this life,
Each day one at a time.
Now if you spend your whole life
Worrying about something
that's gonna happen,
Before you know it,
your life's over
And you spent an awful
lot of it just worrying.
Hey, you hear that?
That's what life's all about--
Laughing and loving each other,
And knowing that people aren't
really gone when they die.
We have all the good
memories to sustain us
Until we see 'em again.
It's hard not being afraid, pa.
I know, sweetheart
I know.
You've got to be joking.
May I come in?
Absolutely not. Why not?
You don't get to kick me out at 3:
00 in the morning
And then come 'round the next day
With puppy dog eyes
and a sad sunflower.
Look, I don't know
If you're just lonely or
guilty or completely mad.
Buy you know what? I don't care.
You blew it.
What you got in here?
None of your business. Keep moving.
Come.
He's here, sir.
Thanks, zoe.
Would you leave us, please?
Of course.
Hello, mr. Ford.
My name is charles widmore.
Do you know who I am?
Of course I do.
You're the fella sent a
freighter to the island,
It's sad, really...
How little you actually know.
Well, I know you murdered
all them people out there
And dropped 'em in the ditch.
We didn't murder those people.
But I don't expect
you to believe that.
Good, 'cause I don't.
So why don't you tell me what
brought you over to this island?
John locke sent me.
John locke's dead.
I think we both know the
guy I'm talking about
Is not really locke.
So here's the deal, chief.
I'll go back over there and
tell him the coast is clear,
That I didn't find anybody.
Then I'll bring the old man
right to your doorstep.
Then you can kill him.
And what do you want
in exchange, james?
One-- the people I come back with--
The people on my boat--
Don't get touched,
not even a hair on their head.
And two--
You give us safe
passage off the island.
How do I know I can trust you?
Same way I know I can trust you.
So...
Do we have an agreement?
I suppose we do.
Kate.
I--
I just, um...
I-I just wanna say I'm sorry.
I don't know why I did that.
I know everything you did was
just 'cause you care about me
And out aaron.
thank you.
Thank you for taking care of him.
I'm sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
It's okay.
How'd go?
You didn't really
send me over there
To find passengers from
that plane, did you?
No.
Well, in case you're interested,
They're all dead.
Well, that's terrible.
What happened?
I don't know.
Well, what do you know, james?
I know there's a man
over there on that island
That ain't gonna let us get
on that plane without a fight.
Came over on a sub. Name's widmore.
Charles widmore?
Well, I guess y'all
know each other.
He ain't alone.
I counted at least six
armed compadres with him,
Not to mention whatever
crew's on that sub.
There's a locked room on there-
somethin' they're hiding.
And they're settin' up pylons,
like the ones at new otherton.
You know...
The ones that keep
out that smoke thing.
And what did you
tell them about me?
I told them
I'd tell you the coast was clear
and bring you back with me.
Walk you right into their trap.
That way, they could kill you...
Which means they'll be
caught with their pants down
When we change our plan of attack.
I appreciate your loyalty, james.
You said you were gonna
get me off this island.
Deal's a deal.
What are you doing here?
Get in t car.
Who's sawyer?
When I was 9 years old,
My father shot my mother,
and then he killed himself.
Sawyer was the reason why.
He was a grifter.
Con man.
I've been hunting him down
Since the day I left the academy.
I chased down a lead in australia,
Got a name--anthony cooper.
I ran the name. I got a
list of anthony coopers,
And I've been calling them.
And when I find the right one...
I'm gonna kill him.
Why didn't you tell me any of this?
I knew you'd try and
talk me out of it.
Damn right.
Fair enough.
whoa! My car!
Hey!
Uhh!
Son of a bitch.
What's for dinner?
Rabbit.
I think.
Good. I'm starving.
What are you doing running
errands for locke?
I ain't runnin' errands for nobody.
He said he sent you over
to the other island.
Did you find the plane?
Yeah.
And that ain't the
only thing over there.
A guy named widmore set
up camp on the beach,
Got a whole team with him--
Guys with guns.
They're here for locke.
So what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna let them fight it out.
And while they got their
hands full with each other...
You and me are gettin'
the hell off this island.
Even if we could get on that pla,
who's gonna fly it?
We ain't taking the plane,
freckles.
We're taking the sub.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Transcript by Addic7ed.com