Previously on Lost...
- Can I ask you something?
- Anything, Pal.
How do you know Claire was drowning?
I could hear her calling for help.
You...
Hear the lightning as well?
I wasn't saving Claire, Charlie.
I was saving you.
When I saw the lightning hit the roof,
you were electrocuted,
and when you heard Claire
was in the water...
You drowned trying to save her.
I've tried, brother,
I've tried twice to save you,
but no matter what I try to do...
You're gonna die, Charlie.
You're insane, mate.
Superman can fly
round the entire planet
in the blink of an eye.
Dude,
if we're going by a pure foot race,
Supes would get dusted by the Flash.
But why would the man of steel
agree to a sodding foot race?
Uh, for charity?
And Flash would totally win,
'cause he can, like,
vibrate through walls and stuff.
Vibration.
Well and what would Superman do
if he came against a wall?
Well, no smashing allowed.
No flying, no smashing.
Any other restrictions
I need to know about?
Perhaps we should fit superman
with a pair of kryptonite...
The hell?
No, don't! Don't touch it.
- My God,my God!
- Just breathe.
Looks like it's homemade.
We've got to get back.
- No! You help!
- I can't help!
I'm sorry, mate.
Here it is. Here it is.
Superman can fly around
the entire planet...
Where's the wire?
Did you eat those mushrooms
Jack warned us about?
Listen to me.
There's a wire,
a cable buried in the sand.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
This is future crap, isn't it?
The cable ! Do you know where it is?
- This is important.
- Why?
Superman...
Because someone's coming.
Subtitles: swsub.com
God tests our faith in many ways.
So, as you well know,
we have our own test here...
A vow of silence that lasts
as long as we see fit.
This challenges both one's patience...
and his faith.
For some, it may last a week.
Those we're less sure about, a month.
Personally, Desmond,
I never thought you'd last...
and so now I stand corrected.
For whatever reason,
your path has led you here.
And now you're one of us.
Welcome, brother.
Thank you...
Brother.
Morning, Jack.
Must be nice
to wake up in your own bed.
Home, sweet home.
So I was wondering
if I could borrow your first aid kit.
I've...
twisted my ankle.
- You want me to take a look at it?
- No, you're all right.
I've taped my share of ankles.
Right.
Thanks.
Something wrong, Hurley?
No, just...
keeping Desmond here company
'cause we're friends.
Bring that back when
you're done with it, okay?
Absolutely.
What the hell was that?
Do you want him to get suspicious?
Suspicious of what?
Oh, this is like when you knew
Claire was drowning, isn't it?
That's why you got the first aid kit.
Someone's gonna get hurt.
- Is it me?
- No. It's just a precaution.
Look, dude, you want me
to take you to the wire?
I want an explanation.
I saw a sequence of events...
Things that are gonna happen.
What'd you see?
It was...
It was like a sort of jigsaw puzzle,
only I didn't have
the picture on the box,
so I don't know
how the pieces fit exactly.
But one of the pieces.
The first one...
It was you,
pulling the cable out of the sand.
So what are the other pieces?
If I tell you that,
it'll change the picture on the box.
So what?
Isn't that the point...
Preventing something bad?
Not this time.
So you're not trying to stop
something from happening.
You actually want it to happen.
More than anything.
Hey, Freckles, you home?
Thought you weren't
allowed to use nicknames.
You weren't around
when I lost the bet,
so you're...
exempt.
What's up?
I wanted to ask you something.
I'm up here.
So did you tell him?
Did I tell who what?
You know.
Did you tell the doc...
about you and me?
But he knows.
He saw us on one
of their surveillance monitors.
She said the camera was broken.
Well, they had another camera.
Perverts.
Anyway, he knows.
Well, now that that's outta the way...
How about a little afternoon delight?
That means sex.
Come on, Freckles, wait. Now...
Do you need me
to make you a mix tape?
Yeah, why don't you do that?
Dude, you're gonna have
to tell me again.
What do we need Jin for?
Because he was there with us.
On the beach,
when I find the cable?
This way. Here it is.
That's right.
In one of your puzzle flashes?
Aye.
So... If he doesn't come,
then neither does the someone
you won't tell me anything about.
That'd be the long and short of it,
but I've no bloody idea
how I'm gonna get him to come with us.
Watch the master.
- Camping?
- Yeah,
you know, like,
sleeping under the stars,
fire on the beach, marshmallows.
Camping.
Everybody likes marshmallows.
Good man.
Get food, water.
Where are you going?
We need one more.
How daft do you think I am?
This isn't a camping trip.
You've had another one
of your visions, haven't you?
What was it this time?
Someone's coming to the island.
Coming?
As in someone who's not already here?
How the hell is that gonna happen?
I can't tell you.
It's got nothing to do with me?
Well, you're a part of it, yeah,
as are Jin and Hurley.
Right, but with all due respect,
you haven't previously told
Jin or Hurley that they're gonna die.
Well, that's not gonna happen,
not this time.
Can I bring my guitar?
Absolutely.
All right, I'm in.
You had me worried there for a second.
This is it.
Well, how can you tell?
'Cause that's exactly where
I followed the wire into the jungle.
Where is it, then?
Wait to go, dude§
Here it is !
Here it is!
The beacon fell this side of the rise.
Just one thing...
Last time I followed this wire
into the jungle,
I almost got kebabbed by one
of Rousseau's spiky death trap things.
Cut her down.
We're not going in the jungle!
Well, not yet.
It's getting late, so,
we'll camp here the night.
Camp.
So when do they get here...
your mysterious someone?
Soon.
You do realize you are free
to talk again, brother Desmond?
Used to being quiet, I suppose.
Moriah.
I find the name
the brothers have chosen
for the wine made here...
interesting.
And why is that, brother?
Well, Moriah is the mountain
where Abraham was asked to kill Isaac.
It's not exactly the most...
festive locale, is it?
And yet God spared Isaac.
Well, one might argue that...
God need not have asked Abraham
to sacrifice his son in the first place.
Well, then it wouldn't have been
much of a test, would it, brother?
Perhaps you underestimate
the value of sacrifice.
Brother Desmond!
I met this man waiting at the gates.
He says he needs
to have a word with you.
Sorry, sir.
Forgive me, brother.
The oatmeal's awesome.
It is, huh?
It's strange, huh?
What's that?
Being back,
not...
looking for a way out of a cage,
not finding a reason to go running off
into the jungle again.
I almost don't know
what to do with myself.
Well, enjoy it.
I'm sure something
will go wrong soon enough.
Well, my big, dangerous
adventure for tonight
is gonna be
doing the dishes in the ocean.
- Well, be careful.
- I'll try.
Can I borrow that spoon?
Thanks.
Good night.
Yeah, good night.
What, my doorbell busted again?
What the hell are you doing?
Shut up and don't talk.
You crying?
I said shut up.
You got it.
Dude, I love the part about the bird.
It was a bird, right?
- You.
- Me?
Have you heard the one
about the chupacabra?
Chupa?
Yeah, it's like a bear with spines,
but Mexican...
Thanks.
Who's that?
Her name's Penny.
That's not bad, Des, not bad at all.
So how did you manage
to leave her behind and come here?
Because I'm a coward.
Sorry.
You and me both, pal.
You know,
I tried to run away from her, and she...
She tracked me down.
"With enough money and determination,
you can find anyone," she said.
You know,
I used to get through my nights
thinking that she actually meant it,
that she never gave up...
that maybe she spent
the last three years...
looking for me.
What's that?
Is that a helicopter?
Rescue.
Is that how a helicopter's
supposed to sound?
We gotta go out there.
- Out there?
- Well, yeah.
In what?
Well, we gotta do something.
Look.
Look!
My god.
No dude, it's not a food drop.
You saw the beacon thing.
Someone, like, ejected.
Yeah, but that was a helicopter.
You can't eject from a helicopter.
Well, maybe they jumped.
All that matters is that they're here.
"They"?
How do we even know it's a person?
Because he said "someone" was coming.
Where are you going?
Out to where it fell.
- Come on. Let's go.
- No, slow down.
We're not gonna trudge out
into the jungle
- in the middle of the night.
- Yes, we are.
Were you even listening to Hurley
when he mentioned Rousseau's death trap?
Now it's gonna be light in two hours.
- We'll wait until...
- She can't wait.
She?
They. Whoever it is...
could be hurt.
We have to go all four of us now.
Why?
Because that's the way
it's supposed to happen.
Right. Well, I guess
it's supposed to happen without me.
Superman...
We'll leave at first light, then...
together.
Terrific.
Is your sister in?
Leave. Now.
Let him be, Derek.
Hello, Ruth.
So you're a monk now, are you?
Well, technically
I'm still what they call a novice,
- till the abbott says...
- Why are you here, Desmond?
Well, now that my initiation is done...
I felt like I owed you an explanation.
You can never begin
to explain what you did.
You left one week before the wedding.
Everything was planned,
bought and paid for.
You just disappeared completely.
I had a calling.
We dated for six years,
and the closest you ever came
to a religious experience
was Celtic winning the cup.
Yes, I was scared about the wedding,
so I had a few pints, too many, maybe.
I raised my eyes, and I asked,
"am I doing the right thing?"
And that's the last thing I remember.
And when I woke up,
I was lying on my back
in the street,
and I don't know how I got there.
And there was this man standing over me,
and he reached out his hand
and he said to me,
"can I help you, brother?"
And the first thing I noticed was...
the rope tied around his waist,
and I looked at him and...
I knew...
I was supposed to go with him.
I was supposed to leave...
everything that mattered behind.
Sacrifice all of it...
for a greater calling.
Well, it's a good thing
a bloody shepherd didn't help you up,
or I suppose you'd be off
with the sheep, wouldn't you?
Next time you want to break up
with someone, Des,
don't join a monastery.
Just tell the girl
you're too bloody scared.
You a doctor or a carpenter?
What, your dad never taught you
to use a hammer?
No, my dad taught me how to drink.
Well, at least it's something.
Hope I'm not interrupting.
You two arguing over
who's your favorite other?
What do you want, Sawyer?
Oh, what I wanted, doc,
was to inform you
there's been some developments
since you were A.W.O.L.
So tell me...
how's your backhand?
Where'd you get the table?
Don't you recognize it?
It fell out of the purple haze
when the hatch went blammo.
If we don't play every 108 minutes,
the island's gonna explode.
Finally, something I can beat you at.
You know, considering
I haven't played since I was 12,
I wouldn't be too proud.
What is that, 18-point?
It's kinda strange, huh...
being back?
Something funny?
Kate said the same thing
in the kitchen last night.
- She did?
- She did.
19-point.
So you guys ate together, huh?
No, Juliet and I had dinner together
last night.
Best two out of three?
You got it.
So what's next?
Next?
Yeah, you saw the wire,
the flashy thing falling out of the sky.
Now what?
- Maybe I can help you find...
- That's it.
There is no next.
We find the beacon.
Why are you lying to me, mate?
Look, mate,
I've saved your life three times now.
If that hasn't bought me your trust,
I don't know what will.
Let's move.
Dude...
seriously, I'm gonna have a coronary.
Actually, you're not,
and if you don't get a move on,
we're not gonna make it
before nightfall...
Look at this!
It can't be Rousseau's.
If it was Rousseau's, a massive rock
would be flying at my head right now.
Don't move.
- What are you doing?
- Don't move.
Did that come down
with the flashing red light thingy?
Walkie-talkie.
No, dude, that's a satellite phone.
Crap, it's dead.
Shocker.
My God.
Is that you?
Then who's she?
That would be Penny.
What's this?
Your mix tape.
Well, you gonna take it, or ain't you?
"The best of Phil Collins," huh?
Don't get picky.
And if Bernard asks,
I don't know a thing about it.
Thanks, James.
So why'd you jump me last night?
What?
Was it 'cause you saw the doc
hanging out with Juliet?
It is not like that.
It's not?
You ain't gotta use me, Freckles.
All you gotta do is ask.
You think it's her, don't you?
Who?
Your girl... Penny.
You think it's actually her
who bailed out of the helicopter.
Earlier I hoped it.
Now I know it.
Why didn't you tell us?
Would you come if I had?
Of course.
Why wouldn't I?
I didn't wanna tell you because...
I didn't want anything to change.
Fair enough.
Look, if whatever you're seeing
leads to your girl getting us rescued,
why would we want to change anything?
Right?
Right.
Thanks for the heads-up
about bringing an umbrella, dude.
Brother Desmond?
What are you doing?
Well, I believe I'm...
getting pissed on our lovely wine.
That bottle of our lovely wine
fetches over 100 quid.
We've only bottled 108 cases this year.
It's just as well we've taken
a vow of poverty then, isn't it?
We've also taken a vow of charity.
Right.
Something tells me, Desmond,
that you're not cut out to be a monk.
Well, you know, I've had a tough week.
I'm sorry for the wine.
I'll take the penance.
I'm afraid
you're beyond penance, Desmond.
Brother Desmond.
Not anymore.
Are you firing me?
I am indeed.
You can't do that.
- I heard the call.
- I'm sure you did hear the call,
but the abbey clearly isn't where
you are meant to end up.
I have little doubt that God
has different plans
than you being a monk, Desmond...
bigger plans.
- Aye, sure he does.
- He does.
You've just spent
too much time running away
to realize
what you may be running toward.
What am I supposed to do now?
Whatever comes next.
Who's Penny?
She's a chick Desmond used to date,
and now he thinks she fell from the sky.
So we're gonna go save her life,
and she's gonna get us rescued.
Dude, even if I spoke korean,
it wouldn't make any sense.
We'll move faster if we stop talking.
She might be hurt.
I'm moving as fast as I can.
In case you haven't noticed, dude,
I'm not exactly the Flash.
The Flash is pathetic.
You got something
against the fastest man alive?
You're insane, mate!
Superman can fly around the entire
planet in the blink of an eye.
Dude, if we're going
by a pure foot race,
Supes would get dusted by the Flash.
But why would the man of steel
agree to a sodding foot race?
Uh, for charity?
The Flash would totally win,
'cause he can, like,
vibrate through walls and stuff.
Vibration!
And what would Superman do
if he came up against a wall?
Well, no smashing allowed.
No flying, no smashing.
Any other restrictions
I need to know about?
Perhaps we should fit Superman with
a pair of kryptonite ballet slippers...
The hell?
Charlie, duck!
Dude.
This way.
No, the beacon
fell this side of the rise.
No, there.
How about we split up?
Me and Charlie'll go that way.
You and Jin go around,
and we'll meet up
at that ridge over there.
You and Jin.
I'll stick with Desmond.
You said "duck."
- Sorry?
- You shouted, "duck."
You knew, even before we set off.
- You knew all this time, didn't you?
- Aye.
Then, why didn't you say anything?
Because if I told you the truth,
you wouldn't have come.
Oh, you need me to come
'cause I was part of your vision.
You thought the only way
you could get your girl back
was if took an arrow in the head.
You were gonna sacrifice me.
If the flashes don't happen exactly
as I saw them,
the picture changes.
I was supposed to let you die, Charlie.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means it's bloody pointless.
I keep saving your life,
and what good has it done?
It's just gonna keep happening
again and again.
Maybe that's the point, yeah?
- Maybe it's a test.
- A test?
Like God testing Abraham,
except I failed...
Because I changed what I saw.
Hey, can you hear me?
Dude, she's not moving.
I'm sorry, Penny.
I'm sorry.
I was afraid you'd left
without saying good-bye.
No.
I nearly took this with me.
If you're not in a hurry,
brother Martin's
heading into town in a few hours.
He can give you a ride.
That is, if you don't mind
doing some heavy lifting.
All ten cases are ready to go.
Desmond there
is just getting the last one.
Thank you,
and my father sent the check in advance?
And please thank him
for his generous donation.
Always a pleasure to see you.
Good-bye, Desmond.
I think we should be able
to fit it all in the back,
and if not,
we'll put the rest in the front.
Is that all right?
Absolutely.
You'd better drive safe, miss.
This vineyard only makes a limited
number of these cases each year.
Is that so?
Aye. It's because the monks are lazy.
You know, it's easier
making grape jelly than wine.
And how do you know so much
about monks?
I'm an ex-monk.
Really?
As of last night.
I was fired.
Well, it wasn't that funny.
I'm sorry. I've never... I've...
I didn't know monks could be fired.
Oh, they can.
You know, I was told
in no uncertain terms
that the abbey
wasn't where I was meant to end up,
just a...
step along the path.
You know,
God allegedly has bigger plans for me.
Something tells me
you don't entirely believe that.
I suspect that's because I don't.
Well, maybe they're right.
I just think,
if you hadn't gotten fired,
we wouldn't have met,
and then...
how could you possibly help me
unload these crates in Carlisle?
Did I say
I was coming to Carlisle with you?
Not yet.
I mean, of course,
if an ex-monk already has plans...
You know, I don't usually get into cars
with strangers.
Well, in that case, I'm Penelope.
Penny.
Desmond.
Very nice to meet you, Penny.
She's alive.
Stand back!
Get away from her!
I'm here. I'm here, Penny.
- Be careful.
- Just get off, Charlie.
Sorry, Penny. Sorry.
Desmond?