Previously on "lost"...
what is that?
The secondary protocol.
What does it say?
If linus knows that
we're gonna torch the island,
there's only one place that he can go.
What do you mean,"torch the island"?
go and gas up the chopper,frank.
I think they want us to follow 'em.
Are you jacob?
No,but i can speak on his behalf.
Did he tell you what we're supsed to do?
He wants us to move the island.
We got a little chop ahead.
Put that away,man.
You're freaking me out.
We need this thing.
With the cargo we got back there?
Bad mojo.
Ms. Decker?
Yes?
Wanna head back there and
let 'em know we're landing?
Sure.Of course.
we're coming in for a landing.
It's a military facility just west of honolulu.
It's completely private.
Your...your families are already here.
Now there's a lot of press
that wanna speak to you,
but as far as oceanic is concerned,
you don't have to speak to any reporters.
Wel talk to 'em.
Is that all right with all of you?
It's fine.
We all agreed.
We just...we just wanna get it over with.
Okay.
Um,they're referring to
you as the "oceanic six."
That's not the best branding as far as
we're concerned,but it's catchy.
We'll see you on the ground.
we all know the story.
If we get any questions that we don't
wanna answer,or that we can't answer,
let's just keep our mouths shut.
It's okay.They'll...
they'll think that we're in shock.
We are in shock,jack.
Well...
then this should be easy.
it was sayid and...and desmond
in the helicopter,right?
I mean,it had to be.
Why else would they have dropped
that thingamabob right over us?
then why wouldn't they just land?
I don't know,but this thing
is trackin' the chopper.
So if they were on it,
they want us to know we're they're going.
it's a phone,right?
Can't we just call?
Well?
Don't try anything stupid.
Understood.
- put it down over there.
- is that from the chopper?
we're still 5 klicks from the site.
I said put it down,frank.
Okay,gear up,boys.
Soon as we hit the ground,
we deploy to the orchid.
Heads down!
Let's do this.
you know what "the orchid" is?
No.
I didn't hear desmond or sayid either.
Kate.
wanna take a walk?
Absolutely.
I'll get the guns.
- You get some water,okay?
- Okay.
You can't possibly be serious.
- You just had surgery,jack.
- I'm gonna be fine.
If your sutures rip,
you're not gonna be fine.
I can't just sit around waiting.
Recovery is not "sitting around"!
- Look,I have to do this.
- Why?
Because I promised those people that
I would get 'em off this island.
don't bleed to death,jack.
I'll see ya in a couple hours.
Daniel?
What's wrong?
charlotte,did you hear what he said?
They're going to t orchid.
They're using the secondary protocol.
What are you talking about?
we have to get off this island.
Right now.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync: rocket
LOST
Season4 Episode12
中国红十字会总会救灾专用热线:(8610)65139999
请伸出一份援手 为受灾的汶川人民尽点心意
we're catchin' up.
The chopper must've landed.
Why don't you take a break?
you're bleeding.
No,I'm not bleeding.
I'M...I'm suppurating.It'S...
discharge.
My body's just fightin' the
infection around the stitches.
You know when most people are lying
and they can't look you in the eye?
You do the exact opposite.
hey,long time no see.
hey,who are you talkin' to up there,genghis?
Where's claire?
We lost her.
You what?
She just walked off in the middle of the night.
We looked for her for a da but she was just gone.
I was hopin' maybe she went back to the beach.
She didn'T.
well,what are y'all doin' out here?
What's that phone for?
The chopper flew over the beach.
Someone tossed this out.
It must've been sayid.
Well,you better hope it ain't sayid,
'cause if he's with those animals
that just blew up half of new otherton,
you do not wanna  tussle with 'em.
What,they tried to kill you?
Just like locke said they would.
So...what?We're supposed to just...
turn around and hide?
'Cause it seems like that
didn't work so well for you.
I'm sorry,doc,maybe this is dj?
vu,but didn't you just do the whole
"run through the jungle with a walkie" plan?
That helicopter is our only way off this island.
what's with you and "gettin' off the island"?
- You're like a damn broken record.
- Stop it!
Are you two fightin' each other now?
look.
I put sad and desmond on that chopper.
It was my call.
It's my responsibility.
I'm going after it whether they're on it or not.
You can all head back to the beach.
Jack...
no,no,no.You can't go by yourself.
Take care of the baby.Okay?
That son of a bih is stubborn.
hold up!
You don't get to die alone.
Based on the location of the wreckage,
our best estimate of the crash site is...
here.
From there,the survivors were
carried by the ocean's current to...
here... an uninhabited island in the
lesser sunda islands known as membata.
As you've all read in your
briefing books,on day 103...
a typhoon washed up the remnants
of an indonesian fishing boat,
including basic supplies and a survival raft.
On day 108,the remaining six survivors,
including ms. Austen's baby
which she gave birth to
on the island of membata,
used this raft to journey here...
an island called sumba.
They then came ashore near a
village called manukangga.
This photo was taken by the local
fisherman who found them.
Once it was discovered who they were,
they were transported to honolulu
by the U.S.Coast guard.
As you can imagine,this has been an
extraordinarily trying experience.
They have,however,agreed
to answer a few questions.
So,ladies and gentlemen,
the survivors of oceanic 8-1-5.
- yes.
- dr. Shephard!dr. Shephard!
Can you tell us what it was like
when the plane hit the ocean?
Uh,how you survived.
it...it all happened really fast.
I remember the impact.
I remember the...the plane filling up with water.
A group of us got to the emergency door,and,um...
got out before it went down.
And those of you who survived...
you swam to the island?
No.
We had,uh,cushions.
We had some life jackets.
We were in the water for over a day
before the current took us in.
By then,there was only eight of us left.
over here!Over here,please!
Considering the ordeal
that you've all been through,
you look pretty healthy having been on
an island for more than a hundred days.
Was that directed at me,dude?
well,actually,mr. Reyes,you were worth
more than $150 million at the time of your...
death.
How does it feel to know you're going
to get all that money back?
I don't want it back,any of it.
That money was bad luck.
what did she say?
can somebody translate that?
She asked if my husband was one of
the people who died on the island.
the answer is no.
He never made it off the plane.
Ms. Austen...
what was it like giving birth othe island?
Scary.
Your son...uh,aaron?
How old is he now?
He's just a little over 5 weeks.
So that would've made you
about six months pregnant
when the U.S.Marshal service
apprehended you in australia for
an outstanding murder warrant.
Is that correct?
Uh,I'm afraid ms.
Austen's legal issue is off the table.
Next question.
Mr. Jarrah,given the amazing
surrounding the survival of you six,
is it possible there are any other survivors
from the crash yet to be discovered?
No.Absolutely not.
you did good.
Mr. Jarrah?
There's a woman outside.
She says she knows you,but she wasn't
on the list of family members.
Her name is a noor abed jaseem.
nadia?
Nadia.
Over here!
Sayid!
Where's desmond?
He's fine.He's on the freighter.
Listen,I'm going to start takinpeople
back... six at a time.
We have to go right now before the
helicopter gets back to the boat.
Why do we have to go to the boat before
the chopper gets back?
Because the men on that helicopter have
every intention of killing us all.
What?
Jack and kate just went running after it.
so when is someone gonna
tell me where we're going?
We're going to a place called the orchid,hugo.
And what's that?
It's a greenhouse.
And why are we going to a greenhouse exactly?
You heard john.
We're going to move the island.
Right.
And how are we gonna do that?
Very carefully.
Well,if you could move the
island whenever you wanted,
why didn't you just move it before
the psychos with guns got here?
Because doing it is both
dangerous and unpredictable.
It's a measure of last resort.
Awesome.
Allow me.
may I have that mirror,please?
You know,those are 15 years old.
What are you doing,dude?
Communicating.
Communicating with who?
Who do you think?
All right.Now we can go.
Wait.What was that?What did you tell them?
None of your business,john.
Hey,sayid,listen.
If you wanna run off into the jungle
after the chopper,you should do that.
But in the meantime,we need to get
these people off this island.
I won't be long.
If I can catch up with jack and kate...
I can start ferrng people now.
I can get them there safely.
By the time you get back,I can have
most of these people on our boat.
I trust you know the bearing.
- You'd better get going.
- Thank you.
All right,first group in the raft.
We can fit six.
Okay,okay,hold on.
Sun is pregnant.
You should go first.
Sayid?
What are you doing here?
- Jack thought that you...
- I know what he thought.
That's why I'm going after
him how far ahead is he?
I dot know.He's...he's with sawyer.
I left them about an hour ago.
Jack's got a sat-phone,
and they're headed for the helicopter.
I can track them.
Look,you are not gonna catch up
to them unless I go with you.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Sun.
Where's claire?
- Get aaron on the boat,okay?
- What?
It's all right.Just...
I'll see you there.
Ju keep him safe!
All right,this is just the first trip.
Here we go.
Okay.
I told you ------
How could this happen?!
Whoever did it,sir...
...used five different banks.
Get Yoon up here right now!
NOW!
hello,father
I hope i'm not interrupting.
No... It's just business.
is something weong?
Just some -----------.
nothing you'd understand.
How is the pregnancy?
Dont pretend to -----------.
We both -------.
- What did you say.
- You heard me.
You hated Jin.
Who do you think you are?
I am your father.
you will respect me!
Oceanic -----------.
It was ----.
This morning,-----------.
So you -----.
Why...-----?
You ruined ------.
It is ----------.
Two people -----------.
You are one of them.
i am -------.
And then -------------.
Our company.
mom?
Dad?
mr. Tron?
Lady tron?
hello?
why am I doing this?
Why am I doing this?
surprise!
Happy birthday!
- hugo,what are you doing with that?
- I don't know.
I thought there might be
a prowler or something.
Jesus christ is not a weapon.
Okay.
Enjoy your party.
happy birthday,hurley.
Hey,kate.
Hey,little buddy.
Say hi.
Jack's running late.Sorry.
Happy birthday,hugo.
Wow,you guys are here.
Interesting choice of theme.
Yeah,my mom...
really doesn't get it,dude.
How's everybody doing?
what are you talking about?
Building a fire or huntin' boars?
I guess not.
Uh,listen.
Uh,do you mind,uh,
excusing us for a little while?
I-I wanna show you your birthday present.
Come on.
Bye-bye now.
I told you I don't want anything.
Hugo,it's your birthday.
You gotta get somethin'.
Not with the money.
I don't want anything from the money.
Relax.
I got thisbefore you gave us the money.
Ta-da!
Check it out.
- You fixed it.
- Yeah.
After the crash,I-I worked on
it as a memorial to you.
When I was fixing it up,
it was almost like I was with ya.
But now you're back,and it's all yours.
Wanna take her for a little spin?
is somethin' wrong,son?
Is this some kind of joke?
What are you talking about?
4,8,15,16,23,42.
Did you do this?
Do what?
Those are the numbers!
Right there!The nbers I won the lottery with!
- What...what a coincidence.
- no
No,not a coincidence.
I don't want this.
I don't want any of it!
Hugo?
Wait...wait a minute.
Hugo,what are you...son!
Hugo!Hugo!Hugo,where you goin'?
Come on!Hugo!
Okay,let's say this greenhouse
place does what you say,
and,yeah,I get it.
It's really dangerous and unpredictable.
But suppose somehow it works,
and we move the island.
Doesn't that mean the
dudewith guns move,too?
Yes,I suppose they would.
Well,isn'that,you know,a problem?
I'm working on it.
Well,what about me?
I still wanna get off it!
I'm afraid it's a little late for that,hugo.
may I have the binoculars,please?
You might wanna get down lower to the ground.
And why might we wanna do that?
Because we're at the orchid.
What are we waitin' for?
We're waiting,john,
because charles widmore,
the man who's trying to capture me
and kill all the rest of you,
knows about this place and knows
that what we need is inside.
I thought you said you had no idea
why he was trying to find he island.
I wasn't being entirely truthful.
Yeah.
When are you ever entirely truthful?
You need to see this.
What am I looking for?
Look over there on the left-hand side.
Watch the plants at the back.
I don't see any...
They're already.
hey,we're back!
where's sayid?
He had to go after jack.
You go.
They're headed for the chopper.
you okay?
Yes,I'm fine.Thank you.
I'm gonna head back for the next group.
engine's fixed.
Tell hendricks to try it.
Okay,engine should be working.
indeed they are.
all right,well,take us to the island.
but make sure you...
you stay on the bearing of 3-0-5.
It's gotta be exactly 3-0-5.
we've got some kind of R.F.Interference
with the the fathometer.
I can't see the reef,mate.
R.F.Interference?
How is that possible?
The radio room's down.
I don't know,but something
on thiboat is broadcasting.
If we don't turn it off,I'm not going
any closer than 5 miles off the coast.
Then I'll find it.
cut yourself shavin'?
Juliet took out my appendix
a couple of days ago.
You kiddin' me.
Nope.
Well,what else did I miss?
we're here.
Lapidus!
Yeah!
you know this yahoo?
Yeah."Yahoo"?
This yahoo dropped that phone on
you guys so you could find me...
and I could fly you outta here.
So why don't you do me a favor
and get that back compartment?
There's a toolbox.
See if you can find something
to get me outta these things.
You heard the man.
Well,all right.
Can I get you boys a nice,cold glass
of lemonade while I'm back there?
Where are desmond and sayid?
Your buddies were smart enough
to keep their asses on the boat
because right now that's
the safest place to be.
Because when the boys that I brought
over here come stompin' out of this jungle,
you're gonna wanna be long gone.
Where'd they go?
They're up by some greenhouse,
perched up there,waitin' to snatch linus.
Soon as we cut you free,
you'll be able fly us out of here?
Hell,yeah.
Hang on,shaggy.
You said the hit squad's
gonna grab ben linus?
Well,I don't see what's gonna stop 'em.
What are they gonna do with
the people that are with 'em?
Nothin' good.
Hugo's with ben.
son of a bitch.
About ten months ago,I wrote what
I wanted to say at my father's funeral
on the back of a cocktail
napkin at the sydney airport.
I don't remember what I wrote,
but whatever it was...
he would've hated it.
my father couldn't stand eulogies.
"The only good thing about a wake
is the free booze," he'd say.
not much of a wake because
I won't even be able to bury him.
So...
what I wanna say is not for my father.
It's for me.
Good-bye,daD.
I loved you.
I miss you.
- Thanks very much for coming.
- I'm sorry.
Thank you for coming.Thanks.
- I'll see you back at the house?
- Yeah.
I love you,sweetheart.
I love you,mom.
I'm so glad you're home.
- I'll see you soon.
- Okay.
You did that well.
Had a lot of practice.
excuse me.
May I have a word with you?
mr. Shephard...
I'm very sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
How did you know my father?
I believe I'm the reason he
was in australia when he died.
I'm sorry.
I don't understand.Why would
he have come to see you?
Oh,he...he didn't come to see me.
I was still in the hospital.
I never saw him.
He came to see his daughter.
My daughter,mr. Shephard.
- My father didn't have a daughter...
- yes.
He did.
If you don't believe me,
check his phone records.
Would you like to know the...the strangest
thing about all this,mr. Shephard?
My daughter was on your plane,too.
She was on flight 8-1-5.
you were in the air for six hours,
probably just a few rows from her
and you never even knew
she was your sister.
she was one of the ones who died
when your plane hit the water.
her name was...
claire.
I didn't mean to burden
you with this,but...
you needed to know.
I'M...
sorry for your loss.
your son is beautiful.
thank you.
N't understand.
How'd you get back to new york?
Uh,walt and I,uh,uh...
we took ben's boat and
we followed his bearing.
A couple of days,we came to
an island,you know,with people.
I sold the boat...
we hopped a cargo ferry back to the states.
Didn't tell anybody who we were.
And now you're working for ben?
I do not work for ben.
I'm trying to make up for what I did.
I'm trying to help you out here.
Translate what I said.
I understand.
Michael!
I need you now!
Oh,my god.
now.
what's the matter?
these aren't jack or sawyer.
They're different tracks,fresh...
and they're doubling back behind us.
Whoever you are,come out now!
All right.
All right,let's just relax.
All right,let's... let's just rel...
- Stop!Stop!
- Just relax.
Put the guns down.
I said stop right there!
Please just drop your guns.
Take one more step...
I said drop your guns.
I see two of them,
but not the one who killed alex.
He's there.
Hold on to that for me,will you?
What?
Listen to me very carefully,john,
because I'm not gonna
have time to repeat this.
You're gonna go into that
greenhouse through that hole there.
Once inside,you're gonna turn left.
Go about 20 paces until you see
a patch of anthuriums on your left.
They're in an alcove against the north wall.
Face tt wall,reach down with your left hand.
You'll find a switch that
activates the elevator.
The elevator takes you down
to the actual orchid station.
Whoa.Wait.What?
Okay,I'm sorry,ben,but maybe
I missed the part where you explained
what I'm supposed to do
about the armed men inside.
I'm gonna take care of them.
And how the hell are you gonna do that?
How many times do I have to tell you,john?
I always have a plan.
ben!
中国红十字会总会救灾专用热线:(8610)65139999
请伸出一份援手 为受灾的汶川人民尽点心意
my name is benjamin linus.
I believe you're looking for me.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
sync: rocket
proudly presents