Previously on Veronica Mars...
Duncan Kane. He used to be my boyfriend.
Then one day, with no warning, he ended things.
Is Duncan my half-brother?
Meg, you're the last good person at this school.
You do have friends, Veronica.
Lilly Kane was my best friend.
Did you know that the head of security at Kane Software
was the one that made the tip call that got Abel Koontz arrested?
Veronica, I know you have a million questions but everything will make sense when the time is right.
- Have you heard from your sister?
- She sent a telegram.
I know you blame me for your mother's death.
They didn't find a body because she's not dead.
I guess I should be grateful that my mother didn't leave her car on a bridge.
- Logan, what are you doing here?
- I want you to find my mother.
Your mom had fourteen credit cards in her name at the time of her disappearance.
This is the only one that's been active.
No-limit platinum card.
Be my mom's weapon of choice.
This is also the only one that is still registered under her maiden name, Lester.
Maybe it's just a coincidence.
Or maybe she's trying to hide, huh?
It's hard to know for sure.
There's only been one purchase so far, a rental car.
There was no surveillance tape from the point of sale but I ordered a copy
of the card holder's signature. It might take a couple of weeks.
What kind of car?
Benz. Red... convertible.
I'll let you know if she strikes again.
Hey, Veronica, uh...
Thanks for helping out with this.
I know what it's like.
Don't be stingy with the glitter. Remember.
It's an eighties dance.
You know, if I didn't know better,
I'd swear I just saw my best friend ask you to 'Total Eclipse of the Heart'.
No, no one's asked.
But I'm pining away by the phone waiting for that special boy to call.
You never know.
Come on, Duncan. You know as well as I do, my heart was totally eclipsed long ago.
I mean, sure, once upon a time that special boy did call
and the spring dance was the crowning moment of my fairy tale-esque teen girl life.
But now I know better. It felt like love but maybe it was just-
Veronica!
- Hey!
- Hey. I really need to talk to you.
Sorry, girl emergency.
What's up?
I think I have a secret admirer.
Hello.
Oh hi, nice breathing.
Yep, just keeps getting better and better.
Has your secret admirer been calling you all week and hanging up without speaking?
- No.
- Hmm, lucky you.
So tell me about it.
On our way back from our last away game, I got this weird text message.
So I looked around and saw two guys on their cell phones.
Caz is always flirty with me but that guy would flirt with a trash can if it had boobs.
Then there was Martin.
He's sweet but a little moony, if you know what I mean.
Or it could be some maladjusted freshman
who likes to lurk outside your bedroom window with binoculars and a bag of pork rinds.
Come on, Veronica.
You gotta help me find out who it is.
This could turn out to be my soul mate.
When I've had my fill of soul mates, glitter and puppy love,
I always find a private detective's office a refreshing change of pace.
Here's my assistant now.
I'm swamped with this insurance fraud thing but we could use this fee.
Can you take her information, charge her a straight 75?
Shouldn't take more than a half hour online.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Nothing soothes the nausea, headache and occasional dizziness of a romance overdose
like a glimpse of the aftermath.
The custody battles, the affairs
and what I'm guessing is a trophy wife looking for her golden parachute.
She'll take your info and I'll get right on it.
So, how can I help you... Miss...
Lenova, Cat-ta-rina Lenova.
I made mistake. Involving love.
I didn't know what a good thing I had and I lost him.
You must help me find him.
He was my soul mate.
Ah, zat's Tom.
Two years ago I came here from Brask
in Russia to meet zis man.
Like a mail order bride thing?
Not mail anymore. Internet.
We exchange message and, uh,
I came to Chicago as his fiancé.
That's a brave move.
Not if you've seen Brask.
All the boys there, as zey say,
are beautiful, like a princess.
Maybe I am expecting a prince.
When I meet Tom, I am disappointed;
he's not what I imagine.
In his picture he was not, um, how you say...
- Bald.
- Yes.
Before we are married I had zee cold feet, so I leave him after some time here,
alone, I realise I made mistake.
He is good man and he is gone.
I look it but, but with him changing his name...
Why would he change his name?
He  does plays in Chicago.
He always talk about come to California, be an actor.
What's wrong with Tom?
Oh, his last name, ah, c-r-u-z.
I guess it's too much like zat actor, you know... Tom...
Cruise. Yes, I see the problem.
Ah, what makes you think he's here?
Za last I hear from him,
several months back iz zis postcard.
"Catherine, Thank you for the good days, but I need to move on. I won't be in touch again."
Postmarked Neptune, California.
All  right, well this shouldn't be too hard.
Ah, $75 and Mr Mars should have something for you in a couple of days.
How hard can it be to find an actor named Tom Cruz?
Tom Cruise?
Not as good a private eye as I thought.
No. C-R-U-...
Never mind.
Okay.
I'm hanging out.
Hey, you're on the basketball team, right?
You obviously haven't seen us play.
I am the basketball team.
Can you do something for me?
You just stopped hanging out again.
It's a favour for Meg.
She's got this secret admirer; he's been text messaging her.
You know Caz and Martin on the team?
How 'bout you sneak a peek at their cell phones and see if they dial Meg's number?
What is it with you girls and your girly-girl drama?
What are you now? A love detective?
Wallace,
if you do this for me, we'll be best friends forever.
Come on, don't you want us to be BFF?
All right, all right.
But the next time we hang out, you gotta actually hang out.
Secret admirer strikes again and the plot thickens.
He wants me to go to the dance.
I'm dying to know who it is.
Purple faced monkey orchid.
Native to the King Leopold range in the Australian outback. My deduction?
Your secret admirer is an aboriginal tribesman
who shops at Manny's Flower Hut.
What are you doing?
In the detective business, we call this a clue.
What about the text messages?
I've got my best man on it.
Ah, Meg, Meg.
I'm actually, uh, throwing a rage at my house tomorrow night and it should be pretty kick-ass.
Hey dude! What the hell are you doing?
Miss Lenova, Mr Mars was unable to find any trace of Tom. I'm really sorry.
Iz zere nothing more he can do?
Well, he's done all the routine searches, um, you could hire him full time,
it's $250 a day, plus expenses.
I pay, whatever it takes.
Mr Mars is the best in the business.
So can you tell me anything else about him?
He just... zis wonderful man.
He not the most handsome or rich but he's sweet and...
and kind and... oh he make me laugh.
I actually meant, um,
like his hobbies or interests, details like that, other than acting.
He like da, um, hockies.
Um, he play guitar but not very well.
Um, he like-he like detective movies.
Uhh, Chinese food, like that?
Like that.
Please.
Ask Mr Mars to work as fast as he can.
I'm sure he'll come through.
Hi, I'm looking to place a casting notice
and I need this filled as soon as possible.
I'm looking for an ordinary guy type, medium height and build,
dark hair and a little thin on top
and he must be able to play hockey and play the guitar.
Right.
And here's the fax number you can send those headshots.
About this secret mission.
What'cha got?
A reputation as a jock-sniffer.
You can be your own FF.
I'm retired.
What's all this?
Casting call for Tom Cruz with a zee.
Apparently, he has changed his name.
Damn, this dog is a freak show.
He oughta be in show biz.
You think that's some kind of rare breed or something?
That or a drunk dingo had a three-way with an ocelot and a porcupine.
Hold that thought.
Hello, no-limit platinum card.
How many cases you working on here, Rockford?
Twelve hundred bucks?
This is Logan with today's inspirational greeting:
the future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams -
Eleanor Roosevelt. Leave a message.
Hey. Call me when you get this.
There's been another charge on your mom's credit card...
at the Sunset Regent.
I know I'm late. Sorry, honey.
So I talked to this guy on the phone. Let me handle it, he's a bit prickly.
May  I help you?
You may.
My fiancé and I are looking for a honeymoon suite.
Oh, how wonderful.
These are our more affordable packages.
The rooms run $350 for a courtyard and $450 for poolside.
On the weekends of course, it's a two night minimum.
Of course. Here's a little bit more what I had in mind.
Wow, sugarpuss, you've certainly been a busy little bee.
Ah, she's a keeper.
Um, these are our luxury suites.
Ooh. Nope.
No.
Uh, ick.
Well, how much is this one?
Ah, yes. Our Princess Suite.
Twelve hundred a night. It has a hot tub, 360 degree view
and, um, private elevator access.
- Ah, yummy...
- Yeah.
Let's take a look, hon.
I apologise but the suite's currently occupied.
Like literally occupied, because we could just poke our heads in.
Um. I'm sorry but our guest has insisted on her privacy.
Could we maybe just call up to the room?
Oh, I'm afraid that's not possible.
I assure you we will afford you the same privacy, should you choose to stay with us.
All right, stay put. I gonna go talk to the maintenance guys.
No, I think I can handle it from here.
No, I can get them to unlock the service elevator and we can just-
Naw, I've got a better idea.
I'll just sit right here.
Until my mother walks out of that elevator.
As a plan, a bit low concept for my taste,
but Logan seems primed for a stake-out and I've got a pair of elusive Romeos to track down.
Yeah, I-I believe I do recognise my handiwork...
You maybe... remember who bought it?
Yeah, yeah. Unusual order. Most kids order straight up, like roses and baby's breath.
No damn imagination.
But this kid, he, you know, he's thinking outside the box, you know.
I-I mean, what he looked like.
Ah, yeah, right. He's not a bad looking kid. Kinda medium sized, you know.
He's got that look, you know, that...
look, you know.
What look?
You know, kinda that, duh, high school kid look.
Okay. Uh, thanks a bunch, Manny.
Yeah.
Mexican hairless.
What's the point of having a dog if it's bald?
What are you gonna pet?
Skin?
Stay on task, Wallace.
Mars Investigations.
Hey, honey.
Why did I just get a voicemail from this Russian woman asking how I'm doing with her case?
I thought you dealt with that.
My plate is full with this insurance fraud thing.
Uh, I'm still dealing.
Turns out it was a little more complicated.
Veronica. Don't waste your time on this.
If the computer search didn't do it then just tell her we're too busy.
She agreed to the daily rate and we can always use the money.
I mean, wouldn't it be cool to have glasses in the kitchen that didn't have the Hamburglar on them?
Forget about the money.
I just thought it would be nice if, instead of breaking people up,
we brought them together for once.
Honey, we're private investigators, not the frigging Love Boat.
Dad, I'm almost there, I just need to track down...
Steve!
Steve? That's our guy?
No, Steve's a dog.
It's a Catahoula Leopard dog.
Who the hell names a dog Steve?
Tom Cruz?
Don't forget. You're a high school girl.
Do some high school girl things now and then.
Relax, Dad. I'm cutting pictures of Ashton out of Teen People as we speak.
You better be.
Gotta run sweetie.
Exotic Animals Hospital.
Hi. I'm calling about a Catahoula Leopard dog named Steve.
- Uh, nope, not here.
- Sorry.
Pet Hospital.
Hi, I'm calling about a Catahoula Leopard dog named Steve.
- Brought in last week?
- Yes! Right.
Uh, I met Steve on a dog beach a while back and, well,
I have a Leopard dog, Lulu and I was looking to breed her
and it seemed like she and Steve has some real chemistry.
Ah, I know you probably wouldn't give me the owner's name and number but
I was wondering if you might call him and see if he would talk to me?
- My name is Veronica, you can reach me at-
- We've got caller ID.
Caller ID. How do we ever get by? Thanks.
Hey Meg, it's Veronica.
Would you mind leaving a little early for the party so I can make a stop.
No, nothing major.
Okay, I gotta run. I'll see ya.
- Hello?
- Sorry, the dog's owner said no.
Oh, I see.
Well, it was a long shot anyway.
Thanks.
This'll just take a minute.
I  still don't understand what we're even doing here.
Ah-ha. It all seems clear now.
This is just business.
Miss Mars.
You have something else to confess?
I'm just here for a little favour.
What is that?
Oh, we have the sketch artist up from San Diego.
Figured I'd test him out. He's not bad.
I don't have horns.
Yeah, I guess not.
Memory really plays tricks on people.
Hey, Veronica.
Hey Karl.
Long time, no see. What do ya think?
Um, it's great. I finally feel wanted.
Right. Say hi to your dad for me.
I'm just here for a little favour.
You guys can get phone records, right?
We can get anything. We're cops.
Pine Veterinary Clinic?
I need to know what numbers they called between four and four ten today.
I don't know, Veronica.
Leo, there is a long and proud history of mutual back scratching
between cops and private dicks.
So when do you scratch my back?
Well maybe I'll see you tonight when you and Sacks bust this party we're going to.
I'm looking forward to it.
My, Veronica, he totally wants to serve and protect you.
Please Meg. We're looking for your man tonight.
Okay, the game is afoot.
Nice house.
Oh, you like?
Your folks must be really laid back.
Oh, these aren't actually my parents.
This isn't my house house.
It's one of the model homes in my old man's cheesy new sub-division.
But would you girls like a drink?
- Umm, I'm fine.
- Yeah, you are super-fine.
A soda?
You know, I think we're fresh out but, um...
So did you get a chance to go to the game last night?
I was cheering.
On the sidelines.
Because I am cool.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Totally spaced.
Hey, remember when I jammed it over that Long Beach party guard?
Knocked his wreck-specs off!
Sorry.
You won't find anything in those cupboards, it's a fake house.
Uh, right.
So I see you got Caz's little game recap, huh.
Yeah, like all over me.
Oh, no, no, no. I don't want to ruin your sweater.
No, it's not mine, it's Caz's. Go crazy.
Hey Martin, can I borrow your cell phone?
Sure.
Oh, you have got to be kidding me.
Hey.
Do you know what's going on with Logan?
What do you mean?
Well, he's camped out in a hotel lobby in LA.
How do you know that?
I just talked to him.
He's still there?
Uh, I'll take care of it.
Martin.
There you are.
Did you find out anything?
I'm totally confused.
Okay. Granted, I would look good on Caz's arm
but do you have anything available in sensitive or charming.
- I can check in the back.
- Good.
I'm so sorry Meg, I have to run. Can you find a ride home?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
No, you'll be super-fine.
I'm sorry. But the lobby's reserved for hotel guests only.
So book me a room, Jeeves.
Bring me a room service menu while you're at it.
You know you can't sit here forever.
What do you say we smoke her out.
I'd like to report my card lost.
My name is Lynn Lester.
That's her.
Oh, hey, Logan.
Did you just call me Mom?
You okay, brother?
You know Mom's gone, right?
Wow. You're supposed to be in Australia.
Yeah, well that didn't work out.
Veronica, hey!
Hello, Trina.
So, is the whole brat pack here?
What is this, like, like, prom night.
You guys get a room here for some after-party.
Oh, hey. Oh. I've been kinda outta the loop lately.
- Are you two-
- Stop! You shut up.
You're wearing Mom's clothes, you're wearing Mom's hat.
She was your mom, my step-mom.
The lady who liked to parade though the house in a string bikini,
whenever I had a boy over.
Yeah, well to be fair when didn't you have a boy over.
Oh, you...
Dad could've used you there.
So now you're worried about Dad's welfare.
Isn't he the big bad wolf?
Cigarette burns and broken noses.
Oh, the stories you used to tell.
Wow, we should get together and do this more often.
Yeah, well, you're in luck. I'm heading home now.
I guess some accountant finally cancelled Mom's cards.
But if you're coming home, who will play Dead Hooker Number Two on CSI this week.
How will you get your attention fix?
Maybe I can be the ring girl at one of your bum fights.
You know what?
Shall we get going, Logan?
Veronica, look at you. All grown up.
Hey, we should hang out when I'm in town.
Okay. Yeah.
Logan, come on. Let's go.
See ya guys. Drive safe.
She's gone. She's gone.
Yep, I got some pictures.
Mr Neckbrace with a former lawyer, Joe Allen,
who was disbarred last year for repping a fake accident ring.
Hey, you got any other guys working this case, maybe drives a silver Chevy?
I keep seeing it behind me.
No, no, no, it's nothing.
So I'll send the pictures when I get back.
Okay. Bye.
- Good morning sir.
- Hey.
Thank you.
Here you are sir.
The wrong place I guess.
You know which hotel has the medical supplies convention?
Anyway. I'll just take the keys... one right there. Thanks. Have a good day.
You too, sir.
Hey, it's Keith Mars.
I got a name check to run.
Yevgeni Sukarenko, all right?
Thanks for doing this, Karl.
Yeah, no problem.
Is this the guy?
This is Manny.
Manny, this is Karl.
He's gonna help you with your... recall problems.
Yeah, good luck.
Don't worry, Manny, I'm a professional.
Right.
- I'll fax the results to your place.
- I owe you one.
Well if it isn't my local policeman.
You got a pen handy?
Always. What do ya got?
Three outgoing calls between Pine Veterinary between four and four ten.
I got a Fred Ellis, John Frampton and a Carla Stern.
You're a prince, Leo.
Yeah, I'm writing that down.
I'll talk to ya later.
So it seems that saying about people resembling their pets is true.
Fred Ellis was as old and droopy as his Basset Hound and single mother, Carla Stern
was a dead ringer for her Pomeranian. Two strikes.
So it all comes down to John Frampton bearing a slight resemblance to his...
Catahoula Leopard Dog.
Catherine? It's Veronica in Mr Mars' office. It's good news. He found Tom.
Veronica, thank you. It's a miracle.
You have a pen?
Of course, please.
So the address is-
Dad, what are you doing?
This isn't Catherine Lenova.
It's Yellana Sukarenko.
Yevgeni and Sergei Sukarenko,
Russian mob from Chicago.
Anthony Thomas Cruz worked for their father.
Turned State's evidence and put him away.
He's not a long lost love, Veronica.
He's in the witness protection programme.
Just like we said.
Mars Investi- Catherine.
I'm sorry, I got excited and dropped the phone.
You still have your pen?
Okay, the address is
124 Driftwood Terrace.
Right.
Of course.
It's no problem.
Buh-bye.
It's good work, honey.
- So, what's gonna happen?
- Don't worry.
I'll take care of it from here.
Do svidaniya, Mr Cruz.
Oh! Prevet!
Put down your guns, now.
Get your hands on your head, get your hands on your head.
Prevet?
It's Russian for hi. I looked it up.
- Hey!
- Meg, I am so sorry.
What for?
I told you I was gonna find your secret admirer before the dance and I haven't come through, I...
it's just been a million other things I've been working on...
Forget it, forget it. I don't even care anymore.
Oh, here.
You can have it. It's the flowers he sent me.
Supposed to be our signal tonight or something.
Thought you were excited about it.
Truth is, I'm not sure I wanna go out with Caz.
And Martin's nice but not...
I just don't want to hurt his feelings.
How come you're all dolled up.
Now who says I need a date to go to the dance.
Oh. Right.
You... go girl.
I'm taking you.
Okay.
Well, what do you think?
I look like Manilla Whore Barbie.
No, no. Where are you going?
- Don't you dare run away on me.
- Just business.
Come on, lover boy. Show us your face.
What is it?
Nothing.
Come on, let's go. We're gonna be late.
Wow. Eighties fashion.
Grody to the max.
Don't spaz.
Aren't you totally stoked to go to this thing.
Oh, for sure.
I just didn't know the dance would be such a major couple-o-rama.
What happened to all the girl power?
The we-don't-need-dates resolve.
Reality has set in.
Forgive me, gal pal.
I'm weak.
What are you doing?
You'll thank me later.
Where are you going?
My work here is done.
But you'll miss your big surprise.
I'll live.
Would you care to dance?
Between getting fooled by the Russian bride and finding out that Duncan has the hots for Meg,
I've had my fill of surprises tonight.
J Geils was right. Love stinks.
You can dress it up with sequins and shoulder pads but one way or another
you're just gonna end up alone at the spring dance
strapped into uncomfortable underwear.
What's wrong, Veronica?
Are you ready for a... a total eclipse of the heart?
You look beautiful.
I love the eighties.
Heads up. Risky business at 12:00
Come on everyone. Let's wang chung tonight.
What, everybody wang chung tonight.
Wang chung or I'll kick your ass. Everybody!
Don't touch me, dude.
Every class has one.
I cannot escape Tom Cruise.
Come on Logan, just give me your keys. Leo, can you follow us in your car?
No. No! No. No.
'Cause tonight I'm gonna party like it's 1999.
Hey, who's this dude.
As I have told you now three times, this is the friendly officer of the law
who is going to overlook your underage public drunkenness.
Crockett or Tubbs?
Logan, when did you stop wearing pants?
What are you doing here?
My first night back home and I get the call, come get Logan, he's wasted.
It's like I never left.
Is that Kajagoogoo?
There's no point you going in there, Trina. Entertainment Tonight is not covering it.
Bummer.
Well I guess I'll just drag your sorry little self home.
As long as you let me puke in your car.
Of course, just like old times.
A promising young man.
Thanks for showing up tonight.
I assume I have Meg to thank for getting you here.
She called but I came because I wanted to see you.
You wanna go back?
Ah, no, here's not so bad.
Are you going to kiss me?
I was thinking about it.
Cool.
Hello?
Your other boyfriend.
No someone keeps crank calling me.
- Star 69 them.
- I do but it just rings and rings.
I am a deputy sheriff, allow me.
I hear you're bothering my girl...
Who is this? Why do you keep calling me?
This is a pay phone.
You must be talking about that blonde lady.
Blonde lady?
A pay phone where?
Sage Brush Cantina, Barstow.
Uh, raincheck?
What?
Mom!
Veronica.
Oh, my god, no. No, please.
- I'm gonna get you out of here.
- No!
No. I can't be seen with you. They are gonna hurt you.
Mom, I know who's doing it. I know who's blackmailing us. You're safe now.
Veronica.
Synchro: Amariss
- www.forom.com -