Previously in
Veronica Mars...
If it isn't my predecessor and mentor.
Are you doing anything special to mark the
one year anniversary of Lilly Kane's murder?
Tell me again how you solved
the crime. An anonymous tip.
Did anybody show up to collect
the reward? Do'ya find that strange?
Damn it!
Wow. That's really criminal of you.
- I'm Veronica, by the way.
- Mac.
I know who's responsible for scaring Mom away from Neptune.
Clarence Wiedman. The man who took
surveillance photos of me.
So if Jake Kane is my biological father,
that information is going
to be worth millions.
Good morning.
Or not.
You don't go to the oceanside bars that
the college kids hang out at, do you?
I prefer the biker bar by the train
station. I get more attention there.
I'm kidding.
Why would you ask me that?
Twenty year old co-ed washe
up dead on the beach.
Scary.
Wait. Wasn't this your case?
I thought they caught this guy
in Oakland two years ago.
Well, apparently they didn't.
Everyone wanted to believe the Oakland
strangler committed the Neptune crimes too.
It never quite fit.
Oh, but it was so important for
the mayor and the Chamber of Commerce
to put that scare behind us.
People are really freaking out
about this E-String Strangler.
My mom is scared to drive home alone.
I told her this time she can be
happy she's not the guy's type.
My dad barely let me out
of the house this morning.
I hear you do detective stuff for people.
- I do favours for friends.
- I can pay.
Sit down, friend.
What can I do for you?
I was hoping that you could
find some dirt on my parents.
Why Jackson Douglas, I do declare!
You want me to dig up dirt on your own parents.
I need leverage.
They're crazy strict. They grounded me
for two months for smoking up in my room.
Apparently you've never spent time in a black woman's house.
Be glad you're still walking.
Yeah, well, they act like
they were always perfect.
And every little thing I do
wrong is catalogued
so they can rub my nose in it later.
Sure you can handle the truth?
The '70s and '80s were not
pretty decades for people.
- We've all seen the pictures.
- I can handle it.
Now as for the small
matter of compensation.
I love my parents.
All right. Come to my party.
No need to bring gifts.
Happy birthday to me.
The rite of fall.
Madison Sinclair's birthday.
Best party of the year and
I can't go because I'm grounded.
- Her parents must looove her.
- They really loved her,
they would've gotten the real Beatles.
Veronica Mars.
Is your daddy here, or is he busy
peeking in people's windows?
You stop dressing up like Little Bo Peep,
he'll stop peeking.
Your father?
Deputy Lamb is here.
He's got the mayor with him.
Show him in.
Yeah, sure. I'll just have Rod Serling
wait out here on the couch.
The detective will see you now.
- It's been a long time, Keith.
- I know.
Good to see ya.
- I wish it were under better circumstances.
- Sit down.
Can I get anybody anything?
Water? Coffee?
A banana?
- We're good.
- Okay.
Just leaving.
So how can I help you gentlemen.
You know the situation...
Thank you Keith. Appreciate it.
See you tomorrow, Lamb.
Um-hmm. Can't wait.
What was that about? What's tomorrow?
The day I go back to work
at the sheriff's department.
Season 1 - Episode 11
Silence of the Lamb
You're going back to work
at the sheriff's department?
It's temporary. I'm just there to work
on the E-String Strangler case.
And you're teaming up with Lamb?
It's a bitter pill, I know but they're
paying me my normal hourly.
And Lamb agreed to this?
His head didn't explode?
The mayor didn't give him a choice.
I'm the closest thing they have to
an E-String Strangler authority
and it's a big priority for the mayor.
A killer preying on partying college girls
tends to kill the Spring Break business.
So this is all about tourist revenue.
- God bless America.
- Well, whatever their motive,
I'm glad to be involved.
Hey, if you're working
at the Sheriff's office,
you'll have access to the Lilly Kane files.
We can finally get our hands on
that Crime Stoppers Hotline recording,
find out who the anonymous source was,
the one who fingered Abel Koontz.
Veronica, that won't be on my agenda.
Here are the highlights.
Your dad was busted trying
to buy an eight ball
from an undercover cop at
an Eagles concert in '74,
your mom had five speeding tickets
and a collision on her record
before she graduated high school.
I don't care what they say about you,
Veronica Mars. You rock.
Yes, I do.
I also take cash.
I hear you can dig up dirt on parents.
The first two victims,
Katherine Wills, Andrea Sims were found
in 2001 and 2002 respectively.
They had certain shared characteristics.
Both were undergrads on break, both
were attractive social girls, both had...
- Hard partiers.
- ... both had high levels of
alcohol in their blood
- and both were abducted on Friday nights.
- Technically,
early Saturday morning from midnight
- to closing time.
- The bodies were found in the bay.
A single nickel-plated guitar
string tied around their necks.
The latest victim, Amy Polk,
was killed with the exact same MO.
So he kills them with the guitar strings?
- Naw, that's just...
- It's his signature. His mark.
The girls are asphyxiated.
The strangler thing came from
the press, it's a misnomer.
There's evidence that these women
have been held for 48 hours in a
contained space, basically suffocated.
The murders are reminiscent
of the Hillside Strangler case.
Except the Hillside Strangler
actually did strangle the girls.
Party girls, like ours.
Picked up outside of bars.
- Killer leaves his mark.
- Okay.
Okay, except for the asphyxiation,
the imprisonment,
the body disposal,
these cases have a lot in common.
What do we know about the killer?
He hates women, he craves
attention, he's a luuser.
The weekend killings suggest
the guy has a traditional job.
Amy Polk was found with wrist bands
from local bars on her wrist
and smudged ink on her palm that looked
like it could be a phone number.
Lab boys in LA are trying to decipher it.
Imagine the poor sucker
waiting for that phone call.
Your mom sued her parent for
emancipation when she was sixteen
and then moved to Hollywood.
According to the Internet Movie Database,
she went on to play such roles
as "Trucker's girlfriend",
"Screaming maid" and
"Bi-curious room mate".
Your mother was married
in 1985 for 36 days.
- Shut up.
- To a pro-skier she met on Spring Break.
They drove to Vegas, did it drive-through
style and she had it annulled.
And she calls me boy crazy.
You just made my gear.
- Hey.
- Hi, Mac.
Hope I'm not interrupting anything.
Come on in.
It's a spiffy new Beetle
you're driving these days.
Yeah.
Well, the purity test was
probably my finest hour
but that's nothing compared
to what this could be.
It's time to think global and act local.
Okay, you're exposing parental
secrets for fifty bucks a pop.
We create this website, double the fee,
we have no overhead because
I've already bought the domain name.
With your sleuth prowess
and my programming skills,
I don't think it's an exaggeration to say
that we would rule the entire known universe.
I can barely handle school
and my cases as it is.
Think about it.
This isn't just a college fund.
Potentially this is our retirement fund.
I will definitely think about it.
There is just one more think, about my
folks that I was wondering about.
You PIs have access to search engines that
would take me weeks to hack into, so...
- I mean I have cash.
- No. Gotcha. Keep your money.
It's a professional courtesy.
It's not that they're bad parents.
They just... don't get me.
They're nachos and NASCAR
people and I'm more...
- Falafels and Fellini?
- Exactly.
Your last name's Mackenzie, right?
Um-hmm, Natalie and Sam,
9715 Colony Place.
- Mom is Natalie Franklin?
- Yep.
Oh, you had a birthday a couple of days ago.
Yeah, one more year
until I can leave home.
Okay.
Sam's had a few tickets,
tax audit, nothing strange.
...huh, except that.
What?
According to this,
they won a million dollar lawsuit against
Neptune Memorial Hospital in '92.
- No way. That's got to be a mistake.
- Hello? Sleuth prowess.
Come on, they hate lawyers and
they never even go near the hospital.
You want me to look into it?
Yeah, I do.
Neptune isn't short on millionaires
but I figure a judgement that big against
the local hospital might have made the papers.
It's beginning to look like I'm wrong.
Hold the phone!
I was expecting something like
"Woman Accidentally Receives Pig Heart"
but no, I have to find out the one thing
that can completely wreck Mac's life.
How do you live a normal life once you
find out you were switched at birth.
Hello Cleveland.
- "Spinal Tap".
- What?
The movie "Spinal Tap".
You've never seen "Spinal Tap"?
No.
That explains a lot.
Is there someone that actually works here?
Dawg, look like you need help.
He's waiting for you to throw your panties.
Can we lose the noise?
Noise!
All I hear are sound waves
woven into melodic poetry.
Hey!
We can do this here or down
at the sheriff's department.
So what's up? You lookin' for
a band to play the policeman's ball?
We're looking for a murderer.
Found this guitar string tied
around the neck of his last victim.
Is there anything special about it?
This exact string?
This is a triple nickel antioxidant special
order string we get for just one customer.
- A guy we call Devil Dave.
- Do you know where we can
find this Devil Dave?
- Devil Daaaave?
- Huh?
- Did you kill anyone this week?
- Uh-uh.
Your basic guitar string?
Same as any other string.
Betcha the criminals in town are shakin'
in their boots knowin' you're on the case.
- Mental note: put in a security system.
- Right.
So ya, ya think the killer's
a guitar player?
That is brilliant.
I think guitar players are a little too
busy nailin' women to strangle 'em. Ooow!
Even the wannabes and losers living in Neptune who don't realize
if they haven't made it by the time they turn
thirty it's because they're not going to?
They're too busy?
Nice art work. Yours?
Guitar players,
the heroes of our modern age.
Strappin' on a guitar.
Does it get rid of feelings of inadequacy?
Does strappin' on a gun?
- Hey.
- Got a minute?
Ho, ho, ho.
Ryan, open that door
and you'll know pain like you've never
known in your pathetic little life.
Enjoy the peace.
Lasts about seven minutes tops.
Whoa. Who's your curator?
You like it? It's my own little cave.
Whenever I run out of space,
my dad just builds me more shelves.
Knock, knock.
You must be Veronica.
I wasn't sure if you were a normal eater
or one of those freakball vegans, like Cindy.
Uh, more normal than freakball, thanks.
Okay, thanks Mom.
Okay.
Cindy?
It won out over Barbie.
So what did you find out?
Has to be pretty big for you
to come deliver it in person.
Suspense effectively built.
Hit me.
Dad always says, this is the job.
Telling people stuff they might
not want to know
or might be better off not knowing.
It is big, like,
life-altering big, so you should really
think about if you want to hear it
or if you'd rather just forget it
and go on with your life.
- And may I suggest option B.
- I'm adopted, aren't I?
Go ahead and tell me,
it would explain a lot.
Well, yes and no, um,
the Mackenzies aren't
your biological parents.
So what does that mean.
You were sent home from the hospital
with the wrong family.
Oh my god.
And there's more.
More than that?
Another family was awarded
a million dollars at the same time.
Okay.
Um, another baby girl,
born the day after you were
and your biological parents took her home.
Another girl, born a day after me.
I was switched at birth
with Madison Sinclair?
You were bartending Friday night
at Body Shots when Amy Polk came in.
Recognise her?
Honestly, I can't tell them apart anymore.
They all have that same
sorority girl in heat look to me.
We suspect she was there with the man
who killed her and you remember him.
Gentlemen, I can't help you.
It was Friday night and
Friday night is ladies night.
Two for one shots.
It's wall to wall drunk bitches.
Do you mind toning down the language.
Ooops. Sorry.
Now that one, I would've noticed.
That's my daughter.
Wouldn't mind havin' her call me daddy.
Whoops! Sorry!
Sit down.
- Can I help you?
- You must be new.
I'm Keith Mars' daughter, Veronica.
Ah. Leo.
Did you just tell me your sign?
My name, actually, though
I am coincidentally enough a Leo.
I'm just bringing some food for my dad.
Ah well, you can put it
on his desk if you want,
unless it's gonna go bad or something,
then we have a mini-fridge,
I could put it in there.
I might just take you up on
that 'cause there's coleslaw.
No problem.
Word of caution.
You probably shouldn't trust me.
Oh yeah?
Every night at nine, the whole crew
goes out to dinner
leaving the rookie here
to answer the phones.
I usually wind up getting dinner
at a candy machine.
A pastrami sandwich could
prove to be very tempting.
- You looked in my bag.
- I told you, I'm a scoundrel.
A rogue deputy is among us.
No sandwich is safe.
I tell you what. If you promise
to come back and visit me,
- I will stay out of the fridge.
- Deal.
Oh my Deputy Leo. You might as well
leave me a key and a map.
What about the guys who hang at Body Shots?
Anyone suspicious?
Mostly loud-mouth frat boys.
You know who you should talk to?
The Worm.
The Worm?
Yeah, this guy who shoot
videotapes of all the girls,
then sells them to "Girls Gone Bad".
Where do we find the Worm?
Think he's got a girl in there?
I think he's got a video rental.
- Yeah, can I help you?
- Sheriff's department.
- We need to ask you a few questions.
- You recognise her?
No.
Are you sure?
'Cause we heard you were filming at
Body Shots the night she disappeared.
Take another look.
No, really, I don't know her.
Listen, I've gotta get dressed for work,
so if that's everything...
Sure, no problem, thanks for your time.
- Right, yeah?
- Hey,
if you think of anything,
just give us a call.
I guess you didn't notice, the guitar
sitting out there in plain sight.
- I saw it.
- So what does he need,
a shirt reading
"I'm the E-String Killer, arrest me"?
Let's go back.
He needed to look like
he's not going to soil himself.
If he gets any more freaked out,
he's going to destroy those tapes
before we get a warrant.
You should have consulted me first.
What did you want me to do,
consult you in pig-latin?
He was standing right there!
You don't make the decisions
around here. I am the Sheriff.
I noticed. Thank you.
Hey, did you get any sleep
last night because I...
Helping to keep America
beautiful by picking up the litter?
Wanna crash a party with me?
Bad idea, Mac.
- Bad, bad idea.
- It's my chance to see how the other half lives,
especially since I should
have been the other half.
So this is where the bourgie folks live?
Upper upper bourgie.
It'll be fine.
Hey, happy birthday.
What are you doing here?
I came to celebrate your birth,
but these two just wanna hook up.
I mean, who invited you?
That would be Seth Russell, from History?
No, it was Adam Bunting.
Adam Bunting. Isn't that
the guy who looks like Fievel?
No, no, that's Adam Hamilton.
Nobody talks to him, he's poor.
He still looks like Feivel.
But... I didn't invite Adam!
I remember, it was Kevin Powell.
- Who?
- Kevin Powell.
The last time I crashed an 09er party,
I got ridiculed,
roofied and woke up missing my underwear.
You can imagine how glad I am to be back.
Hey, hey. I hear you're working
some magic lately.
Uh, can you help me get
my parents off my back.
I'm gonna go find a bathroom.
Uh, shop's closed right now, Bud.
All right, come see me
at school on Monday.
Hi.
You didn't see me, huh.
I'm Lauren, I'm Madison's sister.
Hi Lauren.
- I'm Mac.
- That's a cool name.
Thanks.
So.
- What are you reading?
- "The Westing Game".
- It's really good.
- Yeah, it is.
I'll probably finish it tonight.
Madison says I have to stay in here.
What are you doing in my parent's library?
- She's read my book.
- No one's supposed to be here.
It's off limits.
There you are.
And you. I won't even start.
God, Madison,
they're here for your party.
No, Lauren, they're crashing my party.
You need to leave. You don't belong here.
- Well actually...
- We were just leaving, right Mac?
Happy Birthday, Madison.
Thanks for being such a gracious host.
Martha Stewart has nothing on you.
I could tell Mac I know how she feels,
but the truth is, I don't.
When I had the opportunity
to learn my paternity,
I chose blissful ignorance with
a side of gnawing doubt.
Think she's even read
five books in that library?
She wouldn't know Monet's Water Lilies
unless Revlon named a nail polish after it.
I have a blood sister
I've never even heard of.
And Madison has a brother.
Why didn't they just trade us back?
We would have gotten over it eventually.
I suppose they got kind of
attached in those first four years.
They should have figured it
out way before then.
At two I was spitting out corn dogs
and tuning the radio to NPR.
Did you ever find out what
happened to that million dollars?
Still working on it, unless
you wanna just blow it off.
No.
Keep checking. I've come this far.
See ya.
Okay, well, thanks for calling me back.
That was one of the
"Girls Gone Bad" producers.
They've never even heard of Eddie LaRoche.
Ah, so this guy's been videotaping
girls for his own personal enjoyment.
Nice.
Told you I had a bad feeling about that guy.
- This the stuff from his apartment?
- Yeah.
Pervert's recorded 40 tapes-worth
of girls flashing their ta-tas.
Okay, well, we should split these up...
We'll split 'em up and we'll see
if any of the victims are on 'em.
Perfect.
Hey. Strings from Eddie's guitar match
the strings left on the victims.
I know, I'm shameless.
But every time I start to feel guilty,
I remind myself that Lilly would be
thinking about colleges right now
or what new CD played at maximum volume
would most annoy her mother.
And I remember my mission.
Hungry?
So what made you decide to be a cop?
Oh, well the same old tired story.
I was sent here by the agency
to do a strip-o-gram for Inga.
An armed robbery call came in,
I figured I was in uniform anyway,
so what the hell.
So you're saying you just
kind of stumbled into it.
Uh, what I'm trying to say is,
this uniform, it's... it's a tear-away.
Hello?
Is anyone back there?
- Hi!
- Hi.
I need to talk to someone about the
noise level in my neighbourhood
which is truly out of control!
I mean, you got motorcycle gangs, gunshots...
- Wha...
- ...heavy metal music?
It's gotten to the point where
I can't even sleep at night.
- Well, why don't...
- I'll bet that if my zip code ended in 0909,
you'd have a patrol car swinging
by the house every 10 minutes.
"Good evening Mr. Weevil.
Is there anything we can do for you?"
That kind of service.
But no, it's the barrio.
So you figure, hey,
they'll sort it out themselves.
And don't get me started
on what this is doing to the property
values in my neighbourhood!
I have a good mind to run for
the city council and if I win,
I'll promise you this. Heads...
...will roll.
We could send a patrol car by....
I'm wondering if I'm better off
speaking with your supervisor.
Well, he won't be in until morning.
Well then you leave the sheriff a note:
he shouldn't expect Eli Navarro
Esquire's vote this year!
Sorry, couldn't get rid of him.
No problem.
Seventeen?
You're seventeen?
I don't see how my age
is relevant to this discussion.
Well then, you're not reading my mind.
I'm afraid to ask.
- And how old are you?
- Twenty.
Yeah, I can read the wisdom in your eyes.
I've one line, that's it.
You wanna hear it?
Sure.
My band's playing this weekend.
If you wanna come down,
I'll put you on the guest list.
- And that line works?
- On occasion.
But the good thing about the line is,
it's a no-risk line.
You throw it out there. If she
shows up, hey, she's interested.
If she doesn't, you haven't
embarrassed yourself.
Of course, if the girl you're
chatting up can't get into the club...
then the whole thing's kinda useless.
A cop that rocks.
What will they think of next?
I'm trying to cover all fantasy bases.
The Crime Stoppers Hotline CD
I snuck out of the evidence room
should have a recording
of every call on it.
What I wanna know? Who gift wrapped
Abel Koontz for Sheriff Lamb.
There's been a suspicious vehicle
parked on my street for days
and I'm wondering if it's somehow
connected to the Lilly Kane murder...
I think I saw the girl on the day of the
murder, at the gas station on main...
What's up? It was me. I killed her...
- My neighbour? I can hear him...
- I have grave concerns about
a sheriff's department...
- I would love to send them a card...
- The logical by-product of the evil
practices of Kane Software...
I know who killed the Kane girl.
His name is Abel Koontz.
He lives in a houseboat on the marina.
Amy Polk is on this tape.
Let's bring this guy in.
As always, a day late and a dollar short.
I already got him sweating in interrogation.
She was on one of mine.
- So how you wanna play this?
- I say we play to our strengths.
So I'm good cop?
Why don't you admit it, scumbag?
Say it.
I killed those girls.
I wanna go home.
Oh, I'm sure you do.
But you still haven't told us
why two of the murdered girls
ended up in your little
do-it-yourself porno tapes.
Why'd you lie to us, Eddie? Why'd you
tell us you didn't know Amy Polk.
- There have been so many.
- Why'd you keep them alive 48 hours, huh?
Are you lonely Eddie, did you just
need someone to talk to. Huh?
If I tell you can I go home?
Start writing. We'll see.
Don, can I talk to you a sec?
Everything we have on
this guy is circumstantial.
I mean, obviously he has
some mental issues.
No judge is gonna allow his confession.
I'll take that chance.
I'm saying I'm not sure he's our guy.
What's the problem?
Too easy for you?
Let me ask you something.
Where did he keep those
girls for all that time?
It couldn't have been his apartment,
the walls are too thin.
We know he doesn't have other property.
I don't think we can eliminate the
possibility that it was someone else.
Like who?
Jake Kane?
Ah, well lookie here.
He's writing.
Keith, I'll handle it from here.
We'll send you a cheque.
What do you got for me, Eddie?
Is it a page turner?
- Hello?
Mac. It's Veronica, hey.
I just emailed you a sound file.
The voice on it has been digitally altered.
Do you think you can strip it down?
Maybe, I'll give it a shot.
Thanks.
Also, I think I found out what happened
to the money from the lawsuit.
You know "Funtime Motors"?
They sell jet skis and four wheelers?
Yeah, sure. My dad's a salesman there.
He used to own it.
Your dad started that business in 1992.
He filed for bankruptcy in 1994
and it was bought out in early '95.
You still there?
I'm okay, Veronica, really.
Mac, I know this is hard to hear but
you did have a choice in all this.
There's a reason this was kept a secret.
Yeah.
I'm not gonna do anything stupid.
I just need time to think.
I'll talk to you later.
Hello.
Hi.
I'm Cindy.
I think I left my purse in the library
when I was here for Madison's party.
You were...
Okay, well, come in.
Lauren,
- this is...
- Hi, Mac.
- Hey. Finish your book, yet?
- Twenty pages left. Can't wait.
Mac thinks she might have left her purse
in the library. Would you go check?
It's leopard print.
So, how's school?
It's good.
I mean the actual school
part is good, anyway.
- What kind of college do you think you'll...
- Mom!
Did you pick up the dry cleaning?
I can't find...
Oh, hi honey.
I guess you know Cindy.
She thinks she might have
left something here.
You were here long
enough to leave something?
So, anybody want a snack?
No thanks. I'm not hungry.
- Sure, if it's not too much trouble.
- No, no trouble at all.
I'm going upstairs.
Thank you.
- So I could make you a sandwich or...
- You know, I...
I should probably go.
It was nice to...
Are you sure?
Somebody help me, please?
- What's the problem?
- My daughter Kelly.
She went off last night
with a group of girlfriends,
even though I warned her
not to go to those bars.
She didn't come home.
Ma'am, I'm sure she's all right.
- What's going on here?
- Her daughter's missing.
The strangler's got her.
I know he does.
If you don't find her,
I will hold you responsible.
All of you.
What are you doing here?
I told you, you're out.
Yeah, well, that was before I knew
there was another girl missing.
We got the test results back from
the writing on the victim's palm.
They were able to put together
a seven digit number.
It belongs to Vic Sciaraffa.
The bartender from Body Shots.
- Who's out in the field?
- Haymark and Jones.
- Send them to his apartment...
- Already did. He's not there
and his car isn't in the carport.
I want you to send out
an APB, notify the Feds.
We gotta move on this thing.
Okay, let's go.
Veronica, hey, it's Dad.
I just need to know where you are right now.
Veronica? It's me again.
Listen, I'm tracking your phone right now.
Can you call me as soon as you get this?
It's cool. It's cool.
Dad, everyone.
Everyone, Dad.
- Hey.
- Ah, dude.
Are you okay, honey?
Aside from never wanting
to show my face again.
- What's going on?
- There's a new girl missing.
The killer might still be
on the loose and he's...
he might be a guy who doesn't
like me and does like you.
So you two know each other?
Did I forget to mention that?
You do this yourself?
Yeah, we were getting a lot of
noise complaints from the neighbours.
Will you follow Veronica back
to the sheriff's department?
Yeah.
- You got your piece with you?
- Ah, yeah.
Okay, you go, come here.
Deputy D'Amato and I are
checking out Evermore Guitars.
- It's probably nothing.
- Roger.
Closed Saturday and Sunday.
Abducts the girl Friday, disposes
of the body Sunday night.
It's a theory at least.
What do you wanna do?
Find a way in.
What is it?
Wrist band from Body Shots.
Hey, can you stay here?
Give me a signal if he shows up.
Hello? Is someone out there?
Hold on, hold on, I'm coming for ya.
I'm with the sheriff's department.
Hang tight.
Are you okay?
Breathe.
Stop. Now, or I will shoot you.
You know,
saving the life of a gal's dad,
smooth.
Hey.
- Is everything okay?
- Not really.
Sheriff just came and told me
I've been suspended for a week
seeing as the evidence room was left
unlocked on my shift the other night.
Somebody must have snuck off
with the key when I wasn't looking.
You know anything about that?
Can't say I wasn't warned.
Same old story.
Girl uses boy. Girl falls for boy.
Boy saves girl's dad's life.
Girl gets what she deserves.
Yeah?
It's me. Are you busy?
No,
I'm suddenly very free.
I decoded the message, I think,
so do you wanna swing by
tomorrow morning and hear it?
Sure.
You gotta make it early though.
I'm going camping with my family.
Camping?
It's a bi-annual rite of torture.
I'll play this recording at a few different speeds.
- Tell me when you think it's right.
- Sounds good.
Oh, ah, honey. Did you remember a pillow?
- Yeah, I've packed it.
- Good.
So where are you guys headed?
Ah, Yosemite maybe.
I never know 'til I get there.
Okay, here we go.
The Kane girl. His name is Abel Koontz.
- No, nothing yet.
- Let's try this.
I know who killed the Kane girl.
Veronica, I gotta go soon.
I know. Can you just
try it one more time.
His name is Abel Koontz.
He lives in a houseboat on the marina.
Stop.
I know who it is.
Ryan, if you don't want to be left,
I suggest you get into this camper.
Honey, you have everything you need, uh,
pocket knife, headlamp, latest
works of staggering genius?
- Yeah, Dad, it's all accounted for.
- All right.
Cindy! What are you doing?
Come on, let's go.
I'll be there in a minute, Mom.
So where are we going this year, anyway?
Come on. Let's hit the road.
I suppose this isn't my smartest move.
I don't care.
I want him to know what it feels like.
Hey boss.
Package came for you.
How'd this package arrive?
Messenger.
I wanna find out who paid
to have it sent here. Today.
You send target photos of me to my mom.
You call in the Abel Koontz tip.
Two words for you, Clarence Wiedman:
game on.
Synchro: Flovap
www.forom.com