No, Amy, it's definitely not
the fifth moon of Sinda Callista.
I think I can see a Ryman's.
It's saying we're on Earth!
Essex, Colchester.
It's taking off again.
Can you hear me?
Hello? Hello, please?
Hello?
I need your help.
There's been an accident.
Please, help me.
Hello?
Please, will you help me?
Help you?
- What's wrong?
- Something terrible's happened.
Please help me.
- Craig, what's that on the ceiling?
- What's what on the ceiling? That!
It's coming from upstairs.
Who lives up there again?
Just some bloke.
So what's the plan tonight?
Pizza, booze, telly?
Pizza, booze, telly.
What is he doing up there?
- You put the advert up yet?
- Did it today, paper shop window.
"One furnished room available
immediately, shared kitchen,
"bathroom, with 27-year-old male,
non smoker,
"£400 pcm - per calendar month -
suit young professional."
Mmm, sounds ideal.
That's your mission in life, Craig.
Find me a man!
Otherwise
you'll have to settle for me.
You'll have to settle for me first.
Oh, Melina again. What?
Right.
But I've kind of got plans.
- No, nothing important, just Craig.
- Thanks, Soph!
Sorry, you know what I mean!
I'll talk to Craig, OK.
Now she's having a Dylan crisis
on top of the Clare crisis.
It could be another all-nighter.
I'm sorry, but I really should go.
Do you mind if I go?
No, not at all.
No, honestly, course not, go.
- Cos I could stay. We've got plans.
- No, go on.
Just pizza.
It's just pizza.
Right, I'm going.
All right, then.
Well, I'll see you soon.
All right, and give me a call,
I hope everything's OK.
Thanks, sorry.
Just tell her.
Just tell her. "I love you."
"I love you."
Just:
"Hey, I don't know if you knew..."
Every time!
I love you.
I love you!
Well, that's good, cos I'm
your new lodger.
Do you know, this is going
to be easier than I expected!
U-Sub.net et la Allons-y Team
présentent
Doctor Who - saison 5
Transcript : Red Bee Media Ltd
Synchro : Citrøn, Darkevil, Dauphinus,
Delphiki, Imaginos, Jojo
But I only just put the advert up
today, I didn't put my address.
Well, aren't you lucky I came along?
More lucky than you know.
Less of a young professional,
more of an ancient amateur,
but frankly I'm an absolute dream.
Hang on, mate, I don't know
if I want you staying, and
give me back those keys,
you can't have!
Quite right. Have some rent.
That's probably quite a lot,
isn't it? Looks like a lot.
Is it a lot? I can never tell.
Don't spend it all on sweets.
Unless you like sweets. I like sweets.
That's how we greet each other
nowadays, isn't it? I'm the Doctor.
Well, they call me the Doctor,
I don't know why.
I call me the Doctor too.
Still don't know why.
Craig Owens. The Doctor?
- Who lives upstairs?
- Just some bloke.
- What does he look like?
- Normal. He's very quiet.
Usually.
Sorry, who are you again?
Hello?!
Excuse me?
I suppose that's...
dry rot?
- Or damp. Or mildew.
- Or none of the above.
I'll get someone to fix it.
I'm good at fixing rot.
Call me the Rotmeister.
No, I'm the Doctor,
don't call me the Rotmeister.
This is the most beautiful parlour
I have ever seen,
you're obviously
a man of impeccable taste.
I can stay, Craig, can't I?
Say I can.
You haven't even seen the room.
Your room.
My room?
Oh, yes, my room, my room.
Take me to my room!
This is Mark's old room,
he owns the place,
moved out about a month ago.
An uncle he'd never even heard of
died and left a load of money.
How very convenient.
This'll do just right. In fact...
No time to lose. I'll take it.
Ah... you'll want to see
my credentials.
There...
National Insurance number...
NHS number...
References...
Is that a reference
from the Archbishop of Canterbury?
I'm his special favourite.
Are you hungry? I'm hungry.
I haven't got anything in.
You've got everything I need
for an omelette fines herbes!
Pour deux!
So who's the girl on the fridge?
My friend. Sophie.
- Girlfriend?
- A friend who is a girl.
There's nothing going on.
That's completely normal.
Works for me.
We met at work about a year ago
at the call centre.
Oh, really, a communications
exchange? That could be handy.
Firm's going down though. The bosses are
using a totally rubbish business model.
I know what they should do,
I got a plan all worked out, but
I'm just a phone drone, I can't
go running in saying I know best.
Why am I telling you this?
I don't even know you.
I've got one of those faces.
People never stop blurting out
their plans while I'm around.
Right, where's your stuff?
Don't worry, it'll materialise,
if all goes to plan.
Oh, which one, which one?! No!
Why won't you land?!
Oh, that was incredible!
That was absolutely brilliant.
Where did you learn to cook?
Paris, in the 18th century.
No, hang on,
that's not recent, is it? 17th?
No, no, no, 20th. Sorry, I'm not used
to doing them in the right order.
Has anyone ever told you
that you're a bit weird?
They never really stop.
Ever been to Paris, Craig?
Nah, I can't see the point of Paris.
- I'm not much of a traveller.
- I can tell from your sofa.
My sofa? You're starting to look
like it.
Thanks, mate, that's lovely!
No, I like it here.
I'd miss it, I'd miss...
- Those keys?
- What?
You're sort of...
... fondling them.
- I'm holding them.
- Right.
Anyway...
these...
these are your keys.
I can stay?
Yeah, you're weird and you
can cook, it's good enough for me.
Outdoor, front door,
- your door.
- My door. My place. My gaff!
Me with a key.
And listen, Mark and I,
we had an arrangement where
if you ever need me out of your
hair, just give me a shout, OK?
Why would I want that?
In case you want to bring someone
round. A girlfriend or...
a boyfriend?
Oh, I will.
I'll shout if that happens.
Yes. Something like...
I WAS NOT EXPECTING THIS!
By the way, that...
the rot.
I've got the strangest feeling
we shouldn't touch it.
Earth to Pond, Earth to Pond.
Come in, Pond.
Oooh. Sorry!
Could you not wreck
my new earpiece, Pond?
No, I mean, he seems a laugh.
He's a bit weird,
good weird, you know?
'And he just happens to have three
grand on him in a paper bag?
Wait, wait. "The Doctor"?!
Craig, what if he's a dealer?!
Hello. Stop, please.
Can you hear me? I need your help.
How's the TARDIS coping?
See for yourself.
Ooh, nasty.
She's locked in a materialisation loop,
trying to land again but she can't.
And whatever's stopping her
is upstairs in that flat.
So go upstairs and sort it!
Please. My little girl's hurt.
I don't know what it is yet!
Anything that can stop the TARDIS
from landing is big, scary big!
Wait... aren't you scared?
I'm so sorry, but will you help me?
Please.
Help you?
A bow tie, are you serious?!
Hang on a sec.
What? Craig, Craig?
Orange juice, eocenes Arbuckle,
rare tarantula on the table, ooh!
I can't go up there until I know
what it is and how to deal with it!
It is vital that this "man" upstairs
doesn't realise who and what I am.
So no sonicking.
No advanced technology. I can only
use this cos we're on scramble.
To anyone else hearing this conversation,
we're talking absolute gibberish.
Practical eruption in chicken.
Descartes Lombardy spiral.
All I've got to do is pass
as an ordinary human being.
Simple.
What could possibly go wrong?
Have you seen you?
So you're just going to be snide?
No helpful hints?
Hmm, well, here's one...
bow tie, get rid!
Bow ties are cool.
Come on, Amy, I'm a normal bloke,
tell me what normal blokes do.
They watch telly, they play
football, they go down the pub.
I could do those things!
I don't, but I could!
Hang on. Wait, wait, wait! Amy?!
Interesting.
Localised time loop.
- What's all that?
- Time distortion.
Whatever's happening upstairs,
is still affecting you.
It's stopped... ish!
- How about your end?
- My end's good.
Doesn't sound great,
but nothing to worry about?
No, not really! Just keep the zigzag
plotter on full, that'll protect you.
- Amy, I said the zigzag plotter!
- I pulled the zigzag plotter!
What, you're standing
with the door behind you?
OK, take two steps to your right
and pull it again!
Now, I must not use the sonic.
I've got work to do,
need to pick up a few items.
Don't get comfortable!
- Doctor!
- Hello!
How long are you going to be
in there?
Sorry, I like a good soak!
- What the hell was that?
- What did you say?
I'm just going to go upstairs,
see if he's OK.
Sorry?
What did you say?
Yes? Hello?
Craig?
It's me from downstairs.
I heard a big bang.
No choice... it's sonicking time.
Thank you, Craig,
but I don't need your help.
- What happened, what's going on?
- Is that my toothbrush?
Correct. You spoke to the man upstairs?
What did he look like?
More normal than you do at the moment.
What are you doing?
I thought you might be in trouble.
Thanks!
Well if I ever am,
you can come and save me
with my toothbrush.
Hello?
Hello! The Doctor.
- Right.
- You must be Sophie.
No, Dom's in Malta, there's
nobody around.
Hang on a sec.
We've got a match today, pub league,
we're one down if you fancy it?
Pub league? A drinking competition?
No... football... play football?
Football! Yes, blokes play football!
I'm good at football, I think.
You've saved my life!
I've got somebody.
All right, see you down there.
I thought I'd come
early and meet your new flatmate.
Do you play, Sophie?
Soph just stands on the sidelines,
she's my mascot.
I'm your mascot? Mascot?!
Not my mascot, it's a football match,
I can't take a date.
- I didn't say I was your date.
- Neither did I.
Better get dressed.
The spare kit's just
in the bottom drawer.
Bit of a mess.
- What d'you think?
- You didn't say he was gorgeous!
You unlocked the door. How did
you do that? Those are your keys,
you must have left them
last time you came here.
Yeah, but I...
How do you know these are my keys?
- I've been holding them!
- I have got another set.
You've got two sets of keys
to someone else's house?
I see!
You must like it here too.
I'm going out,
if I hang about the house all the time,
him upstairs might get suspicious,
notice me.
Football, OK, well done,
that is normal.
Yeah, football, all outdoorsy.
Now, football's the one
with the sticks, isn't it?
What are you actually called,
what's your proper name?
Just call me the Doctor.
I can't say to these guys, "Hey, this is
my new flatmate, he's called the Doctor."
- Why not?
- Cos it's weird.
All right, Craig. Soph.
All right, mate.
Hello, I'm Craig's new flatmate.
- I'm called the Doctor.
- All right, Doctor. I'm Sean.
- Where are you strongest?
- Arms.
No, he means, what position?
On the field?
Not sure. The front? The side?
- Below?
- Are you any good though?
Let's find out!
That's not bad.
Yes. Go!
One two, one two!
Go on, Doctor, go on, Doctor!
You're brilliant, you're amazing!
Come on, Craig, show them
what you've got!
I love this game!
Please can you help me?
Can you help me, please?
Can you help me?
Hello?
I've lost my mum,
I don't know where she is.
Please can you help me?
Help you?
You poor thing, what's happened?
Can you help me find her?
You are so on the team!
Next week we've got the Crown
and Anchor, we'll annihilate them!
No violence, not while I'm around,
not today, not ever.
I'm the Doctor, the oncoming storm...
and you meant beat them
in a football match?
Lovely, what sort of time?
- It's happening again! Worse!
- What does the scanner say?
A lot of nines.
Is it good that they're nines?
Tell me it's good!
Yes, yes, it's... it's good!
Zigzag plotter, zigzag plotter.
Are you there?
Yes, hello.
Thank heavens. I thought the TARDIS
had been flung off into the vortex
with you inside it,
lost forever.
That could actually happen?
- You have got to get me out of here.
- How are the numbers?
All fives.
Fives?
Even better.
Still, it means the effect's
almost unbelievably
powerful and dangerous,
but don't worry.
Hang on, OK?
- I've got some rewiring to do.
- Hey! You..."hang on"!
Hello, flatmate.
Hey, man.
Listen, Sophie's
coming round tonight
and I was wondering
if you could give us some space?
Oh, don't mind me.
You won't even know I'm here.
That's the idea.
Yes, perfect!
What a beauty!
- That's got bigger.
- Oh, yeah.
Are we going out?
I've had a bit of a weird day,
can we do pizza-booze-telly?
Great, love it! Wait.
No Melina, no crises,
no interruptions.
Great. Excellent.
I've...
I think...
Where's this going?
I think that we...
... should...
Hello. What?
Sorry, don't worry, I wasn't listening,
in a world of my own down there.
- I thought you were going out?
- Just re-connecting all the electrics,
it's a real mess.
Where's the on-switch for this?
- He really is on his way out.
- No, I don't mind, if you don't mind.
I don't mind, why would I mind?
Then stay, have a drink with us.
What, do I have to stay now?
- Do you want to stay?
- I don't mind.
Great!
Cos life can seem pointless, Doctor.
Work, weekend, work, weekend.
And there's six billion people
on the planet doing pretty much the same.
Six billion people?
Watching you two at work,
I'm starting to wonder
where they all come from.
- What? What do you mean by that?
- So, the call centre. That's no good?
What do you really want to do?
Don't laugh.
I only ever told Craig about it.
I want to work
looking after animals.
Maybe abroad? I saw this
orang-utan sanctuary on telly.
- What's stopping you?
- She can't,
you need loads of qualifications.
Yeah, true. Plus...
it's scary, everyone I know
lives round here.
Craig got offered a job in London,
better money, didn't take it.
What's wrong with staying here?
I can't see the point of London.
Perhaps you'll just have
to stay here, secure
and a little bit miserable
until the day you drop.
Better than trying and failing, eh?
- You think I'd fail?
- Everybody's got dreams,
very few are going to achieve them,
so why pretend?
Perhaps, in the whole universe,
a call centre is where you should be?
- Why saying that? That's horrible.
- Is it true?
Of course it's not. I'm not staying
in a call centre all my life,
I can do anything I want!
Oh, my God!
Did you see what he just did?
What's happening? Are you going
to live with monkeys now?
It's a big old world, Sophie.
Work out what's really
keeping you here, eh?
I don't know.
Dunno.
So, are you going to be taking off
then, seeing the world?
What? Do you think I should?
Yeah...
Like the Doctor says,
what's keeping you here?
Yeah, exactly! What?
- Bye.
- See you.
See you in a bit.
Right. Shield's up.
Let's scan!
What are you getting?
Upstairs.
No traces of high technology.
Totally...
normal.
No no, no, no, it can't be!
It's too normal.
Only for you
could too normal be a problem.
You said I'd be lost forever.
Just go upstairs.
Without knowing, get myself killed,
then you really are lost.
If I could just
get a look in there...
Hold on.
Use the data bank,
get me the plans of this building,
its history, the layout, everything.
Meanwhile, I shall recruit a spy.
The Rotmeister...
Craig?
Breakfast, it's normal.
I told you not to touch it!
What's that?
An unfamiliar
and obviously poisonous substance.
"I know what would be really clever,
"I'll stick my hand in it!"
Come on, Craig, breathe.
Come on, Craig, breathe!
Thems are healthy footballer's lungs!
Right. Reverse the enzyme decay.
Excite the tannin molecules.
- I've got to go to work.
- On no account.
You need rest.
One more.
It's the planning meeting,
it's important.
You're important.
You're going to be fine, Craig.
What!
Afternoon.
I'm so sorry, Michael,
I don't know what happened,
I've got no excuse
I think that's not what my screen
is telling me, Mr Lang.
- What are you doing here?
- If that's your attitude, Mr Lang,
please take your custom elsewhere.
No, that's one of my best clients!
Craig, how are you feeling?
Had some time to kill,
I was curious, never worked in
an office. Never worked in anywhere.
You're insane!
Leave off the Doctor,
I love the Doctor.
He was brilliant
in the planning meeting.
- You went to the planning meeting?
- I was your representative.
We don't need Mr Lang any more.
Rude Mr Lang.
Here you go,
and I found some custard creams!
Sophie, my hero.
I went on the web,
applied for a wildlife charity thing.
They said I could always start
as a volunteer straight away.
Should I do it?
Great, yeah, good, go for it.
You look awful.
About turn! Bed. Now.
Who next? Oh, yes.
Hello, Mr Joergensen.
Can you hold?
I have to eat a biscuit.
Have you been upstairs?
Yes?
People who never come back down.
That's very bad.
- Hello.
- I can't take this any more.
I want you to go!
- You can have this back an' all.
- What have I done?
- For a start, talking to a cat.
- Lots of people talk to cats.
Everybody loves you, you're better
at football than me, and my job,
and now Sophie's all
"Oh, monkeys, monkeys!"
And then...
there's that!
It's art!
A statement on modern society,
"Ain't modern society awful?"
You've been here three days,
the three weirdest days of my life.
Your days will get a lot weirder
if I go!
I can't do this any more!
I can't leave this place.
I can't see the point of anywhere else.
Madrid, what a dump!
I have to stay.
- No, you have to leave!
- I can't go!
Just get out!
Right! Only way! I'm going to show
you something, but ssh, really!
I am going to regret this.
OK, right... First, general background!
- You're a...
- Yes.
From...
You've got a TARDIS!
Eleventh!
Right... OK,
specific detail!
You saw my ad
in the paper shop window.
Yes, with this right above it.
Which is odd,
because Amy hasn't written it yet.
Time travel,
- it CAN happen.
- That's a scanner!
You used
non-technological technology
of Lammasteen.
Shut up!
Please can you help me?
Please.
Will you help me?
What's the matter, my love?
Help you?
I am never,
ever doing that ever ever again...
- That's Amy Pond!
- Of course, you can understand us now,
Got those plans yet?
Still searching for them!
I've worked it out
with psychic help from a cat.
- Cat?
- Yes,
He's got a time engine
in the flat upstairs.
He's using innocent people to try
and launch it. Whenever he does,
- they get burnt up, hence the stain.
- From the ceiling?
Well done.
And you, Miss Pond,
nearly get thrown off into the Vortex.
Lovely!
People are dying up there?
People are dying.
They're being killed!
Someone's up there.
Craig, come on...
someone's dying up there.
It's Sophie.
It's Sophie that's dying up there,
it's Sophie!
- Where's Sophie!
- Wait, wait!
Are you upstairs?
- Just going in!
- But you can't be upstairs.
- Of course I can be upstairs!
- No! I've got the plans,
you cannot be upstairs,
it's a one-storey building.
There is no upstairs!
What?
Of course!
The time engine isn't IN the flat.
The time engine IS the flat!
Someone's attempt to build a TARDIS.
No, there's always been an upstairs.
- Has there? Think about it!
- Yes.
No. I don't...
Perception filter. It's more than
a disguise. It tricks your memory.
Oh, my God, Sophie!
- Craig!
- It's controlling her.
It's willing her
to touch the activator.
It's not going to have her!
- Ah! Deadlock seal!
- You've got to do something!
What? Why's it let her go?
- You will help me.
- Right! Stop! Crashed ship, let's see.
Hello, I'm Captain Troy Handsome
of International Rescue.
Please state
the nature of your emergency.
The ship has crashed.
The crew are dead.
A pilot is required.
You're the emergency crash program.
A hologram. You've been luring people up
here so you can try them out.
You will help me,
you will help me....
- Craig! Where am I?
- Hush!
Human brains aren't strong enough,
they just burn. You're stupid,
you just keep trying.
17 people have been tried.
6,000,400,026 remain.
- Seriously, what is going on?
- For goodness sake, the top floor
of the building is a space ship,
intent on slaughtering
the population of this planet.
Any questions? No, good.
I have questions.
The correct pilot
has now been found.
Yes, I was worried you'd say that.
He means you, doesn't he?
The correct pilot has been found.
The correct pilot has been found
What's happening?
It's pulling me in!
I'm the new pilot!
Could you do it?
Could you fly the ship safely?
No, I'm way too much for this ship.
My hand touches that panel,
the planet doesn't blow up,
the whole solar system does.
No... worst choice ever,
I promise you. Stop this!
It's getting worse.
It doesn't want everyone.
Craig, it didn't want you!
I spoke to him
and he said I couldn't help him!
It didn't want Sophie before today
but now it does. What's changed?
No! I gave her the idea of leaving!
It's a machine that needs to leave,
it wants people who want to escape!
And you don't want to leave, Craig,
you're Mr Sofa Man.
You can shut down the engine.
Put your hand on the panel
and concentrate
on why you want to stay!
- Craig, no!
- Will it work? Are you sure?
- Yes!
- Is that a lie?
Of course it's a lie!
It's good enough for me. Geronimo!
Craig, what's keeping you here?
Think about everything
that makes you want to stay here!
Why don't you want to leave?
Sophie! And I don't want
to leave Sophie!
I can't leave Sophie! I love Sophie!
I love you, too, Craig, you idiot!
- Honestly, do you mean that?
- Of course! Do you mean it?
I've always meant it.
Seriously though, do you mean it?
What about the monkeys?
Not now, not again!
Craig, the planet's about to burn!
For God's sake, kiss the girl!
Kiss the girl!
You've done it.
You've done it!
Now the screen's just zeros! Now it's
minus ones, minus twos, minus threes...
Big yes!
Help me. Help me...
Big no.
Did we switch it off?
Emergency shutdown, it's imploding,
everybody out!
Look at them. Didn't they see that?
The whole top floor just vanished.
Perception filter.
There never was a top floor.
- So have we spoiled our friendship?
- Totally ruined it.
And what about the monkeys?
We could save them together,
you know.
Do whatever we want.
I could see the point of Paris
if you were there with me.
First let's destroy
our friendship completely.
What, you're trying to sneak off?
Yes, well, you were sort of...
busy.
I want you to keep these.
Thank you. Cos I might pop back soon,
have another little stay.
No, you won't.
I've been in your head, remember.
But I still want you to keep them.
Thank you, Craig.
Thank you, Doctor.
Now then.
6,000,400,026 people in the world.
That's the number to beat.
Back in time! You need to go to the
paper shop, leave that note for me.
Right little matchmaker, aren't you?
Can't you find me a fella?
Rectifier's playing up again...
Hold on.
You write the note
and I'll change that will.
- You got a pen?
- Make sure it's a red pen.
There were cracks.
Through some we saw silence
and the end of all things.
It's the crack in my wall.
Two parts of space and time
that should
never have touched,
pressed together.
All through the universe,
rips in the continuum.
How could it be here?
- How can it be following me?
- I don't know yet, I'm working it out.
Some sort of
space-time cataclysm, maybe.
Big enough to put cracks
in the universe.
But what?
The universe is cracked.
The Pandorica will open,
silence will fall.
Pandorica...
That's a fairytale!
If it is real,
it's here and it's opening.
What is it?
A box, a cage a prison.
There was a goblin or a Trickster,
or a warrior, soaked in the blood
of a billion galaxies.
The most feared being
in all the cosmos.
The Pandorica.
More than just a fairytale.
It's opening.
Your world has visitors.
Daleks and Cyberships, Sontarans,
Slitheen, Chelonian,
Nestene, Drahvin, Sycorax...
What's in there,
what could justify all this?
What are you?
What could you possibly be?