Well done, Mabel.
Well done, Alfie.
Good girl, Tabitha.
Very well done, Ranjit.
Good girl, Chloe.
Well done, Ben.
Well done, Mandy.
Bad boy, Timmy.
Zero.
- You got a zero, didn't you?
- Yeah. So?
- You'll have to walk home, then.
- Walk to London? That's 20 decks!
You can't ride a Vator with a zero.
You know what happens.
You'll get sent below.
I'll wait for you.
Welcome to Vator Verse,
sponsored by
McLintock's Candy Burgers.
London, please.
A horse and a man, above, below
One has a plan, but both must go
Mile after mile, above, beneath
One has a smile, and one has teeth
Though the man above might say hello
Expect no love from the beast below.
Help!
Help me!
U-Sub.net et la Allons-y Team
présentent :
Docteur Who Saison 5
Transcript : Red Bee Media Ltd
Synchro : Dauphinus, darkevil, delphiki,
Imaginos, JOJO13 et Sargeros
Traduction : citrøn, darkevil, delphiki,
Imaginos, Mika, et mmime
Relecture : Arno, citrøn, G-Lo,
Imaginos et Killarney
The Beast Below
My name is Amy Pond.
When I was seven,
I had an imaginary friend.
Last night was the night before
my wedding...
Come on, Pond.
... and my imaginary
friend came back.
- Now do you believe me
- OK,
your box is a spaceship.
It's really, really a spaceship.
We are in space!
- What are we breathing?
- I've extended the air shell we're fine.
Now, that's interesting.
29th Century.
Solar flares roast the earth,
and the entire human race
packs its bags
and moves out
till the weather improves.
- Whole nations migrating to the stars.
- Doctor?
- Isn't that amazing?
Doctor!
Come on.
I've found us a spaceship.
This is the United Kingdom of
Britain and Northern Ireland -
all of it, bolted together
and floating in the sky.
Starship UK. It's Britain,
but metal.
That's not just a ship,
that's an idea.
That's a whole country,
living and laughing and...
shopping.
Searching the stars for a new home.
- Can we go out and see?
- Of course but first, there's a thing.
- A thing?
- An important thing. In fact, thing one
we are observers only. That's the one
rule I've always stuck to in my travels.
I never get involved in the affairs
of other peoples or planets.
- That's interesting.
- So we're like a wildlife documentary,
yeah? Cos if they see a wounded cub or
something, they can't just save it
they've got to keep filming
and let it die.
That's got to be hard.
I don't think I could do that.
Don't you find that hard being all,
like, detached and cold?
Doctor?
Welcome to London Market.
You are being monitored.
I'm in the future.
Like hundreds... of years
in the future.
- I've been dead for centuries.
- Oh, lovely.
You're a cheery one.
Never mind dead, look at this place.
Isn't it wrong?
What's wrong?
Use your eyes, notice everything.
What's wrong with this picture?
Is it... the bicycles?
- Bit unusual on a spaceship, bicycles.
- Says the girl in the nightie.
Oh, my God! I'm in my nightie.
Now, come on, look around you.
Actually look.
London Market is a crime-free zone.
Life on a giant starship,
back to basics.
Bicycles, washing lines,
wind-up street lamps.
But look closer. Secrets and
shadows, lives led in fear.
Society bent out of shape, on the
brink of collapse. A police state.
- Excuse me.
- What are you doing?
Sorry.
Checking all the water in this area.
There's an escaped fish.
- Where was I?
- Why did you just do that?
I think a lot.
It's hard to keep track.
- Now, police state, do you see it yet?
- Where?
There.
Are you sure?
Saw it myself.
Are you going to tell her?
We're under orders to tell her.
Well done. Keep tabs on him.
Sorry to interrupt.
There's been a sighting.
London block, Oxford Street.
A man.
Did he do the thing?
Apparently.
I'll have a look on the monitors.
One little girl crying. So?
Crying silently.
I mean, children cry
cos they want attention, cos
they're hurt or afraid. When they cry
silently, it's cos they just can't stop.
- Any parent knows that.
- Are you a parent?
Hundreds of parents walking past and not
one of them's asking her what's wrong,
which means...
they already know, and it's something
they don't talk about Secrets.
They're not helping her, it's something
they're afraid of shadows.
Whatever they're
afraid of it's nowhere to be seen,
which means it's everywhere.
Police state.
- Where'd she go?
- Deck 207,
Apple Sesame block, Dwelling 54A.
You're looking for Mandy Tanner.
This fell out of her pocket
when I accidentally bumped into her.
Took me four goes.
Ask her about those things.
The smiling fellows in the booths.
They're everywhere.
But they're just things.
They're clean.
Everything else here is battered and
filthy. Look at this place.
No-one's laid a finger on those booths.
Not a footprint within two feet of them.
Ask Mandy, "Why are people scared
of the things in the booths?"
Hang on, what do I do?
I don't know what I'm doing here
and I'm not even dressed!
It's this or Leadworth.
What do you think?
Let's see.
What will Amy Pond choose?
Gotcha!
- Meet me back here in half an hour.
- What are you going to do?
What I always do.
Stay out of trouble.
Badly.
So is this how it works, Doctor?
You never interfere in the affairs
of other peoples or planets,
unless there's children crying?
Yes.
You're following me.
Saw you watching me
at the marketplace.
You dropped this.
Yeah, when your friend
kept bumping into me.
- What's that?
- There's a hole. We have to go back.
A what? A hole?
Are you stupid? There's a hole
in the road. We can't go that way.
There's a travel pipe down
by the airlocks, if you've got stamps.
- What are you doing?
- Don't mind me.
Never could resist
a "keep out" sign.
What's through there?
What's so scary about a hole?
Something under the road?
Nobody knows.
- We're not supposed to talk about it.
- About what?
Below.
And because you're not supposed to,
you don't?
Watch and learn.
- You sound Scottish.
- I am Scottish. What's wrong with that?
Scotland's got to be here somewhere.
No.
They wanted their own ship.
Good for them. Nothing changes.
How did you get here?
Just passing through, you know,
with a guy.
Your boyfriend?
What?
Nothing. It's just...
I'm getting married.
Funny how things slip your mind.
- Married?
- Yeah, shut up, married.
Really, actually married.
- Almost definitely.
- When?
Well, it's kind of weird.
A long time ago, tomorrow morning.
I wonder what I did.
Result!
- Coming?
- No.
Suit yourself.
Stop! You mustn't do that!
My God.
That's weird. That's...
Can't be.
The impossible truth
in a glass of water.
Not many people see it.
But you do, don't you, Doctor?
- You know me?
- Keep your voice down.
They're everywhere.
- Tell me what you see in the glass.
- Who says I see anything?
Don't waste time.
At the marketplace,
you placed a glass of water
on the floor, looked at it,
then came straight here
to the engine room. Why?
No engine vibration on deck.
Ship this size, engine this big,
you'd feel it. The water would move.
I thought I'd take a look.
It doesn't make sense.
These power couplings,
they're not connected. Look.
They're dummies, see?
And behind this wall, nothing.
It's hollow.
If I didn't know better, I'd say
there was...
No engine at all.
But it's working. This ship is
traveling though space. I saw it.
The impossible truth, Doctor.
We're traveling among the stars
in a spaceship that could never fly.
- How?
- I don't know.
There's a darkness at the heart
of this nation.
It threatens every one of us.
Help us, Doctor.
You're our only hope.
Your friend is safe. This will
take you to her. Now go, quickly!
Who are you?
How do I find you again?
I am Liz 10. And I will find you.
Welcome to voting cubicle
330C.
Please leave this installation
as you would wish to find it.
The United Kingdom
recognizes the right
to know of all its citizens.
A presentation concerning
the history of Starship UK
will begin shortly.
Your identity is being verified
on our electoral roll.
Name: Amelia Jessica Pond.
Age:
1,306.
Shut up!
Marital status...
Unknown.
You are here
because you want to know
the truth about this starship,
and I am talking to you because
you're entitled to know.
When this presentation has finished,
you will have a choice.
You may either protest...
or forget.
If you choose to protest,
understand this.
If just
1% of the population
of this ship do likewise,
the programme will be discontinued,
with consequences for you all.
If you choose to accept the situation,
and we hope that you will,
then press the "forget" button.
All the information I am about
to give you will be erased
from your memory.
You will continue to enjoy the safety
and amenities of Starship
UK, unburdened by the knowledge
of what has been
done to save you.
Here, then,
is the truth about Starship UK,
and the price that has been paid
for the safety of the British people.
May God have mercy on our souls.
MESSAGE EN ATTENTE.
This isn't a trick.
You've got to find
the Doctor and get him back
to the TARDIS.
Don't let him investigate.
Stop him. Do whatever you have to.
Just please,
please get the Doctor off this ship!
What have you done?
Yeah, your basic memory wipe job.
- Must have erased about 20 minutes.
- But why would I choose to forget?
Cos everyone does.
Everyone chooses
the "forget" button.
Did you?
I'm not eligible to vote yet.
I'm 12.
Any time after you're 16,
you're allowed to the see the film and
make your choice.
And then, once every five years...
And once every five years, everyone
chooses to forget what they've learned.
Democracy in action.
How do you not know about this?
- Are you Scottish too?
- I'm way worse than Scottish.
I can't even see the movie.
Won't play for me.
It played for me.
The difference being
the computer doesn't accept me as human.
Why not?
You look human.
No,
you look Time Lord.
- We came first.
- So there are other Time Lords?
There were, but there aren't...
Just me now.
Long story. There was a bad day.
Bad stuff happened,
and you know what? I'd love to forget it
all, every last bit of it, but I don't.
Not ever.
Cos this is what I do,
every time, every day,
every second.
This.
Hold tight.
We're bringing down the government.
Say, "Wheee!"
It's all right, love.
It's only me.
High-speed air cannon.
Lousy way to travel.
- Where are we?
- 600 feet down,
20 miles laterally, puts us
at the heart of the ship. I'd say...
Lancashire.
What's this
then a cave? Can't be a cave. Looks
- like a cave.
- It's a rubbish dump,
- and it's minging!
- Yes, but
only food refuse.
Organic, coming through feeder tubes
from all over the ship.
The floor's all squidgy,
like a water bed.
But feeding what, though?
It's sort of rubbery, feel it.
Wet and slimy.
It's not a floor, it's a...
It's a what?
The next word is kind of the scary word.
Take a moment.
Get yourself in a calm place.
Go "omm".
It's a tongue.
- A tongue?
- A tongue. A great big tongue.
This is a mouth?
This whole place
is a mouth?
- We're in a mouth?
- Yes.
But on the plus side, roomy.
How do we get out?
How big is this beastie?
It's gorgeous!
Blimey! If this is just the mouth,
I'd love to see the stomach.
- Though not right now.
- Doctor, how do we get out?
It's being fed through surgically
implanted feeder tubes, so
the normal entrance is...
... closed for business.
- We can try, though.
- No! Stop, don't move!
- Too late. It's started.
- What has?
Swallow reflex.
- What you doing?
- I'm vibrating the chemo-receptors.
Chemo-what?
The eject button.
- How does a mouth have an eject button?
- Think about it!
Right, then.
This isn't going to be big
on dignity.
There's nothing broken,
there's no sign of concussion
and yes, you are covered in sick.
- Where are we?
- Overspill pipe, at a guess.
- Oh, God, it stinks.
- That's not the pipe.
Can we get out?
One door, one door switch,
one condition.
We forget everything we saw.
Look familiar?
That's the carrot.
Here's the stick.
There's a creature living in the heart
of this ship. What's it doing there?
No, that's not going to work on me,
so come on.
Big old beast below decks,
and everyone who protests gets shoved
down its throat. That how it works?
Stop it. I'm not leaving
and I'm not forgetting
and what are you fellows going to do
about it? Stick out your tongues?
Doctor?
Look who it is.
You look a lot better
without your mask.
You must be Amy. Liz.
Liz 10.
Hi!
Lovely hair, Amy.
Shame about the sick.
You know Mandy?
- She's very brave.
- How did you find us?
Stuck my gizmo on you.
Been listening in.
Nice moves on the hurl escape.
So, what's the big fella doing here?
You're over 16, you've voted.
Whatever this is, you've chosen
to forget about it.
No. Never forgot, never voted.
Not technically a British subject.
Then who and what are you,
and how do you know me?
You're a bit hard to miss, love.
Mysterious stranger,
MO consistent with higher alien
intelligence, hair of an idiot...
I've been brought up on the stories.
My whole family was.
Your family?
They're repairing. Doesn't take them
long. Let's move.
The Doctor.
Old drinking buddy of Henry XII.
Tea and scones with Liz II. Vicky was a
bit on the fence about you, weren't she?
Knighted and exiled you
on the same day.
And so much for the Virgin Queen,
you bad, bad boy!
Liz 10?
Liz 10, yeah. Elizabeth X. And down!
I'm the bloody Queen, mate.
Basically, I rule.
There's a high-speed Vator
through there.
Oh, yeah. There's these things.
Any ideas?
I saw one of these up top.
There was a hole in the road,
like it had burst through,
- like a root.
- Exactly like a root.
It's all one creature - the same
one we were inside - reaching out.
It must be growing through
the mechanisms of the entire ship.
What? Like an infestation?
Someone's helping it.
Feeding it.
Feeding my subjects to it. Come on.
We've got to keep moving.
Doctor?
Oh, Amy.
We should never have come here.
Don't let him investigate.
Stop him. Do whatever you have to.
Just please, please get the Doctor
off this ship.
Winder division one.
Ten has penetrated
to the lower levels.
Initiate the protocol.
God save the Queen.
Why all the glasses?
To remind me every single day that
my government is up to something,
and it's my duty to find out what.
A queen going undercover
to investigate her own kingdom?
Secrets are being kept from me.
I don't have a choice.
Ten years I've been at this,
my entire reign
and you've achieved more
in one afternoon.
How old were you
when you came to the throne?
40. Why?
What, you're 50 now?
No way!
They slowed my body clock.
Keeps me looking like the stamps.
- And you always wear this in public?
- Undercover is not easy when you're me.
The autographs, the bunting.
Air-balanced porcelain.
Stays on by itself,
cos it's perfectly
sculpted to your face.
So what?
Oh, Liz.
So everything.
What are you doing?
How dare you come in here?
Ma'am,
you have expressed interest in
the interior workings of Starship UK.
You will come with us now.
Why would I do that?
How can they be Smilers?
Half Smiler, half human.
Whatever you creatures are,
I am still your queen.
On whose authority is this done?
The highest authority, Ma'am.
- I AM the highest authority.
- Yes, ma'am.
- You must go now, Ma'am.
- Where?
The tower, Ma'am.
Doctor, where are we?
The lowest point of Starship UK.
The dungeon. Ma'am.
Hawthorne!
So this is
where you hid yourself away.
You've got some explaining to do.
There's children down here.
What's all that about?
Protesters and citizens of
limited value are fed to the beast.
For some reason,
it won't eat the children.
You're the first adults it's spared.
You're very lucky.
Yeah, look at us. Torture chamber
of the Tower of London.
Lucky.
Except it's not
a torture chamber, is it?
Well, except it is.
Except it isn't.
Depends on your angle.
What's that?
Well, like I say,
depends on the angle.
It's either the exposed pain center of big
fella's brain, being tortured relentlessly.
Or it's the gas pedal.
The accelerator,
Starship UK's go-faster button.
- I don't understand.
- Don't you? Try.
Go on.
The spaceship that could never fly,
no vibration on deck.
This creature. This poor,
trapped, terrified creature.
It's not infesting you,
it's not invading, it's...
what you have instead of an engine.
And this place down here
is where you hurt it,
where you torture it, day after day,
just to keep it moving.
Tell you what.
Normally, it's above
the range of human hearing.
This is the sound
none of you wanted to hear.
Stop it.
Who did this?
We act on instructions
from the highest authority.
I am the highest authority.
The creature will be released.
Now.
I said now!
- Is anyone listening to me?
- Liz.
Your mask.
What about it?
Look at it.
It's old.
At least 200 years old, I'd say.
Yeah, it's an antique, so?
Yeah, an antique made
by a craftsmen over 200 years ago
and perfectly sculpted to your face.
They slowed your body clock,
all right, but you're not 50.
Nearer 300.
And it's been a long old reign.
Nah, it's ten years.
I've been on this throne ten years.
Ten years.
And the same ten years
over and over again,
always...
always leading you... here.
What have you done?
Only what you have ordered.
We work for you, Ma'am.
The Winders, the Smilers,
all of us.
If you are watching this...
If I am watching this,
then I have found my way
to the Tower Of London.
The creature you are looking at
is called a Star Whale.
Once, there were millions of them.
They lived in the depths of space and,
according to legend,
guided the early space travelers
through the asteroid belts.
This one,
as far as we are aware,
is the last of its kind.
And what we have done to it
breaks my heart.
The Earth was burning.
Our sun had turned on us,
and every other nation
had fled to the skies.
Our children screamed
as the skies grew hotter.
And then it came,
like a miracle.
The last of the star whales.
We trapped it.
We built our ship around it,
and we rode on its back to safety.
If you wish our voyage to continue,
then you must press
the "forget" button.
Be again the heart of this nation,
untainted.
If not,
press the other button.
Your reign will end,
the Star Whale will be released,
and our ship will disintegrate.
I hope I keep the strength
to make the right decision.
I voted for this?
Why would I do that?
Because you knew if we stayed here,
I'd be faced with
an impossible choice.
Humanity or the alien.
You took it upon yourself
to save me from that.
And that was wrong.
You don't ever decide
what I need to know.
- I don't even remember doing it.
- You did it. That's what counts.
I'm...
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, I don't care.
When I'm done here,
you're going home.
Why?
Because I made a mistake?
One mistake?
I don't even remember doing it.
- Doctor!
- Yeah. I know.
You're only human.
What are you doing?
The worst thing I'll ever do.
I'm going to pass a massive electrical
charge through the Star Whale's brain.
It should knock out all its higher
functions, leave it a vegetable.
The ship will still fly,
but the whale won't feel it.
- That'll be like killing it.
- Look, three options.
One,
I let the Star Whale continue
in unendurable agony
for hundreds more years.
Two, I kill everyone on this ship.
Three, I murder a beautiful,
innocent creature
as painlessly as I can.
And then I find a new name,
cos I won't be the Doctor any more.
There must be some other way.
Nobody talk to me. Nobody human,
has anything to say to me today!
Timmy!
You made it, you're OK!
It's me - Mandy.
Come on, use your eyes.
Notice everything.
Our children screamed.
It came, like a miracle.
It won't eat the children.
Children screamed. Then it came.
It's the last of its kind.
- Just me now.
- The last of its kind.
Is this how it works, Doctor? Never
interfere with other people or planets.
- Children screamed.
- Unless it's children crying.
- The last of its kind.
- Just me now.
- Unless there's children crying.
- Yes.
It won't eat the children.
Then it came.
Like a miracle.
The last of the Star Whales.
Doctor, stop.
Whatever you're doing, stop it now!
Sorry, Your Majesty,
going to need a hand.
Amy, no! No!
Amy, what have you done?
Nothing at all.
Am I right?
We've increased speed!
Yeah, well,
you've stopped torturing the pilot.
Gotta help.
It's still here?
I don't understand.
The Star Whale didn't come like
a miracle all those years ago.
It volunteered.
You didn't have to trap it
or torture it -
that was all just you.
It came because it couldn't stand
to watch your children cry.
What if you were really old,
and really kind and alone?
Your whole race dead, no future.
What couldn't you do then?
If you were that old, and that kind,
and the very last of your kind...
you couldn't just stand there
and watch children cry.
From Her Majesty.
She says there will be
no more secrets on Starship UK.
Amy, you could have killed
everyone on this ship.
You could have killed a Star Whale.
And you saved it.
I know, I know.
Amazing, though, don't you think?
The Star Whale.
All that pain and misery...
... and loneliness.
And it just made it kind.
But you couldn't have known
ho wit would react. You couldn't.
But I've seen it before.
Very old and very kind,
and the very, very last.
Sound a bit familiar?
What?
Gotcha. Ha!
Gotcha.
Shouldn't we say goodbye?
Won't they wonder where we went?
For the rest of their lives.
Oh, the songs they'll write!
Never mind them. Big day tomorrow.
- Sorry, what?
- It's always a big day tomorrow.
We've got a time machine.
I skip the little ones.
You know what I said about
getting back for tomorrow morning...
Have you ever run away from something
because you were scared, or,
or not ready, or just...
Just because you could?
Once...
a long time ago.
What happened?
Hello!
Right.
Doctor, there's something
I haven't told you.
No. Hang on,
is that a phone ringing?
- People phone you?
- Well, it's a phone box.
Would you mind?
Hello?
Sorry, who?
No, seriously. Who?
Says he's Prime Minister. First
the Queen, now the Prime Minister.
Get about, don't you?
Which Prime Minister?
- The British one.
- Which British one?
Which British one?
Winston Churchill for you.
Oh! Hello, dear. What's up?
Tricky situation, Doctor.
Potentially very dangerous.
I think I'm going to need you.
Don't worry about a thing,
Prime Minister. We're on our way.
In bed above, we're deep asleep
While greater love lies further deep
This dream must end.
This world must know.
We all depend on the beast below.
- Winston Churchill.
- Doctor, is it you?
Cabinet War Rooms, right?
I have something to show you.
Our new secret weapon.
- This is one of my ironsides.
- Your what?
I am your soldier.
- You didn't invent them, they're alien.
- They'll win me the war.
They're up to something,
but what is it? What are they after?
I've defeated you time and again.
I've saved the whole of reality
from you.
I am the Doctor,
and you are the Daleks.
Behold the restoration
of the Daleks.