It is said that
in the final days of planet Earth,
everyone had bad dreams.
To the west of the north of that
world, the human race did gather,
in celebration of a pagan rite,
to banish the cold and the dark.
Each and every one
of those people had dreamt
of the terrible things to come.
But they forgot.
Because they must.
They forgot their nightmares
of fire and war and insanity.
They forgot.
Except for one.
They call it
the Legend of the Blue Box.
Oh.
I've never been in here before.
I'm not one for churches
too cold.
This was the site of a convent,
back in the 1300s.
It's said a demon fell from the sky.
Then a man appeared.
A man in a blue box.
They called him
the sainted physician.
He smote the demon
and then disappeared.
That's a bit of a coincidence.
It's said there's
no such thing as coincidence.
Who knows?
- Perhaps he's coming back.
- Oh, that would make my Christmas!
Doctor Who - Special Christmas 2009
The End Of Time (Part 1)
Transcript: bean
Subtitles: Grîshnak, LauCass
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~
Ah! Now, sorry, there you are.
So, where were we?
I was summoned, wasn't I?
An Ood, in the snow,
calling to me.
I didn't exactly come straight here.
Had a bit of fun, y'know?
Travelled about. Did this and that.
Got into trouble, you know me.
It was brilliant.
I saw the Phosphorous Carousel
of the Great Magellan Gestadt.
Saved a planet
from the Red Carnivorous Maw.
Named a galaxy Alison.
Got married. That was a mistake.
Good Queen Bess, and let me tell
you, her nickname is no longer...
Anyway...
what d'you want?
You should not have delayed.
The last time I was here, you said
my song would be ending soon,
and I'm in no hurry for that.
You will come with me.
Hold on, better lock the TARDIS.
See? Like a car.
I locked it, like a car.
Like... it's funny.
No? Little bit?
Blimey, try to make an Ood laugh.
So how old are you now,
Ood Sigma?
Magnificent!
Oh, come on!
That is... splendid!
You've achieved
all this in how long?
100 years.
Then we've got a problem.
Cos all of this is way too fast.
Not just the city,
I mean your ability to call me.
Reaching all the way
back to the 21st century.
Something's accelerating
your species way beyond normal.
And the Mind of the Ood is troubled.
- Why, what's happened?
- Every night, Doctor...
every night, we have bad dreams.
Returning, returning,
returning, it is slowly returning.
Through the dark and the fire
and the blood, always returning,
returning to this world.
It is returning, and he is returning.
And they are returning, but too late,
too late, far too late, he is come.
Sit with the Elder of the Ood
and share the dreaming.
So...
Right.
Hallo!
You will join, you will join,
you will join, you will join,
you will join.
He comes to us.
Every night.
I think all the peoples
of the universe dream of him now.
- That man is dead.
- There is yet more.
Join us.
Events are taking shape.
So many years ago,
and yet changing the now.
There is a man...
..so scared.
Wilfred! Is he all right?
- What about Donna, is she safe?
- You should not have delayed,
for the lines of convergence
are being drawn across the Earth,
even now.
The king is in his counting house.
I don't know who they are.
And there is another.
The most lonely of all,
lost and forgotten.
The Master's wife.
We see so much,
but understand little.
The woman in the cage, who is she?
She was...
It w-wasn't her fault, she was...
The Master,
he's a Time Lord, like me.
I can show you.
The Master took the name of Saxon.
He married a human, a woman
called Lucy. And he corrupted her.
She stood at his side
while he conquered the Earth.
I reversed everything he'd done,
so it never even happened.
But Lucy Saxon remembered.
I held him in my arms.
I burnt his body!
The Master is dead!
And yet, you did not see...
What's that?
Part of him survived.
I have to go!
But something more
is happening, Doctor.
The Master
is part of a greater design.
Because a shadow
is falling over creation.
Something vast
is stirring in the dark.
The Ood have gained this power
to see through time
because time is bleeding.
Shapes of things once lost
are moving through the veil.
And these events from years ago
threaten to destroy this future,
and the present, and the past.
- What do you mean?
- This is what we have seen, Doctor.
The darkness heralds only one thing.
The end of time itself.
Events that have happened
are happening now.
Mrs Saxon.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm your new Governor.
I'm afraid the previous Governor
met with something of an accident,
which took
quite some time to arrange.
Miss Trefusis, if you will prepare.
You kept your silence well,
Mrs Saxon.
Your trial was held
in secret, with no jury.
So, no-one knows
who Harold Saxon was.
Where he came from.
Why you killed him.
Make her kneel.
There are those of us
who never lost faith.
And in his wisdom, Harold Saxon
prepared for this moment.
He knew that he might die
and he made us ready.
Tonight, Mrs Saxon...
..he returns.
As it was written
in the Secret Books of Saxon,
these...
are the Potions of Life.
Listen to me!
Whatever he told you...
you've got no idea
what you're doing!
Miss Trefusis...
- the catalyst.
- What are you doing?
Leave me alone! Don't. Don't!
You were Saxon's wife.
You bore his imprint.
That's all we needed -
the final biometrical signature.
You can't bring him back, you can't!
I'm begging you!
Stop this now before it's too late!
We give ourselves...
that Saxon might live!
Can't you see?!
He lied to you!
His name isn't even Harold Saxon!
And this was written also.
For his name is...
the Master!
Never.
Never. Never.
Never dying. Never dying!
Never dying! Never dying!
Never dying!
Oh, Lucy...
sweet Lucy Saxon.
My ever faithful.
Did the widow's kiss
bring me back to life?
- You're killing them!
- Oh, let them die.
They're just the first.
The whole stupid stinking
human disgrace can fall into the pit.
Can't you hear it, Lucy?
The noise?
The drumbeat?
Louder than ever before.
The drums,
the never-ending drums.
Oh, I have missed them!
But no-one knew you
better than I did.
I knew you'd come back.
And all this time, your disciples
have prepared.
But so have we!
What are you doing?
The Secret Books of Saxon
spoke of the Potions of Life.
And I was never that bright,
but my family had contacts.
People who were clever enough
to calculate the opposite.
Don't you dare!
I'm ordering you, Lucy.
You will obey me!
Till death do us part, Harry!
NO-O-O-O!
I think we might
be in luck, darling.
It's the footage from Broadfell
Prison the night it burnt down.
Take a look at this.
Someone survived!
Do you think it's him?
Oh, that would be
such a Christmas present.
You just leave it to Daddy.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it seems help is at hand.
Christmas is cancelled.
Prepare the gate.
Just going down to the Lion.
Quick little snifter.
Christmas drinks.
Right, ta-ra.
Paratroop One to Paratroop Two,
we are mobilised, I repeat,
we are mobilised.
Rendezvous 1300 hours.
Over and out.
Come on!
Shake a leg!
Right, come on, let's get going.
Everybody all right?
Who's got the chocolates, then?
He's tall and thin, wears
a brown suit, maybe a blue suit,
he's got a long brown coat.
Modern sort of hair,
all sticky-uppy, right?
Oh, and on page two,
be on the lookout for a police box.
Exactly like the old ones.
I got locked inside one of them -
August Bank Holiday 1962.
- Were you misbehaving, Minnie?
- I certainly was. Wa-hey!
Yeah, all right, all right.
Listen, this is important.
We have got to find it,
so phone around,
phone everybody.
Sally,
will you get onto the Bridge Club?
Winston, you try the Old Boys.
Bobby, want you to ring
the skiffle band, right?
We've got the city covered.
- The Silver Cloak.
- Yeah.
Who is he, then, this Doctor?
No, I can't tell you that. I swear.
But answer me this -
have you been
having bad dreams? All of you?
Dreams you can't remember?
Yeah.
That's why we need him.
We need the Doctor.
More than ever.
- Onions with that?
- Oh, yeah, go on, pile 'em on.
What about you, Ginger?
Onions?
He don't say much.
Give him onions.
- He's down from Huddersfield.
- Well, you look after him.
And don't forget tomorrow night,
the Christmas broadcast.
President Obama,
he's promised to end the recession.
- Bad times will soon be over, Ginger.
- Well, season's greetings to you.
And you. Happy Christmas.
Now, what can we get you, sir?
Everything.
I am so hungry.
They're saying that
the President's got this grand plan.
He's going to save the world
with some big financial scheme.
Whatever it is,
I bet it won't reach you and me.
Somebody's lively on his feet.
Starving.
Now, y'see, that's what you don't
want to do - eat it all at once.
Tempting, I know.
But if you make it last,
it can last all day.
Want more.
Want cheese and chips.
And meat and gravy,
and cream and beer,
and pork and beef and fat,
and great big chunks of hot, wet red.
Good for you, mate!
Maybe we'd better be going.
You look like that bloke.
Harold Saxon.
The one that went mad.
Isn't that funny?
Isn't that just the best thing of all?
The master of disguise,
stuck
looking like the old Prime Minister.
I can't hide anywhere!
He can see me,
he can smell me...
Can't let him smell me!
Doctor, Doctor, shockter
stopped-her, got to stop the smell!
The stink, the filthy, filthy stink!
Ginger.
Come with me, right now!
Because it's funny...!
Don't you see?
Look at me!
I'm splitting my sides.
I am hilarious!
I am the funniest thing
in the whole wide world!
Sarah!
God help us!
There's this man...!
Dinnerti-i-i-ime!
Please, let me help!
You're burning up
your own life force.
Oh, my gosh, Doctor,
you're a sight for sore eyes.
Out of my way!
Did we do it?
Is that him?
Tall and thin, big brown coat.
The Silver Cloak. It worked.
Cos Wilf phoned Netty,
who phoned June,
and her sister lives
opposite Broadfell,
and she saw the police box,
and her neighbour
saw this man heading east.
Wilfred?
Have you told them who I am?
- You promised!
- No, I just said you were a doctor.
And might I say, sir,
it is an honour to see you again.
But you never said
he was a looker!
He's gorgeous, take a photo!
Not bad, eh?
- Me next!
- I'm Minnie. Minnie the Menace.
It's a long time since
I had a photo with a handsome man.
Just get off him,
leave him alone, will you?
Hush, you old misery.
Come on, Doctor. Give us a smile.
- That's it.
- Hold on...
Did it flash?
No, there's a blue light, try again.
I'm all fingers and thumbs.
- I'm really kind of busy, y'know?
- Oh, it won't take a tick.
Keep smiling.
Is that your HAND, Minnie?!
Good boy.
Come on, then.
Here we are, hurry up.
Bye. You behave, bye.
Over here, come on.
What's so special about this place?
We passed 15 cafes on the way.
Yeah. Afternoon.
Oh, we had some good times,
didn't we, though?
All those Atmos things.
And planets in the sky.
And me with that paint gun, and...
I keep seeing things, Doctor, I...
This face. At night.
Who are you?
I'm Wilfred Mott.
No, people have waited
hundreds of years to find me
and then you manage it in a few hours.
Well, I'm just lucky, I s'pose.
No, we keep on meeting, Wilf.
Over and over again. Like
something's still connecting us.
What's so important about me?
Exactly. Why you?
I'm going to die.
Well, so am I, one day.
- Don't you dare.
- All right, I'll try not to.
But I was told.
"He will knock four times."
That was the prophecy.
Knock four times, and then...
But I thought when I saw you before,
you said
your people could
change, like, your whole body.
I can still die.
If I'm killed before regeneration,
then I'm dead.
Even then.
Even if I change,
it feels like dying.
Everything I am dies.
Some new man
goes sauntering away...
And I'm dead.
What?
I'm sorry. But I had to.
Look, can't you make her better?
Stop it.
No, but you're so clever.
Can't you bring her memory back?
Just go to her now, go on,
just run across the street,
go up and say hello.
If she ever remembers me,
her mind will burn,
and she will die.
Don't you touch this car!
- She's not changed.
- Nah.
Oh, there he is...
Shaun Temple.
They're engaged.
Getting married in the spring.
- Another wedding.
- Yeah.
Hold on, she's not gonna be called
Noble-Temple?
- Sounds like a tourist spot.
- No, it's Temple-Noble.
Right.
Is she happy,
is he nice?
Yeah, he's sweet enough,
he's a bit of a dreamer.
Mind you, he's on minimum wage,
she's earning tuppence, so all they
can afford is a tiny little flat.
And then sometimes I see
this look on her face,
like she's so sad.
But she can't remember why.
She's got him.
She's making do.
Aren't we all?
Yeah, how about you?
- Who've you got, now?
- No-one.
Travelling alone.
I thought it was better.
But I did some things.
It went wrong,
I need...
My word.
Merry Christmas.
Yeah, and you!
Look at us.
But don't you see?
You need her, Doctor.
Wouldn't she make you laugh again?
Good old Donna?
And so it came to pass that the players
took their final places,
making ready the events
that were to come.
The madman,
sat in his empire
of dust and ashes,
little knowing
of the glory he would achieve.
While his saviour
looked upon the wilderness,
in the hope of changing
his inevitable fate.
Far away,
the idiots and fools dreamt of a shining
new future.
A future now doomed to never happen.
As Earth rolled onwards into night,
the people of that world did sleep,
and shiver,
somehow knowing
that dawn would bring only one thing...
The final day.
I had estates.
Do you remember my father's land,
back home?
Pastures of red grass,
stretching far across the slopes
of Mount Perdition.
We used to run across
those fields all day,
calling up at the sky.
Look at us now.
All that eloquence.
But how many people have you killed?
I am so hungry.
Your resurrection went wrong.
That energy...
Your body's ripped open.
Now you're killing yourself.
That human Christmas out there,
they eat so much.
All that roasting meat.
Cakes and red wine.
Hot,
fat, blood, food.
Pots, plates of meat
and flesh
and grease and juice,
and baking, burnt, sticky
hot skin, hot, it's so hot!
- Stop it.
- Sliced, sliced...
- Stop it!
- It's mine, it's mine...
to eat and eat...
What if I ask you for help?
There's more at work than you and me.
Oh, yeah?
I've been told, something is returning.
And here I am!
It was something more.
But it hurts. I was told
- the end of time.
- It hurts,
Doctor, the noise...
The noise in my head, Doctor,
one, two, three, four,
stronger than ever before!
Can't you hear it?
I'm sorry.
Listen, listen, listen!
Every minute, every second,
every beat of my hearts,
there it is...
calling to me.
Please, listen
I can't hear it.
Listen.
But
that's...
What?
I heard it.
But there's no noise
there never has been,
it's just your insanity, it's the...
What is it?
What's inside your head?
It's real!
All these years,
you thought I was mad.
King of the wasteland.
But something is calling me, Doctor,
what is it, what is it,
what is it?
Don't!
Let him go!
Now then, steady on,
never too early for margaritas,
that's what I say.
I forgot to get lemons
so I used oranges instead.
- It's all fruit, same difference.
- Now that's lovely.
Look at that.
Absolutely beautiful.
"Love from Donna."
Did you keep the receipt?
Yes, I did.
Come on Gramps, you've been
a right misery ever since you got up.
Do you like it, then? The book?
Joshua Naismith,
what d'you get me this for?
I don't know.
I just saw it in the shop,
and thought of you.
It just felt like the sort of thing
you should have.
Now look at that,
that's from Charlie Morton,
isn't that rude?
If you would, Mr Danes.
I'm starving.
You've my daughter to thank for this
it's all her idea.
She heard rumours of Harold Saxon.
His disciples, his return.
It's the sort of thing
she finds rather...
- thrilling.
- And I was right.
He's back.
The very man we need, and he's here.
This is going to be wonderful.
Here are the presents.
I couldn't afford much,
but not for long,
if President Obama
ends the recession tonight! C'mere!
Keep it quiet, you lot,
it's the Queen's Speech.
Now come on, sit down, show respect.
- Merry Christmas, Mr Mott.
- Thank you. Will you behave!
Honestly, all right now. She's on.
It's our sovereign.
Events are moving, Wilfred.
Faster than we thought.
Can you see that?
Frankly, I'd tell Her Majesty,
it's time for trouser-suits.
That's not...
Only you can see.
Only you stand at the heart
of coincidence.
Why, what have I done?
You're an old soldier, sir.
Only you were too late.
The war was won and passed you by.
I did my duty.
You never killed a man.
No, I didn't.
No, I did not, no.
Don't say that like it's shameful.
The time will come...
when you must take arms.
Who are you?
Tell the Doctor nothing of this.
His life could still be saved.
So long as you tell him nothing.
I lost him.
I was unconscious. He's still on Earth,
but he's too far away.
Listen, you can't park there,
what if Donna sees it?
You're the only one,
the only connection
I can think of, you're involved
if I could work out how...
Tell me, have you seen anything,
I don't know,
anything strange, anything odd?
- Well, there was...
- What?
What is it? Tell me.
- No, it's nothing.
- Maybe something out of the blue,
connected to your life, something.
Donna was a bit strange.
She had a funny little moment,
all because of that book.
What book?
His name's Joshua Naismith.
That's the man.
I was shown him, by the Ood.
- By what?
- The Ood.
- The Ood?
- Just Ood.
It's all part
of the convergence, maybe...
maybe touching Donna's subconscious.
She's still fighting for us, even now.
The Doctor-Donna.
Dad, what are you up to?
You!
But...
- Get out of here!
- Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, but she can't see you,
what if she remembers?
Mum, where are those tweezers?
- Go!
- I'm going.
Me, too.
No, you don't!
Mum?
Gramps?
Dad.
- I'm warning you...
- See you later.
Bit old for hide and seek.
Stay right where you are!
- You can't come with me.
- Don't leaving me with her.
- Fair enough.
- Mum?
Just you listen to me.
I forbid it.
Get out of there!
Doctor, bring my father back,
right now!
Come back here!
Come back here, I said. Come back!
Are you shouting at thin air?
Possibly.
Naismith.
If I can track him down...
Right.
Bigger on the inside.
Do you like it?
I thought it'd be cleaner.
Cleaner?
I could take you back home, right now.
Listen, Doctor
if this is a time machine,
that man you're chasing,
why can't you just
pop back to yesterday and catch him?
I can't go back inside my own timeline
I have to stay relative
to the Master within the causal nexus,
- understand?
- Not a word.
- Welcome aboard.
- Thank you.
Demonstrate.
That's not from Earth.
And neither are you.
A perfect combination, don't you think?
Excuse me, sir.
If I could check the basement?
We're getting fluctuation
on the power cords.
Of course.
Miss Addams? If you could bring
the calibration statistics.
Who the hell is he?
What if he finds out?
An expert, they said,
what sort of expert,
- who is he?
- I don't know.
According to the records,
Harold Saxon was Prime Minister of this
stupid country.
I'm choking in this thing.
I'm sorry.
By the saints, that's better.
These people are so flat!
But what do we do?
We were so close,
we almost had it working.
What if this visitor
is some sort of genius?
Think about it.
We're hijacking this project,
maybe we can use him, too.
Harold Saxon,
or whatever he is,
might be exactly what we need.
The Gate was found inside a spaceship,
buried at the foot of Mount Snowdon.
It was moved to an institute
known as Torchwood,
but when Torchwood fell,
let's just say, I acquired it.
I like you.
Thank you.
You'd taste great.
Mr Danes?
The visitor will be given food.
Anyway.
The device came equipped
with its own power supply
a Nuclear Bolt.
One technician remains in charge
of the feedback, 24 hours a day.
The power feeds through to the Gate,
where it encourages some sort
of cellular regeneration.
Miss Collins was our test subject.
She carried some burns, as a result
of an accident when she was a child,
down her left side.
If you could?
The Gate mended her.
Thank you.
- But what do you want it for?
- We calculate
that if this device can be
fully repaired by your good self,
it can restore the body, forever.
Hence its given title.
The Immortality Gate.
Because that's what I want.
Not for me,
but for my daughter.
I want her never to die.
My gift to her.
She will be
immortal.
Abigail.
It means "bringer of joy".
Better get to work.
We've moved! We've really moved!
- You should stay here.
- Not bloody likely!
And don't swear. Hold on.
Just a second out of sync.
Don't want the Master
finding the TARDIS.
That book said he's a billionaire,
he's got his own private army.
Down here.
We're getting encouraging results
from the ratio-foldback.
Can you confirm?
The man's a miracle.
All the systems
are slotting back into place.
The shatterthreads have harmonised...
and the multiple overshots
have triplicated.
- Nice Gate!
- Hello.
Sorry.
Don't call security,
or I'll tell them
you're wearing a Shimmer,
I reckon anyone wearing a Shimmer
doesn't want the Shimmer to be noticed.
- I'll need a Shimmer in a first place.
- I'm sorry?
What's a Shimmer?
Shimmer.
My Lord.
She's a cactus!
Miss Addams?
Miss Addams.
If you'll just excuse me.
Now,
please don't imagine I'm a slave-driver.
We can resume work
on Boxing Day, Mr Saxon.
My name...
is the Master.
Excellent.
Excellent!
Mr Danes?
The visitor will be restrained.
What?
- But I repaired it.
- I'm not an idiot.
Don't let him anywhere near that thing.
He's got it working, but what is it?
What's working?
What are you doing here?
Shimmer!
Now tell me, quickly,
what's going on? The Master,
Harold Saxon,
Skeletor, whatever you're calling him,
what's he doing, up there?
Your reputation precedes you, sir.
I have no doubt you've laid traps.
Perhaps explosives.
A means of escape.
Or murder.
Everything you've done to the Gate
will be checked
and double-checked
before anyone stands inside.
I checked the readings,
he's done good work,
- it's operational.
- Who are you?
I met someone like you, brilliant
but he was little and red.
That's a Zocci.
We're not Zocci, we're Vinvocci.
- Completely different.
- And the Gate is Vinvocci.
We're a salvage team.
We picked up the signal
when the humans reactivated it,
and as soon as it's working,
we can transport it to the ship.
- But what does it do?
- Well, it mends,
it's a simple as that,
it's a medical device
to repair the body,
it makes people better.
There's got to be more.
Every single warning says the Master's
going to do something colossal.
So that thing's like a sickbed, yes?
- More or less.
- Well, pardon me for asking
but why is it so big?
Good question. Why's it so big?
It doesn't just mend
one person at a time.
That would be ridiculous.
It mends whole planets.
It does what?
It transmits the medical template
across the entire population.
But it's time for the broadcast.
The President's grand initiative.
You might want to see this, sir,
proof that the human race
can mend its own problems.
And now, anticipation is rising
as we go live to Washington.
Here, on Christmas Day,
the President has promised
an instant and radical solution
to the worldwide depression.
Barack Obama will lead us all
into a new age of prosperity.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the President of the United States.
I'd like to speak briefly about
the state of our economy...
Turn the Gate off, right now!
At arms!
Whatever you do,
don't let him near that device.
Like that was ever gonna happen.
Homeless, was I?
Destitute and dying?
Well, look at me now.
Deactivate it.
All of you, turn the whole thing off!
He's...
inside my head.
Get out of there!
Doctor!
Doctor, there's this face...
- What is it? What can you see?
- It's him.
I can see him!
- I see him!
- There's something wrong...
It seems to be affecting the President.
- I can't turn it off.
- That's because I locked it, idiot.
Wilfred!
Get inside, get him out.
Just need to filter the levels.
I can see again. He's gone.
Radiation shielding.
Press the button.
- What?
- I can't get out
until you press the button,
that button there.
50 seconds and counting.
To what?
You're gonna love this.
He was hiding the codes.
He's extrapolated the Gate's power,
a million times over.
But it's not affecting us.
He's set the template to human!
Hello?
- Donna?
- Where are you?
It's Mum and Shaun
- something's wrong.
- There's this face.
But wait a minute, what about you?
- Can't you see anything?
- I can see them,
that's bad enough.
Not now, Winston!
Wilfred!
Those dreams...
I can remember
that face.
There's a face.
In my head.
Wilfred.
It's everyone!
What is it? Hypnotism?
Mind control?
You're grafting your thoughts
inside them, is that it?
That's way too easy.
They're not gonna think like me.
They're gonna become me.
And,
zero!
You can't have!
What is it?
But they've changed!
Granddad,
that's like...
like the sort of thing
that happened before!
My head.
Doctor!
She's starting to remember.
What is it?
What have you done, you monster?
I'm sorry, are you talking to me?
Or to me?
Or to us?
Breaking news.
I'm everyone.
And everyone in the world is me!
I'm President.
President of the United States.
Look at me!
Financial solution.
Deleted.
The human race
was always your favourite, Doctor.
But now,
there is no human race.
There is only...
the Master race.
And so it came to pass,
on Christmas Day,
that the human race did cease to exist.
But even then,
the Master had no concept
of his greater role in events.
For this was far more
than humanity's end.
This day, was the day
upon which the whole of creation
would change forever.
This was the day...
the Time Lords returned.
For Gallifrey.
For Gallifrey!
For victory!
For the end of time itself!
This is the Doctor's final battle.
He must stand at arms.
Or lose himself and all this world.
A rhythm of four.
The heartbeat of a Time Lord.
The Master is going to kill you.
Then kill him first.
At last.
Sometimes I think
a Time Lord lives too long.
~ Bad Wolf Team ~
~ www.seriessub.com ~