Previously on Swingtown:
Office pool on who'll be the
first to bag the hot new runner.
Which trader
are you married to?
Uh, Bruce Miller.
He's one of the good ones.
- You're my teacher.
- I'm not your teacher anymore.
Corporate is forcing me
to make cutbacks at every level,
but I wish you luck
wherever you end up.
I got fired today.
Janet doesn't know.
You don't do well alone, Tom.
- Luke?!
- I can't believe it!
Tom doesn't have to know.
My wife and I are
a package deal, Luke.
Now, don't go corrupting
our Oriental friends, Rex.
You'll give the old U.S. of A
a bad reputation.
Japanese sure do have
peculiar taste in music,
don't you think?
Now how's a girl
supposed to dance to this?
Oh, I don't know.
I dig a little variety
now and then.
Spice of life, right?
So tell me,
what kind of variety are
you looking for tonight?
Hey, T-bone, pass over
that ice bucket, would you?
Oh.
I'll just make a little
run to the ice machine.
Oh, just when things
were heating up.
You hurry back, Captain.
Oh, hey, grab
that, would you?
I think the others might
be trying to find the room.
Captain Decker's room.
Y'all looking
for the party?
No, I'looking for my husband.
Trina?!
Hi, sweets.
It's Bobbi.
I gathered.
Uh, Tom just stepped out
for a teeny weeny moment.
May I give
him a message?
No, thanks.
I'll give it to him myself
when he gets home.
Okay, hon.
You take care, now.
They're saying
check the fuse box.
The fuse is fine.
It's this piece of crap
air conditioner
that's not working.
Can you send someone out?
Okay.
Thank you.
They're all backed up
because of the heat wave,
and no one's available
for two weeks.
Two weeks?
I'll call around,
see if I can get someone
else to come out.
Well, if not, I'll pick up
a new one this weekend.
God, this weather
is ridiculous.
I just got out of the shower,and
I'm already sweating like a pig.
At least you'll
smell nice.
Finally opened the Paco Rabane
I gave you last Christmas.
It's a defensive measure.
I'm on the trading floor,
bumping up against
50 sweaty guys all day.
Poor Melinda.
I hope you've been
keeping an eye out for her.
Uh, yeah,
as a matter of fact.
We've been meeting
before the bell
so I can teach her
how to work the market.
Really? That's
nice of you.
Well, it's no big deal.
You know, she wants
to step up, asked for my help.
A woman trader--
that's rare, isn't it?
Well, if any girl's
got a shot, it's Melinda.
You know,
she's smart, tough.
Pretty, too.
Well, yeah,
that's not gonna hurt her.
You know,she could have a bright future
if she plays her cards right.
One of the good ones.
Huh?
That's what she said
about you
at the benefit last week.
I'm just trying
to help the kid out.
Man, I am sweating
right through this thing.
I got to change
my shirt.
May I have your attention, please?
Where you heading?
To pick up the wallpaper
that I ordered.
Thought I'd get started
on the living room.
It's gonna be
105 degrees.
Why don't we just hire
a couple of guys to do it?
Because I want
to do it myself.
Do you even know how?
The only way
to learn is to do it.
Suit yourself, but I'm on record
as saying you're crazy.
Hey, there, you two.
Hey, Rog.
- Hot enough for you?
- Uh, Susan,
I'm headed over
to Marshall Fields to cool off
and, uh, pick up Roger
some new work shirts.
Oh, I got plenty of shirts.
New job deserves a new look.
Roger got a promotion.
- You don't say?
- Congrats, buddy!
It's not that big a deal.
Don't be so modest.
He marched right
into Mr. Stone's office
and demanded more money.
And got it.
It's pretty gutsy
in this economy.
I'd have shot you down.
So, Susan, what do you say--
you want to carpool to the mall?
Actually,I have some things I have
to take care of around the house,
but I'll take a rain check.
- All right.
- Come on, Rog.
- See you tonight.
- Bye.
I am so proud of him.
Things are finally
looking up.
Who knows?
Maybe we'll be neighbors
again soon.
Nothing would
make me happier.
www.1000fr.com presents
Sync:FRM@Dwight
Swingtown Season1
Episode07
Your breakfast, sir.
Now what you want to do is keep
an eye out for repeating trends.
Well-structured companies tend
to perform well over time.
- And bad ones?
- Uh, they trend down.
Same applies to people, I guess.
Yeah,and I'd say stock in
Melinda,Inc. is on a steady rise.
Maybe the guys will start
another office pool over me.
Oh, they're all morons.
So, what's your story?
How'd a nice guy
like Bruce Miller end up
in a racket like this?
I got married when I
was still just a kid.
All I had was a diploma
and a job pumping gas.
Everybody thought I'd do
that the rest of my life.
It's funny. My mom always said
I'd end up with that guy.
How'd you turn it around?
Well, I had this one regular
at the gas station.
He drove this-this
cherried-out Caddy.
He used to tip me five bucks
every time he filled up.
One day, we
got to talking,
and he told me he was
a top dog at the Merc.
So next time he came in,
I pulled out all these fives
I'd been saving,
and I asked him to invest it
in his favorite stock.
And he told me he'd
do me one better,
and he hired me as a
runner on the exchange.
You know,I learned the most valuable
lesson right there in that day.
What's that?
It's all about relationships.
Between people,
numbers, the news.
All you got to do is figure out
how all the pieces are connected.
On the trading floor.
And in life.
Uh, the bell
goes off in 20.
Think you're ready?
- Let's do it.
- Great.
Why are you dressed
like a rodeo clown?
I'm hanging wallpaper.
It's messy.
You have no idea
what you're doing, do you?
Nope.
Okay.
Good luck.
Laurie?
Congratulations.
You must have really impressed
your philosophy teacher
with your oral report
last week.
Your summer school
grades came in.
All As.
I'm really proud of you.
Thanks.
Off to the beach?
Softball, actually.
With who?
Logan?
Logan's ancient history.
Oh.
Someone else special, then?
Yeah... I think...
maybe.
You're-You're not going
to tell me who?
I don't want to jinx it.
Fair enough.
Whoever it is,
have a good time.
You worked really hard
all summer.
You deserve to get out there
and enjoy what's left of it.
That my girl?
Hey.
How was the trip?
Pretty much the old
in and out.
Chicago, Tokyo,
Tokyo, Chicago.
Where have
you been?
I was a little worried
about you.
I went down to the lake,
took some shots of sun came up
Decided to stay a while.
Oh, your old Nikon.
You got the itch again, huh?
Yeah.After dusting off those old slides
with Luke last week.
Need something to keep me
occupied while you were gone.
A problem you
and I don't seem to share.
What is that
supposed to mean?
Hi.
Oh, looks like we're both
sliding into some old patterns.
O'Hare was 100 degrees,
so I invited the
crew over for a dip.
I didn't think
you'd mind.
Well, would have been nice
if you'd checked in first.
Or do we not
do that anymore?
I called when we landed.
What's going on?
Hmm. I rang your room
last night.
Bobbi answered.
Now she's in my house...
in a bikini.
All right, I
slipped a little.
You slept with her,
didn't you?
Hey, in my defense,
Bobbi's on the list,
and very hard
to resist.
Remember that
layover in Dallas?
That was five years ago.
We were all
on the same crew then.
This is exactly
what I was worried about.
Oh, you can't seriously tell
me you're jealous of Bobbi.
You don't get to tell me
how I feel right now.
Uh, I'm sorry.
If you want, I will
ask her to leave.
No, don't.
You want to have a pool party?
Let's have a pool party.
Nice hit.
Laurie, you made it.
What can I say?
I'm a sucker for a guy
in a baseball uniform.
So why aren't
you in one?
Uh, because
this is softball.
Disappointing.
Well, I'm sorry.
How can I redeem myself?
You might have to hit
a homerun next at bat.
Or at least a double.
Double? I think
I can manage that.
Game's just
getting started here.
Safe
Thompson residence.
This is she.
What kind of problem?
Well, that's impossible.
Yeah, I'll call our banker.
I'm sure this is all
just a big misunderstanding.
Okay,
bye-bye.
Uh, hello,
Mr. Talbott?
Janet Thompson.
Well, not so good, I'm afraid.
Uh, I just received a most
upsetting phone call from Marshall Fields.
Apparently, someone at your bank,
uh,neglected to clear my check.
I don't understand.
My husband should've made a deposit
on Friday, same as always.
I see.
No, of course, I'll-I'll speak
to him right away.
Thank you, bye-bye.
- Roger?
- Hey, Susan.
I think we need to talk.
You're looking good, Rex.
Back at you, Trina.
That a vintage SLR
you got there?
- You're a shutterbug?
- Amateur.
My mom used to freelance
for National Geographic
while I was growing up.
I never knew that.
Yeah, yeah, she was
a real trailblazer.
She used to take me
wither everywhere.
Iceland, the Congo...
It's why I
became a pilot.
Always looking for the
next great escape.
Huh.
Keeps life interesting.
Sure does.
Pour me something tall and cool.
Here you go.
Thank you,captain
Trouble in paradise?
Oh, well, I think you
know the answer to that.
Guess I should've told you Trina
called last night, huh?
Yeah, but it's not your fault--
I'm the one that messed up.
I just assumed you and Trina
still have an open relationship
We do
Maybe I just don't understand
y'all's rules.
And right now,
you're not the only one.
It's been five days, Roger.
You're not being fair
to Janet.
I know.
Then, why haven't you
told her?
Well,I had an old friend pull some strings,
got me an interview over at All-State.
That's where I was headed
this morning.
Thought if I could
get a job lined up,
maybe it'd soften
the blow a little.
They didn't offer you the job?
I'm not even sure I'd want it
if they had.
I mean, it's the same old thing
I was doing,
just less money,
at a stuffier company.
Why don't you tell Janet
that-that you're looking
for something
more personally satisfying?
Janet would get that.
I don't think so.
I mean, ever since
you moved away
she's had this need to
keep up with the Jones.
That's ridiculous.
That's easy for you to say.
You're the Jones.
So what are you gonna do,
you're gonna let her just...
drop you at the train station
every morning
and pretend to go to work until
they come and take your house away?
That's not a very good plan,
is it?
Janet is not as fragile
as you think.
She just might surprise you.
Can I use your phone?
It's right there.
Doesn't look like she's there
But...
while I'm coming clean,
I think you should know
there is another reason why I walked
all the way over here
to see you
in this heat.
What's that?
Well, I could've sworn you guys
had air-conditioning.
There's a window unit upstairs,
but it's broken.
Want me
to take a look at it?
I'm kind of handy that way.
You're just procrastinating
talking to Janet, aren't you?
Maybe. Yeah, a little.
Okay, but since she's not home,
I might as well make myself
useful somewhere.
Come on.
So, how many innings do they
play in 16-inch softball?
Uh, full nine.
I thought maybe since the ball
was twice as big,
they'd make the game
half as long.
Are you bored already?
'Cause I could fake
a sprained ankle, and...
we could go to the
Art Institute, if you want.
I'm fine.
Hey, Stephens.
Want a beer?
Um, no, I'm all right,
thank you.
- Hey, Doug!
- Yeah, go play, Stephens.
We'll take care
of your girlfriend for you.
Laurie,
this is Liz.
Do not listen to a word
she has to say, all right?
Probably
good advice.
So, you're the
new girl, huh?
Is that what he told you?
When it comes to his love life,
Doug's not much of a talker.
If you want to talk governing
principles of existence,
you can't get
him to shut up.
I'm sure you've seen his massive
collection of books and essays.
Actually, I haven't been
to his apartment yet.
It's practically
a library.
So, I'm gonna guess
you two met at school.
Why is that?
Doug only goes for smart girls.
Grad or
undergrad?
Um... under.
- Nice catch, Doug.
- Do you want to grab a seat?
Sure.
I'm so sorry,
Mrs.Thompson.
Mr. Stone is in a
budget meeting.
It might go a while.
You can't just tell a person
her husband's been fired
without some sort
of explanation.
I have no idea
where Roger is,
and I am not leaving here
until I get some answers.
Let Mr. Stone know I'll wait
for him until he is available.
I'm afraid you
can't do that.
My husband has worked
for this company for 12 years.
Was he not punctual?
Did-did he not dress
well enough?
No, Roger
was a very good salesman.
Well, perhaps there
was some kind of scandal, then.
No, of course not.
People don't just get fired
for no reason.
Surely, you must have some idea.
Mr. Stone was forced to cut back half
the department in the last six months.
As far as I know, Roger
was laid off, plain and simple.
Then, why wouldn't he
just tell me that?
Don't you think that's a question
for your husband to answer?
Evidently not.
Thank you, Doreen.
Good luck, Mrs. Thompson.
I'm sure Roger
will land on his feet.
You always close a good day
with a smooth single malt.
What about
the bad days?
Try three or four.
Uh, two Glenlivets, neat.
You were great this afternoon.
Kept a cool head all
the way to close.
So, what was the biggest lesson
of today?
Always keep your antennae up.
Read the right players,
you'll read the market.
So, who'd you have your eye on
in the pit?
You, like everybody else.
Okay.
Who was I watching?
Rattigan.
Makes the market
for United Airlines.
Exactly.
Guess what?
I'm still
watching him.
Table by the wall, gold jacket.
Who's that with him?
Malloy, Boeing specialist
for Waterhouse.
What do you think,
happy accident?
Think they're making a play?
Bingo.
The question is,
what kind of play?
Doesn't matter.
Tomorrow at the open,
we'll watch both stocks.
If either one breaks up
or down,
we'll see it first
and catch the wave.
It's always better
to be lucky than smart...
but it is best to be both.
Hey, kids, getting a
little poker game going.
Interested?
Yeah, sure, Mareno.
Deal us in.
No.
- Go ahead and sit down.
- Over here?
- Yeah.
- Okay, just anywhere?
Well, back against the thing,
I think, would be nice.
Okay, now behave.
Here's your problem.
Dirty thermostat--
can't connect to the compressor.
Okay, how did you know that?
I spent a year at UIC--
pre-engineering.
Hold on, you...
you went to college?
Don't act so surprised.
No, I...
You never mentioned it before.
It was before I knew Janet.
Anyway,I never finished,so it's not
a whole lot to crow about.
Okay.
Here we go.
What happened?
Is it a fuse?
I don't know,
might be a transformer.
Sometimes they'll blow
from too much strain.
The phone's
still working.
- Hello?
- Hi, Susan.
Hi, Bruce.
The power's out down here.
Yeah, the power's out here, too.
Well, it might be a while before
the trains start running again.
Uh, you... do you want me
to come get you?
No, no.
Yeah,if it's not back on in
a few hours,I'll just grab a cab.
You sure?
- Yeah, I'll see you at home.
- Okay.
The power's out downtown, too.
Something must've tripped
the whole grid.
Lots of cars at the Deckers.
Maybe Tom and Trina
are having a pool party.
You're wasting your time, Tom,
power's out.
- Hey.
Hey, listen, Rex,
you, uh, mind if I borrow
my wife for minute?
Only if you bring her back.
I'll be back.
What's up?
I was just going
to ask you the same thing.
I'm just enjoying
our guests.
Don't forget
you invited him.
Look, I know
I messed up with Bobbi,
but that doesn't bring Rex
into the mix.
- Not yet.
- No, not ever.
I fly a plane with the guy.
Oh, that's rich, Tom.
So you can sleep with your
co-workers but I can't?
Or are we making up
the rules as we go now?
Why are you making
such a big deal out of this?
I don't remember losing my cool
when you were playing house
with your high school
boyfriend last week.
That's because I
cleared it with you.
Open and honest at all
times-- that's how it works.
That's why it works.
Okay... we're being honest here.
I wasn't exactly crazy
about you sleeping with the guy.
Well, then you should
have pulled the plug.
I asked you
point blank.
You could have said
no at any time,
which is also what you
should have told Bobbi.
God,could you give it
a rest already, huh?
I made one mistake.
Well, maybe I want
to make one, too.
Or should we both just agree
not to ball your crew entirely?
Hey, guys.
What are you two doing
here... together?
Roger stopped by
the house to, uh...
Fix the air-conditioning.
Uh... when the power went out,
we saw all the cars and...
heard you in
the pool, and--
Oh, I should have called
first, shouldn't I?
Oh, no,
don't be ridiculous.
You're always
welcome here.
You, too, Roger.
You're sure we're
not intruding?
Oh, on the contrary.
The party just started getting
interesting, didn't it, honey?
Tom, will you dig up a
pair of shorts for Roger?
There must be one in his size
around here somewhere.
I'm not going to stay long.
Oh, well.
If you're staying at all,
there's only one other option.
It's way too hot out here
for a business suit.
Come on, Rog, see if we can
dig up something for you.
Your husband's yummy.
Oh, he's, he's
not my husband.
Then he's available?
No, he's not that either.
I'm down a hundred, Bruce.
- He's bluffing.
- Your call, doll.
It's going to cost you
to see what I got.
Call him.
I'll call.
Show 'em.
All right.
Jacks and tens.
- Three fives.
- Whoa!
Read 'em and weep, Mareno.
- That's it, I'm out.
- Where's everybody going?
- She's just warming up, man.
- Too bad, Moreno.
Take half.
I would have folded like
a tent without you.
No,keep it, consider
it a bonus.
Then, next round's on me.
Won't say no to that.
Careful, there, boy-o.
You're playing with fire.
Beautiful.
Trina, are you okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
You sure?
You and Tom seem
out of sync.
Actually, we're in
a full-on fight.
What happened?
Tom had sex
with someone in Tokyo.
Yeah, that
someone, actually.
I called his hotel,
she answered.
Th-That's...cheating,
isn't it?
We'll work through it.
So where's Bruce?
Stuck downtown.
But Roger isn't?
Roger... took
the day off.
Janet doesn't know
he's here, does she?
Not exactly.
Maybe honesty's overrated.
Maybe ignorance is bliss.
Well,no wonder Janet keeps Roger
under lock and key.
Oh, I'm gonna
need more film.
Coming in?
Water's perfect.
Sure.
It's why we came, right?
- Whoo!
- Hey, batta, batta.
All right,that's enough
out of the peanut gallery.
Come on, this is
serious business here.
Oh, Nietzsche
would be so proud.
Not to be dense, but if
you don't become a teacher,
what do you do with a
master's in philosophy?
write a book.
Apply to law school.
Smoke a ton of weed
and collect unemployment.
You ever want to teach?
Sure.
I'd glly push Doug do a flight of
stairs for his gig at Lakeview High.
Lucky for him,
summer school's over.
They just offered him a
full-time position in the fall.
To be faculty?
It's his dream job--
a chance to have a positive impact
on the future thinkers of America.
And the weird thing is he hasn't
given them an answer yet.
- Did he say why?
- Nope.
Like I said before,
Doug's not much of a talker,
but he's definitely stalling
for some reason.
Home run!
Whoo...!
I think I'm done
with all this sun.
Might go cool off in the
Deckers' basement a while
if y'all want
to find me.
So this is what I missed
on the Fourth of July.
And the '60s.
I think I can see
why you and Bruce went for it.
We got caught
up in a moment.
Truth is...
we hadn't...
connected in that way
in a long time.
I read somewhere
that falling in love happens
when someone sees you
like you see yourself.
How do you see
yourself, Roger?
Ah, well, I don't even...
know anymore.
I'll tell you
how I see you.
Loyal.
Caring.
Smart.
Janet sees
that, too.
I'd bet my
life on it.
Wow, you, uh,
you got some sun today.
- Did I?
- Yeah.
Does that hurt?
Not too bad.
Well, I better, I better go home
and face the music.
Janet would have a stroke if
she knew I spent the day here.
Maybe you should
leave that part out.
Yeah, I think
you're right.
The lake light's amazing.
I bet you got some
good snaps today.
I hope so.
I'm kind of rusty.
It'll come back fast.
I'd love to see
your darkroom.
No offense, Rex,
but even my husband
doesn't get to see that.
Then how about
your playroom?
I'm not sure I'm in the mood
to play right now.
- If you change your mind...
- I know where to find you.
Thanks, folks.
Good night.
Uh, uh...
Time to go, I guess.
- Bruce...
- Yeah?
All day you've been telling me
to keep my antennae up,
watch for connections.
Can't you see
what's right in front of you?
I... I have a wife, Melinda.
And I have an apartment,
right around the corner.
Wow.
This take you
all day?
I... took a few breaks.
What do you think?
Looks good.
Uh... I'm-I'm sorry
I'm home so late.
I- I threw back a few
with the guys after work.
Kind of lost
track of time.
You want something to eat?
No. I...
I grabbed a burger.
How did Melinda do today?
Good.
She's a natural.
I'm glad it's working out.
Um...
I'm going to...
grab a shower.
Long day,you know?
I don't suppose you found
someone to fix the AC?
I did, actually.
It had a bad, um,
connection or something.
It's as good as new now.
Great.
- If the power were on,that is.
- Right.
I'll... see you up there.
Are you hungry?
We could stop at that
all-night Chinese place.
Probably not a good idea
in a power outage.
Right.
Hey, Doug...
Yes, Laurie?
You should take
the job at Lakeview.
You heard, huh?
Why haven't you
said "yes" yet?
Hmm... just thinking
about it, I guess.
Liz told me it's
your dream job.
I don't know.I think...the future
will take care of itself.
I'm just trying to live life
in the moment right now.
Practice what I preach.
And in the fall?
Fall's... a long way off.
So I was thinking...
...maybe tonight could be the night
we go back to your place.
I don't know. I, uh...
I just... I like where
we are right now.
You still want to take it slow.
Slow and easy.
Everybody gone?
Well, there's a...
few diehards downstairs.
Rex is there.
You didn't go with him.
Too easy.
Might've been fun...
but it wouldn't
have helped.
Would you have told me
if I hadn't caught you?
Honestly?
I don't know.
I think we need to revisit
the rules...
and be exclusive
for a while.
Is that what you want?
What I want is... this.
I'm tired of the ocean
between us.
Me, too.
So, it'll be just
you and me
until we figure this out.
Yeah.
I'm going to stay here for
a while, if you don't mind.
Sure.
Well, look what
the cat dragged in.
I have something to tell you,
Janet.
That you got fired?
I bounced a check today.
I've never done that
in my life.
The bank said you didn't make
a deposit last week.
So I called your office...
I found out from a secretary.
I'm so sorry, Janet.
I wanted to tell you,
but I thought if I could...
find another job first--
something better--
it might...
make it easier.
It's not about a job...
Roger, it...
I'm your wife.
We took vows--
in sicknessand in health,
for richer or poorer.
Did you think
you couldn't trust me?
Did you...
That I wouldn't get it?
I can't sell insurance
anymore, Janet.
I need more.
I want more.
From you,
from myself.
I don't even know
what that is yet.
You got it.
What?
I said...
you got it.
You are my husband,
and I love you...
and whatever you need,
that's what I want for you.
Now go outside and fire up
the grill.
T- bones?
I thought you were saving these
for a special occasion.
Well, this food won't keep
overnight.
Might as well stay up
and cook it all.
I'll work this out, Janet.
- I promise.
- I know.
Now get going;
I haven't eaten a thing all day.
welcome to www.1000fr.com