Previously on Kyle XY.
How are you not burned?
I... I don't know.
I don't want anyone to have
a reason to take me away.
No one else needs to know
that you're different.
I feel hurt and angry,
and if you want to break up,
- you're going to have to say it.
- I wanna break up.
Doesn't matter anyway.
I've already erased you. Never happened.
What if I just wanna be normal?
I'm not gonna let you ruin
what we're trying to do!
I don't wanna do it anymore.
Now that's a well-balanced meal.
What the... This is a guys bathroom.
Relax. I have brothers.
At least I'm in the right bathroom,
Miss... whatever your name is.
Andy Jensen.
Tonight's mine and Charlie's
two-year anniversary.
We've been through so much,
he's been so patient.
I feel like I'm ready.
You're not gonna like this,
but I think there's something
you should know about Amanda.
What's going on?
It's a really stupid joke.
I slept with him.
This is what you wanted to tell me?
You didn't think I wanted
to hear it from you? You were wrong.
Get her into that family's life.
Destabilizing
the boy's support structure will
make him more vulnerable,
receptive to her.
I'm ready.
Life is made up of routines.
For as long as I lived with the Tragers,
my routine had been simple...
until now.
I wanted to explore
and develop my potential,
which meant strengthening
my mind and body
so I could use my abilities
without harming myself.
But I had to do it in secret.
The early morning and after-school
hours were the only times
- I could meet with Tom Foss.
- Faster, faster. Pick it up.
I was the athlete in training.
I didn't come here to watch you walk it.
Pick it up, pick it up, pick it up.
- Better.
- And he was my coach.
Faster!
While I was finishing
my morning routine,
the family was just starting theirs.
I had to get home
before they knew I was gone.
Lori! Let's go!
Kyle?
Breakfast!
But life is far from a perfect science.
Statistically speaking,
we're all bound to slip up.
Good morning.
Breakfast ready?
You okay?
- Just hungry.
- Then come eat.
Be there in a minute.
This was my life, my routine,
and making it work was going to be
a lot harder than I thought.
- Transcript : swsub.com -
- Projet-SG.net | SeriesSub.com -
Season 2 Episode 4
- Balancing Act -
Is Josh still asleep?
You're kidding, right?
Stephen took him to take his driver's
test this morning.The first appointment.
That's right. I forgot.
How? He hasn't shut up
about it all week.
Hey, how'd it go?
You totally bombed, didn't you?
If by "bombed" you mean a direct hit,
as in I nailed it...
Did you pass?
Yes, I passed.
In fact, the instructor said I was
the best she'd ever tested.
- He was very impressive.
- Aw, way to go, Josh.
- Thanks.
- Let me see that.
God, that's frightening.
I'll get it.
You do realize
what this means, don't you?
You can drive.
Yes, my obvious friend, that is true.
But more importantly,
Dad gets to make good on his promise
of buying me a new car.
Oh, great. You remembered that.
Dad, it's for you.
A car.
That's a pretty big birthday present.
It sure is.
That's us. Soon,
we'll be the ones picking people up.
And after work,
I wanna go scope out some dealerships.
- Are you in?
- Absolutely.
For Dad.
Some light reading.
Okay.
Have a good day, guys.
Stephen, what is it?
That was the office.
The company was sold this morning.
Sold? I didn't know it was for sale.
Neither did I.
Some big conglomerate snatched us up.
Well, what does this mean?
It means...
I just lost my job.
Hi, Amanda.
I don't want to talk to you.
It's ok, I'll talk to you.
I mean I don't want you
to talk to me, either.
- I just wanted...
- You're still talking.
A little service here.
Hang on a sec.
You must just rake in the tips.
The extra 20 cents isn't worth it.
Fantasizing about your dream car?
Just narrowing down my choices.
You're actually getting a car?
It was my birthday this week,
and it's all systems go from my parents
and the state of Washington.
It's incredible who they let
behind the wheel these days.
Don't worry.
I brake for minors.
Did you clear things up with Amanda?
Didn't get a chance.
I saw you talking to her.
No talking allowed.
She'll get over it,
just give her a little real estate.
You know, give her some space.
Is space what you wanted from Declan?
What I want from Declan
is an explanation.
Or a distraction.
I need to do something
to get him off my mind.
How about something from here?
I'm not really
the "activity board" type.
I mean, have you seen the people
who post these flyers?
Totally hideous.
The guitar, on the other hand,
is a very sexy instrument.
What's the latest?
Everybody's still in shock.
Not even a hint this might happen?
I thought things were going great.
I mean, I was expecting
a big bonus at the end of the year,
but now I'm looking for a job.
You'll find something.
Well, hon, at my level,
jobs aren't easy to come by.
Everything else is a big cut in pay.
I got a lot of good contacts out there.
I'll put the word out right away.
We should tell the kids.
No. There's no point in worrying them.
Let me line something up first.
What are you doing?
- Giving you space?
- No, you're staring at me.
I just want to say one thing.
You may want to say it,
but I'm not ready to hear it.
When are you looking for this...
offensive and irresponsible
gas-guzzling heap?
Right after my shift, with Kyle.
Looks like you're flying solo.
There goes your wingman.
What are we doing?
Finding equipment.
- For what?
- Your next challenge.
Balance,
coordination,
and weights.
You had me run 7,642 steps this week.
Now I'm gonna be lifting cement?
Baylin's body gave out because
it couldn't keep up with his mind.
Baylin's body failed internally.
Weight training won't stop that
from happening to me.
Mental and physical strength
are connected.
Look, I don't mind doing the work,
but do you even have a plan?
We should look at Baylin's journals.
- He may knew a better way.
- I saw his journals.
It's formulas, equations
you can learn that yourself.
But this kind of conditioning,
I can teach you.
- What else do we need?
- Grab that.
That's right.
Inside.
Looking for something?
The guitar Dad got me.
Have you seen it?
Well, I thing we sold it
at the garage sale, which,
if I remember correctly, you told me to.
Oh, yeah. Crap.
Well, if you wanna play,
I'm sure you can borrow your dad's.
I guess.
Did you ever feel like
you're not interesting?
Like you hope people
look at you and say,
"Hey, that Lori Trager,
she's really good at...
whatever."
Everything I ever tried to be good at
is in this closet.
And most of it is
in the original wrapping.
Why do I get the feeling
this sudden interest in guitar
has something to do with Declan.
Because you're a super psychologist?
- Have you tried talking to him?
- Yes!
Did you try "warm and fuzzy" or
go straight for "agro-crazy teen girl?"
I'll take "agro-crazy" for a thousand.
I just want to know
what happened with us.
Then really talk to him.
You might not like what you hear, but
you can get some closure and move on.
How would girls survive
without a mom like you?
They get by.
Have you seen Kyle?
I'm supposed to bring him
to buy Josh a present.
I saw him rush out after school,
but I don't know where he was going.
I love you.
Two thousand...
four hundred...
and one.
Square it.
5 million, 10 hundred...
You lost focus!
- I was trying.
- Well, try harder.
An ordinary mind can convince
the body to withstand the most
extreme conditions.
You should be able to handle more.
Like carrying 200 pounds
while doing a math drill?
- I know what I'm doing.
- Except you're not the one doing it.
I've done a lot worse.
What do you mean?
I was in a recon extraction
unit in the service.
What's that?
That is "military speak"
for rescue and torture.
Which one were you trained for?
We're done.
After I leave,
do you just stay here?
It must get lonely.
In your old apartment, I saw a picture.
A woman and a little girl.
Are they your family?
They were.
You're not together anymore.
They were killed by a drunk driver.
Look, you should go.
They'll be looking for you.
You know, if you ever need anything...
You're here all alone,
and this neighborhood seems kind of...
Don't worry about it.
I'm just saying if you're ever
in trouble, you can call me.
Okay, don't call me.
Text message.
Three stars.
All right?
Go home.
You're late.
- I'm sorry.
- Again?
I lost track of time.
Kyle, you know we have
rules about curfew.
If you're gonna break them,
I expect a phone call.
You're right.
I didn't mean to worry you.
I was putting away some laundry.
I found this in your room.
From the fire.
I don't think you should
leave it lying around.
I'll get rid of it.
Well...
good night.
Night.
Hello?
Who is this?
Notice the way she struts?
You'd need something
sleek and sexy to get her.
A luxury import,
definitely.
Pickup truck.
And her?
Miss Perky?
Convertible.
Goth girl.
Batmobile.
Please, challenge me.
Okay.
- What about you?
- Me?
- A hearse.
- You are sick.
I'm so sorry.
It's been one of those days.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, fine.
- Your jacket isn't.
- Don't worry about it.
I was just so focused on my phone.
Please let me pay to have that cleaned.
Oh, no, really, it's not...
I'm sorry. Do I know you?
I... I don't think so.
Have you ever lectured
at U.W. in child development, like,
two or three years ago?
Actually, I speak there fairly often.
I knew I recognized you.
I was finishing grad school.
It's Trager, right? Nicole?
- I can't believe you remember.
- Oh, you were so great.
Okay, now I'm definitely
paying for the cleaning.
- I'm Emily. Hi.
- Hi.
You know, I have to run, but please
let me know when you get the bill.
I insist on reimbursing you.
- You're very kind.
- Well, call me.
I will.
Where's Josh?
- Upstairs.
- We're clear.
Put it in the fridge.
Please tell me you're not
taking him car shopping.
A car is a big responsibility.
Josh is ready.
But gas is really expensive these days.
I'm not sure he can afford the gas.
He'll be fine.
But with your recent car trouble...
you're gonna...
need a new engine.
So I'll get a new engine.
There are plenty of mechanics out there.
What if repairs
take longer than expected?
Then you'd have to borrow my car,
and my car doesn't get nearly
the mileage your car gets.
Nicole, I made a promise.
It's just... bad timing.
You know, we'll talk about this later.
Sorry you lost your job.
Cars are expensive, and...
you can't afford one for Josh
since you're out of work, and...
Nicole doesn't make as much as you.
I mean...
get as good gas mileage as your car.
Well, to tell you the truth,
I'm glad you know.
Walking around here
the last couple of days,
keeping a secret just...
it feels awful.
Must have been tough.
Yeah, but don't worry.
Everything's gonna work out.
What are you gonna tell Josh
about the car?
I'm not sure.
My dad was notorious
for breaking promises.
I don't want to be that kind of father.
You're not.
You're a great father.
What's up with that?
I'm taking lessons.
Well, see ya.
Is it so impossible
to have a conversation?
We're having one right now.
Don't do that.
You can't just blow me off.
You can't just end what we had
and move on like it didn't matter.
You erased me!
I'm sorry about that. I didn't mean it.
Look, we can't really talk here.
Why don't you come over later?
I'll be home around 4.
And if you don't show up then
I'll know there's nothing left to say.
Police are still searching for any clues
that may shed light
on the murder of a hunter
found in the woods near Victor Falls
almost a month ago.
The victim's throat was crushed.
So far police have
no motive for the killing,
and no suspects have been named.
It's Saturday.
I know.
I want you to come in.
I thought I had weekends to myself.
If you slack off for one day,
you'll stop making progress.
This isn't a game.
It's about your survival.
I'll be there.
Josh, stop hitting the horn.
The neighbors are gonna freak.
You are the neighbor. Relax.
I just wanna hear her purr.
Naughty. Let me guess.
.357 magnum, about 5,000 horsepower?
Do you have any idea
what you're talking about?
Of course.
Just the guy I was looking for.
You ready for tonight?
Tonight?
Dude, my birthday dinner at La Scala.
Killer calamari,
awesome shrimp, garlic everything.
It sounds good.
Kyle, I'm not sensing
your excitement here.
This isn't just dinner.
I get my new ride.
That's a huge lift
to both our social lives.
Dinner's at 6.
Bring your "A" game.
He's really excited about his birthday.
- About Charlie...
- Kyle.
I should have told you
what was going on.
Yeah, well, being someone's friend
isn't about what you should have done.
It's about what you do.
I know you're hurt,
but you always look
for the best in people.
Don't ever lose that.
Where the hell is he going?
I don't have time for this.
Josh's birthday dinner is tonight.
Then start climbing.
From weight training to this?
What happened?
Your anxious about something.
Is it Zzyzx?
Zzyzx is gone.
Stop the analyzing, and climb.
Hey, buddy.
You got a second?
Sure. Just getting ready
for the big night.
Josh, what happened to your room?
What do you mean?
It's clean.
I just got tired of living
in a mess all the time.
I'm impressed.
Is Kyle back?
Uh, I don't think so.
Listen, I gotta talk
to you about something.
It's like he doesn't care anymore.
The guy's been AWOL all week long.
- Has he?
- Yeah. Where have you been?
I don't know.
I guess I've been
a little AWOL myself this week.
I just wish things would go
back to the way they were.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Listen, Josh, things change.
That can be hard to accept.
But what you need to believe is that
things will work themselves out...
in the end.
About the car...
- What time is it?
- You're fine. Keep going.
You're almost there.
That's right. Keep going.
The way you've built
this wall is impossible.
Not for you.
- If I fall...
- If you fall, I've got you.
Trust me.
Again.
Do it!
Hey. I'm glad you called.
- Come on in.
- Thank you.
- Great house.
- Thanks.
So, what do I owe you?
$26.
Expensive cup of coffee.
Make yourself at home.
I'll get my purse.
Thank you.
- Okay. Here you go.
- Oh, thank you.
This was really so nice of you.
And I have to confess,
I actually had another
reason for stopping by.
My sister Jessi,
she's been having some problems,
more than just
the typical teenage things,
and I was hoping that
you might be able to sit down with her.
Oh. Well, unfortunately,
I'm not in private practice,
but I'd be happy to recommend
another therapist.
It's just...
Our parents abandoned us
when we were young,
and I was left to raise Jessi by myself.
I've just been having
a really hard time lately.
And unfortunately, there's a history of
mental illness in the family.
I just don't know where to turn anymore.
And you were just so warm.
I know that you would be
so good for Jessi.
It's just a shame that
you can't see patients on the side.
You know, I...
I think I might be able to help you.
That would be great.
It's Hollander.
Jessi's got herself a therapist.
Don't get discouraged.
The jump is too far.
You just gotta trust yourself,
believe that you can do it.
I know that you can.
Why do you think I push you so hard?
I don't wanna let you down.
It's not about that.
You just... You keep trying,
do your best.
You'll get there.
And that jump is too far...
for now.
I'll add a few holes.
You can work your way up.
Okay.
- I better go.
- Do you want a ride home?
No, thanks.
This is faster.
We should go.
Kyle's not back yet.
Where is he?
Do we ever know where he is anymore?
Let's just give him a few more minutes.
Sorry, Josh, we gotta go now,
otherwise we'll lose our reservation.
I don't care anymore.
Don't move!
Wait! You can't reach this from there.
Okay, let go. I got you.
Trust me.
I got you.
Save it. I'm tired of your excuses.
I promise I'll make it up to you.
Your promises don't mean anything.
You know, I can deal
with not getting a car,
'cause I thought
I still had my best friend.
I guess I was wrong.
We need to talk.
We know what's going on.
You do?
We understand you're still adjusting,
but being part of this family
is about trust.
Now, if you don't want
to live here with us...
Why would you think that?
You're hardly here.
You missed Josh's birthday.
And we know that you've
spoken to Mr. Taylor.
Mr. Taylor?
Your cell phone rang the other day.
The caller I.D. said it was from T.
Was he calling because
you don't want to stay?
Of course I want to stay.
I know I've been
distracted lately, but...
I never meant to give you the impression
that I didn't want to be here.
You know how committed
we are to you being part of the family.
We need to know you feel the same way.
Nothing is more important to me.
Rough night last night.
Josh is still mad at me.
He's disappointed.
Feels like all I do these days
is disappoint people.
I know that feeling.
I just wish I could have
gotten him that car.
I wish there was some way
I could make it up to him.
I had this great old junker in college.
Junker?
Yeah, this crappy old car.
I remember the day I bought it.
Well they practically
gave it to me for free.
Now that would have been
the perfect starter car for Josh.
I think I know where we can find one.
Watch your step.
Okay, now.
What is this?
It's your new car.
So what do you think?
This is...
the coolest thing I've ever seen!
It doesn't run right now,
but we're gonna fix it up.
Where'd you get it?
Well, you can thank Kyle here.
He found it.
I thought you were too busy.
Hey, this isn't just benefiting you.
It's a huge lift for both
our social lives.
Thought the three of us
could work on it.
Dad, you don't know how to fix up a car.
Well, that's true,
but Kyle just read the manual.
Here, check it out.
What song is that?
Song?
You're too kind.
It's G,
D, and C.
Beyond that, it's the great unknown.
It sounds good so far.
Thanks.
Can I try?
Knock yourself out.
Each string had a particular sound.
Like a mathematical equation,
it was just a matter
of recognizing patterns
and familiar shapes.
Finding the right formations would
translate into musical notes.
Finally,
something you're not amazing at.
I never thought I'd see that day.
Get out.
I'm just kidding.
Seriously, though, give it back.
So what's your song about?
New beginnings.
And Declan.
Mainly Declan.
I'm trying to eviscerate his name.
It's very therapeutic.
- So you guys are...
- Over?
It appears so.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Who knows what he's up to these days.
Sweet car.
It's not the greatest?
Happy birthday.
You didn't have to get me anything.
I know.
It was on sale.
I didn't know what you'd like,
but I couldn't bear myself
to buy those flaps with the
naked ladies on them.
I love these. They're awesome.
Wanna check it out?
Cool.
So what kind of girl do you think
I can get with this car?
The kind who appreciates potential.
How long has it been?
Ten years next month.
You were the drunk driver.
When you told me what happened to them,
your heart rate doubled,
and your body temperature rose.
It doesn't matter. I just...
wanna say I'm sorry.
I wanna...
thank you for coming back to help me.
You can count on me...
like I count on you.
But here's the thing.
I can tell when you're
not being truthful.
So if there's something else out there,
something you know could
bring danger into my life,
I need you to tell me.
There's nothing
to worry about right now.
Let's get back to work.
We all struggle to find
the right path to take in life.
It's not always easy
to know what that is
or where it will lead us.
In the end, it's the people in our lives
that provide us the balance
to help us make it through.
Projet-SG
SeriesSub
http://projet-sg.net
www.seriessub.com