Previously on Kyle XY...
When I knew that I would not
always be here to guide you,
I knew I'd need a way to communicate,
and more importantly...
assure you that
you would never be alone.
I wanna understand
why you think the way you do.
You don't wanna get inside my head.
It's a scary place.
I want you to read Andy's mind.
I think I like her.
You make fun of me, you put me down,
you always have to have the last word.
I thought that was...
our thing.
We have a thing?
I got a letter from
this conservatory in New York.
And I kinda got in.
- Admit it, now you're having doubts.
- I do have doubts.
- There's something I need to tell you--
- No!
I've doubts about
everything in my life...
except how I feel about you.
Madacorp sent some wicked-hot mentally
scrambled science experiment
to invade your life.
Why?
I don't know.
It's like they've been watching.
Get her into their family's life.
Destabilizing the boy's support
structure will make him more vulnerable.
Her nutcase sister is
the one who hit me.
There must be a logical explanation.
Whatever she did to Lori,
I don't think Jessi's
gonna flip out on Kyle.
I think I just read your mind.
My sister...
she shot me.
I think you should know something.
- What do you want?
- I wanna know who I really am.
Kyle, they said you--
Just believe in me.
That's what Charlie always said.
I can't stress it strongly enough,
Captain.
Jessi should be treated
as a psychiatric case...
not a criminal one.
Thank you.
I'm worried about Lori.
She's angry at...
Are you okay?
Times like this, when the professional
line blurs with the personal,
- it's...
- Difficult.
The hardest part is the guilt.
Guilt?
I'm the one who brought Jessi
into this house.
No.
You tried to help her.
Tried.
What's the matter?
My head is...
I'm fine.
You need to get some rest.
You're exhausted.
We all are.
Why?
I'm too riled up to sleep.
Therefore I don't get to sleep either?
I spent all night scheming
revenge against Jessi.
- And what did you come up with?
- Nothing good.
I need a diabolical mind in my corner.
And I'm said diabolical mind?
Exactly.
Good morning, guys.
Dad, do me a solid.
Go downstairs and throw
some black into that pot.
Not quite sure what that meant,
but we'll go with no.
How you doing, Lori?
What do you think?
I'm gonna go.
Now, I know you've been
through a lot lately,
but your tone needs adjusting.
Oh, so we're going with stern,
responsible dad now? That's rich.
I have dealt with your attitude
because I know you're angry.
I know you're confused,
you need to lash out against someone.
But don't you dare treat me
like I'm some peer
you can cut down with some snide
little comments.
I am your father. This stops now.
What are you doing?
Same thing as you.
Which is?
Pacing.
Continuous back-and-forth walking
in an effort to clear one's mind
for mental breakthrough.
I got that part.
Why are you pacing?
Why are you?
There's some seriously toxic mojo
going down in this house, and I'm
looking for a solution.
Me, too.
Well, good. 'Cause I could use some
super brain enhancement to help Lori
figure out how to get revenge on Jessi.
Jessi?
Yeah. You know?
Brown hair, green eyes, 5 foot...
11 personalities.
I don't think
you should get involved in that.
Not get involved?
Are you crazy?
She deserves whatever we dish out.
There's a lot about her
that you don't know.
Dude, are you defending her?
- No, I...
- Whatever, man.
I thought Lori could rely
on her brothers to have her back.
My life was spinning out of control.
The Fallout of my secrets had brought
trouble into the lives
of the people I loved.
And I was powerless to stop it.
Transcript: swsub.com
Subtitles: Projet-SG & SeriesSub
Season 2 Episode 12
- Lockdown -
Hils, I'm talking hostile takeover
of Jessi's reputation.
Declan, things are falling apart and
I need help figuring out what to do.
I'm coming over.
Fire up that G-Force.
I need your mind working at it's best.
Hold on.
Where's everyone going?
- I gotta go see Hillary.
- I gotta go see Andy.
And I'm meeting Declan.
I don't think anyone should leave.
Jessi's still unaccounted for, and
we don't know what her state of mind is.
Sure we do. Six ticks past psychotic.
Too much?
So... what, you're putting us
on lockdown?
Until further notice...
yes.
He survived.
Barely.
His brain function is still intact.
No residual damage.
I'd say the chair's retrieval system
performed better than expected,
and I expected a lot.
You can't put Kyle in that chair.
Actually, I can.
At best you'll get 10 percent
of his data before you fry his brain.
I'd settle for one percent.
You called?
Where's the girl, Hollander?
In the field.
In other words,
your mission remains incomplete.
I'll give the girl one more day.
But if I don't get what I want,
I'm strapping the boy into the chair.
Okay...
I've called in the Andy reinforcements.
Two diabolical minds at your disposal.
- Forget it.
- Forget it?
Has your thirst for revenge
been quenched already?
Never.
But I don't need to drag
you down with me.
I'm supposed to be your bad-ass brother,
ready to serve a beat down on command.
Go have fun with Andy.
You guys have better things to do
than get... caught up in all my drama.
Okay, but we'll just be
a room away from turning
our G-Force skills
into real-life mortal pain.
Yeah, that's sort of exactly why
I'm keeping you out of it.
Probably for the best.
Hillary.
Operation Vengeance in effect.
- I brought cookies.
- Thank God.
- Amanda.
- Is Kyle home?
I'm sorry I compared you to Charlie.
You don't need to be sorry for anything.
I'm the one who should apologize.
- It's just what I saw...
- Was confusing.
I know.
But I promise nothing
physical was going on.
I wouldn't lie to you.
I know you wouldn't.
And I do believe in you,
even if it doesn't seem like I should.
Thank you.
Maybe if you told me
why you were so drawn to her.
She's lost.
Troubled.
And you wanna help her?
This is what I get
for dating a do-gooder.
You're still mad.
This isn't what I came
over here to talk about.
What did you come over here
to talk about?
I'm leaving.
- You just got here.
- No, I mean I'm leaving town.
Leaving town?
For how long?
For the rest of the semester.
I got accepted to
a music program in New York.
I leave in two days.
Two days?
Usually, the whole
multiple-question thing is cute,
but I'm really struggling here.
Why are you strug...
You're struggling because
you're not sure if you wanna go.
It's a dream come true, but...
You're afraid you're using it
as an excuse to run away...
because you have doubts about us.
What do you think I should do?
I think it's your decision to make.
I'm just so confused.
I need to clear my head.
Don't bother with pacing.
It hasn't been working for me.
I'm gonna go play for a while.
See if I can figure it out.
Whatever you decide...
I'll be here for you.
Promise?
Promise.
Then I know it'll happen.
- Hello?
- Kyle...
Emily.
Yes.
What do you want?
Jessi needs your help.
She knows the truth about who
she really is, and she's run away.
She's in danger huh?
Yes.
You're the only one who can
bring her home safely.
I can tell when people are lying.
- I'm not lying.
- Or telling the whole truth.
You want the truth?
If you don't find Jessi,
they'll hurt my family.
- Who are they?
- You're in danger too,
Kyle. You and everyone
who matters to you.
I'm gonna ruin her reputation.
You do it right, she'll be wearing
a Sacred Heart skirt by Friday.
How you doing, Lori?
I vow to kill the next person
that asks me that.
What are you doing here?
I... came to talk to Kyle.
Oh, good. Maybe you can talk
some sense into him.
His whole "believe the best
in people" philosophy
has gotten way too close to Jessi
"spawn of the devil" Hollander.
Clearly you're not willing to give her
the benefit of the doubt.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, no, you didn't.
I just meant that it's complicated.
Oh, my God.
This thing's messy enough already
without you two going haywire.
- She beat me up!
- I know that!
Then you understand
she deserves whatever she gets.
What is happening up there?
Lori's outta control.
She's just upset.
She's more than upset.
She's acting like a 12-year-old.
What's going on between you two?
She thinks I'm having
an affair with Emily.
I think I was hoping
for a little more outrage.
It's not an outrageous assumption.
- It damn well is.
- Stephen.
I can't believe you would
even think for one minute...
No, I don't think that.
I just meant that Lori...
You're the psychologist.
Isn't the first reaction
- usually the most telling?
- Let me finish.
- Please.
- I just meant that Lori has picked up
on the dynamic you have with Emily.
She's my co-worker.
It's a little more than that.
Even I noticed it.
Real mature, Trager.
- Stephen, I'm trying to make a point.
- Which is?
There was no way I could help.
Nothing I could do.
More than anything, I wanted it to end.
a total disconnect between you and me.
And then suddenly it did.
Adam?
Is that really you?
No. It's really you.
I don't understand.
You don't need to understand what I am.
Only that I can help you.
Thank God you're here.
You do realize that I went
out of my way to pimp out
my mom's media room
for our G-Force marathon.
I'm hoping this will make up for it.
Check it out.
What do you think?
It's perfect.
Cover fire on the left flank!
Especially for our last day together.
Hey, Kyle, I made it.
Okay.
Guess I'll talk to you later.
Kyle...
you're upset because you think
all the anger
that's dividing this house
is because of you.
Madacorp obviously sent Jessi and Emily
into our lives to mess with me.
I just can't figure out why.
Well...
what do they want?
It has to be the information I took
from Zzyzx that's inside my head.
How far will they go to get it?
- I don't know.
- Yes, you do.
- Just tell me.
- I can't.
You need to slow down, Kyle...
and think.
I was able to get inside Jessi's head,
read her thoughts.
Madacorp must believe that
she can get into mine.
But she hasn't.
Not yet.
Why?
I had to get her to trust me,
let her guard down before
I was able to dig deep enough.
So then she's trying
to get you to trust her.
But all she and Emily have done
is cause chaos.
And how does that chaos make you feel?
Upset.
- Uncertain.
- Vulnerable?
It makes me feel like everything that's
important to me is gonna disappear.
When you're vulnerable,
you let your guard down.
Jessi.
No...
but it could have been.
I'm losing my mind.
Actually, you're just
beginning to find it.
Madacorp manipulated everything.
And my whole family has suffered for it.
So what does that say about Jessi?
She can't be trusted.
She's bad like everyone said.
When Kyle wakes up,
will you tell him I was here?
Right, because I'm so in the mood
to be your messenger service.
Trager...
For the love of Peter Petrelli,
will you two cut it out?
I have been a guest
at your pity party of two for months.
Wah wah, bicker bicker, boring boring.
Now, for the sake of my sanity,
and your future children,
we're putting an end to this right now.
You two need a mediation.
I'm gonna go fetch our own
resident Dr. Phil.
Ah! I don't wanna hear it
from Kyle right now.
And he's asleep.
All righty, then.
You'll have to temporarily
settle for second best.
Dr. Hils at your service.
Hils, I really don't think...
Sit!
Okay, I've had enough.
Hey,
I was about to beat you.
I'd say you already did.
No. See, your player's still alive.
I'm talking about that
little bomb you dropped earlier.
I think that was your bomb.
And if you want some advice, I'd lay off
the junk food, let your stomach settle.
Andy, quit messing around!
I'm in trouble, huh?
How could you say it's
gonna be our last day together?
What, are you, like, dying tomorrow?
How many cancer patients
do you know that die overnight?
You're doing it again.
All right, fine.
It's our last day together because
I start chemo tomorrow.
What does chemo have to do with...
It has to do with me puking,
you sympathizing, me withdrawing,
you resenting me,
me resenting your resentment,
blah blah blah.
Trust me, it's messy.
That's why I think it should
be our last day together.
So why don't we make it special, okay?
To kick things off,
I think we should
go upstairs and make out.
Pacing's not working for you.
How do you know that?
You said it.
But not to you.
That's right. You said you were me,
which means I'm talking to myself.
Your self-doubt was paralyzing you.
You needed someone to talk to.
Someone I trusted more
than my own instincts.
Someone like you.
Kinda cool, isn't it?
Okay, then.
I need help deciding
if I should go after Jessi.
You just realized she's
Madacorp's secret weapon.
Wouldn't you be playing
right into their plan?
But I can't believe that
she's a willing weapon.
Which means she's out there
lost and alone.
Why are you worried about her
after everything she's done?
Because if I don't believe in her,
no one will.
Maybe no one should.
What are you doing?
Now, you gotta be nice.
You wanna play?
Let's play.
No. No. Please.
No, let him go!
Why aren't you letting him go?
Don't! Don't kill him!
Oh, God!
- I have to go to work.
- What?
I rushed out last night
when I got the call about Kyle.
I didn't get a chance to
shut down all my systems.
I don't think it sends
a good message to the kids
about the lockdown
if you leave right now.
I am not in the mood to be lectured
about what's appropriate.
- I'm not.
- No, let me finish.
I ver betrayed the vows
I made to you when we got married.
I never cheated, I never lied,
and I never kept any secrets.
But I guess you'll either
believe that or you won't.
So why do I get the happy
family and the great life?
You mean why does she get
the short end of the stick?
- It's just a...
- Expression.
I know. You're me, remember?
Maybe she was born bad.
The same way that you were born good.
But was I?
Or would being taken in
by a loving family make me good?
She didn't have that.
There's no one that cares
enough about her to help her.
You're a do-gooder like Amanda said.
Help her.
I can't leave this house.
So don't help her.
- Stop confusing me.
- You just need to trust yourself.
That's what this is all about.
Even if I wanted to help her,
I have no idea where she is.
You should ask her.
Help me.
You're not really here.
That's true.
You look so happy.
If I had what you have,
I wouldn't come after me either.
You made a promise to be here for her.
I know.
Would you break it just to help me?
I'd help you so that we could
take down Madacorp and save my family.
Do you think that's possible?
It has to be.
I can't live like this anymore.
Then you should come find me.
But where are you?
That's for you to figure out.
You already said that,
you and I were the same.
In a way, yes.
So...
have you ever run away?
Once.
Where did you go?
Back to the beginning.
Then you know where to look.
The question is...
will you?
Are you okay?
Stay away from me.
- I'm bad.
- Are you lost?
Do you need some help?
I don't deserve help.
Sweetie,
what happened to you?
I said stay away from me!
- What are you doing here?
- Hey.
I'm sorry about earlier.
You know the situation's sensitive.
It's okay. We're all
under a lot of pressure.
Well, you being here is a good sign.
I take it Jessi made it home.
Yes.
We had a long talk.
She's got a lot to work out,
and I'm gonna get her some more help.
Oh, good.
The police are still
gonna want to talk to her.
Of course.
So what brings you
up to the fifth floor?
I was shutting down
my system from the trial run,
and I noticed the diagnostic results
have been erased.
That doesn't sound right.
The entire server's on lockdown.
I don't have any access to it.
I'm worried that it's viral,
I'm gonna check out the mainframe.
You can't go in there right now.
Ballantine's
giving a tour to a potential investor.
On Sunday?
Yeah, the human trial was so successful
that he wanted to show it off.
What? That's just the thing.
We don't know if it was
because we don't have
any access to the system.
Stephen, go home.
Worry about it tomorrow.
What's going on in there?
Nothing, just a business show-and-tell.
I'll see you tomorrow?
Sure.
You're acting weird.
I'm on top of you making out.
What's weird about it?
You're being hesitant.
Guys aren't supposed to do hesitant.
I'm not being hesitant.
Totally hesitant.
- Stop using that word.
- I'm sorry, but it's true.
Any other guy would have his hand
halfway to the promised land by now.
I'm trying to be respectful.
No,
respect is the slow, steady inching,
waiting for me to swat your hand away.
Respect is at least trying to go there.
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless you've never gone there before.
- You've never touched a boob.
- I've touched a boob.
A real one or one of those inflatable...
I've touched a boob, okay?
Just never...
Never what?
Never one that mattered.
My boobs matter?
Well, of course they matter.
Why else would I put up
with this humiliation?
Then let me help you out.
There you go.
They're all ready for ya.
Go where only a few men
have gone before.
You're not helping.
I'm serious. I want you to.
Besides, this is your
only chance, remember?
See?
That's the problem.
You're ruining it.
You said this would be our last day.
Which means that'll be
the last time I can touch
them... boobs.
And that's not cool!
Because I wanna touch them tomorrow
and the next day and
all the days after that.
So quit acting like today is it for us,
'cause I don't want it to be.
It has to be.
You're gonna have to find
someone else to feel you up...
'cause I'm not having it.
What we have here
is a failure to communicate.
Hils, I've spent a year trying
to get Declan to communicate.
- I seriously doubt...
- You say that like it is all my fault.
I don't know, Mr. Secretive and Moody.
What do you think?
You haven't exactly made it easy lately.
Good. So it's my fault
that you dumped me
for no reason and then
took up with La Femme Nikita.
This is good.
We're speaking from the heart.
Declan, I need to talk
to you for a minute.
- Gladly!
- Oh, no! No way!
We were just making progress.
We're not making progress here.
We're wasting each other's time.
So you think trying to get to the bottom
of our problems is a waste of time?
Come on, Lori! You think
this is just as stupid as I do!
I just need a minute.
What you need is to accept
your part of the responsibility
for the tragic demise
of Beachwood's best couple.
For cryin' out loud!
Seriously! I'm all in favor
for a good romance.
But the intensity of
the Kyle-Declan friendship...
we'll call it Kyclan...
clearly interfered
between the relationship
of Lori and Declan.
Kyle, what do you have
to say for yourself?
I'm sorry.
I'm not doing this.
Lori, if you wanna talk to me,
really talk, minus the circus,
then I'm here.
Until then, leave me out of it.
She's right.
You, Lori, everything that's happened
to this family is all because of me.
I need to put a stop to it.
How can I help?
Loan me your car.
I thought you couldn't leave the house.
You're going after her.
The thing I admire most
about you is your faith in people.
But I worry this time...
it's gonna be the end of you.
Does this mean
you won't give me the keys?
Thank you.
Good luck.
You're gonna need it.
Hello.
I don't know how you do it.
Do what?
Help people.
I gave it my all...
with Angst and Angstier.
I learned from Phil and Oprah,
yet everything comes up Springer.
I'm a fraud. A Faux-prah.
Well, helping people, get in touch
with what they're really feeling
is a complicated process.
I just hate all the drama.
Lori's my best friend.
I just wanna help her.
All we can ever really do
is encourage people to
talk openly about their problems.
They may not like it, but...
it's imperative to put issues
out on the table.
That's what I've been saying.
I mean, really, is honesty
that freaking difficult?
It shouldn't be, should it?
And people think I'm the dumb blonde.
I have to say, Hillary, I don't think
there's anything dumb about you.
What happened to you?
The old Tom,
he would have fought it out
till the bitter end.
Big,
strong, stoic
Tom Foss.
Survived a war, brought down Zzyzx,
then a little trip down memory lane
did him in.
All I want,
all Baylin wanted,
was to see Kyle reach his potential.
But now Ballantine's
gonna put him in the chair
and go for broke.
It's gonna make what happened to you
look like a day at the spa.
You let them beat you, Tom.
You let them break you.
And now they're gonna break Kyle.
You are the traitor!
I'll never help you!
You'll never break me.
What are you doing?
I came in here to ask
your permission to tell Stephen
about the secret we kept
from the family only to find you
sneaking out of the house?
I'm going to find Jessi.
- I wanted to tell you, but...
- But you knew I wouldn't let you go.
This is important.
More important than our trust in you?
I'm doing this for all of you.
I can fix this.
I can fix everything that's broken.
Why Jessi?
Why you? How are you two connected?
You already know the answer
to that question.
She and I are the same.
What is that supposed to mean?
I don't even know who you are.
You told me once that I never brought
anything by love into this house.
But all I ever brought was pain.
I need to make this right.
Please.
I have to go.
I had promised her I'd always be here,
just like I promised
myself I'd never put
my family at risk.
I had broken both those promises.
I'm not hungry.
Consider it a peace offering.
Considering I made them
for you in the first place,
your gesturing's a little hollow.
Don't be so cranky.
Right.
What are you pausing it for?
Go ahead. Put the final nail
in the coffin of this miserable day.
There's no rush.
I can beat you tomorrow and the next day
and all the days after that.
Really?
Really.
No more wild revenge scenarios?
Not today.
It's too exhausting.
Where's your partner in crime?
She said something about
a lost marathon and bailed.
Which just leaves us.
Lucky us.
Listen, Lori, I don't wanna be that guy,
the guy who's all locked up.
You were the one I could
always open up to.
But you never did.
I did.
Sort of.
As much as I could.
Says the guy with more baggage
than an airport carousel.
I suppose I could limit myself to
carry-on if it meant
that we could be friends again.
One of those big rolly ones you have to
scrunch and shove in the overhead?
You really want to run
this metaphor into the ground, huh?
It's what I do.
I miss this.
I miss you.
I miss you, too.
I won't be able to change overnight.
But if you can bear with me,
I can try to be a little more...
Communicative?
I suppose.
Open and honest?
About... certain things.
Warm and sunshiny?
You may wanna quit while you're ahead.
Downgraded from darts.
Things are looking up.
I guess they are.
Why did you come after me?
You need me to.
I'll betray you.
That's what they want me to do.
You don't have to do
what they want you to.
You can make your own choices.
That's what Nicole said.
Nicole's smart.
She helped me.
Now let me help you.
They'll take me back.
We're not going back.
Not until this is all over.
I want it to be over.
So do I.
There's something I want to tell you.
I want to talk to you, too.
I don't know where to begin.
Why don't we begin with me because
there's something I need to tell you.
I accused you of keeping secrets.
What I have to say goes far beyond that.
I've been keeping secrets, too.
- I discovered something about Kyle.
- Secrets about Kyle.