Previously on Kyle XY...
I got accepted to a music
program in New York.
I leave in two days.
I'll call...and text,
and I'll come back to you.
The two of you used to play
that song all the time.
She could be you.
- Third row, fourth one down.
- It's not there.
The song on the jukebox?
D4.
You didn't tell me you were coming.
No one knows. I'm surprising
my mom for her birthday.
You will not see or speak to Amanda
until she's back where
she belongs at that school.
Please. You'll have 20 bubbleheads
lined up by tomorrow.
They all have the same thing
working against them.
What's that?
None of them are you.
- Start teaching me.
- I can't.
I have plans tonight with Amanda.
Oh, Amanda. She's home?
You have no idea
how disappointed I am right now.
Your flight leaves
in less than two hours.
Thank you for letting me
know Amanda was here.
Glad I could help.
We made it very clear
you're not to see Amanda.
- You're still grounded.
- Two weeks.
Latnok?
Amanda?
I didn't get on the plane.
Tell me what happened?
I was waiting at the gate,
it was time to board the plane,
and I literally could not move.
It was like my whole body was saying,
"You can't do this.
This is wrong."
The next thing I knew,
I was running through the terminal,
jumping in a cab and
knocking on your window.
A total loss of sanity.
My mom's gonna kill me.
Maybe your mom will understand
when you explain it to her.
Key word "understand".
She's not capable of.
What am I gonna do?
I'll go get Stephen and Nicole.
No. You can't involve them.
I'm sorry I've already involved you.
Amanda, everything's gonna be okay.
Can I stay here?
- Amanda...
- Just until the morning...
Then I'll go straight home.
I'm already grounded.
No one will even know I was here.
I just need some time
to get my head together.
And somehow,
my mom won't be as scary
to deal with in the daylight.
All yours.
Thank you so much.
My luggage is probably being searched
by the terrorist watch squad
as we speak.
Can I borrow something to sleep in?
Sure.
You're being really
amazing about all of this.
I mean, I knew you were the kind of guy
who'd give the shirt off
their back to help somebody,
but this is really above and beyond.
I didn't...
I'm...
I didn't... I just... I meant...
Thank you.
What's the matter?
What do you mean?
Your cheeks are getting pinker.
Are they?
Your body temperature is climbing.
I'll get you a thinner blanket.
Sous-titre VO ::: www.shooter.cn
modifié pour www.forom.com
Traduction ::: La Team XY
Sechs, Jayson.sosweet et MiniBen314
vous présentent
Kyle XY
2x17 - Grounded
Let me sleep on the floor.
You don't like the tub?
No. I'm sorry,
I'm just trying to be polite.
How is sleeping on the floor polite?
I don't wanna take your tub from you.
I want you to have it.
Unless you don't like it.
Why wouldn't I like it?
- It's a tub.
- It's your tub, all of it.
Can you lock the door?
I don't want anyone
to catch me in here.
Asleep yet?
No.
How's the tub?
Are you comfortable?
Strangely, I am.
How's the floor?
It's too open.
No sides.
You could, if you wanted to...
I mean, there's plenty of room.
With you?
With me.
That better?
Much.
Thank you for this.
You're welcome.
I knew allowing Amanda
to spend the night
could get me in more trouble.
But how could I turn her away?
And how could doing something
so wrong feel so right?
Kyle? Is everything all right?
Everything's fine.
Your door's locked.
Is it?
What happened?
Nothing. I, uh...
I just... I just woke up.
- Hi.
- Come grab some breakfast.
- Okay.
Hanted by this photograph
And don't know why
Isn't that beautiful?
Yeah. Where did you get that?
That was with my personal things.
No, I found it on my bed.
You know, Jessi,
all you had to do
was ask for the record,
and I would have given it to you.
Why would you break into my cabinet?
What cabinet?
Come on now.
Don't lie to me, all right?
There's gonna have to be
a certain level of trust
if this thing's gonna work,
and you snooping around in my stuff
is just not gonna cut it.
I'm telling you the truth.
I found the record right here.
That song meant something to my mother.
I was hoping you'd tell me
more about her.
Now is not the time.
No, don't take that from me.
All right, just, uh...
just be careful with it.
Hanted by this photograph
And don't know why
I think Kyle mistook getting
grounded for being in prison.
There's a difference?
He locked his door this morning.
I wouldn't worry about it.
He's never locked it before.
Maybe he just wants some privacy.
Privacy?
I don't get it.
- Oh, I get it.
- People, it's breakfast.
Good morning.
Kyle. Just in time to have
a little breakfast.
Maybe you can beat the batter.
Are we having pancakes?
Or perhaps you'd like
to grill your sausage.
- Okay, Josh...
- I might vomit.
- Kyle, ignore him.
- Why?
Not even worth explaining.
Now that we're all together
enjoying our quality time...
Mandated quality time.
Whatever. You're gonna
make good use of it.
- Meaning?
- Gutters. Clean 'em out.
You and I are gonna wash
all the windows outside.
That's cruel and unusual punishment.
We cooked up a little
to-do list for you guys, too.
Bring it on.
I'll to-do the hell out of it
in exchange for the briefest
of parole periods later this evening.
Your sentence does not
include a parole option.
I'm trying to be
a responsible young adult.
I'm the sober cab to Preston's party.
Sober cab?
Designated non-drinking driver,
and if I bail, I'll ruin it
for everyone else.
Everyone else should not
be drinking at all.
Absurd request denied.
As long as the parole
board's in session,
I really need to see Andy today.
Emotional support.
She's got chemo.
Andy has chemo on tuesdays,
and I can't believe you just falsely
played the cancer card.
It was her idea.
You wanna make a plea, too?
No. I'll do my time.
Man of honor.
Or a giant suck-up.
You can start by cleaning your room.
I'll get started.
Think he's gonna go peel his banana?
This is so sweet,
but I'm too nervous to eat.
Maybe you're underestimating
your mother.
She might surprise you.
I appreciate the optimism,
but I expect bloodcurdling screams
followed by frothing at the mouth.
Well, I'm here if you need me.
I'm counting on it.
Here goes.
- Hi.
You should, uh,
keep your window closed,
unless you want Josh
to spray your whole room.
How long do you think that'll take?
In Josh time, all day.
Thanks.
Amanda, we have a problem.
No.
None of the other window's open.
Great.
So what do we do?
- Amanda?
- What about her?
I was just wondering
how she's doing in New York.
My guess is she'll be thrilled
to get a break from her mother.
No. The front door.
Amanda Bloom,
you little stowaway.
Lori?
Here you go. I left the pieces out
in the dining room.
- Armed and ready to polish.
- Make me proud.
Kyle, I need you at the computer.
Okay.
Whenever I save something,
the hard dive makes
this grinding sound,
like "wooosshh."
I'll take a look at it.
- Mrs. Trager.
- Yes.
I'm Constance Berlinger.
I'm with the department
of children services.
How can I help you?
We've received a complaint
about your ward.
Kyle? Who filed a complaint?
You know I can't tell you that.
Never mind. I can guess.
Carol Bloom?
Unbelievable.
She's angry because she thinks
Kyle interfered with Amanda.
She must have called social services.
He's no longer in the system.
Well, he was, and
if someone files a complaint
about a former ward of the state,
they're legally bound to check it out.
What was her complaint?
That Kyle's living here
without proper supervision
and being disruptive to the community.
- That's not true.
- Well, of course it isn't.
But now we need to prove it.
To that woman?
She doesn't even know us.
This is how the system works.
We just have to get through this.
Let her go through her checklist.
What kind of checklist?
Questions to make sure we're providing
a safe and healthy environment for you.
The first question,
Does the child have his own proper bed?
Great.
Well, the bigger problem is
keeping the truth about you a secret.
I'll be careful.
None of us can slip.
I know her type, very thorough.
We just have to keep
our stories straight and...
stay on our toes.
Be careful.
This woman can't find out
who you really are.
Just so I'm up to speed.
You were first called in
to treat Noah...
Kyle.
I'm a little confused.
We changed his name.
Legally, at his request.
I'd like to see those papers.
Oh, no problem. Stephen,
they're in the family file
in my office.
Could you go grab them?
Absolutely. Could I get you
something to drink?
Ice water, please.
So, you first met Kyle
at the detention center,
diagnosed him with amnesia,
and the very next day,
moved him, your new patient,
in here with your family.
There were special circumstances.
Of course there were.
I hate that some stranger
can just come in here
and decide things about us.
I know. As if we're the kinda kids
who'd smuggle in one of their
runaway girlfriends or something.
Amanda needed help.
Oh, no. You're not getting away
with the nutshell version.
What happened with you two last night?
I heard a knock on my window,
and I went over and
Amanda was out there,
- and she really needed...
- No, no, no.
Never mind, I know nothing happened.
It's you and Amanda, for god sakes.
Still, where'd she sleep?
My tub.
Where did you sleep?
You dog! And?
Okay, the real scandal is did she just
bail on her flight and come here?
Yes.
And her mother, the crypt keeper,
doesn't know.
Well, she must know by now,
assuming Amanda left and went home.
She better have.
You don't wanna get busted
harboring a fugitive
with that social worker here.
Shaken, not stirred.
Thank you.
Following the death of his parents,
you've become his permanent guardians.
Yes. We love Kyle.
Honestly,
the idea of him being disruptive
in any way is ludicrous.
Our son Josh on the other hand...
Is there a problem with
Josh's behavior?
There's no problem.
I have to hide all my porn.
She's gonna search the house?
Oh, yeah.
Social worker is basically
a fancy title for "snoop."
What's she looking for?
Weapons of mass destruction.
Guns, sex toys, drugs, booze.
Oh, no!
Relax. Dad flushed
his pot stash, remember?
I'm not worried about dad.
You have a pot stash now?
No.
I have this.
Oh! beer?
I was holding it for Preston
until his parents left town.
I'm the only one
he could trust with it.
Because I'm the most responsible.
I hate myself!
Well, we have to get rid of it.
First, you. Out.
Smuggling beer
is not gonna score you any points.
But I'm the one that
got you into this mess
in the first place.
Two little words called "peer pressure"
got me into this mess.
Go figure out a story to explain
why you have a bathtub
in your room instead of a bed.
And you...
Tap into that cunning
little brain of yours
and come up with something quick.
Tell me about his relationships
outside the family.
I assume you're referring to Amanda.
It's a very caring,
supportive relationship.
There's nothing objectionable
or inappropriate.
Amanda's mother is overreacting.
She's a little... high-strung.
Amanda, I thought you made it home.
I'm trapped.
That social worker's staked out
your living room.
I bet my mother's responsible.
It's so mortifying.
Maybe we should tell her.
What, that I never got on my plane
and hid out here
in your bedroom all night?
That would prove all the complaints
she had about you.
- So what do we do?
- Sneak me out.
Then I'll wait till she leaves
and head home.
Why wait?
Do you want that social worker around
when my mom's head explodes?
I'll move the ladder.
Look, I know you're nervous,
but when you talk
to her just be yourself.
I'm sorry to put you through this.
It's not your fault.
Carol Bloom's trying
to pin the problems
she having with Amanda on you.
Anyway, I thought I'd show off
some of your drawings.
Can I go grab a few?
I don't wanna show them.
- They're beautiful.
- They're too personal.
Oh. Well, of course.
Then you may want to
take them off your wall
before she inspects your room?
When's that happening?
I'd like to delay explaining your tub
for as long as possible,
at least until you've won her over.
- Right.
- Make sure your room is ready
in case she insists on starting there.
So get back in there and
clear out anything incriminating.
Okay. I'll try.
- What are you doing here?
- What are you?
Amanda, we need...
- What are you doing here?
- That's what I want to know.
You said when she left,
we could spend more time together.
- You did?
- Well, I...
And now she's climbing through
your bedroom window?
I asked you not to do that.
I had to see you right away.
Why?
- That's none of your business.
- Excuse me?
Why aren't you in New York?
That's none of your business!
Both of you, please!
I'm already grounded!
There a social worker
investigating my family,
and I can't let her find two girls
who aren't supposed to be here
fighting in my room!
You both have to go.
Now.
Declan?
How come I got stuck doing this part?
You hid it, you lift it.
That ladder weighs a ton.
Thank god the cavalry's here.
Your leg okay?
A little wobbly, but...
there's beer to be liberated
and damsels to be rescued, so...
I must say I'm impressed.
You coming here helping Lori out,
even though
she's still closed for business.
Jerk!
Oh, smart! Leave a bruise
with a social worker present.
Josh? I need you.
Go, go, go!
Our room's up here
with Josh and Lori's.
Kyle's got the spare one downstairs.
I'll show you around down there
after you've had a chance
to talk to everybody.
Hello, mother.
What can I do for you?
This is Mrs. Berlinger.
She'd like to see your room.
But of course.
It's this one right here.
The one that says "Josh" on the door?
Exactly.
Looking for an escape route?
I just need to get some fresh air.
Yeah. I don't blame you.
Well, hopefully she'll be
quick and painless.
If she asks you about Amanda,
I think you should say
you hope she's having a great time.
but knowing how her mother feels,
you recognize
the appropriate boundaries.
Boundaries.
Right.
- Will you excuse me?
- Sure.
And this is Lori's room.
- They're coming!
- Lori?
Constance Berlinger,
my daughter Lori.
And welcome to my... den of teen angst.
Which I must confess,
I retreat to way too often.
Not kyle, though.
Not Mr. Positive Spin.
You should let some light in here.
What are you doing?
What does it look like I'm doing?
I need to move the ladder.
That's gonna be
a little difficult right now.
Can you not touch that?
I don't think Kyle
would want you to handle it.
How would you know?
I know that box
is very important to him.
Do you know why it's important to him?
Because I do.
Oh, really? Why?
I can't share that information with you
and neither can Kyle.
You have no idea about what Kyle and I
share with each other.
I know you don't know him
as well as you think.
You can't go through the window
and the social worker's
about to start my interview
with a clear view of the front door.
So I'm still stuck?
Not necessarily.
I'll get jessi out of here first.
And if I can't get back to you,
look for my signal then go.
What kind of signal?
I'm not sure yet.
You'll just know.
Come with me.
Finally, we can talk.
- Later.
- No.
This is important.
Here.
It's their song, D4.
It's the missing record
from the jukebox.
Where did you get this?
I found it in my room.
Brian said he didn't leave it
there for me,
but I don't know who else would.
You have to play it.
I will... but I can't right now.
It's part of our history.
I know, but I need to focus
on my family right now.
Brian said that you would be like this.
He said I couldn't count on you.
Why would he say that?
You keep sending me away.
Jessi, you know the situation today.
So what if some social worker
sees me here?
She can't see anything out
of the ordinary.
We are out of the ordinary.
Don't forget,
I'm more like you
than any of these people here,
more than the Tragers
and more than Amanda.
Why do you have to make
this a competition?
There should be no competition.
Jessi! Jessi!
- I'll leave when I want.
- Jessi.
I didn't know you were here.
She was just leaving.
Hi, there. And you are?
- Jessi.
- A friend of Kyle's?
Well, I'd like to think
I'm more than that.
Well, I started off
as Nicole's patient,
but now it's like
I'm part of the family.
How lovely.
Well... bye.
How long was Jessi your patient?
For a few months.
You treated her here?
Yes, but I don't see patients
at home anymore.
Because they kept
becoming part of the family?
What'd she say?
"Mrs. Trager,
you seem to have a history
of getting too involved emotionally."
At least nicole has emotions.
You realize that eavesdropping
is an invasion of privacy
and that me asking you to do it
is unacceptable parenting, right?
- Right.
- Good.
What did she say now?
24 cases, 20 ladder rungs each way.
Just a few weeks post-op.
You know I'll owe you for,
like, ever, right?
I'm already making a list of the ways
you can make it up to me.
No way. We made a deal.
Oh, I think we should
amend our deal to include
one-time payments for heroic measures.
You want me to lose
my born-again virgin status
because you helped me move beer
so you can bring it to a party
that I can't even go to?
Um, pretty much.
You're technically doing it
to help Kyle anyway,
which you always do
for no return favors.
And now that I think about it,
I'm mad at you
because how come you never
ask him for anything,
and yet I get propositioned
for casual, meaningless sex?
Meaningless sex? Really?
Not meaning...
You know what I mean.
No. No, I'm not so sure that I do.
Don't get mad.
I'm being a jerk, huh?
Tell the boy something
he doesn't already know.
Not a good time, Josh.
Look,
I enjoy the
"are they or aren't they" drama
as much as the next person,
but you two seem to have gotten
a little sidetracked.
Yeah, I'm on it.
While you're at it,
figure out how to explain
why kyle sleeps in the bathtub.
Well, he's got a cover story for that.
The one his fake parents used.
Yeah, but that's a lie,
and you know
how Kyle is with the lying.
Meanwhile, he's had Amanda
secretly hidden in his room
for the last 12 hours.
Even if Kyle the rebel makes
an appearance,
pretend you're the social worker.
Does any cover story explain
why two responsible parents
would allow their child to sleep
in a bathroom appliance?
Kyle,
Mrs. Berlinger wants
to speak to you now.
Just another day in the Trager house.
Maybe that's why she's here.
No, seriously.
With everything that's happened
since Kyle came into our lives,
what seems everyday to us
may be just plain weird
to everybody else.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
How many kids help take down
a multi-national corporation
over the weekend?
So, Kyle, how would you describe
your time with the Tragers?
They've been wonderful to me.
I had no one when they took me in,
and they became my family.
But you found your family?
You were reunited
with your real parents.
Leaving the Tragers
was extremely difficult.
When I was gone,
I missed them terribly.
And what was it like coming back here
after your parents died?
She was trained
to pickup on non-verbal cues.
A twitch, a tense grip of my hands,
a nervous gesture,
anything that could indicate
I wasn't being truthful.
Kyle?
Even though the circumstances
were tragic,
I knew I'd be in a home
where I felt loved
and well taken care of.
I'd like to know more about
your relationship with Nicole.
This was Amanda's chance to escape,
but there was no way she could know it.
I had to signal her, but how?
When did it become more maternal
than professional?
I knew if I relaxed and concentrated,
I could control the flow
of electrons through the house.
Nicole and I had a special bond
from the beginning.
I felt a special connection
with everyone here.
They've all taught me
something important.
All of the abilities
I'd explored seemed useless
If I couldn't help Amanda
sneak out of the house.
I had to focus,
just not look like I was focusing.
They've all welcomed me
as one of their own.
My life has changed for the better
by living here with them.
What kinds of things
have they taught you?
I think the most important thing is
what it means to be a family.
Am I passing your test?
This isn't a test.
It merely helps me evaluate...
whether or not this is
a loving and nurturing environment.
Something like that.
I don't understand.
How can you quantify
a family's love for one another?
How can you measure intangible
things like nurturing?
It's just a tool that
social services uses.
A standard checklist.
I need to get Amanda past
the kitchen and out of the house.
If it's a checklist you need,
let me give you mine.
They gave me a seat
at their dinner table
when I had nowhere else to go.
Stephen gave up his work room
so I could have my own place to sleep.
Josh taught me how to play basketball.
And Lori shared her birthday with me.
And Nicole always made me
feel safe and protected,
even when I felt lost and scared.
I could go on and on
cause this family means
everything to me.
Interesting.
Oh. Oh, gosh.
I'm sorry. Oh!
- Amanda?
- Mom?
Someone from the airline called
telling me you never got on the plane.
- Mom...
- You deliberately defied me, Amanda.
I didn't plan any of this!
This kind of deceitful,
impetuous behavior.
You never would have done it
if it weren't for him.
Carol, I know you're upset,
but it's really unfair to blame Kyle.
He has fill her head with
god-knows-what nonsense,
now she is lying to me,
and she is throwing away
everything she has worked for.
That was my choice.
It has nothing to do with Kyle.
But you came here and
ran to him, didn't you?
Yes, but...
And you let her in, did you not?
Yes, but it was late...
And my daughter spent the night here,
and you knew nothing about it, did you?
It's that kind of loose,
permissive attitude...
Mom, stop!
The Tragers are an amazing family,
and Kyle is the most incredible person.
The real problem is you have no idea
and no interest in who I am
or what I want.
So maybe you should ask yourself
why I was so afraid to talk to you
that I hid here all night
instead of coming home.
If you wanted to report
a really messed up family,
uou should have reported our own.
What are you talking about?
Everyone knows you called
social services here.
I did nothing of the sort.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Trager.
I didn't mean to cause you
so much trouble.
I'm sorry.
Well, clearly that's a private
family matter,
not one social services could resolve.
- Then we're done.
- For now.
I still need to file my report.
Is there anything else I can tell you?
No, no. I'll just...
Oh, wait. There is something
I've overlooked.
Kyle's room.
- What about it?
- I need to see it.
Is there a problem?
No, not at all.
It's this way.
We've always believed in
making Kyle feel
as comfortable as possible,
and we encouraged him
to make his room his own,
which includes some unorthodox choices.
Believe me, I've see hundreds
of teenagers' rooms
with the most eccentric designs.
Nothing can throw me.
Well, always a first.
This is it.
This all seems quite ordinary.
If you ask me, perfectly normal.
Thank you.
You'll receiver notice
of my evaluation within 48 hours.
I don't suppose
you could give me a little preview.
It's not easy when someone drops in
and puts your whole family
under a microscope.
But yours survived.
And Kyle seems like
a promising young man.
I don't see any reason
to be concerned about him.
Thank you.
I do, however, have some
gave concerns about you.
The way you've crossed boundaries,
mixing your personal
and your professional life
shows an alarming lack of judgment
and ethical integrity.
It would be remiss of me
if I didn't file the proper notice.
I'm shocked that you feel that way.
Really?
Knowing what I've heard about you,
it doesn't surprise me at all.
How'd you get a bed in here?
I just found it this way.
Beer?
Soft, firm, and extra firm.
Where did it all come from?
Does it matter? We saved the day.
Lori, you have how many
cases of beer in this house?
Not to drink. I was storing it
for some friends.
And I know that's, like,
the most idiotic move ever.
So go ahead and do what you need to do.
Well, you're staying grounded,
that's for sure.
I know it got you into trouble,
but thank you for doing this.
All of you.
Thank you for today.
We should celebrate.
Let's crack open a few, make a toast.
Well, say good-bye to this beer.
Come on, everybody out.
Come in.
You've been in here all day.
A lot to catch up on.
I don't want to disturb you, I...
I just wanna say that
I know letting Amanda stay here
without telling you was wrong,
and I'm sorry.
It's funny.
What?
How even with the best of intentions,
making one questionable decision can...
Lead to such a mess.
I think things are still
gonna be a mess
for me and Amanda with Mrs. Bloom.
Well, hopefully, in time,
She'll cool off and
won't see you as an issue.
Is everything all right, Nicole?
Everything's fine.
Damn, Josh.
You scared the living...
Hey, hey!
You eat with that mouth?
It's been a long day.
What do you want?
I just thought we could spend a moment
and reflect on a job well done.
I still can't believe
we actually pulled it off.
Please.
Child's play to one that is adept
in the black arts of adult deception
as your gifted yet humble brother.
Lucky Declan was there.
Yep.
On the saving your bacon scale,
I'd say he scored about nine.
8.5. What's your point?
Nothing.
I know I'm a new player
in the great game
of adolescent relationships.
But if you ask me,
I'd say the big D
is carrying the proverbial torch.
Yes, sirree.
He's tasted from the fountain of lor,
and he wants to dive right...
Finish that sentence,
and I guarantee you
they'll never find the body.
- Hey, I was just saying...
- Get out.
Amanda.
I'm sorry.
I'm not allowed to let you in.
I'm not allowed to go in.
I just wanna make sure you're okay.
I'm still grounded, but I'm fine.
How about you?
My mom and I talked.
She's still hurt and angry, but...
at least she listened more
than usual this time.
That's encouraging.
Unfortunately,
she won't let me see you,
outside of school, for a while.
And I need to get a job to be
more mature and responsible.
To tell you the truth,
after the way I've handled things,
I don't really blame her.
Well, I'll learn to be more mature
and responsible with you.
That song.
That's the one you asked me to play
when you and Jessi
were out somewhere.
You never told me why you needed it.
It helped us get where we needed to go.
Kyle,
if there's ever anything you
want to tell me,
I hope you know you can.
I do know that.
Okay.
Well, good night.
Good night.
Only a day had passed
since my decision to hide Amanda,
and allowing her to stay in the house
seemed to leave her with
new questions about me.
Still, I didn't regret
making that choice
because it's worth taking risks
to help the people you care about.
And that day, I knew that my family
was willing to take risks for me,
that our love for each other
could never be questioned
and that the secrets
we keep remain unexposed.
I've been to his home.
He's very attached to the family.
It could be a problem.
But now I understand
why you believe he's the one.
After no further questions,
I'd like to say again
what an honnor it is
to be at your service.
Traduction ::: La Team XY
Sechs, Jayson.sosweet et MiniBen314
www.forom.com