Hi, Laura. Diego.
- Let the consumption begin.
- Excellent.
- You gonna behave yourself?
- Ever seen me at a party?
- Hi, you having fun?
- Sure.
- This is--
- Your idea of hell.
In hell you tend to know
a lot of the people.
- I'm having a great time.
- Yeah?
- Can I get you some blood?
- I'm good.
Steve Paymer came.
Can you believe it?
David Paymer's brother? Steve?
Steve!
Sorry. Pardon me.
I need to cool off.
Cordelia sure knows how to throw a do.
These mini-Reubens, with the
little sauerkraut and little Swiss...
...what genius brought these
into the world?
What say a couple of demon hunters
start chatting up the fillies?
- Hey.
- Hey--
- Nice sweater. Hand-knit?
- Certainly not by me.
- I meant, it's a great sweater.
- Oh, well, I'll pass that on then.
To the person who knit it.
I mean, I would if I knew who did.
But I don't.
So I won't pass it on to anyone,
will I?
Bye.
Diego, pants on!
With my master's degree in fine arts,
I launched my own business...
...selling sandwiches downtown
from a little cart.
I do see a lot of stuff on the job.
So I tell myself that I'm
"honing my eye."
Makes sense.
Oh, I love this!
Would you like to dance?
I don't dance.
Hi, Dennis.
How you doing?
Still dead?
I know the feeling.
Holy God!
Hey.
Good morning. Is there coffee?
They're still in bean form.
I thought I ordered the ground.
Can you crush them
with your vampire strength?
Just mush the bag. Just...
...mush them.
- Really fun party last night.
- I'm so glad you came.
I worried someone might suck
the energy out of the room...
...like a hole of boring despair.
But there you were, in the clinch.
I didn't-- Boring?
You used to be a person.
Did people not party in olden times?
I talked to people.
- Laura.
- She thought you hated her.
- I said you were challenged.
- I don't hate her.
I got two modes with people,
bite and avoid. Hard to shift.
- I can't get too close. With women--
- You can be nice.
It's not like Laura's gonna throw
you down and tear off all of your--
- Well, actually, Laura--
- I'll try harder.
Still, I mean, the quiet,
reserved thing...
...don't you think it makes me cool?
- He was cooler.
- Good morning.
- Now I'm depressed.
- I feel rather chipper.
- That was quite the soiree.
- Glad someone enjoyed it.
- I enjoyed it.
- A gala event.
In particular, the tiny Reubens
and the shrimp puffs.
Any leftovers lying about?
Any abandoned...
...shrimp puffs?
- You're broke, aren't you?
- A man's finances are his business.
- Want a job?
- Oh, yes, please.
I don't have much, but if you help...
...you're entitled to a cut.
- I don't know what to say.
- Great! Now we're--
Do I have to take a pay cut?
A team!
You won't be disappointed.
There's something in my eye.
Oh, don't go getting all sappy.
Hold me.
- Why don't we just--?
- Hold me!
- Hold on!
- Cordelia!
Gross! Oh!
Ew, is all.
- What did you see?
- I don't just see. I feel, okay?
- Thank you, Doyle.
- Is someone in trouble?
I'm, uh....
- I'm at the ready.
- You're going to the ice factory...
- ...on 5th.
- What are we looking for?
A corpse.
- No access through the tunnels.
- I'm driving then.
I'm coming with you. I intend
to earn my keep. By the way--
- There's no dental.
- Right, I'll floss.
Let's go.
Hey, be careful.
Guy was burned to death. Thing that
did that could still be there.
Did you see it?
All I felt was his fear
and the exploding eyeballs.
- Did I mention I hate this gig?
- We'll be in touch.
After you, sir.
Here we are. Jerico Ice Factory.
- Boss, why don't I...
- Stay put.
...stay here and wait for you?
Captain Inferno, I presume.
Close enough. I don't do well
near an open flame.
Only, you didn't burn him, did you?
Who are you?
I'm not a talker.
I let others carry the conversation.
I am good at putting these
through heads, though.
I am called Tay.
- I'm not from your dimension.
- I bet.
I was sent to stop it.
That is my cause here.
- Stop what?
- The Bringer of Chaos.
- What is it? Demon?
- More than a mere demon.
It is a vessel of pure rage.
It's almost destroyed my world,
and now it is loose in yours.
- How can I kill it?
- You won't be able to.
It's stronger than one man.
If you and your people wish to live,
stay away.
His name was Tay.
Seemed pretty shook up.
Said it brings chaos
and destruction to his world.
"Tay." Could be a Kovitch demon
from the Caucuses.
He's not from our dimension.
- They must come to ours via portals.
- Portals?
There are portals now?
When did they put in portals?
Don't we have enough to do
without burning monsters coming here?
We'll figure out what it is, boss.
You can count on it.
Stop kissing butt.
It's not like we get overtime.
- I'm on it.
- I also want to know--
About similar killings lately?
See? On it.
- Where you headed?
- Victim's office. He's in security.
- I'd like to know who hired him.
- Okay.
- What are you doing here?
- I could ask you the same.
Working for them?
How much do they pay you to hunt us?
I work for myself. I'm looking
for his killer. Hard to forget.
Burned alive. Know anyone
who does that?
Yes?
Where? How soon?
We're sorry, your call did
not go through, Please dial again,
Angel Investigations,
we help the hopeless.
I hate this phone.
Any luck?
We're stymied on the demon
but we found...
...four recent similar killings.
All guys, all burned
from the inside out.
- Did you find it?
- Yeah.
- It's a "she."
- A chick that burns?
Are you okay?
- Did she...?
- Care about me?
Did she Carrie you?
Carrie, the movie?
I can't hear you. Hello?
Must be in a canyon.
- Can you hear me?
- I can hear you now.
- Are you back?
- A bored warlock must have made these.
Keep trying to find that demon ray,
There's more to this.
I think he's on a mission.
He may be the key,
- What does she look like?
- Two ridges running down either cheek.
Violet eyes, She seemed intelligent,
She was very...attractive,
for a demon.
A hottie, huh? I guess she is,
all right. What with the sizzle.
Sizzler?
The sizzle factor.
- Angel?
- I can't hear you.
- Cordelia--
- Excuse me, sir. I need your help.
- What?
- There's a man who wants to hurt me.
- What man? Where is he?
Over there in the black coat.
- Code three in the front gallery.
- Roger,
Code three.
Said he had a black jacket.
Excuse me, ma'am.
And this brings us to
Manet's incomparable...
...la Musique aux Tuileries,
First exhibited in 1863.
On the left, one spies
the painter himself.
In the distance is Manet's friend,
French poet and critic Baudelaire.
Interesting fellow.
In his poem, "Le Vampire," he wrote:
Thou who abruptly as a knife
Didst come into my heart
He strongly believed that evil forces
surrounded mankind...
...and some speculate that the poem
was about a real vampire.
Baudelaire was actually taller
and drunker than he's depicted here.
Aha!
Better be an "Aha!" of triumph.
I was dreaming there was a sale
at Neiman's.
I think I've located them,
the "Vigories of Oden Tal."
- The what?
- Oden Tal. Vigories.
"They have four ridges on their
foreheads, are fierce warriors...
- ...and the women live enslaved."
- Way to go, Wes!
Angel said Tay was the key.
Any way to find him here in town?
"The men are herbivores.
They eat stew made of rotten plants...
...and must consume
half their body weight a day."
Whoa.
So, we're looking for the
biggest compost heap in L.A.?
You. How?
- A human would have been unconscious.
- Answer my questions first.
- You're a vampire.
- Among other things.
- What's Tay want?
- I don't have time.
- Who killed the guy at the factory?
- You don't think I'll hurt you?
Gotta risk it. I can't allow
tourists to go torching locals.
- Leave. I'm warning you!
- What's gonna happen?
Stay back!
We must go.
- What's wrong?
- It's not your concern.
- You're not one of us.
- No, but I'll stick around anyway.
It's right, this is not your concern.
The traitor, it, and the other
are ours.
- It's best not to--
- Do that?
- What will happen to her?
- She will be unmade.
Please, please! You don't
have to do this to me!
Watch its hands.
I'll be good, I promise.
You don't have to do this to me.
Why does it speak when no one listens?
Please!
- It has been recovered.
- Let me go!
- It will now be restored.
- You bastards!
You'll feel so much better after this.
No!
You should dress that.
Your wound.
Why do this?
I thought vampires were killers.
They are. I was cursed by gypsies.
- Cursed to help people?
- Yeah.
Gypsies have a strange
sense of...humor.
Want to tell me what's going on?
The girl is a runaway. I was trying
to help her escape from our homeland.
If you hadn't--
If I hadn't helped,
you'd both be with them now.
Perhaps.
Why was the girl running away?
- She was going to be unmade.
- They'd kill her?
In a fashion you wouldn't understand.
Try me.
In Oden Tal...
...what you call personality,
our passions...
...these impulses sit in an area
of the body we call the Ko.
Your pursuers want to
take this from you?
From the women, yes.
Once females come of age, Ko controls
our physical and sexual power.
It even signals when we're aroused
and have met desirable mates.
- When it's removed--
- You're easily controlled.
We marry who they command
and serve without questioning.
- We leave behind dreaming.
- But you escaped.
I was the first. I am Jhiera.
Jhiera of Oden Tal.
My family rules the dimension.
I bet they're not loving...
...your portal jumping,
refugee-aiding duties.
They tell the people I'm dead,
but the women know.
Here, we have a name, a chance
to become. But it's difficult.
When the Ko first matures,
the girls can't manage it...
...our physical energy.
We come to your world in a fever.
That's why...the ice.
Yes.
When I first arrived, alone...
...I thought I would die
from the heat under my skin.
And your people...
...the men.
Some respond to the Ko involuntarily.
They try to force themselves.
It wasn't safe.
Until I found the frozen water.
As long as I could stay cool...
...the worst of it passed
in a few months' time.
Then I started to learn
to control my power.
Like last night when you burned me.
I wanted to hurt you.
I thought you were my enemy.
- Who burned the guard?
- He tried to touch one of my girls.
- He probably didn't mean to hurt her.
- She couldn't help killing him.
What about the other four guys who
died the same way in the last year?
- Have you been--?
- No, I haven't been following you.
If you burn people,
there'll be questions.
I understand what you're doing,
and I'll help...
...but you can't hurt men
in my world.
I am daughter to a king, sir.
The king who promised
a better life for everyone.
I didn't denounce him and escape
for my good alone.
I did it to fulfill his promise
for all the women of Oden Tal.
If a few die to protect my people--
They're my people and I protect them.
Then tell them to stay out of my way.
Wait.
You too. I don't need your help.
I'm not sure about coming
out here by ourselves.
We should've waited for Angel.
As his employee, I feel it's important
to show initiative and drive.
We can't just dally about--
Look! Nancy's Petticoat.
They're quite rare. Named for
Nancy Mitford, the author...
...because of her love for--
Right.
- Shoving off.
- I wonder where they keep the compost?
I'd say we follow our noses.
Wait!
Wait, okay? We shouldn't have
come here. Smells like flower poop.
The portal will open soon,
and only for a short while.
When the proper coordinates align,
we must move to the entry point.
You will escort it there,
ensure its quick return...
...and then rejoin us.
We have a lot of work to do here.
It can go home now.
Would it like that?
- Would it like to go home?
- It is happy to go...
...as soon as you say.
And don't you feel better now?
- We've recovered two this month.
- It means nothing.
This won't stop until we find Jhiera.
Jhiera! Just when I need
the artistic eye of a goddess.
Where are the girls?
And namaste to you.
Where you left them.
You okay? You look spun.
- How are they doing?
- They're chilling.
The little sisters are fine.
REM-ing.
Tell me what's up.
- They took the girl.
- Man, that's lame.
They will find us before too long.
We must go from here.
The girls aren't ready.
They need isolation...
...and temperature adjustment
before they can go out.
- We'll move them someplace else.
- My shaman has a place in the desert.
He can't turn away scantily
clad women, from any dimension.
You need work on your mirth chakra.
- If we can trust him, we'll go.
- He's good people.
Then call him.
If he accepts us, we'll leave
first thing in the morning.
- Still no answer.
- I bet he forgot to turn it on again.
You'd think a guy who can use a
Scythian bow could use a cell phone.
- So, what now?
- We head back and find Angel.
Great. Lead the way.
Low and slow.
Hide, hide, hide.
Sir!
- We've found them.
- Where?
An ice worker says he's been shipping
two tons of ice weekly to this place.
Gather the men. Prepare them to
capture the princess and cut them all.
What are you doing?
We nearly got burned...
...and you're here showering?
- Hello?
- She's especially agitated...
...because we tried calling
during a situation.
I had to take a shower.
- What's up?
- The demons said they found someone.
And they said they would
cut the "princess"...
...which I imagine is
not a happy thing.
You'd be right on that one.
We gotta find her first.
The demon said something about a lot
of ice being delivered somewhere.
- Ice?
- Yeah.
- Shipping order address. Let's go.
- That's it?
They seemed....
There were a lot of them.
We need a plan.
We go in, I hit people hard
in the face. See where it takes us.
Wait here. I want a warning.
All right?
Wesley!
- Welcome!
- Where's Jhiera?
Sorry, no Jhiera here.
But I see I can help you.
- Let's start with the clothes.
- She's in trouble.
- Men are coming for her.
- Where are you from?
You don't want to know.
You? I thought I made it clear.
- They're coming.
- We're leaving tomorrow.
Not soon enough.
- They're coming.
- That would be now.
Help get the girls out.
Stall them as long as you can.
I'm helping you
whether you like it or not.
Oh, my. You're--
Allow me to introduce myself.
Wesley!
How about a clay massage?
We heal, brothers.
- That outfit quite becomes you.
- Wesley, get a grip.
They can't hold them off long.
My, what a grip. Very healthy.
Surprisingly firm myself.
- Feel.
- You're pathetic...
- ...and about to get fried!
- No, but...
...just one kiss goodbye?
- Jhiera and the runaways are ours.
- No.
Give them back or the humans die.
Then they die.
Hold it!
Hold it still.
Time to go home.
Let her go or your leader's dead.
Go. Go!
- Don't bring your war here.
- I have to.
If this enemy persists,
our society crumbles.
- Here, you'll have another enemy.
- You don't understand, human.
No, I don't.
And I'm not human.
If I were you, I'd grab
the next portal out.
Sorry.
- I had a--
- Mushing didn't work?
Not to worry. My fault, I'm sure.
Really. Cagey little brutes,
aren't they?
I'll wash them individually.
They'll be like new.
- Better.
- Stop.
You groveling isn't just
a way of life, it's an art.
I don't grovel. Don't fire me.
Yesterday was an anomaly.
- I'm rarely taken hostage.
- Good, and you're not fired.
- I'm not?
- It wasn't your fault.
- You handled yourself very well.
- That's-- I can't tell you how--
- I'm your faithful servant, Angel.
- Like I said, an art.
Look who's here.
Can I get you something?
A knife to our throat?
You can run away?
Come on in.
The girls are safe, outside the city.
Good, but you nearly got
Cordelia and Wesley killed.
- I had no choice.
- Protecting the innocent...
...shouldn't depend
on where they're from.
An easy sentiment when
your people are free.
I'm not saying you shouldn't fight.
Just know that I'll stop you
if you cross the line.
I don't need an extra conscience.
I'll do what I think is right.
And I'll do the same.
Fine. I think we understand
each other then.
I have to go.