Sorry, I guess I have a problem
expressing myself verbally.
I struggle with it.
You stood me up.
You were gonna come to
the station, remember?
I forgot?
Not something a girl likes to hear.
So we'll skip the informal invitation
and do the more formal thing.
You have the right to remain silent,
but I wouldn't recommend it.
Look at the pictures.
I looked at them.
- What's in the pictures?
- Me and Little Tony.
I don't know where he is.
How long are we gonna do this?
So you haven't seen him since
the day this picture was taken?
The day County Supervisor Caffrey
was found murdered.
I heard it was a suicide.
Caffrey shot himself?
- It happens.
- In back of the head?
And he locked himself
in the trunk of his car?
He'd been depressed.
Where's Little Tony?
Burbank. Stockholm. The planet
Mongo. I have no idea where he is!
Losing patience with this crap.
I'm not. I'm just getting started.
I had a big breakfast.
I could do this all day.
Doesn't she ever have to pee?
Fine. You want to play all day,
play with yourself.
You charge me or get me gone
because I'm telling you nothing.
Look at the pictures.
Bite me.
Where is he?
Kate, Kate.
- Sorry.
- Yeah, well...
...we should've gotten
you out hours ago.
- He's not gonna talk.
- Then Little Tony is good as gone.
We can't find him,
then I don't know anyone who can.
It's about time!
Not a lot of enchanted
swordsmiths open on Sunday.
Cut off all limbs and both heads.
Remember to bury the parts separately.
I don't want it coming back to life.
That's it?
I'm gonna go clean out the nests.
I'll see you back at the office.
Am I wrong in thinking that
a "please" and "thank you"...
...is generally considered good form
when requesting a dismemberment?
He appreciates us in his
own unappreciative way.
You know what I think?
I think he uses his tortured
creature-of-the-night status...
...as license to be
rude and insensitive.
Sure, he's polite to
the helpless and downtrodden.
But he ignores the people that are
closest to him, who matter the most.
Can you say "clueless"?
Does giant tentacle spew
come out with dry cleaning?
- Good, you're back. You need to--
- No!
I don't care what's about to happen.
Asteroids are hurtling towards Earth.
Unspeakable evil is rising in
the San Fernando Valley.
Jar Jar is getting his
own talk show. Whatever.
I don't want to hear about it.
Not until you ask us how it went.
Call your mom back. She phoned,
saying she'd like to speak with you.
And what are you talking about?
You do remember leaving us in
a sewer with a giant calamari?
Yeah, and you're both here,
so I assume it went okay, right?
Yeah, it went okay. Of
course it went okay. Okay?
- That's not the point!
- So there is a point?
It is possible to brood and show
interest in the feelings of others.
She thinks you're insensitive,
and not to bring up the irony...
...but consider the source.
I'm reserved. I do care.
- It's like you don't have a pulse.
- I don't.
Spend a little time listening to
how the living interact.
- Kate.
- Angel.
- Got a minute?
- Sure.
- Coffee?
- I'm fine.
Mr. and Mrs. Spock
need to mind meld now.
His name's Tony Papazian. Street
name, Little Tony. He's a bad guy.
We have an indictment against him
for a county supervisor's murder.
One problem: We don't know
where to send the subpoena.
You can't find him.
He's still in the city,
but all my sources are dry.
- Want me to look into it?
- I'll pay for whatever you can get.
- I owe you a favor--
- This isn't a favor.
It's a job. That's how we do it.
- This number is my direct line.
- All right.
Time's a factor.
Tony plans to skip town.
Got it.
Find him, you call me. Nothing more.
You cannot be a part of this.
You don't want a reputation for
going outside the department?
I don't want to get a reputation
for getting you killed.
Anything?
Plenty on Papazian.
Known acquaintances, hangouts.
But the cops have
already been over all this.
Yeah, but we haven't.
Cordelia, I wanted to, you know,
thank you so much...
...for going through
those coroner reports...
...because I can imagine how
not fun it is to read about...
...you know, coroner stuff.
Lame.
- What do you got?
- The weebies.
This guy clearly has
anger management issues.
Victims and victim parts washing up...
...all over the
Southern California Coast.
Long Beach, San Pedro, Carlsbad.
Pull up the tidal flow charts.
- Match them up to the murder dates.
- Tides?
You think this guy has a
primary dumping ground?
Do the victims come
from the same spot?
Somewhere Little Tony feels safe.
- Daddy.
- Katie!
I saw you. Were you
planning on saying hi?
Well, I figured you're working.
I'm not here very long, just dropping
off some pension forms up in records.
If you think you got red tape
on the job, wait'll you retire.
Harlan says they're throwing you
a sendoff at the Blue Bar.
Just the guys looking to give
me a hard time, not a big deal.
He said I should say something,
just a few words...
...to mark the occasion,
seeing as you're my father.
That'd be fine.
Don't go to any trouble.
It's no trouble, really.
- Detective, you got a call on 229.
- Thanks.
- I guess I'd better....
- Yeah.
Lockley.
8843 Hyperion Way,
right off pier 39, San Pedro.
You found him, You're sure?
Mack's Salvage Depot, northwest side.
Got some muscle on hand.
I'm on my way.
Just get out of there.
Damn it.
- And don't forget to water my plants.
- Sure thing.
And talk to them.
They like that.
Hi.
This is exciting.
I love boat trips.
- Who's the mook?
- Herb Saunders.
- It's Herb Saunders.
- The freeways here.
I've been driving all day,
but the brochure did say:
"Boats leaving every two hours."
I think you're still lost.
- Is that to Catalina?
- No.
I could've sworn
the ticket said pier 39.
It's here, I had it.
- Get out of here.
- Benny, I don't like that guy.
Is it the hat?
I knew it was too much.
Hi, Tony.
Which part of "Get out of there"
gave you trouble?
He was getting away.
So you dressed like a road flare
and put my ass and yours on the line?
Look, just go. I'll figure out
something to tell my lieutenant.
I want my phone call.
Gotta cancel the suite in Yerevan?
Think you can get your deposit back?
You've been running after me for a
long time, haven't you, sweetheart?
If I'd known how bad you wanted me,
I might've had you catch me sooner.
If I knew how much you
needed the exercise...
...I might've let you
run a little longer.
- Wolfram and Hart,
- Lee Mercer,
Yes, Mr. Papazian, we're already
well aware of the situation.
And are you aware I got
a certain thorn in my side?
Oh, yes, we understand
the factors very clearly.
And I think I can say with confidence,
that thorn is about to be removed.
Permanently.
Here is our petition to transfer
our client out of this precinct.
- What for?
- For his own safety, lieutenant.
Afraid to stay with us?
Need a nightlight?
You got a pretty mouth.
Hate to see it get broken.
I want that stricken.
He's under great stress
from abuse suffered...
...at the hands of your officers and
an unnamed assailant...
...we believe was with
Detective Lockley at the arrest.
- I wouldn't know.
- I saw you talking to him.
Before or after you
murdered Caffrey, you fat--
- That's enough.
- Enter her verbal abuse in the record.
That too.
Mr. Papazian's rights
will be respected--
Mr. Papazian is a
very important client.
Any violation of his rights
and there will be repercussions.
- What does that mean?
- I'll open the case to public opinion.
We'll shine a light
on this precinct...
...and give people a view of the
brutality of the police...
...that'll make Mark Fuhrman
look like Gentle Ben.
Everybody should have
a lawyer like this one.
How nice is it to finally have a
simple find-the-crime-lord case?
Over and done with.
Yeah.
Wait. You've got pensive face.
- I've always got pensive face.
- "Pensiv-er" face.
I'm not sure this is over with.
- There's something about Little Tony.
- What something?
I don't know, just a feeling I got.
- What?
- Nothing.
I just find it fascinating how your
instincts are so highly attuned...
...when it comes to boring old evil,
but you have yet to make mention...
...of these new shoes.
Look, Cordelia, women's shoes--
Men, they just don't--
Great shoes. New?
You were right.
He's planning something.
- What'd you hear?
- Papazian's planning something.
- That's it?
- Johnny Red says, quote:
- "Papazian's planning something."
- I thought so.
You were right.
- Home run, Lockley.
- Way to go.
Nice work, Lockley.
No, your dad paid for the drink.
Tony Papazian, huh?
Yeah.
- Well, congratulations.
- Thanks.
Hope the bust doesn't fall apart
before you file the paperwork.
Damn lawyers, huh?
Yeah.
- Harlan.
- You see this?
- Sensitivity training?
- Everyone has to take it.
It's because of what
you did to Papazian.
What I did?
Somebody's gonna answer for this.
- Will they make us hug?
- I'm not hugging you.
Glad I'm getting out. In my day,
we didn't need any damn sensitivity.
I'm guessing not too many of
you want to be here right now.
Quick show of hands.
Who actually wants to be here?
Well, I'm not gonna waste your time.
What I am gonna do
is give you some tools...
...to help you experience
the full range of human emotions.
Learning that won't just
make you better people...
...it'll help you diffuse
volatile situations in the field.
It'll allow you to manage
some of your aggression...
...so you won't feel
so tired all the time.
In short, it'll make you better cops.
One of the tools we use is this.
It's called a Talking Stick.
I know, it sounds silly.
But it works if you give it a chance.
It's our contract with each other.
Whoever holds this has the freedom
to express himself completely...
...without judgment, within
the confines of this room.
Heath?
- I don't think so.
- Go ahead, give it a try.
Now, why don't you start by telling
us something about your family?
How you grew up. Any siblings?
- Six brothers.
- And what was that like?
I learned to hit back pretty quick.
Your brothers went
kind of hard on you, huh?
Where were your parents?
It was just my mom.
She did the best she could.
So you had to get tough right out of
the gate. Shut down your emotions.
It's okay. You have our
permission to be honest.
Is there something that you always
wanted to say to your mother...
...but never could?
"Will you marry me?"
Kate, you'd like to share
something? We'd like to hear it.
- No, I don't really.
- Afraid?
Genuine emotion makes you
uncomfortable. That's okay.
Your inappropriate
sarcasm masks anger.
And do you know what anger is, Kate?
It's just fear.
Fear of being hurt. Fear of loss.
You've been hurt, haven't you, Kate?
And you're afraid of being hurt again.
Who are you afraid is gonna hurt you?
Hell if I know,
But you told me you
heard something, right?
Planning something,
that's all I heard.
And who'd you hear it from?
Guys who work for Little Tony.
They're in my spinning class.
- What did they say?
- They weren't actually talking to me.
They were talking to some
guys in Brancato's crew.
I overheard on account of
they had to shout over the bikes.
- And all these guys are at your gym?
- Yeah.
You got some kind of
thug special there?
No, but if you want to
sign up, I get a discount.
Look, guys. What was said?
Right. Izzy's boys, they say to
Little Tony's crew...
...now LT's in jail, they gotta
look for new employment.
But LT's guys say no, because no stupid
bitch is gonna get the best of LT.
- Know what that means?
- I think it stands for "Little Tony."
It means he's going after Kate.
- Angel.
- We need to talk.
I know. I want to
apologize for the other night.
You don't have to.
That's not what my
sensitivity trainer says.
I know, it's pretty goofball, right?
Still, thanks for what you did.
You're welcome.
What are you doing tomorrow
night, around 8-ish?
My father's having this retirement
party with some of his cop buddies.
I'm supposed to say a few words.
It'd be nice if there was at least
one person there who wasn't armed.
It'd be a favor.
Sure.
Okay, that was easy. I'm relieved.
Is something wrong?
- I think you may be in real danger.
- Okay, the relief part's done.
I don't know the specifics yet, but
Papazian took a contract out on you.
- Wow, he's really acting out.
- Well, yeah.
- He wants you dead.
- I get that.
I'm just saying he must be in pain
to strike out at others in that way.
- Are you okay?
- God, listen to me.
Suddenly I'm Dr. Laura.
Soon I'll be talking
about my inner child.
I'll be back to my usual level
of cynicism in no time.
I'm sensing some tension.
I think you should tell me.
What are you feeling?
Concerned.
We went to great effort and expense
to get you into that precinct.
- Is it working?
- Of course it's working.
After tomorrow's session,
you'll see results.
Incredible results.
That makes me feel all warm inside.
That is so true, man!
Boy, I'm scared.
And excited.
And consumed with dread.
And glad you're here.
Little Tony's hired guns wouldn't
try something in a room of cops.
Oh, that death threat overhead.
No, I meant speaking in public.
What's that old saw? Picture your
audience in their underwear?
Way ahead of you.
Happy retirement, Daddy.
- See you later.
- Who's this?
My friend Angel.
Angel, this is my father.
Hello. Congratulations.
For what? All I did was live
this long and not get shot.
- Why do you do that?
- Do what?
Pretend important things don't matter.
So, Angel, how long you
been seeing Katie?
We're pretty new friends.
Good to see her out with a man.
I was starting to wonder
if she leaned in another direction.
All right, everyone, before we cut
the cake, the other Officer Lockley...
...the good-looking one, wants
to say a few words. Kate?
Hi, everybody.
Welcome to the end of an era.
The old man wants us to
believe he could care less...
...about all this attention
and free booze.
But I know him better than that.
He put a lot of years in on the job
and made a difference in many lives.
And now it's over. It's a huge deal,
no matter what he says.
In fact, I don't know what
he's gonna do with himself.
He forgot how to be anything
but a cop a long time ago.
And maybe that's why
I became a cop too.
After Mom died, you stopped, you know.
It was like you couldn't
stand the sight of me.
Her face, her eyes looking up at you.
But big girls don't cry, right?
You said, "Gone's gone and
there's no use wallowing."
Worms and dirt and nothing, forever.
Not one word about a better place.
You couldn't even tell a
scared little girl a beautiful lie.
God, I wanted to drink with you.
I wanted you to laugh once with me...
...the way you laughed with
Jimmy here or Frank.
What the hell did they do to her
in that class?
My best friend, Joanne?
Her mom was soft and she smelled
like macaroni and cheese.
And she would pick me up
on her lap and she'd rock me.
She said she wanted to
keep me for herself...
...that I was good and sweet.
Everybody said I was.
Do you realize that you have
never told me that I'm pretty?
Not once in my life.
Keep going, Katie.
Well, I can't anymore, Dad.
I can't campaign for the office
of your beloved daughter.
You closed your heart after
Mom left us and that's it!
- That was so damn brave.
- Are you kidding me?
This wasn't the forum.
She can't worry about protecting him.
Let it out. I always knew
your mother was controlling.
- I'm passive-aggressive?
- I hear denial.
She abused the process.
You're completely blocked!
Your need for catharsis
isn't the issue!
I'll give you catharsis.
For God's sake, Jimmy.
Keep it together, will you?
I'll take him to his precinct
to sleep it off with the drunks.
You should do likewise.
Come on, let's go.
All right, I'm here.
What's the big emergency?
Because these late hours are eating
into my potential social life.
Why I ever thought it was a nifty idea
to work for a ventriloquist--
- Hi.
Drink this.
You have the most intense eyes.
I see such an old soul.
He gets that a lot.
I thought that enigmatic thing
was an act to get women.
The truth is, you don't have
an insincere bone in your body.
Tell me about the sensitivity
training. Who's running it?
You want to go?
It's pretty wonderful.
Gets you where you live.
I need to know his name.
We all need so much.
What's her deal? Too much...?
- Thumb-sucking?
- Alcohol, dummy.
Don't look at me.
I'm not the one that needs to
brush up on her finger pantomime.
Something to do with
training she had at work.
Someone's got a crush.
- What?
- It's right there.
How he feels about you.
You don't know what to do about it.
Please. We just joke around.
Where is the truth?
He's hiding behind Mr. Humor.
I mean, look at Doyle. Really look
at him. What do you see?
A bad double poly blend?
That's defense, Cordelia.
Maybe you should try to open
your heart to a new possibility.
- She's starting to make sense--
- Angel!
I got his address, 322 Fletcher.
What aren't you telling me, Angel?
I'm glad we came to watch
late Night With Creepy Cop,
Stay with her while I find this guy.
Don't let her out of your sight.
What's going on here?
That's a good question, Allen.
Can we get you some coffee?
Or Valium? Or both?
He walked out on me.
He just walked out.
He'll be back.
Not Angel. My father.
Oh.
- I have to find him.
- Maybe you should hold off for now.
- Angel said we should wait.
- I hear you.
But I need to find my dad.
Detective, you're not yourself.
- Why don't we all just--?
- Help each other?
By staying here.
We could, but I have this...
Personal problem?
...gun. I don't want
to seem insensitive, but...
...if either of you try to stop me,
I'll blow you away...
...because I'm gonna find my dad.
Which demon do you worship?
Which one gives you your power?
A whole bunch, actually.
I'm a polytheist.
I'm not here to play games.
You have rage. I get that.
- What did you do to Kate?
- Do you know what anger is?
- It's fear.
- I know what fear is.
- I can smell it right now.
- That's good.
Give yourself permission to open up.
What were your parents like?
My parents were great.
Tasted a lot like chicken.
Why don't you talk?
Sorry I was insensitive, George.
- Listen, I'm having an epiphany.
- It's not right.
Trapped together that way.
The big ones picking on the weak ones.
It's not right. Makes them more
brutal than when they came in.
Remember this, brothers.
An act of kindness is just as manly--
Dad? Daddy?
Whiplash?
I'll tell you about whiplash.
I've got emotional whiplash from
dealing with people like you each day.
If anyone's the victim, it's me!
I've alienated my friends, my family.
My own children are afraid of me.
I can't even make love to my wife.
I hear you. I don't think you're
listening to your mugger's feelings.
Wait, wait, wait!
- What are you--?
- We followed Kate.
She's lost it. She looked
ready to do some damage.
- And it's not just her.
- The whole place is going nuts.
This is so not good.
Okay, I think someone needs a hug.
Hey, what's your damage?
I think he just found
Mr. Sensitivity.
He was in here all the time,
waiting to come out.
Gosh, what our folks do to us.
Please, Daddy, if you're there,
pick up. We need to talk.
Daddy!
He put the whammy on you!
You stink with whammy.
She's right.
Talking Stick, it's cursed.
There's a stick that talks?
Cordelia, do you have any idea
just how precious you are?
All right, let's just
talk about the stick.
He uses it as a talisman. Anyone
who handles it becomes infected.
He admitted it to me after I
threatened him with physical violence.
What's his trip?
Wolfram and Hart hired
this guy to neutralize the police...
...so Little Tony could escape.
- It'll wear off.
- Soon?
So no contract on Detective Lockley.
Little Tony's plan all along was to
kill her himself. Poor guy.
- Poor guy?
- Well, he's got issues.
Angel, snap out of this!
Right now! It's time for you to get
all vampy. Kate needs you!
I don't want to. You both withdraw
when I go vamp. I feel you judge me.
We won't judge you.
Will we? Give it a try.
Closeness is too important to me now.
- Angel, man, Kate is in there!
- Along with killer guy!
- We're closed.
- You're the police!
- You can't close!
- Why not?
Haven't we done enough?
It's always "find this, rescue that"
with you people. See how you like it.
I wanted to express my regret for
having treated you so shabbily.
So I composed a poem about it:
"I saw a leaf, and I did cry...."
It hurts, doesn't it?
When people don't listen?
When they reject you?
- You know?
- I ought to.
For two years, I've been saying
to you, "Love me, Kate.
Need me the way I need you."
But you never notice.
Never return my desire.
You just sit at that desk next to
mine, smelling the way you do...
...taunting me.
You guys, you're working for Little
Tony now. You'll find I'm stern...
...but fair. Now come on,
let's go kill us a lady cop.
- We need a rock.
- I'm not comfortable with this.
Don't argue.
This is the only way in.
Here, this one should do it.
- Aim for the window!
- I was!
Give me that.
Nice arm.
Angel, now it's your turn. Come on!
Come on! Let's go.
Wow. That's vandalism.
We'll take care of it later.
- We should leave a note.
- Would you come on!
- What's the magic word?
- Urgh!
I don't think "urgh" is it...
...if one would call it a word and
even so, certainly not a magic one.
- We don't have time!
- There's always time to be considerate.
- Oh, please.
- See? That wasn't so hard, was it?
Thought you finally had it over on me?
Thought you were smarter
than Little Tony?
Nobody beats me, baby,
not even a stone bitch like you.
I am not a bitch!
I'm just protected.
- No one protecting you now.
- Hey!
I feel serious negative
energy in this room.
Go on, take care of him.
I've been wanting to see you again.
I'm sure he'd say the same,
but that gun makes you seem hostile.
That and the body language.
It's so closed.
- Yeah.
- Angel, man, fight. Don't talk!
We are so dead.
Now, why don't we all just sit down
together and process this?
Seems that sensitivity training I
paid for really took, Nancy-boy.
How do you think that makes me feel?
Okay, now I'm feeling unheard.
You know, Anthony, you can be
a rainbow and not a...
..."pain-bow."
I mean, it really is all up to you.
You.
No, you.
Come here.
Anyone for vomit?
It's so sad, isn't it?
Some people just really need
to live in the problem.
What do I pay you for?
Where the hell are you?
I want my limo here now!
That's not possible, Mr. Papazian.
What? What are you telling me?
You attempted to murder a police
officer in full view of witnesses.
- We can't risk exposure,
- You're the one set this thing up!
We opened a door for you,
You were to walk through it,
not blast your way out.
The senior partners feel you're a
liability, We can't waste...
...energy when there are
pressing issues.
- What pressing issues?
- Our relationship is terminated.
As is this phone call.
- Morning.
- Yeah, right.
- How do you feel?
- Pretty foolish. You?
I'm all right.
Internal Affairs is investigating the
Blue Bar. Someone spiked the punch.
Seems like everyone went a little
crazy. I know I did with my dad.
Well, maybe it helped.
Did I...?
Did I say anything to you?
I'm a little fuzzy myself.
Good.
- Well, I should get back to work.
- Yeah, me too.
- Hi.
- Katie.
- Got your messages on my machine.
- That was kind of a bizarre night--
Katie...
...don't say anything.
You make an idiot of yourself,
embarrass me in front of the guys.
You don't bring that up ever again.
Far as I'm concerned...
...it didn't happen.