Previously on Dollhouse...
You programmed one of your Dolls
to be Jack the Ripper?
All I know is that Alpha
accessed multiple imprints.
And one of them did this,
slaughtered everyone around your girl
before pulling a smoke-and-mirrors.
- They won't wake up.
- I have a message for you.
- That's not funny.
- They use this body to spy on you.
I know how to find the Dollhouse,
and you know how to get in.
- Where are we?
- We are under the skin
of the mighty beast.
Did you really think you could just
walk into the Dollhouse?
When everyone knows
it doesn't exist?
Well, you kept my gift.
Turns out different every time.
Victor's, for example.
- My prince.
- I told you I'd come rescue you.
Help! I need help in here!
Victor...
He... attacked Victor.
Alpha.
We need EMT response. Now!
He had a scalpel.
He cut...
Exits have been secured.
But I think the horse has left the barn.
Motorpool's reporting a dumped van
about two blocks from here.
Full lockdown. I want a complete
head count... Actives and staff.
Go and help Victor.
Quickly!
He came for Echo.
He took her.
There was an imprint.
I don't know what.
He somehow buried the signature.
We can find them both
because she's tagged.
Not anymore.
Her GPS strip... dug it out of her,
and he went into the system
and severed the bio-links.
I can't see her vitals.
She's just... gone.
I want to know
what he's imprinted her with.
- I'm looking.
- Keep looking.
He asked me if I always
wanted to be a doctor.
Who can fathom the mind
of a crazy person?
The one who made him crazy?
Maybe.
How do you like your new togs, baby?
Oh! I love them.
Thank you.
- It still stings.
- I had to get it out.
You trust me, don't you?
You know I do.
Yeah, I do.
We've been through
a lot together, haven't we?
Ever since you took me out
of that first place when I was 13.
13. Already a woman.
That's what you said.
I remember.
But it never happened.
Did you tell her that?
Shut up.
Baby?
I didn't know you when you were 13.
None us did. One of us did.
One of us did.
I'm not Bobby.
What do you mean you're not Bobby?
I mean...
I'm not just Bobby.
Bobby...
my Tasty Couture printed T...
she left it out of the bags.
You got enough there for now,
don't you?
We can't go back.
You left out my Tasty Couture.
I looked really cute in that shirt, too,
you stupid bitch.
- Crédits -
Ms. Alvarez, Mr. Blevins,
am I to understand you've lost both
your Actives and our client?
- Yes, Ms. DeWitt.
- Alvarez's girl is a bad influence
on my guy, Ms. DeWitt.
I don't know why we insisted on Parent.
There is no "we"
in this equation, Mr. Blevins.
It is not your concern which Active
is selected for which engagement.
Your only task is discreetly
to observe the proceedings.
And we were, but...
- Alpha knew he was being followed.
- I made it very clear
these imprints were
prone to paranoia.
- I flagged it in the paperwork.
- Just as a point of interest,
how potentially lethal would you say
these imprints are?
Okay, Lars.
Who are you working with?
Nobody.
I'm not working with anybody.
Who was in the vans?
Vans?
I didn't see any vans.
- Did you see vans?
- Lars...
It's sad... It's sad how you lie.
I can smell it.
You think that I have survived
this long on the run
without being able to tell
who's lying to me?
And who's not?
You're hiding something.
I can see it in your eyes.
I will cut it out.
It's complicated.
Right.
Make it simple.
You're...
you're not real.
What?
You and your girlfriend...
- What did you say about my girlfriend?
- You're not real!
Either one of you...
you think you're on
a cross-country crime spree.
You're not.
You think you have a doomed love.
It's not doomed.
It's not even love.
I paid for this.
It was supposed to be my fantasy.
Look, I just wanted
to have a little fun.
A little fun?
You wanted to have a little fun?
Well, are you?
Are you having fun, Lars?
She's real.
And it's the last real thing
you're ever gonna see.
Crystal.
Yeah, baby?
I've got a lock.
San Pedro, industrial road 7-18.
We're close.
Whiskey, would you like a treatment?
Yes, please.
Treatment.
Yeah, let's do that instead.
Let's go to the van, okay?
Thanks for the ride.
Where's Kepler?
Don't tell me that hypochondriac
gave you the slip.
Leave us.
This man...
the man you brought here tonight...
was, until last year,
one of our Actives.
Designation Alpha.
You're telling me Kepler's a Doll?
Not at all. Stephen Kepler,
the real Stephen Kepler,
is a corpse.
His body was identified
this afternoon by Arizona authorities.
And these bodies,
you've programmed to massacre?
The Alpha situation
was an unfortunate
technological anomaly.
A technological anomaly?
My God.
What have you people done?
What have you done?
You have brought this thing
back into my house
to defile it a second time.
And now...
he's taken Echo.
Caroline.
I thought that might wipe the smirk
off your face.
- I'm walking out of here now.
- Out of the question.
He broke out of here... Alpha...
and so will I.
Alpha's a genius.
None of the follow teams
has even left the garage yet.
Building's locked down.
Someone called in
a terrorist threat.
He's laughing at us.
I can make this go away.
Set up a perimeter.
Let me know when it's time.
Ballard?
Graham, thank God it's you.
And not someone who can stand you?
Keep your eyes on me. Nod.
They're watching us.
Do you trust him?
I trust that I know what he wants.
- Listen, there's no bomb.
- What?
The tip was bogus,
but the Dollhouse is real.
- The Dollhouse?
- It's right under your feet.
A self-contained facility
built entirely underground.
I've seen it.
I can take you there.
Everybody, back in the trucks!
False alarm.
- What are you doing?
- What am I doing?
A bogus bomb threat, Ballard?
What, suspension wasn't enough for you?
You wanna go to prison?
Don't make me change my mind.
Hi.
I have news.
Have you identified
the latent imprints?
Not yet. I was going to inventory
all of Echo's old imprints to see
if maybe the signatures
matched any residual noise.
And anyway...
they're not there.
- I beg your pardon.
- They're gone.
Every wedge. Primary and backup.
Every personality we've ever imprinted
on Echo... They're gone.
Why would he take the wedges?
What good would they be to him?
Welcome to your castle, my princess.
Behold.
Your throne.
Say, you got a bathroom?
- It hurts.
- I know it does.
It won't always.
I'm not my best anymore.
I want to be my best.
I know you do.
How can I be my best now?
Dr. Saunders.
- How can I be my best, please?
- You can't, Victor.
You can't be your best.
Your best is past.
Your past...
You can't even remember.
You're ugly now.
You're disgusting.
All you can hope for now is pity,
and for that,
you're gonna have to look
somewhere else.
Dr. Saunders.
Hello.
Whiskey.
- What do we have here?
- She came back from the engagement
with some shoulder pain.
Have one of these,
and sit right down here
and I'll see what I can do.
You're overworked, dear.
You're too popular
for your own good.
I keep recommending a week of rest.
Our #1 Active?
Boss lady will never
let her lie fallow.
- I try to be my best.
- I'm sure you do.
We have an intake.
All available handlers to the floor.
- You got this?
- Yeah.
Sounds like you're gonna have
another friend.
Friends are nice.
They sure are.
Impressive, no?
This is where you'll spend the majority
of your non-engagement time.
When does the hankering
for tasty brains kick in?
These people are zombies.
We call them Actives.
You'll be served
five-star cuisine here,
and you'll never want for anything.
This isn't the end of your life.
Then why do I feel
like I'm walking to the gallows?
It's five years,
and to you,
it could feel like an instant.
She is sad.
Dr. Saunders is nice.
So this is it.
This is where you steal their souls.
And then we put 'em in a glass jar
with our fireflies.
Why is there a morally, judgmental man
in my imprint room besides him?
Special Agent Ballard
is going to lend us
his inestimable
crime-solving abilities.
Cool.
Say, maybe he can start
with finding the guy who Tasered me.
Pretty sure he led Alpha
right in here.
He can help.
We need to work together if there's
any hope of finding and stopping Alpha.
You know that better than anyone.
You will assist Special Agent Ballard
with his profile.
All hands on deck.
Do I make myself clear?
Good day.
We're ready for our treatments.
- Who the hell is this?
- Couple more decades.
I'll take...
Sierra first.
Hello.
What is this thing anyway?
And what are we gonna do to her?
Everything, nothing.
Not to her. She won't...
be her.
We won't be needing this,
will we, honey?
Wendy is going away.
She won't be here in a minute.
Wait, what, it's like a magic trick?
- We're gonna make her disappear?
- We're gonna stick her in a wedge.
We're gonna wedge her.
I don't get it.
Of course you don't.
How could you?
The mind...
you have been given
is so tiny, so primitive,
that it is incredible you can perform
basic motor functions or form words.
Screw you, Bobby.
Don't listen to him.
You're perfect.
I needed you just like this,
just like this, not afraid of anything,
so we could get out
of that place, make it here.
And you were great.
Jacking that car,
getting that girl.
You were perfect.
I was.
You're always perfect.
Hello, Echo.
Hello, Alpha. Good...
day.
- I'm going to yoga.
- I like you.
You're special.
I try to be my best.
You are the best.
Topher'd like to see you
for a treatment.
I enjoy my treatments.
Thank you.
Go on ahead. I'll catch up.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Hell.
- I don't understand "hell".
- It's what you would have caught
if it had been Dewitt coming
around that corner instead of me.
You'd be on your way
to the Attic by now.
Just watch your step.
I'll do that.
Topher says it's like childbirth.
I think it's more
like watching someone die.
Well, someone's gonna die if my partner
doesn't get her ass out here.
Trail's going cold.
But you're not cold.
Are you, handsome?
What's your story?
Wait. Don't tell me.
You got multiple contracts
on this job?
That's okay.
I like a little stiff competition.
But when it turns out you're not the one
who collects the bounty,
promise you'll hold it against me.
If you're done molesting the furniture,
can we get these guys?
Well, you're still in your pajamas.
She's not screaming anymore.
She's screaming.
They're all screaming.
Must you always defend...
Why can't you ever take my side?
I didn't say nothing.
You always say nothing.
There she is.
Listen.
- Am I supposed to hear something?
- Not yet.
Bobby, you're scaring me.
Little lamb...
what have you got to be afraid of?
I'll tell you what.
There's only one person
that can hurt you now,
just one...
and that's what we're here
to take care of.
Who was he after
the day it happened...
the day of your unfortunate
technological anomaly?
He wasn't after anybody.
It was a random killing spree.
- You're wrong.
- Look...
you can't profile Alpha.
He's not a person.
He's...
he's like Soylent Green.
He's people.
He experienced a composite event...
48 personalities,
not split personalities.
Full, total, complete personalities
got dumped
into his coconut all at once.
- He snapped.
- I believe he snapped.
Who did he target?
Who did he go after first?
His handler.
Half my staff.
Then Dr. Saunders walked in.
- The woman with the scars?
- This is a waste of time.
In a mass killing, the first victims
will often be whoever's in the way.
Who was the first individual
that Alpha went for
the moment he had a choice?
Himself.
The first individual?
He came over here to the self shelf.
It's where I keep my primaries stored.
It's the original personalities
that the volunteers
first walk in with.
He took his original self...
and he smashed the hell out of it.
And you said this time
he took all of Caroline's imprints...
the ones you created?
Where's her original self?
You have a backup, right?
This was the backup.
Where's the original?
Hello, Caroline.
Has it been five years?
What is this?
What am I doing sitting here
and standing over there?
Baby...
meet yourself.
Oh, God, the wrongness
of this is so large.
Whose body is this?
It's just a body.
They're all pretty much the same.
I think this one wet itself.
What did you mean "meet myself"?
This whining, pathetic creature,
this self-hating human...
that was you.
- What?
- She's responsible
for all of the terrible things
you can't remember.
- My brain hurts.
- How do you think my brain...
That is my brain.
I want my brain back.
I want back in my brain.
You should have thought of that
before you vacated the premises.
- I don't even know this girl.
- Do you know why?
- 'Cause we never met?
- Because she abandoned you.
She walked out on you
when you needed her most.
Time's got a little tough.
The road got a little rocky,
seas got a little choppy,
and she thought...
"I'll go to sleep.
"Night-night.
"See you in five years."
She left you
to the jackals, to the wolves.
To the predators.
Isn't that right, Caroline?
She said
that I would be taken care off,
and that I would be safe.
Do you feel safe?
Do you?
You feel safe?
Safe, do you feel?
What do you feel?
Confused.
I'm with her.
You are her.
But you don't have to be.
You can ascend.
You can evolve.
It's in you. I've seen it.
And I can help you, baby,
just like I always have.
She was never there
when you needed her.
But I was.
I like trees.
Someone's getting a treatment.
Whiskey, would you like a treatment?
- Yes, please.
- All right.
Tidy your station, and then
you may go with Sophie, Whiskey.
That girl keeps getting sent out.
- She's never gonna finish the tree.
- And it's a small tree.
That's my girl.
What can I say?
Most requested Doll in the house.
- #1.
- Really?
Whiskey?
Let Echo be #1.
How?
- How did this happen?
- I don't know. I don't know.
Some residual memory, inactive neurons
from a previous engagement.
All I can do is run
a full-range diagnostic.
I'm bringing up every
last one of his prior builds,
see if anything matches.
You don't leave this room
until it's done,
and when you've finished,
send him to the Attic.
I don't understand.
Was I not my best?
I was making art.
Alpha, you need to settle, okay?
You need a treatment.
A treatment.
Please, I...
I need a treatment.
That's good.
That's good. He's good.
He's down. Thanks.
- I need a treatment.
- Yes, you do.
You surely do.
- I enjoy my treatments.
- Then you're gonna love this one.
It's kind of a greatest hits.
I need some help.
Come here. Come here!
- What have you got?
- He's frying!
You're gonna be okay.
Shut it down!
I understand hell now.
My God, Topher,
what the hell's going on here?
48 personalities,
each with its own rich history,
and none of it tells me anything.
Who's Alpha?
Alpha is all of these.
That's what I keep saying.
And... And of course
it doesn't tell you anything.
It doesn't tell me anything,
and I'm smarter
than everyone in this room.
But less scary.
I know you're all very invested
in your vaunted technology,
and it is very impressive,
but I still don't believe
you can wipe away a person's soul.
Their what?
Their soul.
Who they are at their core.
I don't think that goes away.
You'd be wrong about that.
I wanna know who Alpha was!
Who was he before in private life?
That is not relevant.
With all respect,
one of Alpha's first acts
after compositing
was to destroy his original self.
We should know who that was.
All right.
I still have about 19 personality builds
to reassemble
so I can try and figure out
which of Echo's imprints
Alpha used on her, so...
good luck with the whole God thing.
Do not let him
do this to you, please.
You don't even know
what it is I'm doing.
It's not good.
I know that.
I've been in that chair.
It hurts.
Just for a minute.
- You won't remember.
- I remember.
It still smells
like burnt hair in here.
He's going to make me
a superior creature.
An ascended being.
Do you even know what that means?
Do you?
- So, you're not better than me.
- Look where you are.
You're in a lair, an evil lair.
You're sitting in some messed-up
dentist's chair letting a guy
who talks to himself attach
wires to your head, which, incidentally,
is my head.
Open.
Bite down.
Good.
Go ahead.
Keep talking.
I want you to.
We all do.
This is how it shall be.
She will ascend.
She will know.
And then she will kill you.
What?!
- Why?
- Because...
that's what we need.
A blood ritual.
Yes, yes,
we've got to have one of those.
I mean, the Aztecs knew it.
The pre-Hellenic Minoans knew it,
for God's sakes.
From the moment man first clawed
his way out of the primordial ooze
and kicked off his fins,
he's understood
that the gods require blood.
New life from death.
The ancients had it right.
But the old gods are back.
Alpha?
Meet Omega.
No way!
Get out!
God.
Gods.
I get it.
Now...
I knew you would.
Now I understand everything.
Carl William Craft.
Three names... always ominous.
When the Rossum Corporation first began
its investigations into neural science,
some of our recruits were furnished
by the Department of Corrections.
You experimented on prisoners?
We offered the opportunity
to trade lengthy prison sentences
for five-year terms of service
with us.
- What was he in for?
- Kidnapping, attempted murder.
- He never actually killed anybody yet.
- Not until he came here.
Based on what I'm reading, this man was
well on his way to becoming Ted Bundy.
You have no proof of that.
The only reason he didn't kill anybody
is because the victim got away.
When they finally picked up Craft,
they found a murder kit in his car.
- He was evolving.
- So, there's a living witness.
- You wanna drive?
- I can.
We're confused.
You hit me with a pipe.
Yeah? Call me Omega again,
and you'll get some more.
Something must have gone wrong
with the composite.
Nothing went wrong.
Every imprint this Active has ever had
is alive and awake in her head now.
Then why did you hit me in the head
with a pipe?!
It was handy?
And you wanted me to kill myself?!
I wanted you to kill her!
Her is me.
You made that very clear.
Her is the old you.
Try and keep up!
I'm way ahead of you.
You think we're gods?
We're not just humans anymore.
We're not multiple personalities.
We're many personalities.
And one of my personalities
happens to be a multiple personality,
but that doesn't make me
a multiple personality.
- I'm looking for a little nuance here.
- We're not gods.
Fine!
Übermensch.
Nietzsche predicted our rise.
Perfected, objective,
something new.
Right.
New, superior people
with a little German thrown in.
What could possibly go wrong?
We're not new.
We're not anything.
We're not anybody
because we're everybody.
I mean, I get it.
I understand it.
I'm experiencing
like 38 of them right now.
But I somehow understand
that not one of them is me.
I can slip into one.
Actually, it slips into me.
They had to make room for it.
They hollowed me out.
There is no me.
I'm just...
a container.
There's a you.
She's right here.
He may be crazy, but he's right.
You walked away from me.
You left me alone in that place.
Why did you do that?
It's complicated.
Sweetheart,
however complicated you thought
our life was before,
you cannot tell me...
How's that for a complication?
So, let me ask you something.
It's pretty obvious you're police.
How did you end up
working for these people?
Could ask you the same question.
I'm not working for them.
I'm just trying to save the girl.
There's always a girl.
427.
Anita Walsh.
Hello?
Miss Walsh?
Who's asking?
Special Agent Paul Ballard, FBI.
I'm sorry. I know it's early,
but there's an urgent situation
you may be able to help us with.
We gotta ask you a few questions.
It's about Carl Craft.
I don't have strangers in my home.
I'm just leaving for work.
I'll come down.
You do realize what we're doing
to this woman?
Resurrecting a nightmare.
And maybe for no good reason.
Whoever Carl Craft was
may have nothing to do with who...
... Alpha is.
Agent Ballard.
How may I help you?
You don't know what you're doing.
What you're giving up!
Right. Why would I want to live
in a luxurious spa-like environment
when I could live here with you?
I thought you were different!
I thought you were exceptional.
I was wrong. You're weak.
I may not know who I am,
but at least I know who I'm not.
I'm not you're girlfriend.
You okay?
I kick ass.
Who are you?
I'm Echo.
And who is that?
She's nobody.
I'm just the porch light,
waiting for you.
You have to put me back.
You have to put me back
in that wedge.
'Cause we need to get...
Wendy back in her body.
Why do you have to go back
in the wedge?
Why don't you come home?
I did sign a contract.
I have 38 brains.
Not one of them thinks
you can sign a contract to be a slave,
especially now that we have
a black president.
We have a black president?
I am missing everything.
Let's do this.
Now, do what I say...
or I will blow your brain out.
What's this? Background singer?
Background singer, ninja girl?
I don't know why Alpha would imprint her
as a background singer
unless he was starting an evil band.
Next.
- This is Topher.
- Topher. Question.
When Alpha was an Active,
did he ever have any engagements
that ended up in Pedro?
He had a lot of engagements, Boyd.
Can you be more specific?
When Alpha was a civilian,
he abducted a woman.
Kept her captive for three days
in some sort of defunct power plant.
She escaped.
Cops picked her up on the highway.
Get me Whiskey 1.1.
Too traumatized to find her way
back there,
but it was somewhere in San Pedro.
Actually... yes.
There was one engagement.
He slipped his handler.
It was a double.
He was with Whiskey 1.1.
It took us a while to get a lock
on his location.
Wasn't a place we'd been before.
It was a bit off perimeter.
It explains why you bounty-hunters
haven't turned up anything.
San Pedro. Industrial road 7-18.
Thanks, Topher.
He's using an old Whiskey imprint.
Get in the chair.
What are you gonna do?
Wipe me?
No, I'm gonna put her in you.
That's what you wanted, isn't it?
- Of course, then I'm gonna kill you!
- That's a little elaborate.
Then why don't you just shoot me
and the damn wedge?
I'm not gonna shoot the wedge.
I'm going to keep the wedge.
I'm going to use the wedge.
And I'm going to grab
Wendys and Beckys and Stacys
from all over this great nation,
and every one of them
will be a Caroline.
And every one one of them
will get carved up
and their throat cut
until I get bored.
So, get in the chair!
You like knives.
And scissors.
You like to cut things, don't you?
Whiskey.
You cut up that poor girl
because of me.
For you. It was for you.
Save it!
Don't hand me any more of your crap
about you being
some superior ascended being.
To ascend to anything, at minimum,
you don't cut up women!
- Lay back in the chair.
- You lay back in the chair.
I'm done laying back in the chair!
I'm ready to rinse and spit.
I will shoot it.
I will blast the wedge!
So blast it. What's stopping you,
Edward Scissor Pud?
I'm not fooling.
He's not kidding!
We're not bluffing.
I'm bluffing.
But the rest of us...
we mean business.
I said shoot it!
I don't care.
Yeah? Well, maybe she will.
She won't know.
She's me.
And we're both coming to get ya.
Wanna bet it's stolen?
He's up there.
- Caroline's up there!
- I see.
You wanna save the girl?
Go get her.
You saved her.
Dr. Saunders?
I think you gave me
more computer skills
than would be required
by a medical doctor.
It was very easy for me
to hack your system.
I'm curious.
About?
I guess I understand
why they wouldn't
wanna waste an investment.
And I suppose,
why hire a new physician
when you can just...
imprint the broken Doll.
But why did you decide
it was so important for me to hate you?
I think that's strange.
You didn't open it.
Aren't you curious to see
who you really are?
I know who I am.
So he continues to elude us.
He does.
And the poor child at the warehouse?
An anonymous source
is providing generously for her family.
It's cold comfort.
We'll find him.
I have confidence now.
Our new contractor...
has the skills to inspire it.
I don't work for you yet.
Remember our deal.
The young lady's freedom
has been granted.
- With full payment on her contract.
- Of course.
Send her in.
Come in, my dear.
I just have a few things
for you to sign.
And then our business
will be completed.
Thank you.
Did I fall asleep?
For a little while.
Okay, you can go now.
Thank you.
It was so easy.
- I feel like I just got here.
- Of course.
Thanks again.
Good-bye.
Excuse me.
Shall I go now?
If you like.
I don't think I got your name.
Madeline.
Madeline Costley.
That's a lovely name.
And you are?
I'm nobody.
Caroline.