Previously on Dollhouse:
She's a risk. An increasing risk.
She had control over the situation.
But we can't control her.
No. Stay away from me! No.
No!
please...
There are three flowers in a vase.
The third flower is green.
And our sleeper active
performed perfectly.
I replayed the tap.
More than once.
It did not lack for poetry.
You.
I only have a few minutes.
They can't know this
body left an engagement.
Are we not fighting this time?
I have a message for you
from inside the Dollhouse.
What? Sit back and wait some
more while they dismantle my life?
I could handcuff you right now
and bring the dollhouse to my door.
So, you tell me, who sent you?
You have something we need.
I have something you need.
And what is that?
I'm not a client. I don't need that.
You know you do.
Caroline?
Save me, Paul.
- Oh, god.
- Oh, my god.
Mellie.
I guess I took too long getting back.
You're already with A... her.
I know this is confusing for all of us.
Don't stop, Paul. I need you.
Paul!
I'm sorry. I have a thing she needs.
She's not even real!
You feel me. Trust that.
I need you to finish what you started.
Caroline doesn't need anything
anymore, Paul. She's dead!
No. Caroline? Come back.
I won't let anything
happen to you. Not again.
You let them hurt me, didn't you?
No. I tried to stop it.
How did they know?
I'm trying to stop everything.
How do they know what we shared?
How do they know?
We're all aware there
have been recent problems.
Ours is a complicated world.
But the world of our actives
must be one of constant certainty.
Did you guys start early?
I-I was, uh, backing up my
primary drives to protect them...
from that.
As Topher points out, we are currently
upgrading our electrical and security systems.
We will be instituting
other changes as well.
We have had an active go off mission.
Another has developed urges. Others still are
showing signs of cognizance or recognition.
Nearly all the actives exposed to the n-7316
drug experienced a glitch, a random memory thread.
This house is out of balance.
For the handlers, the main concern
will be identifying behavioral problems
that cannot be quelled
and reporting them.
It's easy to become attached
to your assigned active.
In fact, it's necessary, but
don't think of them as children.
Think of them as pets.
Is that supposed to be funny?
If your child starts talking for
the first time, you feel proud.
If your dog does, you
freak the hell out.
Any developmental progress an active
makes is dangerous to the house,
and a possible first
step toward another alpha.
What about the alpha
that's already an alpha?
Whereabouts unknown.
Let's stay on topic. Topher?
I've scrubbed them as
much as I safely can.
If we pursued the short-range
calcium modulin k2 amplifier,
I could advance the protein's
corrosion of long-term potentiation.
Done, whatever that
means. Anything else?
The sleep cycle.
The sedatives and anti-psychotics we pump into the
pods with the o2, the subliminal tone patterns...
I think I could...
play with that cocktail a bit.
Sleeping is their most vulnerable time.
We could test it out on one chamber
if you're stressed about it...
If you start playing with their meds,
it could backfire or damage them.
Or solve the problem.
I know what I'm doing, doc.
So do I.
But I also care what
you're doing. To our pets.
I will take this into consideration.
I need reports at the end of every shift
detailing your interactions with the actives:
feelings they express, questions they
ask, instincts you observe. Everything.
We can't jump at shadows.
I don't want to report that my active asked
for toast and have her sent to the attic.
We were hired to protect them.
In the field, yes, mr. Langton.
In here, we protect the house.
A tide is rising.
Until we learn how to turn it back,
we pile up the sandbags together.
Unless anyone here thinks
they've got a better idea.
Caroline, I'm Paul Ballard.
I'm with the FBI.
Your name is Caroline.
You don't know this, but
you're being fooled, you're being used.
I will never hurt you.
Do you trust me? Do you
want to play the game?
You remember to be very
quiet during the game, right?
Caroline, wake up.
Help.God. Oh, god.
Help me! Help me, somebody, please!
Help me, somebody!
Somebody get me out of here!
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Dollhouse
Season01 Episode08
Oh, my god, help me! Get me out of here!
Help! Help me!
Who's there?
Who the hell are you?
I woke up in a five-star floor
coffin just like you, pal.
Help! Help me!
Let me out! Let me out!
- Let me out!
- Noise. Not helping.
Doesn't matter. They're listening.
Anyone hear me over here? Help!
- You okay?
- Who's listening?
Aliens.
Pervs behind glass
getting off watching us.
Yeah, we're in outer space, right?
We're in a nuthouse, more like.
What humans you know build circular pod rooms
with stone cavities and peeping windows?
Definitely feeling
kind of lab-ratty here.
I'm leaving before the electric shock.
Sorry. It's a defense mechanism.
I'm just really terrified.
Anybody else got anything
better than aliens?
I'm serious about lab rats.
- Maybe we're supposed to be here.
- What for? I didn't do anything.
Do you know that?
I don't remember anything.
I mean, I know the days of the week, the
capital of Nebraska, but nothing about me.
My guess: We're prisoners of some sort.
We need to assess the situation,
formulate a strategy...
Run.
Strategically.
Yeah, and when they come in
with guns, what do we fight with?
We take the glass shade off the light
fixtures, splinter them. Use them as shivs.
Deranged millionaire serial
killer. That's what I think.
That's not stupider than aliens?
Hey, watch your mouth.
Hey, can we all act like
humans and not monkeys?
I know you, don't I?
How?
I think I have to get to the mountains.
Everything's okay there.
I lost something.
Maybe it's here somewhere.
They probably want to study
our reproductive systems.
Sex with aliens?
Come on. Who doesn't wanna
put alien guy back in the box?
What's behind me?
It's okay. Just walk towards me.
Someone's out there.
A lot of someones.
It's been very nice nearly
knowing you guys. Good luck.
Hey, hey, hold up. You need backup.
I want to know what they look like.
I'm not sure I do.
Hey, we gotta get moving. I don't
wanna leave you behind, please!
- They're people like us.
- But so calm.
Maybe they know why we're here.
See? I think they like it.
So do we, like it like them. Got it?
What we don't want is
to get noticed, so...
until we know what's going on...
Good morning, Tango.
Good morning, Victor. Sierra, Mike.
Hi, November, your clothes
are in the changing room.
How are you, Echo?
Fine, thank you.
- That's not my name.
- Not names, codes. Military.
Who uses those besides...
are we government prisoners?
Everyone does look peaceful.
Maybe something bad happened to us.
And they're helping us heal.
That makes sense.
Good morning. We're having banana
pancakes for breakfast today.
I like pancakes.
We're all gonna die.
I like bananas.
They're naturally sweet.
They're high in potassium.
So's the earth's core.
But that's not food.
No, it isn't, Mike.
A food that's naturally sweet.
Apples, cantaloupe, uh,
kiwis, mango, mayonnaise.
Echo, is there something
wrong with your hand?
No, it's fine.
I don't think so. May I see it?
I'm going to need to take
you to see dr. Saunders now.
Hello?
Echo, what's wrong?
Uh, they made me come
see you. About my hand.
Oh, no, what happened?
Oh, my god!
Did they do that to you here?
Echo, please, sit.
No, I want to know.
What the hell happened?
Don't... they're watching.
You work for them. Who
are they? Where are we?
Please.
I'm not your friend in here, Echo.
I'm sorry. I can't help you.
I'm happy! I'm happy! Guys,
I'm relaxed and I'm happy!
I like banana pancakes.
I want to climb the rock wall now!
Isn't that what you want?
Tell me and I'll do it!
- Please, help!
- Let me.
Help! Somebody help me!
No...
Mike screwed up. Got
noticed. Nothing we could do.
He might be okay. The
doctor said she'd help.
- She did?
- You told her?
She knows we're not like the others?
She warned me. About the cameras.
Keep walking.
Coed showers? I don't believe it.
But we have to do it.
So, no big deal.
Okay, new york starting lineup,
1986, first base:Keith Hernandez;
second base: Wally Backman;
shortstop: Rafael Santana.
Keep your eyes right where they are.
Mookie Wilson: Left field...
third base: Ray Knight; catcher: Gary
Carter: Center field:Lenny Dykstra.
Hey, hey, it's Mike.
Hey, pal. You all right?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- Thank god. What happened to you?
I had a treatment.
Just a spa thing, nothing bad?
Did you see the doctor?
Dr. Saunders? She's so nice.
I was trying to tell these guys,
I think she's a prisoner, like us.
No cameras here. No one's watching.
Mike? Do you remember me? Lab rat?
Yes, you're Echo.
We woke up together,
trapped. We were scared.
I like sleeping in the pods.
Wait, where are you going?
I'm going to swim in the pool.
No, Mike, we're all gonna leave.
Come with us.
I do 30 laps every day.
It helps me be my best.
We lost Mike.
We save ourselves and we do it now.
I'm with her.
Okay.
Yes, mr. Dominic?
I was just informed we have
four actives preparing to escape.
Right on schedule.
Will you at least allow me to
brief the in-house security team?
The entire staff thinks they're preparing
for an exercise two months down the road.
They're not ready.
Every person in this house should
always be ready. For anything.
Echo, Sierra, Victor, and November
need real adversaries, real obstacles.
Freedom has to be earned.
We don't even have
the power to end this.
There's no kill switch;
we can't shut them down.
What if they make it out into the world and decide
to shoot up a liquor store and jump off a roof?
Don't be melodramatic.
We could lose them all.
And there's a limit to what I'll
be able to clean up after the fact.
I've made my decision.
I forgot where the sauna is.
You told me.
I like the sauna.
Big surprise there.
He's very tired.
So, the light at the
end of the tunnel was...
Another tunnel.
No need to be aware of anything but
your breath moving through your body.
Tango... would you
like your treatment now?
It's time.
Come on. Right here.
Did something happen to them?
What's taking them so long?
They're just being careful is all.
We'll give them a little bit more time.
Why don't you tell me
something about yourself?
I'm just making small talk.
We don't remember anything, remember?
Sometimes I feel like we... we do.
The yankees.
The mets, but whatever. And you.
Are you sure?
Can you tell me anything about me?
I just got this feeling
in my gut that...
something bad happened to you.
Probably the same something
bad that happened to all of us.
I don't feel that way
about anyone else. Just you.
Is there any part of you
that... finds me... familiar?
- It's them.
- Thank god.
Nobody saw us, but who
knows what the cameras got.
Or who's watching them.
Sophie. You're off, too?
After a few hours of paperwork
to wrap up the client's file.
What kind of engagement were you on?
I can't believe you are cheating on me
with that perfect woman you just met.
Now I get everything in the divorce.
Easy stuff.
Seems tame next to the crap
you've been dealing with.
Echo's all right. They're just
giving her a few days' downtime.
I can use the vacation.
Ask me, she's not gonna last.
I haven't given up on her yet.
Look, Boyd, you're a classy guy, but
you really shouldn't get too attached.
It's like mr. Dominic
said. They're pets.
Even a good dog needs
to be put down sometimes.
Stairwell ends this level.
There's got to be another.
What's wrong? Look at me... look.
Tell me. What's wrong?
Keep an eye on the hall.
I remember... men.
They had guns. They took me away.
I remember the man who put me here.
Then, we'll get him, understand?
I will get him, but you got to be strong for me
now and go with us, so you can help me find him.
Still no windows. We
got to be underground.
We need to find another way.
This just keeps getting
weirder and weirder.
- What is all this for?
- Us.
These all say "Echo".
There's a rack for each of us.
Yeah, there is.
We can blend in more now.
This fits perfectly.
Yeah. Maybe these are
clothes from our former life.
Never mind. Let's go right now.
I thought we were getting changed first.
I have a daughter. Katie.
Okay. We'll get you out of here.
What's wrong?
She has a daughter.
Please help me find her.
I don't know where she is.
Someone's coming.
Who has the card thingy?
What did you just do?
- Call the elevator.
- What if somebody's in it?
We don't have a choice, do we?
Go up or go back. Anyone going back?
I can't believe we made it.
Start checking doors; see
if any of them are unlocked.
We need to tell someone
about what's happening.
Should we call the police, the FBI?
For all we know, this is the FBI.
What about everybody
inside that needs help?
We do nothing till we understand what
this place is and who we can trust.
Guys, car's coming.
When you wear the uniform, you
got to push it all down, bury it.
It never happened, right?
The good guys lost one today.
I had to watch a man die, and I'm
just supposed to make it disappear?
Guys, wait here.
Did you hear that? Someone died.
He said he was one of the good guys.
But he went in there. How
do we know who to trust?
We trust each other. We figure this out
together. We start with what we know.
You know your name's not Sierra.
And the guy that put you
here, what's his name?
I-I don't know.
No, you do know. What's his name?
His name...
his name...
his name is Nolan.
See?
And you know Katie, your daughter.
And you're gonna think hard and
remember where to find her, right?
And I know a mountain
house. It's safe there.
I need to go there.
Guys, look sharp. Wheels up.
Look out!
You know I don't understand
when you speak french.
Tango?
Let's get out of here.
On your toes, people.We
have a black suv,
license plate number 386pce embarking
with the following four actives:
Victor, Sierra, November, and Echo.
Here we go.
Wait.
What are you doing? What's wrong?
Get back in the car!
I can't leave.
Did you see Tango, that sweet girl?
That is not a costume
warehouse we just busted out of.
That's a people warehouse.
You have to come with us.
The army guy they brought back...
they're doing it both ways.
They make people go out and do terrible things,
and then bring them back and make them go away.
And you'll be putting
yourself back in there.
You didn't fight to get out for nothing.
Not nothing. You guys are okay
now. I go back in knowing that.
This thing-- it's too big. There's too many of them.
They got guns. What do you think you're gonna do?
Try and make a difference.
Echo. What are you doing here?
Don't touch that.
It's okay. I'm just gonna call Boyd.
Remember Boyd, your handler?
You know him. You trust him.
- I said don't touch it.
- Okay.
Uh, I'm a friend of his. Maybe I
can help. Do you know what you need?
Give me the key.
No one here wants to hurt you, Echo.
I don't want to hurt you.
I'm just gonna tell Boyd you're here, and he'll
come and take you for your treatment. All right?
You Jimmy?
Good day to you, too.
Ever seen one of these?
Uh, yeah. Just now, on
the counter in front of me.
I really hope you don't want to pretend
you don't butter your bread this way,
'cause I'm not in a
mood that's gonna care.
I'm just trying to figure out what
kind of business you think you got here.
Look at it.
Look. Any closer, and it will
come out of the back of my head.
This don't even exist yet.
Meaning what?
Meaning, if me and everyone else I know
powwowed, we still wouldn't figure this out.
It's gorgeous.
Can I trace where it was transmitting?
Absolutely. If you were E.T.
It inverts the frequency
into white noise.
The only way you could find it once
it hits the universe is to know exactly
which speck of dust you're
looking for and tune in on it.
What about scrambling it?
Someone put this on you? Huh?
You're gonna need an rf detector,
smart scrambler, and frequency jammer.
And to believe in god, 'cause I
don't care how big you think you are.
They're bigger.
Can't remember which way to go until I see
it, but I'm pretty sure we're almost there.
You've been saying that for 20
minutes while I've been circling.
I know. I'm so sorry.
- Stop the car.
- What?
- I know where Katie is.
- You do?
That's wonderful!
Let me out here.
Can I take you there after
we deal with this guy Nolan?
She says we're almost there.
I'm going alone.
We can't just leave you here.
Until we figure things
out, we should stick together.
Help each other.
I remember my life.
- You're sure?
- Yes.
All right then. It's why we left.
We decide for ourselves now.
Good luck.
You, too.
I hope it's easy for
you to go back home.
Whatever it is.
Well, let's get a tail on her.
November separated from the group.
Is that an active leaving
dr. Saunders' office?
Rewind it.
Oh, my god.
She was in the car.
Apparently she's got
one step ahead of us.
I should've seen this
coming. This is Caroline.
Minus the memories, but it's her and
this is exactly what Caroline would do.
Try and take us down by herself.
You want me to call it in? Round her up?
No, there's no harm in
letting this play out.
Caroline never was very realistic.
Apparently, this is
exactly what she was...
- Stop her?
- Immediately, please.
This is mr. Dominic. We have a rogue
active. Check the power room first.
Topher. Status.
Hard to see. Some confusion.
Are the actives afraid of the dark?
Who knows? They've never seen
it. We always leave the lights on.
Is this that power thing
from yesterday or...
- Echo.
- Really?
Did she cut the main line
or did she go for the...
Can you find her?
I'm looking out the window, but am
hindered by a lack of illumination.
Just be ready when they bring her in.
To do what?
No power, no chair. No wipey.
I am, btw.
Am what?
Afraid of the dark.
Hello?
Echo?
Not anymore.
We're experiencing a temporary
interruption of power.
We assure you there is no need to worry.
Everyone please gather
calmly on the main floor.
We should probably go
downstairs with everybody else...
Is that blood on your hands?
It's kinda dark. I was
hoping that it was...
Tell me what you do to people in here.
They come in one way and when
they leave, they're something else.
It's complicated. But...
I use a process of epifluorescent light.
Make it simple.
Simple, right.
I put them in a chair
and I program them.
You can't program people.
We're not freakin' computers.
Not that different.
Our-our brains are
natural motherboards.
Everything we think, feel, do:
electrical impulses fired by the brain.
I just hack the system.
What year is this?
2009.
How long have I been here?
A little while.
A day? A month?
Kind of more.
My head. Why I don't remember things.
You've done it to me. You
put me in this... chair.
Where?
Show. Don't tell.
Priya.
I'm surprised, uh, and confused.
Is this, uh, some kind of
frequent buyer reward or...
It's him.
Hey, what's going on?
A little blackmail, maybe? I
wouldn't put it past you people.
What you did to me
putting me in that hell.
What did I ever do to you?
You said no. And, uh,
nobody ever says no to me.
Because I wouldn't have
sex with you, you...
you took away my whole life?
Do you have any idea how
much trouble that was?
I mean, all the strings I pulled, and the palms
I greased, I could've bought pierre island.
But owning you is
better than real estate.
So, uh, you're not her handler.
We got out of that freak
show. She's never going back.
Ah, I get it. You kids hopped the fence.
It doesn't matter.
You don'exist anymore.
I'm more of a person than you.
Honey, you're programmed to give me
and-and anyone else whatever we want
whenever we want it.
Which...
you do with pleasure.
And sometimes, you even beg.
Okay.
I can afford one hell of
a security system, so...
I have one. All right, folks were on their way
to grab you up before you hit the elevator, so.
- Go.
- We got to go.
You will see me again.
Yes, and I look forward to it.
This way.
It'll be even better now.
You put this in and it makes us...
whatever you want?
Yes.
I mean, you have to have power
to do that, uh, electricity,
which we don't.So we can't.
You should put that down.
This is seriously screwed.
What the hell is wrong with you people?
We're good people. Nice people.
We help people become better people
by giving them what they need.
I don't usually do the sales pitch.
You murder people. You gut them and
use their bodies as playthings.
Who was I before you killed me?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You are not dead, clearly.
You volunteered.
- You're lying.
- Okay.
You don't have your memories.
I didn't give them to you
so you don't remember that.
In there. Last time you put
me in there you made me what?
You as you were when you came
here only without memories,
which you will get back
when your contract is up
and you leave here and go
and do whatever you want.
Grow a belly, sew a quilt, spend
that truck of money you made having...
wow, just the time of your life.
Yeah, this is fun.
Isn't it?
Why am I not like them,
the rest down there--
what they're like when
you're not pimping them out?
We're running a test on you.
I remember a mountain.
Somewhere peaceful. Beautiful.
I feel happy there. I want to go there.
Is that real or is
that part of your test?
Real.
How come it's there if
you didn't give it to me?
It's coming from you.
It's what you need.
I have your memories.
You can have them back.
- You can do that?
- Totally.
But I have to go in there.
Well, yeah, but...
- Okay.
You first.
- Who are they?
- Maybe Nolan's guys.
- What do they want?
- Take us back, probably.
Or kill us.
That's the only way out.
This way.
Hey, it looks like it fits.
You can't imprint on top of a fully
functional brain; it'll implode.
Oh, is that why you keep us so simple?
Yes. Yes.
Does it hurt when you do it?
Pain is nothing more than
nerves talking to your brain.
Look, I'm just the science guy.
Up here looking down on
everyone, playing god.
I can help you with anything you want.
You just have to tell me.
I want you to let them go.
I don't have that kind of power.
What... No.
I'd pick the chair.
It's just a treatment.
God, no, no, no, no, no!
I can't. I swear I can't.
I can.
Stop the imprint, please.
My chair!
Did I just kill someone, or
should I aim this at her head?
She doesn't really understand.
You wanted to forget.
Who are you?
Adelle DeWitt.
I am responsible for this
facility and everyone in it.
Then, you are one sick bitch.
I eased your suffering.
Is that what you think
you're doing here?
I'm certain of it.
Taking away basic human rights...
free will...
my right to choose, feel, remember.
All relinquished by you
to our care and discretion.
Tell me why I would.
I can't.
I'd be breaking a promise I made to you.
All I can say is that...
you couldn't live with the consequences of
your own actions, and you no longer have to.
You're letting us all go.
You're free to leave.
Who are you to decide for the others?
Something you should
have been asking yourself.
I made the same promise to them to protect them
from the unbearable truths that brought them here.
I won't return those memories.
So, we agree. No one gets in the chair.
They'll be back.
Maybe.
I'm sorry. This is all my fault.
If you didn't want to help me,
this wouldn't have happened.
Exactly.
When we were in that place, when
were like what Mike turned into,
but the rest of them
were empty I remember you.
What?
It's like I'm stuck inside my head somewhere,
and some part of me sees and feels...
it's like a bad dream
I can't get out of. I...
I can't talk. I can't move.
I can't be stronger than what's
taken me over, but I'm there.
It's so awful.
Somebody hurt you... like Nolan.
I could see it happening.
Oh, god, I could see his
face, but I couldn't stop it.
I trusted him.
Why did I trust him?
- I'm sorry.
- Wait... wait.
You wait for me when we go to bed
at night to make sure I'm okay.
What have they done to us?
I don't know which to hope for.
Feels like dying either way.
No.
We'll look for each
other like we always do.
We'll finish this. We will.
You can't take them outside as they are.
They'll find the stimulation, the
conflict entirely overwhelming.
They'll do just fine.
Your unbearable truth, lady...
you're not as important
as you think you are.
Next one goes where your
heart should have been.
Now show us out.
A tide is rising.
And until we learn how to turn it
back, we pile up the sandbags together.
Unless anyone here thinks
they've got a better idea.
We give them what they need.
Dr. Saunders.
Closure.
If actives have particularly poignant
or reoccurring experiences,
these can cause desires--
emotional needs--
or reactivate old ones that
existed before they came here.
Open loops.
If they were able to close those
loops, to get some sense of resolve...
You're recommending we allow them
to take a self-guided journey.
Just the priority cases.
Let the tide come in.
It's the only way to wash it back out.
Has the tide turned?
Are they better now?
Each active's brain was programmed to release
a sedative the moment they felt closure.
They're all back with us, so...
I have to assume they've resolved
the issues that caused them to glitch.
November needed to grieve for
her daughter. I understand that.
And Sierra...
she needed to confront the
man who took away her power.
One of them anyway.
As I recall, you
confronted the other one.
And Echo. She wanted to free us all.
What about Victor?
He wasn't going back to a
trauma or need from his past.
He had a more present need.
He needed to get the girl.
He's in love.
When Echo was leading them out,
I would like to have seen that.
Even if it was all a game. Your game.
Do you think I had fun?
I don't know you very well.
You have to look after Echo.
I have to look after all of them.
She wasn't leading them to freedom.
She was leading them to a world of terror
and chaos that would have destroyed them.
She's not leading them anywhere anymore.
You should be grateful.
Yeah. I'll work on that.
Paul Ballard, this is...
you don't know me, but I have a file.
And your name is in it, and I think we've met.
- I know it sounds crazy.
- Caroline.
But we're here, somewhere underground.
I'm trying to get everyone
out, but if I can't, please...
please find us.