Would you like a treatment?
I was just...
sitting because I'm...
tired.
Life of a handler
is pretty exhausting.
Better you than me.
- You just off shift?
- For a few hours.
Can't really seem to sleep, though.
- It's hard to imagine Echo being...
- Did you touch this?
I didn't...
It's not a toy, Ballard.
Leave the tech to the grown-ups.
So, Echo...
- it's good, right?
- It's different.
Not the romance,
- the other protocol.
- I'm not gonna lie to you.
I kind of blew my own mind
this time.
One special client request,
one minor change
to Echo's bodily functions,
and I just opened up
a whole new world for us.
It's all still new to me.
Yeah, but this...
I made code for the brain...
that changed the physical body.
And I'm not talking about...
muscle memory so somebody can...
play fancy piano.
I made changes on a glandular level.
Do you have any idea
what this could mean?
Explain it to me.
Arguably,
one could program the brain to...
fight cancer.
Or be telekinetic.
Or not have that gag reflex
when you eat sea urchin.
Or whatever.
The possibilities
are pretty much endless
is what I'm saying.
I don't want to use
the word "genius",
but I'd be okay if you wanted to.
So you could do all that to me
with this chair?
Not you.
To an Active.
I can't fiddle with a mind
until it's wiped clean.
The human mind is like Van Halen.
If you just pull out one piece
and keep replacing it,
it just degenerates.
I don't understand.
But it's so cute that you're trying.
Good talk!
Say hi to Echo for me.
Tell her we're all very proud.
I thought I heard you.
Don't wake Daddy.
There, you...
Hush, little baby,
don't say a word
Mama's gonna buy you a mockingbird
And if that mockingbird don't sing
Mama's gonna buy you a diamond ring.
Episode 202: Instinct
v. 1.00
www.subbercafe.fr
Okay, little man.
Mommy needs
to mainline some caffeine.
So you just chill there for one sec.
Babe, you want coffee?
Nate, you in there?
Good morning.
You're up early.
Everything all right?
Yeah, it's fine. I'm good.
Okay. I said good morning.
Jack and I were gonna go
to the park today and feed the duckies.
That sounds fun.
You guys should do that.
You could play hooky and join us.
Yeah... I don't think so.
Could you grab him
while I finish the coffee?
I don't...
Here, you're not gonna break him.
He's not gonna bite you
or spontaneously combust.
You've got a master's degree in finance.
This should be a piece of cake.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I don't...
You know...
I'm gonna be late for work.
Nate, wait.
- Will you be home for dinner?
- Nah, I've got that Prentiss thing.
You shouldn't wait up. Bye.
Then he was supposed to take Jack
for a play date with the neighbors,
and at the last minute,
he's got another meeting as usual.
Nate's a workaholic, Em.
He's always been that way.
It's more than that.
It's like I hand him the baby,
and he acts like I've handed
him a live grenade.
Well, men are all wusses.
He's the one who pushed
having kids right away.
I wanted to wait a couple of years.
Tell him he has help out.
You can't raise this baby alone.
He helps.
Changes the diapers,
shops, does the laundry.
He's even read all the books.
Okay, now I just wanna swap.
I can't believe
how much I love this little boy.
And I don't even know
if Nate likes him.
Or me, for that matter.
Nate's crazy about you.
I think he's having an affair.
When was the last time
you had a full night's sleep?
- I don't even remember.
- You're exhausted.
Your hormones
are all over the place.
This isn't hormones.
He's never home.
He works all day,
and almost every night
he's got dinner or drinks.
And then when he is home,
he's always taking phone calls outside
- so I don't hear what he's saying.
- That doesn't mean affair.
Then maybe he's doing
something illegal.
What?
- Why would you think that?
- I've noticed this black van
parked outside the house every day.
We're being watched.
No one is watching you, Emily.
You're sleep-deprived,
and it's making you a little nuts.
Look,
some guys take a little longer
to get used to the idea of being a dad.
- But it gets better.
- You sure?
I'm positive.
Besides, Nate isn't the type
to sleep around.
What you need is a night
of uninterrupted sleep.
Make Nate take the baby tonight.
Have a glass of wine,
put some earplugs in,
and give yourself a break.
Things will work out, I promise.
I'm so lucky to have you
in my life, Kelly.
I'd go completely crazy without you.
That's what I'm here for.
And you're right.
I'm not obsessing
about this anymore.
I'm just gonna give Nate his space,
and let him figure it out himself.
We're just gonna find out
what Daddy's up to, aren't we, baby boy?
Yes, we are!
And if he's got nothing to hide,
he won't mind if I go through
all his stuff, will he, baby boy?
No, he won't.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Emily? Are you here?
Geez.
- You...
- Who is she?
- Where's Jack?
- He's asleep in his room,
and you still haven't answered
my question.
Who the hell is she, Nate?
- How did you...? You're not supposed...
- I knew it.
- I knew you were having an affair.
- You went into my office.
- That's private, my private stuff.
- Private?
This is where we went on our honeymoon.
Tell me who she is!
I knew her before I knew you.
I was in love with her.
Son of a bitch.
But then she died.
And it was very painful...
for me.
And it took a long time for me
to get over it.
In some ways, I'll never be over it.
But I shouldn't have
kept that from you.
That was wrong. I'm sorry.
You should have told me.
I know.
You're right.
It was a mistake.
This is all a terrible mistake.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have gone
completely mental on you.
I should have talked to you
like a normal person.
I've just been so tired.
Why don't you go to bed?
Right now.
I'll take Jack tonight.
That's the least I can do.
We'll talk tomorrow, okay?
Thank you.
Things will be better
in the morning.
This is a disaster.
Now you people promised me something
that you cannot deliver.
This is not working.
I am calling it off.
Get rid of her.
I'll get rid of the baby.
I think I might have made a mistake.
You think I jumped the gun?
- Which gun?
- The press conference.
I was hoping when we went public,
witnesses would come forward.
What about the man
with the tinfoil hat?
Didn't he say Rossum mailed
his liver to Saturn?
Right now, he's our star.
We have anecdotal evidence that Rossum
and the other big meds are performing
illegal medical procedures
and unlicensed experiments.
But that's all it is: anecdotal.
You have a source at the NSA?
Had. Like everyone else,
he's gone to ground.
Well, you have their financials.
That's a lot of unaccounted
cash transactions for medical research.
It wouldn't be hard to prove
money laundering.
This is nice.
Focus.
You're Foil-Hat Man's only hope.
Sit. I got it.
I'm not after money laundering.
Rossum crossed a line.
And they've gotta be leaning on people
to keep them quiet.
They've got the resources.
Cindy?
There was nobody there.
Good morning, Madeline.
May I come in?
Place looks lovely.
I stripped a lot of it
back to the original.
Work is good?
You know, I haven't worked a day
since I've been home.
- God bless you, my dear.
- I should feel guilty about that.
I really, really don't.
Absolutely not.
Do you know how many people
would kill to have this kind of freedom?
It's strange. I never thought
I'd be among the idle rich.
You should travel.
- You're allowed to leave the country.
- I don't think so.
I've been away so long, part of me
just wants to stay close to home.
Is there a young man
keeping you close to home?
Maybe. I'm not sure.
I thought as much. Do tell.
Don't misunderstand,
it's nice to see you.
But I have this irrational fear
that if I say one wrong thing,
men in suits are going to throw me
in a black van and take me away.
Not at all.
Your obligation to the Dollhouse
is complete.
Right.
So you're just here
for a friendly chat?
You haven't come in
for your diagnostic.
Just because you leave our care,
we don't cast you to the wolves,
Madeline.
I'm worried about you.
I appreciate that.
I suspect you're worried
that I'll flip out
and expose you and the Dollhouse.
- The worries aren't mutually exclusive.
- You know what I'm wondering?
Is if this is really about the fact that
you let me out of my contract early.
Years early.
Why is that?
Did something happen?
Circumstances changed.
I'm not at liberty to discuss them.
For your own well-being,
come and have your diagnostic.
I won't take no for an answer.
I don't imagine you will.
Where are two going?
Just for a walk.
A walk outside.
We'll be right back.
You're holding your car keys.
We're going to the park in the car,
and then for a walk.
You know, I thought that
we could all eat breakfast together.
I just discovered that I can actually
cook something called scrambled eggs,
and I don't wanna brag,
but they're pretty amazing.
You know, that sounds so great,
but I'm not hungry.
- Aren't you supposed to be at work?
- I took the day off.
That's...
great, baby.
Yeah, it's long overdue.
I forgot.
You can't drive anywhere today.
Why not?
I took your car into the shop
to get the brake pads replaced,
and I forgot
the baby seat inside. I'm sorry.
It'll probably be ready tomorrow.
- You didn't need to do that.
- I know.
I'm just trying to help out.
You know what?
Why don't you go back to bed,
and I'll take this little guy?
- Get some rest.
- Wait.
It's okay. Go on.
We're gonna have
a little man time down here.
It's time for him to eat.
I forgot, but I should feed him.
All right.
Why don't you take a nap
when you're done?
Promise.
It's okay.
Hello?
- You have to come get me and the baby.
- What's wrong?
Nate won't let us leave.
I think he's trying to kill me.
- That's crazy.
- He took away the car!
Please come and get us!
I'll explain everything.
All right.
All right, I'm on my way.
Thank you.
Thank God.
Oh, God.
She's upstairs.
Husband says
she's been acting a little paranoid,
and she has the kid,
so let her see me first.
We don't want this
to get out of hand.
Would you like a treatment?
Please be quiet, Jack.
Come on, it's okay.
- What the hell?
- Don't cry, please.
Don't cry please.
Don't cry.
You got to be kidding me.
It's okay, baby boy.
We going to be okay.
- Please sit down, Mr. Jordan.
- I will not sit down.
Your zombie took my Jack,
and you are sitting there drinking tea.
Do something!
Echo will not harm your child.
- She loves him. She is his mother.
- I'm sorry?
Are you listening to yourself?
She is not his mother.
But she is.
This isn't someone
playing make-believe.
In Echo's mind,
she planned for this child.
Carried him for nine months.
Delivered him and nursed him.
For all intents and purposes,
Jack is her baby.
I gave you people money...
a lot of money...
and you send a crazy
kidnapping chick into my house.
What the hell did I pay you for?
A mother.
You could have hired
a nanny, a baby-sitter,
but you wanted someone
to bond profoundly with your child
because you could not
bond with him yourself,
which is understandable.
I shouldn't have done this.
This was a terrible idea.
The formative months
of an infant's life are crucial.
A child who feels loved
is imprinted with the sense
that the world is a safe place.
A child that does not feel loved
grows up to be...
well...
most likely a sociopath.
What happens to a child
kidnapped by a stranger?
I'm sorry, Mr. Jordan,
but your next plan was to put up
the child for adoption, was it not?
Just find him.
We know exactly
where Echo and the baby are.
And we are retrieving them
as we speak.
We're just hitting the bank.
Taking out as much of Daddy's money
as they will let us.
And then we are road-tripping it,
sweetheart.
Won't that be fun?
Officers!
Please help me.
Someone is chasing me,
trying to take my baby.
Where?
Damn it. They were right there, I swear.
You have to believe me.
My husband's trying
to have me killed.
You're safe now.
Come with us.
I know it sounds crazy.
I listen to myself
and I sound crazy.
But I heard him.
My husband wants to take my baby
and get me killed.
It doesn't make any sense.
I don't know what I did.
The important thing is,
you came to us.
Too many women convince themselves
they're overreacting
or pretend things will get better.
Then it's too late.
You have to understand.
He's not an abuser.
He's never laid a hand on me.
He doesn't even raise his voice.
I'm not a victim.
Yeah, not yet.
Let's try to keep it that way.
You had a baby.
Some guys can't handle the stress.
They snap.
He didn't snap.
He just...
went away, you know?
It's like the person I knew
isn't there anymore.
He's been replaced
by a stranger and...
I don't even know what I'm saying.
Yes, you do.
And you're lucky
you got out when you did.
What's going to happen now?
We'll record your statement,
then we'll bring your husband in.
In the meantime, we'll get a judge
to grant you a restraining order.
That's him.
Oh, God. That's him.
And that's one of the men
that came into my house.
Talking to my captain.
Don't worry. You're safe.
Stay put.
I'll see what's going down.
You can't hurt me in here, Nate.
Whatever you've planned,
it's not gonna work.
You sure about this?
I am positive. That is my baby,
but that is not my wife.
No one's going to hurt you.
This man is from the FBI.
He wants to talk to you.
Stay away from me.
Stay away from me!
I promise, you will be safe.
Don't come any closer! No!
Don't take my baby!
Don't take my baby! Don't! Don't!
No! Come on!
It's okay.
I don't want to hurt you.
Just don't fight. It's okay.
I'm not going to hurt you!
Don't take him!
Let me go!
Let me go! Let me go!
Let me go, please!
Don't take him, Jack!
Don't take him!
72, 65, 58,
51...
Thank you.
Repeat these words.
Boat. Cucumber. Wire.
Very good.
Any headaches, dizziness?
None.
Nightmares, deja vu?
Gag reflex while eating sea urchin?
What?
Forget it.
I'm not broken?
You're not glitching.
And I haven't found
any phantom files
or random memory threads.
Physiologically, you're intact.
- So, I'm finished, then.
- What were those three words?
Boat. Cucumber. Wire.
Clean bill of health.
Factory new
and not a scratch on you.
As promised.
We should put you
in the recruiting DVD.
Thank you very much.
How do I get out of here?
I'll let them know
that you're ready to be taken home.
While we're waiting, may I offer you
any additional enhancements?
On the house.
I've been working
on some pretty sick apps.
How do you feel about ventriloquism?
So tempting.
I'll have to pass.
It's a dying art.
Give me back my son!
- Little help?
- Get her in the chair.
- They stole my baby. Help me!
- Did you offer her a treatment?
That's a great idea.
Why won't anybody help me?
Let me go!
You knocked her out?
I can't wipe her
when she's knocked out.
Think.
Okay, just come on.
Put her in the chair.
I'll wipe her when she wakes up.
Whenever that is.
What are you doing here?
Just came in for a diagnostic.
That was really intense.
You're bleeding.
I remember you.
You do?
My last day,
when I was signing the paperwork...
Right.
Come on.
Let's get that taken care of.
Looks good.
Don't even need a stitch.
Thanks.
You okay?
I don't know.
To be clear,
nobody took anybody's baby.
She's an active, like you used to be.
It was all pretend.
- Is it always like that?
- Like what?
She really believed
someone took her child.
Heart and soul.
Like I said, it wasn't real.
But it was, for her.
All that emotion, all that pain.
Was I ever like that?
We're not good for each other.
- Don't be so cruel! This is killing me!
- You'll get over it.
You know, I'm kind of new here.
I wouldn't really know.
She'll be okay.
- Who?
- The girl.
You seemed worried for her.
She'll forget about the baby.
She'll forget everything.
No more pain.
No more grief.
That's how it works.
They did it for me.
I had a daughter.
She died.
I'm sorry.
She had a cold.
And then it wasn't a cold.
It was cancer.
Terminal.
And my world fell apart.
Within six months, she was gone,
and I was left all alone,
completely unable to function.
I had no idea.
How could you?
But what I'm telling you is,
it all worked out.
I met Adelle.
She came to you?
She told me
I didn't have to suffer anymore.
I go to sleep for five years,
I wake up without pain.
So, what, you...
you're happy now?
I'm not sad.
It was nice meeting you.
You seem like a nice man.
Please help me.
They're going to do something
terrible to my little boy.
I am a nice man.
You're going to be just fine.
I promise.
I'm gonna make all this go away.
So, you'll help me?
Absolutely.
Hello, Echo.
How are you feeling?
Did I fall asleep?
For a little while.
Shall I go now?
God!
- What is it?
- Wiretap transcripts.
This is more than medical malfeasance
or ethics violations.
This is... prostitution.
Human trafficking.
Maybe murder.
They take people, and they...
change them...
into whatever they want them be.
That's not possible.
It's very possible.
I read everything about this.
When Mom was sick,
Rossum had the means to help her,
and instead, they...
You know, when we first started
looking into this,
I thought this was
a game-changer for us, a trophy,
the next step up in your career.
I'm scared, Daniel.
The power that these people have...
- Do you want me to back off?
- No.
I want you to do what you promised.
This has to stop.
We're gonna verify all this.
We're gonna find proof.
We've got better than proof.
We've got a name.
Go, please?
What, precisely, was the
last thing she said to you?
I'm telling you,
I remember wiping her,
and then my face exploded.
That's it.
Where's she going?
GPS has her heading to...
Nate Jordan's house...
she's going after the baby.
How can that be?
You were supposed to have wiped her.
I did!
I'm sure of it.
Are we looking at another
composite event, Mr. Brink?
I don't think so.
I think we're looking at a genius.
I'm not as comfy with you saying that
as I thought I'd be.
Think about it: you changed
her on a glandular level.
Maybe her body was stronger
than her brain.
The maternal instinct is the purest.
It's too strong for a normal wipe.
I outplayed myself.
- Like in chess.
- Not like chess...
like Echo was in trouble and pain
because you didn't think it through.
She probably can't even
remember his name,
but she has to have him back,
no matter what.
Perhaps triggering lactation
was a bridge too far.
- Live and learn.
- Go. Now.
Well, I guess that's gonna hold.
What do you think?
You had a crazy day, buddy?
But things are gonna be okay.
You and me...
we're gonna figure it out.
Come here, pal.
All right.
All right. I'm going to see
about getting a bottle together for you.
Okay? Now, don't you go anywhere.
Don't you go anywhere.
All right.
Daddy'll be right back.
Smells like fish.
Damn it!
Hold on, buddy!
I'll be right there.
- Hello?
- Mr. Jordan, Adelle DeWitt.
It's imperative you and your son
leave your house at once.
- What? Why?
- There's little time for discussion.
Our Active is on her way to you.
I've dispatched a team to intercept.
Get out of the house immediately.
She's coming here? Why?
Hello?
Hello?!
Jack?!
Where are you?
Mommy's home.
- Please. Don't hurt him.
- You took away my baby.
- Why did you do that?
- I'm sorry.
Can... Can I please have him back?
I love him.
I don't want to give him to you.
I'm his daddy.
But this is my baby.
I know that you think that he is.
I want you to go away now.
I can't do that.
- Babies need their mothers.
- I know.
- But you aren't his mother.
- That's a lie!
I don't want to talk to you anymore!
I know
that you love Jack very much...
... but he doesn't belong to you.
And I am afraid
that you're going to hurt him.
That's not me.
That's not right.
Do you remember?
They turned you into somebody else.
You're not real.
None of this is real.
I'm not real.
Do you know who is real?
I don't.
And I'm sorry.
This is my fault.
I put you through hell.
They made you love Jack
because I asked them to.
Why did you do that?
My wife,
Karen...
she died while having Jack.
And I couldn't handle it,
and I fell apart, and I blamed him.
I blamed a baby.
Do you believe that?
And after she died,
I needed to find someone
who would love Jack
because I couldn't do it myself.
So, can I be his mommy?
I'm sorry.
You can't.
Karen is a part of Jack.
You aren't.
And he's all
that I have of her anymore.
So...
You can do
whatever you want to do to me.
Just...
Just please don't hurt the baby.
My little boy.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
I had a baby.
Now I don't have him anymore.
I feel sad.
I'm sorry.
All of these things
that happen to me...
I feel them.
I know, Echo.
- I know you remember everything.
- Not remember.
Feel.
I was married.
I felt love.
And pain, fear.
It's not pretend for me.
They made me love my little boy.
And then they took him away.
They make it so real.
Every time, they make it so real.
Why do they do that?
I know you want to help me
bring down the Dollhouse,
but maybe it's too much.
I can do this on my own.
I promise I'll get you out.
I'll get all of you out.
If you want,
I'll tell Topher
what's going on with you,
and he can fix it.
He'll come up with a way to wipe you,
and you won't remember a thing.
You won't have to feel sad anymore.
Feeling nothing would be worse.
That would be like before.
Asleep.
I'm awake now.
I don't want to back to sleep.