Previously...
Three years of my life are gone,
stolen by the Dollhouse.
She's not right.
She's perfect.
It's like they made her just for me.
I call it a Disruptor.
The gentle hum
lets you know it's working.
- Who the hell are you?
- You forgot me already?
If I don't stop Rossum,
no one will.
- You're not a Doll.
- What the hell was that?
We're going back to D.C.,
so you can forget this ever happened.
Here we are.
What's interesting to me
is that you don't call out to God.
It isn't a question
of faith, it's just the vernacular.
Anyone in this much pain prays,
or at least curses, but...
we take God from you, too.
You really are a shell.
Why?
Now's not the time for why.
I like this void.
This feeble, simple world.
Ju pain... over and over.
No reason, no-no end,
no in between.
You can't even pass out.
I've shut down everything
that stands between you
and blinding, searing pain.
Of course, I bluff.
It won't always be like this.
When we get to the why...
that's when it gets really bad.
Episode 206: The Left Hand
www.subbercafe.fr
Please don't let them do this.
Do what, Daniel?
It's already been done.
Don't you get that?
I don't want to forget who I am.
Oh, baby.
You don't want to remember
who you were.
Even though that part's
always been there.
- What are you talking about?
- You already know.
You were a nobody
before we found you.
Just a name.
Everything you care about,
everything you hold most dear,
we gave you.
That's not true.
You know it is.
We took a spoiled, pampered,
selfish child,
and we made a man out of him.
A man the people could trust.
Why?
We needed a senator,
and you had the pedigree.
You didn't create me.
I'm going to expose you. You know that.
That righteous indignation?
Yeah, we gave that to you, too.
We spent three years
building up your credibility.
When you finally exonerate Rossum
at the Senate hearings today,
no one will question you.
Why are you telling me this now?
Because it's funny?
And because you're not gonna
remember in 20 minutes anyway.
Which is also
why I think I can say...
I can't stand you.
Having to be your wife,
letting you touch me,
pretending that
when it doesn't disgust me
it doesn't bore me?
That has been really hard.
Feels good to get that out.
This limo is nice, right?
Very fancy.
You're probably used to it.
See, I definitely am not used to it.
Your sole purpose here
is to hack into the D.C. mainframe
and acquire
Senator Perrin's imprint.
This will require stealth,
clarity of purpose,
and above all, calm.
- Good stuff. Drink?
- No.
- Can I have one?
- Absolutely not.
Roger!
I...
don't like going
outside of my comfort zone.
Our one and only chance
for discovering
Rossum's plan is to pull it
from the senator's brain scan.
There is no margin for error.
So I would suggest that you expand
your comfort zone immediately.
It's just water.
It'll help.
It takes a lot out of you.
We take a lot out of you.
Do you know your name?
Echo.
Your real name?
Caroline.
You know.
It's good.
It helps.
And you know we took your memories.
Is Caroline in there?
Yes and no.
This is one of my memories...
of you.
This is the last time I saw you.
This is what you did to me.
Not just to my arm.
To me.
I want you to feel this.
There is something worse than pain.
Sorry to have kept you
waiting for a few minutes.
25.
Always so precise.
- And who's this?
- My chief programmer, Topher Brink.
You're out of your jurisdiction.
- You've my Active. I'd like have back.
- Geez, lighten up, will you?
- So serious.
- It's a serious situation.
I trust we'll find her undamaged.
Here's the thing, Adelle.
I'm not in a position to help you.
Your girl got caught up
in a major operation,
and there are certain protocols
that I just have to follow.
I just can't give her back to you.
I have to get approval,
and that may take time.
You understand.
Of course I do.
Then why don't the two of you
just fly on back to Los Angeles,
and the moment I get the go-ahead,
we'll ship your Active back to you.
- Does that sound like a plan?
- Absolutely.
I'll need Mr. Brink to examine Echo.
Just to ensure my asset is intact.
Where's the trust?
Protocols.
I'll let my programmer know
you're coming.
Business must be slow
in L.A. if you're here.
Who's minding the store?
We've got our top guy
covering for me.
Only person in the world I trust.
What you're not getting, man friend,
is that this whole operation
is dependant upon me.
Not brain-constructy me,
but Bond, James Bond me, which is...
not so me.
Topher,
all you have to do is stay calm.
This from the guy who had
to dismember my last little outing?
You get into their system,
you make the connect so that we...
you can get a look
at Perrin's brain map.
I'm not up to this.
I suffer from acute agoraphobia.
Or I plan to.
Bennett Halverson is the chief
programmer at the D.C. Dollhouse.
She's a genius.
I think she's a genius,
so, you know,
double it.
She's just gonna look at my 1.0,
and his palms are gonna sweat,
and she's just... She'll know.
I have to track down Ballard.
You just run the House
and wait for yourself to call.
It's starting.
The clammy.
I'm busy right...
I'm sorry?
Topher Brink?
Of course.
Mr. Brink.
I... I'm looking
for Bennett Halverson.
Can you tell me where...?
Or you can show me where she...
It's different.
Than L.A...
Well, I suppose it would be.
You probably have palm trees and...
tans.
We're four stories underground.
Not a lot of photosynthesis.
No, no, you're very pale.
White.
Pinkish-white.
Your skin...
Your skin is like a pig.
- Bennett Halv...
- Because it's pink.
People assume that pigs are bad,
but I love them.
I like them.
I hear they make good pets.
I'm Bennett.
You were looking for me.
For realsies?
You're Bennett?
Not Bennett Junior?
You merged JAMS with ESAMS
to create next gen proteins?
You stud!
I'm sorry... That was...
Clammy hands.
I'm glad that you enjoyed
the report.
What's up with your arm?
It's...
Dead.
From the shoulder?
Nerves are severed.
You're here for your Active.
You won't get her.
What?
She interfered
with a Rossum directive.
It's unlikely
that Mr. Lipman will let her go.
It's unlikely Mr. Lipman
will have a choice.
- Can I see her?
- Of course.
She's still unconscious.
Courtesy of your device.
Just a little project.
Hardly.
Is it weird that I asked
about your arm?
Honestly, it's refreshing.
Adelle DeWitt flies 3,000 miles
across country
to pick up one Doll?
Must be a special girl.
They're all special.
Oh, yeah, but this one,
she nearly took Perrin from us.
I think our programmer wouldn't mind
wading around in that brain.
And clearly, you can't control her.
I think maybe you're just gonna
have to walk away from this one.
Do you honestly think
it's up to you?
Do you think anyone at Rossum
will take your side? Harding?
You're not much
of a poker player, are you?
You got no cards, Adelle.
And you don't know how to bluff.
One for the road?
Now, Stewart...
you and I have similar goals.
I would like to think
we could achieve a...
a mutually...
beneficial...
compromise.
Compromise can be fun.
If you don't return my Active,
I will send someone
to cut these off.
You will be killed, horribly,
over a long period and never found.
Now, look me in my eyes, Stewart,
and tell me
if I've learned how to bluff.
Compromise.
This is not my device.
- She's been tranqued.
- It was probably one of the Handlers.
How do you work it?
The Disruptor.
How'd you know it was called that?
What else would you call it?
The signal goes out for 50 feet,
but everywhere.
That's what...
messed up your senator
and ruined your evil plan.
If you... if you route
the signal through here,
it becomes directional.
Not like a bomb, more like a taser.
- Did you just try to tase me?
- No, no.
That would result in...
You'd be unconscious.
Why would I want that?
And it only works on Actives.
I'm concerned
that you may have tried to tase me.
No, I just...
You're really Bennett Halverson.
This conversation is becoming vague.
So, we have had an Active, Whiskey,
and she was rendered unengageable.
So, we, I made her into a doctor.
And you...
So, I thought maybe...
Similar...
Bennett, the real Bennett...
would use an Active to...
You thought...
That's idiotic.
Actives are beautiful.
Yeah.
And it's not my evil plan.
It's-It's not evil.
Wait. Hey!
I'm just here for Echo.
My last ethical quandary was...
unhelpful.
Let mommy and daddy
do the squabbling.
Yes, sir.
Right away.
Looks like you got the girl.
Let me go check on...
is it "Echo"?...
and get everything signed.
Can I use your phone?
Just wanna check in with my House.
Yes, of course.
Wasabi peas.
I'm excited and scared.
Finally!
Everything good there?
Everything's great, me-man,
except I've got
a long white beard from waiting.
Put the signal through.
Solid.
I see what you see.
I still don't know how I'm gonna get
Perrin's brain map running,
but you can use this link
to route it.
Dude,
Halverson's fine.
- What? Wait! Who? What?
- Bennett.
She's, what?
Like, distinguished?
Like young and fine, I poo you not.
Are we into her?
We may be fierce on the subject.
Oh, God, I wish I was there!
What's she like?
Totally shy,
librarian energy through the roof.
- Glasses?
- Glasses on a chain!
For the win!
Dude, she has a dead arm!
Like, dead?
Like, in a sling, with the glove?
Imagine John Cassavetes
in The Fury as a hot chick.
Which you know I often have.
We lose the connection?
Dude, she's probably an Active!
You're so untrusting.
Bree?
Don't go. Don't go.
We have to go. Come on!
Don't leave me!
I'm not gonna leave you.
We're both going.
Now!
Good-bye, Caroline.
Are you okay?
What happened?
Here, come here, come here.
Look at me. Look at me.
Can you tell me what happened?
It was Echo.
Oh, boy.
Oh, boy!
Bad!
Where is she?
She took Perrin.
Bree, wait.
I'm not Bree. I'm Echo.
Echo, what did they do to you?
She did this. But not to me.
She? Who? I don't understand.
Who is "she"?
- Don't leave me!
- Sorry, sister.
I stay, we both get nabbed.
She wanted me to know how it felt.
It feels bad.
You're not making any sense.
Were they imprinting you?
You don't seem finished.
How do you know
when you're finished?
Listen to me. I think someone
on the inside is trying to help us.
They showed me the way out,
put it in my head so we could escape.
We haven't escaped.
They're coming, they always come.
Because of this.
What's that?
- It's how they find us.
- GPS tag?
We have to cut.
I don't think I can.
You will.
I'll show you how.
That's where Senator Perrin
will sit.
He's gonna make an opening statement,
and then the hearing will begin.
Okay, this is the press area here,
so just...
be prepared for a couple dozen
camera lenses pointing at you.
A couple dozen?
Don't even think about that.
Just focus on your testimony.
Where is the senator now?
He's following up on some last minute
evidence we received.
He wants all the ammunition
against Rossum we can get.
Excuse me one moment.
- Hello?
- Perrin escaped.
I see.
Can you explain how that happened?
He was attacked by that LA Active, Echo.
They're together.
- Has he been wiped?
- No.
That is very unfortunate.
We tracked their GPS,
we dispatched a retrieval team.
I've sent you the coordinates.
You need to be there when it goes down.
On my way.
They won't stop looking.
We won't stop running.
Pull everybody in.
I want every team on this.
Well, figure it out!
He has to be at that hearing in 4 hours,
or Rossum will have our heads.
To be clear, this little project
is your problem, not mine.
Well, I'll remind you of that
when we're bunk buddies in the Attic.
Listen to this.
She's got a great idea.
It's your idea.
It's based on your idea.
But you should tell them.
I can't take the credit.
Spit it out!
We might be able
to reconfigure the disruptor
to incapacitate Echo and Perrin
without actually locating them.
Explain.
Topher's disruptor sends a signal
using a universal frequency,
which affects every Doll,
but only within a limited range.
If we use the neural electric biolinks,
we can redirect the loop
to target a specific brain.
In English.
I do the English part? That's new.
We can plug my disruptor
into the biolink system
and send the signal from here
and put them to sleep.
A painful, bleeding sleep,
but sleep, nonetheless.
Right? She's just...
Genius! She's so good!
- How long will this take to accomplish?
- Not long at all.
I can have Echo's brain map
uploaded into Bennett's system.
I just need Perrin's.
I gotta have a target.
Give him whatever he needs.
Topher Brink...
Meet Daniel Perrin.
It may be the most beautiful thing
I've ever seen.
Selective strand replacement
takes a delicate hand.
This is more
than just an alteration.
This is an imprint married to a...
an existing consciousness.
It's amazing you didn't end up
with a schizophrenic.
I have a theory that the brain can hold
multiple imprints and still function.
- A composite?
- Not a composite.
Something new.
The original Daniel Perrin
is all there.
I just...
made him better.
We'll need your Active's map.
Uploaded.
It's very nice.
She was kind of a hooker.
How about...
While I build the magic bullets,
you work on adapting your gun?
Right. Right.
You can use the whole workspace
over there.
Let's hope when we zap them,
they're not driving down the freeway
or flying a biplane
or something, huh?
You probably don't even need
to make delivery files.
I bet we can just plug this baby
straight into your biofeed...
I know. I just...
thought I'd upload some sweet dreams
to pass along.
Compensate for the searing,
searing pain.
I like that.
- Incoming.
- Is that it?
It's me. The him-me.
- I'm giving the word to myself.
- And what's the word?
It ain't "Grease".
The he-me did it.
I rock. We rock.
The I-other-me has accessed
Perrin's brain map.
That may be the most beautiful
thing I have ever seen.
We can't stay here to long.
It's real.
It's all real.
They didn't program this.
I grew up here.
I wish they had.
Why?
They didn't create me.
Only parts of me.
How can I ever untangle it?
Does it matter?
What do you mean?
Does it matter who you were?
All that matters is
who you decide to be. Who you can be.
You make it sound so easy.
It is.
It's all up to you.
What, the voters don't get a say?
The voters will say yes.
I don't know.
At this stage,
might seem a little cynical.
Like I was trading in
on the family name.
Oh, you would be.
But it wouldn't be cynical.
You use what you have.
Think of all the good you could do.
Even if I decided to run...
Do you have any idea
how much dirt the opposition
could throw at me?
I saw what you were doing
when I walked into this party.
But everybody's got a past.
It's the future
the voters care about.
You show them that, all
will be forgiven.
Where did you come from?
Salinas, Kansas.
And don't say
I'm not in Kansas anymore.
I've heard that one.
I know exactly where I am.
And who I'm talking to.
Did it really happen?
Was she ever here?
Or was it something programmed
into me in some basement somewhere?
Doesn't matter.
She was right.
They made me into something better.
You try to be your best.
Yes.
Even if I could, I don't know
if I want to be the man I was before.
I understand.
You do, don't you?
I'm afraid of Caroline.
If she comes back, where will I go?
I don't want to fall asleep.
Even for a little while.
You're awake now.
And so am I.
That's what they didn't expect.
They were going to use me as cover,
but they didn't get a chance
to reprogram me.
They've created someone
who can bring them down.
And that's what I'm going to do.
There's still time.
We can make it to the hearings.
We can expose them.
And then we can be who we are.
We can be who we decide to be.
Okay. Fire when ready.
I got nothing on Echo.
That's unusual.
I think your senator's
filibustering.
Wait...
What did you do?
Daniel, stop!
They're in your head.
You don't have to listen!
You don't have to be
what they tell you to be.
You can belong to you.
- What do we see?
- Who is it?
I'm looking at a triggered sleeper.
He's not set on stun.
- How's the other one?
- Still alive.
But spiking on every front.
I don't think she can match him.
Get our new girlfriend
to switch him off or bye-bye, Echo.
Roger that.
You hacked into my system.
- You stole Perrin's brain map.
- You're trying to kill Echo.
- So we're even?
- Not even.
Not even close.
Shut him down. Now.
- Do you know who Echo really is?
- She's a friend.
Friend?
That shell?
I was her friend!
I was her best friend.
This is what I got for it.
This is my gift from Caroline.
This isn't about Caroline.
This is about Echo.
They're the same!
Caroline has a power over people,
and however well you wiped her,
she clearly still does!
She has no power over...
When was the last time
that you described a Doll as a friend?
I know about Alpha and Ballard.
You're saying
she doesn't have some power?
I'm saying shut Perrin down.
It's for the best.
You were so close to perfect.
You still with me?
Is Bennett on board?
'Cause I don't see...
- Bennett's out.
- I killed her?
I hit her. It hurt.
But we can't just flip him back.
We can if we isolate
the neural path.
- Do you know how many...
- Then shut up and work.
I'm working.
I wouldn't hold your breath.
No. I wouldn't.
Split up.
Where is he?
Gone.
Something else is here.
Oh, God. Doll-speak.
Watch her.
I'm going to go get the senator.
Please answer me.
Those things I said before...
none of them were true.
I wanted to hurt you.
They programmed you to love me,
but the truth is,
no one programmed me to love you.
And I do.
I love you, baby.
Come with me.
Things can be
just like they were before.
We can be happy again.
Like before.
And ever after.
That's right.
Daniel, stop!
She's got me locked out on this end.
Who's your back door man?
We'll just pretend
I didn't say that.
- Found the worm.
- Step on it.
Squished.
She's broken. We have to go.
I killed her.
- I did this.
- It wasn't you.
It was them.
Daniel, we have to go.
You can still stop them,
but they're coming.
If we don't go...
They'll just make us forget...
forget that I killed her.
They killed her.
If you let them make you forget,
then you killed her.
Can you live with that,
or can you trust me?
Where is Mrs. Perrin?
I apologize to the committee for...
My wife is dead.
I don't want to be here right now,
but I'm honestly afraid
I may not have another chance
to tell the truth.
I was looking for a conspiracy,
and I found something more horrible...
The Rossum Corporation
is the most powerful medical company,
but they are something else,
as well.
For the past several years,
the Rossum Corporation
has been a target.
A target of a consortium of companies
that would stop at nothing
to undermine Rossum and take its place
in the medical community.
They set me on Rossum's trail,
and when I discovered the real truth,
they put a bomb in my car.
The car Cindy took
to stop by the family compound.
My wife was a victim.
There have been hundreds of others.
This woman, Madeline Costley,
is a victim...
of their manipulation
and her own delusions.
What?
There is no Dollhouse.
There are no sex slaves,
no underground fortresses.
Madeline Costley spent the last 3 years
in a mental institution in Canada.
- You know I was there.
- I have the documentation to prove it.
In fact, I have documentation
on all the companies involved in this...
travesty.
There is abuse here.
Not the lurid, pulp fantasy
they drilled
into this unstable mind,
but something more insidious,
something that has cost this country
more than millions,
and has cost me...
... everything.
This hearing is adjourned
until further notice.
These men are from the FBI.
They need to speak with you.
No. Echo's just gone.
And we're certain she wasn't
apprehended with Perrin?
My sources say no.
They don't have her.
- And Mr. Ballard?
- Still no word.
Are we sure
this is such a great idea?
I am sensing tension...
of the palpable sort.
Just lie back.
Finding him obstinate, are we?
- This is so weird.
Seriously, just a few more days.
I could help analyzing
Perrin's brain map.
It wouldn't be a second opinion.
It would be the same opinion twice.
There's more to analyze?
I thought we knew his function.
To inoculate Rossum
against further scrutiny.
More than that.
He's talking about new regulation,
which, inevitably, he'll oversee.
Rossum will be creating
their own laws.
Ah, good throw, Boyd,
but still doesn't win you
the giant stuffed panda.
It looks like Bennett somehow
rigged his SNS
into his higher functions.
- Meaning?
- Let's just say...
It's an awful lot of ambition
for a junior senator.
I was going to say that.
- Did I fall asleep?
- For a little while.
Shall I go now?
For the love of God, yes.
So, what are you saying?
They're manufacturing a president?
- Wouldn't be the first time.
- Delightful.
Well, before the fascist takeover,
we need to find Echo.
She's lost in the world in Doll-state,
utterly helpless.
I want every resource
engaged in her recovery.
And Madeline?
Poor girl.
I'm afraid there's nothing more
we can do.
You don't have to be afraid.
I know how you feel.
I know what it's like
to be betrayed.
To be abandoned.
She's out there.
They're all out there,
and we're left behind.
Alone.
No one should be alone.