Previously On "Ugly Betty"...
Justin?
You're Supposed To Be Working
On Your Algebra, Not Making Out.
Back Off.
You're Not My Dad.
I Miss Him So Much.
I Know, Mija.
But It'll Get Better.
I Want To Postpone
Wilhelmina Is Losing
Her Grip On Bradford.
The Bradford Meade/
Wilhelmina Slater Wedding
Is Back On.
How'd The Meeting
With The Advertiser Go?
I Think
I Lost The Account.
Guy Had Some Issues
With Our Staff.
What? With Who?
You.
I Think We Should
Lose The Account.
What?
We Don't Need Atlantic Attire
Or Their Money.
So You Want
To Destroy "Mode"?
Well, There's Only Room
At Meade Publications.
So The Baby's Yours.
I'm Soy, Betty.
You Should Go.
Henry, I'm Sorry.
I Just Can't See You.
Not With The Way
Everything Turned Out.
The Baby's Yours.
You're Going Back To Tucson
To Be With Charlie.
I Am Not Going Back
I Am Going Back
To Be A Father To My Child.
Maybe We Can
Still Do This.
Long Distance? It--
That'll Never Work.
I Just Think It's Better
If We Just Avoid Each Other
Until You Leave.
So That's It.
Just Like That?
Yes, I Think
That's What's Best.
Excuse Me, Do You Mind
Not Leaning On Me?
Who's Leaning On You?
Well, You See,
That's None Of Your Concern.
People Can Lean On Me
All They Want.
Okay.
No, Not You.
Okay, So I'm Here
For Five More Months.
How Do We Make This Work?
When You Need
Daniel's Signature, Send Kenny.
Okay. What About Meals?
I Go To The Cafeteria
At 1:00.
I Guess I Can Do 12:00.
Except For Taco Tuesdays.
I'm Always Afraid
They're Gonna Run Out,
So I Have To Go Early.
Okay, Sure.
Well, Maybe This Whole
Avoidance Thing Will Work.
Yeah, We Never Have To
See Each Other At All.
Ugh!
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
丑女贝蒂 第二季第5集
Starting Tomorrow,
I'll Take The Subway.
Uh-Huh.
Morning.
Hey, Don't Fill Up On Fruit.
I'm Making Machaca.
Oh, No, I Can't Stay.
It's Thursday.
Santos And I Do
Our Lotto Scratchers
At The Cemetery.
Oh.
Hey, Kiddo.
I'm Making Machaca.
I Know You Say
It Gives You Hips But--
I'm Meeting My Friends.
Oh, Are You All Trying Out
For "The Music Man"?
I Read In The School Paper
Auditions Are Today.
Drama Club?
That's For Losers.
You're The President.
You Even Started The Club.
Whatever. Here.
Oh.
Okay. Bye.
Hey.
Do You Even Know
What You Signed?
Oh, I Don't Know, Papi.
Maybe It Was
For Mail-Order Crack.
Come On, It Was
A Permission Slip For Something.
It's Fine. Bye.
Did You Get It?
One Note Excusing Me
From The Field Trip Tomorrow.
Yeah, Suck That,
Queens County Farm Museum.
So What
Are We Gonna Do?
We'll Take My Family's Car
Out For A Ride.
My Dad Taught Me
How To Drive.
Car Thieves Are Hot.
Marc Jacobs Wants To Send
Over Bags. I Said Yes.
Kathy Griffin Is Begging
For A Date. I Said No.
And Your Father Wants To Have
You And Alexis Over For Dinner
With Him And Wilhelmina.
I Didn't Know What To Say.
Great. I Get To Spend Time
With My Futurestep-Monster.
One Big Crappy Family.
A Grudging "Yes" It Is.
Speaking Of Which,
Your Step-Monster Has Called
A Meeting In Her Office
In 30 Seconds.
Wait, Is That Why
We're Headed This Way?
I Was Hoping We Were
Going To Get Danish.
Are You Really
That Good,
Or Did You Just Happen
To Have That On You?
You'll Never Know. Oh.
Are You Okay With This?
You Can Skip The Meeting
If You Want.
No, I Won't Let This
Get In The Way Of My Job.
I'm A Professional.
Besides, It's Not Like
I'm Writing "Betty Loves Henry"
All Over My Notebook.
Um, You--
Shut Up.
(Wilhelmina) Thank You
For Joining Us, Daniel.
Why Are You In Here? Where Are
All The Other Departments?
Oh, I Only Invited Ad Sales
And Accounting.
I Figured It'd Be Easier
To Discuss
The Advertising Situation
In A Smaller,
Le Judgmental Group.
(Whispering) Excuse Me,
Over There To That Chair?
Well, That's Very Thoughtful
Of You, Wilhelmina,
But I Really Don't Have
Anything To Hide.
I've Been Very Open
About This Whole Thing.
And If You Could Just Move
To That Chair. It's Empty.
I Think We All Know
Atlantic Attire
Pulled Their Advertising
From "Mode."
(Normal Voice) No, No, No.
I Didn't Mean You.
I Meant Him.
Betty? Please.
Oh, You--You Didn't Know?
Uh, Once The News Leaked
That Atlantic Attire
Was Pulling Out,
Well,
Other Companies Followed.
Just How Many Advertisers
Are We Talking About?
Well,
As Of This Morning,
Um... 52%.
(Low Voice) Your Foot
Just Touched My Knee.
(Low Voice) Your Knee
Just Touched My Foot.
Well, Here's The Line.
So What's
Our Financial Outlook?
Well, Uh,
If We Keep Touching--
Spending
At The Current Rate,
Then "Mode" Will Be
Out Of Business In 90 Days.
(Yoga) Yo, Fish!
You Staying In Here All Day
Or We Gon' Play Tennis?
Yoga,
I've Been Drinking--
I Mean, Thinking.
Uh, Actually,
They're Both Right.
Maybe The South Of France
Isn't Such A Good Idea.
I Am So Glad
To Hear You Say That.
'Cause At Piano Man's
Wine Tasting Last Night,
Everybody Was Saying That
Positano Is The New Monaco.
I Don't Want
To Run Anymore.
I'm Turning Myself In.
Whoa, Whoa,
Whoa, Whoa, Whoa.
That Ain't What
We've Been Talkin' About.
I Can't Leave My Children.
Bradford May Have Moved On,
But Daniel And Alexis
Still Need Me.
Need You?
You Gon' Be In Prison.
I need You.
Between The Two Of Us,
You The One More Likely
To Have A Rich Friend
With An Empty Villa.
Well, At Least If
I'm Behind Bars,
They Can Come Visit.
I'm Sorry, Yoga.
All Right.
If That's The Way
You Want To Play This,
I'm-A Start Packing.
We Don't Have
Anything To Pack.
No, But They Do.
It Was Just Stupid To Think
That We Could Avoid Each Other
When We Work
In The Same Building.
Now I Don't Know
What To Do.
You See, The Problem Is You've
Got No One Else To Focus On.
Not Bad, Not Bad.
Turn. Thank You.
You Need To Date.
Da? No, I Am Not Ready
To Get Involved Again.
Who Said Anything
About Getting Involved?
All You Wanna Do
Is Have A Little Bit Of Fun.
Christina,
Ten Minutes
Before The Fun Happens.
Well, You Don't Know
What You're Missing, Do You?
Okay, Turn.
(Low Voice) Christina, What--
What Are You Doing?
You Can't Alter Underwear.
(Low Voice) Oh,
They Never Catch On.
(Normal Voice)
Okay, Executive Decision--
I'm Gonna Put Your Profile
On Bachelocity.Com.
(Normal Voice) Internet Dating?
There Are Freaks Online.
Why Don't You Just
Chop Me Into Pieces Yourself,
And We Can Cut Out
The Middleman?
Mm, They Don't Always
I Don't Need Internet Dating.
I Can Get Over Henry Myself.
I'm Not That Desperate.
(Man) You're
A Little Desperate.
The Internet It Is.
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：
校对：
时间轴：白画游侠  守护天使
"Five Things
I Can't Live Without."
Well, Doughnuts
And My Family...
Ugh, And Eyeglass Cleaner.
I Can't Stand It
When They Get Smudged.
Yeah, You Might Want To
Sex It Up Just A Little Bit.
Why? What Did You Put?
Well, Sex--Five Times.
Oh, Well, Maybe
I'll Come Back To This One.
Oh, Listen, Nobody Cares
About What You Write Anyway.
All They Care About
Is That You've Got
A Cute Little Photograph.
Now Smile.
Ooh.
Oh, No, I Wasn't Ready.
Do Another One.
Okay, Smile.
(Camera Shutter Clicks)
Oh, Well, That One's
A Little Bit Better.
At Least You've Got
One Eye Open.
Head Down, Shoot From Above,
Get Those Bangs To
Cover Those Caterpillars
And Hide Your Chins
By Doing This.
For God Sake,
Lose The Glasses.
Amanda, I Wear Glasses.
I'm Not Gonna Lie.
Whatever.
But Guys Don't Make Passes
At Girls Who Are Fat.
These Are The Shoes
I Borrowed.
You Borrowed The Jimmy Choos.
This Is A Sandwich.
You Usually Don't Open Up
The Box That Fast.
I'll Be Right Back.
Okay,
Let's Try This Again.
Aah, Ham!
Yeah!
That's Your Best One Yet.
Graphics Wants You
To Sign Off On This.
Brilliant.
But You Didn't Even
Look At It.
The First Rule In Ruining
A Magazine Is Stop Caring.
Uh, Why Don't You
Go Downstairs
And Supervise
The Valentino Shoot?
Me? Supervise A Shoot?
Whoa! You've Never Asked Me
To Supervise Anything Before.
Wait A Minute,
Is This Part Of Your Plan
To Make The Magazine Suck?
Do You Care? There'll Be
Male Models In Underwear.
Mm, Not If
I Have My Way.
Knock, Knock.
Your Late.
Take Off Your Clothes.
Ha Ha, Easy Sailor.
Buy A Girl A Drink First.
Oh, I-I'm Sorry, I Thought
You Were The Underwear Model.
Oh, No, No, No, No, No.
I Am Supervising
This Shoot.
(Sizzles)
But It's Funny
That You Mention That
Because I Did Take
A Modeling Class Once.
You Know, Thought About It,
Put It Away,
Could Always Go Back
And Get It.
Hmm, Hmm, Hmm, Hmm.
Ow.
What Are You Laughing At?
You, Uh, You Slapped
Your Own Ass Too Hard.
That's Funny.
Oh, Yeah, I Guess
That Is Funny. Ha Ha.
Cliff St. Paul.
Marc St. James.
Wow, We're Both Saints.
Is Yours Fake, Too?
No.
Mine, Either.
Are You Sure This
Doesn't Make Me Look Fat?
(Sighs) I'll Sign
For That Package.
Well, Please Let Him Be Dumb.
He Can't Have Everything.
Oh. (Laughs)
I Put 'Em On Backward.
Thank You.
I Can Help You.
Hello?
(All) Hello.
Oh, Hey, Papi.
These Are My New Friends
From The Cemetery--
Mabel, Esther, And Lucille.
They Lost Their Husbands, Too.
Heart Attack.
Liver Failure.
Stroke On A Cruise.
I'm Sorry.
You Don't Get
Your Money Back,
But They Don't
Tell You That.
Oh, We're Maki A Quilt
From Our Husbands' Shirts.
Our Dead Husbands.
Fun.
Okay, I Decided
Go With This One.
I Was Gonna Use The One
That Says,
"Drink Till She's Cute,"
But I Buried Him In It.
(All) Aw.
(Cliff) I Think
The Last Shot's The One.
So This Whole Window Thing
You're Doing, It's Genius.
I Love It.
Totally Get The Concept.
You Have No Idea, Do You?
None Whatsoever.
(Laughs)
Uh, "Rear Window."
Hitchcock?
Never Saw It.
Really?
It--It's Amazing.
I-I-I Love Hitchcock.
What Aut "Psycho"?
Uh, Work For One.
Does That Count?
Hey, Did You Guys
See "Saw"?
No.
Wh--I Said "Seesaw."
(Laughs)
Wow.
(Gasps) I Know. Oh.
Okay, You Have To Go
With Me Tomorrow Night.
I'm Seeing "Psycho"
At The Film Forum.
Oh, That Sounds Like Fun.
Maybe We Could
Grab A Beer Before.
Uh, Sure, If By "Beer"
You Mean "Appletini."
Okay.
Gus, Rear Back
In The Window.
What Is It, Girl?
Someone Felldown Their Well?
Betty...
Internet Dating...
Must Mock.
(Gasps) Ooh, Bookmark It.
I Gotta Stick Around Here.
I'm Trying To Work Up
The Nerve
To Ask Out
"Hot Pants" Over There.
Oh, You're Asking Him Out? Maybe
I'll Stay Here And Mock You.
What? You Think
He's Out Of My League?
He's A Nine. I'm An Eight.
He's A Ten. You're A Six.
You're A Bitch.
I'm A Seven.
Now I Know This Is
Going To Hurt A Bit,
But For Starters, We Can
Save 8% By Printing On...
Rice Paper.
Look At That.
That's Not Terrible, Huh?
I Can See You.
(Wilhelmina) Well, We Can
Just Say We're Going Green.
People Will Do Anything If They
Think They're Saving A Tree.
Which Brings Me To...
Soy Ink.
I've Heard That Stuff
Tends To Rub Off.
We Could Throw In
A Packet Of Wasabi,
And Then
We All Got Lunch.
This Is Crazy.
We're Ruining The Magazine,
And It's All My Fault.
No, It's Not. It's My Fault.
Alexis, I'm The One
Who Lost The Advertisers.
Now, Now,
Stop Blaming Yourselves.
It's Both Your Faults,
But Fortunately,
I'm Here To Help.
Now How Do You Feel
About Free Detergent Samples?
B-Licious.
Kenny.
Henry Needs
Daniel's Tag On This.
Okay. Oh, And Will You
Give Henry My Time Card?
I Can't Make It
To The Accounting Department.
Chicken.
Stay Out Of It.
So B.T. Dubs, You Really Did
A Number On My Boy Henry.
I Don't Even Think Porn
And Malt Liquor
Can Heal The Damage
That You Have Inflicted.
Kenny, You're From Greenwich.
Stop Frontin'.
South Side, Yo.
Chris-Tay,
Oh, Lookin' Good.
Oh, Go Away, Kenny.
Listen, Why Don't You
Tell Your Girl To Throw My Man
A Betty Biscuit Before
He Leaves For Tucson?
Tucson.
It's Spelled "Tuc-Son."
It Should Be Pronounced
"Tuck-Son."
I Don't Understand
A Word That Man Says.
Christina, Look. I Already
Have Responses To My Profile.
15 Of Them. First One's
From Ilovetacos.
I Love Tacos.
Then Ilovechurros.
I Love Churros.
Ilovetortillas.
Amanda,
You're Not Funny.
(Laughs)
I'm A Little Funny.
Look, There's One--
Niceguy47.
Oh, It's A Real One.
Mm-Hmm.
"I'd Love
To Go Out With You.
"Your Profile Says
You Enjoy Bowling,
So If You Have
Some Spare Time..."
Oh.
Aw.
I Don't Get It.
"Yes, I Love Bowling."
Send.
Send That Again.
Why?
You Typed "Blowing."
What Else Could They Do?
We Weren't Due To Dock
In Puerto Vallarta
For Two More Days.
So They Put Him
In The Freezer,
Right Next
To The Beef Tenderloin.
(Mabel) Done.
One For
My Grandson's Birthday,
And Then One
For Christmas,
In Case I'm Dead.
I Always Wondered
How My Abuela
Got Such Crisp Bills
In The Cards She Sent.
(Laughs) So What
Are We Doing Tomorrow?
Tomorrow? Look At Her,
The Optimist.
We're Taking
The Senior Center Bus
To Rockaway Beach.
The Beach Is
A Good Place To Die.
No, Home Is Best.
I Always Thought The Mall
Would Be A Good Place To Die,
But I'm A Shopper.
You Know Where's
Not A Good Place To Die?
A Cruise Ship.
They Take Your Money.
I'm Gonna Write
Another Letter.
Ooh, That Reminds Me, I Have
To Write To That Cereal Company.
I Counted.
There's Not Two Scoops
Of Raisins In There.
I'm Writing
The Networks.
Why Won't They Bring Back
That "Highway To Heaven"?
(Hilda) I Wish I Had
Someone To Write A Letter To.
Maybe I'll Find Something
To Hate In Rockaway.
(Mabel) You Coming, Too?
Yeah, Sure. What Else
I Got Goin' On?
Come On, Betty.
Your Opinion
Really Matters To Me.
Ll, The New One
Doesn't Really Say
"Classy Fashion Magazine."
It's More
"Where's Lindsay's Mug Shot?"
Oh, And There It Is.
Daniel, Wouldn't You Rather
Just Keep "Mode" The Way It Is
And Go To Your Father
And Ask Him For Money?
Yeah, But You've Met
My Family.
My Mother Was Arrested
For Murder,
And She's The Nice One.
Yeah, But Do You Really Want
"Mode" Going Out Like This?
Oh, Free Laundry Detergent.
Yeah, Knock Yourself Out.
Thanks.
Why Are You Wearing
Your Lucky Sweater?
It's Not Taco Tuesday.
No, But I Have
An Appointment...
At The Bowling Alley...
With A Boy.
That's A Date.
Betty, You've Got A Date.
I'm So Proud Of You
For Getting Back Out There.
Me, Too.
whore!(Speaking Spanish)
you plotted with Lorenzo to steal my heart...
and then steal my husband!
Would You And The Golden Girls
Like A Snack?
I've Got Some Soft Food.
It's Almost Dinnertime.
It's 3:15.
(Gasps)
We're Gonna Be Late.
It's The Early Bird Special.
Ack! Mabel Left
Her Teeth Again. Ew.
She's Gonna Need These
If She Wants The Roast Beef.
Hold It. You Just
Put Teeth In Your Purse.
What's Going On With You
And These Old Ladies?
They're Fun.
Oh Yeah, "Stroke-On-A-Cruise"
A Laugh Riot.
They Get Me.
Ever Since Santos Died,
Everyone Says, "I Know What
You're Going Through."
Well, They Don't.
They Don't Know What It's Like
To Wake Up Every Morning,
Roll Over And Not See
That Person Next To You.
These Women Do.
Yeah, Well,
I Do, Too, Hilda.
Since I Lost Your Mother,
Not A Day Goes By
That I Don't Miss Her.
I Know.
But It Can't Mean
That Life Stops.
You Still Have A Future
Ahead Of You.
And You've Got A Son
That Needs You.
Justin Is Fine.
I'm Fine.
Well, Except For
This Shooting Pain In Myack.
Feels Like Rain.
All Right, Girls.
(Claps Hands) Let's Go.
Look.
This Is Soy Ink.
This Is Dolce.
Damn It. I've Gotta
Stop Doing That.
Okay, So Maybe Soy Ink
Isn't The Best Option.
We'll Figure
Something Else Out.
We're Out Of Options.
You Know What We Have To Do.
Oh, No. No.
I'm Not Going To Dad.
He's Finally Staing
To Trust Me.
H-How Can I Tell Him
I Lost Half Our Advertisers?
You Can't, But I Can.
I May Not Remember
The Last Couple Years,
But I Know I Was
His Golden Boy.
I'll Just Tell Him
It Was My Fault,
And I'll Get The Money
From Him.
All Right.
You Were Always The One Who
Could Get Away With Anything.
I'll Be Right Back.
This Golden Boy's Gotta Go
Wash Ink Off His Boobs.
G-Stick,
You Sittin' Down?
Um, Ye
You Can See I Am.
Brace Yourself. Bad News
Vis-?Vis Your Old Lady.
Oh, My God, My Mom?
Did She Fall Again?
Nah, I'm Talkin'
About Betty.
Oh, My God,
Did Betty Fall Again?
Worse.
You Know I'm Hooked Up Like
Perez When It Comes To Gossip.
I Hear Everything, Yo.
That's Because You Pee
In The Ladies' Room.
Well, They're Cleaner.
Men Are Pigs.
But This Is Something
I Heard With My Own Eyes.
Kenny, Will You Just Tell Me?
What's Going On With Betty?
Bowling...
Tonight...
With A Dude.
Cuteinqueens?
(Gasps) Niceguy47?
Hi, I'm Betty.
Steve.
It's Nice To Meet You.
Adult Braces. Wow.
Oh, Yeah. Uh, You Probably
Didn't See Them In The Photo.
I'm Glad
You Recognized Me.
Um, Size 6, Please.
An 11.
Yeah, That Was
A Really Good Picture.
I Know, It Was, Like,
My Best Ever.
yo???
you know???
we can??
man??
crazy??
so??
I mean???
So I Fured,Why Even Bother With Ilovebunnies?
Yeah,Why Bother? Lot Of Frames Left.
Oh,You're Right. You're Right.
But Just So You Know,That's How I Ended Up With Cuteinqueens.
I Didn't Want You Thinking I Was Conceited,
'Cause I'm Not.
Oh,That's Me.
Uh,Go Ahead. I'm Gonna Hit The Restroom.
Oh,Okay,Uh,Funny Story About The Bathroom Here--
A Little Gross, But Mostly Funny.
I'll Tell You When You Get Back.
Hello.
So How's It Going?
Good. He's A Really Nice Guy, Just Like His Screen Name Says.
And We Haven't Had Any Of Those Awkward Pauses.
Great. (Computer Beeps)
Oh,I Have To Go.
Someone's I.M.Ing Me On Bachelocity.
Maybe I'll Get As Lucky As You Did. See You Later.
You're not slngle.
"And You Are A Creepy Stalker."
No I'm not. I'm your husband.
Look What I Swiped From The Closet
For My Date With The Underwear Model.
That's Right. I'm Seeing Gus Tonight. I Don't Believe You.
It's True.
I Want Proof. Ooh,Send Me A Dirty Cell Phone Picture.
Oh,But Not Your Parts Again. That Was Gross.
Yeah,Well, Your Left One's Bigger.
Hey.
You Got All Dressed Up.
Mm. (Singsongy) New Cashmere.
Old... Cat Hair.
So Listen,After The Movie, Maybe We Can Go To The Village--
Oh,Yeah,Right. Oh,I Meant To Call You.
I'm Gonna Have To Take A Rain Check On "Psycho."
You're Not Going To Believe This,
But I Asked Out Gus.
For... Tonight? Yeah, And He Said,"Yes."
Aah! (Singsongy) I'm Going Out With An Underwear Model.
(Normal Voice) Are You Dying? I'm Dying.
Oh,Yeah,Yeah,I'm Dying. Uh,I Thought We Were Going Out.
Yeah,But Gus And I Are Going On A Date.
You And I Were Just Gonna...
Oh.
No. No "Oh." It-It-It's Fine.
We Weren't... At All. Cliff...
Okay,I've Gotta Go. Have Fun On Your Date.
* You Can't Have Me
* You Can't Keep Me For Yourse *
* Not You...
Yes,I Got One!
Henry?
Oh,My God,Betty. I Didn't See You.
What Are You Doing Here?
League Night.
The Accountants Have A Team-- "The Debitz" With A "Z."
Totally Intimidates "The Actuaries."
What About You?
Oh,Um,I'm On A Date.
A First Date. It's Going Really Well.
Actually, He'll Be Back Any Second.
He--He Doesn't--He Didn't Have A-A Yellow Shirt On,Did He?
Yeah,Yeah
I-I've Been Calling Him "Yellow Head" All Night.
We Just Laugh. Uh,How Did You Know?
Well,I-I Think I Saw Him In The Bathroom,
And He--He Got A Phone Call And Had To Leave.
Oh,My God. Well,Do You Know Why?
Well,I Think I Heard Him Say Something About A Pet Bird.
It Was Sick. Bird Flu.
Yeah,He Had To Rush And Say Good-Bye,
And He--He Taught The Bird How To Say Good-Bye,
And--You Know What? The Bird's Sick.
Let's Just Leave It At That.
Oh,Uh,Well, That's Too Bad.
Um,Well,I Guess I'll Just Finish My Game On My Own.
It Was Good To See You.
Hey,You Know What?
Um,I Was Thinking...
Well,I Don't See Any Of The Other Debitz Here.
Do You Mind If I Just Warmed Up In The Lane Next To You?
Aren't We Supposed To Be Avoiding Each Other?
Right. How's That Working For You?
Not So Good. Same Here.
Look,Why Don't We Just Try And Be Friends?
Yeah. And In That Case, Friends Bowl,Right?
Right.
Yeah.
I've Been Doing That All Night.
Nice. (Laughs) (Laughs)
(Man) Okay,Lovers,
It's The Time  You've All Been Waiting For.
It's Couples' Bowl.
(Woman) * Yeah,Yeah,Yeah
Bowling Sucks.
Let's Go.
Cliff,I Am So Sorry.
Look,It's-- It's Not A Big Deal.
It's Just-- Just A Misunderstanding.
We--We Never Need To Talk About This Again.
You Know What? We Are Gonna Talk About This Again.
I Don't Know What Planet You're From,
But When Someone Asks You Out For Drinks And A Movie,
That's A Date, And The Only Reason
You Didn't Think So Is 'Cause It Was Me.
That's Not True. Oh,Come On.
We Both Know That I Don't Have "Muscle Tone"
Or--Or Use "Products," And For No Apparent Reason,
I Now Do  Annoying "Air Quotes."
Stop It.
You're Such A Clich?
You And Gus? What Is That?
That's Beauty... And Beauty. That's Not A Story.
Now "Beauty And The Beast"-- That's A Fairy Tale.
I Am Not Dating Gus Just Because Of His Looks.
We Had A Real Connection. We Laughed Together.
We Laughed Together. Gus Just Stood There
In His Backwards Underwear Lookin' Hot.
So You Admit That He's Hot.
Yes. Yes,He Is Hot. But I've Got News For You.
In 20 Years,That Guy Candy Is Gonna Turn Into This.
I Just Got There A Little Sooner.
You Know Something,Marc?
I Thought That There Was More To You.
It's My Mistake.
Alexis,Daniel.
Dad.
And This Is My FiancE, Wilhelmina.
I've Heard So Much About You.
(Laughs) So When's The Last Time I Was Here?
Oh,About A Month Ago, Before The Car Accident.
We Had Dinner Together, As We Do Every Sunday.
(Low Voice) Laying It On A Little Thick,Aren't We?
May I Take Your Coat? Sure.
You Okay?
Yeah,Uh...
I Thought I Just Had,Like, A Memory Flashback Or Something.
Weird. Maybe I'm Just Hungry.
Well,You're In Luck.
Mommy Made Fondue.
Now Everyone Put Your Hats On.
I Am Not Putting That On.
Bah Humbug,Daniel. We're All Together Tonight.
It's A Perfect Time To Take Our Holiday Photo.
Actually,We Usually Do It In Front Of The Christmas Tree
With Our Real Mother. Come On.
Daniel,I Would Never Try
To Take The Place Of Your Real Mother.
You'll Have Two Christmases This Year--One Here
And One On The Lam. Here,Let Me Take That For You.
Unless You Want To Continue In Your Mother's Tradition.
Thanks,Dad.
All Right, Everyone Smile.
(Yoga Whispering) Hey,Fish.
What The Hell Do You Think You're Doing?
I Don't... I-I Don't Know.
I-I Saw The Gun And... And The Wedding Invitation,
And I Just Lost It.
But Look.
The Woman That Ruined My Life Did What I Never Could.
She Brought Them Together.
They're A Family.
That's All I Ever Wanted.
It's Okay Now.
Let's Go To Italy.
(Hilda) I Gotta Say, This Is Very Relaxing.
It Really Does Pass The Time.
You Know What Else Was Nice?
The Applesauce That We Had For Dinner.
I Think I Could Have It Every Day. (Laughs)
They're Sleeping, Grandma.
For Her,It Could Be The Big One.
Ay,Papi.
It's Not Much, But It's There. (Siren Whoops)
Who Died? I Get Her Clothes.
I'll Get It.
Justin.
Hey,Hilda. Listen,Justin Took Your Car
For A Little Joyride With His Friends.
What?
I'm Goin' Upstairs.
Hey. He Crashed It Into A Tree.
No One Was Hurt
Except The Car And The Tree.
Listen,This One's Between Us.
I Know You Been Goin' Through A Lot Lately,
But Keep An Eye On Him.
I Seen These Things Spiral.
Yeah,Yeah. Thanks,Rita.
Mm-Hmm.
Thanks.
All Right,Ladies.
Looks Like We're Gonna Have To Wrap Things Up.
You Don't Have To Go Home, But You Can't Quilt Here.
Will We See You Tomorrow?
I Don't Think So. I Mean,This Was Fun,
But Maybe I'll Just See You At The Cemetery.
I Mean,Above Ground. (Women Laugh)
So Who's Got The Walker? Yeah,Let's Help.
Well,Dinner Is Served.
Come On.
Soup's Not Soup Unless It's Hot.
Wait,Dad,There's Something I Have To Tell You.
It's About The Magazine.
No,Alexis. I Can't Let You Do That.
Hot Or Cold, Soup Is Soup.
I Lost Atlantic Attire,
Which Led To A Substantial Advertiser Pullout.
How Substantial?
52%, But I Can Explain.
Of All The Incompetent-- Hold On,Dad. It's Not His Fault.
He Was Protecting Me. Don't Defend Him.
Your Brother Has A Long History Of Making Mistakes Around Here
And Expecting Everybody Else To Clean Up After Him.
You're The Only One I Can Count On To Do Anything Right.
And Me,Of Course.
Look,I Can Fix This. Just Give Me The Chance.
(Bradford,Voice Distorted) I Always Knew
Something Like This Wagonna Happen.
You've Had Every Opportunity Handed To You.
How The Hell Could You Turn Into Such A Screwup?
You Are Dead To Me,Alex.
Excuse Me.
Oh,Boy,It Really Is Date Night.
Who Cares?
Two Friends Can Have Dinner,Right?
No Big Deal.
Yeah.
What Are You Doing?
Oh,Oh, This Is For Me.
Sucks To Be You.
No,Seriously, Do You Want To Sit Here?
No,I'm Fine.
Thank You.
Oh,Look, It's My Date's Bird.
Guess He Didn't Make It.
I'm Sorry. I'm A Terrible Liar.
????
And You're On A Bowling Team Called The Debitz?
No,The Debitz Are Real. It Just Wasn't League Night. Oh.
I-I Heard You Were On A Date, And It Made Me Kind Of Crazy.
Are You Serious? You Got Jealous?
Oh,No,No,No. We Are Not...
We're Friends. He Got Another Girl Pregnant.
Betty. What? I Can Deal With It. I'm Sure Hcan.
Rose For Your Pretty Lady?
Oh,No,She's Not My Pretty Lady.
I Mean,She's Pretty, Uh,But...
He Got Another Girl Pregnant. Oh.
Oh.
You Know What? Suddenly I'm Not So Hungry.
Wait,Betty,Wait.
No,We Can Do This. You Mean So Much To Me.
Oh,My God, He's Proposing!
What? What? No,No.
(Man) Champagne For The Happy Couple. No,No. No,No,I'm Not.
Wait. I Would,But...
I Can't Do This.
No,Uh...
You Okay?
Where Are Ey?
Down In The Kitchen.
She's Licking Fondue Cheese Off His Fingers.
What's Wrong?
I Remember Everything.
Dad's Been Lying To Me This Whole Time,
Acting Like Some Loving Father.
He Hates Me.
No,He Doesn't. He Just Wanted To Use The Accident
As A Way To Start Over With You.
I Remember The Accident,Too. It Wasn't Your Fault.
What?
We Took Dad's Car, And I Had...
I'd--I'd Paid Someone To,Um...
To Cut The Brakes.
What? No,You Didn't.
Yes,I Did.
He Was Trying To Get Rid Of Me, And So I Was Trying To...
What? Kill Him?
Oh,God. Alexis,What The Hell Is Wrong With You?
I Was Torturing Myself. I Thought I Put You In A Coma.
All This Time You Wanted To Murder Our Father?
Daniel,I'm Sorry.
Please Don't Tell Him.
Wouldn't Believe Me Anyway.
So You Had A Big Day,Huh?
Stealing A Car, Crashing A Car.
I Think We Should Talk About It.
Are You Serious?
Yeah,I Know You Think I Haven't Been Paying Attention
To What's Been Going On Lately,
And Maybe I Haven't, But That's Gonna Change.
Oh,So Now You're Gonna Turn Back Into A Mother?
What's That Supposed To Mean?
It's Not Exactly A Part-Time Job When You Feel Like It.
Oh,No, Get The Hell Back Here.
I Am Your Mother. Don't You Forget It.
Let Go Of Me. No,Justin,Listen.
A Kid Losing His Father--
That Is Not Supposed To Happen.
And I Would Do Anything-- Anything In The World
If I Could Bring Him Back.
But... It's Just You And Me.
We're All We've Got.
And I'm Getting Scared, Justin,
Because I Feel Like We're-- We're Moving Like This.
So I Think It's Time We Pull It Together,Yeah?
I Mean,I Been Acting Like An 80 Year Old,
And You With The... With The Attitude
And The Clothes--
That's Not You.
I Just Wanted Him To Be Proud Of Me.
Oh,Baby,He Was Proud Of You.
He Is.
Just Exactly, Exactly Like You Are.
I Just Miss Him So Much.
Oh,Me,Too.
But It's Gonna Be Okay.
Just Let It Out.
We're Gonna Be Okay.
Oh.
If You Had Told Me When I Woke Up This Morning,
That I Would End Up At Your Apartment,
I Woulnot Have Believed You.
Will You Stop Grinning?
You Picked Me.
I Didn't Pick You. I Just Wanted To See "Psycho."
* You Picked Me Over An Underwear Model *
What Is That?
That--That Is A Dance You're Never Gonna See Again.
Exactly.
So What If I Get Scared?
Well...
Then I'll Be Right Here Next To You.
What? (Henry) I Need To Talk To You.
Why? What Could There Possibly Be Left To Say?
I Just Don't Want Things To End Like This.
So You Had To Follow Me All The Way Home?
No,I Followed You Because I Didn't Want You
Walking Alone At Night.
Henry,Please.
Stop. Stop Being So Nice.
You're Not Making This Any Easier.
Well,What Am I Supposed To Do?
I Don't Know.
Kick A Puppy Or Knock Over A Midget.
I-I Think The More Considerate Term
Is "Little Person"?
No. See? This Is Exactly What I'm Talking About.
Well,I Don't Know What To Do.
We Said We Were Gonna Avoid Each Other
And That Didn't Work.
Being Friends Practically Got Us Married.
So What's Left? Should I Leave "Mode"?
Okay.
I'll--I'll Give My Notice On Monday.
Daniel Can Help You Find Something.
Yeah.
Good-Bye,Henry.
Good-Bye,Betty.
There Is Another Option.
There Is?
(Man) * You Must Remember This
I Know You're Leaving In Five Months,
And I Know Everyone's Gonna Say It's A Big Mistake,
And I Know That I'm Gonna Get My Heart Broken,
But Maybe It's Worth It.
Are You Sure?
* It's Still The Same Old Story *
* A Fight For Love And Glory *
* A Case Of Do Or Die
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入
* The World Will Always Welcome Lovers *
* As Time Goes By