Previously on "ugly betty"...
Why would you ever agree to help wilhelmina?
Can we talk about it?
- Hi,daddy.
- Alex?
Bradford meade won't be able to
keep his hands off you.
That's the idea.
- I saw you acting crazy and I
- Your day is over!
Punch out!
So are you giving petra the may cover or the june?
- What,are you also her manager?
- I'm her mother.
Petra is 16?
You didn't ask to see i.d.,did you?
It's daniel. Sounds like he might be in trouble.
I've punched out.
Ay,betty! What are you doing here?
I sleep here!
What are you doing sneaking in my window
like you're back in high school?
I was out last night... With santos.
But i don't want papi to know,or justin,yet.
I mean,i don't even know if this is " you"
Or just,you know,"i love you naked."
Okay,so,you are back in high school.
What are you doing here anyway?
Aren't you supposed to be at work?
I'm calling in sick.
Oh,what,are you still mad at everyone there?
Why wouldn't i be?
Christina's my best friend.
I confided things to her,
And daniel told me to butt out of his life,
That i'm just his secretary.
- And henry...
- Well,what did he do?
Nothing.
But he has a girlfriend,
And that's just thcherry on the sundae.
Would you like adae?
Maybe
Well,toug it's monday. Go to work. Be an adult.
Said the girl with a leaf in her hair.
I'm just saying,
A job is not about making friends.
It's about making money...
And stealing office supplies.
By the way,we're out of coffee filters.
Well,that's certainly a nice way to
wake up in the morning.
Think of me as your caf?Au lait.
I wish i didn't have to leave.
I am not lookingoroord to my meeting with alex.
Oh,you poor dear.
You wanna talk about it?
No,no. It's my problem. I'll deal with it.
Bradford,i hope you don't just think of me
as your morning pickmeup.
I'd like to think i'm an important part
of your life...
Someone you can talk to.
You know,if you really wanna
take my mind off things...
The postman can always ring twice.
Ah,the miracle of modern medicine.
I already told you,Mr. Meade.
Either you put my daughter on the cover of "mode,"
Or i tell the police that you like to...
How you sa.. Play in the minor leagues.
Stop laughing. You'll get wrinkles.
Uh,look. I put together some money.
There's $75,000.
Is that enough to forget this ever happened?
This isn't about money!
This is about petra's career.
She's going to be the next kate moss,
but notsuch a piggy.
Okay,look. Um... We have a big photo shoot today
With our sister magazine,"mode braz."
I think i can probably get you in.
Ooh,i already have the wax.
Shut up,petra.
Nice try,Mr.Meade,but she is n interested
in a corner picture on page 80.
It's the cover or jail.
Come on,petra. You must be starving.
Let's get you a club soda.
Suck it up. It's just a job.
Betty,i'm glad you're here.
Isabella from bungalow 8 called.
Apparently you left your pantshere tuesday night.
Betty...
Monique wants to know if you're taking her
to the soho house on friday.
Otherwise,wilmer valderrama's in second position.
- Can't we talk about friday night?
- Not necessary.
Oh,and the cafeteria's out of bagels,
So i'm going down to the kiosk to get your bagel.
Can i get you something else?
You're really not gonna let me say anything?
You said it already.
You're my boss,and i'm just your assistant.
I'll be back in ten.
If i ever get my hands on the man
whinvented these things
And let me assure you,
it was a man.
Here find something to replace them with.
Anything but cyanide.
I need him alive...
Just not all of him alive.
So lil' bradford's keeping you up at night?
Try to nod off,
And when the finish line approaches,
he starts howling like a wounded beagle.
Sexy. Is it really worth it?
Well,the only way i can run this empire is
if i marry that horn dog.
Well,what about claire the current Mrs.Horn dog?
First things first.
Willie,i'm not an expert about
moving past the sex
Because well,why?
But if you wanna move from mistress to missus,
Maybe you should make yourself
a little more indispensable.
You know,find the thorn in his paw
and pull it out.
Out of the mouths of gays.
A check for $10 million?
It's all yours...
If you resign from "mode" and disappear,
for good this time.
So you called me in here to buy me off?
I have one child now daniel.
I want him in charge of "mode."
You stupid son of a bitch.
You don't get it,do you?
I'm not going anywhere until i make you pay
for everything you've done to me.
Spend your money on something else.
Good morning,sloppy.
What? I said good morning.
You got messages.
Christina called,like,1,200 times.
I'm pretty sure she was drunk dialing.
And your nerd lover keeps sniffing around.
Henry is not my lover.
And just throw away the messages from christina.
Ooh,someone's got their bih on.
Vares.I'm here to see wilhelmina slater.
I have a 9:00 to show her my new designs.
Mm. Take a seat.
Fierce.
Fierce back.
So wait.
You go to court with this lawyer next month,
And that's it? You're a citizen?
Pretty much.
My new lawyer says i'm on the fast track.
That's great.
We need a party...
With a theme.
"Crossing the border."
We'll have a big fence at the door
and make everyone climb over it.
You do that.
- Hey,mom.
- Good morning.
Lose the earrings.Too big.
Bye!
Morning,papi. No time for breakfast.
I gotta be at the cosmetology institute at 10:00.
If you're late,they make you sweep the hair.
You look a little tired.
Oh,i didn't get much sleep last night.
I started watching suzanne somers
"qvc slumber party."
See,she wears pajamas
and she makes everybody waffles.
And she had this one woman from virginia
named tammy lynn
Who said the funniest thing
You do realize you put in too many details
when you lie?
I know. Damn it! Why can't i stop?
Hilda. You went out with santos.
I heard you climb the drainpipe.
Did he at least walk you to it
and give you a boost?
Okay,so i was with santos. So what?
I'm not a kid anymore. I can do what i want.
That's your problem,mija.
You never think things through.
Oh,you never let up! God,i hate this house!
I'm so out of here when i'm 40!
You got I.D.?
Oh,hello.
You are the man from the office.
Hi. Can i get an onion bagel?
Lightly toasted,with a dollop of cream cheese
Not a smidge,not a smear,but a dollop.
He's very specific.
- Well,i don't!I  i have to work.
- Don't you understand?
Hey! A right.Wait are you waiting for?
Hurry up.Slap it on.I gotta get out of here.
- Betty.Hi.Uh,we didn't see you.
- Hi.
Sorry for the sad face. We're fighting.
You don't have to tell everyone we meet
we're fighting.
It's just betty.
Oh,oh,betty,if you moved halfway across
the country to be with the person you loved,
Wouldn't you want him to come home from the
office at a normal time every once in a while?
Oh,and betty,what would you do
if you had a girlfriend
who relied oyou for absolutely everything?
I don't know.
I'm still trying to figure out
Why does an onion bagel cost
more than a raisin bagel?
I gotta go. Bye.
Oh.It's you.
Uh... Look...
Can we please talk because i am really,
really sorry.
You know what? I need to get this to daniel.
I'm gonna take the stairs.
Hmm? No,i don't think so.
Betty!
Listen,about earlier
Betty!I really need to explain.
Betty!You can't just stop speaking to me.
Betty!Betty!
- Betty!
There she is! Betty!
Oh,get her!
- I can smell her.I can smell her.
- Stop! Stop!
I'm sick.
I'm going home.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:karoro
Ugly Betty
Season 02 Episode 20
Well,well,well.
Look who decided to make a surprise appearance.
Well,this is an editorial meeting.
I am editorin chief.
Why wouldn't i be here? Hmm?
No open bar,to start with.
Well,I think I justsaved next month's issue.
Meet your new cover girl.
Bam!
Bam?
I can't believeI was ever a guy.
Daniel,this girl's biggest credit is
a toothpaste adin the ukraine.
You want me to bumpscarlett johansson for her?
Scarlet johansson?
Tired.
Oh,I get it.
You got this chick in bedby
offering her the cover.
Forget it.
It's been set for weeks.
I control half this magazine.
I want her on the cover.
And I control the halfthat actually does the work
and I'm sayingno freaking way.
I know this isa little uncomfortable
but rinsing the hairwith cold water closes
the cuticlesand smoothes the hair.
-Hey,hilda.
-Hey.
Hey,aunt betty.
Why aren't you in school?
I agreed to let him skip gym
if he agreed to be my hair model.
She made me doa couple push-ups.
Why aren't you at work?
Well,I tried.
But I-I couldn't suck it up.
It was just really hard.
I don't know.
Maybe I should just quit.
Justin,go towel off.
You,sit.
They say that 50%of this job is listening,
and you are in desperate need of hairapy.
-Ms.Slater...
-Do I know you?
-Uh,no.
-Then stop talking to me.
-I guess my meeting is canceled.
-Don't take it personally.
She once made dolcewait for three hours
and gabbana for five.
She hates gabbana.
She never forgave him for something
that she can't remember.
marc!
-I--ooh...
-Bulgy.
Well...it was great while it lasted.
-See ya.
-Hey,wait.
I actually feel bad for you.
And I never feel badfor anyone.
Here.
You can havetuesday at 10:00.
Lindsay'll be backin rehab by then,
anyway.
I don't knowhow to thank you.
Wait,I do.
Here--for you.
Only that would do this justice,anyway.
Mm,you are so right.
Oh,if I were a gay guy,I would so tap that.
Girls,smile!
My conceptis about sun and fun.
This is notabout global warming.
It's about tan lines.
Okay?Listen.
So which one'sthe creative director
from "mode brazil"?
Oh,my god.
When I die,have me cremated and
sprinkledall over his body.
Messages,please.
Uh,your lunch with donnais canceled.
Liz from commes des garnsneeds
to talk to you asap.
And,uh,oh!ta-da! Here you go.
He won't even be able to keep
the remote up tonight.
What'd your eplace them with?
It's better if you don't know.
I'm just kidding. It's mints.
Oh,my god.
-When I die,I wanna be cremated and spri--
-Already did it.
Amanda,where did you get that jacket?
A new up-and-coming designer--tavares.
No last name,'cause he's that good.
Well,the buttonstotally ruin the line,
but besides that,I don't hate it.
Why don't I know about him?
Oh,um,well,he...he....
I think he's in your bookfor tuesday.
Good work,Marc.
Yeah,Marc.Good work.
That is wrong...wrong.
Take five.
Uh,touch-ups?
Why don't you goand ask someone what
global warming is?
I think your models are depressed.
Everyone in new yorkis depressed.
In my country,a woman buries her husband,
throws on a bikiniand goes to the beach.
But a black bikini,becauseshe still has to mourn.
Yeah,of course.
-Rodrigo veloso,creative director of "mode brazil"
-Alexis--
-Meade.
I always know the name of the most beautiful
womanin the room.
I mean,clearly,they're not my friends.
Maybe I shouldjust start over,
find new peoplewho won't let me down.
What is that?
That's my wise hairdresser's nod.
They say you gotta do it,
even if you're not listening.
I was,I was.
Calm down.
And you know what I think?
You're too hard on your friends.
-Are you kidding me?
-You are!You always have been.
You are,aunt betty.
You guys don't know what you're talking about.
-I'm out of here.
-Okay.
Well,I have two words for you-- trina dipaolo.
Mr.Meade.Uh,Daniel?
If you're looking for betty,she's not here.
Yeah,I know.It's not--
Um,it's just about the $75,000 check
I cut for you.
It's kind of a big"miscellaneous expense,"
so if you could justtell me what it's for.
Henry,you don't have to hide it.
You can have the check back.
I'm not gonna need it in prison.
I can't believe you would even say
that name to me.
Who's trina dipaolo?
Betty's best friendin high school,
until she ended it.
No.Trina is the one who ended it,
when she ruined our anti-prom.
What's an anti-prom?
It was our celebration of how much
we hated the prom.
I loved my prom.
And nine months later,
I hada wonderful reminder of it.
Trina and I plannedour anti-prom for months.
We knew no boyswere gonna ask us
So we stayed homeand we ate cookie dough
and we rented "carrie"...
Classic girl rage.
Okay,do you wanna hearwhat happened or not?
So we were sitting on the couch watching "carrie.
Okay,can I look?
Can I look?
Oh,my god.
You two losers are actually doing this?
Yeah,the gym teacherjust got cut in half.
You can look now.
-Trina!
-Move over.
-It's not funny.
-Move.Oh,my god.
John travolta was hot.
What happened?
And then trinagot a phone call
and it turned into oneof the worst nights
of my life.
You're leaving me to go to the prom?
Betty,it's sam pappas.
I've had a crush on him since
he put gum in my hair.
His date got chicken pox,
and he has no one else to go with.
It's a prom night miracle.
But we made a pactin yearbook committee.
This is our anti-prom...
You're sad and pathetic and
will neverhave a boyfriend.
Traitor.
Pig's blood?
okay,I was there,and that is not
what happened at all.
Listen,we made a pact in year book committee.
-This is our anti-prom!
-I know.
And I know it's sad and pathetic,
but this is the closest
I'll ever get to having a boyfriend.
Just go,you traitor.
please understand.Betty--
Okay,maybe I embellished a little.
But it may as well have been pig's blood.
That's what it felt like.
Aunt betty,you are so theater.
Betty,she called you for days,
and you neverreturned her phone calls.
You just totally shut her out
because she made one mistake.
-Well,it was a big one.
-Yeah?
Was it worth it?
How was the restof your school year?
Who'd you eatlunch with?
-The lunch ladies.
-Was it eleanor?She is such a gossip.
Okay,hairapist,what would you have done?
I would've told trina how that made me feel
and that is what you should bedoing with
daniel and christina.
-It's too hard.
-Why,betty?
Because you don't want them to see
how hurt you are?
Because you're afraid that you're gonna lose them?
Haven't you already?
I thought you said jobswere just about paychecks.
Obviously not for you.
I've never known anyone
who'sbeen blackmailed before.
It's so "all my children"...
Which I used towatch with my mother,
and I don't know why I just said that.
Look,I'm sorryI dumped all this on you.
I guess I needed to talk to someone.
There aren't that many people here
to do that with.
Yeah,I miss betty,too.
Well,she warned meabout screwing up.
I know I was drunk,
but I never thoughtpetra could be underage.
Well,it sounds likeyou were set up.
That doesn't change anything.
Maybe I should face the consequences.
No,you have to get alexis to put petra
on the cover.
Look,I tried that.
Well,if you--if youtell her what's going on,
then she'll do it.
Uh,yeah.You don't know alexis.
She is family.
It has to count for something.
Oh,and wilhelmina flipped for the jacket
you gave me.
How much do you love me?
It's matt damon,and then you.
Oh,one thing--she hated those buttons.
If you've got them on anything else,burn them.
Really?
Yeah,and now that I think about it,you might
wanna take the sequinsoff that black cocktail.
Sequins remind herof the bad times at 54.
What about the capris?
How does she feelabout tortoise shell?
Okay,okay,okay.
Mucho,muchobig favor.
Could you please cometo my studio tonight
and tell me what Ms.Slater will love
and what she will hate?
Please.This is such a big opportunity for me.
Well,if fashion duty calls...
and I do love free clothes.
There will be free clothes,right?
Plenty.
After the shoot,perhaps you will
join me for dinner?
There's this little restaurant I know,
and I would loveto take you there.
I'm afraid I havea lot of work to do.
But thank youfor the invitation.
I'll keep myself available in case
you change your mind.
I see you've met rodrigo.
Quite a specimen,isn't he?
I guess.
He asked me out to dinner.
-And you said?
-No.
Alexis,why?
Because it's dinner,and that means sex.
I know that.
I used to be a guy.
And what's wrong with sex?
Well,I haven't-- it's--I haven't exac--
Ever since I-- I haven'T...
Taken the new carout for a test drive?
That's one way to put it.
Oh,alexis.What are you waiting for?
Sooner or later,someone's gonna have to put
the key in the ignition.
*******the girl's mother.
Either we putpetra on the cover,
or they'll go to the police.
My total lack of surprise--
is it real or is it botox?
I need your help,alexis.
This is not funny!
Yeah,it is,because you're the one
our father trusts.
Just this morning,he offered me $10 million
to resign and leave youin charge of "mode.
Look,I didn't know that.
But you can't hold this against me.
Sorry,danny,but you just became a little
pawn in this game.
You want miss teen kazakhstanon the cover?
You're gonna bethe one to resign.
So,what,you'd screw meover just to piss off dad?
Yep.
You have a cold heart,alexis.
Had it installed with the other upgrades.
Here you go,santos.
Have a bite.
You first.
what are you being so suspicious for?
Can't a man have a mealwith his daughter's,um...
what exactly are you two?
We're dating.
Is that why you called me over?
I wanna have a little chat.
Let me take you back in time.
1995--remember that year?
Yeah,sure.
Knicks lost in the play-offs.
Braves won the series.
"Sunset boulevard" wonthe tony for best musical.
Yeah.Justin made mea broadway-a-day calendar.
That was also the year when my daughter
spent a month crying in her bedroom
because she was pregnantand you walked out on her.
Look,man,are we gonnado this again?
12 years later,and I still gotta prove to you--
You don't have to proveanything to me,santos.
I don't careenough about you.
But for some reason,my daughter
and my grandson do.
Look,you walked away once.
We both know you're gonna walk away again.
So do it now,before anyone starts dreaming about
a future that's nevergoing to happen.
My assistant saidyou were looking for me.
Yes.
I've been thinking about your offer for
dinner tonight
-and now I'm thinking...Yes!
-Excellent.
But there's somethingwe should talk about first.
I don't know how this is possible,
but I guess you don't know...
that you used to be a man?
That made it to brazil?
You're international,alexis meade...
like the house of pancakes.
it's nice to see you laugh.
You have so much sadnessin your eyes.
I don't care about who you were.
I want to know who you are now.
See you around 8:00.
Christina?
Hello?
christina,we must talk.
Okay,that's too scary.
what do I say?
God,I want an ice cream sundae.
Chocolate sauce?
No,hot fudge.
Nuts?No nuts?
Yeah,go for the nuts.
Why not?
Okay,uh,focus.
Um,Christina,can we please talk?
-Betty!
-Henry.Hi.
I put your paycheckin your desk.
Are you feeling better?
I didn't think you'd be back.
Uh,I kind of felt I had to.
So you heard about daniel?
What?No.
What do you mean?
-Betty,what are you doing?
-You and me havea lot to talk about.
But first,us.
I shouldn'thave shut you out.
That was wrong of me.
But you were more wrong.
You really hurt meat that club.
I know.I am sorry.
I messed up.
-I didn't mean those things I said.
-Good.
Because when you hired me,
you gotmore than an assistant.
You got a friend.
And it's just who I am,daniel.
If you screw up,I'm gonna tell you,
whether you like it or not.
I know.I need that.
I need you,betty.
So are we okay?
Of course we are.
16!Are you crazy?
What the hell were you thinking?
I was thinkingshe was a lot older.
I swear.I had no idea.
Okay,I believe you.
I believe you.
But what are we--16!
-I know.I-I know.
-Okay.
-How do we fix this?
-There's only one option.
I have to resign.
Alexis is gonna be running this magazine
from now on.
Ah,yes.
Pink silk?
Petal,yes.
Fuchsia,no.
Amanda,I love you.
You are totally saving my behind.
More like an a-plus-hind.
oh,can I please,please,please try this on?Please!
Sure.Dressing room's down the hall.
Oh,like you care,nancy.
So anyway,we should totally do lunch on tuesday
after your meetingat balthazar.
We can celebratewith oysters and champagne.
How does that sound?
Oh,my god.
Is that--do you have a--
Are you thinking about matt damon right now?
I have a little confessionto make.
-You going out with santos again?
-Yeah.
-Is he late?
-A few minutes,but he'll be here.
-He's gonna honk twice.
-Classy.
You know what?
Maybe I'll wait outside for him.
Hilda,maybe he's not coming.
Will you stop it?
Mija,this is santos.
I just don't want you disappointed if--
What are you doing here?
Why didn't you honk?
We don't needto sneak around anymore.
What?
What are you doing?
What I should have done when "sunset boulevard"
won the tony.
I love you,hilda...
and I want you to be my wife.
*********
Tyra's about to kill offf our top models.
Okay,honey.
We need to talk.
I just have to show you something,
so sit,sit,sit,sit,sit.
Half-karat,emerald-cut.
It's beautiful.
Took dad long enough.
-You mean you knew?
-Oh,come on,mom.
Every morning you smell like paco rabanne.
So what'd you say?
Did you say yes?
I didn't say anything yet.
I wanted to talk to you first.
Why?
Because this is about us.
It's been you and mefor a long time,kid.
This isyour decision,too.
No,mom.It's not.
In a few years,I'm gonna beout of this house.
So if you wanna marry dad,don't do it for me.
Do it because you love him.
I love you.
Before I sign this,I have one condition.
You're not reallyin much of a position
to bargain,daniel.
Look,I've given youeverything you want.
Just make sure betty has a job here.
I can't believe alexisis doing this daniel.
They're family.
Even erica kane forgaveher daughter kendall
when she sleptwith her fourth husband.
All my children.
It's just something I know.
What are you two doing here?
Oh,they wantedto do test shots for
petra's cover next month.
Oh,well,you must be so proud of
how you got thisfor your daughter.
Maybe we shouldput you on the cover of
our mother's dayissue.
One cover girl in the family is enough.
Excuse me.
There's no smoking in here.
You got I.D.
-Oh,my god!
-What are you doing?
Daniel,stop!
You don't have to do this.
-She's not 16.
-Give me backthat purse!
Actually,she's 38.
And I thought my work was good.
That's lena.
-No!No,no,no!
-Betty!
-She's 20!
-Yes!
I told you not to carry it in your purse!
Idiot!
shut up,lena!
I can't believe this was a scam.
You almost ruined my life.
I guess I'm not going anywhere.
Unbelievable.
You should ask for a raise.
Henry!Can you believe it?
We saved the day!
I am totally wonder woman!
And I snatched a purse!
I'm kind of a bad ass.
You are!
I missed you.
I missed you,too.
So did I turn you straight?
'Cause I have turned some guys--
just mostly the other way.
No.Um,I'm--I'm straight...
Just,uh,in the closet.
Oh,wow.The straight closet.
So what's hanging in there?
A lot of flannel?
It's the fashion business.
That's the only way
I could get my foot in the door.
No one will even look at
a straight guy's portfolio.
You know,this is just like the time
I pretended to bea lesbian
to get kay schmidt to do my math home work
in junior high.
Don't you judge me,you big faux-mo.
I wish there was a waywe could make this work.
Well,who says we can't?
When we're in public,
I could be partof your entourage.
And when we're alone,
you're straight,and I'm naked.
-You're really up for this?
-Please.
Great sex and free clothes?
-There will be free clothes,right?
-Plenty.
I had a really bad day.
Any chance we could skip dinner?
Do you need a condom?
I've got one in my wallet?
This is your first timeas a girl,isn't it?
It's just too scary for me right now.
I know you're here and everything,
but I just can't havemy heart broken again.
So you're gonnabreak my heart?
Baby,why do we have to rush into everything?
We're not kids anymore.I just--
I wanna make sure that
we are doing thisfor the right reasons.
The reason I proposed to you is
because I love you,hilda.
Can you honestly look at me right now
and tell me that you don't love me?
I love you.I do.I love you.
Santos!
-Santos!
-Hilda.
Oh,thank god.
Wow.That was...
Worth becoming a woman for.
Why did i have to meet you only days
beforeI go back to brazil?
I wish I could go with you.
-Why don't you?
-Yeah,right.
I'm serious.
Why don't you comeback to brazil with me?
After what you told meabout your family,
what's keeping you here?
It's crazy,isn't it?
I have a beautiful placein leblon,
right on the beach.
You can come for a week...a month...
Careful what you ask for.
I may never wanna come back.
Betty!
I thinkwe deserve some champagne.
Oh,wait.How old are you?
What,it's too soon?
You really think this is something
we should be celebrating?
Oh,I don't know.Let's see...
I could've gone to jail.
I'm not.I could'velost the magazine.
I didn'T.
Yeah,I think it's time to party.
-Daniel...
-Do me a favor.
I'd like youto call those girls
I met at trump's party.
See if they wanna hook up later tonight.
See,I'm officially celebrating
the end of petra-gate.
-Are you kidding?
-What?
They're old.
They're,like,20...something.
Okay,as your friend,
I think I should tell you
I think you have a problem.
You sleep with womento distract yourself
from what's going onin your life.
-You're using them like a drug.
-Come on.
No,I'm serious,daniel.
I did some researchon the internet,
and I really thinkyou need professional help.
Betty,really,I appreciate your concern,
but we can talk about this in the morning.
-Daniel...
-Tomorrow.I promise.First thing.
Maybe I should havetold you all of this before,
but I couldn'T.
Do you understand how hurt I am?
Yeah.I do.
Still don't quitesee how "carrie"
and the prom fit in,but...
I'm glad we've talked.
And I can't say this enough,betty.
-I am so sorry.
-I know.I know.
So how deep into this whole wilhelmina thing
are you?
Oh,just enoughto hate myself a little bit
every day,but it stops now.
Tomorrow morning,I'm gonna tell her to piss off.
Christina,just don't do anything
that's gonna get you in trouble.
I have to do something.
I could--
Maybe I couldget some information
that would helpyou and daniel.
She's always yakking awayin front of me.
Do you know she makes her cleaning lady use
the bathroomat the korean market?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
I think I've hadenough intrigue for one day.
I'm gonna get out of here.
Do you wanna maybe grab a bite to eat?
Or go for a sundae?
You wrote iton a post-it...twice.
Not tonight.
But soon?
Okay.
Good work.
I'm very pleased.
The rest of the money will come
when the job is done.
Along with a promotion to editor-in-chief
of mode brazil.
You get herout of the country,
and you'll have everythingyou ever wanted.
It's only a matter of time.
She's already hooked.
You're a genius.
Having rodrigo lure alexis out of
the country was a brilliant idea.
Well,I knew the bribe would never workwith alexis.
She's lonely.
Little orphan trannyneeds a man.
How did I gothis long without you?
Oh,I was asking myselfthe same thing.
We are the perfect team,bradford.
It's like we weredestined to be together.
Willie,what we have is wonderful
but I need to tell youthe same thing I told fey--
I'm never gonna divorce claire.
Of course.
We're just,um,having fun.
So let's have some fun.
-You took one of your pills?
-With you...
I don't think I'll ever need to take one again.
Come here,my evil minx.
-Oh,my god!This is so amazing!
-I know.
I'm gonna bring home every wedding issue
of mode
and then you can pickyour favorite dress,
and we'll go to the bride queen and
get a total knock-off.
Okay,but I wanna show cleavage.
Oh,that's a new lookfor you.
Oh,my god.I gotta get to work.
Oh,and I'm gonna be late tonight.
I'm gonna have dinner with trina.
Yes,I called her.
And it's great thatshe went to the prom.
You know she ended up marrying sam pappas?
-No way.
-They make choke collarsfor dogs.
They're very happy.
-Morning.
-Morning,papi.
Are you okay?
I just had a talk with my new lawyer.
What's wrong?
They're sending meback to mexico.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:karoro