-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
papi are you ok?
what's wrong?
nothing , just a little ?? in my throat
sorry about that
why? no  it's fine.
?
yeah,but..
you know sometimes
when you ???
something like..  seem
smoke can be pretty ??
but this isn't ??
it's.. no ??
you just relax
? don't you anything
like food or more tea?
yeah,something ??
yeah
what i really want is ??
oh mm... ?
papi, medical bills?
didn't i tell you that we're
supposed to worry about these?
i just want to help out.you can help out
by just getting better, okay?
yeah.
what happened?
i thought you said
you were gonna send these
over to insurance.
no. that's what i was telling
you the other day. remember
but, hilda
idisculpe!
everything okay?
(chuckles) yeah.
yeah. oh! did you just hear
a uebird?
oh, yeah, the one that i saw
out back the other day?
uh-huh.
it's winter.
i know.
it's weird, right?
i thought you were gonna
send these in to insurance.
they said that
they could process it faster
if we faxed it in, so i figured
you could just do it from work.
oh, okay, fine.
oh, and before i forget,
i made up a checklist of things
for you not to forget
to do today.
you know, to help you out.
oh, that is terrific.
is that in addition
to all the post-it notes
that you have left
everywhere?
well, you get busy, you know?
it's easy to forget.
which reminds me, you should
probably take papi in
to see dr. steve,
get that cough checked out.
"take papi to doctor--"
to dr. steve. yeah.
betty, i get it. stop worrying.
i can handle it.
get out of here. just go.
go to work.
oh, but promise me
you're not gonna wear this.
(scoffs) no, i just ran out
of clothes.
i have to go back
to my apartment,
which i haven't seen
in, like, forever.
i'm excited to see it.
(gasps) betty!
oh, my god,
you look fantastic!
aah!
how many times
did i tell you
to stop eating
that fatty mexican food?
you are too young
to have a heart attack.
amanda, i didn't have
a heart attack. my dad did.
ow!
how could you let me
worry about you like that?
what?
i'm sorry, betty. i was just
really concerned about you.
wait. your dad--is he...
he's... (sighs) better.
thank you.
it's been
a rough couple of weeks.
(door closes)
oh, i totally get it.
i had to work extra shifts
at d.t. mcdoubleshots
to make up for
the vacation time off at "mode."
and i will never, ever get
the smell of fried jalapeO
out of my hair.
is that why
you haven't had a chance
to clean up around here?
clean? (laughs)
i missed you.
are these all bills?
oh, i can't believe
how much i'm spending
for a place i never see.
well, i have seen it,
and, unfortunately,
we have roaches.
i know.
at first, i was scared,
and then i tried naming them.
oh, look!
aah!
that's little betty.
she's just like you--
a survivor.
ew. ew, ew, ew.
welcome home.
(daniel)
what a great vacation, huh?
(molly laughs)
you know whathi thinkm i'm a ?
running into heidi and serncerev
everywhere  we went.
i know it's like a way
we ??
no ?? did not you
and kind want be  ??
"oh,eidi how could you do that ??
??
oh,???
you know ???
mmm...
?
oh, come on
we had real photoes
can you dou wesome slideshows
like this?
(beeps)
oh. uh... sorry.
(beeping)
guess we're gonna have to
tell him about us eventually.
i know, but...
he's all alone right now.
telling him just seems cruel.
not to mention how awkward
it'll make work for both of you.
back in college, he was
definitely the jealous type.
maybe he just needs time?
yeah.
(electronic female voice)
you have 214 new messages.
message one.
(sighs)
(daniel) betty, hey.
okay.
hi. how are you doing?
daniel!
how's your father?
(chuckles) what happened
to your desk?
yeah. uh, this is what happens
when i'm gone for two weeks.
my dad is doing better,
thank you.
and thank you
for all those flowers you sent.
is 12 dozen too much?
that's why you should always do
the flower ordering around here.
yep.
not that you can't take
as much time off as you need,
of course.
no, daniel,
i need to be working.
besides, hilda and i are gonna
split the responsibilities
of taking care of my father,
so whatcha got for me?
well, you can take my
vacation photos down to the lab.
i was gonna print
some of the pictures up.
oh.
morning, daniel. oh!
oh! excuse me.
yes, yes, you're excused.
no, wait, wait, you're not.
here.
cover photos of our
exclusive halston dres
the press is already sniffing
around for them desperately.
i'll keep them
someplace safe.
what, are you dense?
i want you to leak them.
i'd ask marc. he wants to,
but i hate to reward him
without any good reason.
it's okay, betty.
we'll catch up later.
oh, i did miss work so--
the look of fear
in people's faces.
i take it
from your goggle tan
you did some skiing?
and i take it from your tan
you also got some sun?
mm-hmm.
or is it
that awful spray tan?
you know, you look
a bit jaundiced.
hey.
oh. hi, connor.
(daniel) oh...
it looks like
you did some skiing, too.
uh, snowboarding.
i was in switzerland.
aspen.
well, good.
i'll leave you to it then,
shall i? hmm.
you know, it's kind of funny
you guys had the--
yes. yes, yes. hilarious.
as much as i love
your witty observations,
i need to speak to connor,
uh, about some upcoming
ad meetings.
oh, connor.
(raises voice)
mm.
we have
to control ourselves.
didn't we have an agreement
we'd keep this
out of the office?
we did.
i came in here to pee.
(chuckles) so you did.
look,
we had a wonderful time
in the swiss alps
for two weeks,
but now it's time
to get back to work,
which means we have
to try harder to hide it,
starting with, uh...
this?
mm, it is a bit suspicious,
isn't it?
suspicious?
even the "special" boy
in the mail room
could put the two of us
together.
what's that?
all you need to know is that
it's expensive, illegal
and will even out
your tan lines.
you're not allergic to panda,
are you?
you saw nothing.
uh, well, actually--
oh! oh, oh, oh, oh.
yes, yes.
nothing!
no, no, no, no.
(works zipper)
i saw nothing, but they are
abt to see everything.
(sighs) thank you, marc.
yeah.
(justin) i don't think
mom's had a chance
to talk to dr. steve yet.
really? well,
is everything okay?
no, no, it's good.
this girl from my school
hired mom
to do her and her friends' hair
for her quinceaEra party.
15 girls.
is that betty?
yes. bye, betty.
oh, my god, oh, my god!
did you hear the good news?
yeah!
yeah, that's, um, great.
i just--you know,
i'm--i'm worried
that you might not have time
to do all of that,
you know,
with papi and everything.
ay, what? it's work.
we need the money right now.
yeah. no, i get it.
i just, um...
you know, you haven't even
had a chance to take him
to see dr. steve today.
ay, betty, please,
stop worrying.
i got this, okay?
okay.
look, i gotta go.
we'll discuss this later, okay?
love you. bye.
(sighs)
mrs. meade.
sorry. i have a system.
i didn't mean to snap.
i... i just have a lot
on my plate.
well, i just came by
to say hello.
oh! you're back
from your trip.
how was your vacation
in paris?
well, i spent the entire time
being groped by perverts
in montmartre.
ooh, i'm sorry.
why?
the french still appreciate
something finely aged.
i spent a lot of time
with alexis and d.j.
oh, betty, i was so sorry
to hear about your father.
how is he?
he's... good.
thank you for asking.
he's got this cough,
but my sister's gonna take him
to see dr. steve.
dr. steve?
yeah, he's our family doctor.
we've been seeing him for years.
dear,
i've had many doctors,
and the only ones i ever called
by their first names
were slipping me prescriptions
for painkillers.
oh, well, dr. steve
isn't like that.
tell you what, betty--
i'm on the board
of stuyvesant memorial.
dr. farber
is the finest cardiologist in the city.
why don't i just call and make
your father an appointment?
oh, no. no, i could never
ask you to do that.
and besides, we would
never be able to afford it.
(chuckle
well, dr. farber works
in the meade wing
of the hospital.
it's not gonna cost you
anything.
hey, guys!
i've got some good news.
oh, good. us, too.
talked to dr. steve.
he said it's probably just
a cold, and papi's fine.
um, what did he do,
just listen to his chest,
take some blood samples?
no. we didn't go in.
we just talked to him
on the phone.
(coughing and hacking)
i'm fine.
hey, do you hear
a bluebird?
it's night. it's winter.
i don't hear anything.
well, maybe we should
go and check,
you know, just in case?
hilda, i thought
we were gonna talk
about you taking that job.
i have it
under control, betty.
dr. steve said papi is fine.
it's a mild cough.
it hasn't moved to his chest.
if it gets worse,
then i take him in.
but you haven't
even had a second
to take him in to the doctor,
and apparently,
you couldn't finish
a single thing on my list.
sorry, betty,
i thought things
like "de-linting his sweaters"
could wait.
what is that
you didn't give him
his pills for today?
yeah, he can't take them
before he eats.
it upsets his stomach.
well, then why don't--
why don't--
just wanted
a little more tea.
uh... oh, i think the bird
went around that way.
oh, yeah. crazy bird!
(bird squawks)
look, claire meade got us
an appointment
with her cardiologist
tomorrow in the city.
okay, all right.
so i'm supposed to give up
my job with the quinceaEra?
we still need the money.
got my tea.
oh, good.
i think i heard that bird
out front.
i might not do things the way
that you want me to,
but you can't be
betty bossypants
when you're off at work
all day.
well, you know what, hilda?
i only have to be
betty bossypants
when nothing gets done
around here.
and don't call me
betty bossypants.
well, then stop trying
to control everything.
look, you don't want to take
papi to the city? fine.
i'll do it.
i'll take over.
you'll what?
i'll take over with papi.
you don't wanna help?
i'll just find a way
to do it all by myself.
oh, i would like
to see you try.
i will.
fine.
fine!
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
丑女贝蒂 第三季第12集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：个人id
校对：个人id
时间轴：加饭的菜猪
well, i guess there is something
everyone can agree on.
dr. farber
is an excellent doctor, papi.
mr. suarez,
how are you feeling?
just a little chilly.
is there some reason
it has to be so cold in here?
yes. now i've reviewed
your chart.
i'd like to run
some tests.
dr. steve was pretty sure
it's just a cough.
two weeks
after a quadruple bypass,
you can never be
too careful.
yeah, and, papi, hilda only
spoke to dr. steve on the phone.
on the phone--terrific.
that's how i order
chinese food.
(chuckles)
breathe.
(inhales and exhales)
all right. again.
all right. i want an x-ray
to check for fluid in the lungs,
an e.k.g., an echo,
and draw some blood.
c.b.c.,
check for dressler's?
yeah.
dressler's?
inflammation
of the pericardium.
you did the right thing,
bringing your father in.
who's next?
see? aren't you glad
we came in?
my butt is cold.
(connor) you were a killer
in there.
i'm continuously amazed
by you.
well, that makes
the two of us. (chuckles)
marc, don't just stand there
like a gay flagpole.
we want to celebrate.
go get something bubbly
and expensive.
yeah, it's what
i live for.
how you convinced
the guerlain people
to incase their ad buy
by 6% in this market...
well, you said the advertisers
would never do it,
and i saw it as a challenge.
well, maybe when we meet
with the jaeger-lecoultre people
this afternoon,
i might get them
to increase their ad buy
by, say... 7%.
what about eight?
how about nine?
or maybe...
ten?
yes.
i want you to give me 10%.
ahem. collette!
klaus! other klaus!
you're early.
(laughs nervously)
(swiss-french accent)
jaeger-lecoultre has put us
on a tight schedule, so...
we were hoping that wilhelmina
could see us now.
oh, it's funny.
you'd think people who work
for a watch company
would be precisely on time.
(laughs)
follow me.
you know what?
it's an american tradition
to circle the building
three times
before a meeting.
sometimes four.
well, it's a good thing
we got him in,
because dr. farber's running
a bunch of tests.
what tests? is papi okay?
yeah, but two weeks
after a quadruple bypass,
you can never be
too careful.
(call waiting beeps)
oh, hilda, that's work.
can i call you back?
work?
wait a minute. don't tell me
you're leaving papi there alone.
because i am up to my ears
in teenagers right now.
i cannot just run off.
no, hilda, i told you,
i can handle it.
look, i'll stay here with papi.
i'll call you with the results.
okay? bye. amanda?
hi, betty. some guy
from a photo lab called
and said you messengered
your phone bill to him.
(gasps) if he pays it,
can i send him our other bills?
what?
s. meade,
can i have that back?
(betty gasps) if daniel's photos
went to suzuki,
then everything's gonna go
to the wrong place.
amanda, i need your help.
and i would totally
help you,
but i'm a little busy
covering daniel's desk
like you asked me to.
i know, amanda,
but i'm at the hospital.
i can't leave.
(gasps) oh, my god.
is it your heart?
no, it's my dad. haven't we
had this conversation?
i know, betty, but these things
get passed down.
they're generic.
look, i can't leave my father,
so i need your help.
will you help me track down
some of these letters?
okay, fine,
what do you need me to do?
marc, throw those people
out of the conference room.
i need to use it for
the jaeger-lecoultre meeting.
actually, i'm...
in a good mood.
i'll throw them out
myself.
about that...
uh, collette and the klauses
have already come and gone.
what? they came early?
well... why didn't you
come get me?
because you were busy snorkeling
in the great barrier reef?
so i was otherwise occupied.
you should've stalled them.
i tried,
but that's not the point.
i'm worried, you know,
that, you know...
will... you know?
marc, mince when you walk,
not when you talk. what?
i don't want it getting out
that the most talented woman
in fashion
is missing meetings because
her head is... elsewhere.
oh, because i missed
one meeting with them?
our swiss friends
will not leave new york
without an audience with me.
i'll call them.
it'll all be fine, you'll see.
get, uh, klaus
on the phone or...
klaus.
betty. uh, how's your dad?
he's getting tests done,
and they won't let me see him,
so in the meantime,
i've been dealing
with a little work snafu.
there was a work snafu, huh?
it's all taken care of.
amanda helped me.
oh. that's--that's great.
the only thing left
is something
i was hoping
i can get done tomorrow.
i have to get suzuki st. pierre
to swap out your vacation photos
for the new picture
of the halston dress.
wait, wait.
suzu-suzuki st. pierre...
has my vacation photos?
oh, no.
you didn't ask me to print out
those type of photos, did you?
again?
coming up, more life-ruining
gossip, but first...
betty, i have to tl you
something. i'm seeing molly.
what, connor's mol?
look, she was with me
in st. barths.
wait. connor's molly?
look, it's not
what you think, okay?
we are actually in love.
daniel, you're in love
with connor's molly?
could you stop
calling her that?
they stopped seeing each other
before we got together.
well, does connor know
about you and...
no.
this could be a huge disaster.
i promised molly
i was gonna keep this a secret.
you have to get
those photos back for me.
now?
betty, yes, now.
but, daniel,
i'm at the hospital.
um, i have to wait--
betty, please, there has to be
something you can do.
(sighs) okay, all right,
i'll find a way
to get the photos back.
i promise.
(beep)
(woman) dr. maddox,
dr. chester maddox,
please go
to the pharmacy.
dr. chester maddox
hold it right there, missy.
no visitors
during medical tests.
oh, i know. i just--
i have to tell my dad
i have a work emergency
that i gotta go deal with.
well, he's gonna be in there
for at least four hours.
how you spend your time
is up to you.
okay, well,
can you just tell him
that i'll be back
as soon as possible?
yeah, okay.
okay. okay.
you can do this, betty.
no.
but--but why not?
pictures of daniel meade
having an affair
with the fiancE
of his c.f.o.--
in my business,
we call that news, honey.
but she's not even
his fiancE anymore.
they broke up before she went
on vacation with daniel.
so see? no scandal.
or even juicier scandal.
he stole her, and they ran away
on a sexy caribbean getaway.
all right, suzuki, can you
just do this as a favor to me?
do i know you?
betty suarez.
we've met, like,
a thousand times.
you've interviewed me...
sorry. i've been working
on this story for months.
really?
'cause these pictures literally
just fell into your lap.
just good, solid journalism
is what i say.
and i'm going with the story
tomorrow.
so good-bye, benny.
(normal voice)
what are you doing?
shh!
marc, i was just trying
to borrow these.
b-b-b-b-b-buh!
marc, what?!
(connor and wilhelmina laugh)
oh. hello, marc...
marc's friend.
actually, it's--
hmm.
marc's friend is fine.
oh, my god.
are they...
no, they are absolutely not.
(laughs)
okay.
but you have to swear
not to say anything to anyone.
(giggles)
(gasps)
swear.
ow.
marc, you're hurting me.
am i?
not really.
ohh.
but i get it.
you're serious.
i'm not gonna
say anything to anyone.
god, why are you
being so weird anyway?
(grunts) why must god test
the pretty people
so much more than
the regular lumpy people?
this is supposed to be my year.
i got into y.e.t.i.
willie is
co-editor-in-chief.
i just don't want her star
to wane before i have a chance
to cash in on
having worked for her.
you know what i think?
good things come
to those who wait.
oh.
plus it helps being pretty.
take me.
i have always wanted
to work daniel's desk,
and now check me o.
(telephone ringing)
do you need to get that?
no, it's fine.
it's just i've never
had to deal with a boss
who cared more
about sex than work.
actually, maybe this is what
working for daniel is like.
why are you looking at me?
be--
oh, marc, there you are.
i need your help.
i need yours.
when daniel blows off a meeting
to go sleep with some floozy,
what do you do?
what?
daniel doesn't do that.
yeah, and this is my real nose,
which it totally is.
okay, so when daniel
gets "distracted by life,"
what do you do?
i just like to see those moments
as career opportunities.
you know, a chance to step it
up, show daniel what i can do.
why, is wilhelmina...
(scoffs) no, no, not at all.
why would you even say that?
but she's a woman.
she has needs.
get over, it betty. grow up.
ahem. what did you want?
i need to get
a gift for suzuki.
i accidentally sent him
something that i need back,
and i just--i have to
do it fast so i can get back
to the hospital and my dad,
and anyway,
i thought you could help me.
a gift for suzuki st. pierre?
he's a serious journalist.
he's not gonna take a bribe.
you need to blackmail him.
what? bribery, blackmail--that's
not at i was talking about.
ll, too bad,
'cause his ex works at meade,
and that bitch'll dish.
fabian? fabian, hi!
you don't know me,
uh, but you might be able
to help me with a problem.
i understand
you dated suzuki st. pierre?
i can't talk about that.
but i thought
you said he'd dish.
not if you approach him
like that.
people who have dated
celebrities
are really secretive about it.
hello, i should know.
you've never dated
a celebrity.
as far as you know.
(muffled voice) jeremy piven.
okay, he goosed you
on the subway once, amanda.
you talk about it constantly.
(normal voice) the point is,
you have to make him talk.
go put the heat on,
sister.
ah!
fabian,
you have to... help me.
um, please?
um, no, i don't.
you tell her
what she needs to know,
or i will tell everyone
you have ambiguous genitalia.
oh, yeah, like a ken doll,
and that's the kind of stank
that don't wash off.
is this suzuki's address?
ow!
um, no. suzuki st. pierre
does not live in jersey.
well, who lives here?
oh, betty,
thank god i reached you.
it is teenage chaos here,
but i just wanted to check
and see how papi's doing.
um, he's fine.
the nurse says he's fine.
oh, good.
can i talk to him?
no. he, uh,
they won't let anybody see him
while he's getting
his tests done.
oh. yeah, i get it.
i get it. i'm just worried
about him, that's all.
listen, betty, thank you.
i know you're crazy
juggling dad and--and work
and everything.
hilda--
(woman) hilda, my hair!
i'm coming! betty, let me
call you back, all right?
but keep me posted.
okay, bye.
(beep)
guess my photos aren't all that
important in the big picture.
oh, they are, they are.
i just have a lot
on my plate right now.
so what is it
you're hoping to find here?
i have no idea.
"byron wu"?
daniel! you're not supposed to
just go through people's mail.
no, we want to find out
who lives here. who's byron wu?
i don't know. maybe...
suzuki's boyfriend?
(whispers) come here.
(man) hey, hey!
nice hustle today, kiddos.
now let's get dressed
get inside,
and i'll go grill some brats.
all right.
you heard your father.
(lowered voice)
betty, is that suzuki?
that's his wife and kids?
hi, suzuki.
or should we say "byron"?
oh, crap.
(suzuki) hit it, hit it,
hit it! whoo!
that's my boy.
so when i graduated
from columbia j-school,
you know, i wanted to be
woodward, bernstein.
but the only jobs available
were britney this,
angelina that.
but isn't that
the stuff you love?
it's the stuff suzuki loves.
wait. so suzuki st. pierre
is made-up?
you think "fashion buzz" would
go near a guy like me?
i mean, look at me.
(effeminate voice)
but as a fabulous, bitchy queen,
the fashion world welcomed me
with open, well-toned arms.
that's creepy.
byron?
don't forget to take the garbage
out when you're done.
(normal voice)
yeah, no prob.
so down to brass tacks.
daniel, bessie--
betty.
betty. you know my secret.
what do you want?
well--
we are not here
to blackmail you.
we're not?
no, but we do need your help.
those photos could destroy
people's lives, byron.
you have your own secret.
you should understand.
(boy) you want me
to try for it?
(laughs)
soft!
(boy) i didn't think so.
(daniel)
that was nice work, betty.
so, daniel,
how long do you plan
on keeping this whole
molly thing a secret?
i don't know.
sometimes honesty isn't always
the best choice, i guess.
i understand that.
it's just... secrets kind of
have a way of getting out.
don't even bother with klaus,
either one of them.
collette's the one
with the real power.
the ice queen
of lake geneva.
well, i have a feeling
you'll be able to melt her.
just, uh, flirt
with her a little bit.
you'd be comfortable
with that?
of course.
it's just business.
well, i'm not sure i'd be able
to pull that off.
i can't just turn it on
for anybody.
really? you've flirted
with me a million times.
that's because i meant it,
because it was you.
so we have
been waiting for...
ten minutes.
(clears throat)
well, perhaps if wilhelmina had
one of your beautiful, elegant,
timeless, handcrafted watches...
we'll come back later.
wait.
since wilhelmina is obviously delayed
why don't i take you through our proposal?
you speak french?
actually,
that's all the french i know,
but if you give me
just a minutes,
i know that i can show you
why "mode" and jaeger-lecoultre
are meant to be together.
excuse me.
where's my father?
he left.
he left? but you said he'd
be in there for four hours.
i guess he was done earlearly.
well, where did he go?
i'm sorry. i don't know
what to tell you.
(beep)
what?
hilda?
i think
i might have lost dad.
all right.
somehow we have to find a way
to get through a whole day
without that always happening.
nothing wrong with creating
a little anticipation
for our swiss friends.
well, it looks to me
like your assistant's doing
a pretty good job
of entertaining 'em.
and, oh, this is the best part.
you're gonna love this.
this is very exciting.
so what we do is we should--
ah, bonjour, mes amis.
bonjour.
ah, collette.
mwah. mwah.
klaus! klaus. mm.
i had no idea you were here,
which is particularly tragic,
since i specifically told
my assistant to call me
as soon as you all arrived.
this is... (singsong voice)
beginning to be a problem.
(chuckles, normal voice)
so if it happens again,
it'll be back to spritzing
perfume at the makeup counter.
(laughs)
that will be all, marc.
nice to look at, but you could
sit a picasso behind his desk
to do the same job.
(collette laughs)
how could you have lost him?
you promised me you
weren't gonna leave him.
i know, but there was
this emergency at work,
and i might've maybe left
for just a minute.
betty, i--
i know, i know. you're mad
at me. i'm mad at me, too.
but can we just try
and find papi?
oh, look, there's dr. farber.
dr. farber! hi!
do you know where my dad is?
yeah, see, my sister
sort of lost him.
uh, i talked to your dad
maybe... maybe two hours ago,
but once his tests are
completed, he's free to go.
and you have no idea
where he went?
can't be far.
two weeks after major surgery,
he's not gonna be running
a marathon. (laughs)
look, i wouldn't worry about
him. his tests came back normal.
he's gonna be totally fine.
oh! that's great. thank you.
not a problem.
did you hear that?
papi's gonna be fine.
yeah. so he didn't have to come
to the hospital at all.
hilda, where are you going?
the doctor said
papi's gonna be fine!
yeah, i heard what he said.
well, then what is
wrong with you?
he was already fine...
until you came in and decided
we had to take him to
some fancy manhattan doctor.
and i thought for a second,
okay, maybe betty's right.
maybe we need to be
more nervous.
but you got me scared
for no reason.
well, what was
i supposed to do?
if something's wrong,
then we have to know about it.
i'll tell you what you could ??
you could have stopped trying
so hard to control everything
that you scared me
half to death.
hilda, if there is a problem,
then we can't just ignore it.
you always do this.
and you always make me feel
like everything i do is wrong,
like if i don't
do things your way,
then i don't love papi.
when have i ever said that?
it's not what you say,
it's how you act.
this is exactly like
when mom was sick.
everything had to be your way.
hilda, when mom got sick,
you disappeared.
you went off with santos
or wherever,
and i stayed home
and took care of papi.
like i'm doing now.
you're in manhattan.
you got your job.
you got your apartment.
where are you?
where am i?
i am here!
i have been here every day!
do you have any idea
what i have had to give up
so that i could be
at home helping out with--
you want to talk
about sacrifice, betty?
i live at home.
i work at home.
and now with papi sick, i gotta
fight you to take one job.
well, i need your help. i guess
i can't do it all by myself.
yeah, i guess you cat.
what?
you know what bothers me
the most, betty?
for all your lecturing...
you weren't even there.
i was the one in ambulance.
(crying) i was the one--
i was holding his hand,
and--and i thought
he was gonna die.
and you know where you were?
you were in the city.
you were at some... party.
that is not fair, hilda.
don't you think it kills me
that i wasn't there?
i think about it
every single day.
it's justin. hello?
mom? grandpa's home.
okay. papi's fine.
he's at home.
all right.
love u.
"bluebird"?
(chuckles) come on.
i'm not stupid.
look, i know you're fighting,
but what i can't live with
is that you're fighting
because of me.
papi, honestly--
papi, that's not true.
please.
now you both are strong,
intelligent, capable women,
but you can't do it all.
so... i've decided.
i'm hiring a nurse to help
take some of the burden.
what?
we cannot afford that.
and you're not a burden.
stop. we can afford it.
i went to the medicaid office
and found out that
they'll help pay
for a rt-time nurse.
help? what's that
supposed to mean?
it means we'll manage.
look, i... i can't control
what happens to me.
but i can control some things,
and i won't
come between you two.
you could use a trim.
i'm sorry i wasn't there
that night, hilda.
if i could go back
and change it, i would.
i don't know
what i would have done...
a little gift
from our new friends
at jaeger-lecoultre.
we landed the account.
nice work.
great. now i won't be late
to any meetings.
uh, i'm sorry.
did i miss something?
you're my assistant.
you took a hit for me.
i brought you a fancy gift.
i expect gratitude,
not attitude.
i'm sorry, willie...
but that was humiliating
for me.
i was doing really well
in there--
it doesn't matter how well
you were doing.
they didn't come here to be
pitched by some assistant.
they came here to be pitched
by wilhelmina slater.
well, maybe i wouldn't
have had to step in
if you hadn't been o--
if i hadn't what?
it's just that i thought
after four years,
i might be able to--
getting thrown under the bus
to make me look good
is part of your job...
unless, of course, you'd like
to find another one.
no, i don't want
another job. i...
never mind. you're right.
(whispers) thanks.
hey, sweetie.
okay, what's the matter?
so you know
how we dodged a bullet
with our vacation photos?
uh-huh, yeah.
look at "page six,"
behind heidi and spencer.
you're cut out of the picture,
but i'm not.
are you done with that?
i'm off. lunch with tom ford.
oh, but, uh,
proenza schouler
are coming to meet
with you at noon.
(sighs) those ad meetings
are so tiresome.
why don't you take it?
if you think you can handle it.
of course, i can always--
give my love to tom
and his chest hair.
cable we can totally
just steal from upstairs.
oh, and we both
have cell phones,
so we don't need a landline.
plus i gave that number out
to too many weirdos anyway.
my god, we have so many.
there's electric and gas
and maintenance
and bergdorf's.
god, it is so hard to know which
one to sacrifice, you know?
mm-hmm. amanda?
i have to tell you something.
you're moving out.
how'd you know?
because your family
needs you right now...
and you're good like that.
yeah.
* a dream of togetherness
* turned into
a brighter mess *
* a faint sign,
my spoken best *
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入
www.tvsubtitles.net