The helicopter
was waiting for me,
gunfire going of all around,
but I couldn't leave.
As long as I live,
I'll never forget the faces of those children
All right, we get it. Darfur is a bummer.
But who wants those images in their head?
She's amazing.
I can't believe you get to work for her.
What you do sounds a lot more fun,
especially during fashion week.
Yeah, well, fashion week isn't nearly as cool
as genocide week.
Sorry. That came out wrong.
You can read the piece in this month's
"New York Review."
Brilliant and depressing,
but mostly brilliant.
Ms. Mastronardi has offered to stay a few minutes
if anyone wants to talk to her.
And no asking for jobs.
Something's been bothering me,
and I'm thinking you could help.
-Is this brown?
-Yes
Because, you know,
I never had the big 64 crayons
that every other kid had..
so I don't know all the obscure colors like, uh...
-Brown?
-Uh, mocha or mud or tree bark.
-Those aren't really colors.
Oh, well, leave it to fashion girl to clear that up.
Oh, uh, no. I'm not fashion girl.
-I'm fashion girl.
-But you work at "Mode."
I'm sports guy. You're fashion girl.
-We're known by our magazines.
-Okay
What do you do at "Mode"?
Um, excuse me.
Actually, um, I'm an assistant to the editor-in-chief,
but I've gotten to do other things.
Like, sometimes I write a column for the web site,
and earlier this year I got to oversee a cover shoot.
Sounds like you're on a great path
to becoming a fashion editor.
Oh, thanks. Yeah, but, um, I got into Y.E.T.I.
Because I'm interested in other magazines.
Like, one day, I would love to do what you do.
Then you might want to get off the fashion track,
and get some other experience,
because right now, fashion's where you're heading.
Oh, okay.
So I suggested to Jodie that anyone who wanted
should pair up with a partner from another magazine,
and that way,we can get experience from different places.
Have you not got enough going on at fashion week?
Yeah, but if I get the girl from "The New York Review",
then it would totally be worth it.
-That would be a good fit for you.
Right? I mean, I love it here,
but I've just never seen myself being in fashion forever,
and for once, I would like to be in a place
that comes more natural,
and then people would stop calling me fashion girl.
Who's calling you fashion girl?
This morning, you've got
the Donna Karan preview,
followed by brunch with Donna Karan
and then the Donna Karan show.
So I'm gonna go out on a limb and assume
that you are wearing--
Cavalli.
Are you sure?
I'm worried that the cavalli makes you look
a little too "Michelle Obama at the mall."
Ugh. Remember what we said about unsolicited opinions?
Yes, yes, I do. Uh, it's just--
-The Cavalli, please.
Have I told you lately what a remarkable body you have?
Ugh! You'd never even know you're about to have a child.
-Give me the damn dress.
-They didn't send it
What? Well, why not?
-Well.
Since you've been seeing Connor,
you haven't been working the circuit as much,
and it's possible that you might have...
fallen off their radar.
-Oh, that is ridiculous.
-Of course it is.
Wilhelmina slater is the most important person
at fashion week.
A "yes" from me determines style.
Do you remember micro buckles of '04?
-Um, no. No, not really.
-Exactly. Because I said no.
Now if the cavalli was not sent,
it was because of human error.
Don't let it happen again.
Yeah, make sure I'm sitting near
Phillip Lim at Peter Som,
and nowhere near Peter Som at Phillip Lim.
Or is it the other way around?
You'll figure it out.
Um, more importantly, I really need you
to deal with these.
Last year, the mandate was
for cuffs to be peering out from jackets.
At Marc Jacobs' preview last night,
suddenly they're peeking instead.
Can you believe it?
-Nope, I can't.
-I mean, it was humiliating.
I need an 1/8 of an inch off all them asap.
Please use your discretion.
I'd be mortified if anyone knew they were mine.
Daniel, do you think you have any
non-fashion related assignments for me?
It's fashion week
at a fashion magazine, Betty.
I mean, I do have this press release you could write.
It's for this designer Heinrich.
Last minute addition at the "Mode" show, but...
I'll take it. Knowing how to write
a press release is useful anywhere.
Okay, I'm ready for fashion week.
Wow! You look beautiful.
Thank you.
Everything I'm wearing hurts.
That's good, right?
Uh, whatever it is you're doing,
it definitely works for me. Shall we?
-Bye.
-Have fun.
Peering? My God, Daniel.
Have some self-respect.
Hey, Betty. We're having a little
going-away party for Elena.
You want to say good-bye before she goes away?
It's Betty!
Good-bye, Elena!
Bye, Betty!
We are gonna miss her so much.
Okay, all right. We all know you're very excited she's  leaving,
but maybe you could tone it back just a little bit.
Hey, I'm just happy that papi's better,
and he doesn't need a nurse anymore.
Oh, good, 'cause I don't think this means
they're gonna stop seeing each other.
Ugh. Please. Once that kinky Florence Nightingale fantasy
is over, it's done.
Haven't I asked you not to use the word "kinky"
concerning our father?
Look, I have to go.
Oh! Wish me luck with "The New York Review."
-Good luck!
-Bye.
Okay, now I mentioned last week that
we'd be picking partners.
I advise you,choose carefully,
because you will be working with this person all year.
And if you're like me, you'll hook up, get married,
get married, cheat, divorce and end up bitter and alone,
but I digress.
Okay!
Let's... pick... partners!
Oh, I am so excited you want to work with me!
Totally! Not just because of
the giant cookie you sent to my office.
Oh. Was it good?
All right, is everyone sitting next to the person they picked?
Now turn to the person on the other side,
and meet your new partner.
In publishing, you must expect the unexpected.
-I get fashion girl.
-And I get sports guy.
And one last thing..
your assignment this week is
to trail your partner at work.
Come back ready to discuss five things you learn
about each other's magazines,
and nothing stupid.
Class dismissed.
Jodie.
Um, I don't mean to question you.
It's just.. See, I already work at Fashion magazine,
and I was kinda hoping that I could do something
a little more meaningful, and
I don't know what I can learn working
with the sports guy.
Who's right behind you.
Awkward.
Hey, why don't we just switch partners?
-I mean, you don't want to learn about fashion.
-No, I do,
and I know that you are the perfect person to teach me.
We are gonna knock this assignment out of the park.
That's a sports thing. I'm gonna teach you all about that.
Ugly Betty
Season 03, episode 15
"There's no place like Mode"
Subtitles by IrenePrysbrowsky
(http://nanyscia.livejournal.com)
Matt, I promise we will get to the tour.
It's just, fashion week is crazy,
and Daniel has, like, a million messages.
Hey, no problem.
So did you always know that
you wanted to work in fashion?
-Um, no, not really.
-So how'd you end up here?
What? Oh, I'm sorry. I was listening to the message.
Oh, sorry. You were talking. I thought it was okay.
And I missed it again. That's okay.
I can just do this later.
Oh, Amanda?
I have to write a press release on Heinrich.
-What do you know about him?
-Never heard of him.
He must suck.
-Wow. Heinrich..he's great.
-What, you know heinrich?
-No.
-Oh, 'cause you just acted like you knew him.
I wasn't expecting the follow-up. Sorry.
Oh, Daniel. You were all over the papers today.
-Really?
-Yes. Ahem.
"Looking sensational at Michael Kors' was 'Mode's' Daniel Meade.
He was accompanied by..."  Ugh!
-What?
-Nothing. I just remembered I can't read.
-It's my own secret shame.
-Amanda, what does it say?
"His new girlfriend/charity case..
a frump with a pulled-back hairstyle
that even a turn-of-the-century
librarian would deem too severe."
See? That is not so bad.
They didn't mention her big ears.
Well, that's insane. Molly looked fantastic.
Oh, not according to this one.
"Daniel meade might want to see a dermatologist.
He seemed to have a 5'5' woman-shaped growth on his arm."
Okay, now that one's clever.
You've gotta laugh at that.
Hello? Heinrich?
I think the door is open.
All right. I've never done this before.
I'm a little nervous.
So if you have any questions, maybe wait till after.
Got it.
-Oh!
Is he dead?
S-sorry. That was a question.
Excuse me.
Are you Heinrich?
I am The Heinrich.
Heinrich for short.
I'm Betty Suarez from "Mode."
This is my colleague Matt.
I'm going to write your press release.
We will make love..not today, but someday.
Ay.Are those your dresses?
They're very nice.
They... are..
garbage.
This is what we will present at the "Mode" show.
Wings. They have wings.
I don't know, though.
I kind like this photo he's given you.
-I like the way it catches the light.
-That's shards of glass!
The dress is on the mannequin 'cause the models
won't even sign the release to wear that thing.
Well, who am I to judge anyone?
Two years ago, I was the "Mode" designer to watch.
Now look at me..knocked up with someone else's kid,
forced to take Brad Pitt's cuffs by an 1/8 of an inch.
So the closet is just, like, a really big closet?
There is no comparison between
The Heinrich and The Christina.
Well, it's very kind of you to say, but no one's writing
a press release about me, are they?
So do they ever give you any of the clothes?
'Cause if I'm covering a game
and one of the guys is throwing out a bloody jersey,
sometimes I get to keep that. Score!
That's cool.
Hey, Matt, this is probably so boring for you.
Do you want to go back to my desk
and read back issues?
It's such a good way to learn.
And you can open my confidential drawer.
Don't worry. It's just snacks.
He seems interesting.
I know. It's just a really bad time
to have somebody following me.
I mean, I was willing to make the sacrifice
for "The New York Review,"
but "Sports Experience?
That's not really gonna help me.
All right, what am I gonna say about this thing?
Come here. Here we go.
"For immediate release"...
"It has been said fashion is pain."
-You can't write that.
-No, no, no. I can. I can. No write. It's good for a laugh.
Okay, but this is just for us.
"Science said no, but Heinrich said yes!"
"So get your tetanus shots, and prepare to bleed."
Here you go. I changed "shiny" to "glittering",
and added the words "breakout designer" a few times.
-It's good.
-Thank you so much, Justin.
It was so hard for me to get anything done at work
yesterday with all of matt's questions.
Ooh! Before I forget,
I only get two tickets to the "Mode" show this year,
-so we have to decide who's going.
-I get one or I tell everyone
that you still like Ricky Martin.
I'm sorry. I have to play hardball.
-Mama made pancakes!
Ooh! Someone's in a good mood.
Well, guess who's not taking
papi's blood pressure this morning?
Nurse skank.
-Hilda.
Ay. Let me enjoy myself. Eat your pancakes.
Look, smiley face.
-Aww, chocolate chip eyes!
-Morning.
You have the same hideous robe as grandpa?
It's not hideous. It's, um, retro.
And obviously, we have some things to talk about.
I just hope we can be, um, mature about it.
Oh, sure. I got no problem being mature.
Uh, I gotta get to work. You know, fashion week, all of that.
Sorry. Talk to you later.
Okay, I just have to say something.
You're better than that robe.
And I'm gonna go get you one of mine.
And in the "Ten Designers to Watch" show,
"Mode" presents cutting-edge fashion, literally..
Made of barbed wire and rusty nails,
designer Heinrich's line promises to intrigue..
and danger.
-What?
-Science said no,
but Heinrich said yes.
-No!
So get your tetanus shot and be prepared to bleed.
-Ouch!
-Oh, my god.
That's the wrong press release.
Morning. You would not believe how much
I have already learned about fashion.
And now I know that these are chinos.
-Khakis.
-Damn it.
Matt, did you see where I put that press release
I wrote yesterday?
-Uh, yeah, I gave it to your boss.
-You what?
Well, he asked for it, and it said "for immediate release,"
so I didn't want to wait until you came back.
-No. No,
that was just a joke, a mean and terrible joke.
I wrote
the real one last night.
-That one was never supposed to go out.
Oh, God. I'm really sorry.
Look, if you get fired, I can get you a new job.
The guy who covers wrestling is leaving.
-What?
-Yeah, it's probably not the best fit,
but we'll..we'll figure something..oh.
Daniel, I'm sorry. This was never supposed to happen.
Peering is back.
Why did I ever listen to Marc Jacobs?
Lagerfeld laughed in my face because my cuffs were peeking.
Hey, nice job on that press release, by the way.
I liked that it wasn't full of the same old cliches,
and so did Heinrich.
Really?
He wants you to produce his show.
Some jumping and hugging might be appropriate now.
N-no, uh, produce his show..
what would I have to do?
You know, come up with a concept for the show
that gets people excited about his clothes.
Oh, I don't know if I'm the right person
for this particular line.
Betty, come on. Don't worry.
Designers have very clear visions.
Just listen to Heinrich.
He'll tell you exactly what he wants.
Okay. Yeah.
All right, well, then I guess I'm producing a show.
-What was that?
-It's jumping.
It was your idea.
Marc St.James alerting you that Wilhelmina Slater
is on route to the Proenza Schouler show.
Confirming her usual seat.
That's..that's funny.
It's getting less funny.
You cannot do this to me!
Name your price..box at the met,
reservations at Buddakan, Kidney.
I'm 0-negative. It's a universal donor.
I can hear you, you know?
What's going on?
Oh, you're not gonna throw up, are you?
Roll down the window.
-You're in the second row.
-What?! How is that possible?
-I'm always in the front row.
-I don't know,
but they swear that there is nothing
that they can do.
You say the word, and I will
kill myself right now.
Oh, Marc, stop.
Well, I'm certainly not going in there.
No. It would be more humiliating
than being caught in crocs.
How could this happen?
Have I changed?
Have I gone soft?
No. You're still as horrible and evil as the day
that Satan himself placed you
in your mother's arms.
Oh, darling, that's sweet.
But obviously, the fashion world has forgotten
that I decide who is relevant, not them.
I need to remind them of my power.
I have a surprise for you.
This is Clarissa and Skye, two "Mode" stylists.
You never take advantage of
dating an editor-in-chief,
so I thought, what better time than fashion week?
Thank you.
-Say something.
-I can't
Don't mess up my lipstick.
You are the first person
who understands me, Betty Suarez.
Still, we will wait to make love.
Okay. Let's talk about your show.
I tell you exactly what I want..
the hot, dry vortex of wind,
that blows dreams into dust.
-Okay, so fans..
-No, nooo!
I hate fans. They are cliche'.
-No fans.
-Mm. Give me gray.
Gray..that's good. That's specific.
Gray but obscure.
A rainbow of gray,
but sharp like clear fog.
Heinrich, I-I think we're
going in the wrong direction.
No, no, Betty, Betty,
it is about pain,
und escape, but no escape.
Understand?
Um,  actually..
No, no. Listen to the clothes.
They will tell you what to do.
I am coming to you live from
the Proenza Schouler show.
And now... entering the tent
in a fabulous marc jacobs frock, we have..
looks like somebody's gone from drab to fab.
Hello, "Extreme Makeover: Face edition."
Ugly duckling. Ugly duckling.
Maybe I should have gone with "swan."
Wilhelmina Slater wants to give you
an exclusive review of the Proenza Schouler line.
And trust me, she'll be at her "wilhel-meanest."
Hey! Hey, sorry I'm late.
I was stuck talking to Heidi Klum.
-That woman cannot find her way to the end of a joke.
-Actually, I have to go.
-Everything okay?
-Yeah.
It--my landlord called and th-there's a leak
in my ceiling that might cave in or something,
and it might take a while,
so I'll talk to you later.
Is it telling you what the concept is yet?
Nope, not yet.
Would it help if I told you I googled you and
there are already 47 mentions of you and Heinrich?
No. Actually, that doesn't help at all.
So it's probably not the best time
to ask you about the clip of you
riding a Harley into a vat of Jell-O.
Okay, Betty, you have got
to get me into the Heinrich show.
He is my favorite designer in the whole world.
Okay, didn't you say that you
didn't even know who he was?
Someone's been hitting the tequila again.
It's like mother's milk to her.
Betty, Heinrich is all people are talking about,
so that means he's good, obvi.
Excuse me.
Daniel, can I talk to you
for just one second?
So, like, the buzz on this Heinrich thing..
-it's getting kind of big.
-Yeah, yeah. Actually, I was just coming to tell you.
We're moving him to the closing
position. Isn't that great?
Oh! Wow! Great!
So, like, if you want to go with someone
with a little more experience
to produce his show,
you know, someone who can,
like, hear when clothes talk,
like some sort of a clothes whisperer...
Why are you so weird today?
I just don't think that
I'm the person for this job.
Betty, I trust you more than anyone.
You are gonna do great.
If it makes you feel any better,
I don't get any of this stuff either.
I mean, aren't you supposed
to be able to wear clothes?
-Yep, one would think.
-So why isn't he good?
I don't know, but apparently,
there's something there,
because everyone's going crazy
for the Heinrich,
-and I don't know what it is.
-Oh, that's not good.
It's very not good.
You know what else is not good?
I think I've wasted three years of my life
in an industry that I don't even understand.
And apparently, it's all I'm qualified to do.
Well, when things get stressful, sometimes
it's good to take a break,
Uh, step outside your world.
We can go over to my magazine.
I could teach you about sports.
Great. Maybe I could find
a career in sports.
I mean, I was thinking a magazine
that actually meant something,
you know, like "The New York Review."
But hey! I could have a future
in fashion or sports.
Right.
You know, I was really excited
when we got partnered up.
You know, I've been listening
to you in class, and you seem so smart,
and interested in things, but..
But I don't know.You haven't asked me
a single thing about what I do.
It's like you heard "sports"
and judged me,
which is exactly what you don't
want people to do to you.
You know, I know you think
fashion is shallow, but..
it seems to me like you fit right in.
Matt. Matt.
I'm sorry.
Look, you were right.
I was being awful, and fashion week
is not an excuse,
-and I promise you, I am not shallow.
-I know. I know.
Even as I was saying it,
I wasn't really believing it.
Oh, good, because I do want
to learn about your magazine.
-In fact, let's go now.
-Now?
Yeah! Daniel's out at the shows.
I'm not gonna get any further
on this Heinrich thing.
So let's go learn about sports.
You know, tonight might not be
the best night to start..
I won't take no for an answer.
I tried to warn you.
You could have been a little more specific.
I can't believe you haven't seen
"Step up 2 the streets" yet.
It's only the best
classical-versus-urban dance movie ever.
It totally defines my generation.
Trying to watch a movie here.
Five, six, seven, eight.
We should go dancing sometime.
Mm. I got some moves.
I bet you do.
Everything okay?
I can't hear what they're saying.
It's either about stepping up or the streets.
You know what?
I don't even like this movie.
What is going on with you?
You're acting like a child.
You're acting like a horny teenager.
Hilda, I'm sorry you don't like this,
but I have a right to be in a relationship.
And I have a right
not to have your relationship
shoved in my face
every time I turn around!
No, papi. This is my house, too!
For the record, I really like Elena,
and it's not just because
she's turned this place
into a day spa.
I wish Hilda felt that way.
I know. They used to be friends.
Maybe if she stayed in a room
with her more than a minute,
she'd remember that.
Come on. Andie's about to show
the 4-1-0 crew
the true meaning of the streets.
Hey. Nice game.
Uh, Matt, are you sure it's okay
for me to be in here?
Well, they're okay with it
if you are.
Yeah. I'm fine. Why wouldn't I be fine?
Oh! Sorry. Sorry.
I didn't see anything.
Although I think now we might be married.
Hey. Hey, Sasha. Sasha, great game saturday.
Hey, that, Betty, is Sasha Radovic.
I swear, I once saw him drain
a three from the parking lot.
Oh, well, I understood "parking lot."
So it must be nice, huh
working at your dream magazine?
"Great Sport"? Que nada.
I always..I always stunk at sports.
And I always thought the pros
were just a bunch of overpaid babies.
-Hey, I heard that.
-Good.
-So what changed?
-I got to know the guys.
Brock over there..
got into a car accident when he was 16.
The doctors told him
he would never walk again...
but he had a dream to play basketball.
And, uh, and Jimmy.. um, well, okay,
Jimmy just likes the money,
but, uh, but Sasha..
Just wait. Wait.
Look at this.
Whose names are those?
His siblings.
He was drafted here last year,
passed when he was 18.
Couldn't speak a word of english,
hardly knew a soul,
because the serbian government
wouldn't allow his family
to come with him.
And so he plays to support them.
Want me to, uh, keep going?
Not if it includes pointing
to more naked men.
All I'm saying is that none of this
was a natural fit for me.
You know, but I found my way in
by making it personal.
Maybe that would work for you at "Mode."
Here. Come on.
I want to show you the, uh, showers.
I'm..I'm kidding.
We're actually going to
the, uh, steam room.
Shut up, matt. Hmm.
I spent an hour and a half
trashing Proenza Schouler.
I said the most heinous things.
I'm surprised I wasn't arrested
for a hate crime.
That'll teach them who has
the real power in this business.
Nobody puts baby in the second row.
Oh, darling, that referee
might be current in Australia,
but we're over it here.
Oh, this must be it.
And finally, my exclusive interview
with "Mode's" co-editor-in-chief, Wilhelmina Slater.
We hear she's got some juicy dish
on Proenza Schouler's new line.
Wait a minute. Breaking news? This just in..
doggy jeans are now low-waisted.
That's right, pups. It's time
to ditch those mid-rise denims
or risk looking like last year's bitch.
for more on these hoochie poochies,
let's go to our canine correspondent.
You can't let that bother you.
It's slipping away.
What is?
Never mind.
Talk to me. What is it?
For 20 years, I killed myself
for my career.
I sacrificed everything,
and now because I dared
to flirt with a personal life,
suddenly I'm nothing?
Oh. Silly me. I just, uh, I thought
I could have it all.
You can, with me.
Willie, you and I are both fighters.
And the thing about being
a fighter is, you don't stop.
If you're down,
you look for an opportunity
to claw your way back.
Now people may not like you for it,
but I do.
And we are in this together.
So I learned all about how you
grew up behind the iron curtain,
dreaming of a life
on the other side of the berlin wall
and that you lost your father
when he got caught trying
to escape over the barbed wire.
And so even when the wall came down,
you still carried that pain,
pain that is always with you,
even in the clothes you make.
Maybe the only way
you can imagine escaping
is by raising giant wings
and letting the wind
carry you far away.
Is that right?
Now we will make love.
Well, no. Thank you, though.
Let me show you how I want
to use this in your show.
This is a representation
of the Berlin wall.
You can explain to the fire marshal
that our iron curtain is only
blocking the back two exits.
-There are six more exits in the house.
-Yeah, sure.
Right after I ask him
to introduce me to some firemen.
Everything good?
Steve, we have to move Isaac Mizrahi to the front row.
There are too many sharp objects
for him to throw another tantrum.
-Yeah, everything's great.
-Good. Then it'll seem less
selfish if I make this about me.
-Something is going on with Molly.
-What do you mean?
Well, she ran out of Proenza Schouler
and hasn't returned my calls since.
Well, did you do something stupid?
No, just the opposite.
I got her this big makeover
right before the show.
Daniel, you did something stupid. Thank you.
-What?
-Look,
you basically told her
that you weren't okay with the way she is.
No, I-I am okay with her.
I-I think she's amazing.
Well, then you better find
a big way to tell her that.
Oh! Careful with the razor blades.
What are you doing here?
I've never been to fashion week.
I thought it'd be fun
to watch the show together.
Did my father put you up to this?
-No.
-I'm gonna kill him.
And how could he do that to Justin?
You know he was dying to come to this?
Actually, Justin's the one
who ga me his seat.
I guess your father's not the only one
who wants us to get along.
-Molly.
-Hi.
Hey. I've been calling and calling.
-I know. I'm..
-No, no, no, wait. I have been an idiot.
You don't need a makeover.
I'm the one who needs to change.
You are so different from everyone I know,
and you care about the things that matter,
you won't let met get away
with being shallow and stupid.
When I think about our future,
I'm not scared.
It's just..it's exciting.
And I've never been
that guy before.
I don't want to you to change.
Molly, I love you.
I love you, too.
It's just been an overwhelming week.
Yeah. No, I get that.
Fashion week is ridiculous,
and you have all that stuff
going on with your apartment.
How is that going?
Actually, it's more serious
than they thought.
But they're working on it.
Come on. Who's gonna wear that?
I got the same one in purple.
Christina!
I think it's going really well.
Oh, Mother of God. Pull up
your own nail boots next time.
Perfect.
The show is perfect.
Thank you.
I give you a dress to say thank you.
Your body will destroy the line.
I give you this instead.
Thank you.
Mine. Ow!
Oh, that hurts so good.
-Do you want to get a drink?
-Let's go.
I am this close to throwing a tantrum.
Why is spandex such a glamour don't?
It's the perfect fabric.
You can dress it up. You can dress it down.
Right? You put on a red belt,
some chunky jewelry, you're going out.
-What do you think about stirrup pants?
-You first.
-I love 'em.
-I know. Me, too. I love 'em.
I can't help it.
-You are so busted.
-What?
You're having a good time
with me. You like me.
Fine. I like you.
It's just... this thing with my father...
Look... maybe we could set
some ground rules.
Okay, I'm listening.
Ignacio and I could sit
a little further apart
during movie night,
and keep the P.D.A. to a minimum.
Oh, I don't know. It is kind of sweet..
you guys makingon each other...
Maybe you could go
to your place once in a while.
Done.
That model with the spikes is
a wee bit steady on her feet.
I think there might be an impaling.
I think I finally get it.
Fashion is art.
It's just another way
of taking what's on the inside
and putting it out there
for everyone else to experience it.
It's not shallow. It's courageous.
It's... it's beautiful.
Are you okay? Did you cut yourself
on a dress again?
No, no, no, no.
Well, no, not--not that. I just...
Are you going into labor?
Well, not exactly. I've..I've
sort of been in labor all day.
-What?!
-No, but I didn't want to go to the hospital
until the contractions got
a little bit closer together...
-Which is about now. Ooh! Ooh!
-Well, come on. Let's get you out of here.
Shoot!
The iron curtain is
blocking the back two exits.
Heinrich, I'm sorry.
Christina, let's go.
Oh, no, no, no, no, Betty.
Not the runway.
-Yes, the runway.
-I don't want to spoil the show.
We don't have any other option.
Oh, it is more pain than I could
ever dream of. It is perfect!
Excuse me. Here, just take my hand.
Now watch out
for the broken glass.
Just keep breathing.
Breathe. Breathe.
Daniel, call an ambulance!
You're gonna be okay.
We're gonna get you a doctor.
Uh-huh. Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
Good. Good. No.Oh, no, Christina.
Go ahead. You go
without me. I'll be okay.
What are you talking about?
I have no idea.
I'm delirious.
But I think I'm gonna have
the baby here!
What?
Apparently, the back exits are blocked,
which is why betty and christina
decided to ruin the show.
Yes, I'll hold. Yeah, uh,
paramedics said with the crowds
and street closures it could
be tough to get through,
but I'm checking on a helicopter
right now. Yes. Daniel Meade.
So Christina can't get out,
and they can't come in.
It's a fashion disaster.
Or it could be an opportunity
for me to claw my way
back to the top.
People, she needs her privacy.
Models, come forward.
Let's go.
Now raise your wings.
This isn't quite
how I pictured it happening.
Um, could the models
please turn around?
Is there anyone here
qualified to deliver a baby?
My father's girlfriend is a nurse!
You called me his girlfriend.
-Yeah, I'm growing.
-Chop! Chop! Let's go!
Who's the pregnant lady wearing?
Herself. She's wearing herself..Christina Mckinney.
Yay! That was Isaac Mizrahi!
-You're gonna get really excited later.
-Yes.
Stand by, lights. Cue music.
This is Suzuki st. Pierre,
live from the "Mode" show,
where the child of Wilhelmina Slater
and the late Bradford Meade
is about to make
its first runway appearance.
With any luck, Wilhelmina's chromosomes
will drown bradford's in the gene pool,
and we'll end up with a looker.
I wish she would quit doing that.
I am not crying. I am..
Damn it. It's dan rather all over again.
Go, lights. Go, music.
Cue the hydraulic lift.
Cue the land mines.
Matt, hey.
What are you doing here?
Well, I-I wanted to see what
you did with the show, and wow.
And a live birth.
Heinrich gave you nothing,
and you made it amazing.
I mean, you were the one
who told me to dig deeper,
find my connection.
-Thank you.
-For what?
-I don't know.
It's just an impulse I have
whenever someone says "thank you."
So, Matt, uh, we're gonna be
partners this year.
I get to learn all about sports,
and now that the fashion show is done,
I'll have time to show you
all the things you wanted
to learn about fashion.
To be honest, I wasn't really that interested
in learning about fashion.
I was more interested
in learning about you.
So... I will see you at Y.E.T.I.. partner.
It would have been so much better
if I had left before I did that.
So... what's it feel like
to have a half brother?
It's good.
Weird. It makes me miss my dad.
Yeah.
I didn't get a chance
to tell you. You put on quite a show
You found a way to make
unwearable clothes beautiful.
Oh, stop.
I learned from the best.
Seriously, you have this way
of connecting with people.
Like, you get beneath the surface.
You don't find that in this business.
I know it's not
what you want to be doing,
but I think you'd make
a great editor at "Mode"... someday.
Well, thank you for the compliment.
I'm just kind of embarrassed
it took me so long to figure it out.
Fashion has a lot more substance
than I thought.
-I'm certainly glad you think so.
-Me, too.
Of course... if you ever decide
to have a career in fashion,
we have to talk about
all the colors and patterns.
If I decide to have a career in fashion,
then I get to decide what looks good.
And if you don't watch it,
I'l make you wear Heinrich's hat.
www.tvsubtitles.net