Previously on "Ugly Betty"...
Aah!
You have exactly the right voice
for a new magazine I'm starting.
I want you to help me
run it... in London.
There is something about you
that I automatically liked.
I would do anything for that girl.
My biological father has
that tweety bird tattoo.
It's a great feeling, isn't it,
when everything is...
right in the world?
Hi, Mr. Dunn. I would
like to accept your offer.
I don't want anything from you.
I'm the one who made you feel
this way. Give me the gun.
Fashionista, trendsetter,
loyal friend...
This cherished icon
who once walked the
halls of "mode"
is now eating out of
the hands of angels
and soiling the carpets of
heaven for all eternity.
Amen. Hallelujah.
Poor alston.
He was a good dog, Amanda.
He was.
Good-bye, Halston.
I can't believe it Marc.
The only connection
to the mother I
never knew is gone.
Indigenous. Good look for you.
Officer, there they are! Amanda...
You said you got a
permit for this, right?
Run!
Crisis "mode"...
With "mode" just weeks away
from publishing its
100th anniversary issue,
wilhelmina Slater
is still unconscious
after a mysterious shooting
at the "mode" offices.
And that bullet
must have been filled
with beauty powder,
because she looks ravishing.
So far the only
information we have
is that her longtime
Nemesis Claire Meade
was the sole witness.
She claims the shooting
was an accident,
which has fashionistas
everywhere straining
to raise their eyebrows.
Come on. Let's go.
B., how can you move to London?
Won't you miss all the kidnapping,
shooting and murder at "mode"? Mm,
no, not really.
This looks so good.
Yeah, I gotta say,
I'm really glad I'm becoming
a part of this latin family.
Aw, kid, we are gonna
Spice you up so much,
you're gonna forget you're white.
Okay, this smells amazing.
Let's eat.
Unh-unh. Hands off.
For you, sheep's heart,
liver and lung
stuffed in intestine,
otherwise known as haggis.
Ew! Oh, my God. Oh!
Oh, my God. I'm gonna vomit.
Papi, why?
I-I'm fine just eating what
everyone else is eating.
Mija, that's what
they eat in the u.K.
You need to toughen up
your stomach before you go.
Ugh. Unless, uh...
You want to stay. Papi,
I am taking the job in London.
I understand.
Oh, look, so I been looking
at a couple of houses
that look pretty good. Shh!
He's in the other room.
You guys are moving?
We're just looking.
We haven't told papi yet.
With you leaving and everything,
it's just... it's hard time. Well,
he's gonna have to get
used to it sometime.
Besides, I saw some nice
places in Bay Ridge...
Bay Ridge?! Shh.
Look,
just swear that we are
gonna look in Manhattan.
And thanks to the great recession,
you'd be surprised on how
affordable things are now. Hey, hey.
Betty, you haven't
touched the haggis.
Trust me, you don't want
to eat it when it's cold.
That's my phone.
What's the matter with you?
Where did you even find that?
Oh! Daniel. Hi, Daniel!
Yes. I can be right there.
Sorry, guys. Daniel needs me.
So... I guess I'll just
have to eat with him.
Are you finally gonna tell him
that you're moving to London?
Yes, I'm going to tell him.
It's just not easy. Okay?
He gave me my start.
I owe him everything.
But I've made my decision,
and I'm gonna tell him.
Sorry I can't stay for dinner.
You really haven't
missed that much.
We had this ridiculous aborted
funeral for Amanda's dog.
She brought that big queen
who I think is her father.
But I'm not sure,
and I would just hate for her
to have to go through
all that again.
What else can I tell you?
Oh. Well, I'm still not over Troy
even though he's got a boyfriend.
H... what?
Stop it.
I like him.
Oh, you're so bad.
Willie...
I knew your obsession
with the meades
would get the better of you.
Now look at you.
Your makeup is still flawless,
but you're in a coma.
I just want you to be happy,
'cause all this scheming...
It's killing you.
You know, I think this
is the best conversation
we've ever had.
Are you crazy?
Look, you're doing your fishy
face thing in this one.
No, I'm not. That's just my face.
No, it's not. And you're
standing like a robot.
So my shoulders don't droop.
What's the matter with that?
Daniel, this is your big picture
for the 100th anniversary issue.
This looks like the guy that I
met my first day on the job.
This is pose-y Daniel.
You're not that guy anymore.
Well, thank you.
I will take that as a compliment.
So, um... Daniel,
uh... listen.
There's something I've
been wanting to tell you.
Wait. Uh, one quick thing.
In this issue,
we're doing profiles
of everyone who's ever been
editor-in-chief of "mode,"
and I was hoping maybe
you'd write mine.
Really?
Oh, my God! I would love that!
Good. 'Cause I gotta tell ya,
there's no way I could've
done this job without you.
I think we make a good team,
you and me.
So... I interrupted you.
What were you saying?
You know what? I forgot.
Good morning, sunshine.
No, I haven't had a
chance to tell Daniel yet.
Well, don't you think he'll notice
when you stop showing up
for work in three weeks?
Hilda, I can't talk about this.
I'm at work.
And if anyone here finds out
I'm taking a job in London,
it will spread like wildfire.
You're taking a job in London?
Shh! Marc, please.
Please don't say anything.
Daniel doesn't know yet.
Just give me a chance to tell him first.
Of course. Of course.
I totally get it.
I'm not going to tell anyone.
What are you doing?
What are you doing?! Marc! Oops.
You did not. I totally did.
Say hi to the beckhams.
Hey, Betty, have fun in London.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
No. Oh, God, no!
No, don't send that!
That's not yours to send!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Oh, God.
Stop! Don't take any calls!
Give me five minutes
alone with him!
Daniel!
Betty.
I have something I have
to tell you, and it's big.
Bigger than you taking
a job in London?
I'm so sorry you found out
before I could tell you.
Daniel, I am so grateful
for these last four years.
It has been a pleasure
working with you.
Actually, an honor,
and... did you rehearse this?
A little. Daniel...
We're always gonna
be friends, and I...
Betty, it's fine.
It is?
Yeah.
Okay.
Great.
Is there anything else?
Um, yeah. I...
I need you to...
Sign this form releasing
me from my contract.
They need it tomorrow.
Yep. No problemo.
Okay.
Great.
When I heard what happened,
I had to come.
Connor, I don't understand.
How did you... get out of jail?
I talked a guard into letting
me out for a few hours.
He's just outside.
But I thought you'd
been transferred.
That's what I needed
you to believe
so that you could move on.
But, Willie...
I can't live without you.
Okay, let's calm down...
Before we put you
back in that coma.
Oh! It would be worth it.
I spent my entire life
fighting f a magazine
when I should've been
fighting for you.
It's all gonna be different now.
Wilhelmina Slater is a
completely changed woman.
Well, I hope not
completely changed.
There were some parts
of you I rather liked.
Hi, Daniel.
Just a little reminder that I
need to get that paper signed.
No biggie. When you can...
by tomorrow.
Earlier is better, but nothing
that inconveniences you.
Hi, papi.
Did you know that London is
the dirtiest city in Europe?
What? I'm reading this online...
The dirtiest city,
and the most expensive,
with the worst food,
and they say the people there
are the most unfriendly
in the world.
You know, I was there.
It didn't seem so bad.
This is on the Internet, Betty.
Want me to send it to you?
Aah! Mija, what's wrong?
I'll call you back.
Amanda! Are you okay?
How could you put your dead
dog in my refrigerator?
That dead dog has a name.
Halston.
And he's simply being
cryo-genitally preserved
until I can give him a proper
farewell. In my fridge?!
We are a food-free household.
And you need to lose
a little weight,
so it's really a win-win.
Get him out, please.
I'm going for a walk.
Hey, Betty?
What?
I heard you're moving to London.
And I just... want to say that
I'm really gonna miss you.
Thank you, Amanda.
That is very sweet.
So really,
I can't just keep Halston in
your fridge for a little bit? No.
Claire.
Before this happened,
you would've been
the last person in the
world I'd want to see.
Well, I'm just happy to
see that you're awake.
That's nice. It's very
sweet of you to visit.
I need to talk to you.
We're saying
that Tyler had nothing
to do with your shooting.
You need to corroborate our story.
I do?
You made him drink.
You supplied him with a gun.
This is your doing, wilhelmina,
and you need to fix this.
This... is what we can offer you.
It's funny, I would've
been happy with flowers,
or perhaps a handwritten
note saying,
"thank you for saving my life."
Oh, please. I know
exactly who you are.
And you're going to milk this
until you can get
your manicured claws
into our company,
because wilhelmina only does
things that help wilhelmina.
Well, I guess you know me
better than I know myself.
Now flap those bat wings
of yours and get out.
Look, I'm sorry.
But in my defense,
it looked a lot cooler in my head.
I don't understand.
I thought you were okay with it.
You said, "no problemo."
Well, it is a problemo. I'm angry.
I can't believe you'd
make a decision that big
without talking to
me about it at all.
I'm sorry.
Look, I don't want us
to end on bad terms.
I don't either.
I just don't know how I feel
about releasing you
from your contract.
What are you saying?
We've invested a
lot in you, Betty.
If it was anyone else, I'd say no.
I need to think about this.
Okay. Well...
They need the form right
away or I'll lose the job.
I said I would think about it.
All right. Well, then I guess
we'll talk about it later.
I mean, can you believe
the nerve of that Claire?
What have I ever done to her?
Several things come to mind.
Like, oh, I don't know...
Stealing sperm from
her husband's corpse?
Well, the craziest thing is,
before old chicken neck showed up,
I was just so happy to be alive,
I was just willing to
let the whole thing go.
That's not crazy. That's wonderful!
It was a moment of weakness.
If those idiots want
me to save Tyler,
they're gonna have to hand
over the whole damn company.
Oh, Willie, don't say that.
That's wrong.
Oh, you're one to
be judging me, Marc.
After all these years,
whenever I needed something
that was morally questionable,
you were right there with me.
You're right. I was willing
to do anything for you.
You were like my mother,
my goddess, my diva.
Y-you know, you were-
-you were my life.
I thought that if you had
everything you wanted,
you'd be happy, but...
You'll never be happy.
There's always something more.
Thank you.
Oh, hi, Betty. Oh, hi, Mrs. Meade.
You sound like I feel,
which isn't great.
What's going on? I don't wanna
bore you with my problems.
Oh, Betty, please.
The last two weeks have been
nothing but gunshots and comas.
I would love to
hear your problems.
Well, actually, um,
it's sort of about...
Daniel.
Oh! There you are!
What are you doing?
You know I steal when I get upset.
Spencer screamed at
me 'cause he ended up
in one of those "who
wore it better"? Columns.
And only 82% of people
said Ellen degeneres
wore the suit better
than he did. No.
I hate him. He's dead to me.
I never wanna talk to him again.
He's your father.
Is everything okay, dear?
Yeah. It's just Betty.
Sh-she wants to leave,
and... I heard.
I tawt I taw the
tweety bird tattoo
when he lifted up his shirt
and a little bit of
crackage popped out.
I didn't wanna say anything
to you because, well,
I wasn't sure,
but then Halston died,
and you were so sad. Oh, my God.
Marc, what am I gonna do?
Should I tell him?
But then what if I tell him,
and he rejects me?
What if... what if
he's not my father,
and I have to go through
all of this all over again?
What if you have to go through
this all over again? Ooh.
Hey, Amanda.
Wow, I see you more now
than when you actually worked here.
Not funny, Suarez!
That's not funny at all!
That's terrible timing!
Sorry. I'm not doing well
with anyone around here today.
Okay, seriously, whatever drama
you got going on today...
I've been sucked into enough.
I don't need it!
So what's up?
Well, look, before I go to London,
I have to get released from
my contract... ugh! God!
Betty. Honestly!
Go on.
Okay, are we talking
or not? Mm-hmm.
Just the other night,
we were here talking and working.
I mean, she's writing my bio.
I wouldn't trust
anyone else to do that.
Are you sure this isn't about
more than just Betty's
editing skills?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the fact that
you might have feelings for her.
What?
He's a bully!
And he's manipulative!
And he as a weak chin. Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah, um... what? No! No,
he doesn't.
What does that have
to do with anything?
He's... well, keep... keep-
-keep... keep ranting, though.
Come on, mom,
that's crazy! Perhaps.
Or could it explain your behavior?
What? No! No way.
Daniel, darling, you were so upset
at the possibility of her leaving,
you nearly burned
down your office.
If you are having such a
hard time with her leaving,
you need to give her
a reason to stay.
Well, I think you need
to go and give him
a piece of your mind.
You know what? I will. Thanks! Yeah.
Good! You're welcome.
Daniel, I...
Me first. Betty,
I can't live without you.
So what exactly did Daniel say?
He offered me a promotion-
full-fledged editor...
And a really nice bump in salary.
That's major, a.B.
I know. What do I do?
Seems pretty clear to me.
You have to take it.
Papi, come on. There are a
lot of things to consider.
Hey, we... we got great news, too.
What? Nothing. Nothing.
No, it's not nothing.
It's something.
Come on. What is it?
We're gonna get a place in the city!
Yay!
I think that's great.
Great news. I-I'm
gonna go wash dishes.
Why did you say anything?!
We don't know if we're taking it yet!
Um, Betty might stay.
I thought it was a good
time to test the waters.
Hilda, it's okay.
No, it's not okay!
And you don't tell me what is
okay and what isn't okay! Okay?
Okay.
Ay. I'm sorry.
I am sorry. It's not you, okay?
I just...
Ay. Look, I'm so happy for you.
You're living your dream,
and I am so proud of you.
I just feel like I finally have
a chance at living my dream...
The happy family life
that I've always wanted...
And I can't do it.
I mean, how is papi gonna feel
if we both leave him alone?
I don't know.
I don't know how
papi is gonna feel.
But if you want that place,
get it.
Yeah.
Hilda, you deserve to be happy.
Rouge alert! Rouge alert!
Our sources have just confirmed
that wilhelmina Slater
is en route to "mode,"
where she will be
publicly speaking
about her shooting
for the first time.
Who shot the diabolical diva?
And what gorgeous piece of couture
did they blast a hole through?
Stick with me,
because wilhelmina always
tells suzuki first.
Willie! Willie, suzuks here!
Out of my way, clown.
Cut!
Thank you, all,
for meeting me here.
I have a brief statement,
and then I'd like to
get back to my office.
As you can imagine,
work really piles up
when you're in a coma.
There's been some speculation
as to what happened
the night I was shot. And I...
And...
I'd like to put the
rumors to rest,
let the truth speak for itself.
It was not Claire
Meade who shot me,
although it's obvious why
people would think so.
It was...
It was me.
I s cleaning my gun,
and I shot myself by accident.
So... sorry to disappoint,
but there was no drama
that night. Just...
A foolish mistake.
Well, thank you for
an informative day.
That was a complete waste of time.
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but... thank you.
Don't thank me.
I didn't do it for you. Right.
Forgive me for saying so,
but why do I feel like
I'm going to pay for this one day?
Because you don't know me.
So go ahead and unclench
everything. We're good.
Well, as good as you and I can be.
Really?
Yes, really, Claire.
Chamomile?
Thank you.
Justin, I don't know what to do.
If I go to London,
am I being selfish?
I feel like I'm letting
everyone down...
Papi, Daniel, Hilda.
Not to mention, it's such a risk...
aunt Betty...
You're all about risk.
You took a job at "mode" magazine.
You showed up to your
first day of work
in a poncho that
reeked of disaster.
But...
You became a star.
And it's not selfish.
It helps, kind of,
to... to see you be so brave.
You know, it...
It sort of raises the
bar for the rest of us.
Not to mention,
I get to visit my
cool aunt in London.
How did you get so smart?
I had a few good teachers.
You're leaving, aren't you?
Uh, do you have, um,
another copy of that...
Paper you want me to sign?
Are we good?
We're good.
Daniel... I'm supposed
to be at a meeting,
uh, right now.
So why don't we, um...
Talk later?
Betty, this is such a great party.
And thank you so much
for making it a farewell
to Halston. Yeah.
That was a surprise.
It's just so perfect...
good luck, Betty. Bye.
Finally realizing where
he belongs... "mode."
Oh, Mrs. Meade.
I'm so glad you came.
Oh, Betty. I wouldn't have
missed it for the world.
I'm so proud of you.
Thank you.
Do you think Daniel's coming?
I don't know.
He's been avoiding me for days.
I think he hates me now.
He doesn't.
Losing you is very
hard for him, Betty.
I don't even think he
knows quite why yet.
What do you mean?
I have a theory.
What?
Really? No. No. No.
Hey. Hey.
This is fun. I'm really
glad I got to come.
Well, you were an intern here.
You're a "modie," too.
Why don't you go dance with him?
Oh. Come on. You know you want to.
He's got a boyfriend. That guy?
Mnh-mnh. Reeks of rebound.
I don't think that's
gonna work out.
Oh, what do you know?
You're recently hatched
from the gay egg.
You still have lot to
learn about relationships.
So do you.
Look out, skinny bitches!
I don't care who sits here.
This big orange doughnut
will always be mine!
And Halston's.
Oh, hi.
You made it.
Of course.
I couldn't miss that
pooch's farewell.
I didn't realize you knew Betty.
I was talking about Halston.
Oh.
Right.
Uh, Daniel. This is Betty.
Um... it's my going away party...
And you're not here.
Uh, I was just wondering
if you're gonna come.
I really hope that I get
to see you before I leave.
Okay. Bye.
You know, you do work for
two editors-in-chief.
I have to find out you're leaving
through a mass e-mail?
You never asked my permission.
Permission granted.
Thank you. It's interesting.
You spent four years of your life
working your way
up the ladder here,
and now you're
throwing it all away.
Um... yeah, I...
I never thought I'd
say this, but...
You've got big balls,
Betty Suarez.
That's the nicest thing
you've ever said to me.
I don't know why I got so
competitive with Ellen.
She wore the hell
out of that suit.
Spencer, I have
something to tell you,
and I'm really worried about
how you're gonna react.
I know you're my daughter.
What? How?
I recently found out from a friend
that fey got pregnant
shortly after I... was with her.
It was the '80s, studio 54.
I got so blitzed out of my mind,
I thought fey was Andy warhol.
I contacted an agency to find you.
And then I hired you as my stylist
so I could get to know you first.
I wanted to make sure
I wasn't intruding.
It's okay.
Really?
Really. I've been waiting
years for you to intrude.
Well, then...
I forbid you to see that boy.
Wait. What boy? What are you
talking about? I don't know.
It just sounded like a
fatherly thing to say.
Oh. Then I hate you, dad!
Marc.
Yeah. Got you!
Oh, yes.
I'm gonna miss you.
I know.
And you're gonna miss me.
Take care of everything here.
Are you going to talk to her?
I think I need to let her go.
What?
Go to the marked tabs.
Those'll be your pages to fill.
You're now sole
editor-in-chief of "mode."
I'm stepping down. It's time.
I got this job because
it was handed to me,
but... you've earned it.
Well...
This is quite a surprise.
How does... Claire feel about it?
Oh, she's given it her blessing.
Congratulations, wilhelmina.
And, uh, what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna start over.
Okay, everybody. Gather round.
I'd like to make a toast.
This is gonna be his last
attempt to make you stay.
I just want to say...
I know I can't stop my
daughters from leaving.
But I can give them
a little advice.
Betty...
You're moving across an ocean.
Where you'll have no family,
no friends,
you won't know the city.
Papi.
I know what that's like, mija.
Oh, we were so afraid.
But it was the best decision
we made in our lives.
Something tells me...
you'll look back
and think the same
about this move.
Thank you, papi.
Next.
No, stop. No advice.
I-I gotta tell you something.
Wait. No, papi, me first.
My advice is that
you're very stubborn
and you don't listen. Ha!
Tell him.
We're moving to Manhattan.
And there's plenty of room.
Yeah, we want you to
come and live with us.
Yeah.
That's very sweet.
And I appreciate it.
But I'm not going anywhere.
We're not gonna let
you live here alone.
I want to live here alone.
Don't you think I'm a little tired
of sharing one bathroom
with the three of you?
Believe me, my bladder isn't
what it used to be. Oh, come on.
I thought we were gonna have
an elegant lunch, but...
Oh, I want my daughters
and my grandson
to live their lives
the way they want.
A nosotros.
I heard congratulations
were in order,
and I wanted to be
one of the first.
Thank you, you are
the first, indeed.
You can put the flowers anywhere.
You... always seem
to know what's right.
Okay. Well...
Uh, not so fast.
Now that "mode" is mine,
uh, I'm going to be doing
some housecleaning...
Getting rid of some of the fat.
But Betty already left.
You know, I really
am gonna miss her.
Anyway, uh, I might need to
lean on you a little more...
Creatively...
If you feel you're up to it.
Yes. Sure.
I'm happy to be
leaned on creatively.
Good.
But no more schemes, right?
Well, uh...
There is just one.
I, uh...
Pulled some strings
with the senator
and got you a new cell mate-
a fairly high-profile type.
And why does this
high-profile prisoner
put such a twinkle in your eye?
Well, the feds are hoping
to extract a
confession out of him.
And someone who could
sweet-talk a guard
into letting him out of
prison to visit his girlfriend
might get him to talk.
And if so,
that person could suddenly
find his sentence...
Drastically reduced.
Well...
I think this guy
is going to find me
very hard to resist.
I couldn't agree more.
Okay.
First... what are you...
We have a surprise.
What are you doing?
You cannot go to
Europe in those. So...
Nice. Okay, can I take mine, too?
No. Come o...
Good-bye.
Bye.
You're gonna come
visit me soon, right?
Yeah. Summer can't
come soon enough.
I love you.
Be safe.
You go be great, chipmunk.
All right? Okay.
Be good, Austin.
Te quiero, mija.
I love you, papi.
Okay, okay. Okay.
Um, I will call you
as soon as I land.
It might be very early,
so just wait till you wake up
and call me back, okay? We will.
Betty.
Oh! Sorry.
Daniel.
So... was that hard for you?
Not really.
Well... I just...
I realized I've had
everything handed to me.
I've... I've never really
gotten anything on my own,
like... like you.
Well... I know there's a
lot you can do, Daniel.
Thank you.
And I also realized...
I didn't say good-bye,
which is, uh, really not cool.
So...
Good-bye...
And good luck...
And...
Have a safe flight. Thank you.
I'll call you when I get there.
So...
So that's it? You're, uh,
headed back to New York?
No. I think I'm gonna...
Stay around here for a while,
see what I can find.
Maybe take you to dinner...
Tonight, if you're free.
I would love that.
Well, I better get back to work.
I'm really glad you're here.
I'll, um, call you later.
Okay. Okay.
Hey, if you want something to do,
I am looking for a new assistant.
Sync by YYeTs.net
www.addic7ed.com