Oh, How Weird.
We're Always, Just, Like,
Running Into Each Other.
Hey, Jesse. Hi. Hey.
Oh, Hi! Oh, It's So Funny.
We're Always Just, Like,
Running Into Each Other.
Hey, Betty Rocker.
I Guess We're Just, Uh,
Two Ships
That Pass In The Morning.
How Was Work Last Night? Uh, 34
Bucks In Tips And The Cook Spit On Me.
Why Are You Always Up
So Early?
Oh, Uh, Work. Just So Much
To Do. Gotta Get An Early Start.
Want Some Coffee? The Guy
At The Shop, He Gave Me Two.
It's Decaf, 'Cause I Know You
Have To Sleep In The Morning.
I Mean, He Knows That You Sleep
In The Morning.
It Was Just A Coincidence. Hey, Oh,
I Knocked On Your Door Last Night.
You Weren't There, But I-I Wanted
To Give You Something. Really?
Yeah, It's A Couple New Songs
From My Band.
I- I Think It's Pretty Good.
O- Or It Sucks. I Don't Know.
But Listen,
You Have To Be Brutal,
'Cause You're Always
Way Too Nice To Me.
No, No. That's Just Because
I Always Like 'Em, You Know?
Your-Your Music Is So...
Emotional.
And That Song "I Made Her Cry"?
It Made Me Cry.
You're Sweet.
Oh, Hey. Um,
Do You Know If They Fixed
The Tv
In The Laundry Room Yet?
'Cause There's A Miles Davis Documentary Tonight
- I Have A Tv.
I Mean, You Don't Have To Watch
It In The Laundry Room.
You Could Just Come Over.
You Know, I'll Be Home
Just Doing Stuff,
So Knock Or Whatever.
All Right, Thanks. I Will.
Okay.
So You're Going To Work?
Yes. Yes.
Oh. That Way.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
Oh, My God! Betty. I
Thought I Heard Something.
What Are You Doing Here?
Um, I'm Starting Work
A Little Early.
Me, Too.
You're Naked.
And You're Wearing
A Hideous Ensemble,
But I'm Not All About
The Obvious. Amanda.
Okay, Stop Grilling Me.
I Kind Of Got A Little Evicted.
What? How? Can You Just
Put Something On, Please?
I Didn't Pay My Rent
A Couple Times,
And They Got So Nasty About It.
Well, Amanda, You Can't Live Here.
You Must Have, Like, A Hundred
Friends You Could Stay With.
You-Do You Need Some Money?
Betty, Please Stop Caretaking.
God, It's Like A Disease
With You. And I'm Fine Here.
One Of The Boys In Security
Takes Care Of Me,
And I Take Care Of Him.
Hey, Zander.
* Blind Girl,
Can't You See My Love? *
* Try To Tell You,
Try To Show You, Try To- *
Hi.
You Were, Um, Singing?
This Is My Friend Jesse's
New Song. It's Really Good.
Jesse-I've Been
Hearing That Name A Lot.
Whatever Happened
To No Romantic Entanglements?
Wasn't That The Rule?
Yes, It's Still The Rule.
Now Can We Please Talk About
The Fashion Heats Up Party?
Because We Still
Don't Have A Band.
And M.I.A.'S People
Just Called.
Apparently,
She's On Vacation In Brazil.
No One Can Get Ahold Of Her.
Ooh.
Looks Like Connor's Here.
Man, He Is So Cool.
Hiring Him Is The Smartest Thing I've Ever
Done. Yeah, Just Wait Till Wilhelmina Finds Out
You Tricked Her To Get Him Here. Come On,
Betty. I'm Tired Of Her Walking All Over Me.
I Need As Many People
On Team Daniel As I Can Get.
Besides, We Needed Someone
To Run The Financial Arm Of This Company. Connor's The Best.
Well, As A Member Of Team Daniel,
I Fully Support You. Besides, Everyone
Here Loves Him. It's Always Been That Way.
At Harvard,
He Was A Rock Star-
Captain Of The Crew Team,
All The Girls Loved Him.
Man, He Got A Lot Of...
Uh, Ahem. All The Girls
Really Loved Him.
This Is Why I Hate Women,
Marc. They're Weak.
Ugh. Look At Them
Throwing Themselves At Him.
Although, I Would Love To Live
In His Pants For A Year.
Ugh. You're All Fools.
The Only Thing
That Matters Is That
The New Chief Financial Officer
Loathes Daniel Meade,
Which Means
I'll Have An Ally.
So If It's You
Against Daniel...
He'll Always Agree With Me.
I Have To Agree With Daniel.
Again?
Well, Shooting In The Caribbean
Is Just More Cost Efficient,
And As Daniel's
Already Pointed Out-
Ugh. Yes, Yes, Yes, Daniel Has
Had So Many Great Ideas Today.
I Guess I'm Just Lucky.
Wilhelmina, I'm Just Giving You
My Honest Opinion.
There Simply Aren't The Funds
For Your Proposal.
Well, Then Find The Funds.
Okay, I'm Going To Be Blunt.
This Company Owns
Too Many Magazines.
Now If You Want To Funnel
More Money Into "Mode,"
I Suggest You Have A Look
At Selling Off Some Of Your Titles.
Finally... An Idea I Can Agree With.
Now I Have A Very Strong
Relationship With Cond?Nast.
I Think There May Be Interest
In A Sale.
No. We Are Not Selling Off
A Single Magazine.
They're A Part Of My Father's Legacy.
That's Ridiculous. Connor, Come On.
It May Be Too Drastic.
I'll Explore Other Options.
Excuse Me.
Why Are You Two So Chummy?
What The Hell
Is Going On Here?
I Think
What's Going On, Wilhelmina,
Is You've Been Played.
Why Don't You Try
One Of Connor's Doughnuts?
They're Really Good.
Okay, I've Got Chips And Dip
And Carrot Sticks, You Know,
In Case He's That Guy.
Now Should I Light Candles
Or Is That Too Romantic?
But Maybe I Like Candles.
Maybe I'm That Girl.
If He Could Be That Guy,
I Could Be That Girl, Right?
Ooh! You Are Crushing Hard.
Yes, Maybe I Like Him,
But What Are The Chances
That He's Gonna Like Me Back?
Oh, Stop It. Henry And Gio
Were Crazy About You.
That Was Different.
Jesse's An Artist.
He Writes Music, Hilda,
And I Get So Dorky When I'm
Around Him. Honey, Please.
He's Always Asking
You To Listen To His Music.
If A Guy Needs You To Tell Him
How Great He Is, He Likes You.
Really?
Yeah.
I Don't Know.
Aunt Betty?
Yeah?
It's Not That I Don't Love
What You're Wearing Right Now-
It's Very You-
But, Um, Maybe For Tonight,
We Can Go A Little Simpler.
Okay. Thank You So Much
For Coming.
It Was So Sweet Of You Guys
To Help...
But He's Gonna Be Here
Any Minute, So Get Out.
Okay. Okay. I Love You.
Okay, But I'm Telling You, Re-
Mwah. Bye.
Okay. Okay, Bye.
Okay, Bye.
Coming!
Hi!
??
so ??
www.SUBTITULOS.es
-DIFUNDE LA PALABARA-
*TU COMUNIDAD DE SERIES*
Ooh. What Is This?
Do You Have A Boy
Coming Over?
Wait. It Is A Boy, Right?
'Cause I Need To Know
These Things If We're Gonna Be Roomies.
Um, Amanda, You Can't Stay Here.
Why? You Said I Should Stay With A
Friend. Yeah, But I Meant, Like, Marc.
Oh, Unh-Unh. I Don't Want
To Jeopardize That Friendship.
Besides, Cliff
Practically Lives There.
Okay. You Know What?
I Would Love To Help You,
But Right Now Is
Not A Very Good Time.
But, Betty,
I Have Nowhere Else To Go.
Believe It Or Not,
I Don't Have That Many Friends.
Girls Just Don't Seem
To Like Me.
And You Were So Nice To Me
This Morning.
I Figured You Wouldn't Mind,
Because, You Know,
You're Betty.
You're A Nice Person.
Hey.
Hey. So Bad News.
I Have To Cancel Tonight.
This Friend Of Mine-
Or Person Of Mine-
Is Having Some Hard Times.
I-
No, That's Totally Cool,
'Cause I Probably Wouldn't Have
Been Good Company Anyway.
You Know, We Just Lost This Gig
To Another Band, Buffalo Hump.
You Know Those Guys?
No, Can't Say I Do.
They Suck. Oh, I'm Sorry,
Jesse, But Don't Be Discouraged.
Your Band Is So Great.
It's Just A Matter Of Time
Before It Takes Off.
Well, You Know What's So Cool
About You?
I... I Really Feel
Like You Mean That.
Thanks, B.
You Have A Good Night.
Okay. You, Too.
Betty,
We're Out Of The Dip...
And I'm Hungry.
Dude, I Have To Say,
It's Good To Have You Here.
I Think We're Gonna
Make A Great Team.
Me, Too. Oh, I Put Together
A List Of Ideas To Cut Costs-
Small Things,
But I Think They Add Up.
You Don't Have
To Run Everything By Me.
Do What You Think Is Best.
I Know You Got My Back.
We're Bros.
Ugh. I Hate
That Stupid Fist Bump.
Talk To Me.
I've Been Over And Over
Connor's Contract.
You Can't Get Rid Of Him
Without A Huge Buyout.
Oh, I Put That In There To Screw
Daniel, Not Me. So What Are We Gonna Do?
Get Some Dirt On Connor Owens,
Something I Can Use As Leverage.
I Will Not Be
Constantly Overruled
By Two Silly White Boys.
I'm On It.
Oh, My God.
We Totally Match.
You And I Are
Going To Have So Much Fun.
* Merrymaking
* Come Into My House
* You're Invited Into My House
Is That My Lunch?
Oh. Oh, Sorry.
Halston, Save Some For Betty.
* Come Into My House,
You're Invited Into My House *
* Merrymaking
I Can't Sleep. Oh.
What Do You Want Me
To Do About It?
Sometimes It Helps
If You Tickle My Back
And Tell Me I'm Pretty.
* At My Place, Baby,
At My Place *
You Tickled Her Back?
That's A Little Bit Weird.
I Had No Choice. Christina,
I Needed To Get Some Sleep.
I Get It. I've Done A Lot Worse
Things To Get Some Sleep.
Believe Me. Betty, You're Gonna
Have To Kick Her Out.
But She's Got No Money.
Well, I Don't Like
The Way She's Interfering
With Your Social Life.
I Want You To Take This Crush
On To The Next Level. I Knew It.
Betty Has A Crush. It's Someone
From The Building, Right?
You're Always
Darting In And Out,
All Sweaty And Mysterious. Amanda,
It Is None Of Your Business.
Are You Wearing My Leggings?
It's Cute, Right?
And The Other Leg Makes
A Matching Scarf.
I Have To Say, I Don't Hate It. Well...
Ooh. Ooh. I Know Who Your Lover Is.
It's That Troll From 3g Who Walks His Guinea Pig
On A Leash.
When Are You Two Crazy Kids
Gonna Go Out?
It's Not The Guy
With The Guinea Pig,
And I'm Not Going Out
With Anybody,
Because I Don't Even Know
If This Guy Likes Me.
Here's What You Do.
Invite Him To The "Mode" Party.
It'll Be Totally Casz. That's A Good
Idea. There'll Be Loads Of People There,
And It Won't Even Feel Like A Date. And
If He Turns Out To Be A Serial Killer,
He Can Just Find Someone Else
To Cut Into Pieces.
You're Welcome.
So What Do You Think?
I Think I'm Gonna Ask Jesse
To The "Mode" Party.
Ooh!
Stop.
Hey There, Sexy.
Hey, Big Tiny.
Uh, Can We Please Work
On A Better Nickname For Me?
Why? It's Cute. So After Work,
Let's Meet At Prune,
Because If I Don't Get
A Parsley And Dandelion Salad,
I Swear To Barbra
I Am Going To Throw A Fit
With The Fury Of A Thousand
Queens. Move In With Me.
What? What Did-
What Did You Say?
Move... In... With... Me.
I Mean, We Spend
All Our Time Together Anyway.
I Mean, Doesn't It
Just Make Sense?
Um, We Should Definitely
Talk About That,
Because It Definitely Bears
Further Discussion.
Ahem.
Marc!
Coming, Willie. Oh, My God. This
Day Could Not Get Any Crazier.
Busy. Busy. Busy. Busy. Busy.
There's Just So Much To Do.
In Fact, I Don't Even Know
If I'm Gonna Be Able
To Do Dinner Tonight.
Well, We'll-We'll, Uh,
We'll-We'll-We'll Talk Later
Or-Or Tomorrow,
And, Um, Okay.
Hi, Jesse.
Hey.
I Was Just Thinking About You.
Really? Why?
Well, Um,
I Was Thinking About You
Because I Was Wondering, Um...
Yeah?
"Mode" Is Having This Party
For Global Warming.
Oh, It's Not
For Global Warming Obviously,
'Cause Global Warming Is Bad.
It's For Awareness. Yay!
Anyway, Um, I'm In Charge
Of Finding The Band.
It's Gonna Be Fun, And So I Was Thinking
- If I Could Play?
You Want Dark Sexual Journey
To Play At A "Mode" Party?
Oh, My-This Is Amazing.
Oh, No, Jesse. I Think That-
Do You Know What Kind
Of Exposure This Will Be For Us,
For-For Me? You're The Coolest
Girl Ever! Oh. Um, Uh...
Oh. Oh, My God.
Betty, I-I Was Just
So Depressed Today, You Know?
Like, I Was, Like,
This Close To Just...
Uh, Whatever.
I'll Put It In A Song,
But Oh, My-You Really,
Really Cheered Me Up.
I Mean,
You're A Snow Day, Betty.
Hey, Daniel. Good News.
We're No Longer Bandless.I Found Someone To Play At The Party
On Friday.
You Know What? Already Done.
Guess What?
We Got Mariah Carey.
It Turns Out Connor Knows Her.
Isn't That Great?
Yeah, I Mean,
Mariah's All Right,
But Can We Just Put A Pin In Her
For A Second?
Because I Think
I Found Someone Way Fresher-
Jesse's Band,
Dark Sexual Journey.
Huh. They're Awesome, And They're
About To Break Out Any Minute.
You'll Love Them.
Okay, Um, Great. Yeah. Let Me
Just Get Mariah On The Phone.
Hey, Mariah. It's Daniel.
Yeah, It Turns Out We're
Not Gonna Need You To Sing.
Uh-Huh. We Got Jesse, The Guy
From My Assistant's Building.
He Is So Cute. Yes,
He Is Just The Dreamiest.
I Hate When You're Sarcastic.
I Can't Move In With Cliff,
Right?
I Mean, This Is
Just Such A Big Step.
Sometimes I Think,
I Love This Guy,
And Then Sometimes I Think,
What Am I Doing With Him?
Am I Terrible?
No, Baby, You're Just Scared.
I Am. Look, All I Know Is That
Living With A Fatty Is Hard.
Mm. They're Always Hogging
The Bed And Making A Mess
And Borrowing Your Clothes.
By The Way, Loving This Dress.
It's Betty's Blouse.
I Totally Belted It.
It's Great.
Right?
Is It Good?
Very.
I Made A Few Calls,
Cashed In A Few Favors-
Oh, Yeah. Right. Sorry.
You're Not About The Process.
There's Lots Of Juicy Tidbits
About Connor's Past.
Oh, Females.
Have Connor Come To My Office
After Work.
I Think I Can Make
A Persuasive Argument
As To Whom He Should
Be Aligning Himself With.
I Don't Think You've Got
Any Choice, Betty,
But To Tell The Truth.
He Can't Play At The Party.
I Know. Two Shawarmas
With Everything, Please.
But You Should Have Seen
His Little Face.
Oh.
He's Gonna Be So Disappointed,
And He's Gonna Hate Me Before
I Even Know If He Likes Me. Oh-
Bring It. Who's Gonna Hate You?
No One. Why Are You Always Around?
Betty, We're Roomies Now.
This Is What We Do.
I'm Supposed To Be
All Up In Your Biz.
So Why The Brown Face? Oh, Betty
Told This Boy That She Really Likes
That He Could Play
At The "Mode" Party,
But Daniel Got Mariah Carey.
What? Well, She's Gonna Find Out
Sooner Or Later, Isn't She?
Yes, I Will. So It's A Musician?
Are You Wearing My Blouse?
Don't Change The Subject.
Here's What You Do-
Invite Him To Play At The After
Party. There Aren't Any After Parties.
Um, What About The One
We Are Having On Our Roof?
It Totally Just Came To Me. Your
Guy Will Have A Place To Play,
And I Can Charge Money
At The Door
And Pay Off My Credit Cards.
Aren't You So Glad
That I Moved In?
Bye.
Damn It!
You Okay?
No, I'm Wet.
Why Did You Replace
Our Nice Bottled Water
With Glasses We Now Have
To Fill Ourselves?
Why Don't You Just Hang
A Hamster Bottle In The Corner
And We Can All Take Turns
Sipping Off Of It?
Mom, Relax, Okay?
It's Probably Just One Of
Connor's Cost-Cutting Ideas.
Oh, Like That Memo Telling Us
We Now Have To Sign Out A Key
For The Supply Room?
Is That Connor's Idea As Well? I Told Him
He Didn't Have To Run Everything By Me.
You Be Careful, Daniel.
This Is A Pattern With You.
Whenever You Admire Someone, You
Tend To Give Your Power Away,
Just Like You Did With Your Brother. That's
Not True, And That's Beside The Point.
I Hired Connor
Because He's The Best,
And Because I Can Trust Him. That's
Good. Then I Suppose You're Not Worried
That He And Wilhelmina
Are Meeting Together Tonight,
Privately.
Or Did You Not Know That?
You See, I Make It A Point
To Know Everything
Wilhelmina Slater Is Up To,
And If They're Meeting Alone,
I Don't Like It.
There Are A Million Reasons
Why They Could Be Meeting.
Don't Worry.
Connor's Got My Back.
What Is This?
It Looks Like A Flyer
For A Rodeo At A Women's Prison.
What? I Like It.
Betty, No One Will Come
To A Party
With A Flyer Like This.
Fine. How Would You Do It?
But How Will People Know
Where To Go?
They Won't Even Know What Time To Show
Up. If They Want To Be There Badly Enough,
They'll Figure All That Out.
You Have To Make It Hard
To Get On The List.
That Way, The Party Will Be Full
Of People Desperate To Be There,
And They'll Think It's Great,
No Matter How Much
Of A Humongous Turd It Turns
Out To Be. Um, I Don't Know.
Trust Me, Roomie.
* All Of The Boys
And The Girls Here In Paris *
* Sing To The Night#
* Without Sight
But With Madness *
* I Can't Keep Up,
I'm A Wreck, But I Want It *
* Tell Me The Truth,
Is It Love Or Just Paris? *
* All Of The Boys And The Girls
Here In Paris *
* Sing To The Night
Without Sight *
* But With Madness
300 People. Cool, Right?
Wow.
That Is A Lot Of People.
Yes, It Is.
I'm Glad
We're Gonna Have This Chance
To Get To Know Each Other
Better, Connor.
I Find It Helps Improve
A Work Relationship.
Me, Too. Good, 'Cause,
You Know, I'm Confused.
I Was, Um, I Was Led To Believe
That You And Daniel-
Just How Bad Is
That Headache?
I'm Sorry?
Oh, You've Been Doing That...
A Lot.
Well, It's Been Quite A Day.
I Can Get Rid Of That For You.
No, Thank You. That's What
Drugs Are For. Come On.
Let Me.
I'm Better For Your Liver.
You Know Why You Get Them?
Too Many Ideas In Your Head
And Not Enough Time In The Day
To Get Them Out.
Even If You Could,
Who Would You Trust Them With?
That's A Lot Of Pressure,
Having Only Yourself
To Depend On.
I Get Headaches, Too.
There.
So How Is It?
It's Gone.
Good. Shall We Continue
Our Talk?
Now...
My Guess Is
A Woman Such As Yourself
Would Have A Bottle
Of '61 Single Malt Scotch
Floating Around The Place
Somewhere.
Um, '48.
Perfect.
Older Is Always Better.
I Wouldn't Know.
I've Been The Same Age
For Years.
You Know, Wilhelmina,
You're The Reason I'm Here.
Something Tells Me
I Could Learn A Lot From You.
* I Been Really Tryin', Baby
* Tryin' To Hold Back
This Feelin' For So Long *
* And If You Feel
* Like I Feel, Baby
* Then Come On
* Oh, Come On
* Whoo
* Let's Get It On
* Oh, Baby
Are You Okay?
You Seem Distracted.
Uh, It's Just
Because I-I-I Just Remembered
That I Have A Dinner.
I'll-I'll Call Marc
And Have Him,
Uh, Uh, Reschedule.
300 People?
I- I Thought I Was Making Food
For 50, M-Maybe 60 At The Most.
Well, You Can Thank Amanda.
I Had No Idea It Was
Gonna Get This Big,
But, Papi, What Am I Gonna Do?
I Promised Jesse.
Sweetheart, Why Are You Going To So Much
Trouble For A Boy? Because She Likes Him, Papi.
I Do. I Do Like Him, And I
Shouldn't Even Be Saying That.
A Guy Is The Last Thing
I Should Be Thinking About.
Why? You're Young, You Have
A Good Job, Your Own Apartment.
Yeah, And You're Wearing
Heels Sometimes.
Thank God.
He's Nice To You, Mija?
So Nice, But I Can't.
I Can't Do This.
I Have To Cancel.
I Can't Afford This Party.
You Guys Are Thinking
About This All Wrong.
Okay? It Doesn't Have
To Cost That Much.
You Know, I Was Reading
In "Vanity Fair" One Time
That Going Budget Is
Totally In Now,
Like, Cheap Is The New Chic.
Well, Cheap We Can Work With.
Maybe I Can Get A Discount
At Flushing Burgers,
Cut Up A Bunch Of Jumbos,
Do A Mole For Dipping.
Oh, And We Can Make A Ton
Of Sangria.
Cheap Wine, Old Fruit, A Box
Of Sugar-People Get Drunk.
They Don't Care.
Drinking Is Bad.
Okay, So We Have A Theme
- South Of The Border. Oh, And Then We Can Use
The Decorations From My
QuinceaERa. Oh, Good Idea.
That's Such A Great Idea. Tacky
Mexican Stuff Is So Kitschy.
What? I'm Allowed To Say That.
It's My Heritage.
Oh, And, Guys, Thank You.
You Always Come Through
For Me.
You're Like A Total Snow Day.
That's A Good Thing.
Oh.
Oh. Okay.
So How Did It Go
With Connor?
Did You Break Him?
Did He Cry?
Do I Need To Offer Him
A Comforting Hug?
Check My Calendar, Please.
What, That's It? You're Not
Gonna Tell Me Anything
After All The Work I Did
To Dig Up That Dirt?
I Didn't Use It. It Wasn't The
Time. So When Will Be The Time?
Since When Are You
Such A Nosey Parker?
Your Job Is To Do What I Say
And Not Ask Any Questions.
I Hope I'm Not Interrupting.
Oh, No.
Connor, My, Uh,
My Door Is Always Open.
I Just Wanted To Let You Know
I'd Be Out Most Of The Day.
Hey, How Was
That Dinner Last Night?
It Was Fun...
Just Delightful.
Thank You For Asking.
I'll See You
At The Fashion Heats Up Party.
Fun? Delightful?
You Didn't Have A Dinner
Last Night.
You Don't Even Eat Dinner.
Oh, My God, You Like Him.
Don't Be Ridiculous.
Willie, You Saluted Him.
You Haven't Saluted Anyone
Since Cheney.
You Have Fallen For Him
Like Everyone Else Here.
I Don't Fall For Anyone, Marc.
I'm Not Like
Those Other Women Out There,
Ruled By Their Emotions. Willie,
It's Okay To Feel Something.
No, It's Not, Not When It
Gets In The Way Of Ambition.
How Do You Think
I Got This Far?
Now I've Had
My Momentary Lapse Of Judgment,
But That Is Over Now.
So What Are You Gonna Do Now?
Finish What I Started.
That Party Is Gonna Get
A Lot More Interesting.
Marc.
Oh. I Didn't Even
See You There.
What's Going On, Marc?
I Mean, I-I Asked You
A Really Important Question
And Then You-You Don't Call Me
Back For Three Days?
I'm So Sorry. It Has
Just Been Nonstop Around Here.
What, With The Blackmailing,
Backstabbing
And Going On Pinkberry Runs,
I've Barely Even Had Time
To Take The Curlers
Out Of My Hair.
Is There Still One
Back There?
Why Is The Idea
Of Moving In With Me So Hard?
It-It's-It's Just Big.
It's Like Deciding
To Get A Kid.
How Do You Know It's The Right
Time Or What Kind To Get?
I Mean,
Do You Go Russian, Chinese
Or Stay Local And Do Something
South American?
And Then What If You're Wrong,
And It Clashes
With Your Furniture
- Forget It, Marc. You Gave Me Your Answer.
So I Have A Car Picking You Up
At Your Party At 10:30
So You Can Be At My Party
By 11:00.
Do You Think It's Weird
That I've Left Two Messages
For Connor, And He Hasn't
Called Me Back? No, He's Probably
Just In A Place Where He
Can't Answer. I'm His Boss.
He Should Be Letting Me Know Where He's
Gonna Be All Day. Is Everything Okay?
Yeah, Everything's Fine.
It's Just Something My Mom Said.
You Know What?
You Should Go Home
And Get Ready For Your Party.
I Will, And, Oh, Daniel,
Thank You So Much
For That Donation.
Well, It Is
The "Mode" After Party.
Besides, I Heard The Singer
Of The Band Is Just To Die For.
Why Do I
Tell You Anything?
* Hey, You
I'm Sorry.
You're Not On This List.
S
A Crisp George Washington
Could Persuade Me.
That Means A $20!
Okay, Here You Go.
Not So Fast, Gorgeous.
Mama Owes The Government.
See, The-The-The Trick
To A Good Mole Is Cinnamon.
Hey, Man,
Can I Wear Your Hat?
Don't Touch The Hat.
Aah!
Oh, My God. What A Turnout.
It's Like Everybody's
Showing Up.
I Think One Of The Understudies
From "Spamalot"
Just Used My Bathroom.
No.
Oh, And Have You Seen Jesse?
'Cause I Think The Band Wants To Start.
Oh, Yeah, I Think I Saw Him Downstairs.
Betty, He's So Cute!
All Sad And Tortured-
I See Why You Like Him.
Right?
I Know.
Oh, Finally.
Connor Left Me A Message.
Why Wasn't He
At That Dreadful Party?
If I Had To Sit And Listen
To Scarlett Johansson Babble
About Climate Change,
He Should Have.
He Said His Meeting Went Late.
He's Gonna See Me
At The After Party.
Drama At Casa Del Meade.
Word On The Boulevard
Is That Meade Publications
Is Selling Off Some Magazines.
My Anonymous Source Reginald
Has Confirmed
That Meade's New C.F.O.,
Connor Owens,
Met With Cond?Nast For Several
Hours This Afternoon.
He's Working With Wilhelmina?
I'm Sorry, Daniel.
Oh, He's Gonna Be, Too.
Hi. Welcome. Welcome.
Have Fun.
Jesse.
What Are You Doing Out Here?
The Band's Ready To Start.
Are You Okay?
It's-Th-That's Too Big.
I- I Can't Do That.
Of Course You Can.
No, I-What If I Suck?
There's No Way You Could Suck.
You're Just-
You're Just Having A Little Bit
Of Stage Fright.
I- I'm A Fake, Betty. I-I Just
Don't Think I Have It.
Yes, You Do.
Look, Maybe You Can't
Feel It Right Now,
But It's In There.
I Can See It.
And-And These Bad Thoughts,
That's What's Fake.
As Soon As You Get Up There
And Start Playing,
Everyone Else Is
Gonna See What I Do.
All Right.
Okay.
Whoo!
God, Betty,
You're So Beautiful.
Thank You.
* But I'll Try My Best
* Either You Live Your Life
Or You Sit Witness *
* While A Look-Alike
Comes And Steals Your Bliss *
* So Come On
* Get On With It
* We're Just Wasting Time
Isn't He Amazing?
Yeah, But Ivanka Trump
Just Put A Burger In Her Purse,
So I Have To Go Call Randy.
Okay, Love You. Bye. Okay.
*... With It
* We're Just Wasting Time
* Get On With It
Hey, So I Think I Figured Out
Who Betty's Crush Is.
It's That Old Guy Over There.
That's Her Father.
Oh.
Mandy,
Cliff Won't Call Me Back.
He's Mad Because He Thinks I Don't
Want To Move In With Him. But You Don't.
Well, Why Should I?
Everything Was Fine Before.
We Had Our Lives
And Our Hair Products Separate.
Everyone Looked Good
And Nothing Changed.
Why Does He Want
To Ruin That?
Oh, Marc,
Are You Really Mad At Cliff,
Or Are You Starting To Have
Doubts About Him?
Oh, My God!
They Put Out Cake.
Do What You Want.
I'm Sure You'll Make
The Right Decision. Bye.
*... Always Come To A Head
* Over A Glass Of Wine
And A Cigarette *
* You Got A Little Dagger
Stuck Inside My Chest *
* I'm 'Bout As Ready Now
As I'll Ever Get *
Thanks.
So, Uh, I Wanted To Try
A Little Solo Something, Uh,
And, Uh, Dedicate This
To Someone Here Who's...
We-Well, She's Just
Really Special.
* Every Day
Just Blurs Into One *
* The Moon Starts To Look
Just Like The Sun *
* Full Steam Ahead,
Day To Night *
* Never Fully Charged
* Never Quite Right
* But She Was A Snowy Day
* A Break From Working Hard
* For Such Little Pay
* She Was A Snowy Day
* She Let Me Get Some Rest
* She Let Me Sleep Real Late
* So I Could Fight Another Day
* She Was A Snowy Day
Is Everyone
Enjoying Themselves?
Who Cares? He Dedicated
A Song To You! He Likes You!
I Don't Know.
But I Mean, I Think He Does.
Earlier, He Told Me
I Was Beautiful.
What More
Do You Need, Girl?!
Go Ask Him Out!
I- I Know.
I- I Should, Shouldn't I?
Yes!
Okay, I Will. I Will.
Uh, I Should Probably
Do That Now?
Yes, Yes. Ready?
Okay.
Here I Go.
Go! Go!
* Show Me What You Got
Hi, Ms. Slater. How Are You?
Good To See You.
You A Friend Of Betty's?
What? Oh, God, No.
She's A Nice Girl.
I Live Right Below Her-
4g.
Am I To Understand
I'm On Betty's Roof?
Yeah.
* If You Get That Feeling
* But You Can't Describe It
* It's Okay
* I Know You Like It
* When You Get That Feeling
* But You Can't Describe It
* All You Know
Is That You Like It *
You Look Beautiful. I Think We're
Done With The Charm, Aren't We?
Listen, I Know You're In Bed
With Daniel, So Let Me Be Blunt.
You Start Playing
For My Side,
Or I Will Reveal
Some Things About You
You Probably Don't Want Out There.
Wilhelmina, Can We Go Somewhere And Talk?
Connor, I Know All About
Your Meetings At Cond?Nast.
What The Hell Happened
To Our Deal?
I'm Not Gonna Have You Two
Conspiring Behind My Back.
I Don't Care
What Your Contract Says.
I Want You Out Of Here. Daniel, Do
You Know How Much It's Gonna Cost
To Fire A Man Like This? Oh, He
Won't Need To. I'll Walk Right Now.
God, You Two Are Children.
I Played Your Game
To Get The Job,
But That Is Where It Ends.
I Took The Meeting
Because You Asked Me
To Exercise My Judgment,
Which Is This-That Selling Off
A Couple Of Magazines
Makes Financial Sense,
Far More Sense Than Preserving
Your Father's Legacy
At Any Cost.
And You-Whatever It Is
You Think You've Got On Me,
Let It Out.
I'll Tell You What.
I'll Even Help You.
Drugs? I've Done
Pretty Much Everything.
I've Slept With
My Best Friend's Wife.
Oh, Here's A Great One.
My First Job At Smith Barney?
I Overhear Two Guys In
An Elevator Trading Stock Tips.
I End Up Losing My Shirt
And I Almost Go To Jail.
But I Turn My Life Around.
I Make Myself Into Somebody
That I Can Be Proud Of.
So If You Want Me To Do The Job
That You Hired Me For, Fine.
But If You Want Me
To Pick Sides, Forget It.
I'm Nobody's Bitch.
I Need A Drink.
Jesse?
Are You In There?
Oh! Sorry.
Jeez, Betty,
Ever Hear Of Knocking?
Betty, W-Wait. Betty, Wait!
Betty, It Was Bound To Happen
Sooner Or Later.
Next Time, I'll Just
Leave A Bra On The Doorknob.
You Are
The Worst Roommate Ever.
You Are Selfish And Insensitive,
And I Want You Out.
Just Be Gone
By Tomorrow Morning.
* And Dance To Me
* Again
* Like You Were Stone
Connor, I Wanna Apologize
For My Behavior.
I Always Blackmail People
When I'm Nervous.
It's Just
Kind Of My Go-To.
* Then Dance To Me
There Aren't A Lot
Of Nice People
In This Business.
I... Didn't Expect
To Meet Someone
Who Actually Has Integrity.
Thank You.
We Need You.
So If You Decide To Stay,
Let's Start
With A Clean Slate.
I'd Like That,
As Long As I Don't
Have To "Knuckle Bump"
With Daniel Anymore.
We Still
Have To Try That Scotch.
It's A Date.
Will You Excuse Me?
It's My FiancE.
So Can I Call You?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm In The Book.
Hunter Farthington.
Marc?
Cliff! What Are You Doing Here? I
- I Got Your 20 Messages.
Sweetie, I'm-I'm Sorry.
I- I-I Should've Known That-
That Asking You To Move In
Would-Would Cause A Meltdown.
Hey, You...
You're A Neurotic Mess,
And I Love That About You.
Look, All That Matters
Is That We Love Each Other.
Marry Me.
What?
Marry Me, Cliff.
I Wanna Be With You
Forever.
Oh, I Blew It
Up There With Connor.
I Can't Believe What A Fool
I Made Out Of Myself.
Well, I'm Pretty Sure
I'm A Bigger Fool.
I Threw Him A Party.
Are You Crying?
I Was So Stupid To Think
That He Would Like Me.
Of Course
He Likes Amanda.
Amanda?
They Were Kissing.
I Walked In On Them.
I Should've Known That
When He Said I Was Beautiful,
He Meant On The Inside.
You Are.
You Don't Have To Say That,
Daniel.
I'm Fine With Who I Am,
But I'm Not Beautiful.
Betty... Men Are Stupid.
They Go For The Obvious.
Trust Me. I Know.
I'm Still Doing It,
And I Should Know Better.
But You're 24.
It's Okay To Have A Crush,
Act A Little Stupid.
But You Have To Believe Me
When I Say This-
You Are Beautiful.
Hey.
So...
I Made, Like,
A Ton Of Money Tonight.
And... I'm A Simple Girl.
What Do I Need It For?
Here. You Should
Put It Toward Rent.
Hey, So Remember That Guy
That I Was Kissing Earlier?
Yeah, I Don't Think
You Know Him.
Anyway, I Am So Over Him.
I Was Talking To Him, And It
Turns Out He's Kind Of Stupid.
I Mean, Yes,
He Is The Kind Of Guy
A Girl Would Totally
Fall For, But...
He Is So Not Worth It.
Betty, I Had No Idea.
Amanda, Look.
I Was Wrong.
You Aren't
The Worst Roommate Ever.
And If You Need
To Stay Here
For...
A Little While Longer,
I'm Fine With That.
You Know, Betty,
You're Lucky.
When Someone
Falls In Love With You,
It's Real.
I've Never Had That.
I Never Know
If I'm Loved For Who I Am
Or Because I'm So Pretty.
Why Don't You Finish
Cleaning Up In Here?
Betty.
Have A Seat.
* Details Of Your Look
* Like Your Tights
* Killing Me By Shoot
* Just In Once
* Oh, See, Just Take A Look
* With Your Cries
* Since The Days Of School
* You And I
* You're On My Mind
* Just Let Me Play
www.SUBTITULOS.es
-DIFUNDE LA PALABRA-