Previously on "ugly betty",
Wilhelmina is back.
I ??? Wilhelmina as
creator director of mode.
What?
You can write
an article for "hot flash."
300 words by tomorrow morning.
- I gotta get ready
for the p.T.A. Thing this morning.
- Since when are you on the p.T.A.?
- Since she has a crush
on my gym teacher.
- You wanna hang out sometime?
Henry and i agreed
a clean break would be best.
- You kissed me.
- Yeah, well, you kissed me back.
I don't wanna be
the rebound guy.
I wanna be the guy.
Betty.
Me?
You want me
to play on your team?
- But i've never even played before.
- That's okay.
And mona's so good.
- She's got really strong leggs.
- We don't need mona's legs.
We need you, betty.
Really? You need me?
Mm-Hmm.
Okay.
Yes. Uh, yes, i-I'll play.
Okay, ladies, line up.
Thanks, kimberly.
Get behind the human shield!
Where's the human shield?
What?
No, no. No, stop that!
Aah!
And that is why
i am not a fan of team sports,
And why i will not be playing
In the annual
"'mode' vs. 'Elle'
- Softball game to benefit charity."
- Well, that's just pathetic.
No, gio. It was traumatic.
I can't even think
about that day
Without
getting panic attacks,
- And who cares if i play in the game?
- Daniel does. He even came down
to my deli to recruit me.
I guess this softball team
is daniel's baby.
He loves holding a trophy over
his head while people cheer.
Well, i just thought it would be
something fun for us to do
- As a couple.
- We're not exactly a couple yet.
I told you.
I wanna take it slow.
We're not exactly friends.
No,
But we're in
an exploratory phase.
Oh, okay, explorer.
So when do i get to take you out
on an official first date?
Soon.
Well, it better be
very soon.
- I'm going to italy for a month.
- What?
What's the big deal?
You're the one who said
we're not a couple.
I said, "exploratory phase."
Look,
it's what mario batali did
When he needed
to discover himself,
You know,
find his own unique flavor.
It's all part
of my 5-Year plan.
Well, wow.
That's... really exciting...
And great.
- What are you looking at?
- The next step in my 5-Year plan.
My very first
published article ever!
- Here you go.
- I think it's near the front.
Okay, maybe more
in the middle.
All right.
Not so much the middle.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Let me see.
A bunch of ads
for old lady creams...
Ah, here it is-
"Young at any age
by... "
- "Betty suarez."
- Betty suarez.
Wow. It's a little smaller
than i imagined
And completely rewritten.
"Natch"?
I didn't write "natch."
I wrote "naturally."
Who says "natch"?
Ah, yes. "Natch."
I want
to be honest with you.
The idea for the article
was great.
The execution, not so much.
It was too... safe.
"Safe"?
Okay.
Well, um...
Thank you for
the constructive criticism,
And thank you
for the opportunity.
Betty, what do you want
to be when you grow up?
Wh-
I... want to be you.
You do?
Mm-Hmm. I want to own
my own magazine like you.
Why?
Because i love magazines.
I just-I always have.
Uh, they speak to me.
And i wanna do that
for other people.
I wanna speak to them
and touch their lives.
Well, i have no doubt
That you will achieve
whatever you want,
But, betty, you're never
going to do it by playing safe.
You're going to have to start
taking some risks,
And it's not just
with your work,
But also with your life.
* baby, hurry up,
'cause i can't... *
You know, i always thought
i hated tater tots,
But when i got out of school,
i found myself craving them.
Well, how about that jell-O
with the fruit in it?
- Mnh-Mnh. That was gross.
- Yeah.
Did you bring any?
Straight
from the fine chefs...
Of the p.S. 350 cafeteria.
Oh, you are
a true romantic, coach.
You know,
you can call me tony.
I like calling you coach.
- Yeah?
- Mm-Hmm.
* i just wanna fall in love *
You are a rock, woman.
Excuse me?
I am far from a rock.
- I am one fine gem.
- Yeah, well, if you hadn't
skipped science class,
You would know
that it takes a lot of heat
To turn a rock into a gem.
- It also takes a lot of time.
- And pressure.
Okay. Enough.
I went
through a lot this year,
- So i wanna take it slow.
- Fine.
I'll see you saturday.
Okay.
* baby, i will give you more *
* work *
* then you do your homework *
* get up on the dance floor *
* work *
* if you do your homework *
* baby, i will give you more *
* work *
* entiendo means i get it *
* siempre means
that i won't forget it *
Hey.
Good job on the uniforms.
The girls aren't gonna
wanna wear flats, though.
- I suggest a high-Heeled cleat.
- Yeah, well, that sounds practical.
- Have you been here all night?
- A couple of nights, actually.
There's a lot of work
to be done
- On the madelon de bie presentation.
- Yeah, well, you don't have to kill
yourself doing it.
- Yes, i do. We need the account.
- Look, all i'm saying is,
- You have a really strong creative director.
- No. I told you no wilhelmina.
She wants my job.
She wants my magazine.
She probably even wants
my softball team.
- I don't trust her.
- She isn't the only one you don't
seem to be trusting lately.
Alexis, what do you expect?
You turned your back on me
when you gave her a title.
- Daniel
- I have a presentation to finish.
How cute am i in this?
Pretend you're a man
for a second,
- And tell me how hot i look.
- You look fine, but this is
not working for me.
I like the "v," but it is
doing nothing for my bustline.
Oh, hey, betty.
Great piece in "hot flash."
You totally captured
that old lady voice.
- * natch *
I didn't write that.
Oh, hey, amanda.
You're in charge
of the cheerleading squad
For the "mode"
softball team, right?
See, i really don't want
to play on the team.
You wanna be the mascot?
Um, no to the mascot,
But i have pep to spare.
Oh, my god.
- You are not asking me-
- Gasp. I think she is.
Please?
Well, if you want
to be a cheerleader,
You have to try out first.
Toe touch. Go.
Right herkie. Left herkie.
Star jump. Jump. Jump.
Jump. Jump. Jump. Jump.
Hey, everyone,
we were wrong.
She can get off the ground.
I have proof.
Unfortunately, we don't have
any uniforms in your size,
But thank you so much
for trying out.
Mm.
Uh, pardon, s'il vous plaît.
Parlez-Vous français?
Oh, little french boy.
Do you mind if i
dress you up like a doll
- And put makeup on you?
- Quol?
Exactly.
I don't understand.
What is 23?
23 what?
Oh, that's the average age
of the wealthiest subsector
Of the urban demographic
we're targeting.
See? It's right here
on the chart. See?
I am confused.
Is anyone else confused?
Ja.
Of course you're confused,
because it's confusing.
Thorough? Yes.
Accurate? Indeed.
But it just makes
my head hurt.
Madelon,
we've done a terrible job
Appealing to your head.
- Perhaps we can appeal to your heart.
- No.
What daniel
is neglecting to say is,
This weekend is
The "mode" versus "elle"
charity softball game.
What if we donated the proceeds
to engelen van kinderen,
The children's charity
you cochair in the netherlands?
As an expectant mother myself,
I care a great deal
about the lives of children,
Especially the poor
and the disadvantaged.
And what do you want
in return?
A 1-Year commitment
to 20 pages per issue,
At a 30% reduced rate,
of course. Goed?
Erg goed.
Hmm.
She made me look
like an ass.
I have been working
on that all week.
- She stole the show.
- Yeah, but it was my show.
Daniel, you know
that i hate to say this,
But i don't think
that witch wilhelmina
Is going anywhere
anytime soon.
Maybe you need to find
a way to work with her.
Betty, wilhelmina
doesn't work with people.
She works against them.
There she is,
Probably
bad-Mouthing me already.
"Daniel sucks. Daniel's boring.
Daniel doesn't know
how to do his job."
Okay, i'm gonna let you
work through this one.
I have lunch with gio,
So i'll be back when you're
done with the voices, 'kay?
Oh, betty,
Congratulations
on your article.
Natch. Funny.
I didn't even write that.
And then mrs. Meade says
that my article was too safe.
Well, what would've been
the risky thing to do?
Shorten more words-
"Fabu," "brill"?
Sounds like
you're in a difficult sitch.
Just kidding.
What are you doing?
- I thought we were gonna go
grab some lunch.
- We're gonna have a little batting lesson.
If you're gonna play
in that softball game,
You need to practice.
No. No way. Not doin' it.
I'd rather be the mascot.
Okay,
you don't have to.
I mean, if you want
to play it safe...
Pardon, monsieur.
Daniel meade?
- Can i help you?
- S'il vous plaît.
Parlez-Vous le français?
Je voudrais parler avec vous.
Sorry. I skipped
my french classes in school.
C'est important, monsieur. Je
crois que tu connais ma mère...
All right. Betty.
Et je suis venu de france.
C'est très, très important.
Does anyone speak french?
You know, it would really help
if you kept your eyes open.
Gio, i hate this.
Do i have to do it?
Yes, you have to.
Now stop saying no
and start saying yes.
Focus on the ball.
Okay.
Aah! I hit it! I hit it!
Whoa! Whoa!
- You did. That was a great one.
- Yes!
Yes! Yes!
- Yes! Yes!
- Whoa!
- Whoo!
You did it. Let's go.
Hit it again.
- You see what you can do when
you say yes to things?
- Yes.
- Come to rome with me.
- Yes!
What?
Oh!
Are you serious?
Very.
Betty, i want us to have
The most romantic
first date ever.
And what could be
more romantic than rome?
What do you say?
Okay.
Yes.
Yes, i'll go to rome.
* so far away,
so far away *
Je m'appelle daniel.
He says his name is daniel.
- Ha. Sweet. Like me.
- Ma maman est lucie chainet.
He says his mother's name
is lucie chainet.
Elle est mannequin. Ils se sont
rencontrés ?Paris.. >
- She is a model.
- Il y a quelques années.
He says you met her
in paris many years ago.
Uh, it's vaguely familiar.
Elle est décédée...
She has died recently.
Oh, well, that's-That's really,
um, that's a bummer.
Would you like me
to translate that?
No.
Je suis en voyage scolaire
?New york>
Je me suis échapp?/I>>
pour retrouver mon pére>
He's in new york
on a trip with his school.
He separated from them
Because he wanted
to meet his father.
Uh, okay. I got-
I mean, yeah.
We could help him
find his father, i guess.
Daniel.
You are his father.
±¾×öä»½ö¹©ñ§ï°½»á÷£¬ñï½ûóãóúéìòµóãí¾
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
Ugly betty 218
-=Ææàãðü×öä»×é=-
·­òë: ð£¶ô:
ê±¼äöá:îò°®ê¨ðäð¡s
Okay, i have amazing news.
One-You are looking
at the newest member
Of the "mode" softball team!
* ooh, ooh *
That's right. I know it's crazy,
but i just signed up.
And two-Don't freak out,
But gio-My gio,
pickle napkin gio-
He asked me to go
to rome with him for a month,
And i said yes!
Oh, god, daniel.
You're already freaking out.
Look, it'll be fine.
I know this terrific temp,
And i'll totally be
reachable...
Oh, hey. Who's the kid?
And why are you
wearing eye shadow?
He says he's my son.
What? Oh, my god.
You trumped me.
His mother was a model
i slept with years ago.
She just died.
That's terrible.
It is,
but he's not my son.
You know how many times
this happened to my father?
People just show up,
pretend to be related.
True.
But, daniel, your father
did get around a bit.
I mean, he managed to father
a child after his death.
Betty.
- Sorry, but you guys are really fertile.
- Look, either someone is after my money,
Or they're just messing
with my head and...
And i think i know
who it is.
So what you're saying is,
I researched
every woman you slept with
Found out which one
had an illegitimate child,
Waited for the woman to die
and then arranged
For the child to come
on a class trip from europe
Just to upset you?
You are not gonna
beat me here, wilhelmina.
You may own
a third of the company,
But i am still editor-In-Chief
of this magazine.
You have no moves
in this chess game.
Daniel, i play chess.
You're playing checkers.
Either way...
You have no moves.
Well, that choo choo has gone
off the rails, right?
I mean, it's not like
there's some twisted scheme
That you haven't told
me about, is there?
There is. Oh, my god.
You are diva brilliance.
Marc...
I didn't plan this.
Oh, god must truly love us.
Just in our time of need,
He drops a little french boy
into our laps.
Go, god.
And viva la france.
So what are you thinking?
Well, daniel
clearly doesn't want
To acknowledge
the child is his,
So let's use that
to our advantage.
Check and mate.
Queen me.
Oh, marc.
Vous êtes plus grand
que j'imaginais.
Yeah, i still
don't speak french.
He said you're taller
than he imagined.
That's nice.
Are we almost done here?
Yes, we are.
We'll have the results back
in a couple of weeks.
Okay. Great.
Excellent.
Uh, the day's over.
I am outta here.
Daniel...
what about daniel, jr.?
What? I called the school.
They're gonna pick him up.
Besides, i got three models
waiting for me at lotus.
- What? You mean, you don't want
to spend any time with him?
- Betty, i told you. This is a scam.
We have to go
through the motions,
But that kid is not my son.
Daniel...
What?
He doesn't speak english.
He doesn't have to.
Good evening my little friend.
Good evening.
I'm sorry your father
left you alone.
Are you hungry?
Would you like to have
dinner with us?
Oul.
- Bon.
Mom, i think
you're being a tease.
Shut up.
I just really like him,
So i'm playing hard to get.
Which is
a very good idea, mija.
I mean, what do you know
about this coach diaz?
I know he's hot
and super sweet,
And i know he has
a degree in wellness training,
So he's smart.
And he doesn't sweat ever.
It's bizarre.
We call him lizard man.
- Hello?
- Hey, betty. So what do
you think of this coach diaz?
Um, i'm going
to rome with gio.
- What?
- Oh, my god.
- Aunt betty, you're crazy.
- I know.
- Betty, how are you gonna afford this?
- I've been saving a little,
And-And we're gonna
do things on the cheap.
- And where are you gonna sleep,
in the same bed with him? - Dad, we
haven't really discussed that part yet.
- Well, don't you think you should?
- Ay, papi,
she's 24. It's not like she's a virgin.
- Wait. What?
- Hilda.
Okay. Uh, i'll get
the recap later. Bye.
Dad, look, i don't know
all the details yet,
But it just feels right,
and-And when am i ever
Gonna get an opportunity
to do this again?
Ay, dios mio.
- Do you support this?
- Hey, i would love to go to italy.
Gracias.
Uh, aunt betty?
There's someone
at the door for you?
Oh, my god.
What-What are you doing here?
Will you marry me, betty?
- Um, i'm-
- Shocked?
Totally.
Betty
Henry, why are you
doing this to me right now?
I am just starting
to get over you.
Don't. Don't get over me.
I'm not over you.
I love you, betty.
- No.
- I love you, and we can be together.
- I want you to move to tucson with me.
- Wha-What?
I've given this
a lot of thought.
There's no reason not to do it.
I know you can be happy there,
And i have a friend
that works at a magazine.
I gave him your resume?
He was impressed.
And he can give you a job
as a writer,
And the pay is good, so you can
still help out with your family,
- And you can visit them, and
they can visit you.
- Henry-
Just say yes.
I know this is huge
and crazy.
Yes.
Betty,
it would be amazing.
I'm going back on monday.
I want you to be
on that plane with me
As my fiancee.
Are you out of your mind?
- You're gonna miss the opportunity to
go to rome? - I thought you didn't want
me to go to rome.
That was before henry proposed.
You're only 24 years old.
- You're not getting married.
- Papi, why not?
- She found true love. He wants
to be with her. - She's too young,
and it's too far.
Well, you left mexico
to be with the woman you loved,
- And that was much farther, and you
were younger. - I was not much younger,
and this is totally different.
No, it isn't, so when
the shoe is on the other foot-
- Guys
- Shoes, what are you talking about? Shoes?
You know what?
This is all ridiculous.
She's not going to rome
with some guy she barely knows,
- And she's not getting married and moving
to tucson. - She is standing right here.
And she's asking
for your advice,
Not your approval.
Good...
Because you're not
getting any from me.
Good morning, fashionistas.
For those of you just waking up
or just going to bed,
We have some breaking news.
Just when we thought
the meade family drama
Couldn't get any juicier,
Along comes some
freshly squeezed jus d'orange.
Daniélmeade is
The illegitimate love child
of daniel meade
And the late hand model
lucie chainet,
Whose famous fingertips
scratched through
Many a bare back in some
scandalous mid-90s perfume ads.
So how did daniel
embrace the news?
He didn't! He partied
the night away at lotus,
Promoting this weekend's
"Mode"/"elle"
charity softball game.
- I hope he didn't leave his glove
at home. - Oh, no, she di'int!
Meanwhile, little orphan danny
walked the streets of manhattan,
Digging through dumpsters
for food.
So far,
no comment from daniel sr.
Papa, can you hear me?
- He's got your jawline.
- That's all, fashionistas. Stay
tuned for more updates.
- Mom.
- What?
There is a resemblance. Hmm?
Now why are you fighting this?
I have a grandson.
I'm very happy about that,
and you should be, too.
He's not my kid.
I don't know how this got out.
- I called the school. They were gonna pick
him up. - Madelon de bie just pulled out.
- What? Why?
- Uh, let's see.
We got her on the hook
with a children's charity,
And now it's all over the news
that you abandoned your kid.
- He's not mine. - Hey, i was on
that trip with you in paris.
I remember you drooling
all over his mother.
- "Yeah, i'm gonna go bang the hand
model!" - That's very classy, daniel.
We need to do
some major damage control here.
I need you
to keep a low profile.
We're gonna tell madelon
- That you're taking a
leave of absence.
- Alexis.
- Mom, stay out of this.
- I can't believe you.
When an advertiser
threatened to pull out
Because you became a woman,
i stood by you.
- We almost lost this magazine. - Then i
guess i'm learning from your mistakes.
You slicing ham with those pants?
What?
Papi, that crease
cannot get any sharper.
She's behaving like a child.
She's trying
to figure out what to do with her life.
She's too young
to know what to do.
Is this really
about how old she is,
Or you not being ready
to lose her?
Look, i know how difficult
it is to find love.
And when you find someone, you
gotta seize that opportunity.
You can't just sit around
And act like it's gonna be there
the next day,
Because sometimes-Boom!
It's gone.
And then you have nothing.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
Where you going?
I'm gonna seize
my opportunity.
Oh, god. Daniel, i just heard
about this leave of absence.
What does that mean?
It means nothing.
A couple of weeks.
Good time for you to take
a vacation.
Are you okay?
Yeah. It's daniel.
Look, daniel,
It's gonna take a couple weeks
for the results to get back.
- So i mean, until then
- Betty, i don't need to take a paternity test to know.
I'm his father.
This is a letter daniel's mother
wrote to him before she died.
I had it translated.
She wanted him to know
who his father is
And if anything happened to her,
to come find me.
What am i gonna do?
Daniel, you always complained
About how cold and distant
your father was.
You don't have to be that.
You can be there for your son.
And he just lost his mom,
so he really needs you.
Betty.
Thanks.
And in case you thought
i'd forgotten about rome,
Here is an all-Expense-Paid trip
for you and gio.
First-Class tickets,
five-Star hotels, the works.
Oh, god.
Oh, god. Oh, god.
Is that a good "oh, god"
or a bad "oh, god"?
Oh, i'm sorry, daniel.
I'm so sorry.
It's just that
henry showed up last night,
And he asked me to marry him
and move to tucson.
Betty, that's...
Uh, how-How is that?
I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.
What do i do?
I- I'm the last person you should
ask for relationship advice.
I know.
But you're my friend,
and i need to know.
I think you should go to rome.
Because i shouldn't
be with henry?
No, because i can't imagine
being here without you.
I'm a little biased. Sorry.
So what are you gonna do?
No, no, no.
Thank you
for being so understanding.
Bedankt vaarwel.
Is everything okay?
That was madelon de bie. It took
a lot of finessing on my part,
But she's finally
back on board
Now that daniel's
taken a step back.
Thank you, wilhelmina.
Oh, of course.
It's absolutely fine-
Me taking care of everything
While, uh, daniel's off
dealing with his little bastard.
I understand now
more than anything
The importance of family.
But to be honest,
It's just been a lot easier
Getting things done around here
by myself.
What are you saying?
It's just-Alexis,
you and i-We had a plan.
We were gonna take over
the company together.
And, of course, i understand
why you turned on me.
You chose your brother.
But you're in charge now.
You need to do what's best
for the magazine.
And that would be
getting rid of daniel?
Well, that's a little harsh.
Just think of it more
as a...
A reassignment to another
position in the meade empire
That might be a better fit.
If there's
one thing i've learned,
Family will always be there,
alexis.
But with daniel running things,
i'm not sure "mode" will.
Hello, mr. Meade.
Thank you for coming.
It's nice to meet you.
Here is daniél's passport
and his document.
I can trust you will
take good care of him?
Betty?
Dad.
I wanted to talk to you.
Oh, my god.
It's gorgeous!
It's dominican amber.
A fine gem
for another fine gem.
Oh, i love it.
I love it. Thank you.
Yeah, i was gonna
give it to you on saturday,
But then you called,
and... well, i'm glad
Because i've been
wanting to talk to you.
You know what, coach?
I think we're done talking.
What, now you want
to take it slow?
Uh, hilda, i-I don't know
how to say this.
I'm...
Not single.
You're joking.
No, it's not like that.
Okay? We-We were separated
for a while.
W- We got back together.
We fell apart again.
It's just been so rocky.
Are you together now?
But, hilda-
Stop. Stop.
My fianc?Died a year ago.
This is the first time that
i have opened up to someone,
And you're telling me that you're married?
I didn't know this was gonna happen.
This is the story of my life.
Hilda, i just wanted you to know
Because i feel
like i'm falling for you.
Oh, here it is.
Le building de empire state.
It's a, um,
really big building.
Grand. Yeah?
Oul.
And over here...
oh, there's central park.
Oh, and over here we ha-
Oh, there's someone having
a little fun in the window.
Put that away for now.
Um, so do you like
to go to the movies?
You know, movies...
le cinema?
Ah, oul.
I like, uh, johnny depp,
"Matrix," "transformers."
Yeah.
Uh, shia labeouf, no good.
No.
Megan fox, hot. Super.
Hot chicks.
I know where you get that from.
Give me five. Yeah!
Good. We're getting somewhere.
Um, how about sports?
Do you like any?
Um, soccer?
Sorry. Uh, football?
Uh, no, no.
Uh, um, baseball.
Hey, this is
your first halloween.
Aw. Why am i wearing pearls
and lace gloves?
You were baby madonna.
It was your sister's idea.
Oh, i didn't know you and mom
went to the grand canyon.
It's a photo booth
in coney island.
Your mother always dreamed
about going there,
But she never got the chance.
This is us at the community pool
one summer.
It's what i wanted
to show you.
You wanted to jump off
the high board,
And i wouldn't let you,
and you got so mad.
And then i turn around
And there you were,
standing at the edge.
I think i remember that.
I was so scared.
You were,
but then you jumped.
And it was okay.
I wanted to protect you,
But you knew what you wanted
to do, and you did it.
Dad, i don't know
what i want this time.
Amor.
What do i do?
I can't tell you that, mija.
I can tell you
that i love you,
That i'll support you
either way.
But this is your decision,
betty.
You can't listen
to anyone else.
You just need
to search deep inside,
And then take a deep breath...
And jump.
It's the athletic event
of the fashion season,
The only athletic event
of the fashion season-
The "mode" versus "elle"
charity softball game.
Who will win? Who cares?
It's about who's wearing what,
and more importantly,
Who will naomi campbell smash
in the head with a baseball bat?
Hey! I just want
to reach out to all my fans
Who've been missing me
and facebooking me.
I hear you,
and i miss you, too,
And i'm gonna be back
with a new single
Or reality show or a sex video
very, very soon.
I love you!
We love you.
Go, mode!
Whoo! Go, mode!
Who is that?
-* i should have seen the signs *
- Daniel.
Oh, you brought daniel jr.
Well, he likes baseball,
and he likes models,
I thought, why not?
Naomi campbell, uh, très sexy.
Mm. My french is actually
getting better. I understood him.
Well, i think it's really great
that you guys are-
Oh, um, i'll see you guys out
on the field, okay? All right.
Sometimes
she's a little weird. Sorry.
Is, uh, marc?
Très drôle.
"M-O-D-E."
Uh, funny.
You know marc?
How...
Ready?
Okay.
We're "mode." We're cool.
We'll take your team to school.
You're "elle." You smell.
Your team can go to...
Hell.
Go, "mode"!
Whoo! Go, "mode"!
Whoo! Was that as good as
it felt?
It felt really good.
Oh, i just wish
we could get higher.
I know. We need something solid
that we can jump onto.
We need, like, a bench or a trunk or something.
Betty, perfect timing. We have to jump on you.
I don't have time for this.
Oh!
Oh, my god.
Show some team spirit.
Guys, you can't just jump
on people. It's rude.
Am i crazy, or are...
you avoiding me?
Why would you say that? Well,
because you just looked at me and ran.
Betty, if you don't want
to go to rome with me,
Just-Just tell me.
Gio, i do, but-
Betty!
Henry.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
"Mode" needed more guys on the team, so i volunteered.
I volunteered, too.
I thought it'd be a fun thing
For me and betty to do
before we go to rome.
Rome?
Yeah.
I just asked betty
to marry me.
What?
Wha-
"Modies" take the field.
Play ball, bitches!
Betty!
Time for the opening pitch.
Daniel meade, editor-In-Chief
for "mode" magazine,
Is on the mound.
Daniel meade?
Hello?
You had him
pick through that garbage.
You leaked the video to the press.
Oops. Busted.
Take a look around, wilhelmina.
You see these people?
That's my team, my magazine.
Stop trying to push me out.
Oh, trying?
Daniel, darling, it's done.
Your sister
already pushed you out.
No, she asked me
to keep a low profile
Until we got
the madelon de bie account back.
Oh, so you don't know?
There's no longer
a low profile.
It's no profile.
Mm.
You're no longer
editor-In-Chief of "mode."
I am.
Hello? "Mode," who's pitching?
I'll pitch.
It appears we have a last-Minute
change on the roster.
Wilhelmina slater
will be pitching for "mode."
And first up to bat
for "elle" magazine-
Joe zee.
Strike three!
I must have been distracted
by how fat you look in white.
Oh, no, she di'int!
Next.
How could you do this to me?
It's what's best for the company.
A company i'm still
a third owner of.
We'll find something else
for you to do,
But "mode" just isn't it.
And next up for "elle,"
robbie myers.
Nice try, robbie.
Bite this.
Love you, too, dear. Next!
Nice catch, willie.
Way to handle a ball.
Next up,
The most infamous member
of the supermodel trinity-
The ferocious and fierce
naomi campbell.
* get up out of your seat *
* your seat *
* come on
up to the dance floor *
* i've got something so sweet *
* i'll be your one stop *
* one stop *
* candy shop *
* everything *
* that i got *
Don't worry, darling.
I wield this bat with love.
Oh, god.
Bono!
Not now, darling.
I'm playing cricket.
Okay.
Give it to me, mama.
I'm gonna give it to you.
I got it!
Good morning,
mrs. Grubstick.
I made you breakfast in bed.
Blue corn pancakes
with prickly pear syrup-
Tucson specialty.
Thank you, henry.
Mm-Hmm. How'd you sleep?
Well, i had this dream.
It was so vivid.
It was about the softball game.
Oh, you mean
the best softball game ever?
Yes, the day i decided
to marry you.
Aren't you glad you made
the right choice? Mm...
Hey.
Yes.
Oh, hey, about this weekend.
I thought maybe you,
me and little nate
Could take a road trip
down to the coolidge dam.
You're never too young
to start learning
About hydroelectric power. Oh, henry, my
article's due this weekend. I'll be working.
Oh.
Unless i start right now,
and i finish it all today.
Oh, by the way, did you pick up
that dandruff sham...
...poo?
Okay, i have got
to comp daniel sandwiches
For the rest of his life!
This is the nicest hotel room
i've ever stayed in.
What's wrong?
Um, nothing. Nothing.
I... i was just having
this weird déj?Vu or something.
I was imagining my life
if i had ended up in tucson.
Ha!
Aren't you glad you didn't?
Come here.
All right, let's look
at the itinerary for today.
We're gonna hit the pantheon...
ooh.
And then the fontana di trevi,
and then we're gonna go
To this amazing bakery
in campo dei fiori.
They make an unbelievable white
pizza. Ooh. Can we go there first?
Whatever you want.
Betty.
What are you doing?
Henry?
Yeah, betty.
What are you doing?
I want an answer.
What? I need to know,
betty. Make a choice.
You can't keep me waiting
like this. Make a choice.
Make a choice. Make a choice.
Make a choice! Make a choice!
Is she all right?
I know what to do.
* there's only so much
you can learn in one place *
* the more that i wait *
* the more time that i waste *
* i haven't got
much time to waste *
* it's time to make my way *
* i'm not afraid
of what i'll face *
* but i'm afraid to stay *
* i'm going down my own road,
and i can make it alone *
* i'll work and i'll fight *
* till i find
a place of my own *
* are you ready to jump? *
* get ready to jump *
* don't ever look back,
oh, baby *
* yes, i'm ready to jump *
* just take my hands *
* get ready to jump *
* we learned our lesson
from the start *
* my sisters and me *
* the only thing
you can depend on *
* is your family *
* life's gonna drop you down *
* like the limbs of a tree *
* it sways and it swings *
* and it bends
until it makes you see *
* are you ready to jump? *
* get ready to jump *
* don't ever look back,
oh, baby *
* yes, i'm ready to jump *
* just take my hands *
* get ready to *
* are you ready? *
* i'll work and i'll fight *
* till i find
a place of my own *
* it sways and it swings *
* and it bends
until you make it your own *
* i can make it alone *
* i'm ready to jump *
* just take my hands *
* get ready to *
* are you ready? *
united we're strong!
»¶ó­²îóëãà¾çéççøêâôöáªºïòåâô »î¶¯
¾ßìå»î¶¯ïêçéçë²î¼ûææàãðü¹ùíø