HER NAME IS JODIE PAPADAKIS,
AND SHE'S MY IDOL.
I'VE BEEN FOLLOWING HER CAREER,
LIKE, FOREVER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I FINALLY GET TO MEET HER.
WHEN I FOUND OUT THAT SHE WAS
RUNNING THE Y.E.T.I. PROGRAM,
I SCREAMED.
AAH!
I SHOULD PROBABLY BUY
MRS. BOWEN A GIFT.
OKAY, LESS TALKING, MORE TAPING. HELLO.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I SET THIS PARTY FOR FRIDAY.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO GET
ALL OF THIS DONE IN THREE DAYS?
THAT'S WHAT YOUR FAMILY
IS FOR. DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL GET IT DONE. OH, DID I
TELL YOU THAT SHE STARTED OUT
AS A JUNIOR ASSISTANT
AT "THE NEW YORK OBSERVER"?
FIVE YEARS, SHE BECAME
THE EDITOR-IN-CHIEF.
SHE'S A GENIUS. WOW. AND
YOU CHOSE US OVER HER?
NO, TONIGHT'S JUST A MIXER.
I GET TO SEE HER TOMORROW.
OH, BETTY, WHAT DO YOU THINK
IF, FOR THE REOPENING,
I HIRE SOMEONE TO DO MUSIC OR MAGIC OR SOMETHING
- MA, NO MAGIC.
I TRY SO HARD TO GET THE BRIDGE
AND TUNNEL OUT OF THIS FAMILY.
WOULD IT BE TOO WEIRD TO ASK HER
TO BE MY MENTOR RIGHT AWAY?
BETTY, YOUR SISTER JUST ASKED
YOU A QUESTION. YEAH. HELLO?
OH, RIGHT. YES.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
WOULD BE FUN? GIFT BAGS.
I CAN'T AFFORD GIFT BAGS.
I SPENT ALL MY MONEY
ON THIS BEAUTIFUL SIGN
AND THIS NEW MERCH.
THAT'S SHORT FOR "MERCHANDISE."
HILDA,
IT WON'T COST YOU A THING.
"MODE" GETS SAMPLES
ALL THE TIME.
I CAN JUST BRING SOME HOME
TOMORROW. HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
OH!
HILDA'S BEAUTILITIES PLUS. OH,
MY GOD! THIS IS SO EXCITING.
THIS PARTY IS GONNA BE LIKE
MY VERY OWN BROADWAY OPENING.
YEAH, IT'S LIKE
"SPRING AWAKENING," "AVENUE Q."
AND "SOUTH PACIFIC"
ALL ROLLED INTO ONE.
GRANDPA, NICE.
HEY, I KEEP UP.
HEY, SHOULDN'T THAT
FACE OUTWARD?
PAPI.
AY, DIOS MO.
I WASN'T DONE.
THERE IS
NO OTHER WAY TO SPIN IT.
"ELLE" KICKED OUR BUTTS
LAST MONTH.
WAS IT CLASSY TO SHOW
SARAH SILVERMAN ON THE TOILET?
NO. BUT THEIR NUMBERS WERE
WAY UP, AND A WIN IS A WIN.
SO TRASHY. THAT NEVER WOULD HAVE
HAPPENED AT "ELLE" ON MY WATCH.
WEREN'T YOU AN INTERN?
SHUT UP.
GUYS. ANYWAY, WE ARE
NOT GONNA LOSE AGAIN.
IF WE DO, ONE OF YOU DIES.
I HAVE SOMETHING BIG
PLANNED FOR APRIL.
I CAN'T TALK ABOUT IT JUST YET. TREAT
EVERYTHING WE DISCUSS IN HERE AS PROPRIETARY.
THOSE COWS AT "ELLE" WOULD LOVE TO
KNOW WHAT WE'RE UP TO. ON THE FLIP SIDE,
IF ANY OF YOU HEAR ANYTHING
ABOUT THEM,
THERE IS A VERY NICE
BOTTLE OF WINE IN IT FOR YOU.
AND MAYBE YOU'LL LIVE
TO SEE ANOTHER DAY.
NOW GET BACK TO WORK.
I LOVE THE WHOLE
GOOD COP/BAD COP THING
YOU TWO HAVE GOING.
AH, IT'S NOT REALLY A THING.
IT'S MORE LIKE I'M NICE,
SHE'S NOT.
MM. CAN I HELP IT IF MY BALLS ARE BIGGER
THAN HIS? GOD, I LOVE E THIS WOMAN.
YEAH.
WILL I SEE YOU AT MY PARTY
ON FRIDAY?
I BUMPED GRAYDON CARTER FOR YOU.
I WOULDN'T MISS IT FOR THE WORLD.
MOLLY HAS A SCHOOL PAGEANT
THAT NIGHT,
BUT I PLAN
ON TALKING HER OUT OF IT.
OH, MOLLY'S COMING?
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
WELL, OF COURSE.
SHE'S YOUR FIANCE.
I GUESS I'LL JUST HAVE TO BUMP
ANNA WINTOUR OFF THE GUEST LIST,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
SERVES HER RIGHT.
I THINK SHE STOLE A PAIR OF
SUNGLASSES FROM ME LAST YEAR.
GOOD.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
THIS IS THE RECENTLY UNEARTHED
HALSTON ORIGINAL
FROM THE FIREWORKS COLLECTION.
WOW. THAT IS INCREDIBLE.
I FOUND
THIS PRIVATE COLLECTOR
WHO'S GONNA LOAN IT TO US
FOR ONE SHOOT.
KEIRA KNIGHTLEY
WILL DO OUR COVER
IF SHE CAN WEAR THIS DRESS.
SHUT UP!
I MEAN, ON THAT COVER ALONE,
WE GOT 30 MORE PAGES OF AD BUYS.
THIS COULD REALLY BE A BIG GAME
CHANGER FOR US. SUCK ON THAT, "ELLE."
* GO, DANIEL, GO, DANIEL
WE TALKED ABOUT THAT.
I...
I NEED YOU TO ARRANGE
TO PICK THIS UP FROM
THE COLLECTOR'S LOFT TOMORROW.
HERE'S THE INFO. PLEASE, BETTY,
KEEP IT HUSH-HUSH.
I FEEL LIKE
AN INTERNATIONAL SPY.
EXCEPT REAL SPIES
DON'T ANNOUNCE THEY'RE SPIES.
DANIEL, WOULD YOU MIND
STEPPING INTO MY OFFICE?
I'D LIKE TO SHOW YOU
SOMETHING.
I HAVE SOME FRIENDS
HERE IN SECURITY.
I DIDN'T REALIZE YOU AND MOLLY
WERE SO CLOSE.
YOU'RE AWFUL.
PERHAPS IN THE PAST,
BUT NOT THIS TIME.
LOOK, THIS IS THE ONLY COPY.
IT'S YOURS.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
NOTHING.
THIS IS A PERSONAL MATTER.
I UNDERSTAND.
SHE'S ENGAGED TO YOUR FRIEND,
OUR-OUR COLLEAGUE.
LOOK, I'M SURE
YOU PROBABLY DON'T WANT
TO TALK TO ME ABOUT THIS,
BUT SOME THINGS
ARE WORTH THE RISK.
WE BOTH KNOW HOW HARD IT IS
TO FIND LOVE.
IT'S-IT'S NOT LOVE.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS
OR HOW SHE FEELS.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
AND IT LOOKS LIKE MOLLY
MIGHT BE ON THE SAME PAGE.
DON'T YOU THINK
YOU OWE IT TO YOURSELF
TO SEE WHETHER
THERE'S ANYTHING THERE?
YOU GAVE HIM THE DVD?
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON
WITH YOU, WOMAN?
AND DON'T SAY, "NOT
EVERYTHING'S A SCHEME, MARC,"
BECAUSE I WILL SLAP YOU.
NOT EVERYTHING IS A SCHEME,
MARC.
OKAY, I THINK WE BOTH KNOW THAT I'M NOT GOING
TO SLAP YOU. SOMETIMES HONESTY WORKS, TOO.
OH, I GET IT.
SO HONESTY'S THE SCHEME.
THE OLD HONESTY SCHEME.
YEAH! THAT'S A CLASSIC.
NO, NO, NO. THIS IS
ONE OF THOSE RARE TIMES
WHERE WHAT DANIEL WANTS
AND WHAT I WANT INTERSECT.
NOW IF DANIEL AND MOLLY
END UP TOGETHER,
WHERE DOES THAT LEAVE...
CONNOR?
HEARTBROKEN.
AND THEN YOU'LL BE THERE
TO PICK UP THE PIECES.
YOU KNOW ME.
I'M VERY NURTURING.
YEAH, VERY NUR-
VERY, VERY NURTURING.
CHRISTINA.
"BETTY SUAREZ,
YOUNG EDITOR IN TRAINING." OH.
THIS IS SO SWEET.
OH, I WANTED YOU TO HAVE
SOMETHING SPECIAL
FOR YOUR FIRST DAY.
JUST DON'T YOU FORGET ABOUT ME
WHEN YOU'RE A BIG STAR
AND I'M STILL STUCK HERE
IN MY TAILOR'S DUNGEON.
ALL RIGHT, I KNOW WHEN YOU'RE
FEELING SORRY FOR YOURSELF.
WELL, I'VE BEEN RELINING
WILHELMINA'S DRESS
FOR HER SUPER ELITE
COCKTAIL PARTY,
EVEN THOUGH THE OLD ONE WAS
PERFECTLY GOOD.
AND ALL THIS EXTRA BENDING
DOWN'S MAKING ME FEEL DIZZY
BECAUSE I'M CARRYING
HER LITTLE RODENT,
WHICH SEEMS TO BE
KICKING ME IN THE GUT
EVERY FIVE SECONDS TODAY.
AND THE INTERNET HAS GONE DOWN.
SORRY.
IT'S ALL MY HORMONES.
JUST...
OKAY. ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
HEY, HEY. YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD
CHEER YOU UP? WHAT? WHAT? WHAT?
COME TO HILDA'S.
SHE'S HAVING THIS HUGE REOPENING
OF HER SALON. IT'LL BE FUN.
YEAH, THAT DOES SOUND LIKE FUN.
I LIKE YOUR SISTER.
SHE SAYS WHAT'S ON HER MIND,
AYE? AND SHE DRINKS.
I USED TO DRINK.
OH, CHRISTINA, ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY?
NO, I'M FINE. I D-
I DO THIS ALL DAY LONG.
OH. OOH.
NOW GO. GO!
ARE YOU SURE?
I'M POSITIVE. GO. GO.
UH, OKAY, BUT YOU'LL CALL ME
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING?
YES! NOW GO AND HURRY UP.
I KNOW YOU'RE REALLY EXCITED
ABOUT THIS.
I AM. I AM SO EXCITED.
CHRISTINA, THIS COULD BE
THE BEGINNING
OF THE REST OF MY LIFE.
WELCOME TO THE FUNERAL.
THE MAGAZINE BUSINESS IS DYING.
DYING.
DOES THAT
FRIGHTEN YOU? IT SHOULD.
IT SCARES THE HELL OUT OF ME.
SO... WHAT DO YOU DO?
DO YOU GIVE UP
OR DO YOU TOUGHEN UP?
WHEN I ARRIVED IN NEW YORK
WITH MY CURLY HAIR
AND THIS VOICE,
DO YOU THINK
ANYONE TOOK ME SERIOUSLY?
NO.
THEY MOCKED ME.
SO FROM THEN ON...
I LOVE HER.
DID YOU EAT ONIONS FOR LUNCH? I MADE DAMN SURE
- DO I HEAR TALKING?
HOW CAN THAT POSSIBLY BE?
I'M TALKING.
GOOD. THANK YOU.
NOW LET'S GET STARTED.
UH, MARC ST. JAMES,
RAISE YOUR HAND.
TELL ME THE NAME AND MAGAZINE
OF FIVE OF THE PEOPLE
IN THIS ROOM. GO.
UH... HEATHER JACKSON,
"GOURMET,"
TOM BUCKLEY,
"SPORTS ILLUSTRATED,"
ERIC WEST, "HARPER'S,"
UH, EVIE F-FOSTER, "OUT"
AND RITA THOMPSON,
"ROLLING STONE."
EXCELLENT.
BETTY SUAREZ.
YES.
FIVE PEOPLE-NAME AND MAGAZINE.
UM... WELL, I KNOW MARC.
HE WORKS WITH ME AT "MODE."
HI, MARC.
WHO ARE YOU?
HE'S JUST KIDDING. DIDN'T
YOU MEET ANYONE AT THE MIXER?
OH, I WASN'T AT THE MIXER.
I HAD A FAMILY OBLIGATION.
AND SINCE IT WAS JUST CASUAL,
I SKIPPED IT.
WHO ELSE MISSED THE EVENT
LAST NIGHT?
ANYONE ELSE HAVE A FAMILY
OBLIGATION, A SICK HAMSTER?
NO?
GOOD. BECAUSE LAST NIGHT
WASN'T CASUAL.
LAST NIGHT WAS AN OPPORTUNITY
FOR YOU TO LEARN SOMETHING
ABOUT YOUR FUTURE COLLEAGUES,
BUT I GUESS THAT WASN'T
IMPORTANT TO MS. SUAREZ.
IT IS.
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT TO ME.
CAN I CHANGE SEATS?
NO. FIRST ASSIGNMENT-
CONTACTS-
BY THIS TIME NEXT WEEK,
I WANT EVERYONE IN HERE
TO HAVE 40 NEW ONES.
AND FAMILY DOESN'T COUNT.
YOU HAVE TO MAKE
A LOT OF TOUGH CHOICES
IN THIS BUSINESS.
IF YOU CAN'T DO THAT,
THEN DON'T PLAN ON COMING BACK.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
丑女贝蒂 第三季 第11集
-==破烂熊字幕组==-
翻译：个人ID
校对：个人ID
时间轴：卢 斌
HOLD THE LIFT.
OH.
THANKS, BETTY.
YOU'RE DOING Y.E.T.I.
HUH? OH, UH, YEAH.
MY FRIEND JODIE'S
RUNNING THAT THIS YEAR.
SHE'S REALLY TERRIFIC.
YEAH. YEAH, SHE'S, UH, GREAT.
SHE CAN BE PRETTY TOUGH,
THOUGH.
YEAH, WELL...
SHE WAS A LITTLE UNFAIR TO ME...
YESTERDAY, 'CAUSE,
YOU KNOW, I SHOWED UP
TO CLASS COMPLETELY PREPARED,
AND THEN SHE CALLED ME OUT
'CAUSE I DIDN'T GO
TO SOME SILLY NETWORKING THING.
WELL, NETWORKING IS
ONE OF THOSE ANNOYING THINGS,
BUT IF YOU'RE SERIOUS
ABOUT YOUR CAREER,
IT'S SOMETHING YOU HAVE TO DO.
WELL, I HAD A FAMILY THING,
YOU KNOW?
I COULDN'T DISAPPOINT THEM.
I CANNOT TELL YOU
HOW MANY THINGS I'VE HAD TO MISS
BECAUSE OF MY JOB.
YOU JUST ASK MOLLY.
YEAH, WELL,
IT MIGHT NOT MATTER ANYWAY.
SHE TOLD ME
THAT IF I CAN'T GET
40 NEW CONTACTS
BY NEXT CLASS,
NOT TO COME BACK.
ALL RIGHT, BETTY,
YOU DO WHAT I DID
WHEN I WAS YOUR AGE.
YOU FIND SOMEBODY
WHO'S REALLY GOOD
AT THE SUPERFICIAL STUFF
AND YOU DO WHAT THEY DO.
MY ANSWER IS NUH-OH.
OH, MARC, COME ON. PLEASE.
I'M SO DESPERATE.
OKAY. GIVE ME ONE GOOD REASON
WHY I SHOULD DO THIS.
UM, WELL, MAYBE BECAUSE
IF I HADN'T STEPPED ASIDE,
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE GOTTEN
INTO Y.E.T.I. TO BEGIN WITH.
OH-HO! YOU'RE GONNA BRING UP
THAT OLD CHESTNUT AGAIN. FINE.
YOU DO NOT GET
TO PLAY THIS CARD AGAIN. OKAY?
MEET ME AND AMANDA AFTER WORK.
WE'LL TAKE YOU TO SWILL.
EVERYONE YOU NEED TO MEET
WILL BE THERE.
GREAT. OH, WAIT.
NO, MARC, I CAN'T DO THAT.
I PROMISED MY SISTER I'D HELP
- BUP, BUP, BUP, BUP, BUP. DON'T CARE.
YOU GOT ME TONIGHT
OR NOT AT ALL.
HILDA, HI.
LOOK, I'M SO SORRY,
BUT I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO HELP OUT TONIGHT.
OH, BETTY, WE WERE SUPPOSED
TO DO THESE GIFT BAGS TOGETHER.
I KNOW, AND-AND WE STILL ARE,
JUST TOMORROW.
SEE, IF I DON'T DO
THIS Y.E.T.I. THING TONIGHT,
THEY'RE GONNA KICK ME OUT.
FINE. I GET IT.
WE'LL DO IT TOMORROW. BYE.
BYE.
SWEETIE...
IF BETTY HAD A CHOICE,
YOU KNOW SHE'D BE HERE.
YEAH.
COME ON. WE GOT WORK TO DO.
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
UH, EXCUSE ME A SECOND. MOLLY.
DANIEL.
HEY.
HI.
SO DID THE DRESS WORK OUT?
OH, YEAH. IT WAS GREAT.
YOU KNOW, IT WAS VERY,
UH, GLAMOROUS.
ACTUALLY, I JUST CAME
TO RETURN IT, SO...
UM...
ALL RIGHT. UM, AWESOME.
YOU KNOW, I-
DANIEL, CAN WE-
I... NO, YOU GO.
GO AHEAD.
UH...
WE JUST-WE NEVER...
GOT A CHANCE
TO TALK ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED,
YOU KNOW, IN THE CLOSET.
YEAH.
I JUST-I WANTED
TO TELL YOU THAT-
HEY, BABE.
HEY.
READY FOR LUNCH?
MM-HMM.
THANKS FOR KEEPING HER COMPANY,
MATE.
BYE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU KNOW, I-I'VE BEEN
WITH A MILLION WOMEN.
EVERY TIME I'M AROUND HER,
IT'S LIKE...
I JUST ACT LIKE
A STUPID TEENAGER.
BECAUSE YOU CARE FOR HER.
GOD, I'M SUCH AN IDIOT.
YES, BUT YOU'RE ALSO HUMAN.
YOU KNOW,
I- I SWEAR MOLLY WAS
JUST ABOUT TO SAY
SOMETHING IMPORTANT,
AND, OF COURSE, THAT'S WHEN
CONNOR CAME UP AND KISSED HER.
WELL, MAYBE "MODE'S" NOT
THE PLACE FOR THAT CONVERSATION.
YEAH,
BUT WHAT CHOICE I HAVE?
WELL, YOU'RE BOTH COMING
TO MY PARTY ON FRIDAY.
KNOWING CONNOR,
HE'LL BE WORKING THE ROOM.
IT'S AN OPPORTUNITY FOR YOU
TO FINISH YOUR CONVERSATION,
UNINTERRUPTED.
HMM.
HERE'S MY CARD. M-MAYBE
WE'LL DO BUSINESS SOMEDAY.
UH, "THE GORGEOUS GOURMET"-
THAT IS CATCHY.
OH.
HERE'S MINE.
THANKS.
ALL RIGHT, TALK TO YOU LATER.
OKAY.
WELL? THAT WASN'T SO-
TERRIBLE.
HORRIBLE.
COULD NOT HAVE GONE WORSE.
YOU SPENT
22 MINUTES AND 47 SECONDS
TALKING TO A CATERER.
A CATERER.
A CATERER!
HE WAS INTERESTING.
USELESS!
THE POINT OF NETWORKING
IS TO GATHER INFORMATION
TO ADVANCE YOUR CAREER.
WATCH AND LEARN.
STEP ONE-FORGE A BOND...
YOUR NAME, WHERE YOU WORK
AND ONE MEMORABLE FACT.
I'M MARC ST. JAMES.
I WORK FOR WILHELMINA SLATER.
I ONCE HAD A THREESOME
WITH JON HAMM AND MIA HAMM.
I CALLED IT
THE NIGHT OF THE HAMM SANDWICH.
WELL, THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
IT'S MEMORABLE.
BUT IT'S A LIE.
OR IS IT?
IT IS.
STEP TWO-
GATHERING INFORMATION...
IN ORDER TO GET INFO, YOU'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO GIVE INFO.
DO YOU KNOW WHY HEIDI KLUM
NEVER WEARS OPEN-TOED SHOES?
THE TRICK IS
TO MAKE IT SOUND JUICY
BUT REALLY MEAN NOTHING.
12 LITTLE PIGGIES.
OH, YEAH. IT'S DISGUSTING.
I'M NOT EVEN KIDDING
ABOUT THAT.
SO WHAT WERE YOU SAYING ABOUT
NEXT MONTH'S COVER MODEL?
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY,
STEP THREE-THE EXIT STRATEGY.
GET IN, GET INFO, GET OUT.
SEE,
I- I DON'T LIKE TO BE RUDE.
I MEAN, HOW DO YOU
JUST STOP SOMEONE
IN THE MIDDLE OF A CONVERSATION WITHOUT HURTING THEIR
- OH.
BETTY, COULD YOU
JUST HOLD ON ONE SEC?
* WE'VE GOT WORK TO DO
OH. OKAY, I GET IT.
OKAY, AMANDA, I GET IT.
AMANDA?
SHE'S NOT COMING BACK,
AND NEITHER AM I. I'VE GIVEN YOU
ALL I HAVE TO GIVE.
NO, MARC, DON'T GO.
I'M NOT READY.
YES, YOU ARE.
YOU'RE A MEAN, NOT-SO-LEAN,
CONTACT-GETTIN' MACHINE.
YOU'RE THE TERMINATOR.
YOU'RE THE BETTY-NATOR.
GO GET 'EM.
OKAY, MEMORABLE FACT.
I KNOW A MURDERER.
THANK YOU.
HERE'S MINE.
GIVE INFO THAT SOUNDS JUICY
BUT MEANS NOTHING.
OH, WE TOTALLY HIRED THAT WRITER
TO GO TO MILAN.
JUST FYI, HE HAS
A PAY-PER-VIEW PROBLEM.
PORN.
AND WHAT DESIGNER DID YOU SAY
YOU'LL BE FEATURING THIS MONTH?
THAT IS VERY INTERESTING.
GET INFO, GET OUT.
OH. ACTUALLY, COULD YOU
EXCUSE ME JUST ONE SECOND?
YOU WERE VERY INTERESTING.
37, 38, 39.
SHOOT. ONE MORE.
HI. BETTY SUAREZ.
YOU ARE?
EXHAUSTED. I HATE NETWORKING.
OH, MY GOD. ME, TOO.
I DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS OKAY
TO ADMIT THAT.
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN,
THE NETWORKING POLICE ARE
GONNA COME AND ARREST US?
YEAH, AND, LIKE, CHARGE US
WITH "FAILURE TO CHITCHAT"?
I JUST DON'T SEE
HOW KNOWING THAT
THAT GUY IS INTO S&M
IS GOING TO HELP MY CAREER.
ESPECIALLY BECAUSE THAT GUY
ISN'T IN PUBLISHING.
HE'S A DENTIST.
EW.
I'M TERI, AND I'M NOT
DOING THIS TO NETWORK.
YOU JUST SEEM REALLY NICE.
OH.
THANKS.
"ELLE."
"MODE," "ELLE."
HERE WE GO.
I SUPPOSE WE SHOULD BE
USING EACH OTHER
TO GET INFORMATION.
YEAH. NO.
I MEAN, WE COULD JUST TALK,
YOU KNOW, LIKE, UH, HUMANS.
BLUE BRACES. BOLD.
I LIKE YOUR PINK STRIPE.
IT'S COOL.
THANKS.
I MEAN, IT WAS 20 MINUTES.
THAT'S NOT TOO LONG TO SPEND
ON A CATERER, RIGHT?
HELL, NO. PLUS,
GORGEOUS GOURMET TOTALLY ROCKS.
THEY'RE DOING OUR HOLIDAY PARTY
THIS YEAR.
OH... NO.
UH, I'M GONNA GO
CLEAN THAT UP.
THIS ISN'T MY EXIT STRATEGY,
BY THE WAY.
DIDN'T THINK IT WAS. YOU KNOW,
AFTER ALL THIS FAKE NETWORKING,
IT'S NICE TO MEET SOMEONE
IN THE MAGAZINE INDUSTRY
WHO'S REAL.
YEAH. SAME HERE.
I'LL BE BACK.
HOLD THE PRESSES!
I LOVE YOUR ENERGY, BETTY,
BUT NOW IS NOT THE TIME.
I JUST FOUND OUT "ELLE" IS
DOING THEIR CENTER SPREAD
IN THE VENICE CANALS,
JUST LIKE WE WERE.
SO BACK TO THE DRAWING BOARD.
I KNOW. I HEARD. BUT GET THIS-
"ELLE" BOOKED JESSICA STAM
FOR THEIR COVER SHOOT.
SHE JUST BROKE UP
WITH HER ITALIAN BOYFRIEND
AND REFUSES TO GO TO ITALY,
SO THEY'RE MOVING THE WHOLE SHOOT TO
PARIS. SO VENICE IS BACK ON. NICE WORK!
YOU JUST EARNED YOURSELF
A BOTTLE OF WINE.
WHOO-HOO! I GUESS I'LL BE PICKING THAT UP FOR
MYSELF? UH, YES, BUT I WILL BE VERY GENEROUS.
HMM. THANK YOU. YOU KNOW,
THIS WHOLE NETWORKING THING
IS REALLY PAYING OFF FOR ME.
THE ONLY WAY I KNEW
ABOUT JESSICA STAM IS TERI,
MY NEW BUSINESS CONTACT
WHO WORKS AT "ELLE."
I MET HER LAST NIGHT. SHE GAVE ME THE WHOLE INSIDE
SCOOP. YEAH? WHAT DID YOU HAVE TO GIVE UP FOR THAT, HMM?
THAT PETER FRANCIS IS
HANDS-Y WITH THE MODELS.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT. I KNOW. OH, HEY,
DANIEL, IF IT'S NOT TOO MUCH TROUBLE,
I WAS WONDERING IF I COULD
JUST CUT OUT EARLY TONIGHT.
MY SISTER'S GOT A THING. UH,
ACTUALLY, THERE IS SOMETHING.
UH, I DON'T MEAN
TO SOUND NEUROTIC,
BUT IT WOULD BE REALLY GREAT
IF YOU PICKED UP
THE HALSTON DRESS
RATHER THAN SENDING A MESSENGER.
IT'S GONNA BE READY AT 5:00. OH. UM...
IS THAT A PROBLEM?
NO.
NO PROBLEM.
PAPI, THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR PICKING UP THESE SAMPLES.
TELL HILDA I WILL BEHE
AS SOON AS I CAN.
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU CAN'T HAVE SOMEONE ELSE
DO THIS SUPER SECRET TASK.
BECAUSE DANIEL ONLY TRUSTS ME
TO DO IT, AND, DAD,
I SWEAR, IF IT WASN'T IMPORTANT,
I WOULDN'T BE DOING IT.
WELL, YOUR SISTER WAS
COUNTING ON YOU.
YOU KNOW, THE LOCAL PAPER'S
COMING TO DO A FEATURE ON HER.
SHE'S A NERVOUS WRECK. OH, SHE'S GONNA
BE SO GREAT. SHE'S SO GOOD WITH PEOPLE.
HEY, LISTEN. I COULD ALWAYS
COME AROUND EARLY AND HELP,
IF YOU-IF YOU WANT. OH! CHRISTINA
WILL COME AND HELP. PERFECT.
BETTY, ARE YOU GETTING
HOW MUCH THIS RELAUNCH PARTY
MEANS TO HILDA?
SHE'S PUTTING EVERYTHING INTO IT. DAD, I GET
IT, AND I GIVE YOU MY WORD. I WILL BE THERE.
NOW I REALLY
HAVE TO GET GOING.
CHRISTINA'S GONNA HELP YOU
FINISH IN HERE,
AND I WILL SEE YOU SOON. OKAY. YEAH.
PERFECT. THANK YOU.
OH, DONE.
WOW. I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE
WHAT THIS PLACE IS
GONNA LOOK LIKE TONIGHT-
THE FOOD, THE DRINKS,
THE NEW YORK MEDIA ELITE.
IS IT AS MAGICAL
AS IT SOUNDS?
YES, YES, YES.
NOW THE WHOLE IDEA IS
TO GIVE DANIEL AND MOLLY
SOME TIME ALONE,
SO FIRST, I'LL PULL CONNOR ASIDE
TO MEET ARIANNA HUFFINGTON.
OH! OH, I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO MEET HER.
MM. WELL, STOP HINTING, MARC.
YOU'RE NOT INVITED.
NOW WHILE CONNOR IS OCCUPIED
WITH ARIANNA,
DANIEL WILL SWOOP IN,
TAKE MOLLY INTO THE BEDROOM
SO THEY CAN TALK.
JUICY COUTURE.
AND THEN YOU WALK IN WITH CONNOR
AND SEE DANIEL ON TOP OF MOLLY.
NO, NO, NO. MARC, I TOLD YOU.
THIS IS NOT A PLAN.
OKAY, I AM
JUST NOT GETTING THIS.
I- I-I-MAYBE I NEED
TO BE HERE TO SEE IT.
MAYBE NOT.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
OH, I TELL YOU, HILDA,
THIS IS A GREAT SETUP
YOU'VE GOT GOING HERE.
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN SHOP,
YOU CAN GET YOUR HAIR CUT.
THROW IN A FOOD COURT,
I WOULD NEVER LEAVE.
NO, BUT, LISTEN,
YOU MUST BE REALLY PROUD
OF YOURSELF, THOUGH.
I AM. I AM.
I'VE SCREWED UP A LOT,
AND I FINALLY FEEL LIKE
I'M GETTING MY ACT TOGETHER.
THIS IS THE BIGGEST THING
I'VE EVER DONE.
OH!
NOT THAT MY SISTER'S NOTICED.
OH, NO. I THINK SHE HAS. SHE'S
JUST BEEN REALLY BUSY LATELY.
YEAH, WELL, YOU CAN'T LIVE
YOUR WHOLE LIFE FOR WORK.
I'M REOPENING
MY SALON TONIGHT.
I STILL GOT TO JUSTIN'S SCHOOL
THIS MORNING
TO HELP WITH THE BAKE SALE.
IT'S ABOUT BALANCE.
YEAH, WELL, BALANCE IS SOMETHING
YOU LEARN WHEN YOU HAVE TO.
ANYWAY, BETTY'S
IN A DIFFERENT PLACE RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, I GUESS.
BUT WE USED TO BE SO CLOSE,
AND NOW SHE'S LIVING
IN THE CITY.
SHE'S GOT THIS WHOLE
OTHER LIFE, YOU KNOW?
SOMETIMES I JUST-
I WANT MY LITTLE SISTER BACK.
OH. YEAH, I KNOW.
OOH! OH!
CHRISTINA.
OKAY. OH, GOD.
HOW DO
YOU KNOW WHEN YOU'RE IN LABOR?
IF YOU HAVE TO ASK,
YOU'RE NOT IN LABOR.
RIGHT. OKAY.
EXCUSE ME.
AH. CH-CH.
YES? YES?
HI. UM,
I'M FROM "MODE" MAGAZINE.
I'M HERE TO PICK UP
A HALSTON DRESS FROM HIS, UM,
UH, FIREWORKS COLLECTION.
YES, YES.
SOMEONE FROM YOUR MAGAZINE
ALREADY CAME AND GOT IT.
WHAT? WHO?
BETTY SUAREZ.
OH, NO.
NO. UM, I'M BETTY SUAREZ.
NO, NO.
SHE LEFT A CARD.
AND SHE HAD A RATHER...
HORRIBLE PINK STRIPE
IN HER HAIR.
TERI.
BETTY, YOU'RE FIRED.
YOU'RE NOT FIRED. DON'T
WORRY. DON'T WORRY?
BECAUSE OF BETTY,
WE ALMOST LOST KEIRA KNIGHTLEY
AND 30 PAGES OF AD REVENUE.
I'M SORRY.
I AM SO SORRY.
AT THE CLUB, I GOT UP TO USE
THE BATHROOM, AND TERI
MUST HAVE TAKEN THE INFORMATION
FROM MY BlackBerry.
I THOUGHT THAT...
SHE WAS A FRIEND.
FRIENDSHIP IS
THE OLDEST TRICK IN THE BOOK.
OKAY, LET'S NOT PANIC YET.
"ELLE" MAY BE RIVALS OF OURS,
BUT THEY'RE ALSO
BUSINESS PEOPLE.
WE CAN MAKE THIS WORK,
RIGHT?
MARC, SET UP THE CALL.
HELLO. JOE ZEE, ROBBIE,
NICE TO SEE YOU BOTH.
THANKS FOR TAKING OUR CALL.
Anything for you, Daniel.
ROBBIE, I LOVE THE NEW DO.
All that height
really makes a statement.
Thanks, Willie.
Those earrings really make
your face look small.
Okay, so, uh, listen, guys.
We have reason to believe that one of
your assistants... Teri O'Shoughnessy...
may have taken a certain
Halston dress we have on hold.
I don't know
what they're talking about.
THAT'S HER. YOU'RE LYING, TERI, AND YOU
KNOW IT. Oh, yeah? Prove it, brace face!
YOUR PINK STRIPE IS STUPID.
OKAY. ENOUGH. ENOUGH.
OKAY.
LISTEN, LET'S CUT THE BULL.
WE ALL KNOW YOU HAVE THE DRESS.
YOU'RE HOLDING IT HOSTAGE
AND TRYING TO RUIN OUR COVER.
That's right. We heard you got
Keira Knightley for the cover.
I hope this missing dress isn't
gonna be a big problem for you.
Nice talking to you.
CONSIDER YOURSELVES DISINVITED
FROM MY COCKTAIL PARTY.
Yeah,
they weren't coming anyway.
We're having
our own party tonight.
Betty, call me.
I COULD MURDER SOMEONE
RIGHT NOW.
COME ON.
IT WAS A MISTAKE.
PEOPLE WHO MAKE MISTAKES
LIKE THAT
DON'T BELONG
IN THIS BUSINESS.
MARC!
DANIEL, I FEEL TERRIBLE.
I'M SORRY.
THIS IS MY FAULT.
IF IT'S ANYONE'S FAULT,
IT WAS MINE.
I JUST SHOULD HAVE HAD
AN EDITOR HANDLE IT.
NO. LOOK, I COULD FIX THIS.
I COULD, UH,
I'LL CALL THE COLLECTOR,
SEE IF HE HAS ANOTHER GOWN, AND
I'LL CALL KEIRA'S PUBLICIST. BETTY-
I'M SURE IF WE GOT ANOTHER DRESS, THEN SHE
- BETTY, COME ON. GO HOME. I GOT IT FROM HERE, OKAY?
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR INTERVIEWING ME.
I'VE NEVER BEEN
IN A NEWSPAPER BEFORE.
YEAH, WELL, WE'RE GONNA NEED
ABOUT 40 COPIES
AND PHOTO APPROVAL, IF POSSIBLE. I'M THE
SURROGATE, SO I'M NOT GONNA BE NAMING IT.
THAT'S WEIRD. WHAT DOES
THE FATHER HAVE TO SAY?
NOT A LOT. HE DIED BEFORE
THE BABY WAS CONCEIVED. OH!
MM.
WHAT?
OH.
POOR CHRISTINA'S
GOING THROUGH THE
PREGNANCY STORY AGAIN. AH.
MAYBE YOU COULD GO OUT THERE,
RUN INTERFERENCE.
NO. I'M NOT REALLY
IN A PARTY KIND OF MOOD.
ARE YOU STILL STEWING
ABOUT THAT DRESS, MIJA?
YOU CAN DEAL WITH IT ON MONDAY.
LET IT GO.
LET IT GO?
DAD, BECAUSE OF ME,
"MODE" LOST BUSINESS TODAY.
YOU DIDN'T SEE THE LOOK
ON DANIEL'S FACE.
IT'S LIKE
HE'S LOSING FAITH IN ME.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE THAT I LET
THAT TERI USE ME LIKE THAT.
IN FACT, WHERE'S
HER STUPID BUSINESS CARD?
I CAN'T STAND THAT IT'S ANYWHERE
NEAR MY ORGAN DONOR CARD.
MOM WANTS TO KNOW
WHERE THE CHEESE CUBES ARE
AND CRAZY FINGERNAIL LADY
WANTS TO KNOW
IF WE CAN SPIKE HER CIDER
WITH RUM. HERE. TAKE THIS.
I'LL TALK
TO CRAZY FINGERNAIL LADY.
HA! THERE YOU ARE,
YOU BIG JERK, TERI.
OH, THANK YOU SO MUCH, MARC.
I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
BETTY, MY CLIENT IS DYING TO
MEET YOU. WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I'M SO SORRY, HILDA, BUT I HAVE TO GO.
BETTY, THE PARTY HAS HARDLY EVEN STARTED.
I KNOW, BUT I THINK
I FOUND A WAY I CAN GET
THAT HALSTON DRESS
BACK FROM "ELLE."
IT'S A LONG SHOT,
BUT I'M GONNA TRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD BE NICE?
IF YOU WERE EXCITED
ABOUT SOMETHING I WAS DOING FOR A
CHANGE. OH, I AM. I AM. I-I JUST-
I JUST HAVE TO DO THIS REALLY
QUICK. I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
YOU KNOW WHAT, BETTY?
DON'T BOTHER.
HILDA.
PAPI, CAN YOU TALK TO HER,
PLEASE? SHE'S BEING RIDICULOUS.
NO, SHE'S NOT. YOU ARE.
WHAT? DO YOU HAVE ANY
IDEA HOW HARD HILDA WORKED
TO GET ALL THIS READY,
BY HERSELF, I MIGHT ADD?
THAT IS NOT FAIR.
PAPI, THIS IS MY CAREER.
I AM WORKING HARD
TO TRY AND MOVE UP.
AND IF THAT MEANS
THAT I'M GONNA MISS
A FAMILY PARTY
EVERY NOW AND THEN,
WELL, THEN I DON'T HAVE
A CHOICE. I HAVE TO DO THIS.
YOU DO HAVE A CHOICE.
YOU'RE CHOOSING TO LEAVE.
DAD. NO, NO. NO ONE SUPPORTS
YOU MORE THAN YOUR FAMILY.
WE ARE ALWAYS
BEHIND YOU 100%.
BUT RIGHT NOW
HILDA NEEDS YOU.
PAPI, I AM SORRY THAT
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS,
BUT I HAVE TO GO.
CONNOR, MOLLY,
SO GLAD YOU MADE IT.
HEY. YOUR PLACE IS AMAZING.
WHAT A GREAT VIEW OF THE CITY.
OH, THANKS.
WELL, I LOVE LOOKING DOWN
AT THE LITTLE PEOPLE GOING ABOUT
THEIR LITTLE LIVES.
UM, MOLLY, DEAR, DO YOU MIND
IF I STEAL CONNOR AWAY?
THERE'S SOMEONE
HE HAS TO MEET.
EXCUSE ME.
HI.
NICE DRESS.
THANKS. IT'S NO CARLOS MIELE,
BUT IT DOES THE TRICK.
I CAN'T GET OVER HOW BEAUTIFUL
THIS IS. IT'S BREATHTAKING.
UM, COULD...
I- I'D LIKE
TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
DO YOU MIND IF WE JUST
GO SOMEWHERE
A LITTLE MORE PRIVATE TO TALK? OKAY.
RYAN, THANKS AGAIN FOR HELPING
US GET IN. OH, NO PROBLEM.
YOU TALKED TO ME FOR, LIKE,
20 MINUTES AT THAT BAR.
NOBODY EVER TALKS TO THE CATERER.
WELL, YOU WERE VERY INTERESTING.
TICK-TOCK, BETTY. THAT DRESS AIN'T
GONNA WALK ITSELF OUT. THANK YOU.
YEAH. GOOD LUCK.
OKAY. I HAVE BEEN TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT
THE BEST WAY TO SAY THIS,
BUT.. THERE DOESN'T SEEM
TO BE ONE.
UM...
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO GET YOU OUT OF MY MIND
SINCE WE MET.
DANIEL, I-
PLEASE.
J- JUST LET ME FINISH.
I KNOW I SHOULDN'T DO THIS.
I KNOW IT'S-IT'S BAD
AND TERRIBLE AND WRONG,
AND I'M JEOPARDIZING
A FRIENDSHIP
AND A BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP.
I MEAN, YOU...
CAN'T BELIEVE HOW MANY TIMES
I'VE TRIED TO TALK MYSELF
OUT OF THIS.
BUT I CAN'T CHANGE
THE WAY I FEEL.
DANIEL...
I'M ENGAGED.
I
- CONNOR AND I HAVE BEEN TOGETHER FOR ALMOST FOUR YEARS.
HE HAS BEEN THROUGH
SO MUCH WITH ME.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW MUCH.
I DON'T WANT TO HURT HIM.
NEITHER DO I.
MOLLY...
IF YOU CAN HONESTLY TELL ME
YOU DON'T HAVE FEELINGS FOR ME,
I'LL LET YOU WALK OUT THAT DOOR,
GET ON WITH YOUR LIFE.
I'LL NEVER SAY ANOTHER WORD
ABOUT THIS AGAIN.
I PROMISE.
SO I LEAN ACROSS TO HER
AND I WHISPER...
"NO, THAT'S AL PACINO."
SHE SAYS,
"I DIDN'T ORDER A CAPPUCCINO."
OH, ZAC.
IT'S THAT ACCENT.
I MEAN, WHO CAN UNDERSTAND
A WORD HE SAYS?
WHO CARES WHAT HE SOUNDS LIKE?
LOOK AT THE WAY HE LOOKS.
SO, UH, HOW LONG
HAVE YOU BEEN DATING?
OH. OH, NO, NO. NO. NO, WE'RE NOT.
WE'RE-WE'RE NOT DATING. I'M SORRY. IT'S
JUST-YOU MAKE THE MOST DIVINE COUPLE.
EXCUSE ME.
FOR THE RECORD, I-I WAS
EXTREMELY FLATTERED BY THAT.
ANY MAN IN HIS RIGHT MIND
WOULD BE PROUD TO BE WITH YOU.
WELL, WE WOULD MAKE
QUITE THE POWER COUPLE.
WELL, WE DEFINITELY GET
WHERE EACH OTHER'S COMING FROM.
THAT CAN BE HARD TO FIND.
CONNOR, I, UM,
I- I HAVE TO ADMIT,
EVER SINCE WE HAD
OUR BUSINESS TRIP,
I FIND IT HARD
TO BE AROUND YOU.
I'M SORRY.
I'M NOT FEELING TOO WELL.
DO YOU MIND IF WE LEAVE?
NO, NOT AT ALL.
UM... THANK YOU FOR THE PARTY.
IT-IT WAS LOVELY.
OH, YES. THANK YOU.
MM.
HAVE YOU FOUND IT YET?
OH, WAIT. HERE.
I FOUND THE LIGHTS.
YAY! THERE IT IS.
EXACTLY WHERE
I SAID IT WOULD BE.
OH, THANK YOU SO MUCH, MARC, FOR HELPING ME.
I'M NOT DOING THIS FOR YOU. I'M DOING THIS TO GET
A BETTER CHRISTMAS PRESENT
FROM WILHELMINA.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT. OH, MY GOD!
THEY STILL DO THE UGLY WALL!
THIS WAS TOTALLY MY IDEA.
EVERY DAY WE WOULD PUT UP
PICTURES OF COWORKERS WE HATED
AND THEN MAKE FUN OF THEM.
OH, GOOD TIMES.
HEY, HURRY UP,
SLOWPOKE RODRIGUEZ.
I DON'T WANT TO BE HERE ALL NIGHT. YEAH,
WELL, THESE VINTAGE SNAPS ARE VERY SENSITIVE,
AND I DON'T WANT
TO TEAR THE DRESS.
COME ON! COME INSIDE.
EXCUSE US. PARDON US. EXCUSE US. UH,
OH, OH, OH. OUT OF THE WAY. SORRY.
SORRY, SORRY, SORRY.
EXCUSE US. PARDON US.
WE JUST HAVE TO GET HER
TO A TAXI. SHE IS REALLY DRUNK.
EXCUSE US. NO, NO, NO. THIS WAY. THE
ELEVATORS ARE THIS WAY. YES, NO, THIS WAY.
THE ELEV-
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
UM...
WE'RE TAKING OUR DRESS BACK.
MARC, RUN.
YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
WHOO! HEY. GET OUT OF HERE.
HOLD THE ELEVATOR!
HEY, TERI! CALL ME.
* ALL IS NOT AS IT SEEMS
THANK YOU.
I TAKE IT YOUR CONVERSATION
WITH MOLLY DIDN'T GO VERY WELL.
I GUESS WE BOTH LOST OUT
TONIGHT, HUH?
I BEG YOUR PARDON?
COME ON. I'M NOT STUPID. I KNOW
YOU'RE INTERESTED IN CONNOR.
WELL, WHAT WOULD
MAKE YOU THINK THAT?
WELL... ONCE I REALIZED
YOU DIDN'T HAVE
A BUSINESS MOTIVE
FOR HELPING ME,
I FIGURED YOU MUST HAVE
A PERSONAL ONE.
AND I'VE SEEN
THE WAY YOU LOOK AT HIM.
WELL, THAT'S JUST-
RELAX.
I'M NOT GONNA HOLD THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE HUMAN AGAINST YOU.
YOUR SECRET'S SAFE WITH ME.
* YOU WILL SEE
* HEAVENLY
I CAN'T SAY I'M NOT INTRIGUED.
I GUESS THE THREE OF YOU
MAY COME IN.
WE'RE IN.
PINCH ME.
DON'T TOUCH ME.
YOU GUYS ARE UNBELIEVABLE.
IT WAS NOTHING.
WELL, IT WASN'T NOTHING.
WELL, EITHER WAY, YOU TWO
SHOULD STAY, ENJOY YOURSELVES.
YOU DESERVE IT.
OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS A DEFINING MOMENT.
I'M THE FIRST ASSISTANT
WHO'S EVER BEEN INVITED
TO A WILHELMINA SLATER PARTY.
WELL, I'M HERE, TOO.
NOT WHEN I TELL THE STORY.
DOORS ARE REALLY OPENING FOR US,
AREN'T THEY?
IT'S ALL STARTING.
OH, MY GOD. THERE'S TOM WOLFE
AND ZAC POSEN.
MM.
AND...
JODIE PAPADAKIS.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE EVER SEEN AN ASSISTANT
AT A WILHELMINA SLATER FUNCTION.
WELL, YOU KNOW, JUST, UH, NETWORKING.
I HAVE ALL 40 OF
MY NEW CONTACTS, BY THE WAY.
DO YOU?
MM-HMM.
TELL ME-
AND THIS IS IMPORTANT-
HAVE YOU TRIED
THE SHRIMP YET?
NO.
THEY'RE VERY SPICY.
SPICY!
I CAN'T FIGURE OUT
IF I LIKE THEM OR NOT.
I THINK I DO.
JODIE,
CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
I HAVE BEEN A FAN OF YOURS
FOR A VERY LONG TIME NOW,
AND...
WELL, I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU WOULD EVER CONSIDER
BEING MY MENTOR?
LET'S START
WITH ME NOT KICKING YOU
OUT OF Y.E.T.I...
AND WE'LL TAKE IT FROM THERE.
HI. BETTY SUAREZ, "MODE"
MAGAZINE. WELL, HOW DO YOU DO?
OH, I'M A VERY BIG FAN
OF YOUR PUBLICATION.
HELLO?
JUSTIN?
PAPI?
9个未接电话
HILDA, WHERE ARE YOU?
WHAT HAPPENED?
WE'RE AT THE HOSPITAL.
What?
OH, MY GOD!
DID CHRISTINA GO INTO LABOR?
No.
BETTY...
PAPI HAD A HEART ATTACK.
WHAT?
MOLLY?
YOU WERE RIGHT.
I CAN'T SAY I DON'T HAVE
FEELINGS FOR YOU.
I BROKE UP WITH CONNOR.
* OH, NOTHING'S GONNA CHANGE
MY LOVE FOR YOU *
* I WANNA SPEND MY LIFE
WITH YOU *
* SO WE MAKE LOVE
IN THE GRASS UNDER THE MOON *
* NO ONE CAN TELL
* DAMNED IF I DO
* FOREVER JOURNEY
ON GOLDEN AVENUES *
* I DRIFT IN YOUR EYES
* SINCE I LOVE YOU
* OH
* I GOT THAT BEAT
IN MY VEINS FOR ONLY RULE *
* LOVE IS TO SHARE,
MINE IS FOR YOU *
破烂熊字幕组作品
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢 迎 光 临
www.tvsubtitles.net