Previously on The O. C.:
Promise me you will not say
anything to him.
-Get out.
-I've gotten a hotel room.
You have a week to find
somewhere to live.
If I have to sacrifice our friendship
to be with Summer, I'll do it.
So it's war.
I'm worried about how much
you're drinking.
-I love you.
-Pull over, and I'll come get you.
Ryan.
Hey, Ryan.
-What time is it?
-It's 5:30-ish.
You're showing up earlier and earlier.
Yeah, well, we have a lot of ground
to cover, so I figured...
...since we're both up,
we may as well get a jump on it.
Yeah, no. We've been over this.
Summer doesn't want you.
She doesn't want Zach.
All there is to it.
Good night.
-Something occurred to me. A wrinkle.
-The prom?
Yeah, and I have convince Summer
to go with me.
We must partake in the magical rite
of passage known as the prom.
Oh, yeah, you mean people
getting drunk, making out...
-...throwing up on the gym floor?
-No, I mean romance.
I mean tuxedos, corsages, limousines.
I don't know. I don't see Summer
buying into the prom thing.
You're wrong. Summer's fantasized
about prom since fifth grade.
-How do you know that?
-Sat behind her in computer class.
I really honed my eavesdropping skills
that year. The point is, Summer's...
...forever dreamt of going to the prom,
and I would dream of going with her.
You need to get that out of your mind.
If it helps, I don't think I'm gonna go.
Just because you saw Trey leaving
doesn't mean they're hooking up.
-What does it mean?
-Maybe he went to borrow something.
Like a book.
Or one of her newsboy caps.
-Y eah, maybe they hooked up.
-Okay, you're just...
...married to the worst possible
scenario, huh?
I'm gonna talk to her about it today,
but whatever happened...
...she seems dead set
on keeping it from me.
-Kind of early for a phone call.
-Kind of early for a lot of things.
Hello?
Dad, what are--?
Where are you?
Oh, my God.
Okay. Yeah.
We'll be right there.
-What is it?
-My mom got in a car accident.
She's at the hospital.
Oh, honey. I am so glad you're okay.
I'm so sorry.
We'll get through this.
I promise.
They had to cut it off.
Well, you were due
for an upgrade anyway.
Mom, are you okay?
Oh, I'm fine.
The doctor says she has a concussion,
but, fortunately, no internal injuries.
-What happened?
-Talking on the cell phone.
Stupid. Thank God for airbags.
-Well, is there anything we can do?
-Oh, not a thing.
I'll just probably spend the day
on the couch.
Well, under the circumstances, I'll lift
my parental ban on my DVD collection.
-What an honor.
-lt is.
You can watch anything you want.
House of Flying Daggers...
...Evil Dead II.
If you must, X-Men 1 and 2,
but you gotta do 1 first.
-I kind of like 1--
-That's sort of the catch. No, 2's better.
I don't know what to tell you, Sandy.
She blew a.08.
Look, maybe....
Maybe I read it wrong.
Maybe it was a.07.
-I'm not asking you to do that.
-Just promise you'll get her some help.
It's an underwater theme?
Yeah, but it turns out that's a lot
more work than I thought.
Do you have any idea how to make
a papier-mâché octopus?
No, but maybe Ryan could bring
you one instead of a corsage.
I don't think Ryan's gonna be
bringing me anything.
But you guys are going
to prom together, right?
-I wouldn't count on it.
-Coop, did I miss something?
Because for, like, a blip,
you guys actually seemed happy.
-It's complicated.
-It's you and Ryan. It's supposed to be.
-Can we not talk about this anymore?
-Yeah.
-Coop, are you okay?
-Fine. I'm fine.
So everyone's saying you're
gonna be voted prom queen.
Isn't that your fifth-grade dream
coming true?
No. My dream involved an actual date.
A hot guy in a tux with a carnation
pinned to his lapel.
Instead I'm drawing straws between
Nerdboy and Assclown.
-So, what are you gonna do, not go?
-Exactly.
If I go, I have to decide
between Seth and Zach.
Fast-forward to prom.
There's me standing alone while...
...they wrestle like two girls
in a mud pit.
I'm building the lost city of Atlantis
out of streamers and tape.
-You gotta at least show up.
-Fine.
If you work out your mysterious issues
with Ryan, then maybe I'll go.
I wouldn't hold my breath.
So how is she?
Well, the doctor says she'll be fine.
She's resting now.
I should've seen this coming.
So she's been hitting the bottle hard.
It's been a rough couple of weeks...
...for everyone, even me.
Okay, I'll bite.
-So, what's the problem?
-Sandy...
...I did not come here
to talk about myself.
But as long as we're on the subject,
I could kind of use your advice.
Hey, if this involves you being naked,
please, you gotta warn me.
It's my prenup.
It says if you and Caleb have been
married for a year...
...you get $3 million at least.
If you have been married for less
than a year, you get nothing.
Eleven months, 27 days. Why do you
think he's in such a rush to divorce me?
I'm not surprised. He's a wily old guy.
He's a cheap son of a bitch who
wants to throw me out on the street.
-You've gotta find a loophole.
-I don't know, Julie. This looks ironclad.
All Caleb has to do is file the papers
by Monday with the county clerk.
Unless you can figure out a way
to stop him...
...you're out of luck.
Hey.
-Cohen.
-Dude.
I'm so sorry about the launch.
I had a Bruce Banner moment.
Yeah. Yeah, we're both to blame.
Let's put it behind us.
-Okay, like it never happened.
-Yeah.
I'm going this way.
-You think Summer's willing to forget it?
-Sure.
If she sees how mature
we're being, right?
Look how much we've grown.
We're shaking hands...
-...we're using brains instead of brawn.
-We're not ruled by Y chromosomes.
No, we're civilized gentlemen.
We can handle any situation
with grace and dignity.
Here comes our first test.
Summer, hey.
We were both just talking and--
Save it, Cohen.
I'm done listening to your excuses.
Summer, we're really sorry.
Are you willing to forgive us?
Nope. Don't want to forgive you,
but prom is tomorrow night.
And I have wanted to go my whole life.
So I'm not gonna let our demented
little threesome ruin that for me.
So I'm going with one of you.
-Which one of us are you gonna take?
-Don't care.
I am too pissed off and tired to choose,
so you're gonna decide.
Don't care how, but tomorrow
I will be at my house in a dress...
...and one of you will pick me up.
Got it? Good.
My dress is a magenta color, so my
corsage should be in that general family.
-Dude, she's hanging by a thread.
-Yeah, I'll take one for the team.
-I'll take her to prom.
-No way. Why do you get to go?
Because, dude, I saw her first.
That doesn't make sense.
Sure it does.
I got a text message from Reed. She
wants to meet us at the diner for lunch.
Dude, the ladies are all over us,
but not in a good way.
Okay, listen. I say we go to the diner,
we meet with Reed.
-We deal with this Summer thing later.
-All right. One battle at a time.
-What is that?
-It's the best facility on the West Coast.
-You're sending me to rehab?
-I'm asking you...
...to get help.
Nobody needs to know.
We can say you're taking a trip.
-ln this town, a trip is always rehab.
-All I care about is you.
You don't have to worry.
I'm done with drinking.
Just like that, huh?
Last night scared me.
You don't snap your fingers and
make something like this disappear.
Well, you do when you could lose
everything, and last night I almost did.
Look.
I'm going to the kitchen now, and I'm
gonna pour out every drop in this house.
-Are you coming?
-Right behind you.
-Marissa.
-Hey.
Look, I know there's something
going on, so just tell me.
-Tell you what?
-I saw Trey leaving your house last night.
-It's not what you think.
-I asked you what happened...
...when I was in Miami,
and you're not talking...
-...so I'm taking my best guess.
-Which is?
You and Trey.
What, you think we hooked up?
-Thanks for the vote of confidence.
-You've been strange since I got back.
Trey's avoiding me.
What am I supposed to think?
-You should give me a little more credit.
-Okay, fine.
Tell me.
I didn't hook up with him.
And if you don't believe me, why don't
you ask your brother what happened?
I understand you're probably
a little bit upset about the launch.
Well, I think one day pretty soon we're
all gonna have a good laugh about this.
I know that day feels far off.
But comedy is just tragedy...
-...plus time.
-Reed, we're really sorry.
We had a huge opportunity,
and we blew it.
-I hope we can make it up to you.
-Thank you, Zach.
-I was gonna say that.
-I hate to give you guys good news...
...but unfortunately I have some.
George Lucas is interested
in Atomic County.
He might want to make it
into his next movie.
-Oh, my God.
-This is incredible!
Oh, my God. It's happened.
We're this decade's Matt and Ben.
Look, he's coming to town.
He wants to sit down with you guys,
but here's the deal:
-Only one of you can take the meeting.
-What?
-Reed.
-Face it.
You two can't do anything together
except whine about Summer.
I can't face another debacle.
I can't handle another debacle. I--
No. One.
-Well, which one of us do you want?
-I am pissed off enough that I don't care.
But George is coming to town
tomorrow night.
So he and I will be at Al Forno,
and one of you will be there.
And if either of you utter the name
Summer, so help me God....
Dude, this is amazing.
I have to go to that meeting.
Do you realize
what this could do for me?
I've dreamed about meeting
George Lucas since I was a fetus.
-You wanted to go to prom.
-I think you said that too. I think you--
-Yeah, you did.
-All right.
So one of us takes the meeting.
The other one goes to prom.
All right.
Do you have any ideas
how to settle this?
No.
Not even one.
-How is she?
-Well, she's doing all right.
-A little rattled.
-I hope she'd be rattled.
Drunk driving at her age?
It's a disgrace.
What Kirsten needs right now
is a little support.
If you can't give her that,
show yourself out.
I see you're employing your softball
approach. That might be appropriate...
...when your son runs off to Portland,
but this is more serious.
I know how to help my wife.
Sandy, l....
-I can handle this.
-Okay. I'll be outside.
Behave yourself.
I'm glad to see
you're still in one piece.
Dad, I know you're worried,
but I'm fine.
See? A couple of sprained fingers.
Not the end of the world.
So how are things at the office?
-You could've been killed.
-I learned my lesson.
-Always eat dinner.
-ls that the lesson to be learned here?
I made an error in judgment.
You should be familiar with that.
This is not about me, Kiki.
You have a problem.
My God, did you give
any thought to your kids?
-I am a good mother.
-You're also an alcoholic.
Your mother was one too. She did
her best to hide it, but I always knew.
Why do you think Mom drank
the way she did?
Why do you think Hailey
left the house at 1 7?
If this family is screwed up,
it's because of you.
I gave you everything you ever wanted.
I may like my chardonnay,
but I am not gonna die alone.
And that's more than I can say for you!
Trey.
Trey, you in there?
Trey, look, it's me.
I know you're avoiding me,
but I need to talk to you...
...so do me a favor, call me back. Bye.
Summer.
-What do you want?
-We both want to take you to prom.
Now, I know it feels like deep down
you hate us both equally.
But somewhere,
if you look inside yourself...
...you've gotta hate one of us less.
I've tried choosing. When Seth
went to Portland, I chose Zach.
When Zach went to ltaly, I chose Seth.
Somehow it just doesn't seem to stick.
So I'm done deciding.
I am leaving it up to you guys.
-What if we can't decide?
-Flip a coin. I don't care how you do it.
Bye.
-Heads, I go to the prom. Tails, you go?
-Okay, fine.
-No, wait. Hold on.
-No. No changies.
No, I think we should wait.
If we flip the coin now...
...we'll both try and get out
of whatever we're supposed to do.
-lf we wait till right before the prom....
-Neither will have a chance to back out.
-I'll meet you at your house before prom?
-Fine.
-You talked to Marissa.
-Yeah.
-She said she didn't hook up with Trey.
-Good news, right?
-Something happened. I know it.
-Have you tried talking to Trey?
-See what he says?
-I went to his place. He wasn't there.
-He's not taking my calls.
-Your options are, A, sit here...
...spin conspiracy theories
about Trey and Marissa...
...or, B, you can believe her.
Now, my personal recommendation--
-Let me guess, B.
-Yes, B. Believe her.
And might I add, first of all,
that you have no reason not to.
But if you believe her, you can put
this weird non-fight behind you guys...
...and you can go to prom together.
-I'm not in the mood to go to prom.
-You have to go. Look.
I've seen too many Saved by the Bell's,
but if it's taught me anything...
...it sure has taught me that prom
is a seminal moment, okay?
It's meant to be shared.
-ls this about you and Summer?
-No.
Maybe. Yes, but only because Summer
and I aren't gonna go to our prom...
...because of some fight. You should
really learn from the error of my ways.
Please.
Somebody really should.
Well...
...is this a booty call?
Not in the least.
I've come for my sleeping pills.
Well, they're upstairs.
Yeah, I haven't been sleeping very well
either. This divorce, it's so ugly.
Oh, it's not that.
I had an argument with Kirsten,
our worst yet.
-I just can't stop thinking about it.
-Oh, well...
...I'm just thinking outside the box here,
but you could apologize.
-No, I couldn't face her.
-So write her a letter.
Say all the things you're too stubborn
to say to her face.
Come on. We both know
you can't stand to fight with her.
Sometimes you surprise me, Juju.
Hang on. I'll get your pills.
Orange bottle, blue-and-white label,
little black-and-white things.
I know. Just a second.
I could've found them in half the time
without my glasses.
Okay, okay. Here.
Now make sure you only take one.
-Yeah, I know.
-Wait, Cal, wait.
Would you like to do something
tomorrow night? Maybe get together?
-You asking me out on a date?
-ls that so odd?
All right, I guess it is.
But just think of it as one last hurrah.
It'll probably be the last night
we ever spend together.
Julie, you're not gonna seduce me
out of this divorce.
I'm meeting my lawyer tomorrow
to finalize the paperwork.
-I'm filing bright and early Monday.
-So send me the papers.
I'll make the marks.
We'll make a party out of it.
Oh, why not?
-A fitting end to a marriage like ours.
-I'll see you tomorrow?
See you tomorrow.
Hi.
-Hi.
-So...
...I'm sorry I went off on you yesterday.
I was confused.
I get it. I know I've been
kind of all over the map lately.
No, no. You say nothing happened,
and I believe you.
-You feel like going to prom?
-You mean it?
-I thought you weren't into PDA.
-I'm coming around.
Good morning.
-Did you sleep at all last night?
-Not a wink.
Listen, I'm an expert at fighting
with your father.
And believe me, every time
you think you've driven him away...
...he comes back asking for more.
You couldn't beat him off with a stick.
Oh, but the things I said.
He'll forgive you.
Give it some time.
I guess so.
How about we lay low tonight?
We'll order some takeout...
...maybe watch one of Seth's DVDs.
I should try and talk to my dad.
If we're gonna get through this
all by ourselves...
...we need to get back on solid ground.
Well, I've never seen
House of Flying Daggers.
-Scared you.
-Jess.
Walk me to class. I feel like
we haven't chatted in a while.
-What do you want?
-A date for the prom.
-You taken?
-Yeah.
Let me guess, Marissa Cooper.
It doesn't bother you?
Getting your brother's sloppy seconds?
Look, nothing happened between
Marissa and Trey, okay?
You're getting your chain yanked,
Atwood. Bad.
-You got the story? I'd love to hear it.
-Ask your brother.
Although I don't think he's too anxious
to share, since he took off for Chino.
-You better not be screwing with me.
-Apparently I'm the only one who's not.
Okay. I'm prepared for whatever
fate throws my way tonight.
I have a tuxedo pressed
in case I'm going to prom.
-Mine's in the trunk.
-All right.
And if I am, in fact,
meeting with George Lucas...
...I have my Boba Fett T -shirt.
-It's a little small.
-I got it when I was 8.
Hopefully it will stretch. Shall we?
-You do the honors.
-Okay.
-Heads, I go to the prom. Tails, you.
-Great.
-Works for me.
-Just as I hoped.
-Good luck tonight, man. Have fun.
-Yeah, same to you.
Julie.
Just a second. I'm coming.
You're early.
I see you've pulled out all the stops.
One last-ditch effort to stop
this divorce from going forward?
God, paranoid much?
I just wanted one last night with you.
And if you don't believe me, here.
-You signed.
-Told you.
So now maybe you can relax.
Have a drink. Take a dip.
Here, I made it just the way you like it.
On the rocks, plenty of salt.
I think I'll start with a Scotch.
Okay. No hurry on the margs.
Scotch it is.
Ry. Good to see you, man.
Cut the crap, Trey. You got
something you wanna tell me?
-What do you mean, man?
-About Marissa.
All right.
Fine, let's take a seat, get a drink.
Two 7&7s.
One 7&7, and one just 7.
When you were in Miami, Marissa and l,
we got drunk together.
And you came on to her.
Why do you always assume
that it's my fault?
Because it always is.
Well, anyway, we were both wasted,
really wasted...
...on the beach, and your girl, she can
drink, but she can't hold her liquor.
Look, I'm sorry, Ryan.
She threw herself at me.
I don't believe you.
We agreed not to tell. We thought
it'd be better if you didn't know.
There's no way.
You swear?
On Mom.
I wouldn't lie to you, Ryan.
Not about this.
-Ryan, look--
-I gotta go.
Man, I'm so sorry.
Marissa, hey, it's me.
I'm not feeling well...
...so I'm not gonna make prom.
Sorry.
Ryan?
Theresa.
So, what are you doing back, huh?
I'm visiting my mom for the weekend.
Believe it or not, I miss it here.
I mean, it might not be paradise,
but it's home.
-And Atlanta?
-It's fine for now.
You know, I wrote you all those letters.
I know.
I needed a clean break.
-Or you were mad because I left.
-I wanted you to leave.
You belong in Newport. I mean....
Which doesn't explain,
why are you back here?
-Trey.
-He's out of jail?
He was crashing with the Cohens
for a little while.
-Everything was going good, but--
-Let me guess.
Trey got into trouble.
He hooked up with Marissa.
Trey says she came on to him.
She says nothing happened.
-I don't know who to believe.
-I do.
Ryan, Trey has been jerking you around
your entire life. I mean....
-And Marissa--
-Has made mistakes.
She would never hurt you like that.
How do you know?
Because last year, when I needed you,
you know, she....
She let you go.
Even though it broke her heart.
I mean, they both love you,
but of the two of them...
...Marissa is the one
that you can trust.
Well, this is me.
-Oh, is your mom in? I'll say hey.
-Yeah, but-- It's getting kind of late.
-All right. Let me help you in.
-No, it's okay. I got it.
-Yeah? You sure?
-Yeah.
Okay.
Talk to Marissa, you know.
Make this right.
Yeah, I will.
Okay.
-Take care.
-Yeah.
Bye.
-Hi.
-Somebody missed you.
Oh, he looks more and more
like his daddy every day.
I'm glad it's you.
I didn't know what magenta was,
so I got you white.
Perfect.
We gotta get our picture taken with
the mermaid. It's for the yearbook.
Okay.
-Yeah, just give me a second, okay?
-Okay.
-Coop. Hey.
-Hey.
-Under the O. Sea is awesome.
-Thanks.
-Where's Ryan?
-He couldn't make it.
-He's sick.
-Sick? Too sick to take you to prom?
He better be really sick, like dead.
If he's not, I'm gonna strangle him
with his own wife beater.
It's okay. You know, I mean,
I've got plenty to do anyway.
I'll be okay.
I'll have a seltzer on the rocks
with a twist of lemon.
I'll have the same. Seltzer. On the--
George Lucas drinks seltzer.
Everything you do, every little detail,
to me, it's just--
-It's fascinating.
-You're too kind.
Let me ask you just one question,
then I promise we'll get into the book.
How did you first come up
with the lightsaber?
I'm sure Mr. Lucas doesn't have time
for such large-scale questions.
Okay, fine. I'll go smaller.
Did you go to your prom?
Prom?
-Oh, my God.
-As in "prom"?
It's a personal thing, and I wondered if
you went to yours. It would help me out.
Well, actually, I didn't.
I spent my time being creative.
-Drawing Ewoks, Jar Jar Binks.
-Good to know.
If George Lucas can skip his prom,
I can skip mine.
No. No, wait a minute.
I do regret not going to my prom.
-Really? Because it's a seminal moment?
-Exactly.
Mr. Lucas, I'm sorry.
We can get back to the point.
No, wait. It would be good
for me to talk about this.
The prom is a great American tradition.
It's important to experience the things...
...of being a teenager
when you're a teenager.
When I made American Graffiti,
I'd never had the experience of a prom...
...and I had to make a movie about it.
I felt hopelessly inadequate...
...without having really done it myself.
Not having been part of that
pivotal moment in teenage life...
...I felt very sad and alone.
You're buzzing.
Yeah, Reed's sending me text messages.
I don't have to check them.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Oh, God, she's saying George Lucas
is checked out.
God, Seth is totally ignoring
the talking points.
He always--
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
No, it's not. This is ridiculous.
I'm here with you at prom,
just like I wanted.
If you have to talk yourself
into this...
...it probably means
you shouldn't be here.
I'm your date. Even though
you didn't want me to be.
-I did want you to be.
-No. You didn't.
I saw your face
when I got out of the limo.
And I saw yours.
You want to be there talking
about your comic book with Reed.
Look, my prom fantasy,
it didn't quite happen...
...but you've been dreaming about
this comic book your whole life.
This is your shot. You should go.
I can't abandon you.
I did it to you.
-Good point.
-Go.
Save Cohen from himself.
So we ended up--
Well, we flipped a coin.
-You flipped a coin?
-Yeah, and I know it sounds crazy...
...but at the time--
Will you excuse me for one second?
I'll be right back.
Hey. You didn't have to come here.
Look, we need to settle this thing
once and for all.
And I think for the first time you and l
both know where we need to be.
-You want the comic book.
-And you want Summer.
All right. Hey, you don't have
much time.
So take this.
All right. Thanks, man.
So movie time.
Now, Seth recommends
Shaun of the Dead.
He says it's a very funny,
romantic zombie comedy.
Actually, I'm pretty wiped out.
I'm gonna go soak in a hot bath.
The food's here.
I'll wait then. I can take a bath later.
You know what? Go ahead. We can
heat the food up when you're done.
Thanks.
Hey.
You know what? I don't have my wallet.
Hang on. Let me grab some cash.
So...
...you about ready for this marg?
Why not?
You know, I've never been
in this pool before.
No, you're more of a land shark.
We should have done
this sort of thing more.
-Enjoyed each other more.
-Well, we had our moments.
I suppose this calls for a toast.
You know, I really did love you, Juju.
Past tense. That stings.
Sorry. Grammatical error.
To us.
Wait, stop.
-What?
-I didn't put lime in your drink.
-Let me make you a new one.
-There's no need.
Well, it looks like we're both
flying solo on prom night.
-Why? What happened to Zach?
-Oh, he went to go save his comic book.
-Are you okay?
-Y eah.
So prom was a letdown.
You know, I bet it is for everybody.
It's like New Y ear's.
Well, we could always go back
to your house.
Yeah. Curl up with Princess Sparkle...
...watch the season one
of The Valley on DVD.
-That sounds perfect.
-Yeah.
-Come on.
-All right.
All right, it's the moment
we've all been waiting for.
It's time to announce Harbor School's
prom king and queen.
And your prom queen tonight:
Summer Roberts.
-Summer, come on up here.
-Oh, no.
-Get me out of here.
-And your prom king:
Zach Stephens.
-I'm making a run for it.
-lf the king and queen could join me...
...on-stage, they'll kick off
your spotlight dance.
There's the queen. We found her.
We're halfway there.
Summer Roberts, come on up here.
-All right, Summer!
-Yeah, Summer!
Way to go, Summer!
Looking good!
Zach Stephens, we're waiting.
All right, Zach!
Zach, where did you go?
What's up, man?
-Zach Stephens, we're waiting.
-They're calling you, dude!
No one's coming.
-Cohen.
-I'm sorry I'm late.
-I was caught in traffic.
-Get off the stage!
-I'm on-stage.
-That's not Zach Stephens.
-No, I'm not.
-I think you should step down.
-You're not the prom king.
-Seth Cohen's a tool.
Okay. I know I'm not who
you all imagined as prom king...
...seeing as how I'm not
who any of you actually voted for.
But she's the queen, and I love her.
So I guess that that makes me king.
No, I'm just a guy standing next to you.
You're the queen, all right?
I'm the jester, perhaps, if that works.
So let me ask you this, Your Highness:
What can I do to make it up to you?
Well, you--
Well, you can start
by dancing with me.
But he's a tool.
Marissa.
Ryan.
Sorry I missed prom.
You're just in time.
Julie.
Julie!
Cal?
Cal!
That moo shu smells great.
What are we gonna do about you?
I found your stash.
-It's just in case.
-And I trusted you.
I believed you when you said
you were done.
Sandy, I'm doing this my own way.
How? By sneaking around?
By lying to me?
I just don't want you to babysit me
like I'm some wayward child.
Well, maybe that's exactly
what you need.
Right now I feel more like your dad
than I feel like your husband.
Hello. What? Julie?
Wait, wait, wait, calm down.
Well, say that again.
Oh, my God.
I understand.
Of course.
It's about your father.
What is it?
He's all right, isn't he?
He's dead.
I am so sorry.