-Previously on The O. C. :
-You' re a tough kid from Chino...
...with an ex-girlfriend who's the
most beautiful girl ever in high school.
-Yeah. But right now I'm here with you.
-He snuck out to see his girlfriend.
-What are we doing?
-I call it "prepping the oven. "
What are we doing
in the larger sense?
I'd like to place an order for delivery.
Can I get the crispy noodles
with shrimp and the calamari salad?
Get the Vietnamese rolls.
And the chicken with the spicy curry.
No, just one. And Vietnamese rolls
and chicken with spicy curry.
You guys want something
from Thaiphoon?
Yeah, some pad thai, please.
Y eah, Mom, will you order
a couple gallons of the tom yum soup?
And then the salmon with the
chili-lime sauce. And dumplings.
Okay, can we get some pad thai,
some tom yum soup...
-...salmon with the chili-lime sauce--
-Dumplings.
And the steamed dumplings.
Yeah. Great.
-We ordered enough for a small army.
-I got an idea.
Why don't you ask
your female cohorts over?
Lindsay's with her mom. Family therapy
and to a Truffaut retrospective.
That's a hell of a double-header.
What about Alex?
-Howdy.
-What are you doing here?
Okay, that's not the warmest greeting
I've ever received, but I will take it.
I didn't expect to see you here
right now. I'm kind of busy.
I wanted to invite you to have dinner
with the family.
I don't think it's a good idea.
My ex is in town.
Actually, in my office.
Waiting for me.
Your ex.
Well, part of the ABC's of the ex is
to step aside for the I and the U.
But the ex isn't technically an ex.
We never really broke up, officially.
It's part of what we need to figure out.
But I really do wanna come
have dinner with your family...
...so maybe we can do it
after the ex leaves.
Okay, so the ex is leaving.
When? Later tonight?
Staying the night. That's cool.
Staying the week?
I don't know. I didn't know
this was gonna happen, and now it has.
I have to deal with it. It would be great
if you could just let me figure it out.
Just, in other words, stay away
while the ex is in town.
Unless you're cool
with the three of us hanging out.
Okay, well, I'm gonna have
to get back to you on that.
I like the new club.
-You ready to get out of here?
-ln a minute.
-So what if Alex has an ex?
-Most people do.
That's right. He's probably just
some meathead thug...
...with her name tattooed
on his bicep.
Well, no threat to you.
Unless...
...he's a thug with a heart.
He's done his time,
1 8 months for robbery.
It was wrong. He understands that.
He's mature, he's sensitive, seasoned.
-So you're not okay.
-Not at all, Ryan. Not at all.
-He's spiraling, huh?
-Seth? He hasn't even begun.
-Hey.
-Hi, guys.
Marissa, that's an amazing skirt,
and I love your shoes.
Thanks. I really like your....
Your backpack.
Where's it from?
L.L. Bean.
Well, I'm late for class. But maybe
this weekend we can all hang.
-See a movie or go to Balboa lsland?
-Yeah, sounds great.
Every day, she looks like she could
be on the cover of a fashion magazine.
Yeah? I guess.
-Good thing I'm not competitive.
-What are you talking about?
Nothing. It's just, you know, you said it.
Everyone has an ex...
...and you seem to hang out
with yours a lot.
-We do?
-You do.
-Like, constantly.
-Maybe you two should become friends.
We can all hang out,
and it wouldn't be weird.
Yeah, me and the Cosmo Girl.
Yeah, that wouldn't be weird at all.
A massage.
-You must really need something.
-Favor. Tiny.
Ask me while you're giving me the
massage. I'm more inclined to say yes.
It's about work.
As you know, the Newport Group's
reputation is pretty much in the toilet.
-It's well-deserved.
-The board wants us to come up with...
...a plan to improve the company's
image. I figured who better to ask...
...than you, the man who practically
invented hating the Newport Group.
Well, I was doing it
long before it was trendy.
Yeah. So any ideas?
Yes. As a matter of fact, this is perfect.
-Perfect's good.
-I just got a call to work...
...with the Newport Housing lnitiative.
They want low-income housing.
-I was gonna petition the city council.
-The Newport Group can find the money.
Exactly. The housing board
gets a development.
And the company could do something
good for a change. Honey, that's perfect.
You've earned more than a massage.
Where I come from,
that only means one thing.
Hey. I have a surprise for you.
I love surprises. Especially when
they're named Jimmy Choo.
Am I about to get whacked?
Hey, a cupcake.
It doesn't have stiletto heels,
but I'll eat it anyway.
You know it's not my birthday.
Yes, and I also know
it's our six-month anniversary.
Oh, my God, it is.
God, it's been six months?
-Holy mack.
-I know, it's amazing.
I've never been in a relationship
this long.
-Neither have l.
-Well, I think we should celebrate.
I would like to take you to a romantic
anniversary dinner at The Arches.
What do you say?
So, what'd you say?
You know, that I'm fasting
for an upcoming colonoscopy.
I'm sure that was the answer
he was looking for.
Yes. Look, Zach is so unbelievably great.
But six months?
I did not even date Cohen that long.
When did we get so old?
When did life get so complicated?
I know. Remember when we were little,
and it was just you and me...
-...and the boys had cooties?
-Yeah.
And we had sleepovers and watched
Full House and Step by Step.
Oh, my God. I loved Full House.
But my favorite character was named
DJ, so I guess that's ruined.
No. Look, forget DJ.
Forget Cohen and Zach and Ryan.
You know what?
-We need a break from the boys.
-You mean a girls' night out?
I do. You telling me you couldn't use
a night without boys?
-Well, Full House is on Nick at Nite.
-Really?
Thanks.
So great news.
Sandy has an amazing idea to kick-start
an image makeover for the company.
-I have better news and a better idea.
-You haven't heard his yet.
It would be hard for Sandy's idea
to top the best idea ever.
-You ready?
-Probably not, no.
Oh, my--
There's so much you here.
A magazine, Kirsten, about Newport life,
restaurants, events, gossip.
Selling Newport Beach
as an aspirational brand.
Well, Sandy's idea,
which is in a different direction...
...involves funding
a low-income housing development.
That's kind of cute. I guess.
But, Kiki, we're trying to appeal
to the Newport elite.
We need to think about
who these people are:
Bored, rich gossipmongers
who like to shop.
They're me. And I don't care
about low-income housing.
You have a point.
-This is as far as I go.
-Thanks for walking me.
Have fun at your emergency
comic-book meeting.
Why do I get the feeling
Seth won't be talking about comics?
Yeah. You okay?
-Yeah, sure. I like eating alone.
-You know who you could sit with--
No. That's okay, really.
Get to know her, she'll stop being
my ex and become your friend.
Ryan, don't. Okay, please.
I'm sure they don't even eat.
-Hey.
You guys mind if Lindsay joins you?
-I gotta meet Seth.
-No. Emergency comic-book meeting?
-Zach was summoned too.
-You heard.
-Have a seat, Lindsay.
-Great. Thanks, you guys. See you.
This is so good. Great idea
hitting the drive-through for lunch.
It'll probably be hours on the elliptical
trainer working those off, huh?
Coop exercising? Now, that's funny.
So you guys can just eat cheeseburgers
and look like you?
No. Well, sometimes we get
chili fries too.
Why? What are you eating?
It's a Zone meal.
It's low-carb.
So we were planning our
girls' night out for this weekend.
Do you want to join us?
Me?
What do you say?
Okay. Sure.
So break it down for me, guys.
And don't afraid to be honest.
Well, what you should've done is
tell her, "Take all the space you need.
I know this must be hard. "
Boom! You're a hero.
You look confident,
but like you still care.
Yeah, that is so the way
I should've played it.
When do we discuss
The New Avengers?
Philip, your membership has been
revoked. You're not there for me.
-I'm not there for you. Beat it.
-He doesn't mean it.
-He's just upset.
-I don't care if you're in junior high.
I think you're onto something. I like it.
You know what? I'll call her.
-Tell her I'm giving her some space.
-Dude, don't do that.
-What's happening?
-He's calling her.
-Give me that.
-I'm leaving a message.
No, you are not.
Jeez, man. Fine. Whatever.
-Forget calling. I'll go down there.
-No.
If I'm losing her,
I wanna see who I'm losing her to.
-You are not going down there.
-I have to. My paycheck's down-- Yes.
Yes. That's perfect. She owes me $38.
I have to go down there.
Okay? How can I live
without that money?
-I gotta eat.
-What if I go down there?
-I come with you. Okay.
-I'll go down there.
I'll say I'm picking up your paycheck,
sniff around for the ex.
Okay. Check him out. Report back
to me. Maybe snap a few photos.
-Sure. What do you say?
-All right.
Listen. You gotta apologize to Philip.
He took that really hard.
Philip. He's always been the weak one.
Hey. Come on. I'm sorry what
happened back there. Heat of passion.
You know how it is? Sorry, sometimes
Bruce Banner turns into the Hulk.
Hey, I talked to the housing initiative.
They are on cloud nine over there.
Good.
They're gonna draw up a proposal
for you to bring to work. Okay, honey...
...I don't want to alarm you, but there is
a giant Julie Cooper on the table.
It's Julie's idea for an image makeover.
A magazine.
I'm assuming you nipped this one
in the bud.
Well, she did her homework.
Ran the numbers.
-The proposal wasn't bad.
-You're not considering this, are you?
Well, there's a lot of ideas
on the table, Sandy.
Well, when you shoot down hers,
be sure to toss this.
It's giving me the willies, okay?
Hi. Hi.
I'm here to pick up a paycheck.
Name's Cohen.
So you must be Alex's new guy.
The famous Seth Cohen.
No. I'm his friend, Ryan.
I'm just doing him a favor.
I really wanted to meet this Seth.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. I'm Jody.
You're the ex.
So you didn't see anything
at the club?
I mean, there were no shady guys
hanging around Alex's office?
Definitely didn't see any guys.
Are we meeting Zach here
or at the comic-book store?
Here. Now, you must have
seen someone.
Tell me this. Who gave you the check?
Tell me everything that happened.
In fact, better yet,
reenact it word for word. Go.
Zach. Hey.
How are you? So good to see you.
-How are you?
-Good. I'm good.
I'm terrible, actually.
I think I freaked Summer out.
I don't know. She bailed on our date.
Now she's doing a girls'-night-out thing
at the Bait Shop.
She's not returning
any of my phone calls.
I don't know. Maybe new comics
will ease the pain.
I feel that pain. Let's go down
to The Bait Shop tonight...
-...and talk to the girls.
-Or we could forget the girls.
Do our own thing.
Have a guys' night out.
-I like my plan.
-We spend every night with the girls.
-Let's try one night without them.
-lt could be kind of fun.
It could be just what I need.
A reinvestment in my manhood.
A timeout to reflect
on what it means to be a man.
-Seth.
-Yeah, I'm in.
Sanford.
Kirsten here? I was hoping
to have a bit of a chat with you both.
It's about this ungodly magazine
of Julie's. You heard about it?
Heard about it?
I got an 80-foot mock-up in my kitchen.
-It's gonna haunt me in my sleep.
-I don't intend to let this thing go ahead.
If Julie launches it, she'll embarrass
herself, the company, the family.
So how you gonna break it to her?
The woman's a warrior, Sanford.
I'm not facing her alone.
-So that's where we come in.
-The three of us form a united front.
Tell Julie that the magazine
is a terrible idea, that she'll regret it.
-What do you say?
-How about that?
I actually agree with you.
-Relax. You're gonna have fun.
-Yeah. Definitely.
Not only am I spending the night
with Marissa...
...but I'll get to see my dad,
who barely acknowledges me.
No. He's gonna be out at dinner.
I checked with Marissa.
So when did you guys meet?
How did you start going out
in the first place?
-Me and Marissa? Come on.
-What?
I mean, were you guys lab partners?
-Fire-drill buddies?
-No, no.
Actually, it was my first night
in Newport. I was....
I was sitting in Sandy's car waiting to
see if Kirsten would let me in the house.
And I walked down to the end
of the driveway...
...and there she was.
We started talking, and....
I don't know, we just...
...connected.
She wasn't like anybody
I'd ever met before.
Until you.
Right.
Have fun.
Hey, do me a favor.
Take care of her tonight, all right?
Okay, Ryan. I'm not 8.
I promise I'll take care of her, Dad.
Or I'll try, anyway.
Please don't feel like
you have to babysit me.
No. That's just Ryan.
He gets very protective. You'll see.
So Summer should be here any second.
Cool.
So this is where you live.
I mean, of course it is.
I mean, it's....
It's really nice.
Thanks.
Yeah. Sit.
Hey, you know what?
How about an icebreaker?
-I don't really....
-Sorry.
-That's totally cool.
-Not that I judge anyone who does.
-It's not something I do.
-Don't worry about it.
Okay.
That must be Summer,
so I'll just go grab the door.
You know, hang out.
Make yourself comfortable.
What am I doing here?
Okay. It is 0700 hours.
Let the record show that guys' night out
has officially begun.
Okay, Seth, 0700 means it's 7 a.m.
Okay, nobody cares that you
were in ROTC. Now, listen to me.
Tonight, Newport is our bitch.
Okay? So let's go out there,
and let's do what guys do.
-Yeah.
-Ryan, what do guys do?
We could head up to L.A. You know?
Hit a club. Go to Vegas.
-Road trip to Tijuana.
-That didn't work out well last time.
But these are good shapes of ideas.
-You want to play video games.
-So bad.
This Summer thing's got me
tied in knots. I vote we stay in.
We should get you out of the house.
It'll take your mind off things.
We can let the fun come to us.
We have all we need for a perfect night.
We've got a working television,
a bevy of comic books.
Lamps. Right? Okay.
That's all you need for a rollicking good
time, so my proposal is guys' night in.
Guys' night in.
-Well, here we are. Just us.
-Right.
This is so much fun.
So, what happens now?
Well, we could walk by the bar,
see if anyone checks us out.
Hello? No boys tonight.
That's the whole point.
Okay, well, we can at least
talk about them, right?
Let's face it. Without that,
we got nothing.
So boy talk. Who wants to start?
You know...
...I'm rethinking
the whole sobriety thing.
You read my mind.
Maybe some tonic and lots of ice
would help.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, burned me a little.
Do what you want
if you need to call him so bad.
What? I had no idea that you were gonna
show up out of nowhere.
I didn't have a chance to tell him
about us.
Why? Are you embarrassed about us?
Sorry to interrupt...
...but there's no paper towels
in the girls' bathroom.
I'm all over it.
Thanks. That was a conversation
I did not wanna have.
Yeah, I know all about those.
I have them with my mom all the time.
The nerve of Alex. She has a secret
boyfriend the whole time...
-...and never gets around to telling me?
-I know, man.
I wanted to celebrate our six-month
anniversary. Summer heads for the hills.
-You've been going out six months?
-This isn't how I imagined our night out.
-Let's go the club and put up a fight.
-Bad idea.
Why? Our girlfriends bailed on us
to go drinking at a club.
Have you seen Girls Gone Wild?
-This is exactly how it begins.
-He's right.
-l' m going.
-Me too.
Seth, l' m telling you as your friend.
Don't do this.
-You know something.
-No. No, I don't. Don't ask me.
Dude. I am a man in the desert.
I'm dying of thirst.
You have a thermos full of Kool-Aid.
Come on, give me a sip.
Did you meet the ex?
-I know you did.
-All right. Yes, I did.
-And who is he?
-He....
-He's a she.
-What?
Who needs a little more?
-Somebody's gotta drive.
-Not me.
Why don't I go track down some coffee?
You're not scary.
-Thanks, I think.
-I mean, before you were, like, scary.
Not like bogeyman scary, you know--
Lindsay, you've got nothing
to worry about.
-Ryan really likes you.
-Y eah.
Can a guy ever get over a girl like you?
Summer, right?
-We're in Comp Lit class together.
-Right.
-I'm sorry. I'm usually asleep.
-Matt Miller.
So where's Zach?
I don't know. It's girls' night out.
You know about me and Zach?
We're on the water-polo team.
Happy anniversary.
You know about our anniversary?
He brought it up in the locker room. Six
months is big. We were talking about it.
So Zach's turning the locker room
into a Lifetime movie.
The water-polo team is very sensitive.
-It's tough to see from here.
-Yeah, always tough to see from here.
You wanna try upstairs?
Yeah. Sure, why not?
I haven't scoped it out yet.
So Alex hooked up with a girl.
It's not a big deal.
My girlfriend dated a girl.
It's a very big deal.
-Only one thing can make it okay.
-You're gonna hook up with a guy?
I repeat. There's only one thing I can do
to make it okay. I need to see this girl.
Because right now my imagination's
just running wild.
-Dude, so's mine. She's hot, right?
-Listen.
I know I'm supposed to be attracted.
I'm supposed to be turned on.
I've read Maxim and Stuff.
But you know what? It makes me feel
like Alex is even more out of my league.
Maybe you should talk to her
when you calm down.
Nope. Got testosterone
pumping right now.
Testosterone being the key ingredient
missing from Alex's previous relationship.
I just need to remind her of that.
Come on!
-This should go well.
-I hate traffic.
You have to think big picture.
This magazine could go national.
America would be fascinated with
the lives of O.C.'s rich and fabulous.
We're all beautiful,
we're all dysfunctional.
Surf, sex and scandal. It's a recipe for
a cultural phenomenon, don't you think?
Well, I would rather hear
what Sandy and Kirsten have to say.
Let's not talk about work anymore.
Kirsten. Why don't we put her
out of her misery?
Julie, it's a lousy idea.
Thanks for rushing to my defense.
Really very touching.
It's my job to remain impartial.
-Objective.
-And cowardly?
Fine. I'll just sit here and get insulted
by a man so ignorant about business...
...he chose as a career
to work for free.
I don't work--
That's pro bono work, Julie.
Why am I defending myself? If you want
a business perspective, ask Kirsten.
I did. She called Newport Living...
...just the thing to keep
the Newport Group living.
-She said that?
-I wasn't that poetic.
Honey, I did some research.
This has promise. I' m so sorry
it had to come out this way.
No. It's my fault. I once again let myself
get caught up in the middle...
...of this nasty game
of Hungry Hungry Hippos.
Well, this time, I'm out.
You're all on your own.
Waiter. He'll take the check.
-I'm gonna check the bar.
-I'll look upstairs.
Seth, we can still turn around.
-Yeah, that's a good idea, Ryan.
-Yeah?
You take the lounge.
-Thanks.
-Hey. So where is she?
-Because I'll totally fight a girl.
-I have a job I'm busy doing.
If you came here for some big, dramatic
confrontation, it's gonna have to wait.
Fine. I will wait.
I don't know what my problem is.
I just get so claustrophobic.
Sounds like maybe
you don't want a boyfriend.
Well, if he's not right for me,
then nobody is.
Zach. What are you doing here?
-Tonight was girls without the boys.
-lt doesn't look like it.
What are you doing here with
Matt Miller? That guy'll hit on anything.
Thanks for the news flash.
-Are you making your rounds?
-Yeah. That's what I'm doing.
-I'm checking up on you.
-Then why are you here?
I don't know. Bad idea.
-Hey. There you are.
My numb is tongue.
You're drunk?
-I think that I need some fresh air.
-That's a good idea.
Let's get you out of here.
Bye.
-Julie took off?
-She insisted on me putting her in a cab.
Apparently, it is my husbandly duty
to support her ideas.
She's got a point.
Support each other no matter what.
It's the name of the game.
Which is why I'll support Sandy
at the board meeting.
Putting the marriage
ahead of the company.
-Bold move.
-Go with Julie on this one.
You won't regret it.
You know, you're not as stubborn
as everybody thinks you are.
Yeah, it's just too much wine.
So how you feeling?
-I feel so great.
-Yeah?
Let's go swimming.
-Come on.
-Hey, swimming in the ocean at night.
Yeah, what's the matter?
Are you scared?
No.
You all right?
Jeez.
-How much did you drink, huh?
-I don't know. As much as Marissa.
-That's a lot.
-Well, I am on a liquid diet tonight.
No dinner too, huh?
Well, in that case...
...you hang tight for a minute.
I'll go grab some greasy fries.
And a lot of coffee.
The Dawn Atwood special.
-Fries sound so good.
-Don't they?
And then we'll go swimming.
It'll be fun.
Because when the weather is cold,
the water is warm.
All right. We'll talk about it
when I get back. All right?
-Okay.
-All right. Stay there, okay?
You all right?
Are you trying to wait me out?
It's not working.
Yeah, it is working.
That's why you're not waiting.
Let's get this over with.
Come in and tell me everything
I've done to wrong you.
-Okay. For one, you lied to me.
-I did not lie to you.
I told you that my ex was in town,
and you filled in the blanks.
Blanks that you left blank.
You know, it's part of your move.
It's kind of part of what you do.
You got your too cool Jem-
and-the-Holograms thing happening...
...and blowing me off
is part of your act.
-You think it's an act.
-It's a crutch.
The hair and tattoos,
whiskey and cigarettes for breakfast.
I've actually seen The Banger Sisters.
Part of it, on cable.
And I know how the story ends.
I'll make sure to Netflix that so I can
be up to speed on your little theory.
Great, you do that. The point is...
...this was really fun for a while,
but it is just not worth it...
...so I will see you.
So, what are you gonna do?
I don't know. Maybe find a new girl
to walk all over me.
Or maybe even be cool to me.
Lindsay!
Ryan! What are you doing?
Lindsay! She's out here somewhere!
Get help!
-Lindsay's fine!
-What?
I just saw her.
She's fine.
She's passed out in Alex's office.
She went looking for you, ran into
Marissa, who was doing the same thing.
Yeah? I can't wait to see her.
What happened to you?
-ls she okay?
-She'll be fine. She's just sleeping it off.
-I should get her home.
-I can do that.
-I think you've done enough.
-Okay.
This is the part
where you blame it on me?
You're right. It was Lindsay's idea
to pound vodka and pass out.
-Good to see someone else messed-up?
-lt was her idea.
-Okay, so it got a little out of control--
-lt always does with you.
You spent last year trying to
drag me down with you. And now her?
You want to make a mess
out of your own life? Fine!
Doing a good job of it, if you ask me.
-No one asked you.
-What did you say?
-Hey, Ryan, let's-- Let's go.
-I'm not leaving her here.
-I'll take care of her. You go.
-Yeah, come on. It'll be fine.
Ryan, let's go.
Just call and let us know she's okay.
Let's get her out of here.
Yeah.
Hey.
Black-and-white milk shake, please.
One.
Zach.
So...
...I'm sorry for being
Ultra Bitch 2000 tonight.
-Tonight?
-Fair enough.
It's just that
my whole dating experience...
...amounts to a six-month angst-fest
with Cuckoo for Cohen.
So when I'm with you,
someone who is sane and normal...
...it's like I was raised by wolves.
-Do you need the drama?
-Well, if by that you mean...
...do I miss the wolves? No.
See, wolves, they pee all over the place
marking their territory. Gross.
But while I'm learning
how to not howl at the moon...
...I need to take baby steps.
-Like this anniversary thing--
-I got it.
And don't worry.
If we're still together when we hit
one year, I'm gonna totally blow it off.
I think that is the sweetest thing
anyone has ever said to me.
Alex called. Lindsay's home.
Everything okay?
I assume so.
We didn't really have a long talk.
She hung up on me.
Which was maybe a hint
that I really screwed things up tonight.
I don't think me and Marissa
will be hanging out any time soon.
I was probably too hard on her, huh?
There were flashes
of the old Ryan Atwood.
It just brings back old issues,
you know. Marissa, my mom--
You don't have to lump Lindsay
in that category.
She was probably just trying
to let loose.
Or Marissa pressured her into it.
I think if Lindsay was feeling pressure,
it was probably coming from you.
I mean, you kind of shotgunned them
into that relationship.
But, I mean, the girlfriend
and the ex as friends?
I think that goes against nature.
-Someone could follow their own advice.
-Y eah.
Y eah, I should apologize.
It's just my pride.
What pride?
-There's nothing standing in my way.
-You wanna drive or me?
-You.
-All right.
And now my wife has given us all
the opportunity to find out.
Ghosts, et cetera, being only
creations of hysteria....
-Hey.
-Hi.
I think everyone wonders
what they would do if they saw a ghost.
If you' re still angry,
you have every right to be.
No, well, that-- That's good to know.
But here's the thing.
I' m not angry at all.
Since I left the law firm, your father's
been grooming me to be his henchman...
...and I've been letting him.
I think, in some way...
-...I've been postponing the inevitable.
-And that is?
Figuring out what to do next.
Sandy, we can still
make your housing idea work.
I'm gonna go on record
recommending the project.
I appreciate that.
But I'd rather you didn't.
Julie's magazine will always
give me the heebie-jeebies.
And business-wise,
it's probably your best bet.
Besides, if I work with you...
...your father will ambush us
every time we try to have a date.
That was the worst date
we've ever had, wasn't it?
A double date with your father
and Julie Cooper.
Sounds like the plot of this movie.
Maybe we shouldn't both be here.
It's potentially too much apology
for one doorstep.
-We're not doing it at the same time.
-That's good.
I don't think the synchronized apology
would work.
It's like you're stalking me.
Yeah. But I'm stalking
with good intentions.
-I came to apologize.
-So did l.
-Marissa's inside.
-Thanks.
And so is Jody. So you and me...
...are outside.
Hey.
Look, I don't know. I--
I was hoping this could be easy.
For you and me to stay friends...
-...you and Lindsay to be friends--
-We all live happily ever after?
Yeah, something like that.
I know it seems like a million years ago
we dated. But it wasn't.
-I know that.
-And, okay, maybe you're over it.
Maybe it doesn't mean anything
to you anymore.
Maybe it never did.
But it meant a lot to me.
You meant a lot to me.
You still do.
It's not like that. I....
I don't know what it's like. Thinking
you and Lindsay should be friends...
-...was a bad idea.
-Why? I like her.
And if you do the math,
she's my stepsister, so....
I guess.
Clearly, it's gonna be strange for us
for a while.
Yeah, I know. You're right.
I'm sorry.
That's what I came here to say.
I'm sorry too.
So you and Jody?
You getting back together?
I doubt it.
She's kind of a pain in the ass.
-But maybe that's my type.
-Right.
So then, I mean, does that mean
we can go back to before? Because...
...I can forget this ever happened.
Okay. I'll wait.
Because that's what adults do.
They wait. So I'm waiting. Adult style.
Hey.
You ready?
Yeah.
I guess so.
Thanks for coming by.
And I'm sorry too.
At last, you've got it all.
Everything I have.
-Even my life.
-Hey.
-Jody went to sleep.
-Cool.
-I think we've seen the last of the guys.
-I wouldn't be so sure.
There's still, like, what,
four minutes of girls' night out left?
I've had enough of girls and guys.
There's an old horror movie on.
Works for me.
Are you cold?