We've exhausted all medical
and scientific evidence.
By that I mean nothing
we can find... no disease,
no hint of disease. Only symptoms.
The brute fact is he's experiencing
so much activity in his temporal lobe...
that it is effectively
destroying his brain.
Enough!
There's only so much bluntness
a mother can take.
- Sorry. I just...
- All you do is sedate him.
You're turning him...
into a zombie.
I know you can hear me, Fox.
- Can you give me a sign?
-  I can hear you, Mom.
Fox?
Mom, I can hear you.
I'm here.
I love you, my darling boy.
Mom, where you going?
Mom? Mom?
Come back, Mom!
Mom!
When in disgrace
with fortune in men's eyes.
Ah, but your mommy
will still love you.
All a mother wants is to...
shield her boy
from pain and danger.
Safe in the world
as he was once in the womb.
But maybe we think a father
demands more than mere survival.
Maybe we're afraid a father demands
worldly adulation.
Success, heroism.
I know you can hear me.
I can always hear you.
Even when my mind is jammed
with a thousand voices,
I can hear you like a snake
hissing underneath.
How the hell
did you get in here?
How does anything I do
surprise you now?
Aren't you expecting me
to sprout vampire fangs?
You've come to kill me.
It'd be better than living
like a zombie, wouldn't it?
I'm giving you a choice.
- What choice?
- Life or death.
Your account is squared
with me, with God,
with the I.R.S.,
with the F.B.I.
Rise out of your bed
and come with me.
I'm dying, you idiot.
If I could get up,
I'd kick your ass.
Don't be so dramatic.
Only part of you is dying...
the part that played
the hero.
You suffered enough...
for the X-Files,
for your partner,
for the world.
You're not Christ.
You're not Prince Hamlet.
You're not even Ralph Nader.
You can walk out of this hospital
and the world will forget you.
Arise.
What... What the hell
are you doing to me?
I'm showing you how to take
the road not taken.
Take my hand.
- Why should I take your hand?
- You can't read my mind?
No. I can't.
- All the voices are gone.
- Take my hand, Fox.
You have to take
the first step.
Take my hand.
I'm your father.
Sleep is a luxury, Agent Scully.
A self-indulgence we have no time for.
- Nor does Agent Mulder.
- How did you get in here?
Getting in is easy.
It's what you do once
you're inside that's key.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- You are the only one
with access to Mulder.
- I need you to use it wisely.
- Like you?
Almost killing him by shooting
him full of phenytoin for
a few moments of lucidity?
It's what Agent Mulder wanted.
He knows what's wrong.
What he wants now is to prove it.
It's why he asked for me, not you.
I don't believe that.
Two years ago your partner was infected
with a virus he claimed was alien.
A virus reactivated in him by exposure
to a source of energy, also alien.
Agent Mulder is living proof of what
he tried so long to substantiate...
the existence of alien life.
But whatever it is,
it's killing him.
And we have to get it
out of him.
You destroy this
and I'll destroy you.
- Scully.
-  Agent Scully,
you need to go to the hospital.
- What happened?
- Mulder's gone. He's disappeared.
There were guards posted here.
A man who's gravely ill doesn't
just get up and disappear.
- I know, I know.
- How did this happen?
- His mother checked him out.
- His mother?
- That's what they're saying.
- Has anybody spoken with her?
I'm leaving that up to you.
It's better I not be involved
any further in this case.
Sir, this isn't just a case. This is
Agent Mulder we're speaking about.
And I'm trying
to help him...
by staying out of this
from now on.
Sir?
I'm in a compromised position.
The less I know about Agent Mulder's
whereabouts and yours,
the better.
The child is father to the man.
You've been asleep
quite a while.
I suspect it'll be sometime before
your sleep patterns return to normal.
Would you like an explanation?
I'm not sure.
While you were lying unconscious
in the hospital this afternoon,
my doctors worked on you.
- Why?
- At some point I realized that...
if the Syndicate didn't kill you,
the F.B.I. would.
If the F.B.I. didn't kill you,
your own misguided heroism would.
There's really
no way out for you.
There's no way for you
to cheat death except by disappearing.
A man can't just disappear.
Oh, we've made
entire cultures disappear.
Like me now, you'll become
a man without a name.
But even while you miss
your former identity,
you'll learn to love
life's simpler pleasures.
Well, that'll be kind of tough
with these on.
When you no longer wanna run,
those will come off.
How do you feel?
I feel better than I did.
I gotta tell Scully.
I gotta tell her.
If you do have contact with her,
you'll put her in danger.
You're entering a kind of...
witness protection program
for want of a better term.
- Can I offer you a cigarette?
- I don't smoke.
Well, maybe now you do.
Don't move.
- Who's there?
-  I don't mean to frighten you.
Albert Hosteen.
What are you doing here?
How did you get here?
- I'm sorry to surprise you.
- Surprise?
That you're standing here...
Last time I saw you
was in New Mexico.
They'd taken you from the hospital.
Your doctors feared the worst.
- I was hoping to see your partner.
- He's missing.
You must save him.
He's very ill.
You must find him
before something happens.
Not only for his sake,
for the sake of us all.
- Where are we?
- Home.
This is your new life.
I don't understand.
You can drive away
right now.
Drive back to Scully and your X-Files
and imminent death.
I wouldn't be surprised
if you did.
But I think you should
take a look around.
I mean, why leave something
behind until you... until you
know what it is you're leaving?
Mulder was taken out of
the hospital just before 2:00 a.m.
His mother's signature
is on the hospital documents.
It's her handwriting.
She checked him out A.M. A...
against medical advice.
It's all legitimate
until you go to surveillance.
This is a camera in the hall
outside Mulder's room.
Here's inside his room.
And two other cameras
on the ward.
We're guestimating there were
at least three others involved.
Check this out.
Where's Waldo?
She's talking to someone.
Yeah.
I know who that is.
Hello?
Anybody home?
They can change your name,
but they can't change
the things you love.
It can't be.
- You're dead.
-  No.
No, just really relaxed.
Scully...
saw you get shot...
on the bridge six years ago.
I was sure you were... dead.
One, uh, well-placed bullet.
A punctuation mark on a man's life and
you get to start a whole new chapter.
I'm fine, son,
aside from a little tennis elbow.
I felt responsible
for your death.
You can let that go.
Clearly I'm alive.
I thought that you died
for my quest.
Yes, along with Scully's sister and
the man you thought was your father...
and Duane Barry and-and
even Scully's mysterious illness...
and on and on and on.
You can let go
of all that guilt.
I'm here to tell you that
you're not the hub of the universe...
the cause of life and death.
We, you and I,
are merely puppets in a master plan...
no more, no less.
You've suffered enough.
Now you should enjoy
your life.
Let me show you something.
That's my wife and daughters.
We live just down the street.
I hope you visit us
for dinner.
Oh. Oh, hey, buddy.
That's okay.
You can build it again.
Just start again.
Okay?
Who's there?
- Who are you?
- Hundreds of little joys...
to open a door and have
a woman beckon you in.
To have her make a fire
and lay the table for you.
And when it's late,
to feel her take you
into her arms.
This is Tina
Mulder. I'm not in to take your call.
- Please leave your message.
This is Dana Scully.
Thank you. As before, you can reach
me at your son's office at the F.B.I.
Thank you.
- Skinner.
Sir, did you send me
this book?
- Excuse me?
- This book?
It explains everything
that I found in Africa,
using the same symbols
that I found on the ship.
Agent Scully, I asked you
not to involve me in this.
It's all here, sir.
A foretelling of mass extinction.
A myth about a man who can save us
from it. That's why they took Mulder.
They think that his illness
is a gift...
a protection against
a coming plague.
I'm sorry, Agent Scully. The assistant
director has given me express orders...
- Not to let you in.
Sir, are you hurt?
Are you cut?
Get on the phone.
Hey!
Stop that man!
Good morning.
- What's wrong, Fox?
There's nothing wrong.
Perfect.
It's all perfect.
What the hell am I doing here?
- You just need some coffee.
- No, I'm... I'm serious.
I have commitments to the X-Files,
to Scully, to my sister.
You think you know
what that means... commitment.
- It's all just childish, Fox.
- Childish?
Yes. You've been a child...
with only the responsibility
of a child,
to your own dreams
and fantasies.
But you won't know the true joy
of responsibility until you
plant your feet in the world...
and become a father.
Wow.
Diana, you... you lay all this on
me after I sleep with you one time.
What's it gonna be like
tomorrow?
- You have to let go, Fox.
- Just like that?
I'm just supposed to slip
into domestic bliss even after
I was dropped here by a man...
I have every reason to believe
left here to carry on his dirty work?
Hey. He lives
the next block over.
We'll go visit
after breakfast.
You told someone, didn't you?
You let the information out.
- What are you talking about?
- A man attacked Skinner in his office.
- For what?
- For what he knows about Mulder.
I haven't told anyone.
What is this?
These are mine!
You've hacked into my files.
What are you doing with these?
- I was having them analyzed.
- By whom?
- The National Institute of Health.
- What?
The material you have there,
encrypted data that describes
advanced human genetics,
where did you get it?
This was not supposed
to go public.
- Wherever you got it,
that data supports
what's happened to Mulder.
It proves what he's become...
biologically alien.
- What are you hiding?
- It doesn't matter.
It matters to someone.
Whoever it is, it sounds
like they're looking for Mulder too.
I wasn't expecting you
so soon.
I thought you'd take
a few days to settle in.
I think you need to allay
his unhappiness with things
he perceives as left undone.
Including why you live
in a bigger house than I do.
I've got quite
a few mouths to feed.
Three grandkids...
and, uh, your sister.
She's been living here
all along.
Living a life you'd forsaken.
He said you were coming.
A father has high hopes
for his son.
But he never dreams his boy's
gonna change the world.
I'm so proud of this man.
The depth of his capacity
for suffering.
Like father, like son.
They think what he has
is killing him,
but in actuality,
he's never been more alive.
- Do you think he dreams?
- Oh, I'm sure he dreams.
- About what I wonder.
- The dreams all men who
are owned by the world have...
a simpler life...
full of small pleasures.
Extraordinary men are always most
tempted by the most ordinary things.
Dreams are all he has now.
- Bum a cigarette, Agent Fowley?
- I don't smoke.
Really? I could swear
I smell cigarette smoke on you.
- Let's cut the crap, shall we?
- Yes. Let's.
Where's Mulder?
Maybe before you go around
blaming everyone you can find
for what's happened to Mulder,
you could think about
what you could have done to prevent it.
I just want you to think...
think of Mulder
when you met him,
think of the promise and
the life in front of him.
Think of him now.
And then try and stand there
in front of me, look me in the eye...
and tell me Mulder wouldn't
bust his ass trying to save you.
I'm thinking, Agent Scully.
I'm always thinking.
It's a chance none of us
ever expected,
let alone hope for.
After all these years, trying to develop
a compatible alien human hybrid,
to have one ready-made.
All these years,
all the questioning why.
Why keep Mulder alive
when it was so simple to remove
the threat that he posed?
There was no way you could
have predicted this.
The fact remains,
he's become our savior.
He's immune to the coming
viral apocalypse. He's the hero here.
He may not survive
the procedure.
Then he suffers
a hero's fate.
Diana?
Fox.
It's time, honey.
How you doin'?
Don't think of the man.
Think of the sacrifice he's making
for all of us... for the world.
It would have been nice
to give him a choice.
You don't think Mulder
would have chosen this?
To become the thing
he sought for so long?
To feel what it's like?
He is what he sought.
We'll never know.
Besides, his task
is almost complete.
I'll carry the burden
from here on in.
I know about the boy.
The boy on the beach.
The vision you go to
in your mind.
We all have such places...
a point of memory and desire.
I've seen him
thousands of times.
I've never seen
what he wants me to see.
Close your eyes.
He's ready to show you,
if you're ready to see.
Wow!
What did you make?
An unidentified flying object.
Hey, what are you doing?
Why are you destroying your spaceship?
It's your spaceship.
You're destroying it.
You were supposed to help me.
- You're running out of time.
Why do you come to me
like this?
Why, when I can't find him?
You don't look in
the right place.
- I don't think you're hearing me.
- You don't know where he is?
Even if I did,
I wouldn't know how to save him.
This science makes no sense to me.
Have you looked for him...
here?
Are you asking me to pray?
There are more worlds than the one
you can hold in your hand.
I hope you see
the poetry in this, Diana.
You're removing genetic material
that may kill your son.
We're forcing the next step
in evolution to save man.
We're doing God's work, Diana.
Without this immunity,
everyone would die.
This knowledge
is God's blessing.
I'll carry on
for Mulder from here.
The patient's come out.
Mulder's awake.
We've got him topped off, but he
won't stay under. I don't think
we can take him any further.
-  Is he feeling any pain?
-  Flat on the monitor.
- Any flatter,
he'd be circling the drain.
-  Okay.
Let's do this thing.
Rest now.
Can you open the blind?
I'd like to take
a look outside.
I wanted you to have peace.
Where's Samantha?
Your sister died
five years ago.
What about Deep Throat?
We've been over this.
He's dead.
Diana's dead.
And Scully.
Scully's dead?
She's dead.
It's time for you
to let go.
They're waiting for you,
if you let go.
Close your eyes, Fox.
We're the last, you and I.
The end...
and the beginning.
There's nothing to be done.
Nothing at all.
Scully. I knew you'd come.
They told me you were dead.
And you believed them?
- Traitor.
- What?
- Deserter. Coward.
- Scully, don't.
- I'm dying.
- You're not supposed
to die, Mulder. Not here.
What do you mean?
Not in a comfortable bed
with the devil outside.
No, you don't understand.
He's taken care of me.
No, Mulder.
He's lulled you to sleep.
He's made you trade your true mission
for creature comforts.
There was no mission.
- There were no aliens.
- No aliens?
Have you looked outside,
Mulder?
I can't.
I'm... too tired.
No, Mulder.
You must get up.
You must get up and fight.
Especially you.
This isn't your place.
Get up, Mulder.
Get up and fight the fight.
- Scully?
Scully?
Mulder?
Mulder, you've got to wake up.
I've got to get you
out of here.
- Mulder, can you understand me?
Mulder, you've got to get up.
I don't know
how much time we have.
- You've got to get up, Mulder.
No one can do it
but you, Mulder.
Mulder, help me.
Please, Mulder.
You... help me.
Scully, what are you doing here?
Actually, I was just
getting dressed to come see you,
but I couldn't find a tie
to go with my victory cap.
Mulder, no work.
You have to go back to bed.
Oh, wait.
Tie goes to the runner.
Scully, I, uh...
I was comin' down to work
to tell you...
that Albert Hosteen is dead.
He died last night
in New Mexico.
He'd been in a coma for two weeks.
There was no way he could've been
in your apartment.
He was there.
We... We prayed together.
Mulder, I don't believe that.
I... I don't believe it. It's impossible.
Is it any more impossible than what you
saw in Africa or what you saw in me?
I don't know what
to believe anymore.
Mulder, I was so determined
to find a cure to save you...
that I could deny
what it was that I saw.
And now I don't even know.
I don't know...
I don't know what the truth is,
I don't know who to listen to,
I don't know
who to trust.
Diana Fowley was found
murdered this morning.
I never trusted her.
But she helped save your life
just as much as I did.
She gave me that book.
It was her key
that led me to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I know she was your friend.
Scully, I was like you once.
I didn't know who to trust and I...
I chose another path,
another life, another fate
where I found my sister.
And even though my world
was unrecognizable and upside down,
there was one thing
that remained the same.
You were my friend...
and you told me the truth.
Even when the world was falling apart,
you were my constant,
my touchstone.
And you are mine.
Ah!