AJell-O salad
with little pear chunks.
It's the Wednesday special at the
hospital cafeteria. I can't escape it.
Listen to you. That didn't stop you
from eating my dessert.
Well, all right.
The profiteroles weren't bad.
- You didn't want me to starve, did you?
He ate mine too.
Daddy, why don't you take this
before my arm falls off.
Thanks, honey.
Everybody?
- One last shot.
- Oh, Dad.
Do you think we can draw the line
at 600 photographs?
Six hundred and one.
Quit griping.
And hold up that eyesore, Robert.
God knows when you're
gonna win another one.
Irv, you wanna think
about staying the night?
- It's awful late
to head back to the city.
- Yeah.
What? I get to stay at the home of
the Bay Area Doctor of the Year?
It's a deal.
Proud of you, Robert.
Up. Hold it up.
Say "cheese."
"Presented to
Dr. Robert Wieder M. D...
"for the great wisdom,
skill and compassion...
he exhibits in
the practice of medicine."
It's gonna look awfully nice
in your office.
What are you thinking?
How this is just
the cherry on top.
How lucky I am.
- What is it?
- Downstairs motion sensor.
You think Dad
tripped the alarm?
The alarm
hasn't been tripped.
You got me.
I'll go check it out.
Irv?
Irving,
is everything all right?
What do you think, Scully?
Is this a name, possibly,
or a code or an anagram?
T-H-E-E-F.
I assume it's supposed to be
T-H-I-E-F. Thief.
Insert your own
Dan Quayle joke here.
Lousy spelling aside, what do you think
it refers to? Who's the thief?
Well, that's certainly one question.
I've got many.
"Mulder,
why are we here?"
Mmm, to be fair,
I might have used the words,
"Mulder,
how is this an X-File?"
You see that, Scully?
You always keep me guessing.
This is Dr. Irving Thalbro, age 66,
found hanged with his throat cut,
his family tucked away and
in bed not 40 feet from here.
Didn't see or hear anything.
Which would certainly shine
the light of suspicion on them.
Except they're the ones
that called it in,
and there's no evidence whatsoever
to link them to the crime.
Which is why the police
are rightly wondering...
if Dr. Thalbro
killed himself.
Except who, then, did this?
Blood pattern doesn't indicate
that the good doctor did it,
who I am assuming could read and write
above a fourth grade level.
I'll admit, Mulder, this is not
an open-and-shut case.
But, uh, it doesn't
make it an X-File.
Well, there is
one detail that does.
This.
Dirt?
Dirt. It's a very powerful
component of hexcraft,
as well as the pattern in which
it was originally arranged.
Check this out.
- Looks like a human form.
Hexcraft, as in putting
a curse on someone?
Murdering them magically?
That's what it looks like to me. Now,
I know what you're gonna say, Scully.
No, hexcraft. I mean,
I'll buy that as the intent here.
It certainly jives
with the evidence.
I say we talk
to the family.
I'll always
keep you guessing.
It was probably
the greatest night of my life.
Till...
Sir, can you think of any enemies
your father-in-law might have made?
Maybe inadvertently through
his medical practice...
or a business dealing,
perhaps?
Everybody loved Irving.
Everyone who knew him.
He was...
No, I can't conceive of it.
Dr. Wieder,
do you have any enemies?
I'm sorry I have to ask.
There was a message left behind.
If it doesn't refer to your
father-in-law, it may refer to you.
Thief?
Are you asking
if my dad's a thief?
He saves people's lives.
He's a good man.
Honey.
If I have any enemies,
I don't know them.
At the home of his son-in-law,
Dr. Robert Wieder,
Dr. Irving Thalbro was found
hanged at 1:48 this morning.
The details are sketchy.
It's my understanding...
that police are treating
the case as a murder.
This is due in part to
core evidence left at the scene.
Hello? Mr. Peattie?
Mr. Peattie,
I know you're in there.
Are you cooking?
You aren't
supposed to be cooking.
You aren't supposed
to be cooking.
That smell like somethin'
you wanna eat?
- Well, what is it, then?
- Medicine.
Oh, all right.
Uh,
just so long
as you're not cooking.
Seems like you could use yourself
a poultice for your back.
Old Peattie fix ya right up.
Be ready later.
- Scully. This dirt we found?
Gas pneumatograph shows...
- Mm-hmm.
pronounced spikes of methane
and sulfur compounds.
The signature of decay.
It's graveyard dirt,
also known as conjure dust.
It's one of the most powerful hexing
elements, whether for good or evil.
Not the kind of stuff you want
to be on the wrong end of.
Uh-huh.
Well, go ahead, Scully.
Keep me guessing.
Kuru.
The-The, uh...
The disease that
New Guinea tribesmen get?
From eating the brains
of their relatives.
I thought my grandpa
slurping his soup was bad.
Practically speaking, Mulder,
Kuru doesn't even exist anymore,
not in New Guinea
and certainly not in the U.S.
But this man's cerebellum
and his triadim...
clearly show signs of it,
Mulder.
I mean, these plaques...
his brain is riddled with them.
Kuru makes you crazy, right?
Yeah, stark-raving, among other things.
But in this case,
stark-raving mad enough to
slit his own throat and hang himself.
Mulder, that's what
his autopsy shows...
from the wound pattern
to-to the blood spray.
- This man did it to himself.
There's no question.
- Unless...
it was inflicted upon him.
The graveyard dirt, the hex.
He was given this disease
so that he would kill himself.
Nan? Honey?
Robert?
Look at this.
It could be
they needed it as evidence.
I'm telling you,
I'm scared.
I can't stay here, Robert.
I can't live in this house anymore.
Lucy can't, not after
what's happened here.
And now this picture of us
is missing.
- It'll turn up.
- No. It doesn't make any sense.
Nothing that's happened here
makes any sense.
It does.
Nan,
listen to me.
Your dad was ill.
He had a kind of
progressive dementia.
That's what
the F.B.I. autopsy showed.
I reviewed their findings,
and I have to agree.
Honey,
we will get through this.
- Oh, my God! Nan, honey!
Oh, my God!
- Nan!
- Dad?
Lucy, call 911.
Call 911!
Nan!
Dr. Wieder?
We understand
you've made a diagnosis.
Diffuse Cutaneous Flesh Moniliasis.
Old World type.
- I take it that's rare.
- In San Francisco? It's unheard of.
Maybe in Central Africa.
- Well, the rarer, the better.
- What do you mean by that?
Someone directed this
to happen to your wife...
just as someone directed
what happened to your father-in-law.
My enemy you were talking about...
the one who thinks I'm a thief?
Agent, you're a doctor.
Explain to your partner...
that no one can direct
a person to get sick.
The dirt you found in your bed
drawn in the shape of a body,
that's indicative of
folk magic.
That's what I believe
is being used against you.
Folk magic?
You mean, like, Babayaga?
Gypsies?
I was actually thinking
less Eastern and more Celtic.
Maybe Scots-Irish
or Appalachian, even.
I'm supposed to
take this seriously?
Sir, regardless
of the particulars,
I think it's clear that
there was an intruder in your home.
And I think it would be
prudent for you...
to accept our protection...
and help us to identify
this person.
Prudent for me would be to
continue treating my wife.
If we don't stop who's causing this,
your treatments won't matter.
So modern medicine
and all it encompasses...
artificial hearts, laser surgery,
gene therapy, to name a few...
all of that arrayed against
a pile of magic dirt?
And you tell me I'll lose.
I have M.R.I. s to look at.
Oh, yeah, Mulder,
win him over.
He will lose unless
we can find a way to stop it.
What do you suggest?
A second opinion.
The truth always hurts,
don't it, Doc?
Who are you?
Is this you?
You did this?
What do you want from me?
Don't you be frettin' none
about that.
I'm gettin'
my nickel's worth.
You're doin'
a fine job so far.
What the hell are you talking about?
What is this all about?
Lynette Peattie.
And don't you be sayin'
you don't recollect her.
Uh-uh.
No, no, no.
Look, if I've done anything
to upset you, I...
It's no use trying to intimidate me
if I don't know how I've offended you!
Tell me!
What makes me a thief?
You be a smart man.
I figure...
you ponder it a while,
it gonna come to ya.
Wait!
No. No matter how I spell it,
there's no Lynette Peattie.
- She's not in my patient file.
- She's not in any doctor's patient file.
No one by that name has ever
been admitted to the hospital.
You think you treated her?
What aboutJane Does?
You treated three
in the last two years.
Pull the files, please.
You remember old Boon.
I know you do.
This mangy, old, ugly dog.
Smart.
People-smart,
and then some.
Oh, he sure did love you.
He crawled up
under that house...
the very day you left.
Wouldn't come out for nothin'.
Not no ham bone, nothin'.
He just knew that
his life was over.
You stole his heart too.
You shouldn't oughta left.
You're there.
I... wanted to thank you.
That poultice worked
a miracle on my back.
I was about to knock and...
and ask if I could get
a little more.
Whatever that is,
it sure is stinky.
Stinky's good.
Good afternoon.
Can I help you?
Yeah, we're looking for some
alternative medical advice.
Well, you've come
to the right place.
I get a lot of folks
fed up with their H.M.O.s.
- Well, actually, we're not here for us.
- Yeah.
Oh! Chief,
back in your pocket.
It's dirt.
It's goofer dust
is what it is.
I don't know what your
intentions are with that.
- Goofer dust?
- Conjure dust, goofer dust.
How would you go about
making somebody sick using that?
We're investigating a murder.
That's why I'm asking.
Oh.
Speaking strictly
in the academic sense,
you'd spread it on or near
your victim to direct misfortune.
So you could give them
any illness you wanted...
- One that you chose
specifically for them?
- Oh...
that's a lot trickier.
It requires
something special.
- A voodoo doll.
- No. They're called "puppets."
Inside, you place three thorns
of a blood red rose,
a strand of hair,
and a photo of your victim.
Maybe other items as well.
Depends on the operator.
Sew it up, say your spell.
How would you counteract
one of these?
Depends on who
you're dealing with.
But if the person
you're looking for...
is powerful enough to bring about
a murder, he's probably charmed.
Which would mean what?
It means just that.
He's drawing on
the energy of a charm.
A source of magic power.
It could be any item,
provided that
it's very important to him.
Something that holds
great meaning for him.
And unless you can separate him
from his charm,
you're out of luck.
Poppin' corn.
You gotta put
the money in first.
Don't look like
no poppin' corn to me.
Put it in the microwave.
Then you get your popcorn.
Oh. Microwave.
I heard tell of such a thing.
It's a true wonder.
Radiation.
Come from the heart
of the atom.
I think it be God's own glow.
You're gonna be very happy,
I promise.
The drug therapy I'm giving her
is working wonders.
Come on.
Come see.
- Mom.
- Hi, sweetie.
- You look good.
- Yeah, right.
But I am definitely
feeling better.
- So how come I have to
go through this thing again?
- Come on.
This thing gives off about
as much radiation as a dental X ray.
- Nothing to worry about.
- I know.
It just scares me.
Wish me luck?
Doctor!
Switch it off.
All done.
How could somebody
orchestrate all of this?
You believe that
your wife was murdered?
It was no accident. There was
no malfunction of the machine.
Yes, I believe
she was murdered.
And you still have
no idea why?
The pathologist found this
branded into your wife's chest.
Sir, we can't help you if
you withhold information from us.
A man came
to see me yesterday.
My age, older, maybe.
Tall.
He mentioned someone named
Lynette Peattie.
I didn't know
who she was at first.
Turns out she was a Jane Doe
I treated last October.
She was in a bus rollover.
Came in amid a wave of victims.
She was the worst off.
I could barely put fluids in fast enough
to keep up with the blood loss.
We were rushing around
triaging people.
Everybody knew
she was dying.
It was only a matter of time.
She was in agony.
This was
my course of treatment.
You gave her morphine.
Lots of it.
I pushed it myself.
She kept screaming,
and her heart rate
kept climbing.
So...
I kept pushing.
I took maybe the last
20 minutes of her life.
It was a fair trade to make
for the pain.
Her father doesn't agree.
What makes you think
it's her father?
He thinks you robbed him
of his family.
And that's why he's systematically
robbing you of yours.
What am I supposed to do?
My daughter Lucy...
You don't do anything.
Let us find a way to protect you.
- How?
- I have an idea where to start.
If Lynette Peattie
was Carlos theJackal,
I would've had an easier time
tracking her down.
There's no birth certificate,
no social security number, nothing.
Better known to the world
as Jane Doe, 6149.
Well, her name shows up
once in the records...
of a Vista Inoculation Program
in 1981.
- The Allegheny Mountains
of West Virginia.
- Deepest Appalachia.
That's when her father,
one Oral Peattie,
refused to allow her to be
inoculated against polio.
But there's no address for him.
There's no record of him whatsoever.
Mulder, why are we
exhuming this girl?
Well, I'm thinking of her
dear old backwoods dad...
and where he gets
all his graveyard dirt.
Here?
His daughter's grave?
The occultist we spoke to
said that the person...
casting these magic spells
was charmed.
That he had a source of power
that was very meaningful to him...
and he kept it close by.
Lynette Peattie's body?
That's my guess.
So as long as her body remains here
resting in peace in the Bay Area,
he remains powerful.
But if we were to
ship it off to Quantico...
Hold onto that.
Mr. Peattie?
Mr. Peattie,
my pain's back.
I was wondering if I could get
a little more of that poultice.
Mr. Peattie?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were home.
All right, thank you.
They'll be there before dark.
- You all set?
- We still don't know
where it is we're going.
We rented a cabin for you. It's
important that you get out of town.
And you believe by our leaving
it will somehow weaken him?
Well, what's important
is that he believes that.
At any rate, if he can't find you,
he can't hurt you.
How do you know
he'll come forward?
Because he hasn't gotten
everything he wants.
Our ownJohn Gillness is on the scene.
San Mateo County health
officials admit they're at a loss...
to explain the sudden onset of the
56-year-old woman's bizarre illness,
but insist there is
no cause for alarm.
- Pretty weird, huh?
- There's been no official diagnosis.
Sources say they believe
the woman contracted...
the rare but deadly
Group 'A"Streptococcus...
- Better known as
the flesh-eating disease.
- Freakin' scary.
We will keep a close watch
on this story and any new developments.
Bathroom's clear!
Clear here!
- Scully.
- Peattie may be on to us.
- What happened?
- I found out where he lives,
only he's cleared out and
he's taken his magic charm with him.
At least as much of it
as he can carry.
My guess is
he's looking for you.
I didn't see
anybody following us.
Well, just keep an eye out,
Scully. I'm on my way.
Okay.
Soon.
Very soon.
What was that?
Stay where you are.
Oh! Oh, God!
- Oh!
- What is it?
I don't know.
I can't...
- I can't see!
- Agent Scully!
- Just stay where you are.
Stay down.
- Oh, Doctor!
- Leave him alone!
- Daddy!
- Get back!
Get back!
Don't make me hurt you!
Can hurt the man
that ain't got nothin'left.
You know who I be now?
Maybe you can recollect
my daughter.
I remember!
I never forgot!
I'm-I'm sorry for your loss,
but I did everything
humanly possible to save her!
The arrogant little man.
I did everything I could!
And when I couldn't do anymore,
I eased her suffering!
By killin' her.
If I be there,
I save her!
You weren't there!
Scary death in some field.
No name on her,
far away from her people.
It wouldn't be right.
So now, little man,
I gonna show you
what be possible.
I'm gonna show you...
an eye for an eye.
You're not gonna hurt
my daughter!
Daddy!
Baby.
- Daddy! Daddy!
Doctor?
What's happening?
- Daddy!
Dr. Wieder!
- You're killing him!
Daddy!
Stop! Daddy!
- Daddy!
Daddy.
Lynette Peattie's body is on its way
back home to O'Neal, West Virginia.
She's going back
to her people after all.
You know, Mulder,
I would have made the same call.
As a doctor,
if I was certain that
I couldn't save her life...
and she was in
that much pain,
- I would've done what Wieder did.
- Mm-hmm.
It seems
pretty clear cut.
Except maybe it's not.
You're wondering if maybe
Peattie could've saved her life?
You do keep me guessing.