God's love will set us free.
And I believe...
if I pray for that love,
if I get down on my knees...
and allow God to enter my hardened,
lonely, miserable heart...
and change me
through and through,
that miracle... will come.
Now, who here
believes that with me?
Do you?
- Do you?
- Yes, sir, I believe it.
Do you?
Well, believe, because God's
love is not just some slogan.
It's a promise...
straight to you from
the Lord Almighty himself.
A promise paid for with the
blood of His only begotten Son,
Jesus Christ of Nazareth.
All you have to do
is believe.
-  Amen!
- God's love will set you free.
Now doesn't that
just lift up your heart...
and make you want to say,
"Glory! Amen!"
Glory! Amen!
Join with me.
Allow the spirit ofJesus Christ...
to show you the way
up to our Heavenly Father.
- Glory! Amen!
Let God's love
free you from your prison...
and deliver you
to His side in heaven.
- Glory! Amen!
Praise His name.
Praise His holy love.
- Glory! Amen!
Glory! Amen!
Do you believe that, Donny?
That God loves a sack of crap like you?
- The Bible says.
- The Bible says you kill women,
cut their pinkies,
you get to burn in hell.
- Glory. Amen. Glory. Amen.
- You listening to me?
God's got a place for you,
all right, you sick puke.
Then where's that
leave you?
Sorry. It's not good enough
for the Illinois penal system.
My hands! My hands!
Life without chance of parole...
for the premeditated
and sadistic sexual murders...
of five Twin Cities women
in 1994.
Donald Addy Faster.
You two put this man away.
Yeah. Someone forgot
to throw away the key.
That's another story.
Right now we have
to apprehend this man.
We'd use all the help you can
give us in understanding exactly
who it is we're after.
Donny Faster
is a death fetishist...
a collector of bone
and dead flesh, of toenails and hair.
It's what floats his boat,
gets him off.
- He's a sick man.
- Sick would describe him.
We found women's fingers
in his freezer. He liked to eat them
with his peas and carrots.
- So it's just women he's after.
- Just women.
Been five years in here thinkin'
about only that. I'm sure he's
worked up quite an appetite.
I happen to know you two agents
have a particular forte,
a thing for... what is it called...
the supernatural?
Now, the circumstances
of the escape...
I promise you there is nothing
supernatural about this man.
Donny Faster is just plain evil.
Case closed.
You didn't look
at the file, did you?
A man escaped from prison.
Not a man.
Donny Faster.
He didn't just escape.
He walked out.
He walked out of
a maximum security facility
and no one seems to know how he did it.
- Isn't that why we're here?
- That's why I'm here.
I don't know about you.
Why are you here?
- Go home, Scully.
- Mulder, this case doesn't bother me.
The man abducted you.
Donny Faster did a number on your head
like I've never seen.
And it's okay to...
walk away.
Mulder, that man does things
to people that no one should
ever have to think about.
It's not a question of if I should stay.
I don't have a choice.
So let's get to work.
Well, this isn't
the first incident.
Two prisoners have escaped
from maximum security facilities...
in neighboring states
over the past year.
At 6:06 this morning,
Donny Faster made it three.
6:06?
And what's so supernatural
about that?
Dozens of witnesses, guards and staff
and no one seems to remember anything.
For a while they didn't even know
these guys were missing.
- Have they been apprehended?
- Neither of the men
have ever been seen again.
I'm a Christian, man.
Then I know you'll
tell me the truth.
Yeah. But I got no idea
about Donny Faster...
or how he broke out.
You and Donny Faster
were in the garment shop
at or about the time he disappeared.
Well, it wasn't just me.
There was a lot of us in the shop.
Yeah, but you had something happen.
You had an incident.
Yeah, something like that.
You cried out to the guards
that you'd cut your hands.
My fingers, man.
I saw them all cut off.
- Others saw them too.
- No, but I felt them cut off.
How do you explain that?
God works in mysterious ways,
brother.
- Glory. Amen.
Glory. Amen.
Glory.
Amen.
Posthypnotic suggestion.
Did you see him?
You mean did I see him raise his foot?
Yes, I saw that.
Programmed behavior prompted
and manifested by suggestion.
In this case, a rhythmic motion
of the hands...
producing an unconscious act
in a conscious state.
It doesn't work on you.
- I know what hypnosis is, Mulder.
- Group hypnosis.
If you're suggesting that Donny Faster
escaped from prison...
using a technique from
a Vegas lounge act, I'd think again.
Messmer was able to hypnotize
and command entire audiences.
So, how would Donny have
acquired this amazing ability?
- I'm not saying that it was Donny.
- Well, then who?
Three inmates are missing
from three separate prisons.
One man has had possible contact
with each of those cons.
The prison chaplain.
Glory. Amen.
- Not God. The chaplain.
Scully, what?
That song,
can you hear that?
Barely.
I haven't heard that song since
high school. That's the second
time I've heard it in the hour.
Well, I think if it was a make-out song,
I think it'd be ruined forever now, huh?
Oh, girl, don't look any further
Looking for something to eat?
Me?
How 'bout... today's special?
- You aren't a narc, are you?
- No.
- You're looking at my hands.
- You need a buff and polish.
What are you,
a freak?
I-I just got out of prison.
Hey, missy,
leave the customers alone!
I'll do it for free.
You just got out of prison
and you wanna give me a manicure?
I'll even do your cuticles.
You receive the
Lord's grace, and this is your thanks.
- What?
- Who do you think got you out of prison?
I don't care.
I'm busy right now.
The grace of God
got you out.
And it's the only thing
that will keep you out.
- I thought you were kidding.
- He's chosen you, Donny.
Later.
- You called them on me.
- No.
Then do something.
I have a car.
- We aren't going to make it to the car.
- It's within his power.
Glory. Amen.
- Glory. Amen.
- Is he here?
- Well, uh...
We're trying
to determine that.
Did you see him?
Well, that's a good question.
We thought we saw something,
but apparently we didn't.
We got a call about
a possible sighting of the suspect.
- Something happened here, huh?
-  Guy got hit by a car.
Prison chaplain,
it turns out.
- A Reverend Orison.
Paramedics took him to the hospital.
He's in pretty bad shape.
Excuse me. Could you
turn that up, please?
- Yeah.
- What you need is a lover
Someone to take over
Oh, girl
Don't look any further
And it's strange
When you think
of the chances
You're lucky to be alive,
Rev. Orison.
- Who are you?
- Special Agent Dana Scully.
Believe in the Lord, Agent Scully.
He believes in you.
That's nice. But my partner and I
are more concerned...
with several disappearances
from maximum security facilities
that seem to involve you.
Don't be concerned.
God has them.
What do you mean?
- Reverend?
- You're a believer, aren't you?
- This has nothing to do with me, sir.
- Has everything to do with you.
You have faith.
Have had faith.
You hear Him calling you,
but you're unsure
of what to do.
It's not exactly
a long shot, sir.
You stand as you do now,
neither here nor there,
longing,
but afraid, waiting for a sign.
Well, the signs are everywhere.
What happened to the inmates, sir?
Everything has a reason,
Scout...
everything on God's earth.
Every moment of every day...
the devil waits
for but an instant.
As it is, it has always been,
the devil's instant
is our eternity.
The good reverend.
How do you do?
Or maybe I should say,
how do you do it?
His is the word.
I am but the messenger
who delivers it.
- Well, this delivery
arrived a little late.
A little late
and a little cold,
as a matter of fact.
I thought you'd want
to see it.
What is this?
Blood of the lamb, Reverend.
The handiwork
of Mr. Donny Faster.
- Ayoung girl he picked up
at the bus stop.
- Oh, Lord.
Where is he, Reverend?
He took my car.
She wasn't supposed to die.
No, Donny was
supposed to die.
You were supposed
to kill him.
That's why you freed him.
God knows
you're capable of it.
Rev. Orison is really
Robert Gailen Orison,
convicted in 1959
of first degree murder.
Served 22 years in Solidad.
God spoke to me.
He told me to look
after Donny.
When God spoke to you,
Reverend,
did He happen to mention
where Donny was headed?
- Where are you going, Mulder?
- To prove that man's a liar.
How do you prove that somebody
isn't being directed by God?
You don't believe
that it happened?
God is a spectator, Scully.
He just reads the box scores.
- I don't believe that.
- You think God directs that man,
directs him to kill?
Donny Faster isn't dead and
we don't know the other inmates
who escaped are dead either.
So, what?
You think God directs him to...
let the prisoners out to kill?
No, but I believe that the reverend
believes what's he's saying...
that it's God
working through him.
Well, plenty of nut bags do.
Has He ever spoken to you?
I'm trying not
to take offense.
What did He say?
Mulder, I have heard
that song three times now.
That may not mean anything to you,
but it means something to me.
- What does it mean?
- I never thought about it before.
It never meant anything
to me until yesterday
when it made me remember something.
What?
When I was 13, my father
was stationed in San Diego.
I was listening to the radio
to that song...
when my mother came in and told me that
my Sunday schoolteacher had been killed.
- Mmm.
- He'd been murdered in his front yard.
And that's the first time I ever felt
there was real evil in the world.
Mulder, Rev. Orison
called me "Scout."
That's the same name
my Sunday schoolteacher called me.
Donny Faster escaped
from prison at 6:06 a.m.
That's exactly the same time
that I woke up yesterday
morning when my power went out.
So, what do you think
that God is telling you?
Yeah, all right. Come with me, Scout.
I'll show you how the reverend
talks to God.
Police are
involved in a four-state manhunt...
for a prisoner who escaped
maximum security in Marion, Illinois.
He was last seen driving
a green 1970...
Chevrolet Impala
with a black landau top.
He is described as
six feet tall, medium build...
It's a cerebral edema.
A swelling of the brain.
A trauma not uncommon with
this kind of head injury or accident.
Except this isn't accidental.
The cause, in fact, as it was stated
to me, is self-inflicted.
There's a small hole here
in the skull...
which allows oxygen
into the brain cavity.
The result of which
is the Rev. Orison has three
times the normal blood volume...
pumping through his brain.
- And he did this himself?
- Yeah.
My guess is he probably did it
when he first got into prison...
when he first learned
how to use its powers.
- "Its powers"?
- There's a theory...
that at this point in human evolution
our mental capabilities...
are limited only by
inadequate blood supply.
In fact, centuries ago
in the Peruvian Andes,
holy men used to physically
remove parts of their skull in
order to increase blood volume,
or drill small holes.
So this hole in his head enables Rev.
Orison to help these prisoners escape?
Yeah.
The practitioners of this...
found that they could perform
certain mental tricks.
One of which they called
"stopping the world."
Nobody can stop the world. I don't care
how many holes they have in their head.
But maybe they can
alter perception of it,
creating a disparate version
of reality which they can then
project through hypnosis.
But why? I mean,
even if you could, why?
Donny Faster is serving a life sentence
without possibility of parole.
That's the final judgment
as far as society is concerned,
but not in the eyes of God...
or in the eyes of a man
who thinks he's God's tool.
Well, then if Rev. Orison
meant to kill Donny Faster,
then why is he still alive?
I don't know. Maybe he unleashed
something that he couldn't control.
Maybe he thought he was
opening the door of perception,
but then unwittingly
he... opened the gates of hell.
What?
Glory. Amen.
- Glory. Amen.
Are you Donald?
Yes.
I'm from Tip Top
Gentlemen Service.
This isn't your place,
is it?
- No. Why?
- 'Cause I was coming up the stairs...
and got stopped by the landlord,
like it's any of his business.
He told me some
Rev. Orison lives here.
- Now, you ain't no preacher, are you?
- No.
Good. They always like
the weirdest things.
You know what I mean?
- You okay?
- Yes.
Something you wanna say?
Love your hair.
What are you doin'?
Is your hair
chemically treated?
My hair?
I don't know
which product to use.
Look, you're not usin' no product.
I'm clean, my hair's clean.
- If you're gonna be that weird
about it, I ought to just leave.
- I'm being a gentleman.
Well, be a gentleman and get me a towel.
I'm gonna get out of here.
It's a wig.
They lied to me.
You lied to me!
- Where'd he go?
- Marshal?
- What?
The prisoner, the man you were guarding
in this room, what happened to him?
He's gone, Scully.
So is the marshal's gun.
You didn't see him?
Let's go, Scully.
-  What is it?
- What does this mean?
- Did you tell him?
- No, I only told you.
He must have, uh, overheard us
when we were talking in the hallway.
I didn't mention
the name of the song.
- I'm sure you did.
- No, I'm sure I didn't, Mulder.
Well, maybe this was
meant for you.
"Don't look any further."
"Whosoever sheddeth
man's blood,
by man shall his blood
be shed."
What are you doing?
Taking you home.
"The wicked
will be punished."
Pray for God's love, Donny.
Find the humility in yourself
to allow God into your heart.
All you have to do
is believe.
Repent.
You'll feel God's love come to show you
the way to His heavenly kingdom.
Are you sorry
for what you've done?
You...
What did you say?
Never... No...
No...
- Why are you crying?
- I can't...
Beg His forgiveness
for what you did to those girls,
for what you did to all
those poor helpless girls.
My violence is always
waiting for an instant...
for when His back
is turned.
You can see it now.
Are you crying for your sins...
or for yourself?
No, Reverend.
I cry for you.
Because you cannot kill me.
You know, it's funny.
When all is said and done, there's...
not much mystery in murder.
And for that,
I owe you an apology, Mulder.
- What do you mean?
- Well, you were right.
I was looking too hard for connections
that weren't there.
Orison was a murderer,
plain and simple.
He liberated those prisoners
so he could bring them out here
and pass judgment on them.
I guess in his own twisted way
he was making good with his God.
Glory. Amen.
Let's go home, Scully.
Donny Faster placed the call
to the police that led us out here.
It's almost like he's
begging us to hunt him down.
This X-File is over. Lying dead there
in a grave he dug himself.
Let's let the U.S. Marshals
take over from here.
Don't look any further, Scully.
- This is Fox Mulder.
Leave a message after the...
- Agent Mulder,
MarshalJoe Danno in Marion.
I just talked to a call girl who I.D. 'd
Donny Faster as an attacker.
Claims Faster got real upset
when she was wearing a red wig...
upset she wasn't a redhead.
This mean anything to you?
I'd appreciate a call back.
Go back to hell!
- Who does your nails, girly girl?
- Let me go!
The only reason why you're alive
is because I asked the judge for life!
is because we didn't kill you
when we could!
You're the one
that got away.
- You're all I think about.
- I'm a federal agent.
You do anything to me and they
will not give you a break this time.
I'm going to run you a bath.
Don't look any further
Now, be good and don't
cause me any problems.
Someone to count on
In a world ever changing
Here I am
Stop where you're standing
What you need is a lover
Someone to take over
- Oh, girl, don't look any further
And it's strange
Oh, baby
Don't look any further
Tonight
We're gonna take it
All night long, baby, daylight
Daylight
I'll still be lookin'
in your heavenly eyes
And we'll go on and on
Don't look any further
Someone to count on
In a world ever changing
Here I am, baby
Stop right
where you're standing
What you need
is a lover
Someone to take over
Here I am, baby
Don't look any further
Further
- Excuse me.
-  Yeah, sure.
If you want to pack some things,
we can get out of here.
- You can't judge yourself.
Maybe I don't have to.
The Bible allows for vengeance.
But the law doesn't.
The way I see it,
he didn't give you a choice.
And my report will reflect that,
in case you're worried.
Donny Faster would have surely
killed again if given the chance.
He was evil, Mulder.
I'm sure about that
without a doubt.
But there's one thing
that I'm not sure of.
What's that?
Who was at work in me?
Or what?
What made me...
What made me
pull the trigger?
You mean if it was God?
I mean, what if it wasn't?