Previously on NClS:
Galib, has Abu infiltrated Sealift?
They are about to. Our radio man,
Pinpin Pula is Abu Sayyaf.
He plans to blow the Cape Fear.
This will be as bad as 9/1 1 .
You didn't know him
when he was wounded
- in Desert Storm?
- No.
He seems to be repeating
that trauma,
the coma that he doesn't wanna
wake up from.
lf Galib had intel on Abu's plans,
did he have time to tell Gibbs?
Maybe. They were together
when the bomb went off.
Let's hope Gibbs comes out
of this coma in time.
Jethro doesn't talk
much about the past.
l know very little about his life
before we met.
- Welcome back, Jethro.
- You were in an explosion.
l remember.
l don't know him.
- You don't know Dr. Mallard?
- Ducky.
Ducky. Do you know Ducky?
l'm disappointed, Jethro.
The last time someone forgot me,
l was a baby.
My mother left me on the ferry
from Orkney to John o'Groat's.
She was on the bus halfway
to Thurso before she missed me.
l've often wondered if l inspired
the Liechtenstein T-shirt.
- ''Oh, God. l left the baby on the bus.''
- Quite.
Remember my telling you that,
Jethro?
l remember the T-shirt.
But not me.
No worries. lt'll come.
Absolutely. Temporary memory loss
is to be expected.
Don't let it worry you.
You breathing comfortably?
Good. Let's switch
to the nasal cannula, Maria.
- Okay.
- You're doing fine.
l'm just gonna to take this off.
Most traumatized brain injuries
produce short-term
retrograde amnesia.
But to erase years of memory,
his medial temporal lobes or
hippocampus should be damaged.
No, his CAT scans
and EEG are normal.
And he remembered the explosion.
And l've never had a retrograde
amnesia patient remember the trauma.
Never.
Okay, there you go.
l don't think
it's retrograde amnesia.
l think it's dissociative.
An emotional repression
of memory?
With no physical damage to the brain,
it must be psychological.
- No.
- But, doctor,
you said Gibbs
hasn't spoken of his past.
- Hardly ever.
- Perhaps it's too painful.
lt could explain
the prolonged coma in '91 .
But the present coma
is the result of an explosion.
How could it be psychological?
What if the latest coma
caused a relapse?
So how are we doing?
Confused.
Let's see if we can clear up
some of those cobwebs.
Do you remember the explosion?
Yes.
But where were you
when it happened?
Kuwait.
l have good news.
Gibbs has regained consciousness.
That's great.
However, there's also a problem.
He has some memory loss.
Retrogressive amnesia
is totally normal after severe trauma.
Happens every time the boss
smacks me on the head.
You know,
l had amnesia after my car crash.
Your bumper car
got T-boned at Legoland, probie?
No, Tony. l told you about when l
totalled my Camaro when l was 1 6.
That day is still a blank to me.
Well, Gibbs' blank
is the last 1 5 years.
To him, it's 1 991 .
and he's a Marine gunny sergeant
wounded in Desert Storm.
He doesn't know
he's an NClS special agent?
l doubt it.
He didn't recognise Ducky.
Wait. lf he doesn't know
who Ducky is, then there's no--
He'll never remember us.
l am sure it's a temporary condition.
ln the meantime,
we have an Abu Sayyaf terrorist
to apprehend.
l really don't know anything more,
Abby.
Can l go visit him?
Not just yet.
His neurologist, Captain Gelfand,
will let us know when he's up to it.
Can l run to the restroom?
l'll come right back.
lf anyone else needs a potty break,
now's the time to do it.
We meet at 1 7 1 0.
You know what that means?
The director's taking over
the investigation.
Probably. But l was thinking if Gibbs
doesn't remember the last 1 5 years,
he'll be a probie.
Gibbs would never let her take over.
Not the old Gibbs.
Probie Gibbs.
- Director Shepard?
- Yes, DiNozzo.
l want you to understand
that in Gibbs' absence,
as the team's senior special agent,
this investigation is mine.
- ls it?
- Yes, it is, ma'am.
And if l were to dispute
that assumption?
Then you would be a fool.
And you are no fool, director.
This will be a long,
tough investigation.
You're overloaded as it is,
and no one knows this team
better than me,
except for the boss.
Which evidently isn't me.
l was speaking, of course,
of the team boss, Gibbs.
You are the agency boss.
Not if you keep telling me
what l can and cannot do.
- l would never do that, ma'am.
- Then what is it that you're saying?
You take care of the big picture,
and let me handle the two-reeler.
l always intended to, Tony.
Then why did you make me say
all that just now?
l just wanted to see
if you had as much guts as Gibbs.
What's the first thing you remember
after the explosion?
Did you know when Jethro
was married he had a daughter?
No, that's not possible.
l know all three of Jethro's ex-wives.
They had no children.
With his first wife, Shannon, he did.
They married in '82
and had a daughter, Kelly,
who was born in '84.
l can't believe it.
There's more.
They were murdered when Jethro
was fighting in Desert Storm.
Shannon witnessed the shooting
of a Marine in Oceanside.
She identified the killer
as Pedro Hernandez,
a Mexican drug dealer
working Camp Pendleton.
An NlS agent was assigned
to protect her.
A sniper shot him in the head
while he was driving their van.
He died instantly.
Shannon and Jethro's
8-year-old daughter Kelly
were killed in the crash.
That is so awful.
Kelly looked a lot like Jethro,
didn't she?
Yes, a bit.
She's a beautiful child.
Very.
So was Shannon.
Jethro always did like redheads.
Was Hernandez ever caught?
No. He fled to Mexico.
NlS tried to extradite,
but the Mexican authorities
always claimed they couldn't find him.
lt's in our cold case files.
Well, you can close it.
- What do you know?
- Jethro would have pursued
the killer of his wife and daughter
to hell and back.
Jethro got his revenge.
After conducting the autopsy,
Ducky is virtually certain
Abog Galib was inside the oil drum
when the explosive detonated.
Why would he be
in a laundry oil drum?
Maybe he was looking
for his laundry.
- This is serious, Abby.
- Listen to the pot call the kettle black.
- Got that right, didn't l?
- No.
Yes.
Probie,
why was Galib in that oil drum?
He was hiding.
- From who? Gibbs?
- Maybe. He ran from Gibbs,
even though the plan was
to get arrested in front of the crew.
Another question.
How did Pinpin Pula know
Gibbs and Galib
would be in the ship's laundry?
Right. Because they would have had
to put the bomb inside the oil drum
- before they got there.
- Gibbs knows.
Gibbs also thinks
the Giants won the Super Bowl
and Dances with Wolves
is an Academy Award nominee.
- l loved that movie.
- Me too.
Those Native Americans
were so macho in their--
Enough.
Abby, l want a reenactment
of the explosion, okay?
Using crime-scene photos,
measurements,
- Ducky's--
- Ducky's autopsy findings?
l know how to do
a computer reenactment, Tony.
Ziva, what did you get out of the cook,
what's-his-name?
Alon Atu. From the same
Filipino village in Basilan as Pinpin.
He's hardcore Abu Sayyaf.
- He won't talk unless l--
- No torture.
He won't talk.
- Try.
- Okay. But you're tying my feet.
- Hands.
- Those too.
McGee, Pinpin's photo
get added to the BOLO?
- Yes, Tony.
- Sealift Command get it?
They are faxing it to all 1 1 0 ships.
No way he's gonna infiltrate Sealift.
He blew up Galib
and put Gibbs in a coma.
Rule Number 3:
never underestimate your opponent.
- No, actually Rule Number 3--
- DiNozzo's Rule Numero Tres, probie.
Gotcha.
Never underestimate your opponent.
Hey, Galib.
Today, technology stocks--
He's trying to catch up
on 1 5 years by watching TV.
Jethro hates television.
He can't believe
we're still fighting in lraq.
He's not alone.
Does he remember being
an NClS special agent?
No.
Dr. Mallard's still a stranger to him.
He won't know me then.
Ducky worked with him
years before l did.
Well, who an amnesiac remembers
depends on their prior relationship.
Have you found any Marines
he served with in Desert Storm?
Two so far. One's dead.
The other's a
regimental commander in lraq.
Well, Gibbs recalls visiting his wife
and daughter's graves.
So his memory is up to at least
June of '91 ,
when he was released
from Bethesda.
He joined NlS that August.
How about somebody he knew
at NlS?
Special Agent Michael Franks
headed the murder investigation.
l'll start with him.
- Thanks, Todd.
- When are you coming to see him?
Tomorrow.
l'll be here.
Special Agent Franks retired in '96.
He left no forwarding address
or phone number.
- Yes, he did.
- He did?
Find out where OPM
mails his retirement cheques.
l just got paid.
Then you can pay me
for the groceries.
You owe me 320 pesos.
Your hand is greasy.
- Who you calling?
- Operator.
- l don't know.
- How may l help you?
Collect call
from Senor Miguel Franks.
- One moment.
- They called you at the cantina.
- Who called me?
- Connecting.
Who the hell is this?
Director Shepard's assistant,
Mr. Franks.
- Director of what?
- NClS, sir.
Why the hell didn't you ask me?
They said it was muy importante.
What is the problema? lt's free.
- Speak.
- One moment. l'll connect you.
Mr. Franks?
How many damn assistants
does the director have?
- Just one.
- Then who the hell are you?
Director Shepard of NClS.
Charlene, is this you?
No. My name is Jenny Shepard
and l am director of NClS.
- Thank the Lord.
- That mean you approve?
Means all my thoughts
at early retirement was a mistake,
just proved themselves wrong.
l didn't call you to discuss
your opinions of a female director.
Didn't think you did.
l need your help,
Special Agent Franks.
Ain't been that for 1 1 years.
- Goodbye, director.
- Leroy Jethro Gibbs.
Can you imagine
how scary that would be
to lose the last 1 5 years of your life?
- Oh, my God.
- What?
You'd still be in high school.
Zits. Braces. Raging hormones.
l used to walk around all day
with my notebook in front of my--
ln front of your what, McGee?
The laundry room is off.
lt should actually be
3.962 metres wide. Not 26.
- Better?
- Yeah.
Gotta be accurate.
Absolutely. So was it
one of those tiny spiral notebooks
or one of those big three-ring binder
kind of ones, Timmy?
And where were you 1 5 years ago,
Abby?
So where did you find Gibbs?
Afraid l'm gonna find out--
- What was that for?
- Distracting me.
- l was not distracting you--
- Gibbs.
Between the dryer
and the bulkhead.
A little closer to the bulkhead.
The autopsy report indicates
that Galib was sitting on the bomb.
Which consisted of 1 1 3 grams
of Semtex.
You can compute the amount
of Semtex used that accurately?
l am a scientist, McGee.
l can compute anything accurately,
including the size of the
notebook required to--
Stop.
Can you detonate the bomb,
please?
Sorry.
l forgot to tell you l added sound.
Yeah. Can we try that again
without sound?
Yeah, it was a little loud, huh?
Yeah. And let's go frame-by-frame
so we can see what happened.
Of course.
ln the first microsecond,
less than the time
it takes for you to blink your eye,
the bottom of the barrel
and Galib's lower body are atomized.
The oil drum is disintegrating,
but retains enough integrity
to blow what remains of Galib
into the overhead.
ln the following microseconds
the oil drum disintegrates.
Galib is impacted into the overhead
and Gibbs is...
- ...dead.
- Dead.
lf Gibbs had been standing
when the bomb detonated,
he'd have been blasted into the
bulkhead and shredded by shrapnel.
Gibbs had to duck for cover
before the bomb went off.
- He knew.
- Yeah.
What's wrong with this picture?
Nothing. McGee and l triple checked
all the numbers to make--
Not your picture.
Did l make another idiomatic mistake?
No. You mean something's wrong
with what we know.
Exactly. We know Galib ran.
We know Gibbs pursued him.
We know they were
in the ship's laundry.
We know Galib sat on a bomb
inside the oil drum.
And thanks to Abby and McGee,
we know Gibbs knew
that a bomb was about to explode.
Oh, and we know Pinpin,
a missing crewman on the Kamir
Bakir is an Abu Sayyaf terrorist.
Probably the one who planted
and detonated the bomb.
You left out Pinpin Pula means
''rice paddy dike'',
but other than that,
damn good summation.
- Thank you.
- So as Ziva said,
what is wrong with this picture?
Gibbs knows.
But he doesn't remember.
Jethro?
Shannon?
No, Jethro. lt's me, Jenny.
You still don't remember me?
Maybe.
l'm Jenny.
We were partners.
After Shannon died.
Yes.
Did l marry again?
Three times.
- No way.
- Afraid so.
Oh, you're an ex-wife?
Oh, God no.
l'm the director of NClS.
For a moment l thought
you were somebody else.
You remembered us making love,
didn't you, Jethro?
At least that's a start.
Do you recognise this man?
lt's like a name on the tip of my tongue
and l can't remember.
- Calm down. lt'll come.
- lt's important, isn't it?
- Yes. Very.
- lt's life or death, right?
Don't get upset, Jethro.
You won't remember.
Give me a name.
Pinpin Pula.
That's not his name.
That can't be his name.
- Are you sure?
- No. l'm not sure.
l don't remember.
How can l be sure?
- What's happening?
- l'm sorry. lt's my fault.
1 0 milligrams of morphine.
Agent Gibbs, your blood pressure
is spiking.
l'm not Agent Gibbs.
l don't know Agent Gibbs.
l don't wanna know Agent Gibbs.
l want my family. l want Shannon.
l want...
...Kelly.
l miss them.
l miss them so much.
Normally we'd move you
to a regular room, but for once
the hospital is full up,
and lCU isn't.
Having the sound off
isn't gonna help your memory.
Nothing new. Same war.
Same crime. Same politics.
Aren't you surprised The Terminator
is the governor of California?
No. The Gipper was president.
l'll be right back with your dinner.
And none of that baby food, okay?
A steak. Rare would be nice.
And French fries, please?
Maybe tomorrow.
Tomorrow l won't be here.
Hello, probie.
My brother and l
married the same woman twice.
- Twice.
- She was a hell of a woman, probie.
Hey, boss.
Damn, you got old, Marine.
Have you looked in the mirror lately?
lf you hadn't been in a coma...
They're dead, Mike.
Shannon and Kelly,
they're both dead.
l know, Jethro.
lt can't have been 1 5 years.
Can it?
God, it feels like l just got the news
in Kuwait a couple of months ago.
You investigated Shannon's murder.
That's how l met you.
Camp Pendleton.
You were
the special agent in charge.
Yeah.
l became an agent because of you.
You left the sniper folder
on your desk so l could--
So l could join NlS.
l liked the blue better, boss.
NClS. The Navy changed the name
that same year.
1 990? 90...?
Two.
We investigated crime scenes.
l investigated crime scenes.
You schlepped.
ln Nam l packed twice
what you're carrying
through monsoon mud
with Charlie shooting at my ass
and still went faster than you.
You taught me how to be an agent.
No. l didn't teach.
You observed.
Nineteen U.S. servicemen killed,
37 2 wounded.
Khobar Towers.
Semper fi.
You warned them about Bin Laden.
They didn't listen.
And you quit.
l didn't quit.
l retired.
You were pissed
that they wouldn't listen, Mike.
Pissed that all Clinton did was lob
a couple of cruise missiles
at al Qaeda camps in Afghanistan.
You quit, Mike.
l didn't get calluses on my ass
flying from Mexico to argue, Jethro.
Okay.
You're right. l'm sorry.
Never say you're sorry.
- lt's a sign of weakness.
- Why are you here, Mike?
Your director called me in.
What's with the female
NClS director crap?
l don't know.
l only remember Jenny as a--
- Jenny?
- Yeah.
Jenny.
She said she was my partner.
What kind of partner?
You can't smoke in here.
l forgot l was in a hospital.
lt's against the law to smoke
in any public building.
You're kidding.
Another good reason
to live in Mexico.
You were right, Dr. Mallard.
For once?
- No, doctor. You--
- What am l right about this time?
Galib and the oil drum.
Abby's computer re-creation looks
exactly like he's been shot
from a cannon.
Well, it's a risky occupation
even without explosives.
They don't use explosives
to shoot people out of cannons?
A man of your age and education?
Really, Mr. Palmer.
l know that they don't use
high explosives.
l thought maybe black powder.
Compressed air
or spring-driven catapults
shoot our intrepid
cannonballer into the air.
David ''Cannonball'' Smith
set the record.
Yes, he even was fired across
the Mexican-United States border.
He carried a passport,
although today one wonders why.
lt's a sad fact that 60 percent
of all human cannonballs
are eventually killed.
Well, if they don't use explosives,
then why do so many of them die?
They miss the net, Mr. Palmer.
They miss the-- Oh, my.
What is it, doctor?
Galib wasn't sitting in the oil drum.
He was stuffed in it.
Look.
The neck bone's cut.
Cervical vertebrae was cut
very deeply.
You were slashed from ear to ear,
weren't you?
A machete or a bolo knife.
Yes, l believe
the Filipinos call it a parang.
Whatever they're called,
it answers one of our questions.
And poses a new one.
lf Galib was dead--
Who did Gibbs follow
into the laundry?
- Clear.
Got a pulse.
Give him a mil of atropine.
- Got him at 82 over 58.
- Getting better, ladies.
Blood pressure is coming up.
Death is not my jam.
You haven't touched your dinner,
Special Agent Gibbs.
No steak tomorrow
if you don't eat your Jell-O today.
You got your knife, Mike?
Security took it at the airport.
Was it more than three inches long?
They changed that rule after 9/1 1 .
9/1 1 ?
September 1 1th, 2001 .
Hey, boss. lt's '96
and you just retired.
Damn, this is good.
l owe you.
Had to be a hijacking, huh?
They never change security
until it's too late.
Al Qaeda hijacked four airliners.
Two hit the World Trade Centre.
One the Pentagon.
Fourth was to take out
the White House.
Some gutsy passengers
fought them.
They went down in Pennsylvania.
Twin Towers are gone.
Pentagon's fixed.
Three thousand some dead.
Nearly as many wounded.
Sir?
- Are you all right?
- He's okay.
Got some bad news.
That nurse is right.
l'm not ready for a steak yet.
Well, tell me we did more than
toss a couple of cruise missiles.
We did more.
Bin Laden?
- l don't know.
- How the hell can you not know?
Remember that beach
in Baja we fished?
Yeah. South of El Rosario.
l built a little place there.
No TV, no radio, no newspapers.
l fish. l drink beer.
Listen to old eight-track tapes.
Drive to a cantina up the coast
when l want company
when the pickup's running.
This is the first time
l've been to El Norte in 1 0 years.
Don't ask me for a sit-rep, Jethro.
l don't know.
You don't wanna know.
That's right. l don't wanna know.
You feel guilty because you quit.
lf you hadn't quit
maybe you're the one that stops it.
You didn't quit.
Hey, Galib. What are you up to?
Stretching my legs.
lt's too windy on deck.
Hey, why don't you join
the poker game tonight?
You never leave
that damn radio room.
l talk to ham radio operators
at night.
And you'd rather do that
than play poker?
- They're all girls.
- Right.
You insist this is Pinpin Pula.
lnsist. Yes.
l like this word.
l insist this is Pinpin.
l don't believe you.
Why would l lie to you
when you threaten to kill me?
lt is not a threat.
l will kill you if you lie, capitan.
l believe you.
l'm the one who has doubts.
lt is Pinpin. l swear.
That's not loaded, is it?
Would Gibbs allow Ziva
to carry a loaded weapon in there?
- No.
- And l'm not Gibbs, right?
So, capitan.
You're positive?
l am positive. Absolutely positive.
How many times do l have to tell you?
Once more.
- Take a good look.
- l don't need to look.
The man was on my ship
for months.
lt's Pinpin Pula.
Was he Abu Sayyaf?
Yes. He was Abu Sayyaf.
- Who ran from customs?
- Yes. Yes. He ran when your guy--
You knew it was Pinpin,
not Galib, at the custom's gate.
Yes, l knew. l knew.
They paid me. l was quiet.
They paid me to be quiet.
But Pinpin never told me
there was a bomb.
l never knew that. l never knew--
That's the NClS lD photo
of Special Agent Abog Galib
that l showed Gibbs.
What's your point, DiNozzo?
A scary one, director.
Captain Mahir admitted to Ziva
that Pinpin passed himself off
as Galib at the custom's check.
And Gibbs would have
expected Galib
to change his appearance
going undercover.
Growing his hair, maybe a moustache,
dirty himself up.
So when Pinpin handed him Galib's
passport it was good enough.
- To pass the mustard.
- Muster, not mustard.
Galib's documents are vetted
to get him on any crew in the world.
lncluding the Cape Fear
or Cape Horn.
We sent a second BOLO
with Pinpin's photo.
Both ships confirmed,
he was not onboard.
Send it again a.k.a. Abog Galib.
Get me the crew rosters
- from Sealift Command.
- On it.
DiNozzo, call MTAC.
l want the NSO, Pentagon, FBl, ClA,
hell, everyone on ASAP.
My gut tells me
we're missing something.
Gibbs.
Yeah, Gibbs.
- Yeah?
- Ziva.
- Do we work together?
- Yes.
l'm a Mossad officer
attached to your team.
Mossad?
When did they start doing that?
lt's been a year.
Don't feel bad.
l worked with that M.E.--
Ducky. 1 0 years.
And you don't remember him.
Do you always finish
people's sentences?
Only when l'm in a hurry.
Abu Sayyaf is planning
a terrorist attack on the Navy.
- lt will be as devastating as--
- 9/1 1 .
You remember 9/1 1 ?
My boss told me.
- Director Shepard.
- No. No, my boss.
lt doesn't matter. What can l do?
Remember.
l've been trying to since l woke up
in this room.
Well, try harder.
Good. That's a start.
- What is?
- The old Gibbs stare.
You gave it to all of us.
McGee, Tony, me.
What are you talking about?
Ari.
Ari killed Kate.
And l--
l killed Ari.
Your brother.
Yes.
You killed your brother...
...to save me.
- l'm sure he remembers you, Ducky.
- Ziva's driving him here now.
l don't know.
Maybe she pulled her signal in.
- Ziva's bringing him.
- He's coming back.
- He will remember you, absolutely.
- He insisted.
Any minute now.
- Boss.
- McGee.
- Boss, no, l'm McGee.
- Gibbs.
Hey, Abby.
l do remember you, Abs.
Ducky, how can l forget
your mother left you on a bus?
l have no idea, Jethro.
- Should you be out, Gibbs?
- l don't have time.
l'll talk to you both later.
l should have known it wasn't Galib.
Oh, no.
l'd have made the same mistake.
Well, yeah, DiNozzo. l know.
That's why l'm so pissed.
You didn't forget me.
The Cape Fear is loaded
with 20,000 tons of munitions,
Deputy Director Welch.
Which is why we cannot permit her
to reach Gibraltar
without boarding
a Navy search team.
Agreed. But if that frigate signals a
heave-to and prepare to be boarded,
Pinpin Pula will blow the Cape Fear.
No one will survive.
lf he's on board
and if he's a suicide bomber.
You're risking 19 civilian lives
on ifs, Director Welsh.
ln the Med he could explode
near a cruise ship.
Nineteen will seem
an acceptable loss--
No death is acceptable
when it's unnecessary.
Deputy Director Welsh,
Special Agent Gibbs.
This terrorist isn't after
a cruise liner.
lslamic terrorists love soft targets.
No, he wants
the Marine assault ship
the Cape Fear's replenishing
in the Gulf.
You don't know what he wants.
He's a terrorist.
- A cruise ship, the Suez Canal--
- He told me.
He told you?
Pinpin Pula is an arrogant
son-of-a-bitch.
He thought the bomb
he'd planted would kill me.
So he's not a suicide bomber?
For God's sakes,
order that frigate to break off.
l can't do that.
ls everyone up there
as stupid as you?
Pinpin Pula is on the Cape Fear.
He's the radio man.
He intercepts every BOLO
we send him
and he replies ''No Pinpin here.''
We got that, Special Agent Gibbs.
lt's why we didn't communicate
with Cape Fear until...
...now.
Jeff. Thank God you're there.
Can you get your SEALs
onboard without being seen?
We can execute a HALO insertion
within 1 0 hours.
The Cape Fear will have entered
the Med. That's unacceptable.
lf anything happens,
it'll be on some tourist video camera.
The sailors on that frigate
have video cameras.
We can confiscate those videos.
What?
You don't want this being seen?
An accident at sea
is better than an act of terrorism.
lt's too late.
Cape Fear, heave-to.
Stand by to be boarded
for inspection.
Heave-to. Stand by
to be boarded for inspection.
You bastard.
l was wrong.
You weren't wrong.
l was angry at Mike.
l never understood
how he could quit...
...until now.
Oh, l got them, boss.
l got them from the medics
when they took you.
Appreciate it.
You'll do.
lt's your team now.
Tim, you're a good agent.
Don't let him tell you otherwise.
l won't, boss.
Gibbs.
l owe you, Ziva.
l'll collect, Jethro.
- Give me a ride home, Duck.
- Of course.
Semper fi.