Morning, Phil.
Tom, how you doing?
It's almost Friday.
Rough week to be selling insurance?
- You want me to tell you about it?
- No, thank you, Tom.
Excuse me.
- There's a bakery around here?
- Yeah, it is two blocks up,
and make a left.
Thanks.
My God.
He just ran in the street. I...
Did anyone else see that?
I couldn't stop...
Somebody call an ambulance!
.: Team UnderCovers :.
NCIS Los Angeles 1x23
- Burned -
Last night,
I'm having a drink at the place
Macy took me
after my first shootout.
Just wanted some alone time.
But this guy walks over.
Attractive, well-dressed, bonus points
for taking the lead. You know the drill.
All too well.
Guess what he used as his opener.
"Hi. My name is Mr.
"I Have No Idea What I'm In For.
Can I buy you a drink?"
See? There wouldn't have been
anything wrong with that.
That's not what he said.
"Hey there.
"Noticed your boots.
"Takes a girl with a unique style
to pull that off."
"Unique style"?
As in weird? As in ugly?
- The boots were completely normal.
- The boots don't matter.
He was running game on you.
What?
Game.
The art of seduction.
He offered to buy you a drink,
he'd be looking for approval,
- but he turned the tables on you.
- Putting me on the defensive.
And trying to earn his approval
on a subconscious level.
It's game.
That stuff doesn't work on me.
At least you didn't give him
your number.
Right?
Oh, boy.
Have you seen Callen today?
This guy buy you a drink?
Told me he'd let me buy him a drink.
Game.
Kept checking his phone
like he had better places to be.
- Game.
- Leaned in for a kiss
15 minutes after meeting me.
Definitely game.
At least you didn't let him.
- Right?
- No.
Who do you think taught Mr. Beal
to do that?
- What's up, Hetty?
- Agent Callen's in trouble.
He enacted
the Beauregard Protocol
via text message.
His current cover's been blown.
- How did this happen?
- That's not clear for the moment.
The only thing we know for certain
is that our operations
have been breached.
As of this moment,
we are not to make contact
with him...
That means you,
Mr. Hanna.
Callen's message to Hetty
also contained a location in Venice.
Intersection of Horizon
and Speedway.
That's two blocks
from his rooming house.
This is traffic cam footage pulled
from that intersection
approximately 15 minutes ago.
I'll call Deeks,
make sure LAPD knows
we'll be handling this discreetly.
Eric, pull up everything you've got
about this guy.
According to initial reports,
the dead man's name
was Michael St. Paris.
No criminal record.
Employed
by Northgate Elite Security.
They're a private investigation firm.
Specialize in surveillance work.
He was running a tail.
G caught him, so St. Paris bolted.
I'll call Northgate
and see who hired them.
Callen left the crash scene
almost immediately.
He must have stuck to blind spots and
moved fast, because no cameras got him.
Also, his phone went dead
right after he sent that alert to Hetty.
Off the grid.
Could this have anything to do
with Agent Macy's murder in Annapolis?
It's unrelated.
What's Callen going to do now?
What he does best.
Become a ghost.
So we can't find him.
Not until he's ready to be found.
Northgate said an unidentified man
hired them over the phone
to keep tabs on G's movements.
A single payment was sent
as a cashier's check.
Firm didn't ask any questions.
How long was the tail active?
G caught their man within minutes.
The firm was only tasked
with surveillance. No background.
They don't know anything about NCIS
or Callen's identity.
All they got from the man who hired them
was Callen's name and address.
Hey, buddy.
Buddy,
weirdest thing just happened.
Guy just called the store. Says he wants
to talk to my most recent customer,
which is you.
Yeah?
Mr. Callen.
Or do you prefer
Special Agent?
Sorry, bud. Wrong guy.
The pay phone on Ocean Walk
and Sunset.
You got three minutes.
And Mr. Callen,
I know what the "G" stands for.
- That's for me.
- All right.
Okay, I'm here.
- Who is it?
- My name is Eugene Keelson.
I don't believe
we've had the pleasure yet.
We haven't.
So, who are you?
Someone who knows more
than just your name and address.
I have answers.
And the name
of the individual who hired me
to uncover every detail about you.
I just got a message from Callen.
He's at a pay phone at the corner
of Ocean Walk and Sunset.
I'm initiating a trace
now.
Okay, I'll bite.
What do you know?
A wealth of information
that I think you'd be interested in.
What?
And I'm willing to share
this information in exchange
for a small favor.
What makes you think
you've found something I haven't?
Because I have access to things
you don't even know exist.
See, you haven't been asking
the right questions.
This goes deeper than your name,
your family.
You've been asking who, when
maybe you should start asking
why.
How small is this favor?
Caller disconnected.
Five seconds away
from triangulating his location.
He knew what we're doing
as we're doing it.
Impressive
Some people play checkers.
We both play chess, don't we?
You say you got answers.
Show me.
Underneath the pay phone.
You'll find an envelope. Open it.
Does that qualify as proof,
Mr. Callen?
How did you get this?
You need to decide if you're going
to do this favor for me or not.
What you want me to do?
You see the flash drive?
Deliver it to some clients of mine.
Some Bulgarians.
The location is inside the envelope.
You give them the flash drive
in exchange for a cash payment.
Who will the Bulgarians think I am?
Me.
- Will they expect an accent?
- No, they think I'm American.
But, be warned,
if you are unable to convince
my clients that you are, indeed
Eugene Keelson,
they will not hesitate to kill you.
You having second thoughts?
I've been set up before,
this is pretty much the way it feels.
If I can get to you,
how easy do you think it would be for me
to get to the rest of your team?
NCIS has been compromised.
The only way you'll find out how badly
is by doing as you're told.
Where do I bring the cash
after the deal?
I'll contact you.
You have 30 minutes
to get it to the Bulgarians.
If you contact anyone else,
our deal is off.
If you try to de-crypt the drive,
- Keelson...
- If you ever wanted to find out
the truth about yourself,
now's your chance.
Do you understand?
Your new outfit looks sharp,
but I'd lose the baseball cap
if I were you, Mr. Callen.
I was able to triangulate the source
within one block of the pay phone,
but whoever it was
disconnected just in time.
Pre-paid burn phone, most likely.
Guy's probably already trashed it,
and now he's...
Server breach alert
in the Ops Center?
Hold on...
I gotta I.D. this and be sure.
- Is it related to Callen's call?
- No, no, no, totally separate.
Trojan horse virus. Conficker variant.
F-type strain.
This is a serious attack.
I'm opening firewalls to block it
from accessing any more of our system.
What's happening, Eric?
It's broken through the firewalls.
I'm losing control of a system.
Can you stop it?
It's starting to access our files.
I know,
I can route it in from another segment.
Turn the system off,
Which one?
All of them.
We're going dark.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are officially
off-line.
We're blind.
And if G tries
to check in with us...
He'll get a standardized
prerecorded service error message.
He's out in the cold.
Alone.
The number you have reached
is not in service at this time,
You have reached a number
that is not in service.
Please check the number
and try your call again.
I'm Marinov.
Keelson.
My invitation said,
casual, but... okay.
Right there. Beautiful.
I recently spoke to our mutual friend
in Chechnya.
He says your source inside the FSB
has proven
quite valuable to the cause.
I don't discuss friends or sources.
Better for everyone that way.
I appreciate a man
who's all business.
I appreciate a good client.
You got some money for me?
Show me the flash drive first.
I want to verify the information.
Knock yourself out.
Satisfied?
- Looks accurate to me.
- Wonderful.
So, where's my money?
My money.
The problem is,
you already have it, Mr. Keelson.
Excuse me?
Last year,
the guard shift changes you sold me
for the airstrip in Chisinau?
They were wrong.
Wrong?
Like hell they were wrong.
That information was rock solid.
If you screwed it up, it's your problem.
You think you can play me
for a fool, Keelson?
All right, look,
a little misunderstanding? Obviously,
something got lost in translation.
We're all good.
Let's just...
we'll call it even.
Everyone walks away.
Sidewinder Rugged Appliance.
The most secure
portable IPS antivirus
URL geo-location
encrypted application filtering
in the world.
Let's find out how far inside
the castle walls
this Trojan horse rode.
I'm on it.
Agent Renko,
with Mr. Callen having gone
Three Days of the Condor on us,
I think we need
every able body we can muster.
Speaking of which, where's Sam?
Where indeed?
As far as fail-safe rally points go,
I've seen worse.
You said the same thing
when we picked this out five years ago.
Hoped we'd never meet like this, G.
Thought we'd never get made?
A man can hope, can't he?
First Dom...
then Macy.
Now this.
Something's going on, Sam.
Hetty's convinced
they're mutually exclusive.
You once told me we ain't working hard
enough, if nobody's trying to kill us.
I said that?
Really?
Make you feel better?
A little bit.
Who burned you?
A guy named Eugene Keelson.
Someone hired him
to find out about me.
He did his job well.
What is it?
It's a list of every foster home
I ever stayed at.
All 37 of 'em.
Some of those addresses
aren't even in my NCIS file.
Why contact you?
Wanted me to meet with some Bulgarians.
Pose as him.
Exchange a flash drive for a payoff.
I'm gonna guess
they didn't play nice.
After they downloaded the file,
there was no money. Just guns.
I was an insurance policy
in case things went south.
You thought going it alone with a group
of armed thugs seemed like a good idea?
Keelson implied
that NCIS had been compromised.
It's more than an implication.
Eric found a Trojan horse virus.
Had to take the Ops Center off-line.
This is as close as I've ever come
to finding out who I really am.
That's what I'm worried about, G.
I took photos.
Keep your head down.
Stay out of sight.
As far as I can tell, the Trojan horse
didn't get beyond Callen's files.
Keep looking.
Mr. Hanna. You know,...
I'm aware
you speak several languages,
but I don't recall having
used one you're unfamiliar with
when I instructed you
to not make contact
with Mr. Callen.
What makes you
so sure that I cont...?
It was a breach of protocol...
and one I understand.
So, what do we have?
The guy who burned Callen
is named Eugene Keelson.
Callen made a drop for him
with some Bulgarian heavies,
but it went all wrong.
This guy's got information
about G's past.
Things even NCIS doesn't know about.
That's what he handed over
to the Bulgarians.
Oh, this is encrypted big-time.
Without the mainframe,
this is gonna take a while.
These are the photos he took
before he made the drop.
We need to find everything
we can on Mr. Keelson
before he destroys this unit.
All the Eugene Keelsons I found
check out.
Same here.
This temporary server is Stone Age
compared to the Ops Center, but
I just got hits on the Bulgarians
from Callen's camera.
Luka Dimitrov...
Ilia Tagkov,
Kosta Daimov.
- It's a lot of "ov's".
- All shot and killed this morning,
except for this one...
Ruman Marinov.
All are former Bulgarian
military now involved
with organized crime in the U.S.
They're using a restaurant
downtown as a front.
How do you feel about goulash, Sam?
I thought goulash was Hungarian.
Actually,
the dish is eastern European.
It's got a lot of variations.
Essentially it's a stew.
But what they all have
in common is noodles.
Thanks for the tip, Martha Stewart.
Get me everything you have
on the Bulgarians' connections
to other crime organizations, ASAP.
We're closed.
On a Tuesday afternoon?
That's not a good sign.
I said we're closed.
Five employees, no customers?
This isn't gonna go down well
when I write my Zagat review.
I work for Ramon Casador.
How does Ramon enjoy life in prison?
Well, it's not exactly
his villa in Cartagena
but I hear for the right price,
the food's pretty decent.
Considering his holdings,
I'm sure he eats very well.
He has a small problem
that's affecting his digestion:
Eugene Keelson.
Mr. Casador wants to know what kind of
man he might be getting involved with.
He's heard rumors
you had dealings with him.
I'll tell Mr. Casador that you're busy
running your budding restaurant empire.
As far as information dealers go,
Keelson's the best.
Anything you want,
he can get it for you, for a price.
Anything.
And the price is high.
Any loyalties?
Only to the highest bidder.
He burned you.
Let's just say
he's going to be the victim
of an abrupt retirement
in the very near future.
Mr. Casador
will appreciate the info.
Okay, we're good.
Hello.
Hetty.
Mr. Callen,
is this your third cell phone
of the day?
I'm keeping receipts.
Good.
I'll expect
a detailed expense report
for all of your necessities
while on the road.
And I do mean necessities.
Well, I'll cancel my suite
at the Chateau Marmont.
Did you find anything
on the Bulgarians?
Hetty...
I just broke the encryption
on the flash drive!
- Hetty...
- Uh, I have to go.
I got burned and I can't be involved
in the case. I...
I get it, Hetty.
I do, too, Mr. Callen,
more than you realize.
What? What's the matter?
I have no idea if the drive
is infected until I open it.
If you don't, we may not get
our only clue in the case.
"Live dangerously"
is my creed, Mr. Beal.
Go ahead.
Go ahead and do it.
Harmless.
It's a single file containing
a dossier and a travel itinerary.
Who's "Andres Werner"?
CEO of Haupt Eisen.
It's one of Germany's largest
steel corporations.
Looks like he's in L.A.
completing a corporate merger.
Marinov's a major shareholder.
We're talking millions.
Millions that'll drop like a rock
if the merger goes through.
They're gonna hit him.
Callen gave Marinov the dossier.
He was coerced
into doing so by Keelson,
but we can't allow this man
to be killed as a result.
Werner's plane touches down
at LAX in an hour.
Werner! Get out of the car!
Federal agents!
Put the weapons down!
- Put the weapons down!
- This is gonna be some nasty goulash.
Renko?
You okay?
- Come on. You good?
- I'm good. I'm good.
I'm calling this in to the LAPD.
- Mr. Hanna?
- The decoy car worked.
Werner's safe.
Marinov hit us with his team.
Every one of them is down
except for the man himself.
Backup getaway car picked him up.
Have Kensi get out an APB.
She's on it.
Are any of Marinov's men
in a condition to talk?
They're not
in a condition to breathe.
We protected Werner, but we're back
at square one with Keelson.
Which unfortunately is nowhere.
What happened to protocol?
It went out the proverbial
damn window.
I've been thinking a great deal
about your situation.
Nate has misgivings
about your state of mind.
He's gonna have to get in line.
During this crisis,
he thought he should have a gun.
You didn't?
Perish the thought.
Walk with me.
This, um, Eugene Keelson
is a clever fellow.
It's rare for us
when we have an adversary
who knows more about our operations
than we do of him.
Despite Nate's misgivings,
I think we need
everyone's skills on board.
I'm not sure
that's such a good idea.
I told myself making
the Bulgarian deal
might help shed some light
on just how badly
Keelson had compromised our team.
Is that why I did it?
Or was it just an excuse
to find out about my past?
Only you can answer that,
Mr. Callen.
I can't.
Which is why Nate's right.
I should stay off this case.
Not good news, Hetty.
I've been tracking the damage
Keelson's virus did to our server.
Callen's file
isn't the only one it got into.
- Who else was compromised?
- Everyone.
And everything.
Keelson's got information
on every one of our cases.
I'm talking NCIS worldwide.
Thank you, Eric.
I'll be back with you shortly.
I appreciate your noble return
to reason, Mr. Callen,
but things have taken a turn.
The whole of NCIS
has been compromised.
Like it or not,
you are back in.
Tell me Hetty isn't gonna
string me up for taking a call
- from a burned special agent.
- You're good, Eric.
You should see our new digs.
They are much more intimate,
albeit a tad shadowy,
cavernous and slightly spooky.
I need you to bring
our servers back online.
I want you to reactivate
the computer virus
that Keelson introduced
to our system.
- Are you serious?
- Very.
You're asking me to commit
technological malpractice.
Here we go.
The virus is reactivated.
Our servers are exposed again.
I'm detecting a foreign code
inside the firewall.
It's gotta be Keelson.
Open a new file.
Label it "Keelson",
put it somewhere he'll find it.
Done.
Now include the following message:
"Call me.
I want to cut a deal."
Anything else?
Give him my active phone number.
We're set. Now...
can I ask why we're exposing ourselves
to this guy?
We must go to Keelson before he sells
the NCIS case list on the black market.
This is the only way
to lure him out.
Keelson likes money
more than anything.
If we can offer him enough of it,
he may just expose himself
long enough for us to take him down.
And what if Keelson
would rather die
than face prosecution
for his crimes?
The information he has
about your past
would likely disappear with him.
Are you ready to accept that,
Mr. Callen?
This is Callen.
What you offering?
What, no small talk?
Why bother? You hate it.
Or did you forget that I know you better
than you know yourself?
I can't let that case list get out
into the open market.
Our offer is $10 million
in untraceable U.S. currency.
The list would bring me more
if I auctioned it myself.
The longer you hold on to it, the bigger
risk you're taking. You know that.
This is a guaranteed payday.
Griffith Park Observatory.
Be there with the money.
You've got one hour.
- How will I find you?
- I'll find you.
I can't authorize $10 million.
I wouldn't ask you to.
I'm in position. Kensi?
I've got eyes on Callen,
but, so far,
no one's making an approach.
Renko?
I got nothing.
This guy Keelson could be anyone.
He'll show up.
Looks clear from here.
Wait a minute.
There's a guy in sunglasses approaching
Callen from the south side of the area.
Eugene Keelson?
Guess some tips are legit after all?
Everybody get down!
Get down!
Get out of the way!
Sam, that's him!
That's Keelson.
Eric, guy in the black jacket!
Turn over here.
I'm running facial rec,
but it's gonna take a while bef...
How'd we get a match that fast?
It's the driver who hit
and killed the guy tailing Callen
this morning!
- Callen must've recognized him!
- Who is he?
No name. No address.
We're looking at the only two images
of this guy that exist.
Keelson!
You exposed yourself by coming here.
That's checkers, not chess.
Either you or Marinov
was going to walk away.
That left me
with one final loose end
to snip.
You won't get that chance.
You know,
these elements that play here,
they're way bigger than you and me.
You kill me,
you'll never know the truth...
who you really are.
Who hired me to find you.
Are you...
are you ready to live
the rest of your life
wondering what that "G" stands for?
Fire it up!
Poker? It's game.
They're all games.
- I'm telling you, I just...
- Games.
Have you ever heard
of "running game" on someone?
But that jacket you wear... takes
a unique kind of girl to pull that off.
Glad to see everything back up
and running.
You can surf the Internet for your,
funny cat videos again.
At least my Web browsing
doesn't require a full system
purge at the end of the day.
I'm composing a letter
to Elizabeth Macy.
Someone else looking for answers.
I'm sorry, Mr. Callen.
About what?
You didn't get the information
you were hoping for.
Keelson found answers,
I'll find them, too.
Someone hired him.
He's still out there.
And how do you feel about that?
I will be able to answer
that question eventually.
When?
After I track them down.
Hey, guys?
What is it?
This case isn't over yet.
I just found a local address
on Keelson.
- Where?
- Downtown.
Could be a safe house.
I checked out its electronic signature,
looks like
this place is filled
with some heavy-duty data servers...
And I think we've got the key.
Data means answers.
.: Team UnderCovers :.