Alvy, we're good.
All bets are in.
Let's go!
Orange car,
come up, come up, come up, come up.
Good, good.
Silver car, come up, come up.
You're good, you're good.
Let's go! Just go, baby. Let's go!
Let's go, baby! Let's go!
Let's get out of here!
.: Team UnderCovers :.
NCIS Los Angeles 1x17
- Full Throttle -
You really
got to start taking the freeway.
- I like taking the streets.
- No, you like being late.
The freeway would have gotten us
here faster.
That parking lot they call the 10?
It's also known
as the Santa Monica Freeway.
- They have names as well as numbers.
- Olympic's faster.
You never take Olympic
before noon going west.
What if it's a leap year?
Sam here claims to know the name
of every freeway in California.
Oh, yeah? What about the 8?
- Ocean Beach Freeway.
- The 2.
- Glendale Freeway.
- 215.
Got him.
Escondido Freeway.
My God.
Are you kidding?
- Nice geek chariot.
- Mock away,
bipeds, but I have managed
to shave 43 minutes
of walking time
that I can now apply to my work.
43 minutes.
- I bet he took the streets.
- Yeah.
I'm a firm believer that
what you drive reflects who you are.
Exactly.
- Whatever.
- And where you drive.
Naval Yeoman James Rush,
home on leave
from San Diego Naval Base,
died in an illegal street race
in a parking lot early this morning.
In our culture,
some consider it a rite of passage.
Boys will be boys.
What was Rush's classification?
According to his file,
he was working admin support
for the quartermaster's office.
What's weird is Yeoman Rush's file
is heavily encrypted.
What admin division is encrypted?
The ones used to cover
something confidential.
Eric, find
what he was really working on.
It could just be
an unfortunate mishap.
Maybe.
But that encrypted personnel file
suggests he was working
somewhere classified.
The other driver kept going.
Never even tapped the brake.
You think he was running?
Tinted windows, no plates, no I.D.
Tokkan One?
Tokkan...
it's Japanese.
Means a lightning bolt.
We need to find the other driver.
Let's check out the crash site.
Take Kensi.
You heard me.
I know you're taking PCH.
I'm not sitting in traffic.
I'll find out everything I can
about Yeoman Rush.
You two suck exhaust
for the next two hours.
You suit yourself.
Come on, Kens.
What do you say,
we... stop for some doughnuts?
I love doughnuts.
You didn't say anything
about doughnuts.
There is nothing sexier
than an empty sea of pavement.
Given the rain, I'll take a hammock,
a sunset and a secluded cove somewhere.
You kidding me? Do you know what
the sand would do to your brake drums?
What?
Some people find nothing hotter
than a racing engine
and squealing tires.
If you're dating the Michelin Man.
How you doing?
- Help you with something?
- Depends. Who are you?
NCIS. Who are you?
Allison Pritchet,
Raydex Insurance.
I've been assigned to this claim.
What can you tell me
about what happened here?
Nothing yet.
Street racing's a growing problem.
These kids spend more than the car
is worth making them go faster...
and for what?
Same reason some people spend
a mortgage payment for a purse,
I guess.
I'd appreciate a copy of the report
when it's done.
Don't you file your own?
We like to be thorough...
and professional.
What was that?
I know, right?
I mean you.
Me... me?
She was acting weird.
I don't trust her.
I'm going to go talk to LAPD
about giving us the wreck.
You... breathe a little bit.
You're really funny.
There and back in just
over an hour on the PCH.
You got lucky.
Where's my doughnut?
I thought you were watching
your figure.
It seems you've been spotted again
in a bit of a rush.
Red light camera.
Busted.
I was chasing a suspect.
Nope.
That was our day off.
You were late picking me up
for the Kings game.
No doughnut, no love.
Maybe our buddy, Bernhart from LAPD,
can help you out with that.
He most certainly will not.
Do you want to jeopardize this cover?
You'll do what everybody else does
- and go to traffic school.
- Yeah.
It's no big deal, you can do it online.
You'll love it.
You can if you haven't had a conviction
in the previous 18 months.
Unfortunately,
this is number three
for Mister Callen, which means
16 hours of in-class study.
You're joking.
Don't worry.
Maybe it'll be fun. I enrolled you
in a comedy traffic school
for the next two days.
You didn't.
I'm working on a case.
Sam and Kensi are more than capable
of covering for you
until you're finished.
It starts in one half hour
in Culver City,
so you best be on your way.
We don't want you breaking
the speed limit to get there.
You might want to take the 90.
Just saying.
Which is the Marina Freeway.
What do you got, Eric?
A lot of people posted videos
and photos of last night's action
on their social Web sites,
so I'm just comparing the best of them.
All right, a quick snap.
Photo on the left.
Okay. Shake...
rattle, and
we are rolling.
Photosynth
has stitched together all these random
photos from different sources
and created
one big interactive 3-D image.
We have a close-up of the explosion?
Ask, and you shall receive.
I pulled some audio
from a video cam.
You can actually hear Rush activate
his pressurized NOS, but...
- there's no blinding acceleration.
- Just a blinding flash.
Right.
Which suggests the nitrous
never made it into the system.
Rush ran a wet system,
which mixes nitrous...
Nitrous and fuel into the intake.
Right.
Right... but when the system didn't get
what it was expecting...
Engine pressure built,
temps spiked, blew the engine.
- The lady knows her stuff.
- The lady
also knows that a blown engine
doesn't create this type of damage.
To the naked eye,
it looks like the Mitsubishi explodes
right after the Honda passes, but
if we slow it down,
it's actually a chain reaction
of two separate explosions.
The first explosion is consistent
with a blown engine,
resulting in a mild flare-up.
What caused the second explosion?
Rush was a master mechanic.
He wouldn't have made a mistake
fitting that fuel system.
So, are you saying
that Rush's car was sabotaged?
Encrypted files, possible sabotage.
I'm thinking this just became
a murder investigation.
Good afternoon.
I'm Mr. Loobertz.
Welcome to the...
Fun for All
Traffic School.
Now,
I know some of you
probably aren't real excited
to be here,
but I guarantee you
it's going to be a great day,
because not only are
we Fun for All, why,
we're all for fun.
We put the
"Cool" in "School", don't you know?
Wouldn't that be "Chool"?
The "H" is silent.
I'm in 'ell.
The garage is a family business.
Older brother, Keith,
younger sister, Angela.
Financial records show they're
one oil change away from foreclosure.
A link on Rush's Facebook page
redirects to a site
dedicated to his racing victories.
Looks like Yeoman Rush
was a living legend.
Now...
just a legend.
- What is he supposed to do?
- What am I supposed to do?
You don't understand.
We don't have the money.
- We must let him go.
- It's not right.
What can we do?
We have no choice.
Guys! Guys, guys, don't...
don't worry about it.
It's okay.
I'll be all right.
Good luck.
- Sorry, we're closed.
- No, we're not.
- What can I do for you guys?
- Keith and Angela Rush?
Yeah. Why?
NCIS.
We're here about your brother James.
James was an angel.
I remember on my eleventh birthday,
I wanted a new bike,
but my dad couldn't afford it,
so James built me one from scrap.
He could build anything.
Sounds like a great brother.
The best.
No matter how bad the situation,
he was able to see the good in it.
Even with this garage,
he somehow made it all worth it.
Now that he's gone,
we should just sell it and move on.
That bad?
We're barely staying afloat.
My mom's gone, my father's in jail.
James dies last night,
and Keith is still acting
as if it's business as usual.
It's been rough around here lately.
Sounds like your sister's
had enough.
This garage has been
family-owned for 15 years.
It's all we have.
If we sell it now,
we'll have nothing.
Angela doesn't see that,
I'm not ready to tap out yet.
Sometimes you got to fight
for what you love.
I've taken care of James and Angela
since my dad got locked up.
It hasn't always been great,
but we've survived.
Best thing I ever did
was get James to enlist in the Navy
to keep him
from winding up like Dad, but...
he couldn't stay away.
What happened with your father?
He's six years into a dime
for vehicular manslaughter.
During a race.
So you disapprove?
Hell, no.
I used to race, too.
Why'd you give it up?
I was planning on going pro, but...
one thing led to another,
and here we are.
I'm fighting to keep
this garage alive for Angela,
whether she sees it or not.
I'm not gonna let my brother's murder
force me into selling.
Why do you think
your brother was murdered?
The guy he was dragging,
Silver Honda?
What about it?
Tokkan.
He's been gunning for James
for years,
and when James enlisted,
Tokkan became the guy to beat.
James returns,
Tokkan's back to being second best.
Where can we find this Tokkan?
Nobody knows who he is.
Never shows his face,
never sticks around after he wins.
The guy's a mystery.
We need to see your surveillance tapes,
if anybody got to your brother's car.
James wouldn't even let me
near his car.
Sibling rivalry?
Seems stupid now, right?
Got to admire their spirit.
One tragedy after another,
- and they just keep moving on.
- You have to.
Otherwise, it eats you alive.
- She's funny. Crazy.
- Who?
Hetty sent me a text.
Hetty doesn't text.
She may not hit you.
She hits me all the time.
- About what?
- Dirty jokes mostly.
In Latin. You should hear the one
about e pluribus unum.
We're practically BFFs.
B-T-W. On your left.
This is exactly why Hetty took away
your pogo stick and your unicycle.
Do you actually have something for us,
Ericus Annoyingus?
I ran a check on Tokkan.
The name is well known
in the world of street racing,
but the guy has never been caught
or arrested.
Then, we've got
Ratchethead's mechanic,
Omar Alvares, who's just been fired.
He's not a street racer,
but he's got a criminal record
for his involvement
in a chop shop in Inglewood.
Get us a list
of his known associates,
family members and any guys
that may have done time with him.
Rush Senior's in prison
for killing someone in a street race.
Maybe his son's murder
was a payback.
Need that file, too, Eric.
Been there, done that.
Check your e-mail.
I told you this thing's
making me more efficient.
They just dropped off
Rush's Mitsubishi at the impound lot.
- What's left of it.
- You want to work it?
No. Go ahead. I send Callen an e-mail,
make sure he's up to speed.
Think he's having fun?
Oh, yeah.
Now, as you can see,
the California Driver's Handbook
is well over 90 pages.
That's a lot of information
for anyone to remember.
But you know
what isn't hard to remember?
Anyone?
Anyone at all?
That's a question.
Need a hint?
All right.
That's right.
There you go.
Go music, go lyrics.
Can you feel it?
Fun For All...
Fun For All has broken each section
down into songs, from
rocking registration riffs to
insurance requirement raps.
Wicky! Wicky! Wicky!
Yeah!
So there's something here
for everybody!
Someone shoot me, please.
Give me a wrench.
Careful there, cowboy.
This baby's suffered enough.
Sorry. I didn't know
you cared so much.
What can I say?
Grease is my favorite perfume.
So, tell me.
How do you know so much about cars?
Used to help my dad tune his Nova
on weekends.
In fact...
I used to spend my afternoons
handing him tools
and bringing him cold beers.
- That sounds like fun.
- Yeah.
Every time he turned away,
I'd adjust the carburetor on my own
to surprise him when he came back.
This is not gonna work.
Half-inch socket.
Seriously?
My dad and I never really
worked on cars.
- He was more of a Lego guy.
- Hold on.
I feel something.
Oh, my God.
- What is it?
- I don't know.
But I'm betting
it's not supposed to be in this car.
Maybe Keith Rush
can tell us what it is.
No one's home?
No one friendly.
I'll take the back.
Stop! Federal agent.
It's late for an oil change. You mind
telling us what you're doing here?
I'm Commander Garrison Timmons,
James Rush's commanding officer.
James was a good kid.
I was trying to pay my respects
to the family.
Yeah, okay.
I want to know exactly what this is
and how it works.
Could not tell you.
You dropped it in the garage
when you ran away.
I'm sure there's all kinds
of fancy equipment inside there.
It's a garage.
All that other fancy equipment
doesn't have your prints all over it.
That does.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Give him what he came for.
How about this?
You wouldn't know what this is,
would you?
As a matter of fact, yes.
Where's the other one?
James was working
on an advanced
lithium-ion battery system.
Ultra lightweight, high-powered,
never needs to be replaced.
Unstable,
but if perfected, worth billions.
Two units went missing.
When I heard about the crash,
I got worried.
- Why?
- James was the kind of R&D guy
who liked to get his hands dirty.
It wasn't unusual for him
to test stuff out on his own.
The battery system.
It dramatically increases efficiency
in the combustion cycle.
In effect, it would have made
the car go quicker, okay?
I didn't want the Navy
to discover they were missing.
I've come to retrieve them.
And this?
It's a dosimeter.
It picks up
the battery's lithium-ion signature.
This technology
isn't just worth a fortune.
It would revolutionize
our attack vehicles in the field.
It's something we can't afford
to have fall into the wrong hands.
Well, well, well,
if it isn't our resident scofflaw.
Hope you had a nice day off.
Don't even start.
If someone did sabotage
Yeoman Rush's car,
what was the motive?
Could be a rival street racer,
which puts this Tokkan
at the top of our list.
What about Rush's C.O.?
He came clean too quick.
I think he's legit.
The missing high-tech battery?
On our way to search the garage.
Good morning.
How long does it take a car
traveling at 35 miles per hour
to stop, Mr. Callen?
200 feet.
Try 210.
How can someone so small...
It's just traffic school.
How bad can it be?
Remember the Libyans
that took us off the trawler?
- Really?
- The Libyans didn't sing.
- There's singing?
- And puppets.
I'm sorry.
Oh, good morning, Speed Racer.
Did you get my last text?
OMG, Hetty. Hilarious.
Hope you're watching the time.
Last day and all.
Remember, hands
at 9:00 and 3:00.
10:00 and 2:00.
Hang in there, buddy.
- It's a battery.
- I've never seen this before.
Keith would know more
about this sort of thing.
You can ask him when he gets back.
Mind if I take a look around?
You know where we can find
Omar Alvares?
South Central?
He's always moving.
This must be a lot for you guys
to handle on your own.
I hate street racing.
I begged James to stop,
but he wouldn't listen.
Men are idiots.
Sometimes.
And after what happened to our father,
you'd think he would have...
He just couldn't stop racing.
Nothing here.
You know where we can find Keith?
He said he was making a parts run,
but parts run for what?
It's not like
we've gotten any customers.
- Where do you think he went?
- I'm not sure.
I tried calling his cell,
but he didn't answer.
I'm worried he's out there looking
for Tokkan, and if he finds him...
I can't lose another brother.
Your brother needs to contact us
the moment he gets back.
And so that is why it is essential
that you carry them at all times.
Isn't that right, Mr. Walinski?
Mr. Walinski.
Essential. I got it.
- So insurance...
- Mandatory, Mr. Walinski,
mandatory.
What if you modified your car
for street racing?
Anyone familiar with
the California insurance
reference manual knows
that street racers
cannot be insured.
As a matter of fact, street racing
or any other negligent act
voids an insurance
policy altogether.
Yes, sir.
I hope those are notes,
Mr. Walinski.
Callen was right.
Rush didn't have a policy with Raydex.
In fact, as far as I can tell,
he didn't have a policy
with anyone outside the Navy.
What about the insurance agent
that we met?
Doesn't exist.
Raydex has no one by that name
and didn't have an agent
in the area yesterday.
Alvares' last known address
was bogus,
but his list of acquaintances
probably isn't.
- Who does Alvares trust?
- He was cell mate for a guy
for three years
by the name of Dwight Johnson.
Cell mates can get close
during their time
- if they don't kill each other first.
- Johnson has a place in Echo Park.
What about the case
against James' father?
Let's see,
the person Rush Sr. killed was...
homeless and nameless.
Body was never identified.
Making the chances
of this being payback slim.
I got him. I got him.
Alvares?
Tokkan's car. He just turned off
the 105 into El Segundo.
Kensi, separate cars.
Talk us in, don't lose him.
Where is he?
I don't see him.
He's right in front of you,
turning into the refinery.
He's accelerating.
I got him, but we've been made.
I'll try and get ahead of him.
Federal agents! Out of the vehicle!
Hands where I can see 'em now!
Now!
College student,
wealthy family, no record.
Allysia Takada.
AKA insurance agent.
Aka Tokkan.
Basically, you're just
a spoiled rich kid from Palos Verdes.
The secret identity
was all part of the game, right?
Except this isn't a game.
A man is dead.
Did the frustration of losing to James
Rush finally escalate to murder?
You wanted the title.
Top racer on the set.
Tokkan One. Lightning bolt, right?
Except James was faster,
so you, or one of your buddies,
you rigged his car and you killed him.
No, James and I were competitive,
but I didn't kill him.
I was in love with him.
I was so happy
when James joined the Navy.
He ever tell you
what he was working on?
Not really.
He liked
that it was top secret stuff.
He told me he had a trick up his sleeve
and challenged me to race him.
Was he the only one
who knew you were Tokkan?
Tokkan was James' idea.
None of the guys would race a woman.
You know guys and their egos.
If you loved him,
why didn't you stop when he crashed?
Because I knew he couldn't survive
something like that.
I just kept driving around
all night.
I didn't want to face
what had happened.
I didn't go back until the next day.
Did he have any enemies?
If anyone wanted to make sure
James didn't finish a race,
- it would be Stringer.
- Stringer.
Drives a pearl-black Chevelle.
He lost to James earlier
and was pretty pissed.
There was a lot of bad blood
between them.
You have a first name?
Nick Stringer, biker, car thief,
and all-around badass,
moves around the country,
city to city, stays long enough
to show up on the local law enforcement
radar before moving on.
When he's not racing,
he's either betting on races
or stealing cars to race.
Warrants read like a Zagat guide
to illegal street racing.
There, pearl-black Chevelle.
And there's Stringer.
Unfortunately, being at a race
isn't enough to charge him.
Who's he talking to?
Eric, step frame.
Now blow it up.
Right there.
The reflection.
Keith Rush?
Two on one, huh?
On the ground.
- On the ground.
- No, don't, don't shoot.
There's gasoline everywhere.
Don't do it. Don't be stupid.
Where's Angela?
She said she wouldn't come
to the garage anymore.
She is the one with the brains
in the family, isn't she?
So who are they?
- They work for a guy named Stringer.
- The guy you were with at the race?
Why didn't you tell us you were there
the night your brother got killed?
You're jealous of the golden boy
while you were stuck at home
with family?
Maybe you decided
to do something about it,
like maybe mess around
withhis engine.
No way, I was there
because I wanted to bet Stringer
that James would beat Tokkan.
It was a safe bet.
James had the fix in.
He had this...
Naval battery?
He said it guaranteed him the win.
It didn't. It's what killed him,
that in combination
with his NOS system.
I was going to use the money
to help fix this garage up, but...
now I owe the bank and Stringer,
and I just don't have it.
How much you in for?
- $70 k.
- Where's the other battery?
I didn't know there was another one.
- I swear to God.
- Okay, your mechanic.
Where can we find Omar Alvares?
I don't know.
Omar runs with Los Locos Lowriders.
You find them, you'll find him.
I need a list of known hangouts
for Los Locos Lowriders.
You're approaching an intersection
where the traffic signals
are malfunctioning.
What will you do?
Callen,
Sam and Kensi are going after
the Ratchetheads' mechanic Omar Alvares.
- Mr. Walinski.
- All right, great, keep me posted.
For shame, Mr. Walinski, for shame.
Shouldn't he be wearing a seat belt?
I hope this works.
It's possible we're too late.
Omar Alvares?
Calm down.
Where you going?
Put your hands on the hood.
Federal agents. Stay back.
Don't get cute.
What you got in here, huh?
What is this?
That's a lot of cash
for an unemployed mechanic
who hasn't been paid in weeks.
Where's the naval battery?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Stay still.
Wha... what is that thing, huh?
How long do you think he's got?
I'd say no more than three hours.
I'm thinking closer to two.
Yeah, right, man.
Look, I want my lawyer, okay?
Buddy, if I were you,
I'd want my doctor.
You've got radiation sickness
from exposure
to an experimental
naval battery, Omar.
You know
what radiation sickness does?
Your hair falls out,
your skin blisters,
you bleed from every orifice.
Every orifice.
Okay, so y... you're going
to take me to the hospital?
Tell us where the naval battery is
and who sabotaged James Rush's car?
I think he's starting to sweat.
- Huh?
- Yeah.
It's hyperhydrosis.
- Wha... what do you mean?
- Your heart should be racing by now.
That's tachycardia setting in.
You feel it?
If we don't take him
to the hospital fast,
his tongue's going to swell up.
They'll have to intubate,
- he won't be able to talk.
- My tongue?
You gotta take me to the emergency room.
That's the law.
Seriously, guys,
look, I... I don't...
I don't know anything
about sabotaging James' car.
Look, I liked James, man.
Look, I worked for his family
for a long time.
Even when they couldn't pay me.
Is that why you stole the battery?
Come on, don't you think you owe it
to James to tell us where it is?
Look...
I sold it to this cat
named Stringer, okay.
Stringer's probably a ghost by now.
- With billions in naval technology.
- What about me, huh?
I got... I got radiation poisoning!
Come... come...
I need medical attention.
I'm going to give you two
of these, okay?
This'll help you.
All right. Better?
Man, these are breath mints.
Never underestimate
the importance of good oral hygiene.
- Let's go.
- Do I got radiation poisoning or not?
No. Make a path.
That's it. Time's up.
Pencils down.
All the way down, Mr. Walinski.
You'll be informed of your scores
via electronic mail.
And, hey.
Drive safely out here.
Well, that was fun.
No kidding.
Would you like
to grab a bite to eat?
Maybe a drink
to celebrate our graduation?
I could do that.
Definitely.
No, something just came up.
Tomorrow?
I'm on the red-eye tonight
for the Bahamas.
Nice. Vacation?
Swimsuit photo shoot.
Could be a vacation
if I had some company.
If he's smart, Stringer's moved on.
Maybe.
But he probably doesn't know
what that battery technology's worth.
If he does, he'll try to sell it
to the highest bidder.
Stringer's an adrenaline
addicted personality
who's got his hands on something
that'll give him the edge
over anyone he races against.
He won't be able to resist.
Trouble is, we don't know where the next
street race takes place.
We don't, but I believe
you know a certain female street racer
who can find out.
You're right.
Stringer contacted Tokkan.
He wants to race her tonight.
Very little time to set up.
We're only going
to get one chance at this.
Then let's not screw it up.
Having said that, I've made some
adjustments to the Challenger.
My Challenger?
It may be your car, Sam,
but Uncle Sam pays the gas.
Anyway, it's... it's not...
state-of-the-art naval technology,
but it'll give it a little extra oomph,
if you need it.
My car...?
From what we've seen, Mr. Callen,
you don't seem to need any help.
I figured.
Federal Agent.
Nick Stringer,
get down on the ground, now.
I'd do what the lady says.
Everybody stay cool.
We're only here for Stringer.
Don't do it.
Don't.
Stop.
Clearly, this guy hasn't read
the California driving manual.
Failure to use a turn signal,
running a red light?
At least ten points.
I'm a little busy here, G.
- I thought you knew how to drive it.
- I should drop off some of the weight.
This guy's good.
He's good.
- We're better.
- We?
Come on, Hetty.
Show me what you got.
What did she do to this thing?
Down on the ground!
Don't move.
What the hell you got in that thing?
So far above your pay grade,
you wouldn't recognize the view.
How was your flight? Turn over.
Turn over!
Put your hands behind your back.
Get up.
Jackpot.
We got the battery.
And there you have it.
Stringer copped to everything
except killing James Rush.
- No surprises there.
- I don't think it's him.
- Neither do I.
- Well, if it's not him,
it's not Keith, it's not Alvares...
who would want Rush dead?
Well, we must've missed an enemy.
Somebody else that didn't want him
on that track.
What do you got?
Just a hunch.
Thought
you weren't coming back here?
I had to get things
sorted out for Keith.
As it is, this place is going
to be a disaster by the end of the week.
I have to move on with my life.
Keith told me
that you caught Stringer.
Yeah.
Him and Alvares went after the battery.
They thought they could sell it.
But...
that doesn't explain
who wanted your brother dead.
And then it hit me.
It wasn't about
who wanted your brother dead.
It was about who wanted him
to stop racing.
We were looking for an enemy.
But we should've been looking
for a loved one.
Someone he trusted.
Someone with easy access to his car.
Angela?
I just wanted it to end.
I wanted him to stop racing.
I disconnected his NOS injector
after he ran
his pre-race inspection.
It was just supposed to bleed out,
no harm done.
He didn't tell me
that he swapped out his battery system.
I was just trying to save him.
I was just trying...
Well, the Navy's relieved
to get their technology back.
And they're not going
to pursue charges.
Good.
That family's suffered enough.
- Where you guys going?
- Nowhere.
You're taking out the Challenger?
Zero-to-60 before you can sneeze.
Take me with you
or I'm telling Hetty.
What is this, third grade?
- Okay.
- Yes!
But you're not driving.
Going somewhere?
- Boat shed.
- We got a lead.
We have a lead and we are
questioning him in the boat shed.
I hope you guys are
better liars out on the street.
Hetty,...
I'm offended.
Tough.
I've removed the supercharger
from the Challenger.
- Why would you do that?
- Oh, jeez, I wonder.
You want
to do something constructive,
take Mr. Callen out to a parking lot
and teach him how to drive.
All right, I happen
to be a great driver.
Not according
to your Traffic School.
They just called your alias.
You failed.
How could you fail traffic school?
What?
I was working on a case.
you need a note for your teacher?
I'd settle for a little appreciation,
okay?
I passed up the Bahamas to be here.
I gotta get one of these.
.: Team UnderCovers :.