Now we're talking.
That's right.
Right here.
Right here! Yeah!
Now we're talking. Yeah, please.
Right here, baby.
Over here.
Over here, yeah.
Over here, Kelli.
Kelli, you're beautiful.
Come on, right here, Kel...
Over here, Kelli. You look beautiful.
Right here. Beautiful.
Bupkes.
Where you going?
Snooki from Jersey Shore is pulling up.
Hey, somebody call 911.
Over here.
What the hell?
.: Team UnderCovers :.
NCIS Los Angeles 1x19
- Hand-to-Hand -
- Okay, shot caller, call your shot.
- I'm thinking...
of new and innovative ways
to expose your weaknesses.
I have an H.
You have an H-O. Shoot...
Top of the key, off hand, glass.
- It's the same shot as before.
- No, this is a bank shot now.
With the off hand.
The key's not to over, think it.
It's a concept I'm sure
you'll have no problem embracing fully.
Same shot twice.
Hey, I don't break the rules,
I just bend 'em.
Listen, I love the rules,
the letter and the spirit.
They're the foundation
of civil society.
Ball.
Knock yourself out.
Guarantee you I make this shot.
The humanity!
You want to take a shot?
I prefer the attaque au fer,
when the tip of my foil scores
a direct hit against the unguarded chest
of my opponent.
Come on, Hetty, one shot.
Save the planet.
Boys' games can wait,
a dead Marine can't.
A l'étage.
Upstairs. We get it.
That better be wastepaper
you're using.
- Of course.
- Absolutely.
Lance Corporal Daniel Zuna. Stationed
without incident at Camp Pendleton
until last night.
Taken by a member of the paparazzi.
That'd be "paparazzo",
then wouldn't it, because "paparazzi"
with an "I" is plural.
So paparazzo...
These were taken last night near
an alley outside of a night club called
Four-Twenty on Hollywood Boulevard.
Four-Twenty has an incredible DJ.
What? A girl's got to get her freak
on now and then.
Preliminary autopsy
indicates Lance Corporal Zuna died
from massive blood loss.
Gunshot?
No. No signs of physical trauma.
But here's the freaky part.
He bled out through his eyes,
ears, nose and mouth.
Lance Corporal Zuna
was on a two-week leave.
Spends a lot of his off time
at an MMA gym
called the Blood & Guts Warriors.
MMA, Mixed Martial Arts.
The victimhas been on leave after
coming off a guard duty rotation
at a bio-lab facility, so
assume he may have been exposed
to a biohazard.
Hazmat assured me
there's no contagion,
but due caution is advised.
We need to track Zuna's movements
while he was on leave.
Sniff around Zuna's gym. See
what you can find out from his buddies.
We can always bring them in later
if we have to.
Meanwhile, Sam and I will be
wearing gloves in an alley outside
of Hollywood Boulevard.
Substantial pooling.
It's more like a lake.
Don't go too close.
You don't have to say
"biohazard" twice.
It's close to the club.
You think he was waiting somebody?
Didn't have a stamp on his hands.
He never even went inside.
He was worried enough to come armed.
Average body holds six quarts
of blood.
- Looks like Zuna lost every last drop.
- And then some.
- Hit me, G.
- Eric?
Does Zuna's preliminary autopsy
report estimate blood loss?
Let's see.
Yeah. It estimates the victim lost
half his blood supply.
This is more than three quarts{\
of blood}.
Call the pathologist, see
if Zuna's toxicology report is in yet.
All right, hold on.
I'm checking now.
Before a fight, some fighters like
to boost their blood supply.
It adds red blood cells
and increases endurance,
they store up their own blood,
and they re-inject it.
It's called blood packing.
So Zuna gained a tactical advantage
by bending the rules.
- And it cost him.
- Maybe.
It does explain the excess blood
in the body and on the ground.
So, do you have a theory
on why a healthy guy
with no signs of trauma
would bleed out in an alley?
Guys, toxicology's back.
Zuna had high levels of heparin
in his system.
It's a blood thinner.
He's says that amount of heparin would
have caused unstoppable hemorrhaging.
Made the blood seep out
the most porous membranes in the body,
eyes, nose,
ears.
But nobody packs their body with blood
and willingly takes blood thinners.
Looks like Hetty can stop worrying
that he was exposed to a biohazard.
Yeah, and we can start worrying
about who the murder is.
Don't wait! Don't wait! Gil!
He gives you his back, get hooks in.
Start working for the rear naked choke.
- Yes, sir. Sure.
- Let's go. See it again.
There you go.
You want to train,
it's 60 bucks a month.
You bring your gear, no women's locker
room, you have to change in your car.
I mean, hi.
I'm not here to train. I'm a frie...
wasa friend of Daniel's.
You heard what happened?
Still can't believe it.
I just thought I'd come see this place.
He was always talking about it.
Danny was a hell of a fighter,
even better man. I'm Victor Janklow.
Tracy.
You his girl?
I guess.
We only just started dating, but...
it was intense.
So, how can you guys keep training if,
you know?
We're Marines. It's how we do it.
I was Danny's platoon sergeant.
He talked about you a lot.
Yeah, probably only half
of what he told you was true.
Bad half.
I thought if I saw where he trained
would help me stay connected.
- You know any of the guys?
- No, never met 'em.
Come here. Hey, guys, come here.
Come here!
This is Corporal Craig Mangold,
retired.
This is Corporal Dale Johnson,
Corporal Nelson Shabazz,
and that's Jason Wyler.
This is Tracy, Danny's girl.
Yeah? How'd you find out?
Police called me.
My number is in his cell phone.
Danny had a lot of girls' numbers
in his cell phone
Well, I guess mine was just
the last one dialed.
Come on, Jason.
We're all feeling bad.
Maybe it was a mistake coming here.
You come by here anytime, okay?
- Thank you.
- Thanks for stopping by.
I'm sorry about Jason.
He's...
- wound a little tight.
- It's okay.
If you want to talk,
there's some things I...
- Maybe a drink sometime.
- Sure.
One for Danny?
The pathologist says the heparin
was injected an hour before he died.
Means he lost a lot of blood
very quickly.
Surprised he didn't lose consciousness
sooner.
His staff NCO said
he was one hell of a fighter.
Which is especially interesting,
given his slight stature.
Daniel Zuna was essentially
the runt of the Warriors Litter.
Not physically strong,
more of a scrapper.
Never turn your back
on the small guy.
You know,
when I was surfing in Vietnam,
they called me "khong lo",
"the giant."
This giant was forced to develop
the ability to take
a lot of physical punishment
and keep on fighting.
That explains the blood packing.
Zuna was desperate to prove himself.
In my experience,
relentless behavior like Zuna's
is almost always driven
by some major-league personal demons.
Does "major-league personal demons"
actually appear in the DSM-IV?
Sometimes I feel like
I'm getting too technical,
so I like to throw
in the occasional colloquial term.
Okay.
Blood & Guts Warriors,
or in layman's terms,
the badass kickboxers.
The Warriors fight as a team,
mostly taking on other gyms in the area.
Victor Janklow and Craig Mangold
are former Marines.
Janklow was their platoon sergeant
when they all served together in Iraq.
He lost an eye, left the Marine Corps.
Now he owns the gym,
and all the other guys train there.
Dale Johnson and Nelson Shabazz
are active-duty Marines.
Both served with Zuna.
What about Jason Wyler?
He strikes me as kind of a wannabe.
Wannabe Wyler is the only one
who wasn't a Marine.
- I got nothing on him yet.
- Keep looking, Khong Lo.
Something about him
set off a warning bell.
Maybe it was his baby blues.
Or his fluffy hair.
What about Zuna's phone records?
Let's see.
In the last few days,
he called several of the Warriors,
and his former commanding officer,
- guy named Scott Davis.
- What about the last call he made?
That was it... to Davis.
He left the Marine Corps
as a lieutenant.
Talk to Davis,
find out why Zuna called.
Kensi and I will hit Zuna's crib.
That's colloquial for "house".
I knew that.
Zuna wanted to meet this week.
I told him I was too busy.
- Were you?
- Truth is, I resented the call.
Dan Zuna was trouble
when he was in my command.
Trouble how?
When I was his lieutenant,
it was my duty
to mentor him, but as a civilian,
it's a different story.
What about the others,
Mangold, Shabazz, Johnson?
Every man in Staff Sergeant Janklow's
platoon was a fine Marine.
Except Lance Corporal Zuna.
If you have to know,
Zuna had a drug problem.
- It never appeared on his record.
- I never reported it.
We were taking casualties every day.
There was no letup in sight.
Those were the dog days.
You need all the Marines
you could muster.
I gave him a warning.
I told him to get it together
or take an other
than honorable discharge.
Did your platoon sergeant
know about this?
If Staff Sergeant Janklow knew,
he never let on.
Maybe Zuna kept it from him,
but I don't know how.
It's amazing
what you overlook in war.
Platoon was tight.
Still are, from what I hear.
I lost two men
in a firefight in Fallujah.
It's a miracle I didn't lose more.
What does this have to do with Zuna?
Zuna was driving the Humvee.
I don't know
if he was high or not, but
somehow he got lost
in the back streets,
he drove us straight
into an enemy strong point,
we got pinned down, and we had
to fight our way out. And after that,
the unit was never the same.
Thanks for coming.
You never told me.
How Zuna died.
Was it the drugs?
Someone pumped him
full of blood thinner.
He died in an alley.
Bled out all over the pavement.
I know what you'll ask me.
Did anyone in his squad blame him
for what happened in Fallujah?
Blame enough to kill him?
It's been a long time.
Long enough
to forgive in my book, but...
it's a fair question.
This is Zuna's place.
You want to do the honor?
- What, no key?
- What's the challenge in that?
Why does everything have
to be a challenge for you guys?
Lock has a double-sided cylinder.
You saw it coming up the walk.
Pain in the ass, aren't they?
For some.
Crappy furniture, brand-new TV.
Man had his priorities.
Laptop.
Left on and not password protected.
This is going to be easy.
Maybe he's got nothing to hide.
It's like a pharmacy in here.
Oh, my God, you scared me.
How'd you get in here?
Danny gave me a key.
What do you do here?
I live here. Spare room.
Danny's laptop?
I e-mailed him some photos.
Private photos.
Like the two of you watching the sunset
at Santa Monica Pier,
or the kind where you're not wearing
anything?
Certain kind of person
finds private photos like that,
they end up on the Internet.
So, definitely, uh, X-rated then,
Nobody under 17 admitted?
Well played.
Danny said he met a girl.
Said that she was hot.
You think he meant me?
I sort of assumed he had others.
No, no, no.
He, uh...
He definitely meant you.
Talked about how you two
used to party pretty hard together.
One thing leads to another,
next thing you know,
out comes the camera.
Right. Except for,
he said your name was Kate.
So, who the hell are you?
I met him at a party.
Paid him for some stuff he never
delivered. I came to pick it up myself.
- Is that why you're here?
- No, 'cause I don't do drugs.
Maybe Danny's connection never came
through. You know who his supplier is?
I was hoping it was you.
Or maybe you found what you were
looking for before I got here.
Maybe you found some cash.
Maybe you should empty
those pockets.
Did you call for a cab?
That would be me.
Thanks for stopping by.
Nice save with the cab.
Dirty pictures.
Nice touch.
Except it didn't work.
Had to switch up to a drug buy.
And he was interested.
You should consider investing in some
of those green tree air fresheners.
I'm just saying.
Thanks.
That was my snitch money
for the entire month.
Hetty's gonna blow a gasket.
Yeah, Eric.
Whoever Kensi's been talking with
it's not Jason Wyler.
I've checked every known database.
There's only a driver's license.
No Social Security number,
school records,
immunization,
not even a library card.
Your Jason Wyler doesn't exist.
Anything new on Wyler?
Still tracking his alias.
Maybe he killed Zuna.
He shared his house.
He must have known he was blood packing.
He could have introduced the heparin.
Lieutenant Davis said Zuna
had a drug problem in Iraq.
Maybe it was a drug deal gone wrong
between him and Wyler.
We can't answer the why
until we know who Wyler is.
Nate, check for any recent
drug-related activity at the gym
or involving MMA fighters.
These guys are looking to get an edge.
Methamphetamine, ephedrine, cocaine.
All likely stimulants
to appear in that environment.
Not to mention
performance-enhancing drugs.
Check it anyways.
And the paparazzi footage?
Literally thousands of shots.
I'm still sifting through it.
I'm still stuck on Wyler.
Stuck. Smitten.
- Whatever.
- He's hiding behind an alias,
he's carrying a weapon.
From the first moment I saw him,
he seemed hinky.
- Warriors are down a fighter.
- You might want to try out.
I need to backstop you.
Better hurry up,
I got to get that open spot
before somebody else does.
Sounds like you're headed
for the gym.
DeMarco Williams.
Striker.
Standup fighters tend to get
their asses handed to 'em around here.
- I've got ground game, too.
- Really?
Is that right?
Word is you are looking for a new man.
I'd like to show you what I've got.
- You ever fight outside North Carolina?
- Not yet.
But I'm looking forward to giving West
Coast a little taste of home cooking.
Well, you know, we've got
a spot open on tonight's card.
Let's see how you do.
- Cool. Appreciate it.
- Did I just hear that right?
DeMarco Williams, Jason Wyler.
- I thought I was getting Zuna's spot.
- You're still a little green, Jason.
This guy walks in off
the street and takes my place?
- Wait, fellas.
- Hold it.
Williams has a lot of fights under
his belt. He's had 27 bouts, 26 KOs.
- What happened in that last fight?
- Forfeit. Guy never showed up.
All right, listen,
I kept my head down,
I did my training,
I deserve my shot.
Okay. You want to fight your way in?
You and Williams tonight.
Winner joins the Warriors.
Have fun, gentlemen.
Wyler's seen me, so I'm gonna be
watching from the ops center.
But Kensi will be in the crowd.
This guy doesn't stand
a chance going toe-to-toe
with you, so he's gonna want to grapple,
get you on the ground.
It's okay. I'll sprawl and brawl,
stay on my feet and outlast him.
Outlast? This isn't Survivor.
Look, he tries an armbar,
slam his head. Don't wait.
In the SEALs, we learned combat
techniques from a lot of martial arts.
- I know my countermoves.
- Sam, take him out.
Take him out fast.
The longer this thing goes,
the better chance he has
of getting lucky.
- Do you hear what I'm telling you?
- G, I'm gonna be okay.
Trust me.
Trouble, Mr. Callen?
He's not ready.
I beg to differ.
But Sam's technique is splendid.
I'm not talking
about his technique, Hetty.
- He's reluctant.
- Because he has nothing to prove.
There's no joy in a blood sport
for a man like Sam
who's been tested
so many times in battle.
Wyler's not going to hold back.
- But you think Sam will.
- Sam doesn't want to hurt him.
And I think
that makes him vulnerable.
Sam knows what he has to do.
I just hope he does it.
The body versus the mind.
There's a fight, indeed.
Introducing first,
from the red corner,
weighing in at 185 pounds,
he hails from Los Angeles,
California, with 19 wins,
15 by the way of KO,
and only four defeats.
He is Jason Wyler!
His opponent,
from the blue corner...
Full 1080 p resolution
on the security cam.
- We got a great angle.
- On the big screen.
... record of 26 wins...
26 KO's and one forfeit.
He hails from Raleigh,
North Carolina.
Please welcome...
- DeMarco Williams!
- Janklow, I need to talk to you now!
All right, gentlemen,
it's the first round.
Are you ready?
Let's get it on.
Not good.
Come on, Sam.
Don't hold back.
No spiking.
We need to take care of this...
What are you doing, DeMarco?
Come on!
Stay down! Stay down!
That's it.
That's it. He's done.
- That's the end of round one.
- Fight's over, Hetty.
But it's the first round for us.
Sam's in.
Winner by knockout,
DeMarco Williams!
- DeMarco Williams!
- I'm done, Janklow!
Thanks for coming out.
Come back tomorrow night for
another night
of hard-hitting action...
Mangold, wait.
It's got to stop.
Do you hear me?
Why? 'Cause you say so?
I didn't take orders from you
in the Marine Corps,
and I sure as hell ain't taking orders
from you now, Corporal.
Are you okay?
Hotheaded son of a bitch.
What happened?
Nothing.
It was nothing.
Janklow and Mangold just had it
out in the office.
I couldn't tell what it was about.
Kensi, where's Sam?
You did North Carolina proud.
A little rusty, but I felt good.
Looked like, uh, you pulled
a couple punches out there tonight.
Don't want to show my "A" game
until I have to.
Always keep a little in reserve.
That's a good strategy.
He's coming out now.
Janklow's with him.
Look, make sure you alternate heat
and ice on those bruises tonight.
We'll see you first thing in the morning
for training. Welcome to the Warriors.
- Thanks.
- All right.
I worked hard for that spot.
Guess not hard enough.
Trouble.
Janklow just went back inside.
Wyler came out.
Stand by. Let Sam handle it.
So, how much, huh?
How much for you to walk away right now?
Nobody buys me.
Really? 'Cause if you stick
around here, you're going
to be looking over your shoulder
every minute, every day.
Is that supposed to scare me?
I already kicked your ass.
Stop it.
They're fighting.
Bigger problem.
LAPD's on scene.
LAPD?
How'd they get there so fast?
Who called them?
I don't know,
but they're taking them in.
We cannot risk blowing Sam's cover.
Eric, call Parker Center.
Get me the chief of police.
LAPD is screwing up our undercover.
Watch your head.
You might need a stitch.
Come on, Wyler.
What's your angle?
Why you want in the Warriors so bad?
Hang out with Marines?
- That it?
- Wyler, on your feet.
Well, well, well.
Tell you what.
It's, uh...
it's been nice
meeting you, Williams,
but I think I'm going to take off.
Williams, you're sprung, too.
Wait. What?
- Who are you?
- I was just going to ask you.
So, let me introduce you.
Special Agent Sam Hanna,
NCIS, meet... Detective
Marty Deeks, LAPD,
who's undercover.
Ain't that a kick in the head?
So,
I put a call to the West L.A. station,
had them hide
two black-and-whites around the corner.
Need you off the street,
so I picked a fight in the alley.
LAPD swooped in, arrested us both.
Figured they wouldn't release you
for 24 hours
and that might buy me the time
I need back at the gym.
Now, you guys...
You guys are some serious operators.
'Cause when, when I go in deep,
I'm on my own.
But not you guys.
No.
I tell you what, our...
safe house doesn't have
a view of the water...
except for, of course, when the...
plumbing backs up.
But I bet you got some sort
of a situation room, too. Yeah?
Lots of technical support,
lots of cool hardware
plasma TVs, maybe a guy at a keyboard
typing in some logistics.
I mean, not right next door, but...
but close.
Am I right?
- Monterey Park.
- Culver City.
That is adorable.
Both talking at once.
And you
well, at first, I wasn't too sure
about you, but that,
that Internet photo thing really
sold me. So, riddle me this...
did you preplan that,
or maybe...
maybe that happened in real life.
Crashing in his spare bedroom?
Is that the best you can do?
You are lucky I didn't shoot you.
I was vamping.
Are you in the mood to share?
That depends on if the mood is
reciprocated, 'cause I got to be honest
- not feeling a lot of love right now.
- Sorry for the left hook.
That's okay. You aren't the only one
that pulled their punches.
Okay.
LAPD's been getting intel
on the gym for about six months.
We think it's a possible distribution
point for the Juarez Cartel,
so heroin, coke, meth.
It's essentially a mini-mart for drugs.
It's what you want,
when you want it.
Now, Warriors,
it's a tight-knit group,
but I managed to work
my way in through Danny Zuna.
Zuna's autopsy turned up negative
for illegal drugs.
That's because Zuna's jones were
steroids and prescription painkillers.
Zuna was literally two days away
from introducing me
- to his supplier when he died.
- When he was murdered.
He was acting pretty paranoid
like something was eating at him.
We're working a homicide, and all
you have is possible drug distribution
and some loose connections
south of the border?
These past 24 hours have been tense.
Okay? This thing's coming
to a head. I can feel that.
Thanks for all your help, Deeks.
Thanks for...?
What, are...
are you kidding me?
I was undercover on this thing first.
You guys should be backing me up.
This is a Los Angeles Police
Department investigation.
Because the case
involves serving Marines,
it falls under NCIS jurisdiction.
That said, let's call
this a joint operation,
- and you'll both stay undercover.
- I have to run this by my boss.
I already have.
Ruben says "hi".
Pull up the unit's service records.
Logs, reports, anything you can find
from their deployment in Fallujah.
You ready for round two, Detective?
Ring that bell.
The conquering hero.
What's up, Williams?
Newest Warrior.
- What's up, Devil Dogs?
- You a Marine?
- Second Regiment, Lejeune.
- I knew it, man.
I could tell how you carried yourself.
What was your MOS?
3381. Food service.
You were a cook?
0311. Infantryman.
Knuckle dragger.
Although I did cook up a pretty good
ass-whupping for Wyler last night.
Whoa, whoa.
I'm sorry, Wyler.
Except for the ass-whupping part.
Laid him out like Sunday supper.
We might have something.
Turns out Lieutenant Davis
was disciplined
- after the Fallujah ambush.
- The incident he blamed on Zuna.
But the investigation was shelved,
because a week later,
Davis was wounded by a sniper
and repatriated home.
From weak in the knees
to a Purple Heart. Go figure.
If you read in between the lines,
Davis was not the most popular leader.
Buried deep in one of the reports
is a disciplinary reprimand by Davis
to one of his men,
who...
"verbally attacked him
and accused him
of being a widow-maker."
What's the Marine's name?
Corporal Craig Mangold.
I searched through the photos leading up
to the discovery of Zuna's body.
Whole lot of nada.
What about
after they found his body?
Paparazzi went on a feeding frenzy
until the cops shut down the alley.
All these were taken after that.
There.
Lieutenant Scott Davis.
We're going to need
his current address.
It's a pretty nice house for a 28-year
old former Marine Lieutenant.
Daddy's money or something else?
Our drug connection?
NCIS, federal agents.
He's over here.
They're clear.
You think Mangold beat us here,
took Davis out?
- You know this guy?
- Yeah, his name's...
Mangold.
Find Davis.
Looks like LAPD's already got
a BOLO on him.
I'll try using his cell as a GPS.
Word travels fast.
Chief of detectives called me
as soon as you ID'd Mangold's body.
- So how is it laying out?
- Zuna and Mangold
suspected that Davis was responsible
for their friends dying in Iraq.
So Mangold's upset over Zuna's murder,
thinks that Davis killed him.
But when Mangold gets here,
Davis spots him, shoots him first.
Callen, I'm tracking Davis.
He's pulling up to the house.
Davis is here.
Federal agents.
Out of the car.
- What the hell?
- Your hands behind your head
- I didn't do anything.
- Turn around, hands behind the head.
- You people crazy?
- Behind your head.
Your place or mine?
We can manage okay.
Come on, Callen,
at least let me hear his story.
We'll take it from here.
What story?
What have I done?
Thanks, Deeks, for everything.
What, no hug?
I didn't kill Daniel Zuna.
He was waiting for you
outside the nightclub.
That's right,
we know you were there.
And by the length of
the miniskirt on your lady friend...
I'm guessing she wasn't your wife.
If you got anything you want to say,
now would be a real good time to say it.
Zuna called, said he needed to see me,
so did Mangold.
Didn't know what they wanted.
The problem is...
they're both dead.
Craig Mangold's dead?
Found him at the side of your house.
That's two murders
with premeditation.
Suddenly, this becomes
a death penalty case.
- I'm not saying anything else...
- You were an officer, not a grunt.
If they came after you
and you killed them in self-defense,
there's a chance you walk away from this
but you've got to get out in front of it
- now.
- I didn't kill anyone.
Not even in Fallujah?
Officers said you led them
into an ambush.
- Called you the widow-maker.
- I made some mistakes.
I was 24 years old, for God's sakes.
I got over there and saw things
you couldn't imagine.
Those were bad days, very bad days.
Hard to tell the friendlies
from the insurgents.
Somebody had to make the decision.
You didn't always make
the right one, did you?
We were driving and I got
to this intersection, and...
I got confused.
The streets all looked the same.
I told Corporal Zuna to turn,
but he said he didn't want to,
he said it was the wrong way.
I ordered him to turn down that
backstreet, and I got those men killed.
A week later, I got shot, and
I'll tell you something, I felt lucky.
Got me the hell out of there.
I think if I'd have stayed,
my men would have killed me.
Pretty big admission he thought he was
going to get fragged by his own men.
When you told him Mangold was dead,
his reaction appeared
to be totally honest.
His brow never furrowed, he never
looked away, not even for a moment.
And when he talked about his fears
of being killed by his own men,
it not only felt genuine, but
it seemed as if it was the first time
he'd ever even admitted it...
to anyone.
- Eric.
- Yeah.
Bring up Janklow's service records.
- We're on our way back.
- I'm on it.
Keep him company.
Let's go.
Janklow wasn't wounded
in the Fallujah ambush.
That means he was still in Iraq
when Davis was shot by the sniper.
If his men thought Davis
was a widow-maker,
you can bet Janklow did, too.
And a week after Fallujah, Davis
is shot by a sniper while on patrol?
Who else was with him
on that patrol?
Zuna, Mangold, Johnson
- and Shabazz.
- Everybody but Janklow.
Warn Sam.
Mom, I told you
not to call me at the gym.
Fallujah was Davis' fault.
Now Mangold's dead.
Janklow killed him and Zuna.
Get out of there now.
Mom, I'll call you
when I'm done, okay...
So, I got a buddy in personnel
at Camp Lejeune.
My mom gave me that phone.
Don't break it.
Sam's phone's been shut off.
Battery is disconnected.
Eric, pull up the camera in the gym.
Something about you
didn't sit right with me.
- Little too good to be a grunt.
- So you had
- your buddy check me out. So what?
- The records show you were there
- exactly when you said.
- All right, then.
Then I called some men I know
in the Second Marine Regiment
they never heard of you.
Nobody else down there has, either.
Looks like you only exist on paper,
Williams.
We've got a problem.
Eric, find Deeks.
Watch the door.
So let's start with your name.
Your real name.
Why don't you tell me about Fallujah,
Platoon Sergeant?
- So that's what you're here about?
- That and Lieutenant Davis.
Lieutenant Davis was an amateur.
If I hadn't done something,
he'd have killed us.
There's no clock on a battle.
It's a waiting game.
You're up two, three days,
your adrenaline's pumping.
It's only a matter of time
before your body betrays your mind.
You don't want your men
falling asleep out there.
You're damn right I didn't.
Or every man's at risk.
You had to do something,
keep 'em awake,
keep your men sharp.
It's the only way to give 'em
an edge for that long.
But the drugs didn't stop coming
when you got home.
You think 'cause you're home, everything
just goes back to the way it was?
You kept the supply coming.
Painkillers, uppers, downers,
steroids, whatever they need.
Yo, I want to cancel my membership,
- turn in my key.
- Wyler, not now.
Take him.
Deeks.
I'm good.
Timed that pretty well, Deeks.
Good job.
You're not so bad yourself.
Janklow injected Zuna with heparin,
told him it was steroids
to stop him confessing to Davis.
Mangold tried to warn Davis
that he may be next,
Janklow followed him and killed him.
Which is just about the time
that Deeks showed up
to save your butt at the gym.
Yeah, that's exactly
how it happened.
He's not a bad operator, Deeks.
He's all right.
- Where are you going?
- Little light workout,
- iron out some of the soreness.
- I don't think so.
- We've got unfinished business.
- What are you talking about?
I believe you had H-O, I had H.
Have fun.
No, no, no, no, I have H
and you have H-O.
No, no, no, no, no.
Call your shot.
Strong hand, straight in,
nothing but net.
Let me see.
The humanity!
Detective Deeks?
Hetty.
Who doesn't have a last name.
Lange.
Hetty Lange.
- Can I get you anything, Ms. Lange?
- I've already had tea,
thank you.
And it's Miss,
and I prefer Hetty.
Hetty it is.
I imagine you're still smarting from
where the chief of police
just ripped you a new one.
- How did you know that?
- Because I just experienced
something similar from my director.
It seems
we need to coordinate
our operations a little better.
My boss wants to assign
a liaison officer from LAPD,
and your boss thinks
it's a good idea.
But you guys don't need
a liaison officer.
I agree.
I told him we already have one.
Who are you guys?
How did you get
all this information?
The only thing missing here is...
No need to date it.
.: Team UnderCovers :.