Look at that...
You're beautiful.
Two more?
You got it.
- I want to see you.
- Bad etiquette, Homes.
Can't be touching the dancers.
Look, guys.
We don't want
any problems tonight, okay?
I got no problems.
You got a problem?
All right. Settle it down
or take it outside, boys.
We got a zero tolerance
for trouble in here.
How about a dance?
I'm done for tonight. Sorry.
Dude, where's the beer?
The natives are getting restless.
- Where you going?
- I think I'm in love.
You want to grab
a coffee or something?
It's late.
- Decaf?
- Listen...
Look out!
.: Team UnderCovers :.
NCIS Los Angeles 1x10
[ Breach ]
I already sent the others upstairs.
Good morning.
Well, that's a matter
of perspective, Mr. Callen.
I've been doing some accounting
and I came across an anomaly
in your expenses.
This is a $1,400 restaurant bill
from Matsuhisa.
That's from the Miyagomi case.
It's not a mistake?
You actually spent $1,400
on raw fish?
Not me, my alias, Tony Z, did.
And is Tony Z going to reimburse me?
You'll have to talk to him
about that.
When I go undercover as a beach bum,
I eat at the Kogi truck.
When I'm going after high rollers,
I gotta hit it a little harder.
Try ordering soup, playa.
I'll tell Tony that.
You do that.
What are we looking at?
This footage is
from a gentlemen's club in Hollywood.
That's Petty Officer Mostel Renny.
The driver of the car
and P.O. Renny were killed.
The woman's still in the hospital.
It's tragic, but since when do we start
investigating DUIs?
Renny was there last night
with several other sailors.
All of whom are
Crypto Language Technicians.
Basically, the Navy's top secret
geek squad.
Any surveillance footage
from inside the club?
Pervs don't like to be filmed.
The driver of the car was
African-American, had no I.D.
- Probably left his wallet at home.
- The car was stolen weeks ago.
Might be a coincidence.
Maybe not.
I contacted the hospital.
The young lady is well enough
for questioning.
Sam, why don't you and Kensi
take the accident scene?
Crime scene.
Find Renny's friends, see if they know
anything. The address for the hospital?
Hollywood Presbyterian on Vermont.
Take Sunset.
I'll need anything
you can find out about the girl.
She's Ukrainian.
Thank you.
Problem?
We've got rubber in the street.
No skid marks. Which means
the driver didn't even try to stop.
Parking lot is too small.
There's no way to accelerate
that fast in this distance.
So, the driver
probably left the lot,
turned around, accelerated back,
- which means...
- It means Hetty's right.
It's a crime scene.
Katya Vitkoya?
Hi. My name's Callen.
I already spoke to the police.
I'm not a cop. Department of Transport
and Highway Safety.
Did you know Petty Officer Renny?
Maybe you could come tomorrow.
I'm sorry, I'm very tired.
Really?
'Cause they told me that you...
you just woke up.
You're from the Ukraine?
Where about?
Small town, Pavlivka.
- No one's ever heard of it.
- I know Pavlivka.
I spent some time in Balaklauski
a few years ago.
Really?
Years ago, even locals
weren't allowed to Balaklauski.
Were you... supposed to be there?
I was working on a big pothole problem
that they were having.
- How long you been in the U.S.?
- Not long.
Long enough for your visa to expire?
I'm applying for a student visa.
You're in school?
I'm applying for school, too.
Oh, yeah. Which one?
Look.
I'm not from Immigration.
I just want to know what happened
in that bar last night.
A man in the club grabbed me.
The guy who drove the car
was with him.
That sailor intervened,
but the club owner and...
a bouncer stepped in
before anything really happened.
Still no I.D. on the driver
but Forensics got a hit
on a set of prints
they pulled off the car window.
The guy's name is
Cesar "Chi Chi" Vargas.
He's had run-ins with I.C.E.
and the DEA for smuggling everything
from drugs to human cargo
across the border.
I'm sending you his photo
and arrest record...
- now.
- All right, copy Sam and Kensi.
See if they can get anyone at the bar
to make a positive I.D.
And find me a last known address.
Have them meet me there.
Was this the guy
that grabbed you at the bar?
You're sure?
The man was older and...
scruffier.
This guy was older.
And he was with the African-American guy
who crashed the car.
- They use a credit card?
- I already checked. Sorry.
Thanks.
Of course.
He knows more than he's telling us.
There's an alley out back.
I'll take the front.
Hola.
Senior Vargas?
I'm going in, Sam.
Go.
Clear.
- Place is locked up.
- He must've been gone for awhile.
That might be
why it smells musty in here.
If I had a place on the beach like this,
I wouldn't go anywhere.
He's clearly past
his expiration date.
You found this guy in a fridge?
Weird.
When they said
NCIS was coming with a body,
I kind of expected Nate.
Well, Nate was busy,
but he sends his regards.
Really?
He's so sweet.
You know, he works so much.
I wish whoever was in charge over there
would just cut the guy
some slack, you know?
Right. Don't ignore the corpse.
He's still in the room.
Looks like he's been dead
for at least two weeks.
The cold temperature slowed
the decomposition,
but it certainly didn't stop it.
- Cause of death?
- Best guess at this point,
suffocation following
blunt force trauma.
Clean and quiet.
I'll know more once I open him up.
You two are welcome to stay
and wait if you'd like.
I don't usually have an audience,
but visitors are always welcome.
- Pretty cool, huh?
- Tempting.
But we'll pass.
Did you finish with the driver
from the club accident?
Another weird one.
He wasn't drunk.
In fact, he didn't have
any alcohol or drugs in his system.
- Nobody calling to claim the body?
- Not yet.
We haven't been able to I.D. him.
Still running his prints and dental.
But this might help.
At first, I thought they were
some sort of gang initiation.
- Looks like machete wounds.
- Last time I saw anything like this,
I was in Rwanda.
Do you guys know
if Nate is seeing anyone?
'Cause, you know,
I'm just...
wondering.
Renny's sailor buddies
didn't see anything,
although one of them said Renny
was hitting on the dancer, Katya.
I ran the driver's prints
through Immigration's refugee database.
I got a match...
Deng Oyat.
He's not African-American.
He's African-African.
Originally from Sudan,
he was placed with a foster family
in Toluca Lake 3 years ago.
He's one of the "Lost Boys".
Second Sudanese civil war
left two million dead
and around 25,000 young men
displaced or orphaned.
They became known
as the "Lost Boys" of the Sudan.
Agent Vaile.
Lucky ones managed
to get into the U.S.
and other countries
through humanitarian aid.
Well, maybe his foster parents
know who he was with last night.
That was Hollywood Presbyterian.
Katya Vitkoya
just signed herself out.
Looks like we'll paying her
a house call, Dr. Hanna.
Take Kensi.
I need to check something.
Want to share?
If it pans out.
32 hours.
Excuse me?
You had 32 hours
of overtime last week.
It was a busy one.
Apparently,
you've had a lot of busy ones.
You have seven weeks
of unused vacation time owing.
- I do?
- Were you planning on,
sailing around the world?
No, just been busy.
You know, working...
Just a...
a lot.
Yes, we established that back
at the start of the conversation.
I don't determine
the caseloads, Hetty.
No, but I do set the schedules,
so start packing.
On Monday morning,
you're on holiday for a week.
Where am I supposed to go?
I'm not a travel agent.
- What was that about?
- I've been banished.
I think something's up with Hetty.
What you think you're doing?
- What you doing?
- Pretty quick for an old man.
- It's a joke.
- Yeah, try again.
What's up, man?
Come on now.
You kidding me?
How does a stripper afford
a place like this?
Some of these strippers
make six figures a year.
- Oh, really?
- So I've heard.
Going on a trip?
- My sister is sick.
- You don't have a sister.
And you'd probably have stayed
in the hospital.
Does the name Deng Oyat
mean anything to you?
He's the guy who tried to kill you
and P.O. Renny last night.
- Sorry. I really have to go now.
- But you need to answer the question.
This is Nate.
He's a good listener.
Thank you.
How you feeling?
Fine.
Well, that's the adrenaline
pumping through your body.
And when it wears off in a while,
you're gonna start shaking.
Might even feel like you're gonna
throw up, but don't worry.
It's a natural reaction.
You're...
safe here.
- Who were those men at your house?
- I've never seen them before.
Any idea why anyone
would want to hurt you?
Any... ex-boyfriend...?
This is the man who almost killed you
outside the club. You recognize him?
He might have been with the man
who grabbed me in the club last night.
But I can't remember.
You suffered a concussion.
It's not uncommon for the events
immediately preceding that
sort of injury to be a little fuzzy.
You should probably go back
to the hospital.
- No.
- Do you want us to help you, Katya?
Do you?
'Cause if we don't,
you're probably going to end up dead.
Right now, we're your only friends.
And maybe this... Deng here...
maybe he wasn't trying
to kill Petty Officer Renny.
Maybe...
he was trying to kill you.
Why? I don't even know him, okay?
Or Renny or any of them.
She's hard to read.
Girl's been on her own a long time.
She's used to take care of herself.
It's a defense mechanism.
You bury your identity
to protect it.
Well, she might have seen or heard
something and not even know it.
Any word on our gunmen?
Car had no plates,
and Eric wasn't able to find the vehicle
on any street or traffic cams.
Perfect.
Where is Sam?
Thanks.
Here.
Thank you.
How'd you make out
Saturday on your S.A.T.'s?
710 in math.
That's nice.
It's not math I'm worried about.
400, writing.
It's getting there.
I still remember the first time
you took me to the sea.
The Gulf of Aden.
You were eight.
I'd never seen so much water.
The ocean made you feel safe.
Only makes me feel small.
What makes you feel safe?
Being around my friends.
I've told you before that
youth center has reputation
for teaching radical views.
Americans have a bad reputation
in some parts of the world.
In this country,
if I wear baggy clothes,
I'm a hip-hop gangster.
If I wear a taqiyah,
I'm a terrorist.
At the youth center,
I am just Mowadh.
You know this guy?
That's Deng.
Deng Oyat.
Is he in trouble?
Trouble?
He's dead.
- Crashed a stolen car into some people.
- I just saw him last week.
Why would he do something like that?
He doesn't even have a driver's license.
He was with another man.
Older, scruffy.
Might be passing himself off
as Hispanic.
You know him, don't you?
You know him?
I've seen him at the youth center,
talking to Deng.
He gives religious lectures.
His name is Safar.
What kind of religious lectures?
I don't know. I don't attend.
I keep telling you.
I only go there to play basketball.
Does Safar have a last name?
Jaddalah.
Born in Algeria, raised in Libya.
Safar Jaddalah's file reads like
a who's who of Islamic militant groups.
He's moved around a lot,
and he's suspected,
along with other Al-Qaeda members,
of having entered Sudan
to train the Janjaweed.
"Devils on horseback with guns."
They've traded in their horses
for SUVs and upgraded their weaponry.
So what's Safar doing in L.A.?
I doubt he's auditioning
for "American Idol".
Recruiting alienated
and impressionable young men,
just like that group
of Somali teens in Minneapolis.
Takes them back,
indoctrinates them, and...
gets them to fight his jihad.
Well, maybe he hired Cesar Vargas
to smuggle him into the country?
He probably came in
over the Mexican border,
passed himself off
as a Mexican-American,
and killed Vargas
to tie up any loose ends.
What's a religious fundamentalist
doing in a strip club?
The 9/11 hijackers did the same thing
before their attacks.
Well, last night's incident could have
been a glitch in an even bigger plan.
And Deng Oyat was prepared
to die to protect it?
Deng Oyat did
what Safar ordered him to do.
Alert Homeland Security,
and brief Director Vance.
I'll put Safar's face out there,
talk to the other agencies
and local law enforcement,
see if they have anything.
Find this guy.
How well does
this kid Moe know Safar?
- He doesn't. He knows of him.
- And how do you know the kid?
I brought him here.
From Sudan?
I was in Chad as part
of the Pan Sahel Initiative.
We were called into Sudan
to rescue some aid workers.
Moe's father was killed,
and Moe was injured during a firefight.
I figured it was
the least I could do.
How's Katya?
Scared, but tough.
She's clearly affected
by you and Kensi saving her.
She's not accustomed to having
people do anything for her.
She wants to go back to her house
and get some things.
I told her I had to talk
to you about it.
Maybe you could go over there.
I thought you might need
a few things.
You went back to my house?
Wasn't sure what you'd want so I...
I brought a bit of everything.
Let go of me!
Sit down!
You want to run, fine!
I'll call my buddies at ICE. I'll have
you on a plane to Kiev.
What do want from me?
The truth would be
a good place to start.
Your boss, Dallas...
all these are his?
Yes.
And for the men who were shy
and insisted on lights being off...
night vision.
Blackmail.
Who?
Anyone who might have
something to hide or...
something that Dallas wanted.
Know him?
- At the club?
- Yes.
At your house?
Dallas told us he was
a very special VIP.
They called him a buyer.
I don't like where this is heading.
Dallas's girls compromise
military personnel
with access
to classified information.
Dallas then decides
to sell that information.
And Safar buys it.
Maybe to help plan
a terrorist attack.
Why would Safar have
someone drive a car into Dallas' club?
Somewhere along the line,
the deal went sour.
We gotta get a look
at Dallas' video collection.
Search warrant?
No, Safar finds out
the club's been raided, he's gone.
We'll never find out
what he's up to until it's too late.
Okay, so how do we get in?
Her.
Hello, there.
Lookie here.
Hey, baby...
Stand by, G, she's on her way in.
How's Dallas reacting.
Like his best girl just got back
and he didn't expect her.
Katya said Dallas' hard drive is
in a storage area off the kitchen.
Camera access.
None we could hack into.
Good luck.
Just a little bit crowded in here,
you know.
- Can Dallas see us.
- Well...
I'm sure he's been watching us
since I came over here.
All right, let's do this.
We are gonna have fun.
One for the VIP room.
Give us a good show.
All right.
Let 'em go through.
- She's coming through.
- Okay.
That's my girl.
Got at least three cameras,
Sam, possibly more.
We turn on the jammer, Dallas is not
the only one who's gonna lose picture.
I'm gonna need
about a 20-second burst
to get me out the door
and down the hall.
20-second burst, initiating now.
- Go!
- Nineteen...
Security card.
Third door down on the left.
Twelve...
- Seven...
- He needs to be down the hall now.
Six...
Five...
Four...
Two...
One...
Zero. Jammer's off.
Tell me you're in the kitchen.
G, you reading me
We got picture, no audio.
Accessing computer now.
Where is he?
- Everybody out! Out!
- I got company, Sam.
- Don't move! Don't move!
- Kitchen's closed.
How's that for a lap dance.
You got a warrant to go
into my place.
FISA warrant.
Terrorism investigation.
I'm not a terrorist.
I'm a patriot.
Is that why you fell out with Safar?
Is that why he attacked your club?
All good questions...
for my lawyer.
He's smug.
I hate smug.
Guy thinks he's going
to walk out of here.
- Is he gonna walk out of here?
- It depends what's on those tapes.
There. Him.
- Who's he?
- I think he's a senator.
Which one
Okay, maybe he's a congressman.
- Another one for the maybe column.
- What do we got?
At least a dozen identified,
including two senators,
the CEO of an aeronautical company,
a former child star
and four senior military officers.
And we are only
a third of the way done.
- Safar
- Not yet.
- Keep looking.
- You don't need to keep looking.
This investigation is over.
- They're shutting us down.
- All evidence, physical and electronic,
is to be sent to DOD.
What about Dallas?
We're under orders to release him
immediately.
We're putting together a good case here,
okay. A big one.
Hetty, Safar's up to something.
We can't stop now.
This is coming from on high.
When I say on high,
I mean those
with the political venom
to end the careers of each
and every one of us,
including Director Vance.
I can't believe this.
- All we need is a little more time.
- I know, I know.
If I may slip into the vernacular,
it sucks.
But when you hear from me again
in an hour or so,
you will
shut this
down.
Don't forget to release Mr. Dallas.
Guys, you've got to see this.
Fire it up on the big screen.
I don't think we want this up
on the big screen.
So look what I found
on Dallas' sleaziest home videos.
I'm guessing Safar's imam
would not approve of that.
Definitely haraam.
What's that?
- It's Arabic. It means forbidden.
- No, no! What's that?
Whatever it is,
it can't be good for you.
Come on,
I'm in up to my knickers now.
Dallas is an extortionist.
Once he got these guys on the hook,
there's no telling what information
he got out of them.
Technology, money, secrets.
He was a clearinghouse
for confidential information.
Safar must have known this.
He went to Dallas for something
specific weapons, intelligence...
maybe both.
Maybe as part of their deal,
Dallas offered Safar a night with one
of his girls, as a sign of good faith.
It's disgusting,
but perfectly probable.
So, Safar is being blackmailed
like everybody else.
But why would Dallas blackmail Safar
if they got a deal going.
Dallas is a criminal,
but he's not a traitor.
It's not like Safar could go
to the police.
- He could drive a car into the club.
- Interesting theory, but
Safar is a terrorist,
he's not Miss America.
Why would he care
if anyone had a sex tape on him,
despite the feculent content.
He's recruiting idealistic young men
to fight a holy war for Islam.
If a sex scandal
can bring down a Democrat,
what about a devout Muslim
on the road to martyrdom.
- Couldn't he just denounce it as fake.
- Publicly, sure.
I'm guessing if that got out, Safar's
sleeping on Salman Rushdie's sofa.
So you think you can lure Safar out
of hiding with this tape.
But you don't even know
where to find him.
I need to get a message to Safar.
Some of you listen to his teachings
and know how to reach him.
A friend of mine has
something he wants.
All the information he needs
is right here.
All right? Just plug it in.
My friend's number's on it.
Carry on, gentlemen.
Beginning to think
you weren't going to show up.
Hope you brought cash, 'cause,
I don't take travelers checks.
I am not paying you
or Dallas or anyone.
Is that what you came out here
to tell me? Look,
you know the deal, Safar.
Either you pay me $50,000
or your little
sexcapade goes out on CNN, Al Jazeera
and the Home Shopping Network.
- Not if you're dead.
- Kill me, the tape still goes out.
It won't matter.
By then, you, the girl and Dallas will
all be dead, and I shall be forgiven.
That's your plan? What, are you going
to shoot me out here in broad daylight?
You won't even make it off the pier.
After I shoot you,
I'm going to shoot that elderly man,
then those children
and several of those young women,
before I have to reload.
By then, no one will be getting
in my way.
Point taken. Let's take a walk
and let's talk about this in private.
- Just leave them out of this.
- The time for words is over.
Gun!
Don't move!
Turn over!
Get up!
I am but one
in a legion of warriors.
True warriors don't use innocent kids
to do their dirty work.
You are the friend of Mowadh.
The man who killed his father.
What?
Who is using children now?
I'm not using anybody.
I gave Moe a new life.
And now, so have I.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Sam, back off!
Not this way, not this way.
What's going on, man?
Where are you going?
I got your message to Safar.
- What else do you want?
- Listen. Hold up.
I'm not letting you get
until you tell me where you're going.
- You can't stop me.
- Wait a minute!
What are you going to do?!
Kill me like you killed my father?
Is it true?
- Did you murder my father?
- I was protecting innocent people.
Your father was working
with the Janjaweed.
- Everything you said to me is a lie.
- No, no. Come here. No.
I didn't lie to you.
I didn't tell you everything
because I wanted to protect you, man.
I know you're hurt, all right?
I'll tell you everything you want
to know about me, about your father.
Let's just go talk about this.
The time for words is over.
Good bye, Sam.
So, I got a lawyer for Katya.
Still not sure
how that's going to play out.
- Did Sam hear anything?
- No.
- What about the deal on Safar?
- Turned him over to the CIA.
They'll try to turn him into an asset,
put him to work,
find out what he was planning.
They also took
the blackmail material.
Do you think that will ever see
the light of day?
Not publicly.
But it will be put to use.
On the street it's called "blackmail".
In government, it's "leverage".
Speaking of leverage,
Hetty told me I had to give
in my case reports every Friday by 5:00,
and I was really counting on having
the weekends to get caught up.
- I'll talk to her.
- Awesome. Thank you.
You are my hero.
Did you find Moe?
No. His foster family
has no idea where he is.
Youth center's claiming ignorance.
Got a hit on Moe's passport.
He's on an Air France flight to Paris.
- What time's it leave?
- Left.
By the time you told me
to start looking, it was too late.
That's all right, Eric.
Is Paris his final destination?
He's on a connecting flight from
Charles De Gaulle
to N'Djamena, Chad.
From there, he'll probably try
to slide across the border into Sudan.
- Why would he go back?
- He's looking for answers.
Keep tracking him.
Moe's father used to work
with the Janjaweed.
I killed him.
Does Moe know?
Now he does.
So what are you going to do?
Right now?
Go for a run.
Last time you said that, I had to drive
out to Joshua Tree to pick you up.
I'll bring my cell phone.
What's up with Hetty?
You, too?
So is this another money-saving cutback
or are you,
writing
your tell-all Hollywood memoir?
It's a eulogy for an old friend.
I'm sorry.
This was his typewriter.
It seemed fitting, almost poetic,
three hours ago.
Now, it just seems like a...
lachrymose act of folly.
I can't help you there.
Lachrymose-intolerant.
You would have liked him.
He was the perfect combination
of scholar, soldier,
and scoundrel.
Was he romantic?
No, I'm afraid he was married...
to his job.
He worked for the intelligence service
in England.
Never married,
no children, but a stellar career.
He died
alone in his office,
filling out paperwork.
Something
you'll never have to worry about.
Is that why Nate's being forced
into exile?
That man
hasn't taken a vacation in years.
And what about you?
When was the last time you took
a day off that wasn't caused
by a bullet?
I don't want you waking up one morning,
wondering if it was all worth it.
I'm sorry if I was...
a tad strident today.
I just want to make sure that...
you all take the time
to smell the roses.
How about Saturday?
There's a Rembrandt exhibit
at the Norton Simon Museum.
- I'll pick you up at 11:00?
- Rembrandt, Mr. Callen?
Don't get too excited.
I just go there to meet chicks, so...
Essentially, you'll be my wingman.
I relish the assignment.
If only it were true.
What about tonight?
I think I'm going for a run.
Just tell me we're not running
to Joshua Tree this time.
Bugger!
.: Team UnderCovers :.