You've been aware of drug
dealers working your premises?
Because a responsible, conscientious
club owner like you would be aware.
Right, Alan?
Yes, of course.
How old was that last girl
we talked to would you say?
Fifteen, no older then sixteen.
We just got this new bouncer.
He's a bit of an idiot.
The girl's charming, you know...
Did they charm you, too?
No.
Tonight, your night?
- Yes, I wanna tonight DJ.
- That's right.
You run it for Alan.
You're his boy.
Right, I want copies of your
licence, financial records
purchase orders, guest lists, the lot.
By tomorrow.
The club was over
capacity by 200 tonight.
Are you listening?
We let everybody in, underaged
people, they were all underage.
Yes, so?
And do you know drug dealers working
- we see them on that...
- I don't know that!
And neither do you, okay?
So shut the fuck up, Thomas.
Yeah?
- Bonus.
- What's for?
For shutting the fuck up.
And if you do slip up,
someone will come, Thomas,
and snap your fucking spine.
Come on.
Thomas, where have you been?
Merde.
Mom.
- God what's...
- Daniel is ill again.
Who is that with you?
Hello Kasoke.
You know my rules.
It was too late to get home.
We're not gonna, you know, do anything.
Like what?
You know, having sex.
But we not gonna have
sex, we wouldn't do that.
No?
Yeah, I mean...
We have done stuff, possibly I'm not...
Lows, probably you could say lows.
Okay maybe you should stop talking now.
Yeah just, "the whole truth, nothing
but the truth, so help me God", mh, no.
Bloody hell.
Someone tell me please, where
to find a virgin in this country.
Well, difficult.
Hold him up.
It's okay, Dan-Man. Thomas is here.
What were you doing that was more
important than your family this evening?
Speak to me boy.
Mom, a girl died tonight.
That's my club-nights.
I think she was on drugs, or any...
Now she's dead.
What's that?
Money.
We don't want it.
- We do, we need it for...
- We don't want it!
Why do you bring
trouble to the door?
We have enough here.
Now go and do, what you're meant to do.
I put Daniel to bed.
We were waiting for you.
Who are you?
Daniel wanted to story
about, I didn't mind...
I don't think you're selfish.
But I don't think you're tickly
Get off.
Mom says, we've got to pray.
Please...
Kneeling.
Dear God in the sky, help
us to care for each-other,
let the sun shine, send
us songs and keep us safe.
And don't kill Daniel.
- Right, don't do that.
- Amen.
- Sleep now, okay?
- Okay.
Night, Daniel.
Night.
Panda...
Panda, we can't, my mom will hear.
I don't care.
My blood feels frozen.
I keep seeing her face.
I need you.
Come on, Thomas, dance.
Friends, friends, please.
Remember the power of God.
Thomas, it's a long time
since we've seen you.
Yes, sorry.
He's fooling father,
fooling and fornicating.
His friends, his girlfriend.
They are bad for him.
- You don't know my friends.
- I know enough.
- That girl, she is a who...
- Kasoki, please.
We do not fight here.
Thomas, I expect you to say
that your friends are not so bad.
They love you and they are there for
you in times of need, no matter what.
- Yes?
- Yes.
Are you sure about that?
Thomas...
We are your people.
And we will never ever let you down.
But we are waiting for
you to take the first step.
That first step into a wider world.
- That's Star Wars.
- Excuse me?
Obi-Wan Kenobi says that after
Luke gets shot by the floaty-thing.
Obi-Wan?
"Well done Luke, you have taken
your first step into a wider world."
- That's good.
- Yes,
because Obi-Wan Kenobi is like
God, but with better weapons.
Obi-Wan Kenobi rules.
Ok, everybody. Watch the card.
See?
Thommo, how the fuck have
you did a-little, man?
- What do you want?
- Oh, all right...
I just thought you might
wanna friend today, that's all.
Give me that shit with that girl.
She was fucked up beyond.
***
- You're not my friend.
- Okay, I'm just saying...
How do you know she was fucked up?
I don't. I mean you just...
Assume, don't you?
Yeah?
Excuse me.
You!
Yes?
Would you mind awfully not smoking?
Thank you.
Just thought that I pop down and say:
Hi I'm David Blood, your
new college director.
And. I'm saying "Hi".
What happened to Harriet?
Harriet has moved on.
- Why?
- Because, because, because...
Let me see, how can I put this?
Because this place is rubbish.
And so are you.
So now...
We're all about change.
Everything's going to change.
We'll all do it together yes?
We can, change...
And if any of you find that difficult,
I want you to know that
I will find you,
I will interrogate you
I will expel you,
I will expunge you.
Great.
Doug has an announcement,
it's very important.
So I know we will all listen carefully.
Otherwise it's rude.
Isn't it, Doug?
Yes of course it is, David.
Professor Blood.
Professor, yes.
So, welcome back everyone.
Oggy, oggy, oggy!
Great, lovely.
And I'm afraid the police
would like to interview you all.
Katie Fitch.
This is fucked up, I didn't even know the
girl. Why are they treating us like criminals?
Because she's dead.
- And we were there.
- So?
That doesn't make us responsible,
if some kid decides to off herself.
Right Naomes? Naomes?
Yeah, it's fucked up.
Cook, we've gotta wait here.
I've gotta slash, don't I?
- Hey, Freds.
- Yeah?
Have you heard from her?
Who?
The Empress Cleopatra, who do you think?
Na.
Thought she might
just show up, you know?
- First day back...
- Yeah.
Well, she didn't.
I touched a nerve.
Guys, you've got to not talk about Effy.
Why?
She really fucked Freddy over.
No, we're just not going there.
I mean, me Cook and Freds,
we're getting through it.
She dumped you all?
Kind of.
Effy's gone and we're happy.
The status of the tribe is
protected. We're happy, right?
Good.
As long as we're all happy.
What are you doing, Cook?
What is this?
The dump police?
I'm thinking somebody
gave that girl drugs.
Yep. So?
It was you. I'll tell them.
Yeah? Fuck you, Thomas.
Tell them what you want, mate.
Never met the girl.
How's your girlfriend, Cook?
I don't have a girlfriend, Thomas.
How's yours?
Still got that dirty
little walt on her ass?
Come on then Thomas, come on at me.
Fucking never finished have we?
Cook.
Cops called your name, mate.
Thomas?
What you doing?
Working. Just work.
Panda needs a hug.
Thommo?
Come on.
Everybody's skipping next
period and going to White Hart.
We all need a drink, get some shots...
That's your answer to everything,
just go and get pissed?
No. Häagen-Dazs is the
answer to everything right?
Come on.
It's all just fucked up.
I don't know anymore. Just don't know.
I know.
What you doing?
Making us feel better, come on stupid.
No. I don't want to.
I'm sorry, I just,
I have to do this work, okay?
I have to get it done.
Fine.
Hello.
Come up, I'm bursting.
I hate prayer group.
Just wait, you have
to be good here, okay?
I gotta go, I'm telling you.
She always needs to go. Girls.
Yes. Why can't you at the right time?
This is the right time
moron, I gotta w-e-e.
Thomas, welcome.
Oh, you came. Cool.
This is Thomas, dad.
Oh yes. I know who he is.
It's coming out.
Quiet! Everybody, quiet!
Everybody.
Everybody, Jesus. Get shut up!
Now we were just about to sing a song,
weren't we? So what should we sing?
- Rihanna!
- Lady Gaga!
Beyoncé!
Those are all people,
who can't really sing,
don't wear very many clothes
and get married far too young.
What do we call that sorts of people?
- Americans!
- That's right, Americans.
Now listen.
What?
- Come on, sing.
- Sing, sucker!
Enjoying yourself?
Yes, it's fun.
I'm wondering...
How is it you spend over a year
at the same college as my daughter,
and only just met?
- I don't know.
- I do, Thomas.
After I spoke to you, you started
noticing things, didn't you?
Things that have always been
there, but you have never seen.
I suppose. She's beautiful.
- She is a beautiful singer.
- She is. She serves the Lord.
If you put your trust in
him and obey his rules,
you see the world in a
new way, it's wonderful.
Just...
Open up your heart, Thomas
and give me your soul.
Give it to me.
Thomas, Daniel's sick. Thomas!
Oh, my God.
Daniel, sit up.
It's okay.
It's okay, Daniel. I got you.
Lung infection. It's okay,
we'll clear it up.
Is he okay?
- Daniel.
- He's fine,
Mrs. Tomoni. We're on top of it.
They brought him straight here.
I told you to look after them,
what did you do to my baby,
Mum, I brought him to
Pastor Babajide's house.
It concerns me that this is
the third incident in six weeks
So?
Now I'm just saying, if there
is an environmental factor,
if your house is damp or dusty...
- My house is clean.
- Yes, right,
but he shouldn't be here this often.
I look after my children, you
can mind your own business.
Mum, the house is dump.
There's mold and the walls are wet.
- We can't get rid of it.
- Right.
Well, then that would...
perhaps social services.
Who are you? You don't know me.
What do you know about
bringing children up?
I've given everything
to you, all my life.
And now you want to tell me what to do?
You have no respect.
If your father was here,
he would beat you.
My father is dead and
he is no use to us!
- Is he all right?
- No he's not, nothing's all right.
- I'm sorry.
- So am I.
Thomas, hang on please.
- What's the matter?
- I can't stand this place.
- This country, no one understands.
- It's all right.
No, nothing makes sense. I can't...
I just can't...
I can't do it. I can't.
It's all right.
It's all right, Thomas.
Something said to me, we need to cheer
up, what we need is a Reese-a-thon.
Oh, and I brought JJ.
What I like about Reese is,
she is a virgin you can believe in.
- What's this one called again?
- Red neck bride.
I feel that was "The Last One".
No, that was "That Damn Man".
Got it, she is ****
No, that's "Kentucky Bride Hitchin'".
Go on, get one. Go on.
I'm all right.
- I got your favorites.
- I'm not hungry.
What's wrong? Don't you like the film?
It doesn't make sense.
What do you mean?
Now you don't understand, why Reese
goes back to Matthew McConaughey
after he slept with Rachel McAdams.
No, I gotta say, you make a fair point.
No, I don't mean that.
Yes, but Reese forgave
him, he made a mistake.
That's what I love about her,
when you make a mistake...
I slept with someone.
Go on, she hid the ring
in her bra, you tit!
You gonna use the metal detector again.
Idiot.
What?
I slept with someone, it wasn't you.
Na, na, na, that's not it.
She is going make him think,
she put the horse down...
and then she's gonna sleep with him,
'cause she thinks they're still married.
You did it first.
- You did what?
- I did it!
I did it, okay? I wanted to.
You fucked it, Thommo.
Ah, Thomas, would you
mind coming with me?
Involvement in the girl's death,
brings your college into disrepute,
and for that reason I am
going to expel you.
Vodka.
Another.
Hey, it's Thommo.
How the fuck are you still deadly
married, jamming cheating todger?
What did you say?
- Everyone knows, mate.
- Your such a tit, Thomas.
- She loved you.
- Yup.
Pissed on our Panda Pop, didn't you?
Who's the lucky lady
anyway, to got Congo-cocked?
This is for selling drugs
in my club, you bastard.
- Now the girl is dead.
- Thomas.
She is dead you cunt.
You fucking killed her.
Break it up, you should stop it.
- Stop.
Dead, dead girl.
Thomas stop.
Come on, then you fucking...
Thomas, Thomas. It was
me, I gave it to her.
What? You what?
Cook, Cook dealt me
the powder, that was it.
I needed the money, and I
just sold it to some random.
She died. She is dead!
I didn't mean that.
Please don't tell anyone.
Do not tell Emily.
She would...
Thomas.
Good evening Papa Babaj... Babaj ...
You're drunk.
No, no...
I was wondering, if maybe
I could possibly see Andrea.
I feel sorry for you, Thomas.
No, no. I need to talk to...
Andrea!
I need to talk to you.
Thomas!
I need to speak to someone.
So tell me what you
did that's so terrible.
I betrayed someone, I love.
With you.
I see.
You feel so right.
Everything about you ... is like home.
- But...
- It doesn't work like that.
You love her.
Good bye, Thomas.
I don't know, why we came here.
For a better life.
I can change things.
You will love this place.
Make your deposit now
and it'll be yours today.
Can I come in?
No, you fucker.
Pandora, we started again
before, can we do it now.
I don't think so.
But I love you Panda.
I know you do, Thomas.
I told him no like you said.
Good.
Eat up.
Well done, he needs to
think about what he did.
I'm glad you're back, Eff.
corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com