We'll be meeting
with agents
from the FAA,
the NTSB and local police.
Usually Booth handles
those people.
Plane crashes don't belong
to the FBI.
Why not? FAA stands
for "Federal Aviation
Administration,"
the NTSB stands for
"National Transportation
Safety Board."
That sounds federal to me,
and FBI stands for Federal...
Zack...
It's the third time
in a row
we've investigated
without Booth.
I don't like it.
Why? He mostly
ignores you.
Ignoring me is Booth's way
of acknowledging my presence.
It's a guy thing.
Here we are.
Dr. Brennan?
Yes.
I'm Ian Dyson
with the NTSB.
This is my assistant,
Zack Addy.
At approximately
0400 last night,
a private jet with five
passengers on board
reported horizontal
stabilizer trouble
200 miles southeast
of Norfolk.
Yeager Airport in Charleston
tracked them for 30 minutes
until they dropped off the radar
screen at 0430.
The plane tried to make
an emergency landing here
when it clipped some trees
and slammed to the ground.
We found another mostly intact
body over near the trees.
The rest is bits and pieces.
What makes this
one of our cases?
I beg your pardon?
We're kind of special.
We're elite.
We don't sort
through just any
set of bodies.
It was a State
Department flight
with a bunch of VIPs on board.
Is that special enough?
I apologize
if I've offended you.
Usually, we have
an FBI agent
who mediates
our interpersonal encounters.
We found another skull.
Two skulls.
Those, uh, pieces
are from two different skulls.
I'll leave you super elite types
to it.
Zack, we don't need Booth
to mediate our interpersonal
encounters.
Pilot, copilot,
brings our count to six.
Three mostly intact sets
of remains,
one partial and two fragmented.
Obviously, bodies are burned
to a crisp.
No dermis, very little
soft tissue, indications
of high-impact trauma;
burst fracture of the lower
thoracic and lumbar vertebrae
consistent with injuries
caused by the vertical impact
of the falling aircraft.
Should I keep talking
as though
you're paying attention?
What do you make of this?
A femur fragment.
No charring.
You think this fragment doesn't
belong to the plane crash.
What are the odds?
A crashing plane falling
directly on a human being?
One in... ten million.
The information that I'm about
to tell you
must not leave this room.
I am philosophically opposed
to institutional secrecy
in all its forms.
Fine. Get out.
Two Communist Chinese trade
attaches were on that plane
when it crashed--
both high-ranking
party members.
Well, obviously,
we shot it down.
The FAA and the NTSB
can prove
that it was an accident.
Also on the manifest
was an American businessman,
a pilot and a copilot.
Five people.
Dr. Goodman,
we found six sets of human
remains on that airplane.
Not to mention
three bone fragments
which were not on the plane.
Is there any chance those bone
fragments were on the plane?
What, you mean
as carry-on luggage?
No, everything on the plane
burned.
They were untouched by fire.
Hmm. And forget about the bone
fragments for the time being.
The State Department
is extremely anxious
to find the identity
of that sixth person.
No one wishes this to become
an international incident,
therefore this
is our only priority.
I disagree.
For the love of God, why?
Because the plane crash
was an accident,
bone fragments were not.
How do you know?
Zack found unusual cut marks.
Cut marks congruent
with dismemberment.
People,
one hour ago,
I received a call
from the Secretary
of State
requesting that the unidentified
extra passenger
be our first priority.
So, now politics
are more important than murder?
I'm not saying "please."
I'm not being
reasonable.
I'm making
the decision.
First and foremost,
identify that sixth body.
Got it, or you want me
to explain again?
I got it, okay?
The plane goes down,
kablooey.
There's an extra body
on board
which you really
don't care about
'cause you're more
interested in these
bone fragments
that you found
on the ground.
Exactly.
Oh, this all you got?
So far.
Piece of skull, chunk
of vertebra, part of a femur.
Not much to go on.
These fragments come from
a person who was hacked.
Hacked to little bits?
No, medium-size bits.
I'm not sure how it turned
into little bits yet.
Okay, and I'm here why?
Dismemberment,
little bits--
it's a murder.
FBI doesn't have
jurisdiction at a golf course.
Well, who does?
I don't know.
Try the PGA.
Uh-huh.
You know, you've done
a couple cases without me
and you miss me.
Zack misses you, not me.
Zack and I don't even talk.
He seems to think
it's a male-bonding ritual.
Maybe he's right.
- No, it's not.
Could be.
- You told him that
so you wouldn't have
to talk to him.
Well, it was nicer
than shooting him.
Goodman has ordered
me to investigate the
other extra body.
Well, then you better
get on that.
Next time you know you miss me,
pick up the phone, call me.
We'll do lunch
or something.
I do not miss you.
Come on. Say it!
I do not miss you!
Dr. Brennan,
Agent Booth,
you have a visitor.
No, I don't.
You miss me.
Dr. Temperance Brennan?
- Yes.
Special Agent Seeley Booth.
I'm Jesse Caine.
You're Jesse Caine?
You've heard of me?
I haven't.
Jesse here is sort
of an expert
on missing persons cases.
I've done some writing
on missing person laws
and investigative techniques.
Interagency cooperation,
jurisdictional dispute,
that kind of thing.
I heard about the bones
you found at the golf course.
I can't really talk about that.
I don't mean the Communist
Chinese on the plane.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Communist Chinese?
The other bones,
the fragments.
How'd you hear about
the Communist Chinese?
Those pieces of bone
you found on the golf course?
I'm pretty sure that's my dad.
Sync:FRM-xxy
-=http://www.1000fr.com=-
My expertise
in missing persons investigation
derives from one thing--
my search for my father.
He went missing five years ago
during a trip to his cottage
in Virginia Beach.
What makes you think
these bone fragments
come from your father?
You know, there is a question
of national security
here that is in
my jurisdiction.
He's not supposed
to know
about the Chinese.
My investigations
lead me to conclude
that my father was murdered in
the area and his body disposed.
What do the police say?
They gave up four years ago.
Because there was no evidence
of foul play.
The investigation was bungled.
The city police didn't have
the manpower.
The state trooper said
it was a federal matter
and you guys suggested
a private investigator.
It was not bungled, okay?
Because there was
no evidence of foul play.
It's a common story, okay?
A guy goes in for a pack
of cigarettes,
he ends up renting out
snorkeling gear in Guam.
He doesn't know what it's like
to lose a parent. You do.
You want back down
a jot there, buddy?
How do you know about that?
No offense, Dr. Brennan,
but you're a writer,
a well-known scientist.
It's out there.
Plus, you're one of us.
One of us?
People whose loved ones
have simply vanished.
In your case, both parents.
Okay, how do you know
about the Chinese?
Do not look
at Dr. Brennan, okay?
Whether you like it
or not,
this is an issue
between you
and the FBI.
If body parts are found
in roughly the area
my father disappeared,
I'm going to know about it.
Radio chatter,
the Internet,
the local law enforcement...
That's all I'm prepared
to tell you.
Do you mind if I ask you
how many bone fragments
you found?
Yes, I do.
I don't discuss ongoing
investigations.
She doesn't discuss
ongoing investigations.
Fair enough,
Dr. Brennan.
These are my notes
from the last five years.
Every lead, every clue,
every person I've ever
talked with is here.
And why would Dr. Brennan
care about that?
'Cause it will at least give her
a candidate to eliminate.
He's got a point.
My father's
medical records,
pictures, last
known whereabouts,
even a connection
to the golf course.
Also my phone number.
But don't worry.
If I don't hear from you,
you'll hear from me.
Pushy.
Well, maybe he discovered
that being pushy
is how you get cops
to pay attention.
What are you hawking
at me for?
The Chinese, the plane crash,
that's geopolitics.
This is murder.
Will you help?
Well, you know, I guess
if you're really asking me
I guess I could, you know,
budget with my boss
to make it
look like
it was attached
to the Chinese
plane crash thing.
We've made some progress
on the mystery passenger.
Fill me in.
Nasal ridges indicate
she was a Caucasoid female,
approximately five feet,
ten inches.
Epiphysial fusion
puts her age
somewhere between 20 to 25.
I have a theory.
Femme fatale
assassin.
Unregistered flight attendant.
Young beautiful girl,
doesn't appear
on the in-flight manifest,
group of high-powered
politicos...
Oh...
What? What?
Someone on
that flight
might have been doing
his daughter
or his girlfriend a favor.
You're so sweet, honey.
You really are.
Oh!
You think she was
the in-flight entertainment.
Yeah. Anything you want
to tell us
about the bone bits
you care about?
Supra-orbital margin
is rounded,
suggesting a male.
Yes, and there's signs
of osteophitic lipping
or polish on this piece
of vertebrae.
Arthritis?
So, middle-aged guy.
Weathering and
discoloration
suggests these bones
have been out there
for approximately five years.
I'm going to ask you guys
to help me on this.
You mean, after
the communist thing?
No, immediately.
I'm in.
You want us to defy Dr. Goodman?
Not defy, per se.
Do both jobs, but...
but keep one a secret.
I'm in.
We get it. You're a rebel.
Zack, I need you
to analyze the cuts on the bone.
I was kind of hoping
to keep my job.
There's not enough skull here
for me to do a reconstruction.
If I give you a picture,
you could tell me if the skull
piece doesn't match?
I could construct a schematic
and see if the shard
fit the general
shape of the skull...
if I had a picture.
Has anyone noticed that I was
the first to offer help
and apparently,
I'm useless?
Not true.
You're the one
that's going
to keep Goodman
from finding out.
I'm in.
CAINE:
So the bone fragments
are the same sex and age
as my father.
Yes.
Thank you.
It's a long way
from conclusive.
Yeah, I know
at times like these
not to get hopeful.
But, on the other hand,
you've got to have hope.
Even after five years?
People are found after decades,
Dr. Brennan. After centuries.
You've done some of the finding.
Booth says you've
made a living
off of the disappearance
of your father.
About six months
after my father disappeared,
I found out nobody
was actually looking for him.
Next thing I knew,
I was an expert
in motivating the police--
victims' rights.
Becoming well-known
is a byproduct
of my search for my father,
not the goal of my search.
You should understand
my motivation
better than most people
in law enforcement.
I'm not really
interested in bonding
over the loss
of my parents.
Booth is looking over
your file now.
I wasn't looking for his help.
We work together.
Booth knows that
the bone fragments
are evidence
of foul play.
That's all the
motivation he needed.
You didn't have to lean on him?
Not at all.
If you say so.
ADDY:
One of the bone fragments
has distinctive
ridge-mark indentations.
A knife mark.
Yes. Specifically,
a carving knife.
Well, what about
the other ones?
The jagged marks?
Some kind
of machine blade.
What? Like a... a jigsaw
or a chain saw?
( Goodman clears throat )
Are you suggesting
one of the
Chinese diplomats was wielding
a chain saw?
Uh... good one, sir.
Very droll.
Zack knows much more
about this than I do,
but we weren't discussing
a literal chain saw cut,
but, rather, the pattern
it leaves
on the bone.
Right?
Zack?
You know, blades move
in several distinctive ways.
Several distinctive ways.
Circular, elliptical,
segmented
Chain saws are designed to cut
soft materials at high speed.
When cutting hard materials
like bone, they create
wave-ridge walls
by the action of the blade.
This pattern's too organized.
Too linear.
HODGINS:
Therefore,
no Chinese Chain Saw
Massacre scenario.
Yes. Fascinating.
What has it go to do with
the victims of the plane crash?
We not only
have to reassemble
each of the plane crash victims,
but figure out how their remains
were scattered.
Not by being cut up.
That's for sure.
Now we've eliminated blades.
Never freeze
on me again.
I find Dr. Goodman scary.
Well, I'm never trusting
any of us again.
We're that good at lying, huh?
We're going to do much better.
Well, you know, I have to admit
Jesse Caine's file on his father
is both well-organized
and complete.
Yep. The main
suspect is his
father's girlfriend.
Karen Anderson.
No alibi.
And, since they were
living together
at the time
of the disappearance,
she remains in the house,
and has access
to their joint accounts.
How much money
are we talking about?
Max Caine, he was
a stockbroker.
He was worth millions.
But, you know,
after seven years missing,
the courts will declare him
officially dead.
By that time, she could have
siphoned out most of the money.
So I say we go
visit Miss Anderson,
and we'll know pretty fast
if she's a suspect.
How?
Subtle psychological indicators.
I looked those up
on the Internet.
Body language, sweat,
tonal quality,
shifty eyes.
Hey, you
know what?
I don't go poking around
your bone stuff, okay?
Just leave the human stuff
to me.
Why has Max's disappearance
become a matter for the FBI?
Max's disappearance
is not an FBI matter.
You're an FBI agent.
Human remains
were found
in the course
of a federal investigation.
Agent Booth is tasked
with the job of
identifying them.
I'd like to eliminate Max Caine
as a possibility, and just
move on altogether.
So this is a
pro forma interview?
Yes. Yes. Absolutely.
Because I know
Max's son Jesse
accuses me of Max's murder.
Why do you think
he suspects you?
Because of the age difference
between me and Max.
Because I'm still living
in the house.
Because, after five years,
I dared to fall in love
with someone new.
And who knows?
Well, some people find it harder
than others
to get over the loss
of a loved one.
Bones? Psst!
What?
Jesse got to you,
didn't he?
The dimples
and the sad smile
and melancholy,
on a mission
to find his beloved father.
You know all that.
Jesse didn't love his father?
Max and Jesse didn't speak
for the two years
before Max
disappeared.
And that was before
I came into his life.
What do you think
caused the rift?
Max cut
Jesse off financially.
Max thought Jesse
was lazy,
running around New York
doing nothing
with his life and,
well, Jesse was furious.
The hack marks
were caused
by a Heidel
carving knife.
And the osteological
profile suggests evidence
of postmortem freezing.
Max Caine disappeared midwinter.
What about the jagged cut marks?
This is the part
that makes me queasy.
The victim was frozen,
dismembered,
and fed into a wood chipper.
Then spread over a golf course.
Either talk
loudly enough
so I can hear all the way,
or whisper so I can't.
Maybe, if we told Goodman
what we know,
he would authorize
a change in priorities.
Or he'd
suspend us all
for defying him.
Angela's right.
So we're going to drop this,
and get back
to what Dr. Goodman told us
to do in the first place?
No. We are going
to keep doing what we're doing
behind Goodman's back.
That's the spirit!
Yeah. It's true.
My father cut me off
financially.
So I take it that means
you talked to Karen.
Anything else
you failed to mention?
Why didn't
you tell us?
I know I didn't
kill my father,
so I'd rather you didn't
waste your time
on that line of investigation.
Too late. So what happened
between you and your father?
Hmm?
About five years ago,
I was enrolled at NYU.
But all I really did
was go clubbing
and have a good time.
My father was right
to cut me off.
I was a disappointment to him.
But if only he
could see you now.
I like to think
he can see me now.
Your father is dead.
A dead person
can't see anything.
Maybe that's true.
Maybe it isn't.
But, either way,
at least I know
my dad would be proud.
Bones?
Tell Jesse
what happened to the victim.
Really?
What?
It's just
that usually
you tell me not to tell people.
Well, it can't
be worse than
some of the things
that I've imagined.
The victim was frozen,
dismembered,
and fed through a wood chipper.
Bones has
figured out
what type of wood chipper
was used, and we're trying to trace it
to the manufacturer and see if
one was sold in Virginia Beach.
I can't believe someone
would do that to my dad.
We haven't positively identified
the victim as your father.
I have our artists
comparing
the skull fragment
to pictures of your dad.
Could I see the bone fragments?
This is all of him?
Yes.
I mean,
it's all of somebody.
He was a big man, my dad.
It's hard
to believe
that this is all
that's left of him.
How can you
get anything
from three small bits of bone?
It's more than
a lot of people get.
I know where my dad was
right before he disappeared.
I know my dad
met with a client
at the North Star Grill
in Virginia Beach.
I know he had meat loaf.
I know he was supposed
to meet Karen at the pier,
but he didn't show up.
I know she waited
two days before
reporting him gone.
I have a good timeline,
and I have three small bits
of bone.
You don't have any
of those things,
and I realize how hopeless
you must feel.
Come with me.
This is all you have?
Yes. You were right
about how little it is.
No, I mean this is simply
your copy of the official file.
Yes. What else
would there be?
You never tried to hire
any private investigators?
Did any poking around
by yourself?
Well, I'm pretty new
at field work.
Mostly been a lab rat
my whole career.
Plus, I trusted
the authorities would
do what the could.
The authorities
have rooms filled
with files like these.
Warehouses.
I'm the authorities.
Booth is
the authorities.
Did you ever show this file
to Booth?
No. No.
This is where I work.
Uh... Which
is my cue.
Um... uh.. um...
Angela, come in.
This is Jesse Caine.
Hello.
Hi.
Hi. Angela
Montenegro.
What's that?
Uh.. uh... nothing
that can't wait.
Is it about my father?
You know, as far as I know,
which is quite far,
believe me, no one
has tried to
kiss Brennan
in this office
and lived to tell about it.
Angela.
Would one of you
please tell me
what that piece
of paper is?
It's a, uh...
It's a schematic
comparing a skull fragment
we found on the golf course
to pictures of your father.
And?
It doesn't not match
your father.
So it could be him?
Yeah. There's
a pretty good chance.
I knew it.
Are you hooking
up later?
I didn't arrange anything.
Why not?
Because you were
right there, hovering.
I was not. I was...
being your wingman.
What's that?
I was rendering assistance
and enabling where needed.
Booth thinks he
might be a suspect.
Oh, now you're just looking for
excuses not to get involved.
Plane crash victim number
four, Captain Jacob Howard.
Pilot, age 47.
Height five foot six.
Weight approximately
167 pounds.
Overlay
the photograph.
Frontal zygomatic
sutures line up.
Cranial menengies are in synch.
Excellent. That's
one more off our list.
Victim number five,
Shenru Fong.
Age 56.
Height five foot six,
weight approximately 140 pounds.
Yes, yes,
that's terrific.
Except, we knew all
of these people
were on the plane.
What the State Department
wants to know
is the identity
of our mystery woman.
I hope I can count on your full
energies on this, Dr. Brennan.
If I could be
completely honest, sir...
Toxicology reports came back
from all six victims.
Pilot and copilot were clean.
Our two Chinese nationals
had elevated levels
of alcohol and Sildenafil,
more commonly known
as Viagra, and our
mystery girl showed traces
of alcohol and cocaine.
So... will the cover-up
start now,
or somewhere between here
and the State Department?
You were saying about
being completely honest?
Yes, sir.
Regarding the bone shards...
Ah, the prostitute was
six inches taller
than anyone else
on the flight,
and she had occupational
stress markers.
Let's not call her a
prostitute yet, Mr. Addy.
What occupational markers?
Ah, it's a foot thing.
She was a fetishist?
Both her cuboid and medial
malleolus show signs of wear.
You can relax,
Dr. Goodman.
She wore extremely high
stiletto heels.
I reconstructed her face
from the partial skull.
She was hot.
What's our next move?
I suggest we
try to match
this reconstruction
with escort ads
both Internet and print
in the DC area.
Oh, I'll do that.
Was that overly enthusiastic?
Thank you for the update.
This case continues to be
your top priority, correct?
If I could suggest...
Dr. Brennan
has been very clear
about your priorities on this,
sir.
What's that?
The only Black Mantis
wood chipper in Virginia Beach.
I subpoenaed the records
fromhe manufacturer
and traced it back
to the town equipment yard.
My people, they, uh,
couldn't find
any blood residue.
That makes sense,
if the corpse was frozen.
Yeah,
not to mention
this puppy here has ground up
about 10,000 trees, you know.
Hey, I figure you
can match the blades
to the cuts on the bones, right?
Or do something
I haven't thought of
much more, you know,
confusing and scientific.
Booth. Nobody told me you
were working this case.
Only two people
have had access to this machine
in the past seven years--
city maintenance foreman and
a maintenance worker
by the name of Ray Sparks.
Sparks has got ejected,
so, what do you say, huh?
You want to come with me
to go talk to him?
Told you.
It's a guy thing.
Um... Yes, I'd
like to come.
All right,
here we go.
Let Angela do
the escort matching.
I have something a lot more
interesting for you and Hodgins.
What's more interesting
than escorts?
I need you guys
to run a dispersal
pattern test on the chipper.
Using what medium?
Assume the victim
was frozen solid
when he was fed
into the chipper.
No way!
The correct response
would be, "Yes way."
Oh. Yes way.
You ignore Zach
and make him think
you've got
some special bond.
Yeah, but it works, doesn't it?
I'm happy, he's happy.
It's not the truth.
But it works.
Ray Sparks, I'd like to have
a word with you, please.
Zach wants to fit into the real
world more than anything.
You're not helping.
FBI. Special Agent Booth.
He went around the back.
No, no. The other
way, Bones.
FBI. Freeze.
Ray Sparks.
Hey, I didn't
do nothing wrong!
Ah, I feel like
kicking him.
That's normal after a pursuit.
We try not to do that.
Too many people.
How we going
to keep this
from Dr. Goodman?
Ah, he's having lunch with the
president of Harvard.
What's going on?
Why is every guy
from the Jeffersonian out here?
They're scientists.
This is a fascinating
scientific inquiry.
Oh, my God.
They're all out here
because you're
going to feed something
through this wood chipper.
Not just something.
A frozen pig.
Ah... Ugh.
The morphology of pig bones is
almost identical to human bone.
By feeding the pig through the
wood chipper, we'll be able
to determine the dispersal
pattern of the fragments.
By comparing the
pulverized pig's remains
to the
fragments we found
at the golf course,
we'll be able to tell
if this is the
actual wood chipper
the victim was fed through.
Liars.
You just want to see
what happens when you toss
a frozen pig
into a wood chipper.
And here we go.
Ready?
One!
Two!
Three!
Yeah!
Okay, what have we got here?
Break and enter, assault,
drunk, disorderly. Wow.
Yeah. I been keeping
myself out of trouble
for the past
four years now.
How long you been a maintenance
worker for the city
of Virginia Beach?
Since '92.
You ever meet a guy
by the name
of Max Caine?
No.
Karen Anderson?
Yeah, I know her.
How?
She bartends at the golf course.
You don't strike me
as a golfer, Ray.
City land is right across
the creek from the course
and I, I go to the clubhouse
a couple times a week
to have lunch.
Hey, how'd you pay for that
house you live in, Ray?
I mean, that's,
that's pretty nice.
You got a hard time sticking
to one topic, huh?
My mom
left me the house.
She left it to me
and my brother Frank.
Five years ago.
Five years ago Max Caine
disappeared-- Karen Anderson's
boyfriend--
so, you know,
you can see how my suspicions
might be a little aroused.
Yeah, but the thing is...
I didn't live in Virginia Beach
five years ago.
I was in
Southampton
Correctional Center...
doing six months for skipping
out on a DUI warrant.
Guess I don't
need a lawyer, right?
There's no way that
wood chipper experiment
was connected to the plane
crash at the golf course.
Look...
- Don't say anything.
Just listen.
Your primary job
is to do as I say.
Failing that,
your job is to fool me.
You failed
to fool me,
Dr. Hodgins.
I'd have fooled you if you'd
gone to lunch as planned.
I'll find some administrative
ways to punish you. Parking,
dining room privileges,
budget reviews, that sort
of thing, but if
it happens again...
I got it.
No. You don't.
You think I'm
a kind and fair man.
Egoless, balanced,
ruled by
intelligent reflection.
But I do have an ego.
I can be vindictive and petty.
I will take you down,
even if it means
striking at you
through
your friends and coworkers.
Now you understand.
Ray Sparks was in jail
when your father disappeared.
He might have acted
as a go-between,
put Karen in touch
with the hit man.
One of the things
that you lecture about
is that the simplest theory
usually turns out to be true.
Usually, not always.
What's the simplest theory
in this case?
Disowned son realizes
that his father
may remarry,
lose his inheritance...
Booth--
are you accusing Jesse
of murdering
his own father for money?
You ever hear of the
Menndez brothers?
- I came to you about
the bone shard,
saying it might be Dad.
Hey, look, your father
is declared dead,
you get your inheritance before
Karen Anderson spends it all.
Oh, you don't seem too upset
about the accusation.
Agent Booth, for four years
I've been making enemies
with law enforcement.
Attacking me is
a pretty typical response.
Booth,
is this one
of those times
when you just
poke and prod
to get reactions?
Now, listen, Bones, we have
to treat him like a suspect.
He is not a member of the team.
Look.
I'm like you.
I need the truth.
I have to get back
to the lab.
Satellite imagery
of the golf course.
These three dots show
where the bone
fragments were found.
Can you show me the results
of the wood chipper test?
The "V" shape indicates
the maximum distance
from the point of origin
a bone fragment could have
traveled given similar
wind speeds and
ambient temperatures.
Okay, and remove
the plane crash.
It's irrelevant to this.
The question is...
in order to use the guys'
pig-grinding experiment,
where do we place
the wood chipper?
I bet the murderer...
aimed the wood chipper
over the stream.
So the evidence
would wash away.
Mm-hmm.
What's that?
That is...
a small access road
for maintenance vehicles.
Try putting the
wood chipper there.
Mm-mm!
Sweet smell of success.
We should see if we can find
any more bone fragments
here and here.
Are we any closer to identifying
our mystery woman?
Um... I'm not...
I'm not certain.
Brennan is still
waiting for an update.
I saw you come in, sir,
and I have an update.
I have a list
of possible matches
on our geisha in the sky.
She is Caucasian.
Our mystery woman
is definitely Caucasian.
We've sent a list
to the FBI
and they're checking it out.
Ah. Well, in that case,
you might want to
turn your attention back to the bone fragments.
I came for the file
on my parents.
You think I might
have killed my father.
No, it's just...
I asked the wrong
person to help me, and...
What?
I just don't think it's
healthy, what you're doing.
Putting your whole
life into this.
And I suppose
the way you're doing it,
putting nothing into solving
the disappearance
of your parents,
I suppose that's healthy?
We're searching the golf course
for more bone fragments.
Amazingly, we found
a piece of finger
with the nail
still attached.
And underneath
that nail...
Polyurethane.
The tough stuff.
The victim must have been
scraping at something
before he died.
Yeah, I can't identify
this bone anomaly.
It's full of osteoids.
Thick.
Maybe part of the mandible.
Human. Something odd
with the cell structure.
Wood chipper wouldn't do damage
at the cellular level.
It's a nonmalignant
bone tumor.
I need the most
recent bone scans
from Max Caine's
medical records.
Hodgins.
It's Booth.
The locals just arrested Jesse Caine
for attacking
Karen Anderson.rs
Local sheriff says
that Jesse showed up at Karen's
house to confront her.
He was ranting about
the murder of his dad.
Eddie tried to throw him out,
but the two of them,
they exchanged punches...
The fact that Jesse
confronted him doesn't mean
that he isn't the killer.
I know.
- You know what, he might have done this
just to make us think
that he was angry at her.
All right, he's smart.
No poking and prodding-- do you
think Jesse murdered his father?
No, Bones, all I'm saying
is we get into these things,
we look into murders,
we can't let our heartstrings
get all plucked, okay?
We got to poke
at people's wounds,
we're gonna make
them bleed a little.
We got to make them
tell us things
that they normally
wouldn't want to tell us.
We got to be willing
to be hard on them,
is what I'm trying
to say-- even when we know
that we're
no different than them.
You didn't answer my question.
Well, I have a opinion.
You want to know?
If I had to bet,
I'd say he didn't do it.
Me, too.
I'm going off my gut.
I mean, what's persuading you?
The bone fragments
at the golf course,
they didn't come from Max Caine.
That's great-- you knew that
when you asked me
what I thought.
You testing out
my instincts, Bones?
Poking and prodding.
I learned from the best.
Ha. Ha.
It's not my dad.
No. We don't know
who it is yet.
How can you be certain?
We found
a juxtacortical chondroma.
A nonmalignant
bone tumor.
Your father's X-ray showed
no sign of such a tumor.
Maybe he got it
after the X-rays.
The X-rays were
taken two months
before he disappeared.
It's a slow growing tumor.
It would have
taken...
years to get to the size
and density that we found.
Look, I'm gonna see if I can
get this assault stuff
to go away
and get you out of here.
I'm sorry, Jesse.
For what?
Suspecting that
I killed my own father.
No. I'm not sorry for that.
I know what it's like
not to know what happened.
I know how painful that can be.
And I'm sorry for you.
If the bones don't belong to
Max Caine, who's our dead guy?
We can send out a description
of the chondroma
to area hospitals,
see if it leads
to any missing
patients.
Yeah, we can do that.
List the pertinents.
Me? Are you talking
directly to me?
Yeah, you can tell because my
eyes are looking at you,
my mouth is aimed
in your direction.
But what about our guy thing?
If you're
speaking to me,
then does this mean
I'm not on the team?
Zack, let's concentrate
on the work.
Pertinents.
The victim died,
we don't know how.
He was then frozen,
dismembered with
a Heidel carving knife
and pushed through
a Black Mantis 1200
wood chipper.
The exact wood chipper
you fed the frozen
pig through.
The exact wood chipper that
Ray Sparks had access to.
But Ray Sparks
was in jail.
Ray was in jail when
Max Caine disappeared.
But our victim isn't Max Caine.
Well, who else would
Ray Sparks have motive to kill?
The victim
is a middle-aged male...
His brother.
What motive?
They both inherited the house.
Okay, you guys,
you look at the tumor,
and Bones and I will
go talk to Ray. Come on.
While you're there,
look for a large freezer.
Why?
The body was frozen.
Polyurethane is a common
insulating liner in freezers.
We found it under
the victim's fingernail,
like he was scratching
to get out.
The detectives who picked up
Sparks say he claimed
his brother was alive and
well last time he saw him.
Yeah, well,
he might have been
for about 30 minutes, until
he ran out of air in here.
My guys, they found claw marks
on the inner linings
on both sides.
What kind of person
could lock
a living human being
in a freezer?
What is that?
- That's a fingernail.
His own brother.
Hey.
Booth got you out.
1,200 bucks bail,
and a promise to stay
away from Karen and Eddie.
We solved the case.
And I'm sorry,
it's not your father.
We identified the victim.
His name was Frank Sparks.
I'm sorry I couldn't
help you, Jesse.
How do you live with it?
What, the disappearance
of my parents?
The fact that
nobody's looking.
I never thought about it
that way until I met you.
There's a Zen koan.
It says that if you want
to find something,
you have to stop looking.
I can't do that.
My dad's watching,
and I don't want
to disappoint him again.
Even if you don't believe it,
I know your parents are
somewhere proud of what you do.
It's not rational, but...
I love the thought of that.
Oh.
How'd Jesse take it?
Like an orphan.
What?
That's just...
That's a little poetic for you.
I didn't mean it that way.
I want to ask you a favor.
Oh, geez. Another favor.
I wonder if you wouldn't
mind taking a look at this.
The file on your parents?
Yeah. Okay.
You want to think about it?
It's a pretty big favor.
You'd do it for me.
Yeah, I would.
I'm proud you asked, Temperance.
Uh, Dr. Brennan.
Uh, Angela wants to know if we
should order anything for you.
Uh, no, I'm not staying.
Thanks, Zack.
Guess we caught
another one, right?
All for one and one for all?
I'll take a look and
see what they didn't give you
and I'll get
back to you, okay?
Back to annoying Zack?
All right, look,
I know you don't approve,
but, you know, it works for us.
It worked for him, so...
Yeah, I get it.
And it... It's kind of sweet.
Hey, well,
your people are my people.
I have people?
Hey, I have people!