NARRATOR:
Previously on Angel:
CORDELIA: The rain of fire, blotting out
the sun, those were the first steps...
...to something bigger.
- We need Angelus.
GUNN: Taking Angel's soul, putting it in
a jar? Hope we know what we're doing.
FRED:
Angel's soul. It's gone.
CORDELIA:
Angelus.
ANGELUS:
Catch you later.
The rumors are true. Angel has
left the building and I am back.
We're gonna save Angel.
I know who we need to help.
This is Faith the vampire slayer.
If Angelus needs putting down,
I'll be the one to do it, not you.
CORDELIA:
We're having a baby.
FAITH: Can you walk?
DRUGGED GIRL: No, but I can fly.
- What'd they do?
WESLEY: She did it to herself.
They shoot up, the vampires feed.
I've read the effects can be intoxicating,
for both of them.
MASTER:
Angelus!
I have wonderful plans for you...
MASTER: ... my sweet boy.
ANGELUS:
You've gotta do better than that.
[GRUNTS]
ANGELUS: Nothing will ever change
who you are.
You're just like me.
You're wrong. I'm different now.
I'm not like you.
You will be.
[GASPS]
What did you do?
ANGELUS:
You've gotta do better than that.
Come on, I'll give you one more.
Strike three!
You, you...
You spiked.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
You all right?
Kicked his ass.
Orpheus
GUNN:
Connor!
FRED:
Oh, my God. Angelus.
GUNN: Pick up your tranq gun.
I don't know how much time we have.
FRED: What happened?
GUNN: Wes called, I went.
Where is he? Where's Faith?
Well, what is all the...?!
Angelus! He's in the hotel!
Give me the steel shackles.
But maybe we're
already aware of that.
- All I had was rope.
- What's going on?
Get down here now.
Leg irons too.
CONNOR: She found him.
- Wesley and Faith, where are they?
- Get him downstairs.
- What happened to Faith?
She captured Angelus.
- What did he do?
WESLEY: Gunn?
- We got it.
- She looks not well.
- Is she gonna be...?
- Wake up. I need you here.
WESLEY:
Help me with her.
CONNOR:
He fed from her.
There's blood on his breath.
ANGELUS:
Kill you.
Scratch you out.
She's not making any sense.
And speaking of sense, have you been
on permanent sabbatical from yours?
Tell me you did not shoot that girl full
of junk and then feed her to Angelus.
- It was her choice. Faith knew the risks.
- Oh, she couldn't.
FRED:
Shh.
I know what that drug does. Especially
when they supersize the dosage...
...to make sure they get the job done.
And you damn well know it too.
- A coma?
- Yeah.
That's what it looked like
when Wesley brought her in.
Like she hasn't pulled that one before.
- I don't think she was faking.
- So the slayer snagged Angelus?
He's in the hotel.
- Is he locked up tight in the cage?
- Don't worry...
...I'll always protect you
and our family.
- That's sweet. Is he guarded?
- Faith really did a number on him.
What the hell is it with you and Faith?!
As if I didn't see the way
you looked at her.
She cracked her whip, and you liked it.
You were practically...
...in her leather-clad lap.
- No, I wasn't.
And how'd you do that, anyway?
What about the anti-demon spell?
I told you, Connor, we're different.
Me and your baby. But I guess
you can't even be loyal to our bed...
...let alone our little family.
I thought you would be a better father
than Angel was.
I will be!
I would do anything for us.
For you.
Wow.
Are my hormones out of whack or what?
Hello! Crazy pregnant lady, aisle nine!
Whoo!
[CHUCKLING]
Why don't you go see
how Faith is doing?
Go on. I'm concerned.
- I want to know...
- What's gonna happen to her?
Actually, I'd like to start
with what exactly was it, Wesley?
Orpheus.
Orpheus?
- Some kind of opiate?
LORNE: Mystical variety.
Humans inject it,
vampires feed off the humans.
Folks tried to deal it at Caritas. The only
folks I ever banned from my club.
- The 'vention.
FRED: But...
So if ordinary humans do this
junk, slayers are all super, right?
That's what makes it so dangerous.
Orpheus isn't entirely physical.
It's an enchanted drug.
Magic. This is what it gets you.
That, plus the biting, makes for
some serious psychic psychedelia.
And the more you take,
the deeper you sink.
It leads you down to Hell.
And leaves you there.
[FOGHORN BLOWS]
[TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
No! Hey! What is that about?
FAITH:
You tell me.
It's your flashback.
[CHUCKLING]
You know what the definition
of insanity is, baby?
Performing the same task over and
over, and expecting different results.
Learned that in murder rehab.
Miss Blow-It-AII, if this is my flashback,
why are you in it?
Don't know. Must be the magic side
effects of my incredibly simple ruse.
All right, so what is this, huh?
Puff the Magic Dragon City? Fairyland?
You'd think. I'm guessing it's more like
Angelus, This Is Your Life, because...
...Lack of Hygiene World?
Sure ain't mine.
Seriously, man, did you miss
the invention of the bath?
The whole way over here he crouched
in the filth with the animals...
...just to avoid human temptation.
This isn't my life, it's his!
Angel's?
It annoyed the crap out of me
the first time around.
This sucks.
Why do you get to be Marley's ghost?
Because I'm dying, dumb-ass.
Not soon enough.
Way I figure, I got one last job.
Babysit the psycho till they...
...shove a soul up your...
- Not gonna happen.
Then I'm whatever, dust in the wind.
Candle in the wind.
- There'll be a wind theme.
- I thought those suicidal tendencies...
...got squashed in the Enlightenment.
- I rolled the dice. Paid even odds.
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS]
[MEN TALKING AND SHOUTING]
Whistle while you're walking, boys.
You're trolling a graveyard.
Throw the bones.
Trippy.
Early '20s by the cars.
What is this? Chicago?
Oh, no. I remember this.
I remember this place.
- I gotta get out of here.
- Why? You freaking out?
- It's coming again.
FAITH: What's coming?
I can't do it again. I won't.
FAITH:
Angel, get out of the road!
[CAR HONKS]
[DOG YAPPING]
- Oh, no!
FLAPPER: Oh!
Dude, you just rescued a puppy.
Oh, my stars. You saved her, mister. Oh.
I'm in hell. This is hell,
and I'm in it.
Gee, big fella, how can I thank you?
We haven't fed on a human in decades.
She's begging for it, you moron!
- Get lost.
- Beg pardon?
Take a hike, Betty. Scram.
Well, pound snow, you mook.
Reliving Angel's good deeds.
You are in Hell.
Wicked.
[FAITH CHUCKLES]
WESLEY: There's only one thing
we can do for Faith now.
Finish what she started.
FRED: You mean re-ensoul Angel.
- Impossible.
We've been over this.
No jar, no soul. No soul, no Angel.
It's not that simple, Connor.
I've been doing some research...
It is simple.
Angelus is all that's left.
He slaughtered Lilah, now Faith...
- She's not dead yet.
- You're lying to yourselves.
You think that I'm taking this
personally so you don't have to.
But inside, you know I'm right.
We need to put Angelus down.
WILLOW:
I don't think so.
I think you need a witch.
- Did I come at a bad time?
WESLEY: Willow...
She's a witch?
Yes, hi. You must be Angel's
handsome yet androgynous son.
It's Connor.
And the sneer's genetic.
Who knew?
- Hi, Willow.
WILLOW: Hi, Fred. It's good to see you.
Oh, and it's the Marlboro Man.
Or at least his extra-stubbly, mentally
unstable, insomniac first cousin.
For the love of Hecate,
somebody stop me.
It's okay.
I'm a yammerer from way back.
Are there forces gathering?
Did the call of magic draw you here?
Oh, no. More like the call of Fred.
Of course.
Bring in the only living person
to ever re-ensoul Angel.
She has a fresh brain. I thought
she might see some things we missed.
Oh, hearing the thoroughness of
your research methodology...
...I don't think that's possible.
Oh. Go on.
We should probably start the debriefing.
- Where's Cordy?
- The guy who you're all...
...trying to magically re-ensoul
shot her with a crossbow.
- She's not up for visitors.
- I think she'll want to see Willow.
After all, she's traveled a long way.
And they have a history together.
[KNOCKING]
WILLOW: Hi, there.
- Long time no see.
It's okay, Connor, I'm fine.
How have you been?
Higher Power. You?
Ultimate evil. But I got better.
- Heard about Faith?
- Coma again.
What about Angelus?
Did you go down and see him yet?
I'm way avoid-y.
Too many memories. I'm just glad I don't
have to be in the same room with him...
...when I re-ensoul him.
CORDELIA:
Oh. You really think you can pull it off?
WILLOW:
Putting his soul back?
It's the first spell I ever learned.
Not going to forget that.
- What about the Muo-ping?
- The jar holding Angel's soul?
- Therein lies our boneage.
- Stolen right from our safe.
If we can't get the soul from the jar,
we can't put it back in Angel.
Question is, how do we
get the soul out...
...if we don't know
where the jar is?
And apparently the thing's
impervious to magic.
Yeah, I know. I already tried a
standard locator spell, but zero joy.
CORDELIA:
Right.
Plus, Wesley's shaman says there's no
way to extract a soul from a distance.
Soul trapped in a glass jar,
impervious to magic. It is complicated.
Tough nut to crack.
- Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
- I doubt it.
We just break the jar.
CORDELIA:
Can you hand me that?
That way we don't have to magic
the soul out, just break the glass.
Great idea. I'm really thirsty.
And then Angel's soul is still
released into the ether...
...and there's something
called Delothrian's Arrow.
We don't even need to know
where the target is.
Cordy, this is fantastic.
We're gonna get him back.
Don't you worry, princess.
It'll all be over soon.
I've seen lots of girls go through
just what you're going through now.
[SINGS "MACARTHUR PARK"]
[DONNA SUMMER'S
"MACARTHUR PARK" PLAYS]
Bring on the pain.
[MUSIC STOPS]
[BARRY MANILOW'S "MAND Y" PLAYS]
"Mandy," huh?
Must kill you he's got
a jones for the power ballads.
[BUZZING]
Ah.
Worst were the concerts.
[MAN AND WOMAN CHUCKLING]
[MUFFLED HEARTBEAT]
ANGELUS
You know what that's like?
Every time he gets close, I feel it.
Wanting to tear their flesh apart,
the hunger. It's like a blade in my gut.
Only it's not your gut, princess.
Angel's the one...
...that belongs on the outside,
not you.
Think it's that cut-and-dry,
don't you?
- That if Angel gets his soul back...
- When he gets it back.
You'll hang up your spurs
and ride into the sunset...
...knowing you put the monster
back in his cage.
But I'm always here, Faithy.
Deep in.
MAN 1: Can I help you?
MAN 2: Give me your money!
- Give me the cash in the drawer.
- Okay.
- Open it!
- All right. All right.
CASHIER: I...
- Come on! Now!
It's gonna be okay.
I'll get you to a hospital.
You're gonna be okay.
- All right, everything's gonna be...
- It, it hurts.
- Yeah, I know.
- "Doc, I think we're losing him."
God, I love this episode!
[BUZZING]
What is that buzzing?
CORDELIA:
Hear me, Angelus.
Heed my warning. Awaken at once.
Return from the darkness.
Or just lay there and let that redheaded
meddler put your soul back.
Whichever.
Look, it's working.
I thought Delothrian's Arrow
was used to protect good magics.
- It is.
- So how can you use it to break the jar?
The Muo-ping is a sacred object.
It's holy.
It's glass, therefore crunchable.
The sacred's what's inside.
"All life a container...
- for the heart of all life."
You've studied the Daharim.
It had to be something specific.
There's lots of jars in the world.
Can't shatter them all.
Well, I mean, you could,
but good things come in jars.
Peanut butter. Jelly.
Those two-headed fetal pigs
at the Natural History Museum.
Come on, everybody loves fetal pigs.
Sorry. I think my sense of humor's
trapped in a jar somewhere.
It does seem like you've given in
to that grumpy side of the Force.
A lot's happened. Not just Angelus.
I've been...
I've changed.
I've seen a darkness in myself.
I'm not sure you'd even understand.
I flayed a guy alive and
tried to destroy the world.
Oh.
So...
- Darkness. Been there.
- Yeah.
Well, I never flayed.
I had a woman chained in a closet.
- Oh, well, hey.
- No, it doesn't compare.
No, dark. That's dark.
You've been to a place.
You seem exactly the same
as when I left.
No other major changes I'm not up on?
Just little things.
So, Fred, what's her story?
God, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
ANGELUS: So who's your big hero now?
- It wasn't even his fault.
God, does the guy gotta pay
for everything?
Choices, little girl.
Ones you make with
your heart of hearts.
Uh-oh.
What's gonna happen?
He won't.
- I'm deep in, Faith. Soul or no soul.
- Angel.
Ugh. Ah.
He was gonna save him.
Or did he choose to be
a little slow on the draw?
Dinner by armed robbery.
Look at him, Faith.
You're a murderer. You know just
how good that blurry line tastes.
You didn't think my hell
was private, did you?
[ANGEL SCREAMS]
[GROANING]
LORNE:
She's in the barrens now.
They cry for a while.
Quiet mostly. Like they were letting
go of everything that meant something.
CONNOR:
How long...
...till?
Not long.
You can hold her hand.
[DOOR OPENS]
CONNOR:
Wesley.
You did the right thing.
She was brave, and she died in battle.
It's time.
[BELL RINGING]
You're good. Good bells.
Okay, now all I gotta do is contact
the spirit world, harness...
...the Delothrian Ebb, and focus it
through my little Marble O'Doom here...
...and we'll restore the Muo-ping's
entropic equilibrium.
- The jar goes smash?
- Smash-o-crash.
All I need to know.
I'll be downstairs, in case
the Prince of Darkness wakes up.
Okay.
- You ready?
- Should be a snap.
MASTER:
Stay your hand, witch!
You will not interfere with
what must come to pass.
[PANTING]
[WILLOW CHANTING MAGIC SPELL]
MASTER:
You think to banish me?
There's somebody in my head!
As long as the soul is under my
protection, it will never be freed.
[CHANTING]
I bit my tongue.
He's enormously powerful.
It's the dead Beast's master.
He contacted Angelus the same way.
He wants to stop us
from getting the soul.
Open the window, fill the stone,
inside outside, two made one.
You wanna go, Glinda?
We'll go.
Sure that she can handle it?
[CHANTING]
WESLEY:
I think she can hold her own.
It's okay, Faith. It's okay.
You just wait.
They'll get Angel back
and it'll all be worth it.
It'll all...
ANGELUS:
It'll all be worth it.
Is that what you try to
tell yourself, Faithy?
Is that the nasty lie
that kept those thighs...
...nice and warm in your prison bunk?
You kiss your mama with that mouth?
No. But I ate her with it.
And now for a poem. "Faith Goes
Gently Into That Good Night."
You're fading fast, baby. I can feel it.
All the same, I hear this
holler in the distance.
[CHANTING]
Tells me you're about to
get what's coming to you.
Or not. I have friends in high places.
[MAN GRUNTING]
Him not being one of them.
[RAT SQUEAKING]
- Ugh. When is this?
- When isn't it?
Twenty years after that stupid
doughnut shop, and his fingers...
...never smelled of anything but rat!
"I'm so sorry. I give up.
I'm gonna live in a sewer."
- He's paying for what he did.
- He's hiding from what he is.
Which may be a big pysch 101
revelation for you, cupcake.
I know this crap.
Why do I have to go through it again?
ANGEL:
Maybe because it's not about you.
Jackass.
WESLEY:
Do you feel that?
There's something evil rising in the hotel.
[CHANTING]
CONNOR:
What the hell is that?
Ignore it.
Find your target, leave my side.
Okay, then. Huge floaty head
not enough to scare you?
Then why don't we try...
And now she is on my last nerve.
[CHANTING]
If only this were a few weeks later.
Break the glass!
Where's Connor?
Let loose the soul!
CONNOR:
Cordy, are you okay?
[SCREAMS]
- Oh, shi...
- I don't believe this.
You're the one behind this
whole True Hollywood Sob Story?
Angel, it's good to see you.
- Hate the hair.
- Faith. Why are you still here?
Just waiting to see this
pervert get stuffed back...
...into the deep crazy ground
he came from.
Then what?
After that, what happens?
Probably something like that.
I had a feeling
the rules had changed.
She's not who you're after.
No kidding, rat boy.
The slayer will just be gravy
once I finish you off.
- I've waited a long time for this.
Faith, get up. Are you listening?
Angel, I'm dying.
Yeah, it's a lot easier
than redemption, huh?
Always so concerned with
the human condition.
It's no big mystery. They suffer,
they die. That's what they're there for.
ANGEL:
I'm not perfect, Faith.
Even with a soul, I've done things
I wished I could take back.
Like those Manilow concerts.
You son of a bitch!
CONNOR:
Cordy, I'm coming in!
- Ah! Ah!
- Oh, Connor! I'm so sorry.
I thought it came back,
that horrible floaty head!
Did it hurt you?
- Is the baby...?
- We nearly got killed!
Willow's spell must've opened
a gateway to something.
Evil. If she keeps at it,
there's no telling what will happen.
She's already let Hell
itself into this hotel.
I know. I've seen it.
It's not safe for you here.
I'm gonna make her stop.
Connor, you can't.
She's too powerful.
But you can stop it.
The reason for all of this.
You have to kill Angelus.
So now Angel's soul is just
floating around out there?
Yeah. Until I can channel it
into the Orb of Thessulah.
Connor shouldn't have run off like that.
I'm sure he's just worried about Cordelia.
Do you ever think their relationship
is maybe a little bit icky?
You have to kill your father.
You have to.
Now.
Before anything else goes wrong.
Ready when you are.
[CHANTING]
You know I have fought harder than
anyone to save Angel's life.
But there comes a time when you
have to weigh risk verses reward.
And as much as I love Angel,
as a friend...
Killing Angelus now is the only way
to guarantee our family's safety.
I know it in my heart now.
You're not just protecting me.
You're protecting the world.
Sometimes one death
can spare infinite pain.
ANGEL:
Faith, wake up!
Rolled the bones. You for me.
I used to think that there'd be
a point when I'd paid my dues.
Anybody notice a battle with
your alter ego going on here?
CONNOR:
What will I tell the others?
CORDELIA:
They can 't stop you if they don 't know.
CONNOR:
What about the sanctuary spell?
CORDELIA:
I can fix it.
We're special, Connor.
[CHANTING]
CORDELIA:
Special.
ANGEL:
Faith, listen to me.
You saw me drink.
It doesn't get much lower than that.
And I thought I could make
up for it by disappearing.
I did my time.
Our time is never up, Faith.
- We pay for everything.
- It hurts.
I know.
[CHANTING]
CONNOR:
Hey, Gunn.
You should know, they haven't
finished the spell yet.
ANGEL:
Get up.
You have to get up now, Faith.
You have to fight. I need you to fight.
You understand what I'm saying?
What won't I miss?
The moralizing.
Soul's already in the ether, boy-o.
I can smell it.
How about I send it off to that
big puppy rescue in the sky?
FAITH:
Arf-arf, psycho.
[ANGELUS CHUCKLING]
Faith.
Getting back into the game.
I guess I am.
Hey!
[CHANTING]
[ANGELUS SCREAMS]
- Need you to fight.
- I'm pretty clear about what you need.
Break me off a switch, son.
There's about to be a whupping.
She's alive! It's a miracle!
Connor, it's over. It's me.
Really.
FAITH:
Hey.
ANGEL:
How you feeling?
Like I did mushrooms
and got eaten by a bear.
- That about sums it up.
- Yep.
Now you're going to Sunnydale.
I think I prefer the bear.
But the way Willow talks it up,
that's where I'm needed.
You never stop fighting.
Hey, I was gonna, but someone
got all pep-talky on me.
Yeah.
I'm sorry I didn't get to see you,
our little brain tour notwithstanding.
Another time.
I have a lot to thank you for.
Well, that vice is plenty versa.
Don't even start.
It's only gonna lead to hugging and...
- We can't have that.
- No.
CONNOR:
All right, I get it. I messed up.
Hey, cheer up, punk.
It just makes you one of us.
You headed out?
- Hey, no tears, big guy.
- No, I'm good.
I wish I could've seen you
kicking the crap out of Junior.
It was pretty funny.
[GUNN CHUCKLING]
FAITH:
Wes...
Faith.
See? Brits know how to say goodbye.
Angel here wanted to hug.
No, I didn't.
You run a good show.
Yeah, sit back and let
the girl do all the heavy lifting.
That's pretty much it.
FRED:
I think that volume is outdated.
You'd know better than me, but there's
some interesting stuff about hell mouths.
- It might help.
- This is great.
I have to say, some day I'd love to bend
your ear about the Pergamum Codex.
Some of the really obscure
passages are actually Latin...
...translated from a demonic tongue.
They're kind of a hoot.
All this stuff about bacchanals
and spells and...
Actually, I think it's
probably funnier in Latin.
- You know how that is sometimes.
- I'm seeing someone.
Time goes by, Will.
Okay, good. Wagons west.
- See you guys.
- Willow...
He's gonna tell you how much
he owes you.
Oh, don't mention it. I got a slayer
out of the deal, so we're even-steven.
- I'll tell Buffy you said hi.
- Good. Thanks.
Oh, um...
Next time you guys resurrect Angelus,
call me first, okay?
[CLEARS THROAT]
So we're back.
It would seem.
ANGEL: Look, I know things have been...
CORDELIA: Sorry, Angel.
But if this is the speech about
how the worst is behind us...
...you may want to save it for later.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH SDH]