NARRATOR:
Previously:
This child, it's the one
good thing we ever did together.
[GASPS]
[BABY CRYING]
ANGEL:
His name is Connor.
- You've become a higher being.
- Me?
Get me out of here!
CORDELIA: The rain of fire, blotting out
the sun, those were the first steps...
...to something bigger.
ANGEL: The Beast has a boss.
My apologies, my master.
We're having a baby.
LORNE: A mystical pregnancy
right under my beak?
Having two part-demon parents
might explain the "whoosh" factor.
Connor, before our baby comes, I might
ask you to do some things for us.
I have this cleansing abracadabra
to clear my muddled mind.
Then you'll be able to read me?
[SINGING]
Has Cordy been a bad, bad girl?
All this time...
...it was you, wasn't it?
Took you long enough to figure it out.
But nice turn with the Lorne bait.
There was a time
I would have seen that one coming...
...eons before it ever crossed
your tiny little mind.
- Because you're so clever.
- On a scale of you to me? Pretty damn.
- Until now.
- All good things.
So, what finally tipped off
the great detective?
Tongue.
Slip of.
But this...
...my sweet baby.
"My sweet."
Same phrase the Beastmaster
kept using...
...when he was whispering
in Angelus' head.
Thought it was a bit femme
for the booming macho act.
That's it?
I get away with bringing the world down
around you and two words tingle...
...your spider sense?
WESLEY:
What we already knew...
...what he found out as Angelus.
All the circumstantial led to you.
Just needed to be sure.
A little late to the table...
...but I might have a few scraps left.
- Why are you doing this, Cordy?
This thing isn't Cordelia.
Is that what you think, hero?
She would never hurt
her friends like this.
- Or maybe you just don't know me well.
- I don't wanna know you.
Where's Cordelia?
[GLASS SHATTERS]
ANGEL: Connor, wait!
Cordy's not what you think!
Come on!
Wait, Connor...
You...
Inside Out
Sorry, just got your message.
Being close to Electro-Gwen can
really screw your equipment. What...?
- The hell happened to you?
- Cordy's evil.
Nice suit.
- It's not Cordy.
- We don't know that for certain.
Back it up for the new guy.
You saying popping mama
threw you a beating?
Kid Vicious did the heavy lifting.
Cordy just mwah-ha-ha-ed at us.
- Why?
- Beastmaster.
- You think she's working for him?
- She is the master.
Guy steps out for a few hours,
half the place goes supervillain.
Connor's not part of this.
- Evidence upside my head says contrary.
- He's just...
...confused. Again.
Now we know what she's been doing
all this time. She was grooming him.
As her champion.
She's the evil genius that's been
two-stepping all over us.
How? And when?
And give me a sip of that.
Has she been like this since she
got back from that higher wherever?
And what about that amnesia thing?
- Was that a fake out?
- Or a side effect.
Descending to a lower dimension
was probably disorienting.
Maybe this thing was curled deep inside
for the trip on some kind of autopilot.
All we know for sure is the real damage
didn't start until after Lorne's spell.
Oh, my God.
- We woke it up.
- That's what I read.
That's what Wolfram and Hart
sucked out of my noodle.
It wasn't Cordelia's future.
It was the Smacker Jack surprise.
Damn thing played us
right from the start.
From the inside.
Where it can do the most damage.
Everything the Beast couldn't
have done, it was this thing.
It spiked my blood at Gwen 's,
snuck into the vault, killed Manny.
Wait. When Gwen and I came in, faux
Cordy didn't have blood on its clothes.
- How'd it abracadabra that?
- Lizzie Borden.
It wasn't wearing any.
ANGEL: Stripped down.
Then gave Manny 40 whacks.
- Quick sponge down in the sink and...
- Voila, shower-fresh murder.
Taking out the Svear Priestesses
was much easier.
Slip out while the heroes
are chasing their tails...
... and slaughter the only hope
of banishing her pet Beast.
While everyone was reeling
from that failure...
... it was making sure my soul
was off the market.
And the vision of the spell
to re-ensoul you?
Misdirection.
Getting everyone to look over here...
... while the real action 's
happening over there.
That explains why my mojo's
been gunked up.
Queen be-yatch
put the whammy on me.
Then it let the monster out of the box.
More misdirection, more blood.
All designed to keep us off balance.
[LILAH GASPS]
It was Cordelia.
She murdered Lilah.
- We don't know if it's really Cordy.
- Or what she's got baking in her oven.
Evil and pregnant?
I'm guessing it ain't cookies.
CORDELIA: Are you sure
Angel won't be able to follow us?
CONNOR:
I was careful.
CORDELIA:
How careful?
Why were they trying to hurt you?
You know why.
They're afraid.
Of you, of me.
What our love has created.
They were gonna kill it and me,
if you hadn't come.
I didn't know where you were.
I thought something bad might have
happened. I followed your scent.
But I never thought...
How could he do that?
Because he hates you.
I didn't want to believe it...
...but he does.
He hates you for being with me.
He can't stand the fact that he lost.
That he'll never know the feel
of my touch...
...or the warmth of my lips.
You were right about Angel.
He's an animal.
And he's turned everyone against us.
I'd kill them all
before I'd let them hurt you.
My sweet, sweet boy.
WESLEY:
Any luck?
I swept the area until daybreak.
Checked the sewer tunnels
in case they went underground.
Picked up their scent
half a dozen times, but...
If Connor doesn't wanna be found,
he won't.
Wasting your time.
I'm getting good at that.
It was all there.
Right in front of me.
And I couldn't see it.
- The thought of losing her to Connor...
- Did exactly what it was supposed to.
Play on your emotions
to cloud your judgment.
Draw your attention away so this thing
could continue to murder anyone.
At least you had a reason
for letting it happen.
Wes.
- Lilah and I weren't exactly friends...
- You were mortal enemies.
Why should you care
what happened to her?
Because you did.
There's nothing here.
If this thing could obliterate
all references to the Beast...
...it's very unlikely it would
leave its own bio laying about.
What about pan-dimensional texts,
like the one Lilah...
I have Lorne reaching out to
the black markets, but it'll take time.
Great. Another thing we don't have.
Then let's go to the source.
Whatever happened to Cordelia...
...took place after her ascension
to the higher planes.
- Maybe the Powers might...
- Last couple of times I asked them...
...for help, they made it damn clear
they weren't in the business.
At least one of those
was to save Darla's life...
...a mass-murdering, ex-vampire dying
of syphilis. A strong "no" is not a shock.
You think the Powers couldn't see
this thing was masquerading as Cordy?
What it was doing to us?
They didn't stop it, because they
didn't wanna get their hands dirty.
What we need...
...is somebody who does.
Somebody right in the middle
of all this.
CORDELIA:
More hooks.
Great.
- We could try to find someplace else.
- No.
This will do for now.
Hey, it's okay.
We're gonna be all right.
I know. I just...
I can't believe he tried to kill you.
Maybe it wasn't really Angel.
- Connor.
- Angelus could've tricked us again.
It was Angel. You know it was.
Everything he said.
About how I could help
make the world a better place.
About being a champion.
Lies.
Meant to keep you in your place...
...where he can watch you,
control you.
But Fred...
...Gunn, Wesley, even Lorne.
I thought they were...
...good.
- What does that mean?
Really. Being good,
doing the right thing?
By whose judgment?
Good. Evil.
They're just words, Connor.
Concepts of morality
they've forced around your neck...
...to yank you wherever they please.
You're with me now.
You don't have to live by their rules.
You remember why?
- Because we're special.
- That's right.
We're special.
And our baby...
...is going to be extraordinary.
A bunch of candles, a couple
of broken pieces of the Muo-ping...
...and some toiletries that smell
way too pretty to be evil.
Not much to go on. As insidious liars
go, it kept Cordy's room nice and tidy.
- It even vacuumed.
- Keep working on locating this thing.
- Lf I'm not back in a couple of hours...
- You're dead, we're screwed, world ends.
Or you could stay here with us.
Here's nice.
I've done this before. Don't worry.
Walk in the park.
[GRUNTS]
[ANGEL SIGHS]
I really hate the park.
[CRUNCHING AND SNARLING]
Ah!
Angel, jeez.
- Don't they knock in your dimension?
- Sorry.
Wasn't sure it was you.
Powerful demon Skip, at your service.
Hey, I got some more buffalo wings.
And the game's on at 5
if you wanna just...
I'm a little pressed right now.
When was the last time
you saw Cordelia?
- Who?
- She told me you were her guide...
...when she decided
to become half-demon.
She did?
Okay, look, I wanted to give
you the heads-up...
...but you know how the Powers are.
Always making with the big hush-hush.
- What do you know?
- This is gonna be really hard...
...for you to accept, but Cordelia
has ascended to a higher plane.
- Oh, I know. She's back.
- Back?
- Or something that looks like her.
- Wait. No one comes back from paradise.
- Okay, a slayer once, but that...
- So you haven't heard anything?
Not since her ascension.
Oh, it was beautiful.
Should have been there.
- You were a part of that?
- It's in the job description.
As Cordelia's guide,
I'm there for all important events.
Except her welcome-back party.
So why didn't the Powers
invite you to that one?
Mysterious ways.
That can really drive a guy nuts.
Or maybe if you'd known something,
you might have warned us.
The only one not keen on that slipping
out is the one pulling her strings.
- Not following you, champ.
- You said it yourself. You were there...
...guiding Cordelia to her ascension,
seeing her off to a higher plane.
Which is exactly where this thing
needed her to be to make its move.
So I think either you've been played
for a dupe like the rest of us...
...or you've been in on this
from the start...
...Skippy.
[CHUCKLING]
Angel, buddy, whatever's going on,
I'm telling you true.
Not a dupe.
[GRUNTING]
- Not like last time, is it, monkey boy?
- Ah.
You know, the worst part
about signing on for this gig...
...was having to take a dive when you
rescued Billy from his box of fire.
I mean, come on. You really think a guy
built like this would be so easy to drop?
This time we do it for real, champion.
This time...
...you lose.
CORDELIA:
He won't give up.
You know that, right?
He won't stop until he finds us.
Let him come.
I can take him.
Come over here.
I want you to know
what you're fighting for.
[CORDELIA LAUGHS]
- It moved.
- Of course, that's what babies do...
...when they're happy.
I can't tell you how thankful I am...
...that I found someone like you.
I just...
...wish they could let us be happy.
- I'll make them.
- You can't. They're too afraid.
But maybe when they see
how beautiful our baby is...
You think that will change
how they feel?
Our baby's gonna change
everything, Connor.
How soon before we can show them?
A week.
Maybe two.
But he'll find us before that.
I know he will.
- He'll find us, and he'Il...
- I won't let him.
I promise.
I don't want you killing each other.
It's never what I wanted.
Maybe there's another way.
A way to bring our baby
into the world now.
Before anyone else can hurt us.
How?
I'll need some very special things.
Do you think
you can get them for me?
Well, now, this is just embarrassing.
Tell me what happened to Cordelia.
Or what,
you'll bleed on me some more?
You know, I've always wondered
how many chunks...
...you gotta hack off a vampire
before he goes all dust bunny?
- Tell me what happened.
- Yeah, heard that part.
What are you, Tarzan?
See, this is the nefarious meat
of it, pal.
You die never knowing what really
happened to the woman you love.
Gotta respect the classics.
[CHUCKLES]
Do you really think that's gonna...?
Yeah, I do.
FRED:
Hey, here's something.
Maybe I can...
[SCREAMS]
- Have an embolism!
WESLEY:
What happened?
- We had words.
- Between the pummeling?
Whatever's happened to Cordy,
he's part of it.
We need to bind him to this dimension.
Before he wakes up would be nice.
Mmm. I really love virgins.
[SCREAMS]
You all right?
- He tried to...
- I know. Did he hurt you?
No. No, you stopped him. Thank you.
Thank you. Oh, God,
thank you so much.
Thank...
CORDELIA:
She's perfect.
Did you get everything else?
Yeah.
I know what your heart
is telling you, Connor.
But it will lie to you...
...if you let it.
You have to trust me.
Be sad.
Mourn for her.
But never forget the truth.
She's one of them.
One of the average,
normal people that fill this world.
But what we are doing...
...will elevate her life beyond that...
...and give her death meaning.
Her blood for our baby.
That's more than fair.
Isn't it?
Sand of the Red Palm.
- A child's trick.
- Then why don't you come out and play.
- In time.
ANGEL: You'll have a lot of that...
...after we make your accommodations
a little bit more permanent.
Fred.
"Sphere of the Infinite Agonies."
Every second a lifetime.
Should be able to whip one up in...
...20 minutes.
- Everything you know...
...or she starts whipping.
Hey, whoa. I'm just a merc.
I go where the deal is. And not
getting stuck in one of those? Bargain.
Anybody got a cig?
Cordelia.
- Where is she?
- This is your dimension. You tell me.
The real Cordelia, not this thing
that's been posing as her.
How'd I ever get spanked
by such a chump nut?
That thing which has turned your life
into a burning ring of fire...
...she is the real Cordelia.
She's in there somewhere.
It's this whole thing.
- Is it Cordy or not?
- Oh, it's her.
She just ain't driving.
Something took control
on a higher plane?
Drill a little deeper, Hoss.
How you think
she got there in the first place?
You're saying her ascension
was all part of this thing's plan?
No. Cordelia was chosen
to become a higher being...
...because she's such
a pure, radiant saint.
Please.
[CHANTING MAGIC SPELLS]
It's okay. I'm not gonna hurt you.
Please.
I brought you some water.
I gotta get home.
My mom's gonna be so mad.
I'm sorry.
I won't tell anyone, I promise.
Please, just let me go.
[WOMAN WHISPERING]
Somebody there?
DARLA:
I've always been here...
... close to your heart.
After all...
...isn't that where a mother belongs?
The Powers have sent me
to give you a message.
You can't be my mother.
I have her memories, her feelings.
Isn't that what makes a person
who they are?
GIRL:
Let me go.
Please.
I know that sound.
The look in her eyes.
The smell of fear.
I've nurtured it a thousand times...
...in all the people that I've murdered.
My mother's dead.
But I'll always be a part of you.
You shared your soul with me once...
...when you were growing inside
of me...
...when I'd lost my own.
You brought light to my shadow.
Filled my heart with joy and love.
I'd never felt so close
to any living thing as I did...
...to my beautiful boy.
Why did you leave me?
- Did you hate me that much?
- Baby, no.
I wanted to be with you
more than anything.
You killed yourself.
I wasn't born, and you...
Did what I had to.
My life...
...for yours.
I did so many terrible things, Connor.
So much destruction...
...so much pain.
You were the one good thing
I ever did.
The only good thing.
I'd die every day
for the rest of eternity for you.
And this...
...is how you repay me?
- You don't understand.
We need her...
...for our baby.
To keep it safe.
By anointing it in the blood
of an innocent?
You really think that safety can be
plucked from the arms of an evil deed?
Good. Evil.
They're just words.
Don't let this happen, Connor.
Don't let my death mean nothing.
Do you think it matters? Nothing...
...will change what's gonna happen.
Cut the doom and gloom.
What's taken over Cordy?
Something beyond
your comprehension.
To give it voice would rend your
feeble brain into a quivering mass of...
Fred, Infinite Agony.
Okay, you got me.
It doesn't even have a name.
- Then what do you call it?
- You know, master or...
...hey.
- Unspeakable horror. For real this time.
It doesn't make sense.
Cordy was made a higher being because
she proved herself to the Powers.
By bearing their visions,
this thing could...
Unless it maneuvered her to inherit
the visions in the first place.
Better step on it.
The rubes are catching up.
ANGEL:
It wasn't just her ascension.
Everything that's happened to Cordy
in the past few years was planned.
You really think it stops with her?
You know how many lines have...
...to intersect
for a thing like this to play out?
How many events have to be nudged
in just the right direction.
Leaving Pylea.
Your sister.
Opening the wrong book.
Sleeping with the enemy.
Gosh...
...I love a story with scope.
No way. We make our own choices.
Yeah, sure. A cheese sandwich here,
when to floss.
But the big stuff,
like two vampires squeezing out a kid...
- Connor.
- An impossible birth...
...to make one possible.
- That's what the kid was designed for.
- To sleep with Mother Love?
- To create a vessel.
Look out, the monkey's thinking again.
Being in a human makes it vulnerable.
That's why it had to stay hidden.
Why it needed to create something
stronger to pour itself into.
Wait. So the big nasty inside of Cordy
is gonna give birth to itself?
Circle of life. It's a beautiful thing.
- How do we stop it?
SKIP: That's the easy part, slick.
All you gotta do is find Cordelia
and chop her head off.
- Has to be another way.
SKIP: Sure.
Stab her in the heart, kidney.
- Couple of pokes in the...
- A way that won't kill her in the process.
Takes a whole lot of cramming to get
that much sweetness into a human.
It's in every hair, every cell,
every molecule of Cordelia's body.
And it ain't letting go until
it got a brand-new bag.
What happens to Cordy then?
Drained of her life force during labor.
Those contractions are a real bitch.
- It'll kill her?
- Or she'll end up a head of cabbage.
- What do you wanna do?
- The only thing he can do.
Kill the woman he loves
to save the world.
Times like this...
...really gotta suck being you.
- How do I find her?
- How?
- Well, I'd go with the Bu'shundi Ritual...
...but you're gonna need
a sacred Hutamin paw for that.
- Got it!
- What?
Cordy, the real Cordy,
kept one in her desk drawer.
Probably a knockoff. It's not some
trinket you throw in a desk drawer.
- She thought it was a back scratcher.
ANGEL: Get started.
Wait, wait. Did I say Bu'shundi?
I meant Ru'shundi.
It's a whole different...
Crap.
They hate us...
...because we're special.
I don't hate you. Please.
They're scared because of what you've
done, not because of what you are.
They wanted to kill me
when I was still inside of you.
But that changed
when they saw you.
Held you in their arms.
Felt the warmth of your skin...
...the goodness in your heart.
And it will happen again
when they hold my child.
- It's the only way.
- You have a choice, Connor.
That is something more precious
than you'll ever know.
What choice?
They're hunting us like animals.
Because you're acting like one.
As a vampire, I killed without mercy
or remorse because I didn't have a soul.
What's your excuse?
- You think I want to do this?
- Then don't.
I have to.
Why?
Because she told you?
There are things happening, Connor.
Things that I can't...
It has to be your choice.
You can stop this.
Her blood for our baby's.
It's fair, isn't it?
- Please. I wanna go home.
- Shut up!
This isn't you, Connor.
[GIRL SOBBING]
You've been gone a long time, Mom.
How would you know?
Because we shared a soul.
I feel the pain, the anger,
the hurt like it were my own.
But most of all...
...I feel the good in you.
And no matter how much you're
beaten or twisted or lied to...
...it's still there...
...in your heart.
I know it...
...and deep down...
...you know it too.
FRED:
What do you think he'll do?
What he has to...
...like he always does.
FRED:
Will it make a difference?
If we really are just pieces
being moved around a board.
Then we'll kick it over
and start a new game.
Look, Monochrome can yap all he wants
about no-name's cosmic plan...
...but here's something I picked up
rubbing mojos these past few years.
The final score can't be rigged. I don't
care how many players you grease...
...that last shot always comes up
a question mark.
But here's the thing.
You never know
when you're taking it.
It could be fighting
the Legion of Doom...
...or crossing the street,
deciding where to brunch.
So you just treat it all
like it was up to you.
The world on the balance...
...because you never know when it is.
You been practicing that?
A little bit.
Hug your neighbour, kiddies.
We got it.
You're all puppets.
- Shut up.
- Where is she?
Well, according
to the scorch marks, downtown.
- Meat packing district.
ANGEL: Good work.
- Let's load up.
ANGEL: No, you're not coming...
...any of you.
Whatever's taken over Cordy...
...it's still her inside.
She's still our friend.
She's still the woman l...
- I won't let you carry that. I can't.
- Anybody got a hanky?
He's really gonna do it.
He's going to kill Cordelia.
He doesn't have a choice.
Angel, wait.
Yep, that will go well.
Shh. Shh.
It's okay.
DARLA:
You're all right now.
- Everything's going to be all right.
CORDELIA: What are you doing?
Nothing. I...
It's time. Take her in the other room.
Listen to your heart.
She didn't do anything.
- We should let her go.
- No, we shouldn't.
We need her, Connor.
Our baby...
Shouldn't be anointed
with innocent blood.
Anointed?
Who's been filling your head
with big, confusing words?
CONNOR:
Just been thinking about it.
Or maybe...
...a little birdy's been pecking
at you behind my back.
She'll lie to you.
You know how much they love
to use the magic, Connor.
A spell for this...
...a spell for that.
- Close her out, baby.
Whatever you're hearing,
whatever you think you're seeing...
...it's a trick.
- Don't let her in.
- It's Angel...
- No.
...trying to turn you against me...
...with a cheap vision...
...of Darla.
- You can see her?
- I see the lies.
- Connor, listen to me.
- It's not her.
- You have to let her go.
- It's your father.
- This is how much he hates you.
- I love you. Please.
Torturing you with this sad imitation
of your dead mother.
- Don't let her do this.
- You'll let them do this to us?
Are you gonna let them kill our baby?
Connor, listen to me.
You are not my mother!
[GIRL GASPING]
Please don't do this, Connor.
Don't.
CORDELIA:
There.
That wasn't so hard, was it?
Connor.
We have to do this.
While it's fresh.
[CORDELIA GROANING]
[CHANTING]
Do it, Connor.
Do it now.
[CORDELIA SCREAMING]
GUNN:
Fred!
FRED:
What's happening?
End of the world, cupcake.
For you.
- Ah!
CONNOR: Cordy!
Something's wrong.
- We have to stop it.
- No. It's coming.
[LAUGHING]
It's coming.
The beginning of a new world.
ANGEL:
Or not.
[LAUGHING]
What a bunch of pantywaists.
If you can't stop little old Skipper...
...do you really think
you've got a chance against that?
She lied to you, Connor.
Don't listen!
To all of us.
- That's not Cordelia.
- Leave us alone!
CORDELIA:
Kill him!
Kill him, Connor!
What was that
you were saying before?
Something about Infinite Agony?
You mind? I'm trying to work here.
[GUNSHOTS]
Those things ever work?
I mean, really.
Well, that ain't right.
ANGEL:
You think I wanna do this?
I don't have a choice!
I'm so sorry.
[SCREAMING]
[ANGEL YELLS]
Oh, my God.
You're beautiful.
Angel.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH SDH]