LORNE: A mystical pregnancy
right under my beak?
[GRUNTS]
GUNN:
You're a Power that was?
ANGEL:
We've all been saved.
Hello.
Bless you all for coming.
I scrubbed the other one till my
fingers bled, but I couldn't get out the...
- Fred?
- Blood.
I can't believe Fred's evil.
I'm so sorry.
FRED:
Jasmine's blood...
... somehow it breaks her spell
when it mingles with ours.
Fred infected Angel. He's gone.
We have to help the others.
We need more of Jasmine's blood.
FRED: He figured since Cordy
gave birth to Jasmine...
... they might share a blood link
as well as a mystical one.
What are you doing to the...?
WESLEY: Your wrist, you've cut it.
What happened to you?
ANGEL: We hoped Cordy's blood
would have the same effect...
...when we exposed you to it.
- Thanks for nothing.
- I'm not leaving this hotel...
...without my son.
- Hey.
[YELLS]
You're back with us now, Connor.
They're here!
Come quick, they're here!
Connor, you have to listen to us.
Listen to you?
You're the ones who lie, who hate.
- No...
- Jasmine's controlling you...
...controlling your feelings.
- You're wrong...
...about me, about her. Everything.
But it doesn't matter
anymore what you say.
We're going to tear you apart.
Run! Get to the car.
Get out of here. I'll hold them off.
Someone who knows the truth has
to live through this.
- Go!
- Come on.
CONNOR: I'm finally part of something.
I belong.
I won't let anyone ruin that.
[GRUNTS]
I know, son.
This is wrong.
There has to be a way we could...
We could cut the power
as a diversion.
She has hundreds of followers in there
acting with a single, focused will.
We can't risk going against that.
Not now. Someone...
ANGEL:
Drive.
- We can't just leave him. He's your...
- I know what he is. Wes, drive.
Sacrifice
[WOMAN SPEAKING
OVER RADIO]
And in an impromptu speech today,
the mayor...
I really love that guy, don 't you?
The mayor declared Los Angeles
the First Citadel of Jasmine...
... a cradle of civilization which will
usher in a new age for all humanity.
In related news, the L.A. Archdiocese
has stated to the press...
... that it will remove all false idols
from its churches...
... replacing them with images
of She Who Walks Among Us.
Way to go, Catholic Church.
Well, talk about media bias.
Not that I want to talk about media bias.
Seems rather moot right now.
Speaking of moot, what about us?
Anyone else feel like
the last feisty wife in Stepford?
What are we gonna do?
What can we do?
There has to be an answer.
There has to be a way.
We need time.
To hell with that.
We need a damn break.
But the universe don't seem to be
handing breaks out to underdogs lately.
No leads, no database,
no weapons, no shelter.
Very little gas.
We should have taken Connor with us.
He looks...
What if he doesn't wake up?
What if we took him and he did?
JASMINE:
Thank you. Now, please come to me.
Connor...
...you're awake.
You're...
...indescribable.
I know.
They tried to turn me against you.
They cut me.
Rubbed blood into the wound.
The hateful always have one
or two wretched tricks to play.
You must rest now.
We have nothing to fear from them.
They are alone.
We are many.
But Gunn
and Wesley and Lorne.
They've all been turned.
- We have to stop whatever they're...
- We will.
Connor, there's
nothing they can do.
Every moment that passes,
I grow closer to my followers.
I feel what they feel,
I see what they see.
We're fusing together
like the cells of a single body.
They're my eyes,
my skin, my limbs...
...and if need be...
...my fists.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
- I don't know. It's a lot of pod people.
- It's better than the last three places.
We won't make it out
of the city without gas.
So that's our big plan?
Just keep running?
I hear good things about Belize.
If we could get out of the sphere
of her influence, we could warn people...
...prepare some form of resistance.
Look at them. They're all so happy.
Yeah, they'll be happier when they're
gouging out our eyes and stomping us.
- That's why we have to do this fast.
- Fast works for me.
Gunn, they're just under her spell.
But if it does come down
to a choice between us or them...
Believe me, I'm there.
Sorry, bro, it's for your own good.
That's right. It's the big bad
Free Will Gang gassing up.
ANGEL:
We don't wanna hurt anybody.
JASMINE'S VOICE: But you are
hurting them, Angel, just by being.
Okay, that's new.
You're a disease in the body Jasmine,
and you'll be purged.
Soccer mom, 12:00!
[SPEAKING IN
JASMINE'S VOICE]
You can't outrun my love.
It has wings made of radio.
[SPEAKING IN
JASMINE'S VOICE]
My love sings over the wires
that bind this world.
Okay, getting a little creepy.
JASMINE'S VOICE: The city is mine,
vampire. All its tools are mine.
Yeah, we're working on that.
Okay, pit stop's over. Let's go.
No snacks? I thought snacks were...
[SIRENS WAILING]
[JASMINE LAUGHING]
Never seen so many cruisers.
We're the only criminals left.
No way we're driving out of this.
It's time we disappeared.
Yeah, I'm moving, Angel-cakes.
Might not look like it. But inside...
...where it counts,
I'm running full speed ahead.
Won't take them long to figure out.
One minute.
No one under her control
knows these tunnels better than you.
- It should buy us some time.
GUNN: Time to do what?
Get all stanky and starve to death?
I mean, what are we doing?
I don't know what we'll do.
I don't have a plan.
This whole "Jasmine world order" thing
took me by surprise.
- I ain't eating no rats.
- Good, neither am I.
- All right, plan's coming together.
- Glad to see you're on board.
Oh, God, all the chasing
and the chaos...
- Cordelia.
- I can't believe I almost forgot about her.
Do it.
Forget about her.
We all have to now.
We don't have a choice.
The minute's up.
[SKITTERING]
Connor.
CONNOR:
Look.
JASMINE:
I know. I saw it through you.
It was them, wasn't it?
It horrifies me to see
what they're capable of...
...how far they've let their hate
take them.
They cut into her
while she lay sleeping.
Her precious blood stolen...
...for their black, deceitful,
cowardly magic.
They're always using magic.
Leave me.
I want to be alone with my mother.
You look a little down, sugarplum.
Is it Cordy?
- I can't. I don't care what he says.
- I know, kitten.
But underneath that blood-feeding,
creature-of-the-night facade...
...he's heartless lately.
ANGEL: Hearts get in the way.
- Hearing as good as ever, though.
ANGEL: If we don't gut ourselves...
...burn out everything inside that gave
her power over us, then we're lost.
LORNE: I hate to say it,
but I've been lost for, like, two hours.
Still, I miss her.
I miss the warmth
and the knowing what's right...
...and that you're
doing it just by loving her.
Tough drug to kick cold turkey.
I remember the first time she took me
aside, that fight at the bowling alley.
Me, pale, frail Winifred Burkle,
sitting with a goddess.
She was asking me
what her name should be.
It seems strange now,
a being of her immeasurable age...
...you'd think
she'd already have a name.
Maybe it was embarrassing,
like Hester or Peanut.
[YELLING]
GUNN:
I gotcha.
[CLANGING]
- Wes.
- I'm all right.
No, you're not all right
till I say you're all right.
- Holly, you good?
- Yes.
- Trip.
- Yeah.
That ugly beastie so much
as breathes wrong, stick him.
Ugly... Hey.
You know, I kind of have a thing
about people pointing sharp, wooden...
Give me that.
Enough! Enough.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- It's okay. They're not under her power.
- Her who?
- We'll ask the questions.
- Angel, are you sure?
They're not fighting like a well-oiled,
mind-controlled army of love, are they?
- No, more like a bunch of little punks.
- Punks?
Gunn, let him go.
Gunn?
- Charles Gunn.
- I say you could use my name?
I say you could use my ride
without paying the piper?
What? Paying the...?
Tommy Golden's little brother?
Randall?
Little ass Randall Golden.
This punk stole my car
when he was 12 years old.
- What are you doing down here, man?
- Like I said, son, we'll ask the questions.
[SKITTERING, MOANING]
Starting with, what the hell was that?
It's back.
I'm sorry.
I just couldn't be...
Cordy?
Connor, Cordelia's blood
is a danger to us.
If she falls into hateful hands,
the hate can spread.
- But where is she?
- She's where I want her to be.
And so are you.
Now, come.
Connor.
GUNN: Wow. Really like what
you've done with the place.
LORNE:
Yes, this is homey.
ANGEL:
So it's secure?
It's held so far.
Uh-huh.
Held against what?
Don't know exactly.
Never have gotten a clean shot.
It's not like anything I've ever seen.
Golden's brother used to soldier
in my crew back in the days.
Then he broke off and went solo.
Tommy was running our unit
when the sun went out.
We stayed topside as long as we could,
tried to hold some ground...
...but there were too many of them.
We go out every day
to check the tracks...
They're your crew, aren't they?
You're the leader.
I'm Matthew.
It's okay. All the other ways in
are grated off.
We checked.
Well, now I'm checking.
He's so young.
We found him in a pileup on La Brea.
Vamps laid tire traps on the road...
...having themselves
a car-wreck picnic.
He watched them murder his parents.
They were coming after him
when we showed up.
Matthew, you got any water
in this place?
Yes. We tapped a clean water pipe
right over here.
Anyway, I knew about this place.
Used to crash up here nights
when the missions were full.
So we hit a supermarket that hadn't
burnt down yet and got some supplies.
We went under.
Been down here ever since.
About two weeks and some change.
No offense,
but two weeks here...
...and I'd be ready to move back
with my mother.
Yeah, well, we were holding our own.
Occasional baddie looking for a place
to sleep. Nothing we couldn't handle.
Till that thing out there
moved into our territory.
It's been picking us off ever since.
It got Tommy almost a week ago.
He was out resetting the traps.
Whose blood is that?
Somebody I knew.
Somebody who tried
to do bad stuff to my friends.
- I can't believe you stayed down here.
HOLLY: Worse up there, ain't it?
The world is ending.
What does it matter where we go?
Besides, whatever that evil son
of a bitch is, it killed our people...
...it killed my brother.
We're going to kill him right back.
It's weird, really, us running
into you like this. I mean, we...
We're professional monster killers.
Or we were.
Are, Fred. We are.
- Hey! That belonged to Tommy.
- Now it belongs to me.
Let's go get professional
on this evil son of a bitch's ass.
I heard that.
JASMINE:
Yeah.
Of course. Drop by anytime.
Thank you for calling.
Police lost them hours ago.
Let me go out.
I'll bring them down, I promise.
Soon. Soon you'll go out
with all of my strength behind you.
But first, we have to celebrate.
That was the governor on the phone,
very agreeable.
He's dissolving
his administration tonight.
The time of the politician is over.
This state now answers to me.
Oh, it's happening.
Don't you feel it?
This world is about to kneel before me
and shed all its avarice, all its woe.
I will free them from the Loneliness...
...from the empty horror of their lives.
They won't know what hit them.
I'm sure of that.
And you'll be there at my side.
We will live in a palace built
by the love of billions.
It will make the Pyramids of Giza look
like headstones in a pauper's graveyard.
We'll be a family, Connor.
Together, as one, forever.
It's going to be beautiful.
Yes.
Then why aren't you smiling?
I don't know.
I think I do.
To belong,
to truly be a part of something...
...you have to surrender
to it completely.
- Cordelia has done that, but you...
- I want to, really.
There's a part of you
that you've kept from me.
Your pain.
I don't understand.
Pain has been the only constant
in your life.
The one thing
that has never abandoned you.
You think that pain is yours
to keep and bear alone.
But it's not.
I want it.
I want everything you are, Connor.
Father.
Let it go.
Let me have it.
Okay.
FRED: They're just kids.
- Strength in numbers.
- Angel...
- They just want to strike back...
...at something, anything.
I know how they feel.
I ever tell you I suck at sports?
This is where Tommy got taken.
- What's that smell?
- It's ammonia.
[GROWLING, YELLING]
MATTHEW:
Golden!
[SWORD CLASHING]
ANGEL:
Matthew, it's okay.
Matt!
Matthew!
[SCREAMING]
[SKITTERING, WHINING]
Golden? Sweetie.
- Lf Matthew reaches the surface...
- We'll get him. Come on!
FRED:
Matthew!
That thing is really pissing me off.
Lorne, Wes.
- Yeah?
- Where's Wes?
We loved her first.
LORNE: It got Wes?
- It must have looped around behind us.
It knows these tunnels better than me,
and it's fast.
I'll track it down.
Lorne, take the others back to the fort.
- Wait for Gunn and Fred.
- Lf you insist.
Uh-uh, Dracula, not okay.
All right, fine, you loved her first.
Before your kind was,
my kind loved her.
Stood stone on stone, built the temple...
...always making ready.
[WHINING]
But she came here.
She?
- Jasmine?
- Eh?
Jasmine. That's what we call her.
The superior being...
...that you loved first.
You name her. You filthy little mice!
She is the Devourer...
...the song...
...the peace, the whole.
And you try to name her.
Work to do.
We loved her first.
And how does your kind define love?
Same as all bodies.
Same as everywheres.
Love is sacrifice.
GUNN:
Matthew!
- Matthew!
FRED: Matthew?
- You sure he went this way?
- Heard splashing. It's gotta be him.
Unless it was one
of those skittering creatures.
Well, it better skitter out of my way.
I ain't in the mood.
FRED:
Or it could just be rats.
Now, what did you have to go
and say that for? Damn!
Sorry, I wasn't...
I'm sure if it's not Matthew,
it's probably some horrible monster...
...but definitely not...
- Look at us...
...where we are.
I mean, yesterday we were happy.
Happier than I thought possible.
Now we're trudging through sewage...
...hunting some kid to drag him
back down here...
...so he doesn't find out
a Shangri-La-La-Land up there.
He's scared, Charles.
Think how he feels.
You heard Angel.
Feelings don't enter into it anymore.
That the world we're fighting for?
The right to be heartless
and uncaring shells, to be dead inside?
We'll be dead period
if Jasmine gets a hold of that kid.
- We're fighting for our survival.
- That's not enough, not for me.
Maybe you can turn off your
feelings like Angel can...
...leave those we care about behind.
You had no trouble turning off
your emotions when...
- When what?
- Nothing.
- What were you gonna say?
- Forget it.
- When did I ever...?
- When you and I killed a man.
I mean, when I did.
- We did.
- Whatever.
When the circumstances called for it,
you did what you thought you had to.
It didn't matter
what anybody else thought.
You're right about all of it
except for one thing.
What we did, I felt it...
...every bit of it.
Sometimes when I allow myself
to think about it...
...it eats me up inside.
Yeah, me too.
Well, I don't know about you, but I'd
take that over being a shell any day.
Come on. There's a scared kid
out there we gotta find.
You think I didn't see that back there?
You're one of them.
- Golden, it's not like that.
- He's telling the truth.
Excuse me, not talking to horned demon,
talking to vampire. Thank you.
All right, what you saw,
yes, I can't deny that.
- But he only drinks pig's blood.
- Lorne.
It's true. You gotta give
an undead fella points for that.
Unless you're into the whole
kosher thing, but you're not...
Well, you don't look...
Okay, horned demon shutting up.
I don't blame you
for feeling this way...
...but I'm not going
to justify my existence to you.
I wouldn't be able to.
But what I can do...
...is take that spear away from you
and snap it into kindling...
...and break your neck
in half the time it would take for you...
...to give it a good push.
Or you could step aside
and let me go help my friend.
[GRUNTING]
WESLEY:
That door is open.
Yes.
Aren't you worried I'll just run away?
Not worried. Good at catching furries.
Yes, clearly.
So...
...not from around here, are you?
No.
Other world.
Older world.
You go. Go on. Use my key, visit.
What we breathing there
burn out little mouse lungs...
...before you can make a peep.
Fair enough.
"Fair enough."
"Fair enough-enough."
- Are you preparing a spell?
- This blood magic. Flesh magic.
Older than words. More, much power.
This magic she will hear. She will
hear and remember her true ones.
- So no incantations, then?
- No words.
She give no care about words.
Word magic.
Really?
There is only one word she...
One word? What word does
she give care about?
You is talking meat.
Don't make me come down there.
My God. What is it with you, man?
This is disgusting.
- You!
- Just drop the cliche, serial-killer crap...
...and stake me already. Please.
I tear your guts all inside out.
I stitch your guts every all over.
- Why don't you go dead.
- Why don't you go fu...
[YELLS]
More talky meat.
You can't kill him.
Not that way.
He's already dead.
He's a vampire.
Vampire. Like the one
with the angry steel?
Angry steel?
The one that hurt me
in the tunnels back there.
Angel.
Eh?
That's his name,
the one who attacked you.
You creatures, throwing your names
all over all the time.
That's why you are so weak.
Too many are knowing your names.
Takes your power away.
It doesn't work that way here.
With us...
So that's the word, isn't it?
- The word she gives care about.
- Shut.
- It's her name.
- Shut, shut, shut!
Shut, shut, shut!
FRED:
Matthew.
It's okay. We don't want to hurt you.
We just want to talk...
...but it's not safe here.
You didn't tell me the sun
came back out.
Oh, yeah, forgot to tell you.
Sun came back out.
Angel, he's a vampire,
like the ones who...
We can't explain it up here,
but we're the good guys, I swear.
- And we need you to come with us.
- No.
- No, I won't go.
- Sorry, son, but we ain't asking.
Help! Help!
Fred.
- Fred!
- What?
Get his feet.
She has a name, and it has power over
her. That's why she keeps it a secret.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la!
La, la, la, la!
Not listening!
And somehow, her true name prevents
her from choosing a false one...
...so one of us had to do it.
What it matters, eh?
Eh, talky meat?
I no keep the name.
High priest keep the name.
And you about to go dead.
About to be a smear
on my flesh spell.
I just messenger
from the ones who love truly.
Well, then, I guess it's time
to shoot the messenger.
Or, you know, chop the messenger
into little, bitty pieces. Whatever.
And that's why when we use
words like "ugly-ass" and "beastie"...
...we can sometimes do more
damage than we intend to.
It ain't all about sticks and stones,
my young friends. That's all.
A little life lesson, one to grow on.
Knowing. Knowing is half...
Shut up.
HOLLY:
Matthew.
GOLDEN: What the hell happened, man?
- He'll be okay.
I'm sorry. We...
We had no other...
- Fred.
- What is she talking about?
- Nothing.
- I'm not liking what I'm not hearing.
What did you do to my boy?
There's a new world
of bad going on upstairs...
...and your boy was walking
into it blind.
We did what we had to,
and I ain't interested...
...in your opinion on the subject.
[LAUGHING]
Matty?
- Honey?
- Oh, no.
[SPEAKING IN
JASMINE'S VOICE]
I see you.
Holly, look what they did
to Matthew.
They hit him again and again
until he lost all consciousness.
- He just wanted to see the sun.
- Fred, Lorne, it's time to go.
Golden, my love,
don't you want to hit them?
Don't you want to kill them?
You know, that just might
make my whole damn day.
GUNN:
Go!
[SPEAKING IN
JASMINE'S VOICE]
Hello again, children.
I believe you've met my father.
[GRUNTING]
[YELLS]
Little mice.
They always soft inside.
Wretched little...
Time to go dead, mouse.
[YELLING]
Wait your turn, talky!
[YELLS]
A little soft yourself in there.
Devour this meat...
...I give unto thee.
That creature, he came from a world
that's worshipped Jasmine for millennia.
- A world that we can reach through this.
- What?
I think the universe just handed us
our first break.
LORNE:
I really hate today!
More worried about tomorrow myself.
Come on!
No inscriptions.
No markings of any kind.
No moving parts, as far as I can tell.
- So this high priest holds the true name.
- Exactly.
What else do we know about him?
I'm just guessing
that he's bigger and meaner...
...than our big,
mean friend over there.
Wouldn't surprise me.
What about...?
Wes, something is going down.
Something?
Something bad.
Connor.
Angel.
FRED: Angel.
- God, are we dead yet?
ANGEL:
Guys!
No words. No word magic.
- Angel, it's Connor. He's here.
- I know.
LORNE:
And the National Guard, I think.
- No!
- No word magic. Powerless.
Much more power...
...in blood magic.
WESLEY:
Angel, I got it!
- Okay, I'll hold it. You guys, get going.
- No, we can't go, only you.
ANGEL:
What are you talking about?
That thing's world,
the atmosphere will kill us.
We can't help there.
But someone who knows the truth
has to live through this.
- Angel, that's you.
- I can't.
Hearts get in the way, right?
Angel, wait!
- We can't hold it.
- Time for the big fight scene.
CONNOR:
Move aside.
Count of three.
One. Two.
[SKITTERING]
Oh, hell.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH SDH]