NARRATOR: Previously on Angel:
- I sort of need to talk to you.
- I'm late, I'm late.
- Connor. What are you doing here?
[GRUNTING]
What you're being called to do
transcends love.
- You've become a higher being.
- Me?
I know somehow
it's all gonna be all right.
- You murdered my father.
- I didn't. She knows it.
Connor! Never forget that
I'm your father and I love you.
We've spent three months
trying to find Angel and Cordy.
And all we're closing in on
is an eviction.
I have no idea where Angel is,
Lilah, and I really couldn't care.
It's time. Let's go for a boat ride.
FRED:
We got a call from a friend tonight.
GUNN: He's out there puttering around
on his boat.
FRED: Angel's been down there
for three months, and you knew.
How could you do that to us
and to your father?
How could you do that?
- I believe you're looking for this.
- Angel.
What you did to me was unbelievable.
I love you, Connor.
Now get out of my house.
I need Cordy. Now.
Wherever she is,
whatever she's going through.
We have to find her.
God, I am so bored.
Mr. And Mrs. Raiden,
welcome to the academy.
- I'm Lydia Thorpe.
- We can't thank you enough...
...after all we've been through.
- Honestly, I should be thanking you.
Your gift to the school
was quite generous.
We've already invested a portion of it
into the accommodations...
...for Gwen's special needs.
When should we come back?
Classes end June 3rd.
Well, here you go, Gwen.
You're finally going to school.
Exciting, isn't it?
You be a good girl, now.
You hear me?
Be good.
And remember we love you.
Thanks again. We'll see you in June.
June, all right?
Hello, Gwen. I'm Ms. Thorpe.
I'm going to take you up to class now.
You must stay away from
the other children, of course.
But I'm confident you'll learn
my other rules very quickly.
No, Gwen.
[CHILDREN YELLING]
[MIMICS CAR]
Are you a freak?
I don't know.
- I guess you don't look like one.
- Thanks.
[BELL RINGING]
Okay, kids, inside. Inside now.
You can hold on to this, if you want.
[GASPS]
Gwen!
No!
[THORPE GASPING]
GIRL:
What did you do to him?
Ground State
Smell anything?
ANGEL:
Cordelia.
Maybe some old incense or candles.
Strangely enough, lemons.
Lots and lots of lemons.
I might have gone a little nuts
with the floor polish.
I wanted the place to look nice for when
the landlord starts showing it.
It does. Look nice.
Nice and empty.
You should have seen the size of
the dust bunnies under Cordy's bed.
More like dust sperm-whales.
I can't believe it's been three months.
We paid the rent
for the first couple...
...but then things got sort of tight.
And, well, big apartment,
no one living here.
Phantom Dennis.
Does he know anything about Cordy?
Where she might be?
He's just ticked we haven't
brought her home already.
We will, though.
Soon.
Absolutely.
You already tried talking to Lorne
in Las Vegas?
Yeah. Emphasis on the word "tried."
Fancy-ass Surround Sound.
Fred.
I already packed the Band-Aids, buddy.
From the exactly twice we've
been able to get ahold of him...
...we know that Lorne
is keeping his eyes peeled...
...but so far all's quiet
on the psychic front.
- You show him the box?
- See that one, with the pictures?
That stuff was on the table
the night Cordy disappeared.
It's mostly personal stuff.
Didn't mean much to us,
but you might see something.
What about the police?
"Let's see, abandoned car,
empty apartment..."
"No sign of violence,
no plans for travel."
- "Please file a missing person's report..."
- "And have a nice day."
GUNN:
That was only the first time.
The next seven times they left out
the "nice day" part.
Something must have happened
to her that night.
Something big.
Well, you guys were supposed
to meet up.
I know why I wasn't there.
Sure. Banished to the ocean depths
by your ungrateful snot of a son.
GUNN:
Not that she's bitter.
ANGEL: I appreciate you guys looking
out for Connor all summer.
It's just that he's confused.
He needs time, that's all.
Right.
Time and some corporal punishment
with a large, heavy mallet.
Not that I'm bitter.
Damn it, Dennis, she's not coming back!
I'm sorry, Angel. I didn't...
I meant the apartment.
It's okay, Fred.
Anyway, we got tons of room
back at the hotel.
We can keep everything safe.
It's just, you count on stuff, you know?
Things being where you left them.
What happens if you get back
and they're not there?
- You go find them.
WESLEY: Jones!
Ground sweep, left flank!
[GROANING AND GRUNTING]
Need help?
No. Thanks.
So Mr. O'Leary's being kept in a motel.
How original.
Free him. Report to base.
Have Diana close out the file.
Hawkins. Back of my car.
Running your own game now, huh?
I never got a chance to thank you.
For finding me, bringing me up.
Must have been hard for you.
No map.
All that water.
Look, what went down between us...
...I had a lot of time
down there to think...
...about the way things went,
the way they could've gone.
And I just want you to know, as far
as I'm concerned, we're okay again.
What's this?
What you came for.
That's everything I have
on Cordelia's disappearance.
You did your own investigation.
I don't think she's dead.
Can't say for certain, but I don't believe
she's in our dimension any longer.
Beyond that is a road I couldn't follow.
No living thing can.
ANGEL:
Who's Dinza?
One of the Eleusian mysteries.
A dark demi-goddess of the lost.
Only the dead can enter her presence...
...and those that do
she often traps for eternity.
Sounds cheery.
I managed to locate her lair,
but obviously couldn't enter myself.
This Dinza can tell me where Cordy is.
No. The most she'll tell you
is where to look.
Just beware.
Dinza isn't remotely trustworthy.
What should I do, then?
Send her a gift? A sacrifice?
Unholy fruit basket?
[WATER DRIPPING]
ANGEL:
Knock, knock.
Door was open.
Or it was a second ago.
DINZA:
Are you lost?
Keep it up, you're gonna
make me seasick.
DINZA:
I doubt it.
I think it would have happened
before now.
Tell me, do you miss
the sound of the waves?
You... You know who I am.
I know you were lost.
I know all the lost things.
Really?
City of Atlantis?
Holy Grail? Jimmy Hoffa?
DINZA:
Lost love.
So you know why I'm here,
who I'm trying to find.
She is far from you, champion,
and needs you no longer.
I need her.
[WHISPERING]
They think that you should join them.
That I should never let you out.
[DINZA CHUCKLES]
But who listens to the dead?
The Axis of Pythia rests close by.
What you seek can only
be found inside the Axis.
The Axis?
An ancient power
bridging all dimensions.
Find the Axis
and find your lost one.
Why should I trust you?
Because I'd love to keep you...
...but you have so much more to lose.
I thought I said discreet.
What? Do you see nipple?
- You're late.
- You're screwing me.
The Axis of Pythia is worth
33 million dollars.
You told me it was worth 6.
The Axis is merely a mystical object.
It has no inherent monetary value.
Blah, blah, polysyllabic blah.
I need a drink.
Waiter, I'll take a redcoat, up,
double the voddy.
And can I get one of those
little swizzly things?
Just love those. You were saying?
- My appraiser priced the Axis at exactly...
- At 18 percent of its true market value.
And seeing as how I steal stuff
on commission...
...that's like getting me
for 80 percent off.
Now, let's be honest, Elliot. Do I
look like a Blue Light Special to you?
The street value is irrelevant. I want
the Axis for my own private collection.
As I recall, we had already settled
on a rather substantial fee.
Say it with me, big guy:
Commission.
This my stuff?
Auction house perimeter.
Security system. Vent work. Vaults.
Make the delivery to a private
high-rise downtown.
I'll be in the penthouse, and we'll
transfer the balance of your fee.
Which is going to have a lot more
zeros on the end of it, right?
Gwen, you came to me very highly
recommended for your...
For your talents.
But I have to admit, I was expecting
someone a bit more...
...professional.
I am a professional...
...and we professionals
don't like taking the bone.
Gwen, that is a $ 12,000 watch.
And now it's surrealism.
Thanks for the drink.
The Axis of Pythia.
Forged from the tripod
of the Delphic oracle, the Axis...
...a metal arch set into a marble base,
stands approximately...
...2 feet high and weighs
18 pounds.
ANGEL:
Here. Give you an idea.
Wow.
Is that...?
You didn't draw that?
Huh? Yeah, I just scribbled
it down out of one of the books.
Nice.
The Axis is said to have been imbued
with many mystical qualities...
...one of which is finding souls
or entities across dimensions.
ANGEL:
Entities like...?
Cordelia.
Wow.
That's just...
Oh, hey, baby, I liked your little...
Your ghost guy.
I haven't slept, Charles.
So we need the Axis.
How do we get it?
Currently, the Axis is being held
in a vault in Chandler's Auction House...
...an establishment firmly rooted
in the black market.
Black market means money.
Money means security.
But not to worry, because
I beat the building plans...
...out of a snitch
who thought I was dead.
The plans are only half of it.
Just because we know where it is
doesn't mean we can get to it.
- Surveillance cameras, electric gates.
- Laser sensors, handprint recognition.
Not to mention armed guards.
But if it's an auction house,
can't we just eBay it?
How much is it?
33 million dollars.
I think my lungs have coffee.
I'm still working on a plan...
...but so far it involves being sent to
prison and becoming somebody's bitch.
ANGEL:
Nobody's going to jail.
I told you, a heist like this,
I've done it a million times.
Okay, maybe twice.
But I'm good at it, I swear.
You're not counting the time we
stole the crazy-making death shroud...
...that nearly killed us, right?
This is how we find Cordy,
so this is what we're gonna do.
Okay. I'm just gonna take these
and go over the details...
...and see if I can, I don't know,
whip something up.
Say, a plan.
Okay.
- I'm really strong, if that helps.
- Okay.
That's my girl. Large and in charge.
Okay, teensy-weensy and in charge.
It's amazing the way she
stepped up while I was gone.
Kind of reminds me of Cordy.
Angel, say we use this Axis thing
to find her. What then?
Then we do whatever it takes to get
her back home where she belongs.
So, what are we gonna need
for Operation Chance in Hell?
We can only guess.
Probably some rappelling hooks.
Flashlights, obviously.
Aerosols.
What else?
Thanks, Nick.
LILAH:
No, I can't stay.
WESLEY:
You said you could.
Big meeting in a couple of hours.
Potential client.
First time as the new boss.
WESLEY:
Not interested.
I just want you to know
why I'm going first tonight.
If I let you go at all.
You mean the way you
let your little slave girl go?
Justine, is it?
So you finally heard about that.
I heard. I'm betting she
heard a few things too.
The walls are soundproofed.
But she did call you "impossibly loud."
And all this time you're lying
through your teeth.
"Wes is so apathetic.
Wesley doesn't care."
I had to raise him.
Angel is necessary.
For what?
Fighting people like you.
Good news is,
you might have done me a favor.
As soon as he dried off, Angel
kicked Connor out of the hotel.
Poor little guy.
Friendless, homeless.
[MOANS]
Looks like Connor's gonna
need someone who cares...
...like a big sister...
...or a Mrs. Robinson,
if that's what he's into.
How do you like the bad girls, Wes?
WESLEY:
I don't need to hear your evil plans.
No. It just turns you on
knowing I have them.
- Shut up, Lilah.
- Make me.
ANGEL:
Come on.
GUNN: Damn. This is so much harder
than it looks on Batman.
[PANTING]
[BEEPING]
And 30 yards west.
This is the junction.
All right, I'll be in here trying to hack
into the vault security system. Charles...
Secure the escape route.
Guard station, one floor down.
Disarm and contain. Angel, hit the vault,
wait for system shutdown...
...then steal the Axis.
- You are so hot right now.
Go.
Guys.
Yeah. That's not good.
Please let my cellmate be gentle.
Look out!
I tried to warn you.
Help me out here, Fred.
Not exactly what I had in mind.
You know, I put that down for a reason.
FRED:
No!
I haven't even gotten into
the electrical system, so that...
That means...
GUNN:
We got company.
- Who are you?
- I asked you first.
- What are you, 7?
- Tell me you're not here for the Axis.
- I'm not.
- You're lying.
- I'm fibbing. It's lying, only classier.
What?
Technically?
I excite the subatomic particles
with electrical energy...
...and bounce them off each other
before they hit ground state.
I just love that folks go
for this high-tech stuff.
Electricity comforts them.
- Suckers.
- What are you?
I'm a freak.
- What did you think?
- Uh...
You know, I'm sure there's a lot
of other nice, expensive things...
...that you could steal in there.
It just doesn't have to be the one.
- Where's the bogey?
- Inside. She's after the Axis.
She? As in, she took out
the four armed guards?
That's good to know.
So long, handsome.
Listen, I need the Axis.
See, it's an ancient, mystical relic...
That's fun for a girl and a boy.
I like to think of it as mine.
Please.
"Please"? Are you kidding me?
Hey, there, Denzel.
ANGEL:
I'm trying to find someone...
...someone very important to me,
and the Axis is my only shot.
- He's telling the truth.
- Oh, well, golly, if you say it's true.
So, what? You just want to
borrow this thing?
You can do whatever you want with it
as soon as I find her.
Her?
Of course it's her.
Two questions, then.
One:
Do you really love her?
Yeah, I do.
Two: On a scale of one to 10,
exactly how stupid do you think I am?
[ALARM BEEPING]
- Don't answer that.
- Way to go, Fred.
GWEN: Let go!
- Little help here!
[SCREAMS]
He's dead.
FRED:
No. No! No!
GWEN:
Move!
Sorry, honey.
Just like starting a Chevy.
There we go.
Angel, we gotta get to a hospital.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
ANGEL:
Miss me?
Only in the sense of...
...no.
How's it going, Lilah?
Still knocking them dead
at Wolfram and Hart?
You could say that.
I wasn't sure, what with all the charity
work you seem to be doing down here.
You know, I was just telling someone
how deeply I care for the homeless.
Let him off pretty easy, didn't you?
Kid messed up. He knows he messed up.
Oh, God, the return
of the moral high ground?
This is that "guilt is its own
punishment" thing, isn't it?
Kind of my specialty.
Whatever. I don't get it.
Let me guess.
You're just going to bird-dog the kid
until he gets weepy and pulls a prodigal?
No, I'm not here for him, Lilah.
I'm here for you.
Earlier tonight the Axis of Pythia was
stolen from Chandler's Auction House.
Black market. Upscale.
Thief was too.
What you might call specialized.
The kind only people like your clients
can afford.
And you want the name of the buyer.
Look, Angel, I know you've been
out of the loop for a while...
...but I'm still evil.
I don't do errands unless they're...
...evil errands.
- I think you'll run this one.
- Why? What's in it for me?
Just this once I'll ignore the fact that
you were within 50 yards of my son.
Just this once.
So much for moral high ground, huh?
It's interesting,
you coming to me for help.
You know what I find interesting?
The fact that I can smell you
and Wesley all over each other.
Start making calls. You got an hour.
Kind of looks like art, doesn't it?
I call it Takes More Than That
to Kill Me, Punk.
- "Punk" is what makes it art.
- Did you take your pill?
It's hard to believe these
little pointy jobbies...
...are the difference between
life and death.
- Did you?
- You handed it to me.
- What was it like?
- What's what like?
Being dead. Gone.
See anything interesting?
White light? Shirley MacLaine?
Nothing.
I don't remember.
This was luck. If that woman
hadn't come back again...
Fred, we've been through this.
You would've done CPR. I know you.
What if I hadn't been there?
Then Angel would've picked me up
and Flash Gordon'ed me to the ER.
Sure, but it could've been too late.
Angel would've had to swear
vengeance on your killer...
...and we know how well
that works out.
- Fred, what the hell?
- I am so sick...
...of holding everything up around here.
First Wesley leaves,
then Angel and Cordy.
I'm sick of taking care of everything,
paying bills, making peace and plans...
...and keeping my chin up.
God, I am so sick of my chin being up.
Electrocute me now, because I don't
know what kind of alien female thing...
I thought it would get better
when Angel came back.
I thought I would finally be able
to breathe again.
Fred, no one forced this
responsibility on you.
Well, who else was gonna do it?
Who else was gonna hold everything up
after you left me all alone?
You died and left me all alone!
Shh...
[SOBBING]
It's okay, baby.
ANGEL:
Nice color.
Okay. After I kick your ass,
I'm gonna ask about that.
- I don't want to hurt you.
- That's what they all say.
I don't usually enjoy the hand-to-hand
this much.
Maybe you haven't been doing it right.
- Ah!
- Why are you not toast?
- I'm not even warmed up.
- Oh, really?
I can fix that.
Warm enough?
- You're alive.
- You felt that?
- My heart.
- It was beating.
It doesn't, does it?
Cordelia.
- I gotta get out of here.
- What the hell is going on?
ELLIOT:
Well, that should be obvious.
To a professional like yourself.
It's a double-cross.
I'm not slow. I know it's...
Shut up.
Is he one of yours?
No. I thought he was yours,
what with the tonguing and all.
- In his dreams.
- Not even close.
ELLIOT:
It doesn't matter.
The job's done, Elliot.
You don't have to do this.
I had no choice. The job you
did for me was a train wreck.
The noise, the publicity.
That little stunt you pulled in the bar.
That was just a joke.
Professionals are discreet, young lady.
You, on the other hand, are a freak.
A dangerous...
...freak.
Which is why I had them remodel
the elevator you're standing in.
More of a retrofit, really.
Low-teched the thing with 6 inches
of Plexiglas separating you from...
...any available current.
Tempered Lucite.
- He's gonna seal us in. Turn on the gas.
- What are you, Lex Luthor?
Do you think I'm gonna duke it out
with Electro-girl?
No, don't worry.
I'm told that the gas is very fast-acting.
You'll be dead within...
Whoops.
Where does the time go?
Okay, there's gotta be something.
Get down. Now. Get low!
- You jackass! You get low.
- I don't need to. I don't breathe.
- Must be a turn-on for the girlfriend.
- Utility panel here, you think?
Plastic's too thick, you lunkhead,
I can't get through.
- Simple question: Is it here or not?
- Yes, it's there.
We should be finished here
anytime now.
Uh-huh. I see. Uh-huh.
Well, we had the tuna casserole
last Thursday, Molly.
[COUGHING]
- In case I die...
- You're not gonna die.
Nice kiss.
ANGEL:
Hey.
Get rid of him.
GWEN: I expect to get screwed.
Professional thief.
- Hazard of the biz.
- Wait a second, please.
What I don't appreciate, Elliot,
is being called a freak.
That's my word, and I get cranky
when people like you use it.
Gwen, think about this.
You ever been struck by lightning, Elliot?
I've been struck by lightning 14 times.
It's not my fault. I just attract it.
You know what also attracts lightning?
Maggoty little norms like you.
So you're a freak. Boo-hoo.
So what?
- Excuse me?
ANGEL: You've figured out...
...I'm not the poster boy for normal.
Sometimes you gotta let go.
Hey, I wanted to do that.
- You were gonna fry him.
- Was not.
- Don't fib.
- Fine.
Did you at least break his nose?
You're gonna use that Axis thing
to find her, aren't you?
Figures.
Anyone that bad at stealing stuff's
gotta be doing it for love.
Bummer.
Do you think he found her?
Yeah.
She was beautiful?
God...
...there was all this light around her.
And the light seemed to be made up...
...of pure joy.
And warmth.
You think higher beings
get to take vacations?
The way I saw it,
it felt sort of permanent.
Too bad. Could have all gone to Vegas.
We should've known back when she
started doing that glowy thing...
...the Powers were up to something.
GUNN: Who thought it would be this?
Tell you the truth, doesn't surprise me.
In some small way...
...maybe it even makes it easier
knowing the good she's doing up there.
Even if I can't see her or talk to her,
it's like she's still on my side.
- Doesn't mean you miss her any less.
- No.
All those months under the water...
...I kept thinking to myself,
"I gotta get home to Cordelia."
I get back, and I find out
that she's gone.
I keep thinking,
"I gotta get Cordy back home."
Finally I find her, and I realize...
...she already is home...
...where she belongs.
What are you, deficient?
Get me out of here!
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH SDH]