I'm Guy Johnson,
and this is "On the Line!".
Today, we're with ATF agents
As they prepare to infiltrate
a group of suspected gun runners.
Going after criminals is one thing,
But going after those who deal
in weapons practically guarantees
a violent confrontation.
These agents have no idea.
Just how much firepower
they're going to have to go
up against. Everything from machine guns
to grenades and even rocket launchers
have been used against them.
Agents have breached the door
and are storming inside.
I'm not hearing any shots fired,
they go from room to room right now,
looking for guns and perps.
- All clear!
- That's us. Let's go.
Alpha team all clear.
Building's secure.
Copy that, alpha team.
We're gonna need
a forensic unit in here.
Copy.
They're already dead.
My god, they're already dead.
Cut it.
I said cut it.
What the hell happened here?
.: Team UnderCovers :.
NCIS Los Angeles 1x14
- LD50 -
Morning, Hetty.
Where is everybody?
Upstairs waiting
to be briefed on a case.
- Waiting for who?
- For you.
- Okay.
- But first,
You owe me some paperwork.
I already dropped that report off.
Everyone received a list
of potential new recruits,
And everyone has returned
his recommendation
but you.
We don't need a new recruit.
Dom is missing, not dead.
I'm not trying
to replace agent Vail.
I'm trying to give the team
the support it needs
until his return.
This isn't an office job, Hetty.
We don't need a temp.
You're right,
this isn't an office job.
I'll get to it when I have a chance.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Have a good day.
I will.
Now, you want me
to go upstairs or not?
I'm sorry
I had bothered you with this.
You're not bothering me.
My mistake.
My experience has been
that your need
to get in the last word
is a sign of annoyance.
She found you.
- She always does.
- Yeah.
Go ahead, Eric.
Night before last,
the reality TV show "On the Line!"
was following ATF agents on a raid
of suspected gun runners,
when they found this.
Five dead, no obvious signs of death.
Two in Marine uniforms.
Uniforms are authentic,
the men are not.
- They're not Marines?
- Not even close.
Both guys are career criminals.
I know that guy.
Ian Albers. Small-time con.
We bust him before?
Nope, not according to his record.
Maybe one of those militia guys
we rounded up in bush a few months back?
No. I remember the guys I bust.
But I've met him somewhere.
If these guys aren't real Marines,
it isn't our problem.
- LAPD should be handling it.
- They are.
But, Director Vance
wants to know why
these two criminals
were impersonating Marines
With very authentic looking military
IDs, and what the hell they were up to.
He wants assurances that the security
of our bases has not been compromised.
What is this place?
Eric said it was registered
to a "La Grange enterprises".
Turns out it was a bogus company.
It's a lab,
but they weren't making meth.
Not with what they have here.
So what were they cooking?
I don't know.
Maybe something that killed them.
A drug overdose
would show up on an autopsy.
- So would a communicable disease.
- Fumes of some sort?
Which brings me back
to my first question:
What were they making
and where is it?
Someone cleaned this place out.
Someone who didn't get killed.
What was with the Marine uniforms?
You know, feel free
to chime in here anytime.
Looks like those men weren't
the only ones who died here.
- Yeah?
- Hey, Callen, it's Kensi.
Eric and I have been sifting through
the electronic records of the dead men.
We found a vector
between a recurring phone number
and GPS activity
of one of their vehicles.
- You have an address?
- Yeah, it's...
299 north Sierra Bonita.
Owner's name is Balmore.
Great. Have a HazMat team
come out here and sweep this place.
HazMat?
- Callen, what did you guys find?
- I don't know.
If you and Sam have been exposed,
the medical officermust look at you.
Your health could be at risk.
You know what? So could yours
if you keep eating the burritos.
How did you...
The cheese makes your voice phlegmy.
Not good.
Got 13 birds, two squirrels.
What are the chances these guys were
cooking up some sort of chemical weapon?
I sure I hope not. Because if they were,
then we've been exposed to it.
It's a nice neighborhood.
I hate to see small-time cons
hanging out around here.
Yeah, small-time cons aren't running
this operation,
whatever it is.
The lawn could use a rake.
What a mess.
Mrs. Balmore?
I'm just all butterfingers today.
I just have to clean this up.
I'm Special Agent Sam Hanna.
Special Agent G. Callen.
- Could we ask you a few questions?
- Well, of course, dear.
But I need to clean this up.
It was full of sugar water
for the hummingbirds.
So, if I don't hose it off
right now,
It's going to be like Leiningen
versus the Ants back here.
- Let me help you with that.
- Oh, thank you very much.
Do you recognize these men?
I know Corporal Ames.
And that's Corporal Bishop.
They're my Marine Corps drivers.
- Where did they drive you?
- The research facility.
I wasn't supposed to say that.
It's classified.
National Security.
You can tell us. We're NCIS.
You are?
- How's your research going?
- Very well.
I thought I would be rusty
after all of these years,
but I was able
to isolate several grams
of clostridium botulinum last week.
Botulism?
Most dangerous toxin known to man.
Would either of you gentlemen
like some lemonade?
- Excellent, what about CDC?
- I never wanted to be an Army wife,
but I was in love with my husband.
- There you go.
- You're so kind. Thank you, Steve.
It was Sam, ma'am.
- You're welcome.
- Sam.
I'm so sorry.
Sometimes I think I'd forget my head
if it wasn't attached.
It's fine.
It's okay.
So, you enlisted and wound up working
in the Army's medical unit?
Yes.
Now, that was an old boy's network
back then.
That was so nice of Steve to bring tea.
Are you married?
- Let's talk about...
- A handsome young man like yourself?
I work a lot.
That was Kensi.
The coroner has confirmed
it was botulinum poisoning.
Director Vance,
Homeland Security and CDC
have all been alerted,
along with local medical services.
And HazMat's doing a sweep
of Esther's place.
Who knows what else granny
was cooking up there.
Should Nate be wearing a mask?
No, he's safe. You don't catch
botulism from other people,
But we might have been exposed because
we were in the lab. You feeling okay?
Yeah, nothing a couple weeks
of vacation can't cure.
I hear that.
You're very tall.
My husband Marty was tall.
He died of a heart attack
at Santa Anita several years ago.
He loved the ponies.
Let's talk about your work
at Fort Detrick in the late '60s.
Bacterial purification.
The work we did revolutionized
the production of antibiotics
and other drugs.
And what
about your most recent work?
I'm long retired.
And your research at the lab?
Lab?
Where your two drivers
took you?
I forgot about that.
I helped them isolate proteins.
A neurotoxic protein produced by
the bacterium C...
botulinum?
Yes, of course.
That's it.
Thank you for reminding me.
Why did they need
the botulinum toxin?
Antidote research.
So our boys in uniform will be safe.
She seems
like just a sweet old lady.
She is a sweet old lady.
Someone tricked her into creating
biochemical weapons.
Would you excuse me a moment?
Well?
I think she's delightful
and... extremely dangerous.
She's suffering from Alzheimer's.
She remembers the '60s and '70s in
vivid detail, but has memory lapses
about more recent events.
All right, well, it is one thing
to forget to feed your dog,
it's another when you forget
security protocols,
and you're dealing with bioweapons.
She may be responsible
for those men's deaths.
Or...
The person behind this
use what she created
to tie up the loose ends.
And if that's the case,
she could be in danger.
Botulinum is a neurotoxin protein.
Very popular in Hollywood,
where it is known as botox.
Kills the muscles
that cause wrinkles for that
"don't I look 20 even though I'm 50?"
look.
It can also paralyze your breathing
muscles, and you suffocate to death.
In fact,
it is the deadliest substance
known to man.
The housewives of Beverly Hills should
be classified as biochemical weapons.
Do you guys know what LD50 is?
It's the median lethal dose:
The amount of toxin needed
to kill half the people exposed.
Lower the LD50,
the more dangerous the substance.
Exactly.
Now, the botulinum toxin
has the lowest LD50 there is.
So...
a sample only...
this small could kill up
to a quarter million people.
And if what Esther told us
is accurate,
then she isolated enough
to kill ten times that.
She's like the evil Martha Stewart.
Only she's not evil.
She's vulnerable
because of her Alzheimer's,
and whoever's behind this knew that.
They sought her out
and tricked her into thinking
that her expertise
was needed for National Security.
Yeah, she's an easy mark
but an unreliable witness.
Poor thing.
She must have enjoyed
the company and attention.
The real question is, who's behind this,
and where the hell is the toxin?
We may have a lead.
Remember this guy, Ian Albers?
I've been trying to.
Well, he used to be
a bouncer at club Halo
for our old pal,
I knew I recognized him.
Maybe he's moved on from blackmail
to dealing in bioweapons.
You think Dallas is behind this?
If he is,
he's going to wish he wasn't.
Dallas closed the Halo club
after the Safar incident.
He's been keeping a low profile since.
Apparently, not low enough.
The dude's already proven
he has friends in high places.
And low places.
He's going to call his buddies
to shut us down, like last time.
- He's not going to cooperate.
- At least not willingly.
And get this.
Supposedly, he replaced his security
with a bunch of retired
East German secret police.
The latest Hollywood accessory,
a special ops security team.
Hetty,
any suggestions on getting Dallas?
Yes. I suggest
we don't have this conversation.
Forget diamonds,
in this business,
plausible deniability
is a girl's best friend.
Now...
Sit down and say, "ah".
Hetty, honestly...
I'm fine.
Asset protection
is part of my responsibility,
And you are an asset.
When you're not being
a pain in the asset.
Now, open wide.
What was that for?
It's a healthy gag reflex.
It's the first thing to go
in botulinum poisoning.
Stop laughing. You're next.
Dallas hid his electronic footprint
pretty well. He was hard to find.
For the record,
I walked away 30 seconds ago.
He always was careful.
Last time, we had to go to his club
just to look at his computer.
Yeah, but he didn't hide
his credit cards.
At least not well enough
to hide them from Eric.
Apparently, the crime
syndicate is recession-proof.
Five days a week, Dallas has been
getting massages at a place called the
"Ahimsa retreat".
- What is that?
- A wonderful day spa.
They have
the best foot rescue packages.
It's like sending
your toes to Heaven.
I'm not through
with either of your evaluations.
Hetty, we're both fine.
We really need to move on this.
Well, then,
you'll just have to make it quick.
- You look good in a robe.
- I look good in anything.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
- What the hell?
- Relax.
Don't be so tense.
You have no idea
who you're dealing with.
Come on.
Are you stupid, Dallas?
You think this is a random robbery?
You're butt naked.
I have friends.
Lots and lots of friends.
Right now, all you have
is a gun pointed at your head.
What do you want?
I want information
on biochemical weapons,
Specifically botulinum toxin.
- Come on, I'm not involved...
- I didn't ask you If you're involved.
I said I want information.
Now, you got 2 seconds
to come clean,
or I guarantee this massage
won't have a happy ending.
I don't mess with that crap.
But there's a guy.
He's called the Dutchman.
Supposedly, he's made some,
now he's selling.
That's all I know. I swear to God.
God doesn't like
when you swear to him.
And I don't like to be lied to.
Now, if I have to come back here
if I find out you played me,
I'm going to shiatsu your ass
into dog food.
You hear me?
Make sure you drink plenty of water.
Stay facing down.
Ladies and gentlemen, I give you...
the Dutchman.
Aka Jacobus Troyger,
aka Sebastian Boon,
aka Jurgen Vanderveer,
aka yada yada.
The guy's got more aliases than Callen.
Somehow, I doubt that.
European terrorist.
Technically, he's an arms dealer.
He sells weapons
to radicals and insurgents.
- Ipso facto, he's a terrorist.
- And he's in L.A.
I haven't been able to find any record
of him entering the country.
He probably used an alias
that wasn't on our watch list,
then entered through a port
which doesn't have
a facial recognition system in place.
If he's staying
to sell his bioweapon,
there's a good chance
people come to buy it.
I'll check with Homeland Security
and border control.
I'll contact Interpol,
see if they picked up any chatter
or tracked any movement overseas.
Eric, check the flight manifests,
port surveillance.
We might just get lucky.
Mr. Callen,
a moment.
If she puts on her rubber gloves,
run.
Hetty, I appreciate the concern,
but I draw the line
at turning my head and coughing.
I'm going to pretend
you didn't say that.
Now, first,
how is our elderly bioweaponeer,
Esther Balmore?
- Getting her medical evaluation.
- Oh, good.
That was first.
What's second?
Your partner.
Sam has been reluctant to weigh in
on the selections
for a temporary agent.
Sam doesn't play well with others,
and he doesn't like to share his toys.
But times like these
only emphasize the void left...
by the absence of Agent Vail,
however temporary.
Sam is eternally hopeful
that Dom is going
to return to his post.
Sam sees the glass as half full.
I see it as half empty.
It's why we make a good team.
Kensi,
just drinks right out of the bottle.
Nate wonders why it's a glass,
and Eric breaks the glass
- by putting his feet up on the table.
- Nevertheless,
I want his input,
if only to begin
to move him forward.
Maybe you could
give him a little... nudge.
Big guy does not like to be nudged.
I'll be gentle.
Thank you.
Tell me something good.
Sam was right.
Interpol has various persons
of interest who were stopped
boarding planes bound for L.A.
- In Berlin, London and Madrid.
- We put LAX on full alert.
And we got a hit.
Simon Amputuan.
He's a Filipino militant
with ties to Abu Sayyaf.
Also known
as Al-harakat Alislamiyya,
or Islamic Movement.
They've been waging a bloody campaign
of kidnappings,
bombings and assassinations
in their fight for an independent
Muslim state in the Philippines.
Call ICE...
hold Amputuan for questioning,
and have Nate meet us
at the boathouse.
I don't know any Dutchman.
You realize you're on a terrorist
watch list, Mr. Amputuan?
There are many Amputuans
in the Philippines.
You must be mistaking me
for someone else.
I've heard there are well over
a million people on those watch lists.
It must be easy to make mistakes.
What about your involvement
with the militant group, Abu Sayyaf?
Again,
I'm afraid you have
the wrong information.
I run a business call center.
Great. He's not just a terrorist,
he's a telemarketer.
That's almost worse.
I don't appreciate
your racial profiling.
This isn't about race, Mr. Amputuan.
It's about terrorism,
like your involvement
with the 2004 SuperFerry bombing,
killing 116 people.
That was a tragedy that had nothing
whatsoever to do with me.
Clock's ticking, Nate.
- Time to turn up the heat.
- Please.
Okay, here's the deal, Simon.
The Dutchman was arrested
this morning,
- and he started naming names.
- But I told you, I don't know him.
Really?
'cause if you didn't know the guy,
then you would've at least been curious
to see who I was talking about.
Sorry. Too late.
So, you're either going
to cooperate and work with us,
or you're going
to get fingered by Jacobus,
or whatever name you know him by.
I would feel better if I was provided
with legal counsel,
from here on in,
just so as to ensure there are no...
misunderstandings.
Fortunately for us,
you're an unlawful combatant.
Unfortunately, the boys
at Guantanamo Bay have no vacancy.
So much for that sunny
Caribbean getaway.
We do know some Mossad agents
that would gladly buy you
an all-expense-paid trip to Tel Aviv.
Can you say, "Shalom"?
Okay.
There is a rumor that the Dutchman
is auctioning off
the botulinum toxin.
Where?
I don't know.
You've come a long way
to not know where you're going.
I didn't say I was here
for the auction.
I said I heard rumors of it.
I also heard of a rendezvous point.
I imagine it could be
someplace where...
a would-be bidder could be picked up
and taken to the proceedings.
You ever meet the Dutchman?
- No. I told you...
- Yeah. You know what? We got it.
We want an address,
we want code words,
and everything else
you've heard rumors about.
What if the Dutchman's seen
pictures of Amputuan?
He must have screened these guys.
I'll go in as his muscle.
I'm gonna review the files,
learn the history, his associates.
- Know it cold.
- I don't like this.
I don't, either,
but the auction's today.
We don't have time
to plan anything else.
Besides, I'm the only one
vaccinated for botulism.
Seals are inoculated for everything,
except suicidal tendencies.
And he knows I'm right,
or else he'd argue to go instead of me.
I don't want either of you to go.
Relax.
Sam's the best man for this job.
What's the worst thing
that could happen?
I don't know. Let's see...
Sam gets made, they kill him.
Then you, Kensi and the others
storm the place,
and he releases the toxin,
killing...
all of you and half of Los Angeles?
Which half?
I'm going to go brief the Director.
You have had your shots, right?
Yeah, I had a shot.
Annual boosters?
I go suit up.
The vest is tight.
It's rubbing.
Well, better chafed
than dead, I say.
The camera is right here.
They'll probably sweep you, so
the electronics we're providing you with
can be remotely
activated and deactivated
so as not to be detected, all right?
Eric, let's give it a try.
Turning Sam on now.
Scary.
They'll take your phone and any gun
so I'm providing you
with this.
It's a ballistics briefcase.
It'll stop most bullets.
Inside are $3 million dollars
in marked bearer bonds.
And twist,
pull...
and voilà!
A ceramic blade.
That's it?
No, you know,
parachute or shark repellent?
I put that in your shoes.
Botulinum protocols?
Ingest it or inhale it, you die.
Get it in an open wound, you die.
Let's hope the vaccine works.
I almost forgot.
In here is an ampule
of an experimental antidote.
Click for the needle.
If you're exposed,
use it just
for good measure.
Callen and the rest will be running
a box around you the entire time.
Keep it loose.
No helicopters.
These guys will be paranoid.
You're not ready?
You take longer
to get dressed than Kensi.
I have been ready for five minutes.
Let's do it.
Sam looks
like he's getting impatient.
He is.
And in about ten seconds,
he's gonna complain about it.
They're late.
You guys know
each other pretty well?
We should.
We've been together longer
than most married couples in this town.
You worried about him?
Right now,
I'm worried about all of us.
Yeah.
What if Amputuan lied?
- Hollywood boulevard?
- Sorry. I'm not from around here.
Oh. Where are you from?
Lots of places.
What's your name?
None of your business.
He was grabbed at the airport.
I beg your pardon?
Amputuan.
I got through. I'm authorized
to negotiate on his behalf.
Sorry. I don't know
what you're talking about.
I have 3 million dollars in bearer bonds
that says your boss does.
Excuse me.
Think he bought it?
We'll find out soon.
Follow me, please.
That's it.
Close it up.
I'm so sorry for the hood, mister...
Cook. Felix Cook.
That's him. That's the seller,
Jacobus Troyger, the Dutchman.
Just one more little
security protocol.
Blondie patted me down
pretty good back there.
What do they say during those
American football broadcasts?
Any recording of this game without
the NFL's consent is prohibited.
Same courtesy applies here.
Okay.
Cut his equipment.
Let's hope
we can get him back again.
He's good.
Thank you.
Please.
LAPD, Swat and HazMat are en route.
Rendez-vous is at 7th and Santa Fe.
Nolan,
you coordinate with Swat.
I want them in position,
stay out of sight until we go in.
Morris...
you got HazMat.
They got to be right on our heels.
I don't need anyone else dying.
Start on the rear, move forward.
All right, let's go.
Eric,
- what's it looking like in there?
- Without Sam's feed, we're blind.
Turn him back on.
Troyger must be employing
a jamming device.
I can enhance this later,
but for the live op, this is it.
He look familiar to you?
You're gonna have turn
a little more, Sam.
That's it.
My, my. Benno Dragovic.
Supplies Serbian
mercenaries worldwide.
There are a lot of people
in Washington who will want to see
what we've stumbled upon here.
We're not seeing any more cars come in,
Sam. You think the gang's all here?
Looks like this party's starting.
What kind of firepower
we talking about, Sam?
You ever see The Dirty Dozen?
A dozen?
You ready?
Let's do it.
Tracking.
All teams moving into position.
Welcome.
In 1969, when the U.S. Army
stopped making biochemical weapons,
They were far more advanced
than they admitted publicly.
I have recruited an Army scientist
that remembers the recipes.
On offer today...
a botulinum that is highly flexible.
It can be vaporized against troops
on the battlefield.
Or you can spread it on bullets,
and even a flesh wound
becomes lethal.
Abu Nassim, the old warhorse.
He's not on Troyger's list
of known associates.
Oh, sure he is.
Abu Nassim
Isn't a name.
It's an honorific, from a culture
where older people
are revered with marks
of respect.
His name is Sadiki Hassan.
He's on there,
your honor lady lange.
This party favor
is a vaccine to the botulinum.
Uncle Sam would never let you
have this.
I hope we don't need it.
Now get in position.
Now...
you should all know
the value of what you are buying.
And as many of you will resell
in your various markets,
I thought a demonstration
would add value.
What kind of demonstration?
The kind that makes
international news.
The Mall.
Is there a more iconic place
of American consumerism?
Within the hour,
an associate of mine
will deploy just a few micrograms
of the botulinum,
Cut with a vaporizing powder
that will carry it throughout the Mall.
What Mall?
I can't tell what we're looking at.
Where is that?
Here, in Los Angeles.
But don't worry, Mr. Cook.
You are safe here.
Yeah?
What if I want to do a little shopping
before I go home?
Is that the Hollywood town center?
Or is it the Sunset avenue Mall?
Let's just concentrate on the shopping
in here first, shall we?
Assault teams back
to covert positions.
Eric, Kensi and I will take
the Hollywood town center.
Send agents over to Sunset.
And HazMat teams to both places.
I'm already on it.
I don't want to spook Troyger.
Nobody makes a move on the warehouse
till we find this guy at the Mall.
Big guy, I got some bad news.
You're going to have
to stall for a while.
As you all know, the bidding
will begin at 1 million dollars.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
But I'm concerned
about your demonstration.
We still have to get
this stuff out of the country.
If a whole bunch of people get killed
in a biochemical attack,
they're going to lock
the whole city down.
You would rather pay several million
dollars for something that,
as far as you know,
could be crushed aspirin?
Does anyone else share
Mr. Cook's concerns?
Apparently, you are the only one
who seems to be bothered by this,
Mr. Cook.
And why is that?
I just want to do this smart.
Seriously, are we here
to buy weapons or for you to perv on me?
'cause if these pants come off,
I want a discount.
A big discount.
You know what I'm saying?
All I know is that you are
a very stupid man.
I'm stupid?
At least I don't have these two
in the same room.
Dragovic there killed Hassan's boy.
- Don't listen to him.
- Chechnya,
2002.
Hassan's boy is over there,
paying his jihadi dues,
Ol'Drago was running black ops
for... Putin.
Code name: Crusader.
Sheitan.
You still haven't done me
the courtesy.
I'm a ghost.
Put your hands behind your back
and shut up!
I'm not seeing anyone from the file
of known associates at either place.
Nobody acting like they're about
to kill hundreds of people.
Any luck there, Hetty?
Working on it.
I can't do this.
I mean,
all those people and it's my fault.
Esther, try not to think about why.
Let's pretend
that we are looking for...
old friends.
Our friend that we're looking for
would be right there.
Now, who do you know?
Listen to you using
the objective case properly.
Look!
That's Captain Hogue!
There, there with the backpack.
Hollywood town center.
Eric, could you go back
to the last feed?
Callen, level six.
Tall, Caucasian male,
30s,
bald,
yellow backpack.
Can't see him.
Guys, he's forcing himself
to walk casually,
but he's trying to hide
an adrenaline surge.
This guy is moments
away from deploying.
I got him.
He's heading for the food court.
I just take this for a second.
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh, I am so sorry.
Everybody, down!
Keep the vial in the water!
Keep it out of the air. We stay
right here till HazMat scrubs us.
I hate needles!
It's the antidote, G.
I just saved your life.
I didn't get a warning?
Oh, now I got to warn you
to save your life?
Just keep the vial in the water!
Understood, Director.
That's why I like my job.
Okay, got it.
The FBI's doing the press conference
announcing the arrests
of Troyger and the others.
And stealing our credit?
That was all us.
Sam and you and me.
Right.
But, we don't exist.
That's why you like your job,
because we don't exist.
I like my job
'cause I do press conferences.
It's true,
you do have a better face for radio.
Ms. Blye, if you touch that thermostat,
It'll be to turn it down.
But I'm cold and Callen was pushed
in a fountain today.
Which is exactly
why we need cost cutting.
The Koi fish in that fountain
went belly up from the botulinum.
Oh, dear,
one so rarely uses that phrase
literally. Poor things.
Anyway,
the Mall has billed us $72,000.
- For fish?!
- Yes.
You know what I could buy with that?
I have a pretty good idea.
Apparently, they're a prized lineage
of Taisho Sanke from Japan.
Dead fish will be here in the morning
so I can see them for myself.
What?
I know the difference between Koi
and carp and crap.
All done.
My psychological evaluation
of Esther Balmore.
And my strong recommendation
that she not be charged.
She thought
she was serving her country.
She won't be charged.
That's not all. She needs,
someone to adjust her medications,
consistent home nursing...
I'll take care of it.
You've come to offer to call the ADA
for Esther Balmore.
Because...
you think
watching an old lady go batty
has set off a nerve in me.
I came for a cup of tea
because I'm cold.
You know, in nursing homes,
they only have tea in bags.
It just tastes like paper.
When the time comes,
I'll bring you the good stuff.
Smuggle it in if I have to.
Go in undercover...
As an orderly?
Whatever you need.
You know...
It's not the loneliness I fear.
But you are scared of something.
Yes.
Spilling
everything I know.
All my secrets being
blathered out into a world
that should never hear them.
So, when the time comes,
as you put it,
there's something you can do.
You can smother me with a pillow.
Make sure it's synthetic.
I'm allergic to feathers.
Okay.
Oh, the birds will be so happy!
The delivery man just
left them out front,
and I just couldn't move them.
You are so kind,
Steve.
That's not it.
What is it, dear?
I'm Sam.
Sam!
Right.
Say...
- Sam.
- Yes?
This stone fountain.
Don't you think it would look better
if it was
over there?
Sure.
Piece of cake, Esther.
Oh, careful, Steve!
.: Team UnderCovers :.
Stay tune for seeing
from your next episode.