- Who burned you?
- Eugene Keelson.
Guy's got information about G's past.
That even NCIS doesn't know about.
If you kill me, you'll never know
the truth: who you really are.
I just found a local address on Keelson.
This place
is filled with some heavy-duty data
servers, and I think we've got the key.
Clear.
- Is this place what I think it is?
- Everybody's dirty little secrets.
Including Taylor, A...
whoever he is.
Document boxes.
Alphabetical by surname and initial.
Must be hundreds of them.
Lots of big names.
I'm gonna need the code number
or an angle grinder.
Damn.
What?
You think someone who makes a fortune
buying and selling information's
- gonna make it that easy?
- We're gonna need Eric.
See if they've got one on you...
or Hetty.
Nothing on me.
Two boxes on Hetty.
Guys...
You're gonna want to see this.
"File burn". It must be automatically
erasing the hard drives.
It's not gonna affect
the hard copy files.
Unless...
We gotta get out of here now!
- Move!
- That kinda burn.
I got it.
G, come on!
.: Team UnderCovers :.
NCIS Los Angeles 1x24
- Callen, G. -
After you powered up,
what did you press?
Nothing.
I didn't even touch the keyboard.
Maybe we triggered motion detectors.
I didn't see them,
and I was looking.
Okay... a timer.
If Keelson's not back
by a certain time...
And if he's stuck in traffic?
Cell phone. Dials up,
punches in the code, deactivates...
I didn't do anything.
If you could turn it off with a cell
phone, you could turn it on.
Maybe Keelson isn't the lone wolf
we thought he was.
Eric's gonna see what he can dig up
on Keelson's warehouse.
Phone records, utilities,
all the usuals.
Try to turn up another name.
We good?
Yeah, sorry.
This is the file he was working on.
Surveillance.
They're arguing.
Probably married.
Taylor.
Wonder
what his dirty little secret is.
Great.
450 A. Taylors in Los Angeles alone.
Gonna need a first name to...
This is where he got the addresses.
What addresses?
Every foster home I ever lived in.
Keelson gave me a printout, but...
this is where he got 'em.
They're all handwritten.
What's it doing in this file box?
Well, he left in a hurry. He could've
put them in there by mistake.
Keelson didn't make mistakes.
There's five more addresses here
in the back. I don't know any of 'em.
Maybe this is
our connection with Taylor.
Any of those five new addresses located
in a 6000 block?
We find a Bart's Mart located
on a 6000 block, at least
we got a place to start looking.
Bart's Mart.
67 stores in greater Los Angeles,
but only one on a 6000 block.
6464 Woodman Avenue, Van Nuys.
That's the apartment block
from the photo.
List of tenants, Eric.
Looking for Taylor, initial "A".
Close.
Data search on Steven John Taylor,
same address.
Steven John Taylor, aged 45.
No criminal record. Divorced.
Ex-wife's name's Amy.
A. Taylor.
He's a she.
Age 42. No children.
No current address listed.
Still using her married name.
That's unusual.
What's her maiden name?
I have to go right back
to the marriage certificate.
And her maiden name is...
Callen.
Mr. Hanna, Ms. Blye,
Taylor's apartment.
- Mr. Callen, my office.
- Hetty...
Go.
I much prefer
a good HB
to a Bic.
Press firmly enough,
and people don't have to read
between the lines to get the message.
The answer is no.
You don't even know
what the question is.
It's no to all of them.
Is there any mention of this
in your classified file? No.
Was I aware you had a relative? No.
Am I surprised? No.
Should you stay on this case?
Definitely no.
Is there any possibility
that this is a coincidence?
Keelson didn't think so.
- He had my details in her file.
- But he could be wrong.
Could be.
I'm sorry, Mr. Callen.
You know the rules.
It would seem
that while Keelson is dead,
there is still the possibility
that your true identity
may have been compromised,
along with the integrity
of this unit.
This is the second time
you've taken me off the Keelson case.
Let's make it the last.
Should I read something
between the lines?
Bugger.
Hetty's gonna tell you
that I'm off the case.
She is?
Before she does, what have we got?
The warehouse is owned
by some two-dollar corporation
registered in Nevada. I'm still checking
names and the paperwork,
but they're all paralegals
3 times removed from Keelson.
She could be on her way up.
She will try calling again first.
What else?
I checked phone companies.
Phone lines in
and out of the warehouse.
And I found a dedicated data line,
like a fax line. But here's the thing...
What is the thing?
It's never had a call.
Ever!
The only charge on the phone bill
is for the line rental.
No calls in, no calls out.
Except for one this morning.
So someone dialed in
to trigger the explosives.
Yeah, ten-second call.
If it were me, I'd want to be close by,
make sure it all works.
Time-stamped video
puts him on the scene
30 seconds before the blast
with a clear view of the warehouse.
That's how I narrowed down
the search.
So he makes the call,
and you see a change
in the light on the left of the frame
as the building goes up.
He stayed another 30 seconds,
and left.
Not your typical reaction of someone
witnessing a building exploding.
A cell phone?
Still trying to get it.
But I did get a license plate.
That's the number, the address,
the guy, Carl Browning.
Rap sheet: grand theft auto,
burglary, assault and fraud.
This is Eric.
What in the world's taking you so long
to answer the phone?!
Taylor's got some noisy neighbors.
The neighbors
have got a noisy Taylor.
- Is that...?
- Yeah.
It's Mighty Mouse.
Huh, I was thinking Tom and Jerry.
No, no, it's the mouse.
Taylor hasn't got kids.
So what?
Cartoons?
Not cartoons.
The mouse.
- Clear!
- Clear.
Bedroom and bathroom
look a lot like this.
The whole place is trashed.
He turned the TV up to mask the sound.
Searching for something.
Guessing they didn't find it.
Callen's got the information
and is on his way to Browning's house.
What's the address?
Put your hands where I can see 'em.
Federal agent.
- You alone?
- No.
As a matter of fact, he's not,
Special Agent G. Callen.
Kort.
You know, Callen,
you're not missing anything.
No one ever calls me
by my first name.
It's 'cause no one likes you.
CIA do this?
We were late to the party, like you.
Place was already trashed,
television blaring.
And like you, we wanted to have
a chat with Mr. Browning.
Unfortunately for both of us,
Mr. Browning's done chatting.
Browning worked for Keelson.
Keelson's dead.
I got the memo.
Tell me, did he have a file on you?
But he did have one on you.
Ashes in the wind.
Scuttlebutt said you triggered
the explosion.
Browning phoned it in.
That's how you found him.
Phone logs.
How'd you find him?
Your backup just arrived.
A little late to be of much use,
I would have thought.
I mean,
if we weren't on the same side...
Trent Kort.
He's with the Agency.
We used to work together,
Callen and I.
Kort was explaining
how they knew about Browning.
We've been keeping tabs
on an Iranian.
Karim Akbari.
He lead us here.
Why is the CIA interested
in Karim Akbari?
Sorry. Classified.
Crime scene's yours, Callen.
Let me know if you find anything.
You, too.
- Crime scene?
- Browning.
Someone decided to make him
the light fixture.
Akbari?
Maybe.
So why did Kort give up Akbari?
See how we'd react,
if we're chasing the same guy.
Guess we are now.
Did you find her?
No one home.
Place was turned over. Pros.
TV on?
Mighty Mouse.
Woody.
Same pros.
Call Eric, see what he knows
about Akbari.
Hetty took me off the case.
Full-court press,
Karim Akbari, Iranian.
Got him.
But only for a second.
File got locked down.
By whom?
Our friends at Langley.
Kort just shut us out.
I'd send you home,
but I know that would just move you
from that chair
on to that sofa.
I'm still looking for a place.
I just got a rather
officious phone call from
a mid-level...
time card puncher at the CIA.
He wanted to know why
we had requested
access to a classified file
of an ongoing operation.
Have you ever heard of...
Karim Akbari?
I don't know anything about him.
That's not what I asked,
That was me.
Akbari was given to us
by a CIA operative.
I got Eric to run it,
we got red-flagged.
Sounds like the CIA
is stonewalling us.
I know a lot about stonewalling.
After I finished with the...
time card puncher,
I called the Director of the CIA,
who offered to brief us
on Karim Akbari.
The agent's name is Trent Kort.
Boathouse in a half hour.
She knows. You can't go.
- Where you going?
- To shoot someone.
I think you killed him.
And his entire extended family.
You wanted to see me?
You said you wanted to see me.
You're our operational psychologist,
Nate.
I've got personal stuff
going on in my life,
so you have to see me.
That's your job.
I'm missing something, aren't I?
- What to tell Hetty when she asks.
- What's Hetty going to ask me?
- Why you came to see me.
- And the real reason is...?
Shouldn't this be
in the evidence locker?
Aren't we breaking...
the chain of evidence or...?
You're off the case,
but you need to know the...
Could I go to jail?
- You've done something wrong?
- I think I'm about to.
I could do
some handwriting analysis.
You recognize
any of these addresses?
Every orphanage and foster home
I ever stayed at.
And these five addresses
at the back?
I could run a search,
see if they have anything in common.
In fact, I could...
do it right here.
And you could...
just happen to...
look over my shoulder...
if you wanted to.
Because... how would
I even know you were...
doing that?
Okay, snap up here.
Most of these are
government buildings.
That's the old
Allingham Street Orphanage.
Looks like that one's run
by the county.
So is the one in Torrance.
Let's just take a peek
at that list again.
Four of the five
addresses are either state,
city or county-run orphanages.
And the last address
is a private residence.
It's also the last entry.
If I were looking for answers,
I'd start
with the last address first.
- Hi. Can I help you?
- Hi.
I'm sorry to disturb you.
I was just hoping you might be able
to help me find someone who
possibly stayed here
a long time ago.
Her name's Amy.
Oh, of course.
I remember Amy.
Such a beautiful woman now.
And you are?
I work for a law firm.
We believe she may have inherited
some property,
and I just need
to confirm her identity.
Well, then you'd better come in.
Thanks.
Such a long time ago.
25 years, at least.
She's here somewhere.
My "children".
Some of them not for long,
a few days.
Others a few weeks, months.
Amy was one who stayed a long time.
Hard to believe, huh?
So many.
Most of them from broken families.
Some orphaned.
Is, um...
is your photo up here?
Not here.
But someplace.
Many places?
Thirty-seven.
Oh, here she is.
This is Amy.
She must have been
about 15 at the time.
She stayed almost two years.
She...
She was a troubled girl.
Something in her past, I think,
that she kept to herself.
She still sends me
a birthday card every year.
Not all of them do anymore.
I used to worry
when I would just suddenly
stop hearing from someone.
And then one day I realized...
they probably just found their way.
At least that's what I hope.
That's the latest one.
Powerful emotion... hope.
Yes, it is.
Amy ever talk about her family?
It was a long time ago
to remember something like that.
That's okay.
- Thank for everything.
- Yeah.
You know, Amy...
Amy was an orphan.
But I do remember.
She said she had a brother.
Formerly a senior member of Savak,
the Shah of Iran's secret police
back in the 1970s.
Wasn't Savak trained by the CIA?
In 1979,
the Shah was overthrown
and went into exile.
There were rumors that his supporters
moved half a billion dollars
out of Iran into various
bank accounts in Europe
to be used to restore
the Shah to power.
But 18 months later,
the Shah was dead.
And the money was never recovered.
After the Shah's death, Akbari
started looking for it.
While he didn't find the money,
he did find this man...
Michael Lawson...
an American banker
who lived in Iran.
Akbari believed it was Lawson
who transferred the money
and had access to the account
numbers and passwords.
Lawson was found murdered
six weeks after the Shah's death.
Let me guess.
Strung up by his feet
to a light fitting and tortured.
Keelson uncovered information
that suggested the money
was still out there.
Akbari found out,
came looking for Keelson
and found his associate,
Mr. Browning, instead.
And there endeth the briefing.
So, which one does
the CIA want the most?
Akbari or the money?
Akbari is a zealot.
If he gets his hands on that money,
his plan is to try and buy
nuclear weapons and invade Iran.
Not a good outcome for any of us.
We're all on the same side here,
Agent Hanna.
I'm glad to hear it.
I guess then you won't have a problem
telling me how you got onto Browning.
We intercepted a call
between he and Akbari.
Used it to trace Browning's address.
Got there too late.
Akbari was demanding information
about someone named...
Amy Taylor.
Happen to know who that is?
Your guess is as good as mine.
Yeah.
Get off me.
Federal agent.
No one move!
Eric, south on Lincoln, blue van.
I am in pursuit.
Need LAPD backup.
I'm on it.
Crap.
You need to come up to ops... now.
Did you see it?
Someone get an ambulance!
Okay, no problem.
Steve, where are you?
Is this Amy Taylor?
Who is this?
I'm a Federal agent.
Amy, you need to listen to me.
Your ex-husband has been injured.
If he knows where you are, he told
someone, and they are coming for you.
Is this your car?
I'm a Federal agent.
Give me your keys.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Give me your keys.
Come on.
Eric, check this number.
I need the location
of the cell phone last dialed.
Okay, call was to a cell phone
in South Central near the river.
Callen, I can only narrow it down
to a four-block radius
bordering Allingham Street.
Callen?
- Line must have dropped out.
- Then get it back.
Allingham Street... that's
one of the addresses
in the notebook.
Does Callen know that?
Yes.
Eric, the cell phone number
Callen had you trace...
who owns it?
He's found her.
Who are you?
I called.
I'm the federal agent.
My name is Callen.
Who are you?
I'm your sister.
I don't have a sister.
Now, who the hell are you?
Sam and Kensi are 15 minutes
from the orphanage.
Try Callen again.
My name is,...
Hannah Lawson.
And until the age of about 11, I...
I lived in Iran with, my...
father.
His name was Michael Lawson.
My mom...
She died when I was three,
so my father was...
he was just everything to me.
A while after we got back here,
my father showed me this...
this hiding place
in the house that were staying at.
Inside it was this...
this leather satchel. I don't know
why he showed it to me, but...
he said it was our...
secret.
And a couple of days later,
some men, they forced
their way into the house.
They were, uh, Iranian.
And they turned the television
on really loudly, and they...
tore the lighting fitting.
Eventually, the, uh...
All the lights blew out, and...
they couldn't see me
in the dark, and...
I ran away.
I just lived on the streets.
Finally...
Welfare picked me up,
and this is wh...
where they brought me.
I barely spoke for months,
'cause I was so terrified
that those men would come
and get me.
I just wanted a...
a different name.
Why my name?
You...
you had a sister.
Her name was Amy, and she...
she slept over there,
and she was my friend.
I don't have a sister.
She told me about you.
- No.
- Yeah.
She said she used to push you
in... in a little cart, like,
a little red cart, and you
used to squeal
to go faster and faster.
Faster!
And one day, it crashed
and you hurt your arm.
I'm so sorry.
And Amy cried, and you didn't.
And then she swore
that she would always...
always protect you.
Come on.
Federal agent!
I'm good.
It's Kensi.
We're secure.
Callen and...
whoever she is...
are both fine.
What happened to her?
We used to sneak out...
at night...
down to the river.
This one... one time she slipped.
I tried to save her, and it just...
just swept her away.
So I hid in her bed.
And they thought
Hannah Lawson had gone missing.
Both blondes,
both the same age... they...
didn't really know us,
and they didn't really care.
It was easy to pretend.
And about a month later,
they found her body.
And she was buried with my name.
Hannah Lawson.
And I lived with hers.
Amy Callen.
Done.
You sure you've got the authority
to sign jurisdiction in this case
- over to us, Kort?
- Wouldn't be here if I didn't.
She gives us the address,
we're done.
We have no more interest
in Ms. Lawson.
2175 Ellison Way, Marina Del Rey.
It's in a wall cavity
between the laundry and the bathroom.
It's in a leather satchel.
I'm rather fond of Los Angeles.
Maybe I'll put in for a transfer.
I hope not.
So, what's gonna happen when
he finds out the place
was demolished 15 years ago?
I'm not gonna hang
around to find out.
Me, neither.
She loved you so much.
You know, she cried herself
to sleep every night,
'cause she couldn't be with you.
What'd she call me?
Baby brother.
No, I...
I mean...
Just baby brother.
You disobeyed my directive...
I can't let that stand.
And you wouldn't have done
the same thing?
I know my family, Mr. Callen.
Believe me when I say,
sometimes I envy you
not knowing yours.
I'm standing you down...
- Hetty, come on...
- For one day.
Use it wisely.
Something to share, Nate?
This first address...
That was the first orphanage
Callen was sent to.
He was...
five years old.
I really can't understand
why they'd separate him from his sister.
Each address was entered
chronologically
all by the same person.
Why is that surprising?
It's an aging hand, Hetty.
Different pens, different pencils.
These addresses weren't all added
at the same time, but as they happened.
Every time Callen moved,
the same person wrote down
his new address.
You're saying someone...
someone was watching
Callen all those years?
The same person.
Happy holidays!
See you next season!
.: Team UnderCovers :.