South Park - Season 11 Episode 2
"Cartman Sucks"
This picture I like
to call "The Pierre".
I invited Butters to stay the night,
and while he was sleeping I made
a mustache on his face with cat poo.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
And this time, when Butters stayed
the night, I put a tampon in his mouth.
I call this picture
"The Sleeping Menstrual".
This one, I call "Hot Fudge Mondae".
I really like how the light
plays with the background on this one.
Is this all you brought
us over here to see?
Oh no, there's much more.
Let's see... Oh yes, look at
this one: I call it "New Moon Rising".
I did a whole study using my ass.
Here it is using some
high-contrast stuff.
Trying out some...
different light filters here.
But this is nothing compared
to what I have planned.
Because tonight...
is going to be my coup de grace.
-Butters is staying over tonight?
-Yes.
And tonight, while Butters is asleep,
I am going to...
-Hey, fellas!
-Heh!
Oh, oh hey, Butters!
I wasn't expecting you so soon.
Yeah. I finished my chores
so I came over a little early.
Hey! Are you guys all sleepin' over too?
No no, these guys were just leaving.
Weren't you guys?
Come on, let's go.
Wait, wai- I can't let this happen.
Butters.
Yeah Kyle?
Don't you think it's a little strange
that Cartman keeps
asking you to stay over?
-Kyle!
-What do you mean?
-I mean, that if-
-What he means is that he's jealous
that you've taken his place as
my new best friend! But grow up, Kyle!
-Change is a part of life.
-Yeah, grow up, Kyle.
Hrrugh!
So what do you wanna do first, Eric?
You wanna play a game
or just chitchat for a while?
Well actually Butters I think
we'd better hit the hay pretty soon.
-But, uh-ih-it's only 6:30.
-Yeah, and I'm exhausted.
If you are not sleepy yet,
I have some more of that nighttime
cold medicine you can drink.
You guys! I got it! It seriously!
It's the greatest picture ever!
Oh my God!
-What'cha do to Butters this time?
-Ihit was genius!
I waited 'til he was
totally asleep, right?
And then I got my camera,
and I pulled down his pants,
and then I took a picture
of his wiener in my mouth!
-Dude!
-I know I know, check it out, look.
I got his whole wiener in my mouth, see?
Heheh. Oh man, I got him good!
Dude, how is putting Butters'
wiener in your mouth getting him?
Because that makes Butters gay now!
-No dude, that makes you gay!
-Eh- ...what?
You put a guy's wiener in your mouth,
that makes you gay, stupid!
-Nuh uh.
-Yeah huh!
Kenny, that doesn't make me gay, huh?
(Ehe, that makes you very fucking gay.)
But I'm not g-I'm not gay, you guys!
-You are now.
-No, no, it was a stupid mistake!
-Doesn't matter. You're gay now.
-No, it was just for a second!
What, what can I do?
How how can I reverse this?
-You can't!
-No no wait.
I know how you can reverse it, Cartman.
-How?
The only way you can cancel it out
is to get Butters
to put your wiener in his mouth.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Then it cancels out the gay polarity.
...Shit, I gotta find Butters!
...Idiot.
Help me, I thinking I'm
falling in love with you...
Butters.
Whoa, hey Eric.
Butters, guess what?
I have a surprise for you.
-A surprise? What is it?
-It's so fuckin' awesome.
You're gonna be soo stoked.
It's the best surprise ever!
-Oh boy!
-You ready?
-Y-yeah!
-Okay!
Just open your mouth and close
your eyes and, and get on your knees!
-Oh, okay!
-Hang on a second here.
How come uh, I can't see?
'Cause then it wouldn't
be a surprise, would it?
Oh uh, ho yeah.
All right, that's good.
Okay, open your mouth, Butters?
That's good, just like that.
Hey. Hey wait a minute.
This ain't a trick, is it?
You're not gonna, eh stick
something yicky in my mouth, are ya?
...I swear on my mother's life, Butters.
I am not going to stick
anything yicky in your mouth.
-Wokay!
-All right, you ready?
All right just- okay,
open uh- okay, okay, here it comes.
Just sit very still, okay? Here we go.
BUTTERS!
-Uh!
-Whoa! Hey Dad!
-Butters! What are you doing?!
-I'm getting a surprise!
Oh my God!
My, my only son, reduced to this!
Hey. Where'd Eric go?
Butters, how long have
you been doing stuff like this?
-Like what?
-Don't lie to me, Butters!
I know your secret now! No wait, wait.
It's okay. It's okay, Butters.
This isn't a serious problem.
You're just bi-curious.
What's... bi-curious?
You are. Just harmless curiosity,
and it doesn't mean anything.
We just need to get
you some help, Butters.
What's going on, you two?
Nothin' Mom,
I'm just a little bi-curious.
Father Maxi, I... just don't
know where else to turn.
You see, I've just learned
that my son is... bi-curious.
Is that true, son?
Are you feeling... confused?
-...Yeah, I'm pretty confused alright.
-You see?
Young man, these confused
feelings that you're having
are simply the Devil's way
of trying to get a hold of you.
-Really?
-What can I do, Father?
There is a special camp where young
men who are confused, like your son,
can go and be cleansed
by the power of God.
Many bi-curious boys come
out the camp completely cured.
A secluded camp where lots of
bi-curious boys are all put together?
-That sounds like a good idea.
-Whoa boy! Camp!
Haa haa ha ha ha!
Very funny!
I suppose you think you really got me!
-What are you talking about, fatass?
-I checked on the Internet, Kyle,
and getting Butters to
put my wiener in his mouth
wouldn't make me not gay like you said!
-You figured that out, huh?
-That's right.
And I also learned
from the Internet
that just because I put Butters'
wiener in my mouth doesn't mean I'm gay!
All I have to do is
throw away the picture,
forget it ever happened,
and nobody will ever know.
-Except for us.
-Right, except for you.
And all the people we tell.
-Why would you tell anybody?
-Because it's really, really funny.
...It's not that funny. There's
lots of things that are way funnier.
Like what?
Liiike... a tampon... in the school
cafeteria... in, in somebody's lunch.
Liiike, a, a dog crap...
on, on a guy's face!
-That isn't funny.
-Yes it is!!
Now you guys, I'm getting pissed off!!
You'd better not tell anybody!!
-Well, maybe we will, maybe we won't.
-Fine! Whatever!
You guys don't have any proof
I put Butters' wiener in my mouth!
It will be your word against mine!
And we all know that everyone
trusts me way more than you guys!
You guys, please don't tell anybody.
Okay. We won't tell anybody
as long as you are supernice to us,
every day, from now on.
Oh right, like that's possible!
Alright, fine!
You know what I'm gonna do, Kyle?!
I'm gonna go home,
and photoshop the picture
so that it is your face
with Butters' wiener in his mouth here!
And if ANY of you
say anything to anybody,
I'll simply show them the
picture of Kyle. Ha ha, ha ha ha!
Everyone,
say hello to our new camper, Butters.
Hi Butters. Hello. Hi. Hello Butters.
-Thank you so much for taking him in.
-Don't worry.
Your son just needs to learn that
he can be straight if he chooses to be.
Do you know why you're
here at camp, Butters?
-Because I'm bi-curious?
-That's right.
Like all the campers here,
you're confused,
and you don't think there's a way out.
But even though some
people would have you believe
you can't control how you feel,
the truth is that with the power
of Jesus Christ you can be normal.
Now, just to make sure
you don't slip up while in camp
we assign every camper
an accountabilibuddy.
Let's meet Ryan, your accountabilibuddy.
Ryan thought he could never change.
But now he's learning that
with the power of Christ and prayer,
he can have a whole new life.
Over this way we have the cafeteria.
All the meals are served there.
Uh Bradley! How about you
be Butters' accountabilibuddy?
"Humble yourselves therefore
under God's mighty hand,
that he may lift you up." Peter 5:6
Butters here is new to the camp. He's
chosen to rid himself of his affliction
and forge a personal
relationship with Jesus Christ.
I'm bi-curious.
"Do not lie with a man
as one lies with a woman;
that is detestable." Leviticus 18:22
That's right, Bradley. I think
we're well on our way to being healed.
We've got another one: Room 22.
Aw, darnit!
-Aw man, I've got H O R S now.
-Okay, my turn.
WHERE IS IT, YOU FILTHY JEW?!
-Where's what?
-YOU KNOW GODDAMNED WELL WHAT!!
-Let go of me.
-What the hell are you doing, Cartman?
I went home to alter the picture
of me with Butters' penis in my mouth
to look like Kyle, but it was GONE!
WHAT DID YOU DO WITH MY PICTURE?!
Knock it off!
I don't have your stupid picture!
-Give it back, Kyle!
-I don't have it!
I swear to God, Kyle,
if you don't give it back right now,
I'm gonna break your
fuckin' Jew legs right here!
-Shut up!
-YOU SHUT UP!
You're lying,
and YOU two are covering up for him!
You know what?
You're just like Jews yourselves!
Stan, you're a Jew, and Kenny,
you're a Jew! You're ALL JEWS!!
OW!
OW!! AAAAUH!
NYAAAAAAAAAA!
The Lord is love this for
With Jesus I can just say no
And not be confused anymore.
We will now hear a sermon
from Pastor Phillips.
For those of you who are new to camp,
Pastor Phillips is somebody
who has broken free of
the bonds that afflict you.
He's bi-curious too?
Not anymore.
Because Pastor Phillips prayed,
and by the hand of Jesus Christ,
he's now completely cured!
Let's hear it for
Pastor Phiillips, kids!
Helloooo campers!
Yeth, believe it or not,
I mythelf used to have unclean urges,
and like a lot of you,
I thought I was just made that way,
that I didn't have a choice.
But then I realized that
God didn't want me to be that way!
God wanted me to be a man!
So I buckled up in my little suit and
I prayed to be normal and guess what??
It worrrrked!
That's right, kids. You see,
right now you're like a paper clip.
And just like a paper clip,
God needs to bend you, and shape you,
and make youuuu... straight.
So you say you were robbed.
Yes. A photograph. And I know who
took it! His name is Kyle Broflovski!
If it's a photo, what's the big deal?
Why don't you just
print out another one?
It's a big deal, okay?! That picture
is my propertih, and I want it back!
Okay, what is the picture of?
Why... why does that matter?
Well how are we gonna find
your picture unless we know what it is?
All right. It's a picture... of me.
Yes?
It's a picture... of me.
And um... what appears to be...
a penis... in my mouth.
You were sucking somebody's penis.
No, no I was not! I was asleep,
and this person just... puts a penis
in my mouth without me knowing!
And and took the picture!
-...I see.
-Yes.
Now it may appear in the picture...
that I'm actually looking
at the camera lens and smiling,
with the penis in my mouth.
And giving a thumbs up.
But I assure you, I was fast asleep!
Well we'd have to get a warrant first,
approved by a grand jury.
I don't have time for that!!
We have school tomorrow!
And I know that Kyle
is gonna show the picture
to everybody during Show and Tell!
Well then, you're screwed.
You both do understand that we're trying
to save your souls
from eternal life in Hell?
Well sure, I guess.
Only through Christ
can we cleanse our souls.
And you do know the rule which states
that no impure or immoral images
are allowed to be seen by the eye?
Well yeah, sure.
"So let's purify
ourselves from everything
that makes the body or soul
unclean." Corinthians, ch.7
Then do you mind telling
us why we found this
1979 Sears men's underwear catalog...
in your room?
That's... that's mine.
You know this is strictly forbidden!
Ah I don't understand.
What's wrong with underwear?
What's wrong?! This is what
makes you confused! Don't you get it?!
This is confusing you right now,
isn't it?!
Yes, it's all VERY confusing!
This is just as much your fault,
Butters!
Bradley is your accountabilibuddy!
That makes you accountabilibuddyable.
Both of your boys'
behavior is jeopardizing
all of the work we're
doing here to save these kids!
Right. For having contraband
in your room, you will both do penance
by writing scripture
for the next four days!
That sonofabitch.
He's gonna show everyone that picture.
Only twelve hours from now.
That's it. I don't have a choice. I'm
gonna have to bring Mom in on this one!
I'm just...
going to have to tell her the truth.
Ow. OW. OW!!
Eric? What's the, what's the matter?
I, don't, want to go to school tomorrow.
Sweetie, shhh, tell Mommy what happened.
Kyle, has a picture of me,
and he's gonna show everyone
during Show and Tell,
and, everyone's gonna laugh at meeee.
Oh, now why would he do that?
Because, he's jealous of
how much smarter I am than him.
So, he's gonna show
everyone the picturrrre.
What is the picture of, Eric?
Last time, when Butters spent the night,
I was being really nice to him
and I was... gonna take a
picture of him for his mom to have.
Ohh, that's nice.
But then, right when I took the picture,
Butters got really hot,
so he pulled his pajama bottoms down,
and then I tripped, and, fell down,
and my mouth landed right on his penis,
and, then I thought of something funny,
so I smiled up at, the camera
and gave like a, thumbs up,
and, and then Kyle
took the picture from me,
and he's gonna show it to everybody,
and make them think I'm gaaaaaaay.
Oh, there there, sweetie.
It'll be okay. These things happen.
But, Mom, I've been trying
to get the picture back,
but he won't give it to meee.
It's okay, Eric.
I'll have a talk with Kyle's mother.
You, you will?
"...but that he loved
us and sent his only Son
to be the satisfaction
of our sins." Neato!
Butters, I'm sorry for
getting you into trouble.
Awww, that's okay, Bradley.
I really want to get better. I try to do
everything the counselors say,
but some...how I still feel confused.
Yeah, well hopefully,
when we finish writin' all these verses,
we won't be bi-curious no more,
and then we can go home!
You're really terrific, Butters.
I mean, I think you're great.
Oh oh!
Oh God! Bad thought! Bad thought!
-Wuh-what's the matter?
-I think, I, I th-, I think I like you.
Well I like you too, Bradley.
-You do??
-Wehyeah!
-You like like me?
-Sure, I like like you a lot a lot.
Oh God, we're both unfixable!
Don't you see we're lost causes?!
We're just evil and
nothing can change us!
There's no other way out, Butters!
We have to kill ourselves!
No! Bradley! You can't leave;
you're my accountabilibuddy!
Hello?
Hello, Sheila?
It's Liane, Eric's mother.
Ohh, hello, Mrs. Cartman.
Um, Sheila, I'm sorry to trouble
you with this, but apparently
your son has a picture of Eric
with another boy's penis in his mouth.
Excuse me?
Don't worry,
sweetie, everything is fine.
It is?? Really??
Oh Mommy thank you! Thank you!
You have nothing to worry
about in school tomorrow.
Mrs. Broflovski assured me
that Kyle doesn't have the picture.
What?
She talked with her son
and says he doesn't have it.
Mom, she's lying!!
She said she was sure, Eric.
Mom, you don't know anything about Jews!
They lie all the time!
Well, Eric,
there's nothing more I can do about it.
Then that's it. Kyle wins.
But he won't win completely!
I'm going to print out
another copy of that picture
and show it to the class myself!
I can at least rob
Kyle of his final laugh.
Do you mind telling me how you managed
to lose... your accountabilibuddy?!
I went looking for 'im,
but he runs real fast.
You don't seem to take
this camp seriously, Butters.
I've called your father in for a talk.
Oh no, my Dad?
Do you understand the concept of Hell?
Do you realize that if we don't fix you
you will burn in a
lake of fire for eternity?
Well yeah, but I just don't
quite understand what you're fixin'.
We're fixing your confusion!!
There you are, Butters!
-Oheh- hey Dad.
-What's he done now?!
Mr. Stotch, your son is insubordinate,
unwilling to change,
and worse yet,
he's lost his accountabilibuddy!
They found him! They found Bradley!
You'd better come quick!
Oh Lord in Heaven! Don't jump, Bradley!
Stay-stay back!
I'm an abomination of God!
No no, we're fixing you!
Guess you think today
is your big day, huh Kyle?
To embarrass me in front of everyone?
Well guess what?
I'm not giving you the satisfaction!
Okay students, let's all take our seats.
Since it is Monday, we'll
start as always with Show And Tell.
Who'd like to go first?
Ow! Quit it, dude!
Okay Eric, Jesus, calm down.
You can go first.
HA!!
For Show And Tell today,
I would like to share with you some
very special, very artsy photographs
I've taken in pursuit of
being a respected photographer.
This first picture I like
to call "Moods of Winter",
a simple aspen grove shot
in high-contrast black and white
shows the brittleness of the
trunks and reminds one... of death.
This picture I took
just as the sun was rising
and this lonely man was walking to work.
A statement about...
all of our loneliness, perhaps?
He isn't actually
going to show everyone...
And now this next picture...
Don't jump, Bradley!
You will only make God angrier with you!
It's too late.
Bradley, please.
You're my accountabilibuddy.
How will this make me look?
You get back.
You're only gonna make things worse.
I'm not normal. I'll never be normal!
You're perfectly normal, Bradley.
Get back!
You're just as confused as he is!
All right. All right that does it!
I am sick and tired of
everyone telling me I'm confused!
I wasn't confused until other
people started tellin' me I was!
You know what I think? I think
maybe you are the ones who are confused!
Yeah.
I'm not gonna be confused anymore
just because you say I should be!
My name is Butters, I'm eight years old,
I'm blood type O, and I'm bi-curious!
And even that's okay!
Because if I'm bi-curious,
and I'm somehow made from God,
then I think your GOD must
be a little bi-curious himself!
I think. I think I'd
like to come down now.
-He's coming down!
-We did it!
Through the power of Christ
we have saved this child!
Well Butters,
I guess we might as well go home.
Looks like you're never gonna change.
No. I like bein' bi-curious.
Well you know somethin'?
So do I.
Wait. Now I am confused.
And this photograph I took
of a sunset near the power plant.
Note how the contrasting images make a
statement about our impact on the Earth.
Which brings us to
my last picture. Ahem.
This picture you may find somewhat...
controversial.
Eww!
Dude.
Yes. This is shot at a 5.6
aperture using a low-light filter.
You can see the grain
from the high-speed film,
there's sort of a penis
in my mouth right here,
and the low depth of field
keeps the background soft.
Eric, what the hell is this?!
What this is,
is a statement against the war in Iraq.
It's wrong that we still
have our troops there. It's WRONG!
-And what I think that-
-Uh, Eric Cartman?
We got an emergency
message from your mother?
"Do not show picture. Kyle didn't have
it after all. Found it under your desk."
She said you'd know
what that means, m'kay?
...Lame.
Subtitles by Spirit - Version 2.1
Transcript by South Park Scriptorium