Season 13 Episode 11
"Whales Whores"
Alright, everyone.
Welcome to the dolphin encounter
here at the Denver Aquarium!
My name is Chad
and I'll be your guide and trainer
as you meet these intelligent,
and truly magical creatures.
And here they come.
This is Trigger, Dolly and Bubbles.
- Pretty neat birthday, huh, Stan?
- This is gonna be awesome!
If they come near you,
you can touch their backs.
Just no grabbing, please.
What whimsical creatures, aren't they?
The dolphins you will be encountering
are Atlantic bottlenose dolphins.
Now who'd like to get a kiss
from one?
- I would like to...
- Me! I wanna kiss it!
Alright. Let's just get you to put
your hands, palms down on the water.
What is that?
It's the Japanese!
Fuck you, dolphin!
These are our favorite animals
here at the Atlanta Zoo.
It's Dolly and Seamore.
They are beluga whales.
These whales live mostly
in the arctic...
Fuck you, whales!
Alright, Jessica.
Now put your arms out like this.
Great job, Jessica!
Fuck you, whale!
Hey, pal.
Sorry your birthday got a little ruined
by the Japanese.
Dad, why did they do that?
Well, Stan, the Japanese just...
don't really like dolphins
very much.
Certainly not as much
as us normal people do.
But, at least
you still got your t-shirt!
And you'll always have
your neat picture.
Dan Dierdorf here welcoming you
to this great football matchup
between the Kansas City Chiefs
and the Miami Dolphins.
We're all set for kick-off and...
Dan, it looks like some Japanese people
are now rushing onto the field.
This is not the kind of thing
you want happening during kickoff.
Fuck you, dolphin!
Whales and dolphins were again
slaughtered by the Japanese today.
This time at the Six Flags
Discovery Kingdom near San Francisco.
Aquariums had been experimenting
with methods to keep the Japanese out,
but so far nothing seems
to stop them.
When asked if all of Japan
supported the slaughtering
of whales and dolphins,
the current prime minister of Japan,
Yukio Hatoyama had this to say.
Fuck you, whale!
And Fuck you, dolphin!
Guys!
Look,
it's time for us to do something.
- This is all getting way out of hand.
- What? This song is sweet.
Not the song, the Japanese
killing whales and dolphins.
- They've been doing that for long.
- So?
Don't you guys care?
We have to do something!
What can we do?
It's not like we can change
the way a country thinks.
I don't like it,
but it's just their way.
Everyone has an attitude of...
"that's the way they are"
and "that's the way it is".
Nobody likes it
but everyone's too busy to do anything.
I'm not too busy, Stan.
- You're not?
- No. I just don't care at all.
You don't care about whales
and dolphins being slaughtered?
Me and Kenny don't give two shits
about stupid ass whales.
When all the whales and dolphins
are gone, people are going to wish
that at some point, they took the time
to care just a little goddamn bit!
I wanna roll with him
a hard pair we will be
I don't give a crap 'bout whales
so go and hug a tree
I heard you're looking for people
who care about the slaughter of whales!
You wanna help?
No. I got stuff to do.
But I wanted to tell you,
there's these fellers on TV.
They go out in the ocean
to stop the Japanese wherever they are!
Really?
People who are doing something?
I watch their show all the time.
And they take volunteers!
Then that's where I belong.
We are badass.
Any means necessary.
We're not protesters.
We're pirates.
That's definitely a Japanese boat.
Looks like they're whaling now!
Fuck you, whale!
Oh, my God,
they're gonna kill those humpbacks!
- We gotta do something!
- Pull up next to them. The fight is on!
Sweet!
Are we ready to do this?
- Yeah! Let's do it!
- Are we badasses?
Are we badasses?
Alright, so...
What do we do?
Wait. I know!
How about we go on their ship
and then beat ourselves up!
And then we can tell the media
they did it!
- Great idea, captain!
- I'll start right now!
Oh, my God.
Luke's been hurt trying to save whales!
Wait!
I've got a better idea!
How about I pretend to be shot!
Then we can tell the media
the Japanese shot me
and it'll start
a international crisis!
Wait.
We don't wanna lie about stuff.
Why not?
Because then we're just douche bags.
They're right here. Let's get hardcore!
You know what?
He's right!
It's time to bring out the big guns.
You guys ready?
Ready? And...
Throw the stinky butter at them!
You stink now.
- Wait, that's it?
- Yeah, we make 'em stink!
Your boat is stinky!
Here, throw one!
They're always covered in guts!
They don't care if they stink!
Let's break their boat!
No, that'd be illegal.
I thought you guys
were pirates in a war!
I'm a pirate in a war!
Pirates don't worry about the law.
You guys said you were badasses!
We are! People think
our methods are extreme,
but we'll keep making their boat stink
as long as they're whaling!
The Japanese are scared
of how hardcore we are!
- What do we do?
- We don't have a captain!
Maybe he's okay.
- Oh, my God!
- What did you do?
What you assholes
acted like you were doing.
{\$NEW CAST MEMBER TURNS
VEGAN PUSSIES INTO ACTUAL PIRATES}
Wait for it...
Now!
And now, Larry King!
Live!
My guest tonight is the boy
who took over
the Whale Wars reality show
and turned it into a big hit.
Please welcome,
Stan Marsh and his crew.
Hey, Jordon!
I'm on Larry King, mate!
So, Stan, what motivated you,
what inspired you
to get out there
and make a hit TV show?
No, I don't care about the TV show.
I'm trying to stop
the killing of dolphins and whales.
Once you became captain
the methods used to stop the Japanese
definitely became more aggressive.
Was that the key to helping
boost your ratings?
- I don't care about the show.
- We're pirates!
I want people to know that you can stop
the Japanese if you got some real balls.
I've got balls!
Well, there are many people who see
what you're doing as a positive thing,
and of course
many that see problems with it.
Joining us now
is one of those people...
You say Stan's methods
are unethical.
Larry, you can't just go out and take
matters into your own hands like this.
If you want a hit TV show
you have to go through producers,
directors,
people that are in the unions.
But, Sid, you saw the show
before Stan took it over.
You have to admit that it was nothing
but incompetent vegan pussies
doing absolutely nothing
and trying to turn it into drama.
Yes, but it doesn't justify
changing the entire show structure
that their old captain had pitched
to the network.
Could we please talk
about the whaling problem?
But their old captain,
Paul Watson, was an unorganized,
incompetent media whore
who thought lying was okay
as long as it served his cause.
Yes, of course everyone knows
that Paul Watson was a smug,
narcoleptic liar
with no credibility, but...
Screw this.
I gotta get back to work.
On this episode
of real actual Whale Wars...
Captain Marsh searches
for the Japanese fleet,
knowing they could be
absolutely anywhere...
Would you mind stepping back?
Captain, some volunteers showed up
to help us in our crusade.
No, dude, we really can't take
any more volunteers.
But they say you know them.
Alright, dude.
This is pretty sweet.
- What?
- Now that I have a hit TV show
you care about dolphins and whales?
We always have.
- I asked for your help and you said no.
- That's not what we said.
You said,
"Me and Kenny don't give two shits
about stupid ass whales."
We were talking
about Wales the country.
If you admit that you are doing this
because you want to be on TV,
then I'll consider it.
Admit you just want to be on TV.
I deserve to be on TV.
The Japanese have been spotted
near buoy 24!
Out of port!
All hands to stations.
Alright.
Let's go save those whales!
Captain Marsh races his boat
to the last known location
of the Japanese whalers.
If he doesn't get there in time,
hundreds of dolphins
or whales could die.
When we get there we gotta be ready
to deploy the tracking devices!
We can't let those whales get hurt!
- What the hell was that?
- We just got rammed.
- The Japanese want to play that way?
- It's not the Japanese.
What?
On deck, the crew is surprised
at what they see.
The other boat is from Deadliest Catch,
a crab fishing reality show.
You think you're so cool, don't you?
You think you're a big boat
reality show on the block?
Take it away men's livelihoods.
What?
We're trying to get to some whales.
You're taking viewers away
from our show you stupid ass.
Your show is fucking gay, dude.
Your show is fucking gay.
Screw this.
Turn hard to port.
But everywhere
his reality show boat turns,
the crab fishing reality show
blocks its path.
- Dude, fuck you.
- Fuck you.
It's been three hours and the crab
fishing reality show isn't budging.
Captain Marsh's boat
is dead in the water.
Can't go after the Japanese,
can't help the whales or dolphins.
Once again on Whale Wars,
nothing is happening.
It's pretty difficult times
because...
every minute we're sitting here,
another whale is dying.
Really tough. You know.
It's really hard.
It's like we've dedicated all our times
and our lives to saving these creatures.
He's taking it especially hard.
He's always loved dolphins
so much that he...
Yeah, but keep it in the two shot.
He's always loved dolphins so much
that he would do anything.
Crab fishing reality show
is doing just fine.
But for the Whale Wars crew,
it appears the show is over.
Until a sound is heard.
What was that?
Captain, look!
The whales are taking out
the crab fishermen reality show.
It's like they know.
They do know.
They know everything
I've been trying to do for them.
Our gentle friends of the sea
have saved the day.
They know that only we
can save them from the Japanese.
Jesus Christ!
We got to get something
to shoot them with.
Look out!
I can't believe it.
Dude, you know what?
Japanese people
really do not like whales.
Well, I'm in Japanese prison lord.
Japanese prison got me down.
Said I'm in Japanese prison lord.
Don't belong here.
My eyes are round.
Will you stop that?
Sorry, am I making things
uncomfortable for you?
It's your fault
me and Kenny are in the mess!
It's bad enough
without you being a smart ass.
Whales are being slaughtered
and I can't do anything!{\*There's whales out there being slaughtered right now and I can't do anything about it!}
- So keep quiet.
- You don't have a TV show anymore,
so you can suck
my Japanese imprisoned balls.
I'm in a Japanese prison lord.
Japanese balls got me down.
So you are the ones
who have been a sinking our boats!
You speak English?
You have caused us many problems!
Set us back many months!
We don't give two shits
about you killing whales.
Can we go?
Why have you done this?
Why do you insist
on making trouble for the Japanese?
Why do you do what you do?
98% of the world is against whaling.
Why can't you just stop?
You think you have the right
to tell us
what is OK?
I have something to show you.
This is Hiroshima.
Over 50 years ago,
this entire city was destroyed
by nuclear bomb.
We built this museum
so that we never forget
what happened.
What?
Dude...
At 8:15 AM,
the people of Hiroshima
were just minding their own business,
when out of nowhere,
a flash devastated them all.
Women, children,
who died in the flash
simply evaporated.
Those left alive,
suffered the worst pain of all.
Burns, radiation poisoning.
For generations
the radiation affected the victims.
Japanese babies born without limbs.
Without eyes!
Sorry.
Little gassy.
Excuse me.
140,000 Japanese
were kill by atom bomb.
We have never recovered
from the memory of that day.
It is impossible
for a nation
to ever forgive an act so horrible.
This picture shows the plane
that dropped the bomb.
It was called the Enola Gay.
And it was flown by the monsters
who dropped the bomb that day.
Dolphin, and whale!
- Where did you get that picture?
- The Americans were nice enough
to give it to us
the day after the bombing.
We were so thankful for the picture,
that the next day
we ended our war with America.
We will never forgive.
Never rest
until they are all wiped out.
Fuck you.
Fuck you, dolphin and whale!
That's what this has all been about.
It wasn't a dolphin
and a whale who bombed Hiroshima,
it was the...
They won't rest until whoever
is responsible is completely wiped out.
Right.
Look, I think
I can make everything OK here.
Can I just use a phone?
Are you sitting at your computer?
I need you to do something for me.
Mr. Prime Minister,
Japanese officials...
You need to know something.
The photo you were given
of the Enola Gay was doctored.
Because the real bombers
feared retaliation so badly
that they simply pointed the finger
at somebody else.
My government has authorized me
to give you the original photo,
unaltered,
so you can finally know the truth.
Dolphins and whales
were just framed by the real bombers.
A chicken and cow.
Chicken and cow?
Chicken and cow used poor dolphin
and whale as scapegoat?
This is outrage!
Fuck you, cow!
Fuck you, chicken!
Great job, son.
Now the Japanese are normal,
like us.
SouthParkNews.net (1.0)
La Fabrique