11x01
"With Apologies to Jesse Jackson"
www.sub-way.fr
And now back to the Wheel of
Fortune
All right, Randy !
Grats on making it all the way to the
Bonus Round.
Thanks, Pat.
You've got some family here,
watching tonight ?
Yeah, they're all rooting for me.
And I'm sure you have lots of
friends watching back home ?
Yeah,
Hi everybody watching in South Park.
That's us, hey, hey.
- Hey, Randy.
- Good luck !
Well let see if you can't
make everyone proud.
The category is,
People who annoy you.
OK.
As always we give you the letters,
R, T, S, L
and E.
We just need three more
consonants and a vowel.
OK I'd like a B,
a N,
and a G.
and the vowel ?
an O, please.
OK, looks like you're going
to get a lot of help here.
The category is
People who annoy you.
Audience keep quiet please.
UH, well, ...
Ten seconds M. Marsh.
I know it but I don't
think I should say it.
Five seconds M. Marsh.
I'd like to solve the puzzle.
NIGGERS.
OH, naggers, of course,
Naggers.
Right.
UH, can we cut to ...
could we cut to...
Well,
Gave is my best shot.
At least we had a fup trip, gang ?
I can't believe you said the N-word
on national television.
What ?
Well, what i was
supposed to do, Sharon ?
I thought I was going to make $ 30 000 !
Stanley, the only reason daddy
used that word
is that he thought he would win money !
Dude, did your dad know
the show was broadcast live ?
Dude, the funniest thing I ever seen,
I watched it on YouTube about 60 times.
Can we just drop this, please ?
I don't want to talk about it.
Yeah, well, it's not us
you have to worry about.
It's Token.
He's going to want to kick
your crasher teeth in.
No, he's not.
Is he ?
I don't know
I just need to explain things.
Hey, Token,
Look, I don't know if you saw
Wheel of Fortune last night, but...
Yeah, I was watching it
with my whole family?
and then we saw the replays
this morning on the news.
Listen, Token, my dad is not a racist.
He's just stupid, all right ?
He just blurted out the N-word,
it's not a big deal, OK ?
Well, actually it's kind after big deal,
Stan.
It may be a mistake you don't understand
how it feels when the N-word comes up.
Don't say it isn't a big deal.
OH, *
here we go,
It's on,
race war,
race war !
race war is on, everybody !
It's goind down ! *
Going down !
Token my dad wasn't trying to be
offensive, just forget about it.
It's easy for you to say, Stan.
Yeah, come on. Here we go !
He didn't say it in anger
or anything like that.
That doesn't mean I can just be fine.
Race war, come on, race war !
If you really think it's not a big deal,
then you're really ignorant.
That's all.
I'l not fighting anybody !
Token forefits !
Whites win !
Race war is over again, everybody !
Whites won again !
I want to apologize deeply
and sincerely for using
the N-word on Wheel of Fortune,
and I want to assure you that I'm not
a racist, reverend Jackson.
The puzzle you were solving
was people annoy to you?
Well, like anybody else thought
it was naggers, I mean, right ?
M. Marsh, you need to take time to
understand african-american culture.
Visit black museums, see black
performers and artists.
Oh, I will,
I'm really down
with african-americans.
Do you really want to apologize ?
Are you sure ?
Yes, absolutely
Very well.
If you want to apologize.
I will accept.
Oh, thank you, M. Jackson.
Thank you.
Brian, get a picture of
M. Marsh apologizing.
Ready to go, Sir.
Kiss it.
Uh?
Apologize, kiss it.
- You want me to kiss your ...
- That's right, apologize.
Oh, OK,
let's see.
Apologize.
Hey, Token, I just wanted to let you
know, that everything is cool now.
My dad apologized to Jesse Jackson.
Oh, I see. So I'm supposed to feel all
better now ?
Well, yeah.
You just don't get it, Stan.
Dude, Jesse Jackson said it's OK.
Jesse Jackson is not the
emporer of black people !
He told my dad he was.
Today we are going to have a
guest speaker talk to us about
sensitivity and the power of words.
In a moment, you will meet
Dr. David Nelson,
who has firsthand experience
in overcoming slander
because David is himself
a little person.
Who knows what a little person is?
Yes, over there?
A midget?
Not exactly.
That term is actually considered
offensive.
And that's why Dr. Nelson
goes from school to school
getting us all to think
about what we say.
He has two Ph.D.'s
and has published six books,
Please welcome David Nelson!
Good morning, students.
How are we all feeling today?
I would like to share with you all my--
No, dude, no.
[Bleep]
Way!
Dude.
That, that words are like bullets,
and if you give--
Just stop, stop, stop!
Eric, be quiet.
No, no, it's OK,
he'll run out of steam here pretty soon!
Look, look, look!
They put a little suit on him!
So I said to my wife,
You told me to kill the damn cockroach,
don't yell at me for making a mess!
We got a great crowd here tonight.
Now, how many people are actually
from Colorado?
Nothing better to do on a friday night
than go to a comedy club, uh?
Hey, don't I know you from somewhere?
Yeah, I know you,
You're the guy that said the nigger
on Wheel of Fortune!
Look, everybody, it's the N-guy.
Hey, it is him.
We got a star in the club.
Everyone wave to the N-guy,
say "Hi, N-guy."
Hi, N-guy!
That's all right, N-guy,
you know we're just playing.
Yeah.
No problem.
You've seen these navigation systems
in these cars, these days?
Damn things look like
they're right out of space nuts.
Maybe N-guy has one,
you got one, N-guy?
Hey, look, Patty, it's that N-guy.
N-guy, N-guy.
Hey,
What do you think you're doing?
I just need some aspirin.
You aren't welcome in this store, N-guy.
Fine.
Principal Victoria, I'm very concerned
about the behavior of one of your students.
Yes, we apologize
for Eric Cartman's behavior, Mr. Nelson.
We feel terrible.
Why? I don't feel terrible.
It doesn't bother me at all.
Words are like bullets
and I let them pass right through me.
I just know that with some
one-on-one time together with this
Eric Cartman, I have a chance
to change the way he thinks.
It might be best if you just let it go,
OK?
You don't understand.
You see, words are like bullets
- and if you take away the gun powder--
- Yeah, yeah, we get it, Mr. Nelson.
Very well, Mr. Nelson.
Stacy, go ahead
and please send in Eric Cartman.
Eric, Mr. Nelson is concerned
how you respond to little people.
Oh, did I hurt his little feelings?
You know, think you have the power
to make me insecure,
but your words are actually
completely powerless.
We should get like eight of these and
dress them up like little beavers, right?
and put them in a pond
and see if they build a dam!
You see, no matter what you say,
I'm still standing.
Barely!
No matter how you act,
I can rise above it
Rise above it !
Rise above it,
Get it like he can rise
above anything !
Shut your [bleep] mouth.
M. Nelson !
He didn't get to me.
I was just joking.
Look, look how his face gets
red he's like a little strawbury !
Words with venom,
words that bind,
words used like weapons
to cloud my mind.
I'm a person, i'm a man,
but no mater how hard i try,
people just say, hey,
there goes that n-guy.
Everywhere i go it's
always the same,
I can't get away from
that terrible name.
Hey, n-guy, n-guy, n-guy stop !
Now go !
Call me n-guy,
fill me with your hate,
try to bring me down, oh,
you're too late.
Someone just beat you to it,
but my dream will not die.
To be thought of as more
than just n-guy.
Respect.
Token, hey, wait up.
I just wanted to say
i get it now.
You know, after that little person
talked at that assembly the day.
I understand how you feel about
somebody saying the n-word.
So black people are midgets ?
Dammit !
Excuse me, over here please !
I need all students to
join me over here.
I've called you here because it's time
at that we taught Eric Cartman a lesson
once and for all.
And in a few seconds
Eric will be sent in,
when we walk through that door
i want you al at the same
time to yell hello, fatso.
I don't think that's a
very good idea, sir.
He has to learn his lesson,
you see, words are like bullets.
All right, all right,
here he comes.
Good morning fatso !
Hey, what the hell is that ?
You think [bleep] funny?
cal, did you put
everybody up to this.
I bet you did, what
the hell is going on !
Now you know how it feels!
You didn't like it when the
tables were turned, did you ?
All right, all right, who is
the freakin' genius
who dressed up in little
suspenders, is that you ?
You can't get to this.
Words are like bullets !
And so it's my honor
to announce today the randy marsh
African-American scholarship foundation.
It is my hope that this
foundation will prove
my commitment to the education
of African-American students
and erase once and for all
my identity as the n-guy.
You really,
realy don't know how hard it is to
be constantly reminded of something
lame that happened in your past.
I just want to move on from what
happened on wheel of fortune, you know.
When people call me n-guy,
they're bringing up had a
painful chapter of my history
and the negativity that
went along with it.
You just, you can't
imagine how that feels.
Is this n-guy serious ?
Anyway, here is to a
new start for us all,
thank you !
Hey, look, Skeeter, that's
that guy from the tv.
Well, well, well !
Looks like we got
ourselves a n-guy.
Whoa !
Where you going, n-guy ?
Please, i don't
want any trouble.
Well, you got trouble !
When you first decided to slander
an entire race of people
on wheel of fortune.
Yeah, you like making fun
of minorities, n-guy ?
We don't take kindly
to social ignorance.
You tell him Skeeter, tell him !
What do you want?
What do we want ?
We want to live in a world
without people like you who are
intolerant of African-Americans.
Leave him alone.
Hey, that's that other n-guy.
that's the guy from seinfeld used
the n-word a whole bunch of times.
Michael richards,
well, sonofabitch.
looks like it's our lucky day,
we done got us two n-guys.
Make that three.
- Mark Fuhrman.
- who ?
He done said the n-word
in the oj case.
What is this a n-guy convention ?
We aren't being pushed
around anymore.
Leave !
Come on, Skeeter,
these n-guys ain't
worth our trouble.
Damn n-guys, we will be back !
You better come with us.
come on in, mr. marsh,
we'll make you coffee.
What's going on here.
We've been following your story
since we first saw it on the news,
don't worry you're
with friends now.
Dale here used the n-word
in a racial joke at word.
Scott used the plural n-word to
refer to a group of gardeners
who broke his fence.
They were mexicans,
i was being ironic.
We're all just like you.
No, no, no, i'm sorry,
i'm not like you,
i just said the n-word
by mistake to win money.
I made a mistake too,
i was trying to be funny !
I got frustrated and thought i
would get some shock laughs.
I'm just,
not that god after comedian if
you want to know the real truth.
You said the n-word to
a black man's face,
that's way worse than what i did.
You really think that matters
you really think all those people
out there see a difference ?
Oh, they might see your
racial slur was more
accidental they might
even laugh about it,
but at the end of the day,
all you are to them is just
an another damn n-guy.
- Oh, you don't like that, do you ?
- No.
Randy, we want you to join us.
We have a plan to make this all
go away once and for all.
Now, look, token,
i've done everything i
can to make this right.
You have no reason
to still be mad.
I have every reason to be mad.
You just don't get it.
I'm not responsible
for what my dad did.
No, you can't pretend
is never happened.
- What do you want from me.
- Nothing.
- Stop being mad.
- No !
Fellas, come quick,
Cartman is going to
fight the midget !
Hey, come on!
Dude, you sure you
want to do this ?
Apparently this guy has a
black belt in karate.
He's a midget, dudes.
I'm going to beat the crap
out of this kid to prove a talk.
Hey, it isn't fair i'll
laugh too much.
Senators,
I know it's not normally considered
American to ban words,
but there is one slur that's
caused so much damage
that we believe it should
finally be made illegal.
I'm talking of course
about the term n-guy.
N-guy ?
Two words which by themselves can
be harmless, but which together
form a verbal missile of hate.
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, sure, some people
use the term in guest,
tell a n-guy joke or two,
They use the excuse for violence.
The damn n-guy is trying
to be political now.
Senators,
i've learned to admit I'm capable of
having slightly racist thoughts
once in a while.
can anybody say they never do,
how long before you're all
called n-guys ?
Hold on a second, are you
suggesting that n-guy could
become a slur that refers
to all white people ?
I'm certainly not a n-guy i've
never thought a racist thought.
Oh, come on you're the
biggest n-guy in washington.
Mr. Marsh, we see now the
importance of your bill.
All those in favor to
ban the term n-guy.
- Aye.
- Opposed in.
Nay.
The motion is passed !
All right!
We did it !
For the first time in American history
a word has been officially
banned from use.
From now on, if a person
uses the word n-word,
it must be seven away from
words away from the word guy.
Tom, it appears that the n-guy epidemic
oh, dammit, i said it, didn't I ?
Oh, ow, ow, okay, okay, you win!
- Say uncle !
- Uncle !
Now say carolyn,
don't go into the light.
Carolyn, don't go
into the light !
Man, that's hysterical!
There, now you all see
that I am not limited by my size !
I have proven my point.
My work here is done.
What was his point ?
I have no idea.
- Dude, I don't get it.
- I don't get it either.
Wait a minute.
That's it.
I don't get it.
Don't you see, kyle,
I don't get it !
Token, i get it now.
I don't get it.
I've been trying to say that i
understand how you feel,
but I'll never understand.
I'm never really get how
it feels for a black person
to have somebody use the n-word,
I don't get it.
Now you get it Stan.
Yeah, I totally don't get it.
Thanks, dude.