South Park - Season 11 Episode 9
"More Crap"
Well, there's no doubt in my mind,
Mr. Marsh. You are constipated.
Thanks for the news flash!
I haven't taken a crap in over
three weeks! The question is why?!
Well, what food have you been eating?
P.F. Chang's, mostly. Good stuff.
I'm going to prescribe a laxative.
But I must warn you:
when you do finally pass this stool,
it might be very painful.
How painful is "painful"?
Oh God. Oh, here it comes.
Whoa, hot! Hot hot!
Oh, it's over. It's over.
Oh God. I feel so much better.
That... is huge.
That has got to be the
biggest crap I've ever taken.
He-... Hey Sharon.
Sharon you gotta come see this.
Sha-Sharon?
What is it, Randy?
Do you have any- Oh!! Randy!
Will you look at that? Is that the
biggest crap you've ever seen or what?
- Flush the toilet for Christ's sake!
- Come on! That's pretty impressive!
- Wha-hey Stan! Stan, look at this.
- Randy!
- Look what your old man made.
- No way!
Huh? Never seen one that big, have you?
- No, never.
- Gross, Dad, sick!
All right,
will you flush the toilet now?!
I'll try, but I don't think-
wait wait wait wait a minute.
I gotta call Jimbo first.
- Why?!
- Well he's gotta see this.
- We are flushing the toilet right now-
- No!!
Jimbo has to see it so when
I tell the guys how big it was,
they'll know I'm not lying!
- Oh, for the love of God, Randy!
- Sharon, this is important!
Stan, go call your Uncle Jimbo.
I'm gonna stand guard.
Hey guys!
- Hey Randy.
- Oh, hey Randy.
Are you feeling better?
Yeah, I-naw, I'm totally fine now.
You guys shoulda seen
the crap Randy took last night!
It was honestly, the biggest
crap anyone has ever taken. Ever.
Well I don't know about ever...
I'm telling you this thing
was the size of a freaking football.
I guess it was pretty big.
- A football? That's amazing.
- I've never heard of one that big.
Oh, my brother took a crap once,
that was enormous.
It was the biggest in the
history of the world, I think.
It wasn't bigger than mine was.
Oh no, seriously,
this crap was a monster!
Mine... mine was bigger.
I doubt it.
You wanna see it?
Oh my freaking Lord.
That did not seriously
come out of your ass.
Oh yes, it did. Go ahead and check
it for splits. It's one solid piece.
Jesus...
That uh, a little bigger
than your brother's there, Gerald?
It's... other-worldly.
Randy, have you called the people from
the Guinness Book of World Records?
This might seriously be
the biggest crap in history!
That's why I gotta
make sure to keep it safe.
- Randy Marsh!
- Aw crap!
What the hell do you think you're
doing keeping that thing in our house?!
The guys agree, Sharon:
it could be a record holder.
Why are men so obsessed
with how big their crap is?!
{\Guinness Book
Corporate Office}
Guinness World Records America.
How can I help you?
The biggest crap?
We actually don't keep
track of that record, sir.
Because we don't want to.
Look, we get calls from men all the time
who believe they took the biggest crap,
and we simply can't handle
all the measuring and verification.
You need to call the European Fecal
Standards and Measurements Office.
You're welcome.
Jeez, another one.
Guinness World Records America.
Uh yes, hello. My name is Randy Marsh,
and I believe I took
the world's biggest crap.
You need to call the European Fecal
Standards and Measurements Office.
Their number is listed
on their Web site.
{\European Fecal Standards
and Measurements, Zurich}
President, take a look at this. It is a
crap sent to us from the United States.
Very nice.
- Has it been checked for accuracy?
- It appears to be legitimate,
based on the photo. We estimate that the
crap is over eight and a half Courics!
We'd better get on a plane. Right away.
What was your primary diet for this poo,
Mr. Marsh?
Uh, mostly P.F. Chang's.
General Tsao's Chicken...
Oh and uh, and a lot of uh Aunt Jemima's
Frozen Sausage Biscuits in the morning.
I believe I detect some cabbage as well?
Oh yes, I had a lot of kim chee.
You have got to be kidding me.
These guys are from Zurich, Sharon!
They're Europeans!
It is a tremendous crap, Mr. Marsh.
For the love of God!
Your crap officially weighs...
8.6 Courics.
Courics...
The standard measuring
unit for human feces.
One Katie Couric is approximately
two and a half pounds of excrement.
The current record is
a crap weighing 7.5 Courics.
But that means...
That's right.
You are the new world's champion!
Really?! Yuh, you mean, really?!
Hey Stan!
I uh- Hey Sharon! Hey everybody!
Well, I guess we'd better
call the old champion
and let him know his
record has just been broken.
He has won twenty-two Grammy's,
countless humanitarian awards,
and is the only person
ever to be nominated for
an Academy Award, a Golden Globe,
and the Nobel Peace Prize.
Ladies and gentlemen, Bono!
Thank you. Thank you so much
for this newest award; it means so much.
Oh. Excuse me.
I must be getting another award.
Yes?
Yes, Bono, sir, we wish to inform you
that your record for biggest
crap has just been broken.
What?! That's impossible!
How big was it?
We are here to honor the first American
to bring home the
distinguished EFSM medal
for biggest crap ever taken.
Hey look, Sharon, it's the President!
He-hey Sharon!
To present the award
I give you the dean of the EFSM,
Sir Orloff Broloff.
Thank you, Senator.
For over a hundred years now,
the European Fecal Standards and Meas-
Herr Broloff! Herr Broloff!
Ah ladies and gentlemen,
I understand we have just received
a special video-taped
announcement from Bono!
Oh! Bono? Cool!
Could we play the tape
on the big screen, please?
Hello everyone! I, am Bono.
For years it has been my honor to try
and bring focus to the needs in Africa,
and today, I have very exciting news.
Last night, at twenty past eight,
I took a crap weighing 9.5 Courics.
Bono?!
As you can see, it is one solid piece.
It is my biggest crap to date,
and I swear to its authenticity.
Thank you, and God bless.
You heard it, ladies and gentlemen!
The official biggest crap is...
9.5 Courics!
Congratulations to Bono!
Bo-no!
Dad, um, I think dinner's almost ready.
I almost did it.
I almost made something of myself.
You know, when you get real close,
you start thinking that
maybe your life is gonna matter.
I mean, this was something I made!
Something that came from me!
That was a part of me!
The only thing I ever
made that was any good!
- Gee, thanks a lot, Dad.
- You're welcome.
And I just...
I know that this late in my life
I'll never come so close
to finally having... meaning.
Come on guys, lasagna's ready.
Oh. Lasagna's ready.
You hear that, Stan?
Mom says lasagna... is ready!
I can see through your sarcasm, Sharon!
What are you talking about?
You can say it, Sharon!
I know Bono's better than me!
I'm sorry I'm not Bono, all right?!
Sorry that I don't have... billions
of dollars and a Nobel prize nomination!
Randy, this is ridiculous!
Oh, that's real mature, Sharon!
Just act like everything's funny!
It's a big joke to you, isn't it?!
Just a big joke! Don't touch me!
Can you believe him?! All this
over what guy took the biggest crap!
You don't understand, Mom.
You just don't understand.
Wha? Wha?
How come they just let that
Bono guy send a picture of his crap?
'Cause he's Bono, that's why.
But he could have faked it.
It isn't fair!
Doesn't matter. He's got the record now;
there's nothing I can do.
Oh yes there is! You could do it again!
- What?
- Think about it:
you weren't even trying to
take the biggest crap last time.
Imagine if you actually worked at it!
Hey. Hey that's right.
No. I can't go through all that again.
It's too much.
Come on, Randy. I'll bet
you can crap that big again easy!
With the right diet and training,
who knows what you're capable of?
Guys, forget it! It's over!
It was a fluke crap;
I'll never take one that big again!
Is it over, Randy?!
We all saw that crap you took!
That was no fluke!
There's something inside you
that made you able to do it!
Randy, you have a gift.
Now who knows why God chose you,
but he did!
And if you walk away now,
you'll always... wonder...
how big a crap you could have taken!
I would need a lot of help.
That's what we're here for.
Come on, Randy, what do you say?!
I say...
Let's give Bono a run for his money!
Yeah!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
This is CNN headline news.
Tonight, a possible attack on Iran
may mean the beginning
of a new war in the Middle East.
Oh no.
But first,
the record for the world's biggest crap:
will it again be broken?
Randy Marsh of Colorado is now three
weeks into his quest to make a new crap,
spending nearly every
waking hour at P.F. Chang's.
Is this really newsworthy?
You just don't understand.
You're right. I don't.
At the same time, some people are
questioning Bono's current record entry,
saying nobody has
ever seen it in person.
Bono could not be reached for comment,
as he is currently in
Africa helping the needy.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Hello, hello.
Marsh is attempting
to break the record again.
We thought you should know.
He can't beat my
nine and a half Courics!
Well he's going to try.
Fine, but he has to take
the crap in front of you! In Zurich.
Bono, we've never had that rule before.
Is the only way you
can know he's not cheating!
If he doesn't crap in Zurich,
it shouldn't count!
Ultrasound is very simple, Mr. Marsh.
We're going to use harmless
waves to look inside your belly.
Just gonna put some warm
gel on your stomach first.
Okay, take a deep breath.
I see the crap now.
I can't say for sure,
but I, I'd say is about...
14 Courics.
- Fourteen?!
- That's great, Randy!
- Can I, Can I see it?
- Sure.
This is your colon, and here...
is the feces growing inside your belly.
Guys, we have a problem!
I talked to the EFSM and they say
Randy has to take the crap in Zurich.
In Zurich?
They say that Bono is demanding it
and that their hands are tied.
Sorry, I cannot condone you traveling
on an airplane in your condition.
It is never safe to fly
during your turd trimester.
Hi, could I speak to Mr. Bono, please?
Mr. Bono,
you have a young gentleman caller!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Get the jet ready, Bovis!
I've got to be going.
Hi, my name is Stan Marsh.
My dad's trying to beat
your record for biggest crap.
Oh right.
He can't make it to Zurich, right?
That's kind of what I'm here for:
Do you really need
the biggest crap record?
Could you maybe see your way to just...
letting my dad have this one?
Let him have it? Why would I do that?!
Look, you you gotta understand, sir.
My dad's never won an
award for anything. Ever.
He doesn't have one single trophy.
Even I have a second-place trophy
for most Sports Illustrated
subscriptions sold.
I have the first-place trophy for that.
Dude, don't you have enough? I mean,
you got tons of money, a jet,
and the biggest rock band in the world,
a hot wife, and,
you've been knighted. I mean,
at some point,
can't you just kind of... fuck off?
I want people to know that
I'm worth something. That I matter.
All I'm asking is that
maybe with this one thing,
let my dad be number 1.
And you can still be number 2.
Number two?!
Nobody calls me that
anymore and gets away with it!
- Take it back! Take it back!!
- I take it back!
- Say I'm not number two!
- You're not number two!
That's right! I'm not!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
What is wrong with that guy?
Your father is in grave danger.
Come with me!
{\European Fecal Standards
and Measurements, Zurich}
It must be quite a crap.
Come on, Randy. You have to push!
What are you saying?!
How do you know my dad is gonna die?!
Because nobody has ever
taken a crap that big before!
So Bono's newest record is a lie!
Look, I first knew something
was wrong when I looked at
Bono's first award for biggest crap.
It said he took it in 1960.
- So?
- So that's the year Bono was born.
Then it all made sense to me.
How could Bono be so talented,
so caring,
and yet seem like such a piece of crap?
Because he is crap.
Don't you get it?
Bono is not the record holder...
He's the record.
Yes.
I can't do it! I can't do it!
The crap is simply too big, Mr. Marsh.
We must perform a Caesarean!
But then, does it still count?
Oh no! The biggest crap
means you crapped it out!
I believe that's true.
We are sorry, Mr. Marsh, but,
if you cannot crap out the crap,
it's not really a crap.
No... No...
There there Randy, you...
You gave it your best shot.
I want my wife. Sharon? Sharon?
- What?!
- I'm sorry, Sharon.
Sorry that I let you down.
Sorry I can't crap like Bono.
Well congratulations,
Bono, it appears your record is intact.
I had a feeling it would be.
Wait! Stop!
Dad, your old crap counts.
Bono never took a second
crap to beat yours.
Get him out of here!
What are you talking about, young man?
Somebody's been keeping it a secret.
Bono was never the record holder!
He's the record!
It's not true!
Kill the kid! I want him dead!
It's too late, Bono.
The boy has learned the truth.
Herr Broloff, what do you know of this?
It's true, I'm afraid.
You see, until Mr. Marsh came along,
I was the record holder
for the biggest crap.
I took it back in 1960.
It was the most amazing
crap I'd ever taken.
Poppa no! Say nothing more!
Come to me my... darling precious child.
After I had broken the
record I took the crap home.
I was so proud of it that I...
decided to keep it,
to try and raise it like a child.
No Poppa... No Poppa...
There there, my little crap.
Don't cry.
Here, do you want the biddy?
Hmm? Does Bono want the biddy?
Yes, he likes the biddy doesn't he?
Dude.
I kept the crap in my office,
nursed it, fed it biddy.
And soon biddy made him strong.
Biddy made him grow up!
Into one of the most
influential figures of our time.
Easy Bono, that hurts the biddy.
Biddy.
My little crap has
accomplished many things.
But he could never shed the
fact that he was really... a number two.
So he spent his life trying
to be number one, in everything.
That's why he's able to do so much,
try to help so many people, but
still seem like such a piece of shit.
You have blemished this noble
society's good name, Herr Broloff.
Have I?! Look at the crap
I took all those years ago!
Bono is now almost six feet
tall and over 80 Courics in weight!
No matter how you look
at it he is still the record!
Oh God, here it comes!
Oh hot hot hot hot!
Hot hot hot hot hot hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
My God...
It must be over a hundred Courics!
- Dad, are you all right?
- Yeah,
I'm... I'm good! Feel a lot better.
Mr. Marsh,
we apologize, and if it's okay with you,
we would like to present you...
your long overdue trophy.
Subtitles: Team SouthParkNews.Net
Transcript: South Park Scriptorium