Previously on The Vampire Diaries...
For over a century,
I have lived in secret, until now.
I know the risk
but I have to know her.
- She's a deadringer for Katherine.
- What are you?
I'm vampire.
I've been 17 years old...
since 1864.
I promis I will keep your secret but
I can't be with you Stefan.
- Five bodies all drained of blood.
- They've come back.
Hello, brother.
- She's transitioning.
- Into what?
- A vampire.
- Vicki, what the hell?!
- Why is everybody have to die on me?
- Can you make him forget?
I'll do it.
What do you want him to know?
That Vicki left town, he's gonna misss
her but he knows it's for the best.
Lexi?
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
How could you even ask that?
I missed you.
Happy birthday.
Mystic Falls Team
1x08 - 162 Candles
Adra, Croutch, Haize, Humanidyne,
McFly, MiniBen314, Thirteen, WoLF971
I don't know, okay. Some freak
shot at me with wooden bullets,
I'd bail in under 60. And...
why is a news reporter
hunting vampires?
I don't know who knows about us.
That guy did.
There could be others. Do me a favor.
While you're here, please be careful.
Why stay?
I'm headed to New York
for the weekend.
Bon Jovi in the garden.
"Wanted dead or alive."
It's our theme song.
It'll be a blast.
Do you think that
he would actually remember us?
- That was a pretty crazy weekend, huh?
- We can make him remember us.
Come on! Let's go.
- I mean, what's keeping you here?
- I told you.
Her name is Elena.
Well, let's hope she's better than
the last girl you got all sprung over.
You didn't even know Katherine.
Cause if I did, I'd kick her ass.
Little bitch. Speaking of...
- Where's Damon?
- Inflicting misery somewhere.
You gonna be okay here alone?
I got some things I gotta take care of.
It's not exactly
like I can go anywhere.
And you and Damon are the only ones
with these nifty little daylight rings.
I have a mood ring
from '75. Trade ya?
Doesn't work that way
and you know it.
- I'm really glad that you came here.
- What are we doing
for your birthday? It's not every day
a guy turns 162 years old.
Really?
Where did Vicki say she was going?
- She didn't.
- Did she tell her brother
- where she was going?
- She didn't say anything to me.
She told Jeremy to tell me
she was leaving town.
Is there anyone I can talk to that
may know what happened to her prior
- to her leaving town?
- Stefan Salvatore may know.
He came by the house to see her
but she wouldn't talk to him.
- What was he doing there?
- I was trying to help her.
I knew that Elena was worried
about her brother.
He was dating Vicki and she had
a drug problem, so I tried to help.
So you got involved
because Elena asked you to?
I asked Stefan to help.
I thought that by helping Vicki,
he was helping my brother.
What was her behavior like
those last few days before she left?
Up and down.
Very sketchy, like...
she was coming down
from some major party.
- Any signs of aggression or violence?
- Not that I remember.
So you believe
Vicki really has left town?
I'll miss her, but...
I think it's for the best.
I was tryin' to help her, Matt.
That's all.
I'll meet you guys at the car.
You okay?
I don't think the sheriff
suspected anything.
Jeremy had no memory at all.
All he knew was what
Damon made him know.
Thank you.
I can't do this, Stefan.
Every time I look at Matt or Jeremy,
all I think is that
Vicki is never gonna come back,
And they'll never know why.
Around you, people get hurt
and people die and I just...
It's just too much...
Why don't we go somewhere
and talk about it?
You have to stay away from me.
What an unexpected surprise.
Unexpected surprise?
I think the wrong brother
went back to high school.
- How long you here for?
- Just for Stefan's b-Day.
You mean you didn't come
all this way to see me?
That's it, Damon.
After a century, I finally realized
death means nothing without you.
Do me.
Why are you so mean to me?
Have you met you?
You're not a nice person.
- Because I'm a vampire.
- But you're only the bad parts.
Teach me to be good.
I'm older, and that means stronger.
- Sorry.
- Don't ruin my time with Stefan,
cause I'll hurt you.
And you know I can do it.
You leavin'?
Dad doesn't like it
when I stay here too much.
Because he misses you,
or because he doesn't trust me?
Your father's problem
is he lacks imagination.
He thinks I fill your head
with all my witchy juju.
- He's right.
- He's always right.
That's his other problem.
You need to be wearin' that.
I gotta get it back to Caroline.
It doesn't belong to me.
Yes, it does. It was your ancestor's
and now it's yours.
Emily was your ancestor, too.
Why don't you wear it?
It didn't find me. It found you,
protected you.
A witch's talisman
is a powerful tool.
Don't be givin' that back
to anybody.
I just wish it was prettier.
You're wallowing.
So are you.
My wallow is legitimate.
I was dumped.
- Yeah. Well, Logan's a jerk.
- You didin't get a brushoff e-mail
saying, "I'm leaving town.
See ya."
- Wanna keep it down over there?
- Why? What are you doing?
Homework.
Since when do you do homework?
I gotta finish this. I'm way behind
and I have a quiz tomorrow, so...
What do you think?
Alien?
Some sort of replicant.
He can hear you.
Send him in.
Mr. Salvatore, come on in.
- Could you get the door for me?
- Sure.
I understand from Mrs. Lockwood
that your uncle's out of town.
Yes, he is.
But I spoke with Zach.
He filled me in and asked
if I could bring this to you.
Vervain.
That's all we have at the moment.
I hope it's enough.
It's a small circle...
Founding families,
a few city officials.
And your deputies, of course, right?
Are we any closer?
I think our facts are wrong.
We've always believed that vampires
can only come out in the dark.
What if that's changed?
Is that even possible?
We've exhausted every other option.
We have to consider the vampire
may be walking around during the day
right in front of us.
- So what's the next step?
- We're now looking at anyone
new to town since the deaths began.
Should turn up a suspect or two.
And I of course
will do anything I can to help.
You up?
Why haven't you called me back?
I'm sorry.
Are you gonna stay in there forever?
Move over.
I'm officially worried.
What's going on?
I'm tired of thinking...
of talking. I...
Can I get a one-line version so
I can at least pretend to be helpful?
Stefan and I broke up.
I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
Right. Stupid question.
I know I've been kind of MIA
when you need me the most.
I suck.
You wanna make it up to me?
Get my mind off of it.
Just remember you asked for it.
Be patient.
I need to swear you to secrecy.
It's kind of a bad week
for that kind of stuff.
Swear, cause I'm not supposed
to be showing you this.
- I swear.
- There's no windows open, right?
- Right.
- There's no fan,
- no air conditioning.
- None. What are you doing?
Grams just showed me this.
You're gonna love it.
You ready?
Bonnie, what's going on?
It's true, Elena,
Everything my grams told me.
It's impossible,
but it's true.
I'm a witch.
I believe you.
Look, dungeon boy,
I'm done being your little slave girl.
You seriously hurt me
and I will be damned if you think...
Oh, my God.
Where have you been?
- It's really good to see you.
- Much better.
You wanna throw a party
here at the Grill tonight.
Why don't you do it?
Because then Stefan and his BFF
won't come. I need a lot of people,
big crowd. Invite everyone.
And why am I having this party?
Because you are gonna help me solve
this town's little vampire problem.
- And I want my crystal back.
- But Bonnie has it.
I know that.
Get it from her.
So, this Elena girl,
she'll come around. I'm sure of it.
Have you had sex yet?
Sex always works.
You'll rock her world so hard
with your vamp sex,
- She'll be yours forever.
- Yeah, but see, this isn't about
sex or... or compulsion
or any of our other tricks.
She has to want
to be with me on her own terms.
That sounded
all mature and grown-up.
I'm not getting any older.
Want some?
Thank you.
Relax. I didn't kill anyone for it.
This phlebotomist I went out
with a few times, he's my supplier.
Don't judge, okay?
Listen, I tried the animal diet.
Lasted 3 weeks.
Doesn't matter.
Cause if I started again...
- I don't know if...
- You could stop.
- I'd never judge you.
- I'm just jealous of your restraint.
I have none.
I delight in hedonism.
Speaking of which,
- What are we doing tonight?
- Funny you should ask.
Well, I wasn't asking you.
There's a party
at the Grill. You'll love it.
Banquettes, tacky wait staff.
All of Stefan's friends.
- I don't want a birthday party.
- Well, it's not for you.
It's a party party. No one's
gonna know it's your birthday.
- Caroline's throwing it.
- Damon, stay away from Caroline.
We're friends. It's cool.
It's important for the town to see us
out and about like normal folk.
We need to blend.
I prefer mine at 98.6.
Let's go.
Please?
It's weird, huh? After all this time
joking about being psychic,
I really am a witch.
You don't think
I'm a freak now, do you?
No. Of course not.
I just... I don't understand, though.
If your grams asked you
to keep all this a secret,
why did you tell me?
You're my best friend.
I can't keep secrets from you.
I'm almost ready.
I can't believe you actually think
that we should go to this thing.
It's not like I'm asking you to run
outside midday without your ring.
I mean, seriously, it's a party.
A party that Damon wants us to go to,
you know. So my question is,
- "why?" I think he's up to something.
- Who cares?
I mean, what can he possibly do in front
of all those people in a public place?
He knows how to keep
a low profile, believe me.
So he'll behave.
Come on. One day a year, I get you,
One day that you're not brooding
and existing in your own head.
- It's my birthday, yeah?
- It's my day, and that guy
that jumped naked
in the Trevi Fountain and
got drunk on the Torch
of the Statue of Liberty, That guy
can take a break from all
of his worrying for one night
and go to a stupid party.
So quit your whining...
and go get ready.
Fine.
It's open. Come on in.
How...
- Who...
- I'm Elena.
- Who are you?
- Lexi.
A friend of Stefan's.
- Is he here?
- He's in the shower.
Do you wanna wait?
I'll tell him you stopped by.
That's okay.
Are you out of your freaking mind?
What are you talking about?
I just met Elena.
You have some serious
explaining to do.
emotional damage.
It's not what you think.
She's not Katherine.
Then they're related
because they could be twins.
- I don't know.
- You don't know.
- You didn't find out?
- No. Maybe I don't wanna know.
I have no desire
to tie Elena to Katherine.
The resemblance is what
drew me in but that's it.
Katherine and Elena may look
the same on the outside,
But on the inside,
they are completely different.
So Elena's not
a raging bitch then, huh?
No, Elena is...
Elena's warm,
And she's...
She's kind and she's caring
and she's selfless,
and it's real.
And...
honestly, when I'm around her...
I completely forget what I am.
You're in love with her.
Yeah, I am.
Amazing party, right?
Glad you thought of it.
- Well, are you having a good time?
- Do you have my crystal?
Then I'm not having a good time.
- Where's my brother?
- He said he'd meet me here.
Buy you a...
What are you doing rere?
Lexi said that you came by
and you seemed upset.
Right.
The girl in the towel.
The towel?
Not like that. No.
She's not exactly a girl. Lexi's...
She's 350 years old.
You mean she's a...
And she's my oldest friend.
Nothing romantic.
Ever.
Okay, well...
she kept staring at me.
It was weird.
Well, you know,
I've talked about you
a lot, so...
guess she felt like she knew you.
So why'd you come by?
It was a mistake.
- Elena, talk to me.
- I can't.
Stefan, I can't
and that's the problem.
I'm keeping all these secrets
from everyone.
I can't even tell my best friend.
Do you know how hard that is?
It's like I need to talk to someone
but the only person I can talk to is
you... and...
I want you to know
that I will always be here for you.
You can come to me
about anything, okay?
Well, thank you for coming by.
Do you need a ride
to the Grill tonight?
- Are you going to Caroline's party?
- Lexi's dragging me.
And...
it's my birthday.
Really?
- Happy birthday then.
- Thank you.
Actually, I...
I think I'm gonna stay in tonight.
Well, have... have a good night.
I've been looking for you.
I'm totally sorry to do this.
I know it's so indian giver,
and we're not even supposed
to say that anymore, but
- I need my crystal back.
- Why? You said you hated it.
Then I saw it on you
and I realized how great it is.
And I've got, like, three outfits
I can coordinate it with, so...
I can't give it back to you.
Well, I didn't want
to have to tell you this,
but I'm your friend.
When you wear it,
it makes you look fat.
There. I said it, but
it's because I'm your friend, so...
I'm sorry. Caroline, I can't.
What do you mean
that you can't, Bonnie? It's mine.
- I thought you said it was Damon's.
- It is.
So he's the one
who really wants it back?
Maybe. Just...
Are you wearing polyester?
You were really gonna pull it
from my neck?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Just hear me out?
Please?
I was just trying to help Vicki.
I went through
something similar once.
I'm really sorry.
Don't be.
It's not the first time she's run off.
Turns out
Vicki's just like her mother.
I can't count on either of them.
Thanks for trying.
Where is it?
Bonnie won't give it to me.
So rip it off her neck.
I tried. It shocked me.
Damn it.
Why does it do that?
- I need that crystal.
- Why are you being like this?
I'm so good to you
and I'd do anying.
It's just some stupid necklace.
You are the only stupid thing here.
And shallow.
And useless.
Okay, I'm gonna need
a little more foot movement.
Yeah, I'm not really interested
in making a fool out of myself.
Come on. You're not that bad.
Do me a favor. Tell me if you see
Damon with his camera phone.
Right.
- Where are we going?
- No one's gonna see us...
- Did you hear something?
- No. It's cool.
There's no one coming down here.
Nice!
Stefan smiles.
Alert the media.
You haven't given him
a lot of reasons to be happy lately.
You're right. Poor Stefan.
Persecuted throughout eternity
by his depraved brother.
Does it get tiring
being so righteous?
It flares up
in the presence of psychopaths.
Well, consider
this psychopath's feelings hurt.
What did you do to my brother?
I'm gonna need
a less vague question.
When you did what you did
to Jeremy's memory of Vicki,
- What else did you do to him?
- You asked me
to take away
his memory of fangs and...
and all the bad stuff.
You wanted me
to take away his suffering.
But he's acting different.
He seems okay with everything
and a little too okay.
I mean, he's studying. He's not
doing drugs. He's not drinking.
Are you sure
you didn't do something else?
I took away his suffering.
- Don't talk to me.
- Don't do that. Let me explain.
What is there to explain?
You got what you wanted...
And something that doesn't even
belong to you, by the way.
And I get called a shallow,
useless waste of space.
- Who said that to you?
- Who do you think?
You know that's not true.
Don't let him treat you like that.
As opposed to how
my best friend treats me.
Two shots of tequila.
Make that three.
I need to see some ID.
No, you don't.
- That'll be...
- Free.
- On the house.
- Thanks.
The famous Elena.
Towel girl.
I've been called worse.
Here.
I didn't know
that you guys could drink.
Yeah. It helps curb the cravings,
But makes for a lot of lushy vamps.
I've never seen Stefan drunk.
- He always seems so...
- Uptight?
But not with you.
That's the benefit of knowing
someone for over 100 years.
You can just be yourself.
- He can't be himself with me.
- Well, not yet.
The first step was him telling you.
The rest comes with time.
You seem so sure.
The love of my life was human.
He went through what
I imagine you're going through...
Denial, anger, et cetera.
But at the end of the day,
love really did conquer all.
Are you gonna drink that?
Go for it.
I'm scared.
But you're here...
cause you're crazy about him.
I get it, okay? I mean,
what's not to love?
Listen.
Take it from someone
who's been around a long time.
When it's real, you can't walk away.
It was really nice meeting you.
Yep, I drank yours.
Sorry.
Thank you.
You weren't supposed
to be listening.
I was feeling epic.
Whatever.
Keep this contained.
That's not all.
Did you see what did this?
Tell me everything you saw.
You came.
I couldn't miss your hundredth and...
whatever birthday.
I slim... I'm slipped.
I slipped.
Hammered, huh?
Well...
a very nice but not handsome
bartender
was very kind to me tonight.
Unlike the rest
of the global humanverse.
Are those curly fries?
Coffee for the drunk girl.
Bad night, huh?
Baddest.
Am I shallow?
- Is that a trick question?
- I don't mean to be.
I wanna be deep.
I wanna be, like...
the abyss deep.
No offense, Care, but
deep's really not your scene.
That's true.
I'm shallow.
I am worse than shallow.
I'm a kiddie pool.
You're not a kiddie pool.
Can I just go home?
I'll take you. Come on.
You're okay. She's all right.
Hold still. Hold still.
What happened?
- Is she okay?
- Like you care.
- She's drunk?
- As a skunk.
Are they serving you in there?
I'll take her home. It's on my way.
I haven't been drinking.
I would appreciate that, Matt.
Thank you.
You and I will discuss this later.
Can't wait.
Don't let anybody else leave.
All right, the shots are a bribe.
I need you to answer a question.
What are you really doing
in Mystic Falls?
Have you tried the Brittle?
It wins awards.
Cut the crap.
I have a diabolical master plan.
What is it?
Well, if I told you, it wouldn't be
very diabolical, would it?
Look around.
Let me know if you see him.
What are you doing?
Thank you for the vervain.
Now if you'll excuse me.
What is it?
Excuse me. Sorry.
Can't go out this way.
Why?
It's part of the plan.
You okay?
Thank you.
Get it in the car quickly.
Lady, I checked everyone's ID.
Apparently you didn't.
Pretty handy with that stake.
It just... reflex. I guess the
adrenaline kicked in.
This nightmare is finally over.
Caught a lucky break with that witness.
Without her, you wouldn't have been
- able to ID the vampire.
- Very lucky.
Well, thank you again.
You're welcome.
You gonna be okay?
Do you ever feel like there's not
a person in the world
that loves you?
Life can be a little rough.
I just wish...
What?
Wish that life was...
different.
Yeah. Me, too.
Please...
don't leave me alone.
He killed her.
He killed Zach.
He killed Tanner. He turned Vicki.
I have to kill him.
No. You can't do that.
Why are you trying to save him?
He's never gonna change.
Don't you see that?
- He's never gonna change.
- I'm not trying to save him.
I'm trying to save you. You have no
idea what this will do to you. Please.
Everywhere that I go,
pain and death follow.
Damon follows me.
No more.
Please. Please, just talk to me.
Let me be here for you. Talk to me.
You were right to stay away from me.
Told you I'd take care of it.
Come on. I did this for you
to get them off our trail.
You never do anything
for anyone but yourself.
You missed.
You saved my life.
I'm sparing yours.
We're even.
And now we're done.
It's coming.
Mystic Falls Team
www.forom.com