My father worked as a lawyer for
the richest family in New York
until his plane went down
in Long Island sound.
He left me his biggest client,
the Darlings--
Tripp, the empire builder,
Letitia, the
sophisticated socialite.
Don't you think it kills me to see
you making the same mistakes I did?
- What mistakes?
- Putting three people in your marriage.
- Brian, the man of God...
- Is orphan not P.C. anymore?
- He's not an orphan.
- Your brother Brian is his father.
Patrick, the
principled politician...
I am tired of it all-- the money,
the advice, the support, all of it.
- Patrick--
- we are done.
We finally get together.
- Been a long time coming.
- I'll say.
Karen, the professional divorcée...
Nick is my past,
you're my future, okay?
Letting me risk ruining
my marriage to Freddy
sure makes it seem like
you want me free for you.
And Jeremy and Juliet,
the well-behaved twins.
She was my best friend in the whole world,
and I hate her guts.
Baby, are you sure it's not bad luck
to see each other on the big day?
Who cares? That tradition has not
exactly worked for me in the past.
What's that tradition
all about anyway, huh?
Did Moses cook that up?
It's about seeing your beloved
again for the first time.
And no,
Moses did not "cook that up."
Now have you two given any
thought to your vows at all?
I'm thinking a golf
theme would be nice.
You know, something with hazards
and fairways and holes in one.
No, all we need is have and
hold and sickness and health
and a little open bar.
You know, Karen, as your brother, I agree.
No one cares what you say.
But as your minister,
I am required to honor this... eternal union.
Okay. Just do what you want.
Just, uh, keep it short.
- See you in seven hours.
- Whoo! Amen to that.
Because we are in it to win it.
- Next question.
- Mr. Attorney general, earlier today,
your office indicted one of the city's
biggest real estate developers,
the Fantini brothers,
on multiple counts of--
of bid rigging, fraud,
collusion, tax evasion--
Fred, this lawsuit's a message to all
of New York's real estate developers.
You will be held accountable for your
corrupt and deceive business practices.
Next.
But aren't you worried that
by bringing charges against
Michael and Sal Fantini,
you may come into conflict with your father?
This is not about my family, Dave.
This is about our New York.
Okay. Thank you. No more questions.
The ambassador decided to bring
a date at the last minute.
People can be... so thoughtless.
I'm kinda having second thoughts...
about the wedding.
Yeah, I assumed that's
what you meant.
Is this about Nick?
- Is it?
- Nick? No, no.
No, Nick hasn't even entered my mind today.
It's about... Freddy.
He's not exactly, um... complicated.
You're just like your father.
You want fairy tale love.
You're a romantic.
But... you know what's
really romantic?
Is to wake up every morning and say,
"I choose you...
"again today, no matter what."
Like you chose dad.
Or Dutch.
Oh, well, I chose both, and, uh...
that was my mistake.
But-- but this just
isn't you, Paddy.
This vendetta against my friends,
my colleagues.
Where in heaven's name
did the notion come from?
If this is some kind of a response
to my offer to her, it's childish.
Dad, I am the attorney general
of the state of New York.
I go after the bad guys.
It's what I do.
It's incomprehensible to me that
you could attack me like this,
and on your sister's wedding day.
You have become a complete
stranger to me, Patrick.
The fact that you see this as
an attack in the first place
- is the real problem.
- Son, I think
it would be in the best interests
of everybody if you were to...
move out of the Imperial
for the time being.
Maybe you should go upstairs
and take a look, dad.
- I already have.
- Oh, Paddy, I...
You're doing the right thing...
for you and for your city.
I know.
Come.
You look like you could use a drink.
It's 9:30 in the morning.
Is this about Patrick's
press conference?
No. On the contrary.
Today... everything
is about my Karen.
This is a little tradition, a...
ritual I enact for her weddings.
I got it from her first father-in-law--
Vicente de la Huerta.
You open the bottle of tequila
first thing in the morning,
and by the time you go to bed,
it's gotta be bone dry.
All right.
Wow, that's amazing.
Certainly has its virtues,
doesn't it?
Uh, Tripp, I...
You know,
those silly magazines whip themselves
into a frenzy for pictures
every time Karen gets hitched.
I remember last time.
It was a story unto itself-- the bidding war.
I want you to meet with
these people today,
- come to an understanding.
- I can do that.
Oh, and, uh,
in the interests of the new dispensation,
we could give the money to charity.
Done.
All right.
- To Karen.
I don't know how this
could've happened.
My assistants usually pay such
assiduous attention to every detail.
Well, here's some details for you.
This wedding is in six hours,
and I have to write a sermon for my
sister and her fourth ex-husband,
so fix the cuffs quickly so they
fit my son and not an orangutan...
Oh, my god. Excuse me.
Hi, Brian.
Andrea, where the
hell have you been?
Brazil. I finally went
and saw Iguazú falls.
And it was a
life-changing experience.
Well, it certainly played
hell with your fashion sense.
- I didn't come here to fight.
- Well, then why did you come?
Because the last time I checked,
you dumped our son in my lap
like a half-eaten
sandwich and disappeared.
- I want to talk to him.
- No, not today.
Look, Karen's getting married.
There's a lot going on--
I'm still his mother, Brian.
Just meet me in the
rectory in an hour.
Mei Ling Hwa and the
twins are out of town.
- We have a situation on our hands.
- What's going on?
Karen is having second thoughts, and
I'm quite certain that
they revolve around you.
Me? I--
look, I haven't done anything.
Which allows her to live
in this fantasy world
that someday you two
may end up together.
You know this. You must.
All I'm asking is for you to talk to her.
Let her know once and for all
that there is no possible
future for her with you, none.
- Unless there is.
- I'll talk to her.
Good. Then it's quite simple.
Tell her you're not in love with her
and that you never, ever will be.
Private number? That's so 2006.
- Hello.
- Juliet.
- Hey, don't hang up, okay?
- Who is this?
- Natalie. Natalie Kimpton.
- What do you want?
Listen, just turn the radio station
on to our station, okay? Please.
Never!
Our guest in the studio
today is Natalie Kimpton.
Why don't you tell us
about your new single?
I heard it's quite the, uh, vision quest.
That's what I've been told anyway.
A new single?
You must be kidding me.
Well, Jonesy,
it's called "free to forgive." And...
it was inspired by the most
devastating experience of my life--
my breakup with Juliet Darling.
Do you hear what's
happening on the radio?
I sent "free to forgive" to her
to get her to make up with you!
- Jeremy, I can't hear the song.
- Why do you want to?
That she-devil is evil, Jules.
She is a thief, just like you said.
She pretended to be pregnant to
try and marry me and get my money.
If she's trying to win you back,
it's 'cause she wants something.
Maybe once or twice but
staying mad at me is expensive
and it's free to forgive.
Oh.
And it's free to forgive.
I'm just worried that mom and I are
gonna miss Karen tossing her bouquet.
I already told all my
friends I'd catch it.
It'll be worth, like,
$10 million someday.
Kiki, you're gonna get there as soon
as your mom is done at the gallery.
- That's the best I can do for you.
- Dad.
- No, no cater waiters.
- I've known Stella since college.
If anything smacks of elitism,
it'll freak her out.
I want canned beer and potato chips.
Okay, thanks. Bye. Hi.
Hi.
Uh, you can't wear a
tux to Stella's opening.
I know, but I have to, because I have
to be over at the Imperial right now.
Nick, you promised you would go
with us to the gallery first.
Look, I have to talk to the press,
I have to pick which
magazine gets the photos,
I have to make sure that the
bride actually gets married.
That's a joke, right?
No. Letitia asked me to make sure
that Karen gets down the aisle.
Apparently she's having doubts,
cold feet.
Kiki, will you hang this up
for me in the closet, please?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
She's got cold feet
because of you, right?
According to Letitia, yes,
but she's getting married.
Just not to the man
she really wants.
Lisa, the only reason that I am
not making it to the opening
is so I can go tell
Karen to marry Freddy.
You're gonna see for
yourself in four hours.
You know what?
I really don't need to go to this wedding.
It's not like Karen
and I are close...
and I'm sure there'll
be another one, so--
- All right, fine. Don't come.
- Okay, great.
Wait a minute.
If mom doesn't go, who's gonna take me?
Lisa, come on.
Okay. You can go with your father.
Oh, thank you, god.
You're an evil person.
You abandoned your son.
Oh, I didn't abandon him.
I left him with his father for two months.
Yeah, and because you did,
my marriage is probably over.
My wife and children have
been in China for two weeks,
and I don't know when or
if they're coming back.
Just as a little added bonus to
your little selfish walkabout.
Oh, look who's talking. You haven't
had a selfless moment in your life.
Listening to you sob for weeks about
the untimely death of your mangy cat
was pretty selfless, believe me.
Why'd you even come back here?
To see my son...
and you...
maybe...
a little.
Oh, crap.
Shouldn't you be getting dressed?
The wedding's in
less than two hours.
I'll be ready in time. Don't worry.
Are, uh, you okay?
Look, I know living in this
hotel isn't ideal, but when
the new place is ready,
we'll move in, we'll have a new home.
I'm fine. I like it here.
It feels as much like
home as anyplace.
Okay. Well, I've, uh,
I've gotta run out for a sec.
Don't get lipstick on your collar.
Excuse me?
Or doesn't she wear lipstick?
Am I supposed to be following this?
Because it's all...
going way over my head.
So you're not seeing someone else--
a woman, a man, in between?
I don't know what you're-- I--
no, Ellen, I'm not seeing anyone but you.
Just go.
No, what are you talking about?
What are--
Just go.
Hey, Karen.
- Everyone's looking for you.
- It looks like you found me.
That's Nick--
1, everyone else... zero.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
- I don't think I'm gonna do this.
- That's technically not a question.
I know. I answered it myself.
- You did?
- Mm-hmm.
You don't think me marrying Freddy is...
is a huge mistake?
Like... the hugest?
Look, Karen, if you're hoping
I'm gonna sweep you off your feet
and tell you not to marry Freddy,
I can't.
Nick, this isn't about you.
My entire life doesn't revolve around
a stupid crush I had when I was 18.
This is about Freddy and if
he's the right one for me.
Okay.
Just wanted to get your opinion,
that's all.
Okay.
Hey. Have you presold
my wedding photos yet?
Uh, not yet.
Well, don't settle for
less than $2 million.
That would suck.
- Paddy, my boy.
- "Paddy, my boy"?
I believe that is an
appropriate greeting.
- What the hell were you thinking?
- Lower your voice. I'm not deaf.
- You told Ellen about Carmelita?
- I did nothing of the sort.
And I am offended that you would even
think that I would do such a thing.
Maybe that's because you
hired a private investigator
to follow me around and
take photographs of us.
I was trying to save your marriage.
- Is that right?
- I love you, son.
Whatever nonsense has come
between us doesn't change that.
Now come on. Have a drink.
Your sister's getting married.
It's a great day.
- Dad, this place is a palace.
- Yeah, it's a little like one.
Come on in.
Excuse me. Hello there, young lady.
- Hi.
- Kiki, right?
- Yeah. This is kiki.
- I'm Mrs. Darling.
- And I am Tripp Darling.
- Your house is so beautiful.
Thank you.
Well, maybe you'll bless us by
having your wedding here someday.
- I really could?
- Oh, yes. Of course you can.
Your dad is family.
Thank you for taking care of things today,
Nick. I appreciate it.
It was no problem.
It was... it was fine.
- Uh, are the photographers here yet?
- I asked them to get here early.
The vultures of the tabloids are
in my office even as we speak.
- $50,000.
- Uh, who are you again?
- "Style and grace."
- Well, "Style and grace,"
I'd like to remind you that the
bidding starts at $1 million.
Guys, I want to remind you,
this is Karen Darling.
- On her fourth wedding.
- To a second-rate golfer.
The public's hungry for access,
but they're not starving.
Well, this could be her last wedding,
and the bidding starts at $1 million.
- I think I've been clear.
- Then I think I'll skedaddle.
- Good luck, guys.
- See you.
$500,000.
$400,000?
- Okay, I'll give you $250,000.
- Sold.
But I'm gonna need a little,
uh, s-k-i-n.
I'm 10. I can spell.
I'll go $350,000 if I can
tag along for the honeymoon
- and get some opplesstay actionay.
- I speak pig latin, too, ummyday.
- Dad, look, the wedding's starting.
- We're gonna make it.
Okay, guys, listen,
no skin and no honeymoon.
- Then nothing over $200,000.
- Okay, you can have some honeymoon.
- I'll go $300,000.
- Sold.
- Here we are again.
- Here we are.
You know,
there's a word for how I feel right now.
Aware.
Aware. Whoa.
It's a japanese word.
It means reverence...
for the transient beauty
and mortality of all things.
Daddy...
- you're so wasted.
- I know I am.
I know.
You realize...
that on this day in a father's life...
grief and joy... are intertwined.
Oh, and remember, be kind...
be fair...
and, uh...
- be true.
- Be true.
- And, oh...
- Daddy... it's okay.
You don't have to finish it.
I know the whole thing.
But you know something? I really believe
that this me, it's going to last...
for quite some time.
- Be patient.
Thank you, daddy.
- May I have this walk?
- You may.
Everybody, please sit down.
And so, Karen, Freddy,
I send you off into
the mystery of marriage
with three words that
start with the letter "C."
First, confirmation--
married people provide
confirmation for each other.
When one person sees a
shooting star or an aurora,
then they have someone
to turn to all the time
to whom to which to say, "did you see that?
Did that really happen?"
And in a life that's full of amazing moments,
it's important to have...
confirmation.
The second is consolation--
married people provide
consolation for each other.
When bad luck,
death or even the simple sadness
of the passing of beauty
becomes hard to make it go on,
then you have someone to turn to for a hand,
for an embrace,
for a kiss, for consolation.
And last but not least...
there's joy.
It's not a "c" word, but then...
life and love are surprising.
You may kiss the bride.
Oh, my god.
I feel like a prisoner in here.
Karen, before we go into all that madness,
I need to tell you something.
What are you doing?
When I first proposed to you,
I didn't love you.
- Oh, that's okay.
- No, listen.
I saw this world,
and I wanted to be a part of it.
Freddy, honey, it's okay. I get it.
But during the ceremony,
and hearing those vows,
I realized that I have
fallen in love with you.
And none of the superficial stuff--
the money, whatever--
matters to me anymore.
- I want to propose.
- You already did.
- I want to do it again.
- Oh.
Karen Darling Mason...
I want to spend the rest
of my life with you.
Oh, god.
I want to spend the rest of my life with you,
too, baby... forever.
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I present to you
- Mr. and Mrs. Freddy Mason.
- All right, Freddy!
I want a divorce. Now.
Tell me this is some kind of joke.
I told you I was having second thoughts.
I told you both.
Karen Darling,
you are not going out there
and announcing your divorce
during your wedding.
Of course not.
I would never ruin a party.
Karen, you've been married for less
than an hour. Is it possible--
I can tell when these things won't work out,
Nick. I'm a pro.
You're an embarrassment
is what you are.
You thinks this makes me happy?
Because the last time I checked,
being a 4-time divorcée wasn't
exactly a big selling point.
Then why did you go through
with it in the first place?
- Because you told me to!
- Karen, listen to me.
While Freddy may not be the perfect man,
he is as capable
and deserving a fourth husband
as you're likely to find.
Tables seven and eight
are filled with lawyers.
Am I gonna have to go out
there and hire one of them,
or are you gonna take
care of this for me?
- I will talk to Freddy.
- Thank you.
Now I can go outside and have
my father-daughter dance.
- Karen.
- Yeah, what? I need a drink.
Let's all just agree that your father
doesn't need to know about this right now.
- Let him have his night.
- He's so happy.
I know, and I wish I had it in
me to stay married just for him.
But I don't.
Well, I hope you're happy.
Well, your honor, the seven deadly
sins are not like the constitution.
They can't be amended.
So if I were you, yes, I'd be worried.
May I?
Brian...
what a wonderful wedding sermon--
so much... humanity, so much hope.
There really is such a kind person
buried deep down inside you,
deep... deep down...
inside you...
somewhere.
Thanks, dad.
So how is it being a Darling?
I'm pretty new at it, but I guess it's okay.
The food's good.
Well, when I grow up,
I'm going to live just like this,
no matter what it takes.
No matter what.
This is nice, right?
- We don't dance enough.
- Would dancing satisfy you?
Would dancing give you
whatever it is that you--
- Ellen, I don't want to--
- Smile.
There's a nice fake picture.
Hope everybody in the fake
world likes fake looking at it.
You know what?
I am not going to do this. I can't.
I'm gonna get a drink.
It's an annulment.
Freddy, per Karen's request,
I've prepared all the
necessary legal documents.
There's a judge at table number seven,
he's ready to sign.
- But I still get the check, right?
- Of course, baby, I made a vow.
You will still receive the
full divorce settlement
as specified in the prenup--
$3 million.
All you have to do
is sign right there.
Done.
You must be ecstatic.
- Freddy... I never meant--
- Karen, please...
Don't feel sorry for me.
Okay? I feel sorry for you.
Because you are a screwed up little
girl who has a thing for her lawyer.
And no matter how hard
you try and fight it,
you are gonna die alone and unhappy.
That's what you deserve.
- Hey, listen, Karen, he's just--
- Nick, don't, okay?
- Just don't. Don't.
- I'm sorry, Karen.
So what's the matter?
I came here to discuss with you
a highly sensitive matter, but
I realize perhaps now
is not the best time.
I had a cup of Chai tea.
I'm gonna be up all night. Talk to me.
I have this acquaintance for
whom I care a great deal.
- A mistress?
-  She, uh...
used to be a mister.
It's none of my business
how you like your eggs.
Well, I appreciate that, but, uh,
you see, Ellen-- she keeps asking
all sorts of questions, and, uh,
she knows something, and I just can't--
I just can't keep lying.
Then stop lying. In fact,
I think it's time
for Patrick Darling
to stop apologizing
for being himself.
Come on, it's the 21st century.
People's hearts and minds are open.
They're tired of the
politics of deception.
They're starved for truth,
and I'll bet Ellen is the same.
But if I tell Ellen the truth she,
you know,
she might leave me,
and that could ruin my campaign.
I don't know. I think Ellen's
smarter than you give her credit for.
So you think I should just tell her
the truth, just confess everything?
It's not a confession.
It's a conversation.
And it's the right thing
to do for your marriage,
for your country...
and for your soul.
Okay.
Okay, great. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- All right.
I'm proud of you, Pat.
I appreciate your discretion.
It's all good.
- Good night.
You're sure Ellen Darling has
no idea this came from us?
Yes, sir. Absolutely sure.
Good...
Good... good.
- Quite a roller coaster today.
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, don't worry about me.
I managed to sell those
pictures for $1.3 million.
- That's nothing to sneeze at.
- Yeah, that's nice.
I still matter.
So you want to tell me
what really happened?
He told me he loved me.
Right after the ceremony,
he just spit it out.
- And that wasn't good?
- I don't know.
When I thought Freddy was in
it only for the money, it...
it somehow made it okay. You know?
Like it was easier to deal with.
I knew he'd always be there because
the money would always be there.
- And then it got real.
- Yeah.
More real, anyway.
But then after he said those horrible
things to me at the divorce, it--
it just proved that...
- I did the right thing.
- He was wrong. He was hurt.
He was right about one thing.
I am in love with you.
Karen--
You know we belong together.
We've both known it since we were kids.
We fit.
I gotta go.
O doomed from here to eternity lord
have mercy on such as we bah, bah, bah
Bone dry.
That was a beautiful wedding day.
Oh, Karen finally got it right.
I'll sleep well tonight,
knowing that she has found a man's
heart in which to make her home.
Daddy, can I talk to you?
Oh, I think we might
have set a record here.
How was the opening?
- Amazing.
- Good.
- A-mazing.
- Excellent.
Stella's paintings
sold out in one hour.
She is now passed out
drunk on my office couch
with some cuban short stop who's
just defected to the Yankees.
- Well, congratulations.
- Thank you.
- So how was the wedding?
- It was all right.
Karen's wedding photos sold for 300 grand,
so the Darling family foundation
only had to kick in a cool
mil to protect her feelings.
- That's kinda sad.
- Yeah.
So she actually went
through with it.
And then 45 minutes later,
she got through with it.
What?
Karen had the marriage annulled.
I wonder why.
Well, it had nothing to do with me
if that's what you're implying.
- Of course it didn't, Nick.
- Hey, Lisa, would you wait?
- I'm tired.
- I know, I know, and I'm tired, too,
but I just--
I want all of this to stop.
I love you,
and that is never gonna change.
I don't know how many times I
have to say this-- I'm yours.
- One more time.
- I'm yours.
Come here.
I'm going shopping on Madison.
It's Carmelita.
Excuse me?
Her name is, uh, Carmelita.
Do you love her?
I love, uh...
I love you both.
I can't give her up.
I've tried. I don't know how.
Well, then...
we don't have a choice, do we?
The three of us are gonna sit down
together and set some ground rules.
The three of us? You, me and...
you, me and who?
Carmelita.
She won't destroy this marriage.
And she will not keep us out of Washington,
either one of us.
I didn't marry a
Darling for nothing.
Bingles! Bingles, wait for me!
Bingles!
Oh, thank you so much for coming.
Oh, look what I got. Here.
- Thank you.
- Ta-da!
- Cheers.
Hey, will you tell Germs
that we're friends again?
I think we should
tell the whole world!
He's in here.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Where's Brian Jr.?
He's at a fencing lesson,
but he'll be back.
He's getting really good at it.
You know, I think if he has a few more--
I'm taking him back to Brazil.
What?
Yeah, I realized this morning
when I woke up in Queens...
I went to Brazil to find myself,
but I think I found a home, too.
- In the jungle?
- No, in Sao Paulo.
And what about Brian Jr.? What about
Maple Grove? He's gonna start in the fall.
You can't just come in here and uproot him.
He has a life here now.
I'm sure we can find him a
fencing coach down there.
And you'll pay for it if you
want him to live in the manner
to which he's become so quickly
and completely accustomed.
Did you really think I'd
let you keep him forever?
- Mommy!
- Hi!
- Oh, I missed you.
- I missed you, too.
- Patrick.
- Hello, dad.
Where's Ellen?
Are things okay with the two of you?
Fences mended?
We're on the way.
- So this is where you're living?
- For the time being.
Let me reiterate--
I had nothing to do with Ellen finding out,
- absolutely nothing at all.
- That why you came here, dad, to,
convince me of your innocence?
I came to tell you I loved you
and that you're ways
welcome under my roof,
regardless of whatever business
disagreements we might have.
I feel bad I let it go this far.
But the point is,
if you get tired of hotel living,
the fourth floor of the
Imperial is always waiting.
I appreciate that, dad. Thank you.
But, uh,
we found a place over on the park.
- Where, exactly?
- The Octavius.
Simon Elder owns that building.
I know, dad. He suggested it.
We move in in two weeks.
- Do I really have to go to Brazil?
- You're not going to Brazil yet.
You're just going to
Queens with your mom.
- Do they have lemon curd in Queens?
- I'll send a jar home with you.
And there'll always be plenty
here when you come visit.
Are you sure she'll let me visit?
I'm gonna do everything in my
power to make sure that she does.
Let's go, sweetie.
Don't pack just yet.
Bye, daddy.
Bye, little man.
What in God's name is this?
Just some sock Freddy wanted to sell
to kids as part of a golf video.
Oh. Maybe he wasn't a keeper.
Last night I told Nick that
he and I belong together.
- And then I kissed him.
- Oh, Karen.
I know, I know.
But I just got so caught up in the moment.
You know the wedding made
me feel so romantic.
Yeah, well,
why do you do this to yourself?
Because I want to marry Nick.
Don't I have to try?
I can't go the rest of my life
wondering what might have happened.
- Can I?
- Oh, no. N-no.
- No, you can't. I just...
- Mom, that's a candle. You can't...
Here you go.
- I'll just ask you for one thing.
- What's that?
Let me help you.
He has stolen my son.
Patrick is a person, Tripp,
making his own choices.
This isn't about theft.
There are so many spurious
assumptions behind that statement.
Tripp, do you know that
Patrick is working with Simon?
He's living in Simon
Elder's building.
Ostensibly, to all intents and purposes,
Simon Elder is serving Patrick
in some sort of all-encompassing
advisory capacity, and I am certain that
it is Simon Elder who was behind
Paddy's push to indict my friends.
I'm not a vengeful person, Nick.
I have endured massive betrayal.
And I have responded
with patience...
and with love.
But I will not suffer this man.
What do you want to do?
I want to destroy him.
I want that son of a bitch...
completely and utterly destroyed.
Traduction: Salomon, the-teacher
Isilring, Elorri - Transcript: Raceman
Synchro: Travis - www.forom.com