How long
do we have to wait?
Until we catch
our bad guy.
Can I sleep?
You can't sleep
on a stakeout, Shawn.
You can eat. You can chew gum.
But you can't drink
because if you drink,
you're gonna have to pee.
And the target
always comes out
right when you got to pee.
Now I think I gotta pee.
Well, then, Shawn,
your bladder is going to get
some training tonight, too.
(LAUGHING)
We've got action.
Now, I want you to stay down.
I know, I know, I know.
(SHUSHING) Go! Go!
Come on.
I got you.
I got you red-handed,
you lying son of a bitch.
"I don't know what happening
to your newspaper, Henry."
You're transparent, Clark.
You didn't think
I could nab a liar like you?
CLARK: I can explain!
Tell it to
the Neighborhood
Watch Association.
Give the paper
to the boy, Clark.
What the hell are you doing?
Checking baseball scores.
My fantasy team is killing me.
This is the Chief's office!
I know, she runs the league.
I'm kidding.
She's in a meeting.
She won't mind.
Plus, we look really important
hanging out in here.
Gus, have you
tried this chair?
It's a pregnancy chair.
We have gotta get one
for the office immediately.
My birthing canal
has never felt so in line.
We need to
get out of here.
She told me to wait.
For what?
Gus, I'm not a mind reader.
No, that's just
what you tell everybody.
I want you to try this chair.
I'm not
trying that chair, Shawn.
I'll sit on
the birthing ball.
I kid you not,
that thing is like
a refreshing waterfall
cascading down your vertebrae.
It might help
with your stomach issues.
Who told you
I had stomach issues?
My nose?
The vent in the bathroom?
Air fresheners
all over the place?
I'm trying a new medication
for my lactose intolerance.
I believe
the problem is physical.
And I think it
can be cured by what
I'm now referring to as
the magic springy
bounce-up chair.
Hey, Shawn,
smoothies are here.
Pineapple?
Of course.
Thanks, Buzz.
(SLURPING)
You're having food delivered?
They were already
going out.
Oh, boy. I'm telling you...
Wow.
What did I tell you?
Now, take a hit off this
bad boy and complete
the moment, you've earned it.
What do you think
this is, Mr. Guster?
I apologize.
This will never happen again.
Give me that.
Boys, out!
What is this, Gus,
a smoothie? You know
these things stain.
Mmm. But they
are very delicious.
Chief, would you like some?
That's not my smoothie.
I don't care
whose smoothie it is.
I don't even remember
why I asked you to stay now.
You want us on that case
with the blonde woman.
No.
Mmm-hmm, Wintersby,
Wilacheck, Wislerbottom?
No, no, it's...
Wilcroft?
No, that's not...
Okay, wait a minute,
were you listening in
on my conversation?
I don't know
if I heard it psychically
or if I saw you
walk by with her
and Detective Lassiter,
but I definitely heard
the word "psychic."
The woman, Raylene, said she
visits an occasional psychic.
She wasn't asking for one.
Well, not in so many words.
No, not in any words.
This is a bank robbery case.
We don't need psychics
for a bank robbery case.
Bank robbery?
Mmm-hmm.
I didn't read anything
in the paper about
a bank robbery.
It was four years ago.
So, it went unsolved?
It was solved.
Well, then what does she need
a psychic for?
Gus, that is a perfectly
reasonable question.
Thank you, Chief.
We'll be leaving now.
(STAMMERING)
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm still confused.
Her husband's partners are
getting out of jail.
This is a routine warning
that we issue when someone
may potentially be in danger.
This is the part
where we offer up
our services.
No, I think
this is the part
where we leave.
That's a good idea.
SHAWN: But...
Believe it or not,
Mr. Spencer,
crimes were solved
long before you got here.
And they continue to be solved
when you're not around.
Oh, I remember
what I wanted to tell you.
What?
Stay out of my chair.
Bank robbers?
Dude, that's awesome.
We should go find Lassiter
and our future client.
We gotta go.
Dude, this woman is
on an eternal quest for
a good psychic? That's me!
I'm gonna go find them.
I'm staying right here.
Great idea. Wait ten seconds,
and make an entrance.
Drink some.
Are you saying
that I'm in danger?
Your husband's partners
are being paroled today.
I have reason to believe
their first order of business
is gonna be to try
and find that lost money.
But the only person who knew
where that money ended up
was my husband.
I know that.
But do they?
Hey, Lassi.
Juliet.
Oh, I don't believe we've met.
Or did we meet?
In a bank?
No, that's not it.
Why am I getting "bank"?
Piggy bank?
Sperm bank?
Doesn't matter.
I'm Shawn Spencer.
I am the official
head psychic
here at the department.
CARLTON: You don't
have a title.
And there is serious
doubt as to whether
you're really even psychic.
I solved the McCallum
disappearance.
And the Summerland murder.
Oh, and I found your keys.
And your badge.
Out.
Shawn, where are my keys?
CARLTON: No. Out!
If you don't mind,
we're a little busy.
We have a...
Excuse us, Raylene.
Do we know each other?
No, we don't. I'm sorry.
Psychic, remember?
Sometimes I can't
turn it off.
Do you do readings?
Yes, we do it all.
Full service.
I'm a bit of an enthusiast.
I used to have
a regular girl read for me.
Really?
Here's a card.
We're at the
beachfront location.
I could put my cell number
on the back if you
have any questions.
Any time, really.
Thank you,
you're so kind.
This is a
pharmaceutical company.
Like I said,
we do it all.
Well, I always say,
"A man with many hats..."
"Doesn't like his haircut"?
Exactly. I thought
I was the only one
who read that book.
It's my favorite.
Mine, too.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Really?
And scene!
I know, you know
That I'm not telling the truth
They just don't have any proof
Embrace the deception
Learn how to bend
Your worst inhibitions
tend to psych you out
in the end
(PRINTER PRINTING)
Dude, what took you so long?
This is good stuff.
You gotta see
what happened to this car.
I mean, it was really...
What?
What happened here?
Oh, that?
Oh, I had a drywaller
come in and take out a wall.
A wall?
This is a rental!
What do you think
our landlord is gonna say?
Gee, I don't know,
"Thank you"?
Gus, this place
was way too cramped.
My name is on that lease.
Don't worry, I'll make sure
you get a thank you note, too.
You're taking my name
off the lease. And the door,
and these Frisbees.
Gus, don't be ridiculous.
Look, I'm almost positive
this isn't
a load-bearing wall.
But if you're really
concerned, why don't you go
jump up and down in the attic
and make sure?
What is she doing here?
Ah, she's our
first real client.
Actually client?
Hired for the job?
Actual client.
SHAWN: Go on, man.
I have to admit,
when I met you at the police
station, I was intrigued,
so I checked
your recent track record.
It's amazing, really.
Well, it's a team effort.
Not really.
I do most of the work.
What can we
help you with, ma'am?
I need you to get
in contact with someone.
Well, tracking people down
is our specialty.
What? Oh, it's not, now?
This one might
be a little tricky.
How tricky?
Is the person out
of the state? Country?
He's dead.
Ah, and I assume that's
why you need a psychic.
Hold on. Dead?
Like dead, dead?
Currently being
eaten by worms?
He's actually entombed
in a mausoleum.
Gus, he's ascended
to the next dimension.
It's fine.
No, Shawn, I think we might be
at a bit of an impasse.
What exactly do you
need to know?
My husband was not
a perfect man.
He got himself
in a bit of trouble.
Okay, I'll be honest,
it was a lot of trouble.
He got involved
in a bank robbery.
He was one of three,
but the only one
who didn't go to prison.
Unfortunately, the reason
he didn't get caught
was that he drove his car
down an embankment...
Wait.
I see rain.
No roads, no.
There was a fiery crash,
wasn't there?
Yes.
What would you
like me to ask, Raylene?
Well, this is hard to say.
But he was the one
designated to bury the money.
They were to all meet later
and divide the cash.
Only his partners
were caught first.
So why wait until now?
His partners think that
I know where he hid the money.
If I don't
give it to them,
they're gonna kill me.
Shawn, can I
speak to you outside, please?
I guess.
Dude, what is wrong with you?
Shawn, I don't know
how to break this to you,
but you are not psychic.
Clue me in
on the problem here.
It's a big problem when
the job requires extensive
conversing with the dead.
Gus, what is the question
that she wants answered?
Where is the money, right?
That doesn't require
any actual dead guy chitchat.
We simply trace
his last steps,
do a little research,
ask a few questions,
and bingo!
Stop saying "bingo."
You know how I hate that.
Okay, fine. Yahtzee.
We're not doing it, Shawn.
Mahjong. Gus!
GUS: Mrs. Wilcroft.
Raylene.
Your problem is
outside of our reach.
You are in real danger.
I'd like to recommend
police protection.
I'm pleased
to be of service.
Thank you.
CARLTON:
I know they're in there.
Just so you know,
I am uncomfortable
with inter-office romance.
I wasn't considering it.
And I'm completely
uncomfortable with
the implication.
So, it wasn't true,
the rumor about you
and your last partner?
I'm not going to dignify
that with a response.
This is them.
JULIET: The bank robbers?
Yeah, a little
worse for the wear
than the day I arrested them.
You caught them?
I was part of a team,
but, yeah, it was mostly me.
That's a big deal.
Would've been a big deal
if I had found the money
and closed the case.
Things like that
make a career.
Instead, I got a bunch
of loose ends, a dead guy,
and 3.6 million in cash
that vanished into thin air.
It's funny,
they don't look so mean.
What do you mean "mean"?
They look like repairmen.
Big repairmen,
but they don't
look like killers.
Duck!
Eyes of a serpent,
ears of a bat.
Send us a signal from...
Shawn.
I hear a voice.
Can I see you outside, please?
It wants me to come outside.
Now?
I should go.
Is that my bathrobe?
What are you doing?
What does it look
like I'm doing?
I'm having a séance.
You can't have a séance!
Gus, there are no rules
against having a séance.
Anyone can have one.
It's like a garage sale.
Or plastic surgery.
Okay, first of all,
technically,
you need to have a permit
to have a garage sale.
Secondly, you cannot
speak to the dead.
Oh, Gus, you don't
understand at all, do you?
I don't need to make contact
with the dead.
No, I need to speak
with all the people
in that room.
They're witnesses.
We can piece together
the rest based on
the information they give us.
I'm already on to something.
Check this out.
The dead guy was on the lam
for three days with the cash.
He had help.
From whom?
I'm almost there.
(CHANTING)
Raylene?
Yes, Shawn?
I'm sensing the
last time he called
before the accident.
Ellen was the only
one who talked to him.
Ellen. Yes,
I feel that deeply.
You didn't tell
the police that, did you?
No, I was afraid.
He's my brother.
I didn't want to turn him in.
No, of course not.
Where did he call from?
A pay phone outside a store.
Yes, it was a store,
I feel it. Which store?
I think it was a...
Thriftymart.
Up north. He'd been driving.
(STAMMERING)
I've always imagined
it was the one near Pismo.
Pismo! Yes, but
the spirits are confused,
they need more
specific directions.
Nearest cross street?
Just past the park
we used to hike with Roger.
Who's Roger?
He's our cousin.
Really?
But wait, there's more.
The spirits are asking me.
What is Roger's address?
I really haven't
seen Roger in years.
Come on, Ellen!
Work with me! Think harder.
Okay, sorry.
How about a phone number?
Okay.
Gus, what have you done?
You've broken the chain
of spiritual trust.
I didn't break anything.
Don't ruin it
for everyone, Gus.
I'm not ruining anything.
Listen, Raylene,
I have to apologize to you.
You seem like
a very decent person.
But what you need
is protection, not this.
A bodyguard, a policeman.
I can assure you,
there is no spirit in here.
What?
And let me make
you a guarantee,
there is absolutely no way
there will be
any sort of contact
with zombies...
(SCREAMING)
(CAR TIRES SCREECHING)
You okay?
I think that's all
for tonight, ladies.
Did you do that?
Why would I ruin
our totally cool window?
For effect,
to make me think
you contacted an evil ghost.
Gus, please.
Why didn't you
float that idea by me sooner?
That's genius.
Somebody obviously
wants us off this case.
I think
it's those convicts.
But whoever it is,
we'll never find them.
I just saw them run off.
You sure about that?
Yeah.
Ladies, stay here.
We're going after them.
Or it.
Let's get some tacos.
Okay.
And then the window
just shattered.
And you think ghosts did it?
No. No. No.
Though there may have been
some women present who thought
ghosts were responsible.
I blame it on the two convicts
from the Holmby Bank robbery.
I'm sorry, I still don't
understand why that means
you need to see
the entire case file.
Oh, no, no, Juliet, we don't
need to see the whole thing.
No.
No, just the cover page,
one or two others,
here, there.
Definitely the witness list.
Well, you gotta see that.
And the Chief's
okay with this?
Oh, yeah.
I don't think so.
No?
No.
I liked the other girl better.
Not me.
Hey, since we're here,
we should do some digging.
Good idea, why don't you
dig me getting the hell out
of here
and going to get some sleep?
Hey, I set you up for that.
Lobbed it right
over the plate.
(COUGHING)
Mr. Spencer!
Oh!
Hey, you, what a surprise.
You look different.
Yes, I took your advice.
Three weeks
without a cigarette.
Well, it has certainly
enhanced your aura.
And remember,
it wasn't my advice,
it was your grandma's spirit.
Have you spoken to her again?
She's here.
Now?
Yes.
Where? In this hallway?
No.
In the records room.
I thought I felt
something eerie in there.
Me, too.
Unfortunately, I'm not
allowed down there.
Please.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Not too much light.
You don't want to
scare her away.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Yes, I can feel her,
all right.
She's...
She's over by the W's.
Why?
No. W.
(GASPS) This is it!
I'm nervous.
Don't be.
I want you to relax. Breathe.
Close your eyes.
Why would she be in the W's?
I don't know.
Did you know any W's?
That bastard Walter.
Walter.
Your ex?
Wow! Yes.
I hear something.
Yes, me, too.
Paper.
No, it's not paper.
Yes, it's clearly paper.
You have to concentrate.
Breathe deeply.
No, uh-uh.
I'm definitely not
feeling anything anymore.
I think we've lost her.
I'm so sorry
I couldn't reach her.
It's okay.
I know how temperamental
the spirit world can...
Your hand!
Oh!
It was the spirits!
Yes.
It's a message from beyond.
What does it say?
I think I should
keep it to myself.
It's a private message.
Dude, you look so peaceful
when you're sleeping.
Never come
in my apartment again.
You hear me?
I've seen
the Holmby Bank file.
Look, Shawn,
I don't want to...
The cousin is the key.
Which cousin? The one
the sister mentioned?
And then immediately
regretted. You could see it.
She let it slip.
Dude, the guy runs a cemetery.
Which one?
Oh, I don't know, the one
David Wilcroft is buried in?
I'll bet you dollars
to donuts he knows exactly
where the money is.
Look, it's all right here
on my hand.
His name is Roger Blaine,
creepy as all get-out.
Lives on the grounds,
alone, no wife, no kids.
Not that part. That's
the Italian seamstress I met
at the Renaissance fair.
How much further
is this place?
I don't know,
50, 60 miles.
60 miles!
And you didn't get me a donut?
I did get you a donut.
Then I ate it.
I can't believe
I'm doing this.
Solving a crime?
That happens to be
our job description.
No, driving so far on a whim.
A whim, he says.
A guy dies and gets buried
by his own weirdo cousin
in a tiny cemetery way up
the coast in a town
with a population of 200.
That is not a whim,
that is a clue.
You think the
cousin has the money?
Roger Blaine? That even
sounds like an alias.
He could've killed Wilcroft.
Or it could have
been the sister.
Gus, they're all
kind of creepy.
The dead guy, the undertaker,
the sister, Raylene.
Oh, there's nothing
creepy about Raylene.
Nothing creepy about
the melodramatic widow?
No.
Are you serious?
Who marries a bank robber?
Who sees a psychic every week?
There's nothing
wrong with her, Shawn.
Okay.
What is this thing you have
with women in jeopardy?
They have a name for this,
you know. It's called
the Stockholm syndrome.
No, it's not.
Florence Nightingale's
disease?
Are you trying to be funny?
You can't ridicule me
because I want to help.
I can when you want
to help too much.
You have an unnatural affinity
for this woman that I simply
cannot wrap my brain around.
She dresses like she's
on her way to a PTA meeting.
Fine. She reminds me
of somebody who was
very important to me.
Who?
Don't worry about it.
Oh, no.
What?
Don't say it.
Don't say
Meredith Baxter Birney!
It's not MBB!
This is unhealthy.
Okay, you were in love
with her, too.
I loved her because
she was Mrs. Keaton,
and she gave birth to APK.
It's not her anyway.
Well, who is it?
My babysitter.
Your babysitter.
Yes, my babysitter.
Gus, Mrs. Pilderman
was in her late 60s.
Mrs. Pilderman was
37 years old
and she was a nurse, Shawn.
She taught me things, like,
you know, about books and art.
Things like that.
Things like skinny-dipping?
I did not go skinny-dipping
with Mrs. Pilderman!
Well, at least that sheds
some light on it.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Huh, nobody's home.
No, somebody's here.
You can see through doors now,
that's the new thing?
I can smell
the laundry vent.
No, you can't.
Okay.
(SNIFFING)
Oh, Gus, please
with the supersmeller.
You have to stop!
(BOTH SNIFFING)
Oh, dude, I can smell it, too.
I told you.
Jeans and socks and underwear
and a Bounce sheet.
Make jokes. How long
do you think it takes
to dry a load of clothes?
Thirty minutes?
Somebody's here
and not answering the door.
Gus, I apologize.
That's very
impressive detective work.
I feel a little bad
about the donut thing now.
You should.
Dang it!
Let's try the back.
(CROWING)
(WHISPERING) Just stay
and watch. Go on, G.
Whoa!
You're not Roger!
No, no, you're...
You're David Wilcroft.
Aren't you
supposed to be dead?
Gus?
Look. It's not that easy
to explain.
I'm not a real criminal.
I just... I got in
a little over my head.
You robbed a bank.
I didn't want to.
I was in a bad place.
They trusted me.
I was supposed
to stash the cash.
You lost the money.
Yeah. How'd you know?
It was raining.
Really hard,
for two whole days.
It was the worst rainstorm
in 30 years.
You couldn't find it.
Yeah. By the time
the roads reopened,
every marker I left was gone,
it was washed away.
I lost three and a half
million dollars.
Driving back,
I nearly drove off the road.
It was then I realized
I'd be better off dead.
And you have been
digging ever since.
Every chance I can
get out there without
the risk of being seen
by hikers or
mountain bikers, I dig.
You know what?
Raylene is in agony
over this.
I didn't mean her any harm.
You were never
gonna tell her?
I couldn't.
Excuse us a moment.
What?
Gus, what's happening with you
and this guy's wife?
Are you having
feelings for this woman?
That's ridiculous.
No, no, Gus.
Gus, this is wonderful.
Look, we didn't know he was
alive. When she came to us
she was technically available.
Shawn. Stop it.
I'm not hitting on
your wife.
No, he's not. But there's
some serious crushing
going on here.
Dude, I am not blind.
"A man with many hats
doesn't like his haircut"?
(STAMMERING)
What book is that from?
She's a charming woman.
A charming woman?
Oh, you're Jane Austen now?
She's an adult,
she is attractive,
she's mature.
Shawn...
David, help me out here,
tell him that this is healthy.
Raylene is a
very dynamic woman.
Everybody is drawn to her.
Look, guys,
I know you want to turn me in.
But you gotta understand
I'm close. I am so very close.
I've covered nearly every inch
inside the Kalish trail loop
where I buried it.
And you want us
to let you find it?
Get her to hide someplace,
someplace safe.
I just want to return
the money and
get on with my life.
Hmm?
We have to
think this through.
Yeah.
You know, in my mind,
they were the lucky ones,
they got to go to prison,
pay off their
debt to society.
I've been living
as a dead man.
If Raylene's going to
find out that I'm alive,
at the very least, don't
let it come from a stranger,
let it come from me.
GUS: We're letting him go?
He's not going anywhere
until he finds that money.
I doubt that'll be
anytime soon.
He did have
cool hair, though.
God, we're missing
something else here!
He's the key
to solving this puzzle.
We need to tell Raylene.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. We're
holding all the cards here,
Gus. Why would we do that?
Because she's in danger.
Maybe we can fix that.
GUS: Your husband, he's alive.
Gus! Remember the part where
we weren't going to tell her?
We never said that!
David's alive?
We found him.
He's with his cousin.
Roger? No, no, no.
That can't be.
I'm sure your head is spinning
and that you don't feel
completely safe right now.
But rest assured,
we do have a plan.
We are gonna put
the convicts back in jail.
Where they belong.
And are gonna
stay for a while.
CARLTON: We'll put these
guys behind bars,
where they belong.
So who authorized
this stakeout?
What?
You know, who set it up?
I did.
I mean, who sanctioned it?
Approved it? Above you.
Above me? You know,
I don't think I like
where this is going.
I just mean it should be
officially sanctioned
as per the police code.
Which one?
11A-17.
Ticky-tack. Doesn't apply.
In most cases someone
still has to authorize it.
Oh, that's right,
I remember now. I did!
Well, what about 42.211?
What about it?
Well, it states that...
It's superseded by 15.75.
Not necessarily.
If you're in
the jurisdiction
of a 23.40, it is.
Maybe.
Maybe?
Technically, a 23.40 only
applies in federal cases.
What are you doing in here?
I thought we could share info.
What are we looking at?
Get the hell out of my car!
Shouldn't you be wondering how
I slid in and lounged for two
minutes without you noticing?
You're new and pretty,
so it's okay.
You've got ten seconds
before I latch the doors
and haul you down
to the station.
They don't know
where the money is.
What?
Isn't that why you're
following them? So they'll
lead you to the money?
Psychic. It's amazing.
You'll get used to it.
Look, the dead guy buried
the money and then lost it,
but that's beside the point.
I think we can cut our losses,
put those two back behind
bars, if we work together.
And how do we do that?
Well, first, we dress
up as musketeers
and make a very special pact.
Come on, you've watched
them pull at least a handful
of probation violations.
You've been tailing them.
You saw what
they did to my office.
They haven't been anywhere
near your office.
They were near enough to bust
out my window two nights ago.
No, you're wrong.
You lost them, anyway.
We'll talk tomorrow.
Bye, Juliet.
They don't want our help?
Of course they don't.
But they also lost our guys.
Did you see where they went?
Did I see where they went?
You mean did I see their car
turn right on Riverside?
Or did I see the parking tag
from the 2400 Motel?
Touché!
Did you see what kind of
whiskey they bought?
Shawn, please.
Time is being wasted.
This is breaking
and entering.
No, no, no.
Only if we break something.
And then enter something.
Entering is just entering.
I'm not breaking
a law, Shawn.
Look, you wanna save
your little widow?
We've got to find
some evidence
to put these guys away.
I'm standing firm on this.
Fine, what about the window?
If it just opens,
does that count?
Depends.
Ooh. Hey, I see something.
Shawn?
I might be able to slide
this chain off.
Shawn?
Gus, I'm trying
to concentrate.
You might wanna
turn around.
What? Whoa!
You guys parked
round back, huh?
Okay, okay!
Was that really necessary?
Were we resisting?
Man, window inspector?
In a motel?
Okay, I lied. I did.
I'm sorry.
The truth is I'm a psychic.
That's what I do.
Perhaps you've read about me
in the paper recently.
I've been in jail four years.
You don't have papers?
I thought you guys had TV
and yard darts
and mahjong and...
(STAMMERING) Okay,
I come bearing a message
from a departed being.
David Wilcroft
wants you to know
that he lost the money.
It's gone forever.
Why you telling us this?
(STAMMERING) He is concerned
that you're going to harm
Rins... Racquel...
Raylene.
Oh, that's funny.
(ALL LAUGHING)
That is funny.
Jesse, can you make sure
that we are not disturbed?
You can...
Can you prove
you're a psychic?
Sure. Sure.
You are a bank robber.
Yes, you did not like prison.
You are wearing the same pants
that you were released in,
and you have packed
on a few pounds since being...
No, look, man, I'm talking
about real proof!
Like a test.
Now, look, if you're right,
you live. If you're wrong...
Man, you don't
wanna be wrong.
Here's the thing.
It's not really
a parlor trick.
No.
(STAMMERING) And I don't
want to cheapen it.
Look, prove it now. Let's go.
What's wrong with you,
man? Move!
Okay! Okay!
How many fingers?
Are you kidding?
Do I look like
I'm joking around?
How many fingers?
We gotta be able
to come up with
something better than that.
All right, man. Time's up.
Four.
All right, how many now?
Two. Now can we move on?
Because Gus and I
have some questions that we...
Three. For instance,
why was it so funny...
Three.
And is it possible...
Still three.
Now it's technically
two and a half fingers.
And the guy with the gun
is flipping me the bird.
You can see my fingers,
can't you?
No. No.
Yes, yes, yes, I can.
It's the reflection of the TV
bouncing off the mirror
to the water pitcher here.
All right. Okay, maybe not.
We're gonna try this
one more time.
Now, how many fingers?
Dude, you need
to stop picking three.
Respect, man.
Gee. Oh, man! That's...
Yep. They're back here.
I can't believe we lost them.
Don't think
that wasn't on purpose.
SHAWN: To Wilcroft.
A hell of a wheel man.
He was the wheel man?
Yeah. You should
know that, right?
Well, Shawn's visions
sometimes are scattered.
Incomplete.
How does a wheel man miss
a turn on a mountain road?
(LAUGHS) I tell you what,
he didn't miss that turn.
I bet he just
drove straight off.
You wanna know why?
Because he was trying
to get away from his wife.
Damn, you're good.
No, no. That can't be,
why would he be...
We called her the Viper.
Man, she was cold as hell.
We had to do
whatever she said, man.
We had no choice.
Who?
The wife.
Raylene?
You know her?
Well, she came to us,
she wanted to contact David.
Figures. That was
her only weakness.
The occult. Man,
she'd stop at nothing to get
her hands on that money.
No, she only wanted the money
to protect herself
from you two.
From us?
Yeah.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Man, the last thing
we would ever do is cross her.
All we wanted to do
was get away from her.
Especially David.
Man, she ran him around
like he was an animal.
He did whatever she said.
Look, man, I don't
know if you guys
got caught up
in the charm
or whatever,
but I'll tell you, man,
that was her key.
She could play anybody.
I'm telling you
she is a very dangerous lady.
Raylene was the mastermind?
(WHOOPS)
I already knew that.
Because I'm a psychic.
Come on, guys. We should go.
You don't want
to go out that way.
Why?
We got company outside.
SHAWN: Is there another
way out of here?
GUS:
I can't believe I just crawled
through a bathroom window.
It has to be a lie.
Gus, you're attracted
to dangerous women, man.
It happens.
Joan Jett, for example.
Penny Marshall.
Grace Jones.
Or the woman who played
Pinky Tuscadero.
She seemed so sincere.
So vulnerable, you know?
Yeah! Turns out she's
a domineering snake lady
who drove her
browbeaten husband
to fake his own death.
And we, we led her right
to the poor bastard.
Lizzie Borden,
Kathy Bates!
Raylene! This is not you...
Whoa! What, today's gun day?
Sit.
"Just rush in here."
Bad idea, Shawn.
Let her hang herself.
Quiet.
Raylene, I am sensing
that this is going
to end very, very badly.
Find me my money.
I know you have it.
He doesn't have it.
I'm the only one
who knows where the money is.
Whoa! He doesn't know
where the money is.
Of course I know
Shawn, I don't know
what your strategy is, but you
don't know where the money is.
You have five seconds.
One...
Really? The countdown?
Two...
Three!
Okay, it's in the crypt!
The money's in the crypt?
Well, David here
certainly isn't.
Think about it, Raylene.
Roger runs the place.
It's the perfect
hiding spot.
They can get in and out
whenever they want.
Pry it open.
With what?
With the stanchion.
Apparently those are
called stanchions, Gus,
were you aware of this?
Yes, I was.
How did you figure out
that money was in the crypt?
I'm bluffing.
This is not a good
time to bluff!
I think it's a great time!
She was going to kill us.
And besides, I've always
thought a crypt was a great
place to stash loot, you know?
It's kind of like a vault,
I mean, you can just get in
there whenever you need to.
She's gonna figure
out you're lying.
Eventually. But, come on,
it's gonna take a while
to bust open a crypt.
(CRASHING)
Wow. Not as long
as I was hoping for.
Help him get it out.
Raylene, please.
What are you waiting for?
(DOOR OPENS)
That.
Son of a...
David?
I don't believe this.
Well, what are you
going to do, Raylene?
Shoot all of us?
None of you are armed.
I can do whatever I want.
Really now?
Drop it.
You, move away
from the stanchion.
What took you so long?
Shut up!
He does have nice hair.
Yeah, that takes a lot of
upkeep, though, man.
Yeah.
You gotta worry
about split ends...
Dandruff.
It's horrible.
It's awful.
Yeah. Let's get out of here.
The Wilcrofts are not talking
at all to our investigators.
We get indications from their
lawyers that they will plead
the fifth to all charges,
which leaves me
with a whole slew
of loose ends.
For instance,
Detective Lassiter,
could you tell me how you made
the discovery that David
Wilcroft was still alive?
Well, actually, Chief,
we never made
that connection, per se.
We were on a stakeout...
Yes, I see that.
You describe it
as "harrowing and intense."
I'm sorry,
those were my words.
You wanted me
to spell-check it.
I still don't understand
how that connected you
to David Wilcroft.
Well, that's where
we come in, Chief,
some good work was done...
By Detective Lassiter.
He was amazing.
He figured out there was
a connection to Roger Blaine,
the cousin, who was involved
with the faking of the death.
Burnt body, no DNA,
pretty convenient,
he deducted.
I never said that.
No, but you thought it.
That's how good
you are, Lassy.
You practically solved this
entire case up here without
uttering a spoken word.
I did nothing of the kind.
I was following the money
and protecting Raylene.
Who turned out
to be the dangerous one.
Which I picked up
from Detective Lassiter's
massive brain.
Not true.
True.
Not.
It was so!
Gentlemen, please.
So we still have no idea
where the money is?
I got nothing from him.
But if he figures anything
out I'll be the first to know.
Would you excuse us
for a moment?
We're going to have
a private conversation.
I know what you're doing.
Giving you credit?
You're trying to get me
to admit you're psychic.
You've already done that.
No, I haven't.
You're right.
I'm sorry, you didn't
actually say it.
Spencer, no matter what
you do, I will never, never
ever say those words.
Which words?
You know which words.
No, man, I lost
my train of thought.
Which words?
Oh,
(LOUDLY) that you think
I'm a psychic.
Those words?
So when are you going to
tell them where the money is?
I don't know
where the money is.
Sure you do.
You're seeing dirt.
Am I right?
No!
What am I going to say now?
What are we doing here?
It's Saturday,
I thought we'd
get some fresh air.
We drove an hour out of town
to get some fresh air?
Well, there's that,
and we're gonna find
the dread pirate
Wilcroft's dirty booty.
Shawn, the guy's been digging
for four years.
We're gonna find it
in one afternoon?
Ninety minutes. Tops.
And I brought some chicken
for a hearty snack.
And how do you
plan on finding it?
Well, he said he dug every
inch of the Kalish Loop after
he buried it here. Right?
Yes. Three miles' worth.
But it was dark
and it had rained.
And he said he thought
it was right off the path,
he may have gotten lost.
I heard the story, Shawn.
Did he realize there's
a J. Kalish
and an L. Kalish trail?
Dude, it's completely defunct.
Check it out,
only used by the rangers for
back fires, medical access,
mud slide emergency routes,
like, for instance,
during a torrential rainstorm.
Otherwise, it's gated
and it looks completely
abandoned from the road.
Okay, I find it,
I get credit.
I'm the psychic,
I have to get a vibration.
"Chief?" "Yes?"
"I'm getting
a trailhead, a pathway.
"And something else."
"What is it?"
"Chicken bones.
"Yes, tandoori style.
"Fresh!" "Oh, I bet
they were delicious."
"Yes."
In between the lines
there's a lot of obscurity
I'm not inclined
to resign to maturity
If it's all right
then you're all wrong
But why bounce around
to the same damn song?
You'd rather run
when you can't crawl
I know, you know
That I'm not telling the truth
They just don't have any proof
Embrace the deception
Learn how to bend
Your worst inhibitions
tend to psych you out
in the end
I know, you know