THE FOLLOWING STORY IS FICTIONAL AND DOES
NOT DEPITC ANY ACTUAL PERSON OR EVENT.
Mr. Caceres
is looking at car theft,
assault, eluding police.
Your Honor, Alex
is a good kid.
Mr. Caceres
was in front of this court
on drug trafficking charges
less than six months ago.
Because he was forced to mule drugs
for his previous foster parents.
His father's been incarcerated
since he was an infant.
His mother and his brother
were killed two years ago.
If you could just
let Alex explain.
30 seconds, Mr. Caceres.
Judge...
Your-your Honor... sir...
I... I took my foster father's
car for a ride.
I-I know I was wrong. Just...
needed to get away.
Does that explain your
foster father's broken wrist ?
He tried to hit me.
I got scared, moved out of the way.
The DA recommends
a suspended sentence.
I'm not so inclined.
Mr. Caceres needs to learn
the consequences of his actions.
Your Honor,
I have a decorated
police detective
ready to testify on behalf
of Alex's character.
He must be running
a little late.
So am I.
18 months at Havenhurst Academy.
Approach the bench,
Mr. Caceres.
"In this world" by Moby.
It's over ?
Hang 'Em High Harry
never goes past two minutes.
- Where were you ?
- I got caught up.
Don't tell me.
Alex...
It's cool,
Detective Valens.
They're taking me
to this Havenhurst place.
Can't be worse
than foster care, right ?
Hey, look, I'm going to talk
to the judge.
Hey, Alex.
I got your back, okay ?
Jamal wouldn't step off.
Up in Franco's grill.
Franco put two in his.
Bam, bam.
Just left him there.
Colorful story, Michael.
The thing is,
Jamal was shot in the chest.
Booked the doer last week.
It wasn't Franco.
Look, you're up on petty theft.
I mean, doing three months.
Why yank our chain ?
They're sending me
to Havenhurst. I can't go back.
We're homicide, not concierge.
You don't help,
going to be a homicide-- mine.
They'll do me
like they did Alex.
Alex who ?
Caceres.
Hey, that was an accident.
You know who he's talking about?
Said he slipped.
But I found him.
Bruises all over.
Wrists had marks
like he was tied up.
I read the coroner's report.
There was nothing
about bruising.
I know what I saw.
You're saying someone
at Havenhurst
killed him and made it look
like an accident ?
He talked about you.
Hey, you make up that crap
about Jamal to get me in the room ?
Didn't even know
if you'd remember him.
Yeah, well, I do, so talk.
I ain't saying another word
unless you're going to keep me
out of Havenhurst.
Got your back, Michael.
Said the same thing to Alex,
and look what happened to him.
Cold Case
Season 7 Episode 3
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
COLD CASE 703
Jurisprudence
Alex died
of a subdural hematoma.
Havenhurst said it
was an accident.
- Well, accidents happen.
- Yeah, well, this one happens
in the middle of the night--
no one heard a thing.
The next morning,
they moved him out of his room
- before the cops got there.
- Wasn't it investigated ?
Yeah. M.E. called it a slip and fall,
and that's that.
Thing is, M.E. was a hack.
Scotty, overtime has
been cut to the bone.
Deputy Commissioner is
breathing down my neck.
Oh, come on, boss.
You're going to let
a tool bag like Doherty
back you off a case ?
- I don't see a case here.
- Well, I didn't, either,
till I found the autopsy photos.
I'd never
seen them before.
The bruising consistent
with a physical altercation.
These marks on the wrists
look like restraints.
You're thinking abuse.
It wouldn't
be the first.
I mean, you know-- uh...
private facilities like this
are barely regulated.
Should have looked closer
back then.
What does this kid mean
to you, Scotty ?
A few years back in Narcotics,
Alex's mother
was going to testify
against a dealer
in a case of mine.
Detective V, what's it take
to get a snack around here ?
If I can't get some change
for the vending machine,
I'm gonna sue
for police brutality.
Uh, I'm just playing.
You know I got much love
- for Philly's finest.
- Alex.
Something happened.
His mom and ten-year-old brother
were killed in a drive-by.
I transferred out of Narco.
Tried to look after Alex, but...
You sure this isn't
the guilt talking, Scotty ?
A kid like Michael's been
in the worst facilities,
and Havenhurst terrifies him.
I mean, something's up.
All right, on the QT, Scotty.
Keep it small.
We don't think of our kids
as offenders.
They need a chance
to work out their problems.
We give them a voice.
How's that working out ?
Seven percent improvement
on recidivism rates
compared to the state for
half of what they spend.
Minimal oversight,
too, right?
Regulation never kept
a kid out of jail.
State rewards us
with more cutbacks
and more kids.
Can't turn them away.
We're trying to help.
Well, how about Alex Caceres ?
You able to help him ?
Alex Caceres.
Yeah, that was a
terrible accident.
We're looking
into that.
What do you mean ?
I mean, he slipped in his room,
trying to open a window.
AC was on the fritz.
The cops never
got a look
at the body 'cause you moved it
before they got here.
Wasn't a body to me.
We moved him to
the infirmary,
trying to save his life.
Who has access
to the rooms at night ?
Just the counselors.
Counselors...
that like a guard ?
Um, "guard" sends
the wrong message.
"Counselor" is much better.
Laticia Myers
oversaw Alex's dorm.
She still works here.
You ever use restraints
on the kids ?
Never on a kid
like Alex.
He was pretty well-behaved.
Any other kids have a problem
with him or... ?
I wish I could
tell you more.
Alex wasn't here for very long.
This happened five years ago.
- Why are you guys here now?
- New information.
We'll need a list of all staff
and teachers from 2004.
Employment records,
security logs, time cards.
Whatever you need.
Only a matter a time before
something like that happened.
Your boss says the
place runs smooth.
You got the song and dance
from Mr. Price ?
All the "Kumbaya" crap?
It ain't true?
Place is understaffed,
over capacity.
Add kids who've never had
adult supervision...
you do that math.
A lot of pressure
on you counselors.
Keep your hands
to yourself, Alberto !
I mean now.
I came up Third and Diamond.
I'm used to
boys like this.
Alex was killed in his room.
It possible another kid
could have done it?
Place like this,
doesn't take much to set it off.
Lights out is 9:45.
I catch you out of bed,
it's detention.
Catch you in the common room,
I catch you in the bathroom...
it's detention.
You don't mess with me.
I don't mess with you.
You do, I take you down.
"Luv N My Life"
par Paul Wall.
Open the door
right now!
Give me this
backpack, man.
Look what we got here.
Give it back !
Oh, you wanted that ?
My bad, man.
I didn't even know.
Belongs to him, King Kong.
What you call me ?
You call me a monkey, homes ?
Sure smell like one, bro.
I'm gonna knock
your little smart-ass
Puerto Rican head in half.
How about that?
Ray-Ray !
Get up ! Get up right now !
- Man, get off of me, man.
- Stop!
Come on, Alex.
It's over, boys.
It's over.
We're going to
talk this out.
Evan had a conference with them.
Made them shake hands.
Sent them back
in time for lunch.
This Ray-Ray...
type to hold a grudge ?
Miracle Alex lasted
as long as he did.
Ray-Ray.
Big, bad stickup boy on parole
after serving a deuce upstate.
Yet you got a library card ?
All right, all right.
Be a gentleman.
Darleen...
Lydia...
Marissa.
Just...
breaking hearts all over South Philly.
What you doing, man?
Tell us about Alex Caceres.
Who ?
Played you in front of your boys
day he got to Havenhurst.
Lived in the same dorm.
Till he woke up dead
in his room one morning.
I don't know nothing about that.
Adios, Darleen.
Lydia.
Ooh, Marissa.
Marissa ? No.
Can you leave that one?
Look, man, I ain't got
nothing to hide, man.
All right ? Me and Alex
was tight, for reals.
"Get by" by Talib Kweli.
Hey, man, I'm outside waiting
on my ride, right ?
Cops roll up before I can even
empty my pockets, dog.
Got me on felony weight, man.
Looking at some
serious time, man.
Ain't you got a younger cousin ?
Say what ?
You get a little kid
to deliver your product.
They do what you tell
them 'cause they scared.
And if they're caught,
they can't do serious time.
Man, how do you know that?
Lived it.
Can't throw a punch,
but you're smart.
Heard you was the one got open
the window in your room.
Been trying out
for a month, man.
I almost broke my hand
trying to work the hinge.
Ain't about muscle.
It's finesse.
You stealing from me, boy?
Sit your ass back down.
Take from me again,
I'll pull your arm
right out of the socket.
The look in Jimmy's eyes.
We all knew he'd been upstate.
This Jimmy get rough
with the kids ?
Look, man,
that place was a joke to me.
Except Jimmy.
Him, I took serious.
Oh, sorry, Dad.
I got caught up.
No, no.
Tomorrow works.
Same time. Bye.
Oh, no. You didn't have
to cancel your plans.
Partner's right ?
Share the load ?
Well, the files are a mess.
Employment records mixed
with offender intake forms.
I mean, nothing's where
it's supposed to be.
Well, I did find this.
Criminal record for our shop
teacher-- Jimmy Clarke.
Picked up his prison stare
in New Jersey State Pen.
Seven years
for ag assault.
Nearly killed a guy
with the butt of his gun.
How's an ex-con like this get
hired to teach at Havenhurst?
Well, not a long
line of applicants.
No pay, no benefits,
no background check.
No problem.
Yeah.
It's a gold Mercury Sable
registered
to a Maurice Kitchener.
Whatever you need,
I'll back you up.
Okay.
Deputy Commissioner
Doherty.
Trying to introduce myself
to all the detectives
under my command.
Miller, right?
Used to work Narcotics?
- That's right.
- You the one who opened
this Alex Caceres can of worms ?
That'd be me, Pat.
Just can't help yourself, John.
Got to find new ways
to piss me off ?
Keeps me busy
during the slow times.
Want to tell me why the hell
we're investigating an accidental death ?
What's it matter to you
what cases we take ?
We need closed cases,
not whodunits.
You let me worry about closing them.
You can always take the credit.
I oversee the Detective Bureau
now, John.
Gonna have to get used to it.
You're shutting this
investigation down immediately.
We clear ?
I need to hear you say it, John.
We're clear.
Whatever you need
on the Alex Caceres job, you got it.
Got anger management
issues, Jimmy ?
Meaning ?
You beat a guy to a bloody pulp
in a parking lot in Atlantic City.
Guy owed me money,
wanted to pay me back
with a crowbar.
I was protecting myself.
Did my time for it, too.
Why take a job
at a place like Havenhurst ?
When I went upstate,
I arned carpentry.
Figured that was something
I could give back
to these kids.
- A way out.
- Well,
an ex-con altruist.
Teaching street
kids they could use
their hands to build.
Give 'em pride.
Call it what you want.
What about trouble kids ?
Alex Caceres, for instance.
- This is about Alex ?
- Well, he stole from you, right ?
Like that guy in AC.
Nah, he just made a mistake.
We-we were cool.
Don't seem surprised
to hear his name
come from a homicide detective.
Never believed it
was an accident.
Could have spoken up
back in the day.
Yeah.
Me and cops
don't get along too good.
You have access
to the dorms at Havenhurst ?
Rules were clear. I was only
allowed in the classroom area.
Where were you the night
Alex died ?
Working nights
in a hardware store
so I could afford supplies
for my shop class.
I was the only one looking out
for that kid.
Did a pretty lousy job
of it, Jimmy.
Don't think I know that?
Eats me up every day.
Got any with nuts ?
Two dollars.
Yeah, not today, my man.
I can get other stuff, too.
Anything you want.
Just name it.
Acclimating yourself
like a pro, huh?
Gaming the system
prepares you for one thing--
becoming a repeat offender.
You a smart kid.
You need to put your mind
to something constructive.
Like what ?
Building birdhouses ?
Do the time,
or the time does you.
Gonna tell me
to work the system ?
'Cause all the system done
for me
is take my family,
stick me in places
like this.
That's a raw deal, my man.
For real.
But you can't
keep it bottled in.
It festers in there.
Trust me, I know.
Old picture.
Guess you don't see
him much anymore.
Don't say another word
about him.
Didn't mean nothing.
Let's keep it on you.
Why you got blood
on your shirt, hmm ?
Come on, Alex !
Either you're getting beat,
or you're doing
I gots to go.
Figured he was getting bullied.
Tried a couple more times
to get through to him.
He wouldn't talk.
- Give up after that ?
- Of course not.
I called the only person
who might've actually helped.
His lawyer.
What do you want me to say ?
A lot of kids I used to
work with got hurt.
Many of them
reach out to you,
like Alex Caceres,
days before they died?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Well, his shop
teacher, Jimmy Clarke,
called you, told you
Alex was in trouble.
We need to take you into interrogation ?
Jog your memory ?
We have records,
show you visited
Alex at Havenhurst
the week he died.
I got out of this racket
for a reason.
So damn tragic all the time.
Jimmy said
Alex had blood on his shirt.
What was going on with him ?
Not what you think.
Jimmy thinks you're in trouble.
And he wouldn't go
through the hassle
of calling me unless
he thinks it's serious.
Alex, if the older boys
are bothering you,
we need to address that.
Have a conference.
Ain't no snitch.
It's not really snitching
if it's happening to you.
Why don't I get myself
a cup of coffee, hmm?
If someone's hurting you,
you've got to speak up.
Could be grounds
to get you out.
Not me.
Someone else.
He's young like a runt.
Getting beat every night.
Well, then he needs
to call his own lawyer.
His lawyer won't return
his calls.
He won't survive much longer.
Said you're here to help.
I'm here to help you.
Then get him out of here.
He's 11.
Lifted some comics,
got six months.
That sound right to you ?
Give me his name,
I'll look into it,
but no promises.
Michael. Michael Rodgers.
You'll like him.
I'll call his lawyer,
get into it.
- what's this mean, "juris..."
- "Jurisprudence"?
It's the legal system.
It ensures we get justice.
We all abide by it.
It's how I'm gonna help you.
Found Michael Rodgers's lawyer,
told him Michael
was having trouble,
made sure he petitioned
to have him transferred.
So, that's it ?
I was overwhelmed
with my own clients.
What was I supposed to do ?
Oh, maybe speak up when
Alex died three weeks later ?
Well, I didn't see you there,
either, Valens.
- Yeah.
- Or were you late again ?
Hey, I reached out to Alex.
Told him whatever he needed,
I'd be there.
But he pushed you away, right ?
Ever wonder why ?
Or does self-doubt cramp
your style ?
POLICE HEADQUARTERS
Still on hold ?
Yeah. Trying to get
Michael out of J.D.C.
Court hasn't responded
to my request to move him, so...
Spoke to his lawyer
from back then.
Petition to transfer Michael
from Havenhurst was denied.
Got to love the juvenile
justice system.
The weird thing is,
his lawyer says Michael
was transferred
a few days after Alex died.
Never knew why.
Well, maybe Michael
could fill in the blanks
if I can get ahold of him.
You know what that lawyer said ?
Marci ?
Hey, can't be everywhere
at once.
Should have been there, though.
The system let him down,
not you.
All due respect, Lil.
It was me.
Look, you know,
go to your dinner.
I got this covered.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm still here.
Wait. What-what do you mean,
he was processed ?
Michael's coming with me.
I can't let you
do that, Detective.
He's a key witness
in a homicide investigation.
You don't like it,
call the cops.
Hey, um, yeah, bad news.
I-I got to work late again.
No. No, I'm fine, Dad.
Okay.
All right, we'll do it
another time.
You, too.
********
Hi, it's Detective Rush
from Homicide.
Yeah, I'm going
to need help, um,
tracking a cell.
Lilly, one more step and
I'd have blown your head off.
Nice to see you, too, Saccardo.
You got nothing to eat?
I'm in deep.
Don't usually entertain.
Well, I think for a stalker,
you could at least offer me
something to drink.
Well, it took you long enough
to trace those photos.
Well...
I'm a cop in my spare time.
I guess you missed me.
Not really.
But when I heard they let
Major Scumbag walk on bail...
I know.
I don't really
need you to...
Watch out for you ?
Just want to make sure I got
something to look forward to
when I surface.
We really gotta stop
meeting like this.
Where is he now ?
Probably trying to get
the boot off his car.
Does that make you
feel better?
- It's a Band-Aid.
- So what're you going to do ?
What would you do ?
Situation like mine.
A guy like this ?
We'll figure
something out.
Seriously, though.
I'm starving.
Well, let's go get some eggs.
Said I wanted a burger.
It's breakfast.
- What's it going to cost me ?
- I told you
I wouldn't let them take
you back to Havenhurst.
Kept my word, right ?
Do me a favor.
Eat the eggs.
After Alex died,
you got transferred out.
How'd that happen ?
See, you hustling me
this whole time.
You contacted me, remember ?
I'm seeing it through.
You gotta trust me.
- Alex trusted you.
- Yeah, you're right.
And I let him down.
Alex... deserved better.
Night Alex died...
he swore he was going to get me
out of Havenhurst.
He was trying to save me.
Save you, from what ?
They took me out of my room
after lights out.
I thought they was
going to kill me.
All right. Give me the names
of the kids.
Wasn't the kids I was afraid of.
Get off ! Now !
Back to your room, Alex.
Ain't none of your concern.
I look out for him.
Supposed to be your job.
My job is keeping you in line.
Little punk's a thief.
- This about your damn keys?
- It's about something
he took from
the director's office.
A very expensive pen.
I-I didn't do it, Alex. I swear.
Gold. Fancy.
Says "Jurisprudence" on it.
I took it.
Get him down to
the infirmary!
I want to stay with you.
Get him out of here.
You're going to give me
that pen, Alex.
Or what, Ms. Myers ?
'Cause I'm done
giving in.
We'll see about that.
Laticia made every day hell
for me.
Then she turned on Alex.
Think she hurt Alex ?
Alex gone, ain't he ?
Laticia's still there.
Still don't know why he stood up
for me like that.
Well, maybe...
he was doing for you what
no one ever did for him.
Thanks, Detective Valens.
Yeah, what for ?
The eggs.
I just got off the
phone with JDC.
One of your detectives kidnapped
a juvenile offender last night.
Is that so ?
This ends now.
You're ordering me to back off
an open homicide investigation.
Maybe you're unaware,
since you've never worked
an active squad in your life,
but deputy commissioners don't
get personally involved in cases
unless there's something
to hide.
Budget cuts are a bitch, huh ?
Manpower shortages everywhere.
Except here, John,
in Homicide.
There's an opening
on the midnight shift,
East Detectives.
Going to need you to sacrifice
one of your guys.
Not going to happen.
You pick.
Or I will.
I gotta tell ya,
Havenhurst employment
records are a mess.
Took us days find your file.
Sure glad we did.
Looks like you applied
to the police academy
same time you applied
to Havenhurst.
Wanted to wear a badge ?
Carry a gun ?
I was looking to serve.
'Cause you're from Third
and Diamond, right ?
Tough street.
Whole neighborhood's tough.
Said you grew up with boys
like the ones at Havenhurst.
Did you mean the Hernandez
brothers ?
Every cop in the 26th has
arrested one of those dirtbags
at some time or another.
Look back far enough
in their records,
your name comes up
as a complainant.
So ?
They attacked you, Laticia.
They dragged you
into their house.
Kept you there for hours.
You were 12.
I survived.
Must've affected you.
Being trapped.
Surrounded
by those animals.
That's why you wanted
to be a cop.
But you got turned down.
Said I was unfit.
For psychological
reasons.
Didn't seem to be an issue
at Havenhurst.
You pitted those boys
against each other.
I didn't have a problem
with Alex.
It was Michael
who pissed you off.
But Alex stood up to you,
the night he died.
I told him to go back
to his room.
He cornered me, you understand ?
You weren't a counselor anymore.
You were that little girl
from Third and Diamond.
He wouldn't back down!
Back off, Alex!
Or what ? Don't got
your posse now.
I'm warning you !
Nothing you could do to me
ain't already been done.
You hear me ?
Got one more chance.
Not going to hurt Michael
ever again !
What the hell you doing ?
She got those kids
beating Michael.
I don't care.
You don't put hands on
the staff, Alex.
Screw you.
Pretend to be one of us,
you're as bad as her.
You going back
to your room.
Man, you ain't my dad.
Can't even take care
of your own kid.
Should've seen Jimmy dragging
Alex back to his room.
Last time
I saw the kid alive.
I thought Jimmy wasn't
authorized to be in the dorm.
He did handyman work
off the books.
Got him a key.
Didn't report any of this ?
Would've thanked him
if I had the chance.
What do mean ?
Where'd he go ?
Disappeared after that night.
Out sick for a week.
There's no record of that.
Told you.
Those kids were animals.
Jimmy knew it.
Did us all a favor.
Think it's time
for a new profession, Laticia.
You are disappointing me, Jimmy.
The way you were talking
the other day, I started to believe.
Teaching those boys
self-respect through carpentry.
Just like Jesus.
Here's a fun fact
from your past.
Night you beat
that guy in A.C.,
your three-year-old
son was in the car.
Cops pull you over,
he's in the back.
They take your kid,
put him in the system.
Get out of lockup,
go straight to Havenhurst.
Just trying to make amends.
Be a positive influence
on all kind of kids.
As long as it wasn't your own.
When was the last time
you saw your kid, Jimmy ?
You don't know nothing
about it !
Record keeping at
Havenhurst is a mess.
Couldn't find your timecards.
But your old boss at
the hardware store
keeps everything.
You were late
the night Alex died.
Got an eyeball witness
ready to testify
you got violent
with him.
Puts you in his room
the night he was killed.
I know what Laticia think.
But I was trying to keep Alex
from flushing his future away.
He was way ahead of me, though.
You a damn fool !
Attacking counselors ?
That's a one-way
ticket upstate.
I'm the only one
willing to fight.
A fight you'll lose !
You afraid of them, ain't you ?
I'm not saying don't push.
I'm saying you gotta
handle it different.
Educate me, my man.
You're playing the game
with every disadvantage.
They outman you !
They outgun you !
You got one weapon.
You hear ? One !
Your mind.
"Don't say nuthin' "
par The Roots.
It's like what you said
about the...
the window to Ray-Ray.
You can't force it open.
You gotta finesse it.
"Jurisprudence" ?
What's that ?
System we all live under.
And it's broken.
I get it now.
That's why they keep
Michael here.
Nobody ever gets transferred out.
Ever notice that ?
Sick kids, psychos.
Nobody.
Every bed is full.
Always.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Need you to do me a favor.
Get this to Detective
Scotty Valens.
A cop ?
Hey, whoa, whoa.
What's going on ?
Tell him to hold on to it,
please, Jimmy.
Trust me ?
All right.
Need one more favor.
Let me use the phone.
Main office was the only place
to make a call.
I left the door open
for him on my way out.
Know who
he was going to call ?
I didn't ask.
He said he needed me
to trust him.
I did.
What about the pen ?
You do anything with it ?
Alex was dead.
My prints was all over his room.
Waited in my place for a week
for the cops to come.
Never showed.
You still got that pen, Jimmy ?
I checked the Havenhurst
phone records
the night Alex died,
and a call was made
at half past midnight
to the private residence
of Harold Alvarez.
Judge "Hang 'em High Harry" ?
Just told the
boss, and he says
the judge and Deputy
Commissioner Doherty
are golf buddies.
Explains why Doherty's been
breathing down our necks.
He's protecting the judge.
So why did Alex need
to call the judge ?
Been searching the word
"jurisprudence"
and I still
can't figure out
what Alex was saying to me
with this pen.
Check out the judge, too.
Look, cross-checked
the judge's name
with "jurisprudence."
Look what comes up.
Hey, Judge.
I found this at Havenhurst
a little while ago.
Figured you'd
want it back.
I've toured that facility
a few times.
I must have left it there.
Thank you.
"Jurisprudence"...
it means "justice," right ?
It's also a luxury
ski cabin in Utah.
You own it with
your sister-in-law.
If you don't mind,
I'm running late.
Your sister-in-law's
an entrepreneur.
She owns nursing homes,
juvenile centers--
Havenhurst, for one.
So the state pays Havenhurst
for every kid sent there.
Havenhurst is owned
by your sister-in-law.
She pays you...
You will reconsider
what you're saying
if that badge means
anything at all to you.
It's incentive for
strict sentencing,
a reason to block transfers,
like Michael Rodgers.
Accusing me
of judicial misconduct ?
No... that's for the
Justice Department to sort out.
I'm accusing you of murder.
Alex Caceres.
I didn't kill that boy.
No, you're the type of guy,
has other people do the deed.
Give me a name.
I got records that put
you and Alex on the phone
the night he died.
I'll give you two minutes
to tell me who killed Alex.
The day of Alex's hearing,
I was late.
Should have been there.
But it didn't matter, did it ?
I could have been early, you
still would have sent Alex away
just to make a buck.
You know what ?
Screw it.
Turn around, Judge,
I'm locking you up.
Wait, wait.
The boy had my attention.
Hello.
How do you sleep at night ?
Who is this ?
Sent me to Havenhurst
for a joyride.
Lot of other kids here
for less.
Son, if you know
what's good for you,
you'll hang up this phone now.
I know what "Jurisprudence" is.
Even a delinquent can use
the Internet.
That's why you send us here...
for a fancy house ?
Those are
some very serious accusations.
Get away with it
'cause everyone listens to you.
But not us.
What do you want from me, kid ?
Get my friend Michael Rodgers
transferred tonight,
or I'll call the 11:00 news.
They'll listen to me.
Don't you ?
What are you doing, Alex ?
Hey, get off me.
Give me the phone now.
It was supposed to be
a good facility.
Nobody should have gotten hurt.
Who took the phone from Alex ?
Who was it ?
You're the secret
to Havenhurst's
success.
You come early,
stay late.
You're there weekends, holidays.
My work is my passion.
The problem is your passion
is a business.
We found this
in your apartment
when we searched it.
You searched my apartment ?
Yeah, that's you
at Judge Alvarez's ski house.
You go every year.
Yeah, they're,
they're business trips.
That's not
how the judge put it.
He ain't going
to jail for you.
I mean, that's for sure.
You meant
well, Evan,
till you started hanging
with the big dogs,
seeing what money
could buy.
I'm not interested in money.
Yeah, if that was true,
you'd have put up a fight
every time the judge's family
cut your budget
or stuck you with bad staff
or too many kids.
I tried.
Nobody would listen.
We... we searched your office,
too, Evan.
Yeah, thing
about Luminol--
no matter how long
the blood's been there,
no matter how hard
you try to scrub it out...
...we're going to find it.
You killed Alex there,
dragged him to his room.
I was trying to reason with him.
He wanted Michael transferred.
I was going to do it.
I did.
Afterwards, out of guilt.
Yeah, but that night
all you could see was
Havenhurst, your passion,
in jeopardy.
Please just...
...let me tell you
what happened.
What is the matter
with you, Alex ?!
You got a problem ?
Come to me.
Your thug Laticia
tried to kill Michael tonight.
He shouldn't even be here;
he's a little kid.
Okay, okay.
If Laticia did something wrong,
we'll talk to her about it.
If this isn't the right fit
for Michael, we'll address tt.
We can work
all of this out.
- Sit down.
- It's beyond circle time, man.
You want to work it out,
pick up that phone
and call the judge--
he's the boss.
I run Havenhurst.
If you're in charge, why
don't you fix the problems ?
Too many kids getting screwed over,
not just Michael.
Damn, why don't you do
something about it?!
Do you know how hard I work
to keep this place going ?
Enough to get you there, right ?
Jurisprudence, my ass.
You're just like the judge--
in it to get paid.
That is completely out of line.
We can talk about this, Alex.
What are you doing ?
Give me the number
for Channel 2 news.
Damn it, Alex.
You put that phone down.
You want to talk?
- Talk to the cameras.
- Put the phone down!
'Cause you're going down
with the rest of 'em.
I said listen to me !
Quiet !
Just be quiet !
Shut up.
Let me think.
Just let me think.
"None of us are free"
by Solomon Burke.
* Well, you'd better listen,
my sisters and brothers *
* 'Cause if you do,
you can hear *
* There are voices *
* Still callin'
across the years *
* And they're all cryin'
across the ocean *
* And they're cryin'
across the land *
* And they will
till we all come to understand *
* None of us are free *
* None of us
are free *
* One of us is chained,
none of us are free *
* And there are people *
* Still in darkness *
* And they just
can't see the light *
* If you don't say it's wrong *
* Then that says it's right *
* We got to try to feel
for each other *
* Let our brothers know
that we care *
* Got to get the message *
* Send it out loud and clear *
* None of us are free *
* None of us
are free *
* One of us is chained *
* None of us are free *
* It's a simple truth
we all need *
* Just to hear and to see *
* None of us are free *
* One of us is chained *
* Oh, Lord *
* None of us are free *
* Now, I swear your salvation *
* Isn't too hard to find *
* None of us can find it *
* On our own *
* We've got to join together *
* In spirit, heart and mind *
* So that every soul
who's suffering will know *
* That we're not alone *
* Whoa... none of us are free *
* None of us are free *
* None of us
are free *
* One of us is chained,
none of us are free. *
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-