La Philly Team présente...
........
"Just What I Needed"
by The Cars.
Oh, come on, Barry.
I want to hear the movie.
I don't see anybody else watching.
It's James Dean.
Peach schnapps ?
That's your big move, Barry ?
I thought you liked peach schnapps.
Oh, who told you that ?
Shane Bannif ?
No.
Next time you see Shane,
ask him what happened
at Devil's Pool.
- He took you there ?
- Pumped me full
of peach schnapps,
said he wanted to jump the ledge.
- No way.
- Way.
I jump, but Shane has some
last-minute shrinkage.
End of our big date.
I'll take one of these.
Bottoms up.
Feels like we're being watched.
You want to go in the back ?
Can you put the top up ?
Yeah. Just don't move.
Damn it. It's stuck.
Well, unstick it.
You look...
beautiful...
Help !
Somebody help him !
Well, you look great, Diane.
Ah, capoeira, crunches,
six rounds at the heavy bag.
I never give an inch.
- Boss.
- Lil, I'd like you
to meet a friend of mine,
Diane Yates.
Agent Yates, FBI.
This the one you
told me about, John ?
Uh... something I can help
you with ?
Maybe.
Diane got her start in the PPD.
18th District.
Wild West back then.
She blazed a trail for women.
Oh, that's a bunch of bull, Johnn
I got tired of being
groped by the boys club
and then being passed
up for promotion.
Ah, it's more
complicated than that.
What, you want to compare
detective test scores ?
No.
They spot you ten points
for having a Y chromosome.
Well, it's not too long ago.
At least the Bureau was a
little bit more enlightened.
You back for memories or...
coffee ?
A case you worked on a while ago.
The fresh job.
Mel Shaver.
Shot dead walking his dog.
Elmwood Park.
Suspected robbery,
went cold with no witnesses.
Yeah, well, we'll see about that.
- What's the FBI's interest in the job ?
- Classified.
Listen, I had a rough one
last night,
I need a fistful of Ibuprofen
or something stronger.
"Classified." Give me a break.
Well, just download
her on the case, Lil.
Maybe she can help us solve it.
Got some Ibuprofen in my desk.
Anything stronger ?
Mel Shaver, 43-year-old.
Tax lawyer, shot on November 6,
in Elmwood Park.
Recover any ballistics evidence ?
Through and through.
Gold Rolex, a wallet missing.
Got a string of
holdups in the area.
What else ?
Wife says he didn't
have any enemies.
- Solid citizen.
- What about habits ?
Crack or stripping his bark
in the woods ?
Nothing turned up.
Nothing turned up,
or you didn't ask ?
I worked the case.
There was nothing to go on.
It's a Percocet,
left over from an accident.
Shame not to finish a prescription.
I didn't need them.
Major Maurice Kitchener
got the end he deserved.
Run my name through
the Fed database ?
Wouldn't exactly
describe you as a solid
citizen, Detective.
Though you lean that way.
- I do my best.
- Of course you do.
What's this ?
It's a wooded area,
adjacent to the kill spot.
No, no, no. Here.
I need these blown up.
Get a high-res scan.
This is Philadelphia.
We got one lab tech,
one copy machine and a two-week wait.
That's for a hot case.
I'll do it, then.
So, is this the extent
of your investigation ?
Unless the FBI has
some new information.
No.
We're counting on you
having missed something.
Doubt it. Case is cold.
Start by re-interviewing the wife.
And do you need
approval from Daddy,
or can we just work this case ?
How exactly do you know Stillman ?
Johnny always gave me a
fair shake coming up.
All things considered.
Considering what ?
I broke up his marriage.
Cold Case
Season 7 Episode 18
The last drive-in (Part 1)
Hey.
- You want a piece of me ?
- Nah.
Just came to see
how you were doing.
Well, five hours a day I get
to talk about my feelings.
Can't sleep 'cause my
roommate's up every five minutes
washing the germs off his hands,
and lecturing me
about palm oils in my diet.
Highlight of the day
is taking on my fellow
detectives in ping-pong,
but other than that
things are looking up.
How's the Jell-O ?
Not bad.
Mac and cheese sucks.
Look.
Portable DVD player.
Thank you.
"The Honeymooners."
"The Godfather One."
Two.
"Midnight Run."
"The Cutting Edge" ?
It's a guilty pleasure.
Mine, too.
Between us.
D.A., uh, reopened
the Billingsley case.
Fat lot of good that does Joe Don.
Come on.
All right.
Has there been a break
in the case ?
It's a routine reinvestigation.
Why is the FBI interested?
Quite a collection.
My husband bought those for me.
Cute.
What kind of man was your husband ?
I know what you're asking.
We had a good marriage.
What, because he bought you
these ?
And he was very thoughtful.
Sounds like.
I'm sorry. I don't see
what this has to
do with his murder ?
If you could just tell us
what happened that night.
Mel took our dog for a walk
and was killed by a stranger.
One minute
you're planning a trip to
the Galapagos
and the next you're shopping
funerary urns.
Did he ever live or
work in Upper Darby ?
- Not that I know of.
- Anywhere in Delaware County ?
He was a homebody.
Meaning what ? You'd just sit around
sipping Sleepytime Tea
and watching "60 Minutes" ?
Mel worked.
He watched the Phillies.
He took walks.
Our big excitement was...
dinner and a movie.
Did he ever mention the
Darby View Drive-In ?
Drive-In ?
This is going to help solve
my husband's murder ?
Oh, just answer the question.
I think I want you to leave.
Interesting interrogation technique.
You're a hand-holder.
It works sometimes.
- That woman lost her husband.
- I got that.
As well as he liked the
Phillies and walks in the park.
It's a tragic loss, to be sure.
Well, she might've
given us something.
I'm looking for connections,
not Facebook friends.
She didn't know who
killed her husband,
and I needed to know that.
Boss said these belong to you.
Diane Yates.
Scotty Valens.
You two partners ?
What type of name is that, Valens ?
Italian ? Mexican ?
Cuban, Puerto Rican.
As in Valenzuela.
It's a shame to shorten that.
I dated a Latino once.
All talk, no follow through.
You're dating the wrong Latinos.
Well, I guess so.
How about you put those pretty
brown eyes of yours to good use ?
And don't worry, I don't bite.
Anymore.
I got grass, trees,
rocks, park bench.
Mmm, there's something here.
Could be a homeless squat.
I don't recall an
interview in the file.
They must've split
when they saw the cops.
Yeah, but it'd be nice to
know if he saw something.
I'll call patrol.
Talk to the beat cop.
I miss a spot shaving ?
Just looking.
Thinking you'd fit right in
at the Bureau.
You fill out a suit nicely,
and I'm sure you're
good at sucking up.
- Minority doesn't hurt.
- Yeah.
I'll get right on that.
So, what's the Bureau want
with this case, anyway ?
What's it like working
with the bleach queen ?
Well, Lil and I make a good team.
Oh, I bet.
It's not like that.
You're not her type ?
Thanks.
Guy we're looking for
is Carl Guidry.
The bum in the park.
Patrol picked him up last week
for a visit to the psych ward.
At St. Paul's.
You remember this place, Carl ?
Yes.
You stay there sometimes?
Under my tree.
Well, a man was shot
and killed there last November.
And we think you
might've seen it happen.
No,I did not.
It was right here by the path.
He was walking a dog.
No, ma'am.
Final answer.
Carl ?
We know everything, Carl.
Everything inside
that head of yours.
Even that girl.
You have a problem with people
reading your thoughts ?
I want it to stop.
I can help you with that.
First, you have to help us.
Take that.
It'll keep the intruders out.
Is that better ?
I think so.
It must be working.
Can I have another ?
After you tell us
about the shooting.
Okay.
I was right-right there.
You leave when you saw the police ?
I didn't want no trouble.
The man in the green jacket,
Carl...
what was he doing to the body ?
Taking that gold watch.
I suppose.
How'd you know about
that watch, Carl?
Did you take the watch, Carl ?
I took a few things.
There goes robbery as a motive.
But the shooter checked the body.
Making sure there was no bullet
left behind.
Get something off the homeless guy ?
Saw the shooter.
That's good.
So,
Yates and Stillman had a thing.
A thing, thing ?
It was what she said.
Yeah, broke up his marriage.
The bigger issue is,
Cougar Town won't let
me in on what the Fed''
interest in this case is.
Might have a connect to
Darby in Delaware County.
Yeah, I'll dig around,
see what I can find.
Diane,
I want you to meet another member
- of my team, Kat Miller.
- Can I talk to you ?
Nice to meet you, too.
- You promised to keep me in the loop.
- I will.
But first I need Rush to walk
me through the crime scene.
Shaver enters the park
approximately 9:30.
I figure he keeps
to the lighted path.
The killer waited in the bushes
till he rounds the corner.
Confronts Shaver, and maybe
something happens with the dog,
or Shaver resists.
Shot came from over there.
With a handgun ?
It's got to be 100 yards.
He used a rifle.
Not a lot of thugs using long guns.
Shaver enters the shooting lane
illuminated by the street lamp.
It's a perfect shot.
It puts the trajectory...
...here.
You gonna tell me what's going on ?
We got to get this
back to ballistics.
Look, I don't give a crap
how far back you and Stillman go.
Want to keep shining me on,
go ahead.
I'll call my own friend
in the Bureau.
I'm your friend in the Bureau.
We have a serial killer, a sniper.
Are there other cases
to back this up ?
'Cause I don't recall
other unsolveds with a rifle.
Last one was 27 years ago,
and it looks like he came out
of retirement.
- Where's Yates ?
- Down at ballistics.
Found this.
- Darby View Drive-In, 1980.
- Shooting never solved.
Only evidence was a rifle bullet
recovered from the victim...
25.06.
Well, Yates thinks the Shaver murder
is the work of a serial sniper.
Might have heard if a sniper was picking
off folks in our backyard.
And they sent one agent ?
Feds come two to a box.
Well, I figure,
boss vouches for her,
she must be good.
What if the task force blows in
and starts barking orders ?
Hey.
Kicked me early.
Got those files from the
Billingsley case for you.
Just coffee, Fay.
Trying to help the family out,
you know ?
You talk to the warden ?
They investigated
Joe Don's shanking.
It turns out, he cut the chow line,
the gang took offense.
Well, that's on me.
No, you can't keep beating
yourself up about this, Nick.
No, I can't look the
other way, either.
Well, do the work,
get your head right.
What's that supposed to mean ?
Well, it means,
it's gonna be a while
before you're cleared
back to active duty.
I'm good to go.
Worked with a guy in Vice.
He had a meltdown,
his wife left him.
Substance abuse.
Brass had him take a powder.
Yeah ?
Well, he was chomping at the bit
to get back on the line.
He got cleared,
comes back all smiles.
Two weeks later, I found
him dead in his squad car.
I'm not that guy.
Take as much time
as you need, Nick.
We'll be here for you
when you're ready.
You got to fluff half
the boys in the lab
to get a report back around here.
Come back a 25.06 ?
Same bullet that
killed Barry Jensen
at the Darby View Drive-In.
Nice.
Yes.
Preliminary ballistics
makes it a match.
Well, the same shooter then ?
You think ?
You know, if you want my help,
you need to tell me what's going on.
How about we get a drink ?
If you're 12-stepping,
you can sip diet soda
and silently judge me.
I can attribute five shootings
to our guy.
Victims linked ?
If only.
Kid on his way to college,
bus driver, secretary, roofer,
and now the tax attorney.
And the first one at the drive-in.
Three more after that, and then,
nothing for 27 years.
I thought he was dead or in prison.
Then the Shaver shooting pops.
Same MO : a single
shot to the chest.
No bullet left behind.
You've been hunting
this guy for 30 years ?
Oh, I must have chased
down a dozen cases
I thought fit the pattern.
- Calling in the task force ?
- Nope.
First homicide was right
around the corner here.
Frank's Coffee Shop.
Double murder : waitress, manager.
First on the scene ?
Took initial statements,
and right away I liked
the busboy for it.
And then the detectives show up.
Oh. Yeah, didn't see
it the same way.
No. I try telling 'em,
but they liked the
ex-con grill cook.
The lead laughed in my face.
Told me to shut my trap and
secure his crime scene.
Oh, I remember a few
of those myself.
Well, last thing we need
is some Fed profiler
telling us what kind of
underwear our shooter favors,
or that he had mommy issues.
Another round.
One for him.
Amstel Light at the end of the bar
is kind of cute.
You seeing anyone ?
Was.
Another cop ?
Yeah.
You're looking for the real thing.
Good luck.
Only took me 30 years,
but I stopped believing
in that nonsense
when I figured out what men want.
What's that ?
A girlfriend, not a wife.
All right, Philly P.D.
will work jointly with
Agent Yates and the FBI.
Got five shootings.
The first in 1980,
the last five months ago.
Agent Yates will run
the rest for you.
With the exception of
the first shooting,
the killer chose
isolated targets,
minimizing his exposure.
This guy is patient, smart,
and careful.
Safe to assume military service.
Four victims either lived,
worked or had ties
to Delaware County.
First victim, Barry Jensen,
shot at a drive-in, 1980.
- Any witnesses ?
- No.
I've already done the legwork on that.
There's nothing there.
Felicity Andrews, secretary.
Shot in her car in
New Jersey in 1981.
Assigned theorized a
carjacking gone wrong.
Preston Schmall, part-time roofer,
shot in the Poconos
while camping, 1982.
Next was Fred Norris,
a bus driver,
shot in '83 near the bus grounds.
And now Shaver,
the tax attorney,
shot just five months ago.
Any casing recovered ?
No, but we have the bullet
that killed Shaver.
Matches the first victim, 1980.
All right, re-interview
family, friends,
any folks at those scenes.
See if something was missing.
Interview the bus driver.
Oh. You want me to
interview the bus driver ?
Well, you can relate culturally.
Just right on the surface, huh ?
You got a problem with that,
report me to Reverend Al
after we find this guy.
Why are y'all coming
around now on Fred ?
Reopening his murder.
Well, it's about time.
You two friends?
Played tonk every Friday night.
Didn't have any family.
Just the regulars on his route.
What happened that night, Calvin ?
Well, I was getting
ready for my next shift.
Catching some z's
on the bus, and...
and that's when I...
that's when I heard it.
Freddie ?
- Hey, what are you doing ?
- Get help !
He's been shot !
I thought it was one
of Freddie's jokes.
We were always pranking each other.
This other guy... black? White?
White. When I came back
from making the phone call,
he was gone.
Anything you remember about him ?
Green Army jacket.
Just never made any sense to me.
Felicity was going
to get her radiology degree.
And you worked together before she took
the job at the high school ?
At Philly Savings and Loan.
- Secretaries ?
- Executive assistants.
Just a nicer way
of saying the same thing.
We covered for the loan officers
making promises they couldn't keep.
Were there a lot of angry folks
back then ?
Oh, you bet.
Spent most of the time answering phones,
getting yelled at.
Felicity get in the
middle of something ?
I remember this one
guy who kept calling,
but that was years
before she was murdered.
You got a name ?
Just a nickname.
Mr. 6.83.
A rate the manager
promised him but couldn't deliver.
Wanna get lunch ?
They have a new salad
bar at Maxwell's.
Felicity, aren't you
going to answer it ?
I can't. It's him, I just know it.
Mr. 6.83 ?
He called three times
this morning, and I think
he followed me into the
parking lot the other day.
Philly Savings and Loan.
I want answers.
You promised me that rate.
And I want a new Cadillac
and a boyfriend that looks
like Robert Redford.
Nance !
Where is she ?
The blonde that keeps lying to me,
saying that my loan's
gonna go through ?
Would you like to
speak to a manager?
You're all liars.
Drop dead, creep !
"Strange way" by Firewall.
It got so bad, she finally quit.
Good thing, 'cause the bank
went belly up a year later.
Did she know this guy's name?
I don't remember.
Like I said, there were
a lot of angry people
with the recession and all.
So, you were there
when Preston was shot ?
Not exactly.
You told police that you
were on the trail with him.
I wasn't with him
at the time.
- Did you see the shooter ?
- No.
The police said it was a
stray bullet from a poacher.
So, you went hiking
but just not together ?
We weren't exactly getting along.
We went camping
hoping to reconnect.
A little late.
You filed for separation a
week before he was killed.
Did you tell him?
We argued, he ran into the woods.
That's the last time I saw him.
Why lie about being there
when he was shot?
It was like that police officer knew.
Knew what?
That it was my fault somehow.
It felt like I'd been set free.
I know that sounds terrible,
but it's the truth.
A happy accident.
It's funny, I hadn't thought
about Preston in years.
And then, last month, I ran into
a sister and she told me that...
One of his gambling buddies
had been shut upstate New York.
Shot and killed ?
No,
he survived.
You don't think
there's a connection, do you ?
- Can you give us a name ?
- Tim Hudson.
He'd hire Preston to
help him repo cars.
Bus driver saw the
killer at the scene.
Checking for a bullet ?
Trying to,
until he was interrupted.
What about the secretary ?
A disgruntled bank customer
might've been stalking her.
Pull the loan records
from that period, Scotty,
match them against
military servers,
people in the system.
Well, we got something.
Found a survivor, Tim Hudson.
Worked as a repo man
with victim number three.
Preston Schmall.
Wounded in a drug-related shooting.
Remember how I said I'd
keep you in the loop ?
You know, I'm cutting you
a lot of slack, Diane,
on account of our history.
This guy's out there,
John, I know it.
I'm gonna protect my people
if it turns into a turf war.
It's not going to.
Besides, Rush doesn't
need any protecting.
I just want that out there.
Let's put away the badges, huh ?
Sorry.
Always did take you three
drinks to loosen up.
How's your mother ?
She can't remember my name.
She spends her days
listening to the radio
and humming to herself.
Well, it happens.
When that day comes,
shoot me dead.
Here's to knowing when to fold.
It's been a long time, John.
Too long.
No hard feelings.
I wasn't a boy.
We both knew the game.
I wasn't the one married.
Ah, it would've ended, anyway.
Another one ?
I better not.
I don't wanna regret
anything in the morning.
I won't if you won't.
You know what ?
I'm toast.
Why don't you give me a ride home ?
I...
I'll call you a cab
Grab your keys and take me home.
Or I'll get one of these
other young bucks to do it.
Remember Preston ?
Hard guy to forget.
What'd he do ?
He was shot and killed in '82.
Must've rubbed the
wrong person the wrong way.
Preston wasn't half as charming
as he thought he was.
A little odd that Preston
gets shot and killed
and then a year later,
you get shot ?
Police said it was
probably a stickup.
Probably ?
Ah, I had to take
their word for it.
Why is that ?
Fifth of Old Crow,
half a dozen beeners,
a little herb to even it all out.
One minute I'm sailing,
the next minute
I'm waking up in the hospital
and they're telling me
I'll never walk again.
You don't remember anything ?
I got whole years missing, lady.
Cops said I was in a bad
hood trying to score.
Sounds good to me.
It's like the hand of God just
came down and gave me a crack.
Just changed your ways, huh ?
Been clean and sober ever since.
Of course I, uh, can't walk.
But that is a small price to pay
for getting me off
the road I was on.
You and Preston work
for a repo company ?
Hmm, just me.
Recession was good for business.
I had so much work,
I'd toss Preston a couple of bucks
now and then to give me a hand,
especially if I was
in a bad neighborhood.
Why is that ?
People don't exactly invite
you in for milk and cookies
when you're taking their car
or their color TV.
You guys ever get into
it with a customer?
Oh, from time to time.
Mostly words. Well, maybe a vet
or, you know,
a guy in the military.
One guy I remember.
Intense son of a bitch.
"Even the losers" by Tom Petty.
Come on, man.
Hey! What the hell do
you think you're doing?!
You're behind six
months on your payments.
Just doing our jobs, man.
Oh, what, take things
that don't belong to you?!
The car belongs to the bank now.
Come on, man, I need that
car to get to my job.
Here's an idea.
Get a bus pass.
I was gonna pay.
Come on, I can't afford
to lose this job, guys.
Unless you can pay
the delinquent amount
in full right now...
Times are tough, boudreaux.
Knock it off, Preston.
Hey, you serve ?
Yeah, what about it ?
First Division, Bravo Company.
So, we're supposed to give
you the Semper Fi break ?
Can't do that.
Look, I come back empty-handed,
guess what? I lose my job.
Come on, I'm trying real hard
here, man. Try harder.
Back off ! Stop it !
Hey, hey, stop !
Stop ! Hey !
Someday somebody's gonna take
something from you, pal.
Something real important.
And you're gonna remember me
- when that happens.
- Go back inside.
You wait.
You're gonna get yours, boudreaux.
Marines don't make idle threats.
They take action.
He was pretty steamed,
but, uh, this was years
before I got shot.
- You remember a name ?
- Just the car.
Ford Torino.
Must've been '76 or so.
Boss...
Boss, pulled repo company records.
A dozen cars match
Hudson's description.
We cross-referenced
the names with Philly
Savings and Loans records,
got a hit.
Bill Shepard, ex-Marine,
served in Vietnam.
Well, he knows his
way around a gun.
Owned the Darby View Drive-In.
Tried to get a loan.
Connected to every victim
except the bus driver
and Mel Shaver.
Shepard went off the
grid in the '80's.
No credit card statements,
zero bank activity.
Yates ran the name
through the FBI database
and got a hit.
Lifetime subscriber to The
Long Rifle Review.
That a crime?
Post-Oklahoma City,
gets you on a watch list.
Searching tax records trying
to track down an address.
Rush located his son, Paul Shepard.
A month overdue.
And it's my fault I
gotta charge late fees.
Agent Yates.
This is Detective Rush.
Looking for your father,
Bill Shepard.
Well, that makes two of us.
You're gonna have to
do better than that.
What's this about ?
Your father's a suspect in a
series of unsolved shootings.
What ?
He in contact with you ?
He ran off and left
me when I was 14.
Had to go live with my aunt
and uncle in New Jersey.
- Just took off ?
- Lost everything.
A drive-in ?
Yeah, pretty good business
back in the '70's.
Then they started
opening multiplexes.
- He try to hold on ?
- For a while.
He loved that place.
He used to love watching
people watch movies.
It looks like you caught the bug.
Well, it was hard not to.
You know, my father was
his own worst enemy.
He should've sold the place.
Instead, the bank took it.
So, what did he do after
he lost the drive-in ?
He started drinking.
I still remember the day
the dad I knew was gone.
"Kid" by The Pretenders.
How you folks doing today ?
Going to the park.
Nice day for it. SHEPHARD: Yeah.
You need a little more.
Come on, you know me.
NORRIS: Sorry.
Full fare required for rides.
Those are the rules.
can anyone spot me 50 cents ?
Come on, man.
Don't embarrass me
in front of my boy.
- It's okay. We can walk.
- No, it's not okay, son.
I've got my other
passengers to take care of.
I'm sorry, sir.
There's nothing I can do for you.
You're going to throw
me off the bus ?
I need you to step out.
Look, you can get a free
bus pass at the shelter.
A month later he said
he was going up north
to look for a job at a mill.
That the last you saw of him ?
He was never mean
or anything like that.
Just...
broken.
That the number six bus ?
I think so.
He used to take it all the time.
Well, that driver was
shot a couple years later.
So, back then,
you think that my father...?
We think he's still out there.
We'll put a tap on your phones,
in case he tries to reach you.
Excuse me.
You know, I-I haven't seen or
heard from him in 30 years.
Anyplace he might've gone to?
I-I spent half my life trying
to forget what happened.
Traced his V.A. checks to a P. O. box
in Mount Pocono.
The clerk there's pulling
up a home address.
Let's go.
The guy we're looking for is Walt.
Postal clerk for 40 years.
Bill Shephard still rents a box?
Yeah, all rentals have
physical addresses on file.
Clerk said he just needed
to locate the records.
A good place to hide out from
the world and plot your revenge.
Walt ?
FBI. We spoke on the phone.
Pretty lady...
Get him.
I got you covered.
Let's get him out of there.
- You got him ?
- Yeah.
We need backup now !
Hold on. Hold on !
We got an eyewitness
saw a black Chevy van
speeding away after the shooting.
What about the postal clerk ?
Critical.
Ugh, here come
the FBI stormtroopers.
Hey, John, I'll keep
you out of this.
Keep me out of what?
I wasn't exactly cleared
to work this case.
What ?
Hey, Ryan.
How's your mother ?
Forgot how charming
you could be, Ryan.
And I forgot how reckless you could be,
Special Agent Yates.
Told her section boss she
was on her way to Philly
to look after her sick mother.
I know, I stepped in it.
Now, is that an apology ?
I'm sorry for being
right about this guy.
I can see that.
Now, I'm sure the family
of the postal clerk will understand.
John Stillman, Philly PD.
Ryan Cavanaugh.
Special Agent in charge.
Detective Lily Rush.
Agent Yates had no authority
to investigate this case.
You had full knowledge
of my interest in this case.
Over here, Yates.
You breached protocol,
misled a major metropolitan
police department.
Do you rehearse this, Ryan?
A man is in critical condition
who was in the presence
of an FBI agent
and a police detective.
That's a page one screw up, Yates.
You want to hang me out
to dry ? Do it.
But you're going to need them
if you want to catch this guy.
We've already coordinated
with the state police.
Yeah, SWAT teams are on their way.
Philly PD can assist,
provided everything goes
through our command.
I need to debrief you.
Now.
Could've told me the truth, Diane.
I'll liaison with the Feds--
make sure we don't
get pushed aside.
We'll head to the hospital,
wait for the clerk.
Still in surgery, last I heard.
Well, guy must have known something
our killer didn't want
anybody else to find.
Well, if he pulls through,
we'll question him.
Get him to I.D. Bill Shephard.
What he looks like now.
At what point did you decide
you could just run your
own investigation, Yates ?
That day in your office, Ryan.
When you were too busy
to hear my evidence.
What is it with you and this case ?
Detective.
Agent.
Might want to use the sink.
Got blood on your hands.
Thanks.
- Lieutenant Stillman.
- Yeah ?
We got a location on
the suspect's van.
You're welcome to ride along.
Let's go.
Honey, you can flash all
the badges you want at me.
CIA, NSA, FBI.
The answer's no.
Important to speak to him
the minute he gets out of surgery.
Man lost a lot of blood.
He's flatlined once already.
Have a seat,
you read a Redbook and you
wait your turn.
Still got that blood on
your hand, Detective.
Uh, I was on my way when I realized
I have Agent Yates' cell phone.
Must've grabbed it
in the commotion.
Detective... do you mind ?
Sorry.
Sure.
Thank you.
********
I want to get back to the
part where you decide
to misrepresent the Bureau's
interest in this case.
Lieutenant Stillman
and I are friends.
I bet you are.
- Problem, Yates ?
- I got to hit the head. Oh.
Men's room is down that way.
What's going on ?
Found this in the clerk's truck.
I'm driving.
Are you family ?
Niece.
Is he going to make it ?
Best to say good-bye now.
He's conscious, but...
- Walt ? Is this him ?
- What the hell ?
Bill Shephard.
Is this the man with the P.O. box ?
Crash cart!
Come out of the vehicle,
with your hands up.
We have you surrounded.
Give this guy a wakeup call.
I got no movement.
Stand by.
Go !
Clear !
Clear.
Got no movement.
Negative contact.
This is it.
Can't believe we missed it.
We didn't.
I meant the FBI.
Clear right.
Clear left.
Looks like he's been here.
Here.
25.06.
Got to call this in.
No. In a minute.
It's been a long time since
anyone's been down here.
- You okay ?
- Yeah.
You smell that ?
Another victim.
Exit wound.
It looks self-inflicted.
Hand me that light.
Anything ?
William Shephard.
What the hell ?
"Let's Ride Into the
Sunset Together" playing.
Something the matter ?
I need to borrow your truck.
I don't understand.
Uh, is there something
I can help you with ?
********
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com