(whistle blows, crowd cheering)
................
This is a near-capacity crowd
at Fishtown Gardens tonight.
Dock rats taking on
the Manayunk Chieftains at home.
Vicious rivalry.
Lots of blood on the ice
tonight; two periods
of nonstop mayhem.
Deep in the third period,
chieftains 4-2.
Dock rats feeling the pain.
All right, Flanagan,
get in there.
- Try not to get hurt.
- Okay, coach.
Shorthanded Dock Rats subbing in
little Tommy Flanagan
at the point.
Stick handling up
to the hash marks.
Oh ! He just nailed him !
Stay down, you little pygmy !
Next time, it's your head !
Masters all over Flanagan !
Yet another penalty
on the chieftains.
Cross-checking;
two more minutes in the sin bin
for Cullen Masters.
"Ramblin' gamblin' man"
by Bob Segler.
Flanagan with a breakaway
on the power play,
All alone at the point !
Chance the Dock Rats have been
fighting for all night.
Is this Flanagan's moment ?
He shoots !
No ! That was a scoring
opportunity denied.
Flanagan !
Get your bony ass over here !
Wide open goal,
rookie mistake.
What the hell were you thinking,
Slap shot that close in ?
Get your head in the game !
I'm sorry, coach.
It won't happen again.
President Carter greeting
the U.S. miracle hockey team
at the white house today
following their
incredible upset victory
leading to a gold medal
over the heavily favored
russians.
Cullen Masters...
you ever heard of the guy ?
Who'd he play for ?
Manayunk Chieftains.
Atlantic seaboard
hockey conference.
Bush-league,
folded in '81.
What's his story ?
Well, charged
for a murder in 1980.
A hockey player
named Tommy Flanagan,
played for the
Fishtown Dock Rats.
Killed on the ice.
"Opposing defenseman,
booted out of the game,
threatens to kill the kid
in front of witnesses."
Yeah, Tommy's blood on
his jersey, no alibi.
Arrested him,
but the DA dropped charges.
So what, is he here to confess ?
Skated on this murder
once already.
You sure you want
to try your luck again ?
Night the U.S. hockey team
beats the russians in the olympics,
"miracle on ice",
my life goes to hell.
February 22,
the night Tommy was killed ?
Punk on a rival team
kept getting in my face.
He was five, five, a buck-fifty.
You outweighed him by what,
70 pounds ?
The kid didn't know
when to quit.
You're not making much of a case
for your innocence here.
Tommy got me kicked
out of the game that day.
I made a few threats.
You said you were gonna cave
his head in.
Pretty specific.
That night the U.S. Won,
hockey players were like gods.
Women were going nuts.
Even a goon like me.
Saying you got lucky ?
College girl from Spokane.
Brenda something.
Spent the night
in the back of her pinto.
Next morning, she splits.
Tommy turns up dead.
And you're on the hook
for murder.
Never went to trial,
but it didn't matter.
Everybody was sure it was me,
wouldn't let me live it down.
Look, I messed
a lot of things up.
This is the only thing
I ever did right,
my boy, Jason.
He's 11 now.
Wants to play hockey.
I sign him up.
Junior league asked me to leave.
Won't let him play 'cause
of what they say I did.
It broke his heart.
Well, there's always soccer.
Sad kid Ain't reason enough
to reopen a murder case.
I kept searching for the girl
from that night.
Internet, even hired a PI.
This "backseat Brenda"?
Lives in Maine.
Married, got kids.
Not too happy
about the phone call,
But she'll vouch for me
for that night.
Brenda Patterson.
Look at the file.
Pull the record.
Wasn't my stick killed him.
Whoever took Tommy Flanagan's life,
is still out there.
You find him, maybe my son
gets to believe
in his dad again.
Cold Case
Season 7 Episode 10
Iced
Checked on masters' story
with Brenda from Bangor.
Confirmed his alibi.
Still trying to shake the image
of that man
in the backseat of a Pinto.
So's she.
Country was taking it
on the chin in '80 :
Hostages in Iran,
soviets in Afghanistan,
double-digit inflation.
And then there was
"Miracle on ice".
David takes on Goliath,
and we come out with a win.
We sent amateur kids,
they sent pros.
Country got some
of its pride back.
Yeah, minor leagues
like the one Tommy was in,
Came and went
in the '70s and '80s.
A rough trade.
Aggressive hockey,
lots of fights.
This kid a little small
for that bunch ?
Little guys scrap
until they're hamburger.
Dougie Gilmour,
Theo fleury
in the punch-up in Piestany.
Nigel Dawes.
Rangers ? Screw that guy.
What'd the DA's office
have to say
about dropping
the case in '80 ?
Evidence against Masters
was circumstantial, hearsay.
36 hours in interrogation,
guy wouldn't crack.
Needed a confession
on a case like this
and they weren't getting it.
This murder happened late.
After the olympic game.
What's this kid doing
at the rink that hour ?
Somebody had to have access,
let him in.
Coach, janitors, zamboni guy.
Let's talk to them again,
see if their stories
Still hold up, find out
who else could've had a key.
Took his first hit in front
of the players' bench,
shattered the stick.
Couldn't get a clean print
off the murder weapon.
Sverre...
Brand's norwegian.
Nice gear.
That's a customized hand-carved
piece of wood.
Masters said
it wasn't his stick.
Cops never figured out
whose it was.
I'll run it through CSU.
See if we can get DNA.
Well, Tommy's older brother, Sean,
was pretty hot at Masters
after he got off.
- Hassled him for months.
- Let's talk to him first.
See what he knows
about this number.
Rangers.
So, um...
You find out about this weekend ?
Yeah, Veronica's
got a thing at school.
What about Tuesday ?
Cle review.
I think I'm supposed
to teach it.
I'll try to cancel.
No.
I can try to get a sitter.
Maybe Thursday ?
My favorite day.
Pick me up at 8:00.
Trying to tell me
That meathead son of a bitch
wasn't the one who killed him ?
Just asking if you know anybody
else had it in for Ttommy ?
Me and my brother
weren't real close.
We ran in different circles,
you know ?
This is the stick
that killed your brother.
Recognize it ?
No.
Asked me that back in '80.
It's, uh, high-end stuff.
It's got a really nice
curve at the toe.
- Sound like you know the game.
- Played center in high school.
Got blindsided on a motorcycle
and messed my leg up
and that was that.
Ma was sick.
Tommy was kind
of a layabout.
So someone had
to pick up the slack.
So how'd Tommy get into playing ?
Economy's in the crapper
and no jobs.
Local leagues'd spring up,
Started tossing pennies
to anyone who'd take a hit.
Fight club on skates.
Tommy wasn't really cut out for it.
I tried to warn him, but...
"Her strut" by Bob Seger.
Try this.
Good, right ?
Chicks love the sugar.
They can't taste the alcohol,
till "bam", it just hits 'em.
I don't know.
I mean, what do I say ?
Don't gotta say nothing,
that's the beauty of it.
Listen, all else fails.
Pick up a case of schenkers,
Get enough of that
Schuylkill swill in 'em,
they can't say no.
You are sick, you know that ?
Will you two marys
keep your voices down ?
You're gonna wake up ma.
Tell him, LT.
Dock rats are holding open
tryouts Tuesday.
Little Tommy's gonna
get on the ice.
Now, get serious, Tommy.
What're you gonna
hit them with, huh ?
Elfin magic ?
That's better than just giving up
like you did.
Are you trying to be funny ?
Look at you... a love tap
like that puts you on your ass,
But you're gonna go play league
hockey with these animals ?
Dock rats is no place for you.
It's just a goon squad
looking for cannon fodder
to draw penalties.
You're too little, bro.
So hit me again, sean.
You know I can take anything
you dish out.
'cause I'm still a Flanagan.
I don't know what got into him,
but he took it real serious.
Any idea what he was doing
on the ice that night ?
I don't know...
Practicing, maybe.
How'd he get into the rink
that late ?
Tommy's idiot friend, Dwight.
Two of them were
a regular frick and frack.
Dwight had a key made
so he could play asteroids
in the lobby all night.
He try out for
the Dock Rats, too ?
Dwight ? Please.
Ma on her deathbed
ran a quicker 40.
Closest he ever got was
dealing pot to the team.
Hey, buddy !
You want to pay for that
thing now that you got
the pages all sticky ?
Magazine racket
ain't what it used to be, huh ?
The frickin' internet.
Everybody thinks they can
get their jollies for free.
Well, what can I do for you,
blue eyes ?
Tommy Flanagan.
Remember him ?
Sure, Tommy was my boy.
Buds since the third grade.
Lost my best friend the night
that Masters tool took him out.
And where were you ?
Driving a snowplow.
There was a big storm
that night.
I was clearing
parking lots till dawn.
Anybody else come to mind
have a beef with Tommy ?
You saying Mmasters didn't do it ?
Saying we're looking into it.
Answer the question.
Could've been any one
of those guys on the team.
My stupid idea, him trying out
for those bunch of thugs.
And you'd know--
dealing weed and pills to them.
Whoa, wait. You know,
so I did a little business.
I mean, come on,
the economy sucked.
You had your own key
to the place.
Come and go as you pleased.
So did half the team.
Let me tell you something.
Those characters
were marginal to begin with.
And everybody likes
an underdog,
until he starts making
them look bad.
"Rock'n Roll Never Forgets"
by Bob Seger.
Let's go, Tommy !
That's my boy out there,
in the blue. See him ?
Little Tommy.
The shrimpy guy ?
I thought he was a mascot.
Check out Charlie Hustle.
Scrub with the shiny, new skates.
Nice gear, little man !
That necklace
is beautiful.
What is that, lapis ?
Matches your eyes.
Say, you two ever
do any modeling ?
Whoops, there they go!
Hit him, Tommy !
Hey, that's enough !
That's enough !
Come on !
That's enough ! Hey ! Hey !
You got my attention.
Krause, hit the showers.
Hit the showers !
Get done,
see me in my office.
They all said Little T
pushed to hard.
He never knew
when to dial it back.
The ass-clown who picked
the fight, he get cut ?
Krause.
He was too old to be taking
the kind of hits
that league dished out.
Always shying away
at the boards.
Coach put him out to pasture.
Yeah, and he gave Tommy
his spot on the line.
Krause, you know,
He... He asked the coach
for, like, an assistant job,
but he had to settle
for equipment manager.
So his job to order the sticks
for the team ?
Messed with Tommy's gear, too.
Dropped his helmet
in the john one time.
The cops talked to you
back in '80,
never thought to mention this ?
They never asked.
And with a scumbag
like masters on the hook...
who's gonna listen ?
Ladies are bringing it !
Yeah, we got a shot at division II
championship this winter.
Work 'em harder,
see if they want it bad enough.
Work harder ?
Sounds like something
Tommy Flanagan might have said.
- Kid ever give you trouble, krause ?
- Tommy ? Nah.
Way we heard it, he took
your spot on the line
after you went to seed.
Little guy had no business out there,
but he played hard,
he sucked it up,
left it all on the ice.
Sounds like you respected him.
- I did.
- That why you dropped
a deuce in his helmet
back in '80 ?
We all hazed Tommy.
It wasn't personal.
Recognize this stick ?
Yeah. Sverre.
Too rich for that bunch
of gorillas.
We used koho 310s.
- Ever see tommy with it ?
- Not that I recall.
Look... Tommy wasn't
the one we hated.
Team had a common enemy :
it was coach Heaton.
"Roll Me Away" by Bob Seger.
Again !
Come on !
Pathetic !
Think that weak-ass drill will
hold up against Pittsburgh ?
Bunch of murderers...
Gonna chew you up
and spit you out.
Flanagan the only one with legs
that can finish that drill ?
He's half your size,
but he's got more heart
than any three of you pansies.
I'm not gonna come out here
and waste my time
If you're not gonna bring
your a game to the ice !
Do you hear me ?!
Flanagan !
What the hell are you staring at ?
Uh... Nothing, coach.
Sorry.
All heart, no skill.
All legs, no ability.
You know what that is ?
That's a one-way ticket
to craptown, son.
You just earned the team
another round.
On your feet !
Again !
Heaton was a sadist.
Played guys hurt,
burned them out, no mercy,
Like he got off on it.
What about this girl
in the stands ?
Guys called her "jailbait Molly",
coach's daughter.
Strictly off limits.
You ever see Tommy and this
jailbait Molly together ?
Yeah, once or twice,
chatting it up.
Looked kind of cozy to me.
Let's go, Julie !
Come on ! That's it !
Hey.
So, um, I got the sitter
for Veronica on Thursday;
we're set.
I-I thought you said Tuesday.
Thursday.
Your favorite day?
Curtis...
Let me call my sitter,
maybe switch.
No, it's okay.
I'm busy, you're busy.
- It's like pulling teeth getting
a few minutes alone. / - Yeah. Hello ?
Oh. Hang on.
N-no, not you.
No, no, this is a great time.
Sorry.
CSU got nothing off the stick.
No DNA other than
Flanagan's blood.
Sverre went out of
business in the '90s;
Composite sticks
started taking over.
Hundred-dollar sticks
were big bucks in 1980.
I'm gonna round up
local hockey teams,
see who was rocking
custom lumber.
Well, Heaton's coaching
the Jacksonville Manatees,
an away game in Trenton.
Big-time hockey there.
Said he was meeting
with the team owner
the night of Tommy's murder.
- Checking it out.
- Well, Rush's got his daughter Molly
in the boss's office, gonna see what
she and Tommy had going on.
229 background you filled out...
that's a lot of schools, Molly.
- Move around a lot as a kid ?
- Hockey brat.
Dad was always on the road,
from team to team.
Stayed in Philly to graduate,
never left.
All my friends were here.
All your friends,
like Tommy Flanagan ?
What do you mean ?
Well, you two, you know...
close ?
I didn't date hockey players.
Well, teammates said you two
were making eyes at the rink.
Your father have a problem
with that ?
It was fine for him to be out on the road
300 days a year with those idiots,
But god forbid one of them
holds the door open for me.
- His way of looking out for you ?
- I don't know.
Never was easy to read the guy;
gave up trying.
Think he was hard
on his players ?
Try being his daughter.
Any reason he'd be
especially hard on Tommy ?
Look, he was cute,
but dad didn't have anything
to worry about.
Tommy was focused on the game.
Besides, he had enough problems
without me adding to them.
"Night moves" by Bob Seger.
Hey, Molly !
Slap shot's coming along.
Yeah, I'm not sure your dad
would say the same thing.
You're still here, aren't you ?
Yeah, what's left of me.
I don't really know
what I'm doing out here.
Logging all these hours.
I don't know
if I'll ever be any good.
Yeah, you should probably quit.
Yeah. Maybe.
Are you going to that
new year's eve party,
Uh, over on Cumberland ?
Thinking about it. Why ?
Oh, no, I just was... wondering,
maybe... maybe...
Yeah, maybe... what ?
I don't know. Maybe I'd see you
over there or something ?
What the hell did I tell you ?!
I told you not to touch it,
didn't I ?
- Just checking the...
- Didn't I ?
Now you're out here
driving slap shots with it ?
Sean, I'm not...
You think I'm washed up, isn't it ?
You think I'm done ?
- No, sean, I don't...
- The stick's mine !
I catch you with it again, I'm
gonna take it upside your head.
You could smell the whiskey
coming off the guy ten feet away.
So Sean was still playing hockey
back then ?
You get a look at the stick ?
Not really.
But he definitely had that
washed-up jock thing going on.
I've seen my share.
You Valens ?
Yeah.
Pierson, central.
Got six messages asking
about a robbery pattern.
Listen, uh...
Dayley's market...
what do you got ?
Couple of similars
around the neighborhood,
same M.O.
Knockdown purse snatchings,
older female victims.
Any injuries?
Bumps and bruises;
nothing serious.
Well, what about leads?
Uh, description,
eyeballs, anything?
Usual mess...
he's black, he's white,
He's tall, he's a half-pint.
What's with you on this thing ?
Nothing. A case we got.
Just keep me posted, will you ?
Still gives you goose bumps, huh ?
Even my russian grandpop
went bonkers.
People forget
we still had to beat the Finns
just to get a medal.
What's this I hear about you
going back out on the ice again ?
Little pickup league.
Me and some guys
reliving our glory days.
You want to come ?
You ain't seen hockey
till you seen it live.
I'll have the EMT's waiting.
So Sean wasn't just good,
he was Sean
"the shamrock" Flanagan.
Real stud on ice
in Canada.
Champion center
in the AAA leagues.
Shot at the miracle team in '80.
"Stick and blade magazine,
March '79."
Take a look at the stick.
You see that ?
There it is.
A shamrock.
Luck of the irish
just ran out.
Impressive stuff, shamrock.
Most athletes, can't shut 'em up
about their glory days.
But you,
a champion...
not so much as a peep.
Why so bashful, Sean ?
Ancient history.
Everything I had got taken away.
Accident on your bike
in Calgary.
Blindsided, right ?
Shattered my femur.
Same night you found out
you were invited
to the olympic tryouts.
Could've been the only
Philly kid on the squad.
So close I
could taste it.
Night of the accident,
Your blood alcohol level
was a .16.
Witnesses say you were playing
chicken with a logging truck.
Wasn't an accident
benched you.
Just pure stupidity.
Is that you,
with the stick
that killed your brother?
Same stick you said
wasn't yours ?
I never wanted to see
this damn thing again.
The night I crashed...
this stick survived the impact
that ended my career.
Not even a scratch on it.
Killed my brother.
Thing is cursed.
Stick didn't ice your brother
on its own, Sean.
Somebody swung it.
Not me.
Didn't want to admit it then,
but it was Tommy's time.
Idiot Dwight called
for you again.
I'll catch up with him
after the game.
Are you coming today ?
Ma's not doing good.
Needs me here.
Hey, Tommy.
Alberta...
Final 20 seconds of the game,
I get a clean breakaway.
Mancuso's in the goal and...
Man, I don't even know how
it happened, I just...
I moved my hands,
you know, and this stick
put it in the twine.
Won the championship.
That's yours now.
Sean, you're gonna need that,
you know, when you get back to Calgary.
It ain't gonna happen.
It's over, Tommy.
Look, it's your time now,
bro, okay ?
Take it.
Stick didn't win
that game, Sean.
It was all you.
I'll tell you what.
You girls win today,
I'll catch your next home game.
Maybe even bring ma.
Now go on, get out of here.
I wanted to watch the olympics
with him that night.
But he said he had plans.
You never mentioned these plans
to the police.
Just figured he'd blown
me off for the team.
Like maybe they accepted him.
I used to love that game,
you know ?
Give anything to get back
on the ice with my brother...
Just one time.
Thanks, Michelle.
Scotty, you should
eat something.
You look thin.
Listen, I've been
looking into things
up at dayley's market.
Scotty, I told you alread...
Ma, I know what
happened to you.
The guy knocked you down,
took your purse.
Did you get a look at him ?
It was my fault.
Walking out,
I knew something was off.
I feel like a fool.
Had to cancel all my cards.
It's not your fault.
It just happens.
You don't got time
to react.
No. Your father...
He'd have gone crazy
if I told him.
Never let me
out of his sight.
No, pops don't need to know.
But, ma, look,
I need you to help me
stop this guy
From hitting
anybody else.
I have some mug shots
I need you to look at.
Oh, mijo,
it all happened too fast.
I didn't see him.
I want to help you...
... but I can't.
Your boys are roughing up
Trenton tonight, huh ?
14 and six, hungry season.
This kind of distraction's
hard on them.
Since when do you care
about your players ?
Drive them hard,
burn them out, move on.
Yeah, made a career of it,
starting with the dock rats
in '80.
Don't run games
that way anymore.
A different time,
a different game.
So the night
of the miracle on ice,
remember where you were ?
Meeting with the owner,
ran long.
Future of the team was at stake.
See, that's strange,
Because we checked
with his secretary.
Said the team owner
was on a plane
back to Boston
early that night.
A snowstorm was blowing in--
flew out to beat it.
Missed the miracle.
Must have mixed up my times.
That's not the only thing
about that meeting you got mixed up.
Like trying to get Tommy
kicked off the team.
Now hold on.
No, owner said no way.
That Tommy had spunk.
The kid was a draw.
You were pissed.
The next day, Tommy's on ice,
and you're lying
- about what you were doing.
- I don't have to listen to this.
How come you don't talk to
your daughter anymore, coach ?
Molly.
Hard as I was on my players,
I was tougher on her.
Or after you iced her boyfriend,
the two of youse
had a falling out.
Rules on Molly were clear,
but Tommy was violating
the policy.
You couldn't get
rid of him one way,
time to run a different play.
- One that ends with him dead.
- You got it wrong.
Any player I wouldn't have
minded seeing Molly with,
It was Tommy.
Kid had more guts
than any guy I ever coached.
"Fire down below" by Bob Seger.
We are scoreless
and down to the last two minutes
of the third period.
Both teams fighting it out
back and forth.
Nothing in the twine.
Oh, and yet another
illegal hit
from Cullen Masters.
I'll tell you,
that's going to draw a penalty.
You're throwing me out
'cause this little freak ?!
Get up, punk !
Catch you alone,
I'm gonna kick your candy-ass!
Cullen Masters ejected
from the game.
And none too soon.
Tommy Flanagan will get
the penalty shot.
Once chance, Tommy.
Can you do this ?
Yeah, coach.
I got it.
Flanagan shoots.
He's got it !
And he scores !
Little Tommy Flanagan scores !
One nothing at home,
Dock Rats take it !
Little Tommy Flanagan.
Unbelievable !
He is truly...
a hometown hero !
I put him on the spot,
he delivered.
Tried to get him released
from the Dock Rats
to offer him a better shot,
A better shot ? How ?
A coach at Powell university
lost its
First line to injuries.
Tommy could have subbed.
Division II hockey.
A shot at college.
Well, what about Tommy
and Molly ?
Anything going on with them,
I didn't know about.
But I wouldn't have
stood in the way.
A little gap
in Molly's school records.
What's wrong with this picture ?
Her graduating class, 1980.
December, 1980.
Seven months later
than everybody else.
Straight "A" student...
how does that happen ?
Three days after
Tommy was killed,
Coach shipped her off
to st. Emily's in Lancaster.
That's where good unwed catholic
girls go to have babies.
No one's supposed
to know about.
So Tommy and Molly
weren't just close.
She was pregnant.
And coach covered it up.
No wonder they don't
talk anymore.
Let's bring Molly back in.
Work both of them
till one of them cracks.
I have to say,
I kinda get what you saw
in Tommy.
Not a bad looking kid.
I told you
we weren't involved that way.
The Dock Rats said
you two were getting pretty close.
That is up until
Tommy got killed.
And you got carted off
the Lancaster,
in the middle
of your senior year.
St. Emily's.
Why there, Molly ?
Your daughter was pregnant.
You went out on a limb
for Tommy Flanagan.
- And this is how he pays you back ?
- The kid was a sniper.
He finds an opportunity,
he puts it in the net.
Molly never told me
who the father was.
But you knew,
didn't you, coach ?
He was ashamed of you.
He sent you away,
forced you to give up the baby.
He was my father.
He was protecting me.
No, he was trying to sweep it
under the rug.
Erase it from history
- by killing Tommy...
- You don't understand !
She wanted to give the baby up.
It was her choice.
You're saying you were fine
with her keeping it ?
Then ?
No.
If I could take it all back,
handle things differently,
I'd do it in a second.
But that night, when Molly
told you she was pregnant,
- you went to the rink.
- No !
I swear to you,
I did not kill that boy.
If I just told him the truth...
Maybe Tommy would
still be alive.
Told him what, Molly ?
About the baby.
What about the baby ?
It wasn't Tommy's.
Whose was he ?
Oh, God.
I'm so ashamed.
Yes ! Yes !
Yes ! Did you see that ?!
It's a miracle !
We won !
We just won !
Hey. Hey, come on.
We won.
What's wrong ?
Tommy, that party...
New year's eve...
I thought you were
gonna be there.
I waited.
He kept saying you were coming,
That you were his boy.
Wait. Who said that ?
I couldn't even taste
the alcohol.
Didn't realize
I was getting so
drunk.
He started
kissing me.
Oh, God, I let him !
Molly, who ?
Dwight.
It was Dwight.
Tommy,
I'm pregnant.
I tried to tell
him about it,
but he won't even
look at me.
Tommy, please,
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I broke his heart.
Mine, too.
After you told him, he left...
and headed back to the rink ?
Yeah. Said he needed
a place to think.
My dad came home,
he'd seen I was crying.
I told him I was pregnant.
And let him believe
it was Tommy's.
Had the baby that fall...
little girl.
Never found out
what happened to her.
But not a day goes by
I don't think of them both.
Molly, what name did you put
on the birth certificate
as the father ?
None.
I left it blank.
How's that look ?
Gotta fade the type
a little more.
Spill some
coffee on it.
Try this one.
I'll run it through
The copier again.
Snowplow owner confirmed
Dwight Bbarnes worked for him
until March of 1980.
"Fired for cause subcontracting
plow jobs to his 14-year-old brother."
For months.
Boss got wind when the kid
fell asleep at the wheel and
plowed into a dunkin' donuts.
So Dwight wasn't working
the night tommy was killed.
Remember a girl
named molly heaton?
Coach's daughter, right ?
Major babe.
You ever hook up with that?
I could've.
It's hard to say.
How's that work ?
You ply her
with the schuylkill swill
and quaaludes,
till she don't know
what hit her ?
Please. I had it
going on au naturel.
I didn't need
no chemical help.
Well, you must've peaked
in the '80s, Dwight,
'cause I just don't see it.
Now, Tommy,
that's different;
Athlete, star on the ice.
Little Tommy ? Come on.
Snakin' your
best friend's girl
WWhile he's not looking ?
What kind of loser move is that ?
I never tapped that girl,
all right ?
She shouldn't flatter herself.
Well, congratulations,
Dwight,
you're a father.
Whoa. Whoa, wait a minute.
You never hooked up with Molly ?
How's your name
on the birth certificate ?
What is it,
immaculate conception ?
The bitch is lying !
That's not my kid.
Not my kid, not my problem.
You banged Tommy's girl
to bring him down a peg.
Tommy was ducking
your phone calls.
Getting respect on the ice.
He had a shot to go to college,
a better life.
He was leavin' you
in the dust.
You had to put him
in his place.
That's crap !
You don't know jack.
Know it was your brother driving
the snowplow that night.
Your alibi? Just bit the dust.
And we know Tommy was pissed
at you for jumping on Molly.
And we got the DNA off the stick
that killed Tommy.
Gonna match yours ?
Well, you're gonna need
a sample from me, aren't you ?
No way.
It ain't gonna happen.
- You sure about that, Dwight ?
- Oh, yeah, I'm sure.
Because I know my rights,
and you've gotta have my consent.
Come here !
You just gave it.
Hey, you get out
in front of this,
ve'll talk to the DA,
tell him you cooperated,
and see what we can do.
Damn.
This whole Molly thing,
he couldn't let it go.
He hardly even knew
the girl.
You and Tommy were pals
long before that, right ?
That's what I'm saying.
I just went there to talk.
He acted like
he was better than me.
Figured I'd find you here.
Some win, huh ?
Chicks are going ape out there.
Maybe even get you laid.
Miracles happen, right ?
What the hell is wrong with you ?
Molly.
I know what you did, Dwight.
Tommy, listen...
- You knew I liked her, man.
- Come on, lt ! I told you
chicks respect guys who step up,
pull the trigger.
She's pregnant, dwight.
Come on.
That kid could be anybody's,
sporty little slut like that.
What the hell, Tommy ?!
What are you,
like some big shot now ?
Wouldn't be out here
if it wasn't for me.
Man, just get out of here.
Get out of here.
Oh, play a few hockey games,
now all of a sudden
you're too good to call me back ?
Blowing me off ?
Loses the girl.
Well, boo-hoo !
Now Little Tommy's
gonna judge me.
Little Tommy, tell me
how to live my life ?
Tommy ?
I ain't Little Tommy no more !
You don't get to call me that !
Everybody always
calls you a tool,
and I'm the only one
that sticks by you !
The only one !
Let you push me around,
I play your wingman,
for this ?!
They're right about you...
You're nothing but a loser.
Take it back, LT.
That kid is better off
not knowing the truth
about you, anyway.
Take it back, Tommy !
Take it back !
You're a loser, Dwight.
You always will be.
"Against the wind" by Bob Seger.
* Seems like yesterday *
* But it was long ago *
* Janey was lovely *
* She was the queen of my nights*
* There in the darkness
with the radio playing low *
* And the secrets that we shared *
* Mountains that we moved *
*Caught like a wildfire out of control*
* Till there was nothing left to burn *
* and nothing left to prove *
* And I remember
what she said to me *
* How she swore
that it never would end *
* I remember how she held me,
oh, so tight *
* Wish I didn't know now
what I didn't know then *
* Against the wind *
* We were running against the wind *
*We were young and strong*
* and the years rolled slowly past *
* and I found myself alone *
* Surrounded by strangers
I thought were my friends *
* I found myself further and further
from my home *
* And I guess I lost my way *
* There were, oh, so many roads *
* I was living to run
and running to live *
* Never worried about paying
or even how much I owed *
* Moving eight miles a minute
for months at a time *
* Breaking all of the rules
that would bend *
*I began to find myself searching...*
- Sous-titre non traduit -