the following story is fictional
and does not depict any actual person or event
*******04.06,1998
Guarda Costa!
This is the United States Coast Guard.
You've entered US waters.
You will be arrested.
Coast Guard officials
have confirmed
these men are indeed Cuban rafters
trying to reach dry land.
They've spent days,
even weeks of drift,
navigating through
turbulent shark-infested waters.
According to wet-foot/dry-foot law,
cuban rafter arrested
before reaching dry land
will immediately be sent back
to Cuba.
Should they reach dry land,
they will be granted asylum.
Looks like the last one
is turning himself in now.
Dry land just a few feet away.
Gonzalo Luque trying to steal home.
He dives ! And he's safe !
**********
My name is Jaime Reyes.
And for those who know a little
about Cuban baseball,
this is Gonzalo Luque,
the Cuban Mickey Mantle.
And I'm happy to announce
that he has just signed
with the Philadelphia Phillies
organization,
and he will report
to the Reading Phils
next week.
Gonzalo would like to say
something.
Hello, America.
Thank you.
And I want to play baseball.
ICE agent says this guy's got
information
on a cold job, october '99.
Those are all the possible matches.
A couple of gang shooting,
robbery gone bad.
And two stone-cold who dunits.
- This guy fishing for a deal ?
- Aren't they all ?
Agent Scarcelli, Immigrations
and Customs Enforcement.
Eddy's in our country uninvited.
He got popped for an electronics store
smash-and-grab
along with cannabis possession.
The smoke was for religious purposes.
Let me guess : you're looking at a
boat ride back to Port-au-Prince.
Yes,sir.
Eddie'd rath spend a month
in lockup here
than go back to the Haitian clink.
Look,I testify,I get to stay,right?
- Depends what you got.
- It was October...
Pretty good memory
with all that
praying you be doing, Eddie.
It's the truth.
I remember because of the pumpkins.
Start with location.
That sandlot near Lancaster Avenue.
Wrong answer.
We got no unsolved murders that area.
I warned ya about wasting my time.
It was that baseball player.
He was going to play for the Philes.
Guy's nameas Gonzalo Luque.
Only problem, Eddie,
is Gonzalo was killed about five miles
from Lancaster Avenue.
Body was found in the Badlands.
That's not what I saw.
Yo, man.
I come out, the body's gone.
You couldn't swipe Jesus,
so you settled for the
Louisville slugger?
You see the car?
No.
- What about the b
- Perfectly good bat.
I give it to my nephew Patrick.
He hit real keen with it.
Bring us the bat,
we'll see what we can do about
prolonging your jail time in America.
Play ball.
COLD CASE
Saison 6 Épisode 20
Transcript VO : www.ydy.com
Stealing home
Gonzalo Luque, 23 years old.
Found dead in an alley off Elkhart
in the Badlands,
morning of October 22, 1999.
Cause of death :
blunt-force trauma
to the chest
resulting in cardiac arrest.
Assigned back in the day figured
that 'hood,
Gonzalo was looking for drugs,
guns, or tail.
Played for Double-A Reading.
Guy could rake.
Big league club invited
him to spring training.
Yeah, he'd have won a ring last season.
The bat Eddie the Haitian
says was next to the body.
Bat could be a good match for
the contusion that killed him.
Initls: "ST."
The proffer was asked out that.
He said the letters
were there already.
Lumber could belong to
one of his teammates.
Nobody with those initials
on the team.
So now we got a dead baseball
player's body
being moved across town.
Maybe our doer didn't want
the lot connected to the body.
I didn't even know there
was a baseball diamond there.
Detective back in '99
spoke to Jaime Reyes,
Gonzalo's agent and a cousin,
Juan de la Cruz.
Says here Gonzalo's wife Piedad
and son Andres
washed near Key West day
after his murder.
Wanna double-check thastory
along with this cousin.
Find out what Gonzalo
was doing on that field.
I'll see what the agent
remembers.
Guy makes it all the way from
Cuba, ends up ad in an alley.
Oh, Cuban Pete's all over this one.
Yeah, well...
I'm half Puerto Rican.
Maybe the doer's Puerto Rican.
All right, everybody, listen up !
Sign-up sheet for
the annual softball game
against the fire department.
We won't get hosed
like we did last year.
To that end, I've got a ringer
in Patrol.
The guy is unhittable.
Been a rule change this year :
mandated coed teams, so...
- Sounds good.
Sign me up.
Can you catch ?
Hell, yeah, I can catch.
You throw like a girl ?
You dance like a white guy ?
All right, pencil ya in alternate : bench.
You throw like girl ?
- ya.
- Catch ?
- Not so much.
- All righ you're our catcher.
And you're riding bitch with
me all the way to Union City.
Located the victim's wife,
Piedad Luque.
All right.
See ya later, Mom.
Make sure you take the bus back.
I don't wanna hear about
you cutting through the park.
Okay.
Andres, ven aca.
Please, sit.
Does Andres know the circumstances
around father's death?
No.
I never believed what they said
Gonzalo was doing in that part of town.
He was a family man.
Wondering how Gonzalo could leave
you and your son back in Cuba.
He had no choice.
None of this would have happened if
they didn't taken baseball away from him.
Who's "the" ?
The Cuban government.
They said he and some other players
had contact with an
American sports agent.
That agent Jaime Reyes ?
Yes.
After the ban,
it was a nightmare.
No money, no food,
no friends.
That why Gonzalo left,
to make a new start ?
Hardest decision of his life,
but once he'd made it,
there was no turning back.
*******03.20,1998
***
*********
And that was it.
The last time I saw him.
You had plans to join him ?
When the time was right.
Hell of a raft trip.
Would have done anything
to see him again.
You stay in touch with him
when he got to Philly ?
It wasn't easy.
Our phone calls were monitored ;
letters opened.
He mention any problem
to you ?
No.
Juan said Gonzalo was very excited
we would be joing him in America...
Juan, his cousin.
Yeah, he was my cousin.
But Gonzalito was more
like... like my little brother.
I came to-to America... two
months before he was killed.
Juan, where were you
the nigth Gonzalo was killed ?
You guys are not
Internal Revenue, huh ?
I was, I was removing asbestos,
off the bo at Liberty Towers.
I worked my way up since then.
You ever go to that old sandlot
near Lancaster Avenue with Gonzalo ?
Lancaster Avenue ?
Yeah lot of pickup baseball games there.
Familiar with it?
Not that one. But Gonzalito--
he-he loved baseball.
He would see a game and...
stop to ask if he could play.
He always had his equipment
with him.
Is this Gonzalo's bat ?
No, not Gonzalo's.
It's too heavy.
He was a contact hitter.
He could put the ball anywhere.
You know anybody
with those initials ?
No.
You play ball ?
A little in Cuba.
Pero olvidate-- when I
got here, it was all work.
Did youu happen to see Gonzalo
the day he died ?
I was busy working.
He was training hard.
Getting ready for spring
training in October ?
It what he loved.
Couldn't believe all the things
this country had given him.
"537 Cuba" by Orishas.
Oye,take off that garbage, huh ?
**
*****
Mira.
Take what you want, primo.
- Primo...
- It's all yours.
Oye,can't have you looking
fresh off the boat.
You hungry ?
**
You see this one ?
This one's reserved for the day
that Cuba's free of its oppressor.
May it be soon... and may it be painful.
Amen.
Juan de la Cruz, welcome to the
land of the Yankee imperialistas!
Traidor...!
..............
I still have that champagne.
It won't be be the same when
I can finally open it.
**
On my father's side.
I was born here,though.
******
**
Heo ? Chicos..... Gringa.
No how much money did Gonzalo
tends to make when he got called up, Juan ?
Gonzo made seven dollars a
month playing baseball in Cuba.
He had no idea about millions.
His,uh, agent managed everything.
Jaime Reyes ?
And his agent managed
his money, too ?
After he died, Reyes tried to screw
Piedad out of what money was left.
Detectives.
Bourbon water ?
No. We have so questions about
your former client Gonzalo Luque.
We spoke to Gonzalo's widow.
She said it was your contarcect with him
that got him banned
from baseball in Cuba.
I offered him freedom
and a better way of life.
And what'd you offer
his widow after he died ?
Everything Gonzalo had left,
which wasn't much.
He did what they all do :
fancy cars, nice clothes,
jewelry.
We understand you managed his money.
I run a full-service agency.
There's a problem ?
His widow thought that he should've
been more of that money left over.
Piedad never quite
grasped the probate proces.
Exactly how much did she grasp ?
Lay the money out for us, Jaime.
I'm gonna have to find Gonzalo's
records. It could take a day or two.
I put everything in off-site storage
when we moved to our new offices.
Well, you've done quite well
for yourself.
I started with a desk in my garage.
Cuban players are good for business.
Well, now, yeah, but..
Gonzalo was my first.
With his skills in today's market,
forget it, you're talking about
top-of-league money.
Watch this. Watch this.
"Que Bueno Baila Usted"
by Beny More.
Savage,Gonlo,savage!
It's hard for a guy like that
to see someone who's been touched
by the baseball gods.
- Who's he ?
- Eric Hynes.
He got demoted to right field
to make room for Gonzalo.
That's him on the right.
This Hynes ever make it to the bigs ?
No.
No, he popped a domestic
assault charge.
And he was arrested for waving
a gun around in a nightclub.
Eric "showtime" Hynes.
Showtime ?
ST. Same initials on the bat.
Nothing like having
a signed murder weapon.
Hell, ah, I remember Gonz.
Boy had wheels in center field.
Shame he got killed like that.
Killed like how ?
Messing where he was messing.
You mean the Badlands or
that sandlot by Lancaster Avenue?
You trying to cross me up
or something ?
You're still on probation.
Getting ready to start a hitting clinic.
Pass on my technique to
disadvantaged youths.
Oh, domestic assault ough to go
over big with the baseball moms.
Yeah, why don't you give us
some pointers on...
How you take out
your competition, showtime.
Where'd you get that stick ?
At the crime scene.
The giveaway...
the "ST" right here.
Technically,"showtime's"
one word, Einstein.
May time to change your name to Jailtime,
just to get a jump on things.
I gave that to him.
Told him he could grow into it.
You and Gonz buried the hatchet.
That's rht.
To tell you the truth,
I always felt
a little guilty when..
heard they thought he was uptown
looking for a little something something.
You introduce him to some
of your bad habits ?
Nah, Gonz was a pretty
straight arrow.
I just showed him how to roll.
Hey,Ha.
Want a nipple for that
Cuba Libra nursing there?
We call it a mentira.
Translation, Havana.
It's a lie.
Cuba's not libre.
Hey, how about that ?
That's Marisol.
Mm, she's bringing it tonight !
You want to take a cut at that, Papa ?
No, I'm okay.
Uh, no, you ain't.
What you need is a dip
in the Caribbean.
What's up, E ?
Hey, Marisol, Marisol !
I want you to meet my man here
from Havana.
Gonzalo.
Marisol.
Yeah, Gonzalo here is fresh off the boat;
he needs someone to talk to him
in his native tong.
*******
Oh, my man !
"How do you want it ?"
by 2Pac.
Marisol had an eye for the guys
who were gonna pull down the coin.
You know he had a and kid
back in Cuba ?
He never told me about that.
Gonz was real lonely.
Marisol help relieve him of some
of that loliness on a nightly basis.
You see them together
before Gonzalo was killed ?
I don't exactly recall.
How about you ?
How about me what ?
Where were you the night Gonzalo
got killed, October 21 ?
Fall of '99...
I was patroling center field
for the Taipei Gida.
Had a nice little run over there
in Taiwan...
till I snapped a hammy.
Son of a bitch !
There he goes again,
direspecting the furnishings.
I lost my ringer.
Turns out the guy's wife works for
those fire-dousing ferries,
and she treated to cut him off
if he pitches for us.
Slow or fast pitch?
Slow.
I played a little beer league.
Called me the Golden Arch.
Let's see it, Mickey D.
Ready ?
We'll see you on the field.
Marisol, your name came up
in an investigation.
Gonzalo Luque.
Like a decade ago,
I've moved on.
Heard you had a thing
for ballplayers.
In our line of work,
we get badge bunnies.
Not into cops.
Too controlling.
That's a shame.
Gonzalo another notch
on your bedpost ?
Okay, what is this about ?
Your boyfriend's found dead, and you
don't come forward with information.
He wasn't my boyfriend.
Well, then, maybe another player
in your roaster
took exception to the hours
you were keeping with Gonzalo.
I told you we weren't
together when he was killed.
It was complicated.
Uncomplicate it for us then.
Broke my rule...
and fell for the guy.
How come every time I ask you about
them, you change the subject ?
You know how things are over there.
I... want to know about my family.
Andrecito looks just like you.
**
***
I write, I call.
She's being careful.
- Things are not so easy for her.
- What ?
She... she's with someone else ?
She filed for divorce.
Gonzalito, what did you expect ?
I'm losing myself here, primo.
- I need to get my son back.
- No, no, no, Andrecito is just a kid.
It is too dangerous.
******
Nothing is impossible here Juan.
I'm gonna do what I have
to do to see my son.
He had this whole other
life I didn't know about.
They split up, but he wanted
to get his son back.
He still needed her
to bring him over.
Not what I signe up for.
That's when I knew it was over.
All right.
Agent Scarcelli's faxing me
Piedad's INS file.
Maybe shed some light on what happened
in Cuba between Piedad and Gonzalo.
They broke up.
He must have been
a pretty convincing guy,
get her chaperone his son
across the Florida Straits.
It's still a ticket out Cuba.
Can't say I blame her.
Ever been ?
Nope.
Don't you want to see it before
there's a Starbuck on every corner ?
I'll leave that to the tourists and
hipsters sporting Che T-shirts.
I know too much
about what happens there :
sip mimosas poolside in Havana.
Got something ?
Let me see Gonzalo's
immigration file.
Sunburned and blistered.
Look like she spent a week
at sea the way Gonzalo did ?
Not on a raft, she didn't.
More like overnight speedboat ride,
point-to-point.
Divorce wasn't the only
thing Piedad was lying about.
How was it you got to America,
Piedad ?
I told you already.
You also told us you
were married to Gonzalo.
Failed to mention that you
filed for divorce back in Cuba.
Neighborhood spies were watch us.
The divorce made it
easier for us to escape.
Or maybe you were pissed off
'cause he ditched you,
came to Amica, got rich and
dipp into who knows what ?
No.
When Gonzalo got suspended from baseball
in Cuba, it destroyed him.
He had to leave.
But you divorced him
after he defected.
I had no choice.
When Gonzalo came to America,
the government threatened
to take our house.
I was protecting Andres.
Divorce meant survival.
We're trying to solve
your husband's murder,
but you keep lying to us.
You look pretty good for
just coming off a raft, Piedad.
If you tell us again how you brought your
two-year-old on a 90-mile raft trip.
Andres is gonna come home to see
his mom being hauled away in cuffs.
- I was affraid...
- Of what ?
The man who brought us here.
********
***
****
******
********
**
***********
***
**
*****
****
**
********
****
Hello ? Hello ?
Gonzalo went to see this man.
In Miami ?
No.
He was in Philadelphia.
He arranged the whole thing ?
Yes.
You think this man killed
your husband ?
Yes.
We need a name, Piedad.
All I have is my son.
They already took Gonzalo.
- You want to be safe ?
- Yes.
You make this right and tell us
who did this to Gonzalo.
The men called him "Oz".
That's all I know...
internal recycling ?
Nope.
But an old CI of mine is.
Goes by Clifford.
- As in big red dog ?
- As in white boy with dreads.
Guy's a walking Ghetto pages of
the illegal import/export biz in Philly.
He collects cans on the side ?
Sells to the addicts after
they get their returnable money.
- Enterprising.
- Yo, Clifford !
They try to do me like Rodney King !
Shut it, Clifford.
If I stroke out,
the last thing I gonna do
is shoot your dumb ass !
Yo, blue, I ain't holding.
That's good 'cause we need
a name, Clifford.
Oh, snap !
You looking tight, baby girl.
- Didn't know it was you.
- Called me "baby girl" again...
I apologize for triculating.
Clifford is at your service.
Guy's name is Oz.
You heard of him ?
You trying to see the Wizard ?
Why didn't ya say so ?
Here to see the Wizard.
Grab the rack.
Come on.
Osmany Leon.
Take a walk.
Come in. Sit down.
Cafecito ?
We're here about Gonzalo Luque.
You smuggled his family
out of Cuba.
I don't even own a boat.
Fence, import/export contreband...
'cause I'm guessing fluff an' fold ain't
the one thing you were into.
I'm a legitimate busiman.
I'am a member of the
Chamber of Commerce.
Representing what ? The lollipop Guild ?
I'd hate to disrupt
your business here, Osmany.
Screw up your cash flow,
dinging your name on the street.
You gonna shut me down ?
Okay.
Or you could tell us why you held
Gonzalo's wife and kid
in a motel room in Miami
till he came up with more cash.
It's important to give
back to the community.
Reunite families.
Long as they pay the freight charge.
Sounds like Gonzalo
had a problem paying up.
Bish to D4.
Mate in two.
Nice.
I'm calling the cavalry.
Have 'em toss this place.
Gonzalo Luque and I
had mutual interests.
He wanted to get his family back
and I wanted to send a message.
Tranquilo.
I did what I was told, paid my money,
and now you tell me there was a problem ?
These are the people that your friend
arranged for me to pick up.
Piedad and Andres.
And...
No, no.
- Where ara my parents
- You know those two ?
Teammates back in Cuba.
Look, this is a mistake.
I paid for my family !
That's right.
40,000 was the family discount.
Ballplayers are a premium.
Reyes never told me
about these players !
Well, that makes two of us,
Gonzalo.
You tell Reyes I need another 40K.
I want my family ! Desgraciado !
Oyame. I get my money and
you get your wife and son back.
The rest its between you and your agent.
Now, buena noches, Gonzalo !
Gonzalo wanted to
reunited with his family.
I respect that.
But Gonzalo thought Reyes was
gonna get his entire family over.
We were both being gamed.
Reyes came up with the money ?
That same night.
And I kept my word.
I released Gonzalo's wife and son.
Who were these players ?
I like to look at the box scores.
Lots of interesting information.
Those are some big names.
Gonzalo go to see Reyes ?
Wouldn't you ?
Come over if you want but...
The only thing
you have to worried about is...
I'm in the middle of something here.
Yeah, you were.
This guy takes a whole
lot more than ten percent.
Please !
Butch, give me five minutes,
okay ?
Signed for $6 and $8 million a piece.
That's a tiddy commission.
They were worth it.
Worth having Gonzalo's wife
and kid held for ransom ?
That's it. I'm calling my attorney.
Why ? Only thing you need to
worry about right now
is immigration violations.
But we'll leave that up
to the feds, huh ?
Unless you killed him.
Look. Gonzalo wanted
his familly here.
I said to him that I
was gonna take care of it.
I didn't want him getting
mixed up in that mess.
You mixed him up real good,
but you couldn't fool
the great and powerful Oz.
I was gonna fix it...
By stealing Gonzalo's money to
smuggle players out of Cuba
Big league talent. Can see why
you wanted those players so bad.
Baseball players are a
prized possession to Castro.
By liberating them, I stick it
to that bearded bastard.
You're a real freedom fighter.
Using Gonzolo's account
to stake your little empire.
Only one problem, Reyes.
You got caught.
I didn't kill Gonzalo.
But he wanted to kill me.
I trusted you, Jaime.
You're looking at this
the wrong way.
How else am I supposed
to look at it, huh ?!
My wife and son are being held hostage
and my parents are still in Cuba.
Don't worry about it.
We'll get 'em out.
And I'm gonna cut you in
on the deal.
Wrong. I'm cutting you out.
You fix this,
and then we're done.
Come on, Gonzalo. Gonzalo, don't.
Come on, Gonzalo.
I got a scout coming.
He's going to try out
your cousin.
We're gonna make it work.
I tried to tell Gonzalo but
he didn'd want to hear it.
I put the money back in his account.
His cousin Juan-- what did
he have to do with this ?
Juan was the first Cuban player
I ever tried to contact.
His fastball used to
top off at 95-plus.
His change-up
was a de-cleater.
- Used to ?
- Yeah,
by the time he came over,
the guy had lost it.
But Gonzalo idolized Juan.
k hands.
Nice.
Checked out Juan's story.
Got some major holes.
Starting with his immigration file.
Turns out,
Juan was on Gonzalo's raft.
Wet-foot/dry-foot.
Gonzalo reaches dry land
and stay,
Juan gets arrested in the water,
sent back to Cuba the same day.
Bet you that it was
warm homecoming.
16 months later,
Juan takes another raft,
lands on Key Largo.
Picked up along with five other rafters
begging for water at a tbar.
That and Juan's alibi has got
many holes as softball team.
Where'd you say
you were working again ?
The day Gonzalo was killed ?
Liberty Towers.
Construction a security.
I spoke to your boss.
Said you were working
a jobsite off Lancaster Ave.
Next to the lot
where Gonzalo was killed.
You think I killed him ?
Gonzalito was like my brother.
Didn't play just a "little" ball
in Cuba, either, Juan.
You pl with your cousin
in the Cuban League.
Right with the Industrials.
What did they call you ?
- ***
- The cannon.
Must have had a hell
of a fastball.
Till you and Gonzalo were
banned from playing in Cuba.
You were with Gonzalo
on that raft.
Gonzalo made it to dry land.
You didn't.
Got your repatriation order
from immigration.
April 6, 1998.
Gonzalo got to stay.
They sent you back.
You went back to Cuba as a traitor.
They threw you in prison, Juan.
This is my grandfather
and his older brother.
The revolution split 'em up.
One to Philly,
the other to Castro's jails.
Decades go by.
My grandfather gets word
from Cuba his brother's dead.
A month later,
my "abulo" is gone.
From what ?
Heart attack.
My father, workingstiff said,
"His heart didn't stop.
It broke."
What happens in Cuba
stays with us.
I know what they do
to traitors in prison, Juan.
Ballplayers ?
They ripple 'em.
Put you back out on the street,
as a warning the others.
It isn't just a game, is it Juan ?
If I would have just made it
that day... on the beach...
You'd be playing baseball
right now.
Gonzalo would still be alive.
All this time, we couldn't figure out
why his body was moved from that sandlot.
Then we realized, Epispal was only
a few blocks away.
You went to get the car.
You were trying to get
your cousin to the hospital.
I was trying to save him.
We know you didn't mean
to hurt your cousin.
You just...
lost control.
We're trying to help you here, Juan.
He didn't make it.
Eso, eso ! Juan.
The canon is resurrected !
I heard the canon from the car,
and I had to hit something !
What happened ?
*******
In Miami?
- SO
- ye,primo,congratulati
No. Reyes screwed me.
That son of a bitch-- he gave my
parents' spots a couple of ballplayers.
**
*****
He thougth I was stupid, but I took
care of it, got rid of him.
You did what ?
I fire him.
Reyes was gonna get me
a try out.
Scouts were gonna...
- Hermano, I'll get you the tryout and scouts.-
When they see your fastball...
Hey, man, you know what ?
This is your first out right now.
Now, give me the cannon.
Come on.
*****
I know you got it, man.
***
Juan ?
You okay ?
You need to warm up more.
Throw more pitches, man.
It's just that you don't know.
Don't know what ?
You don't know what
they did to me over there.
******
I'll pitch too, heh ?
Hey, Juan, man.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can !
Mira, primo, no importa.
Don't worry about, huh ?
- I'll take care of it, all right ?
- What are you going to take care of ?
Mi familia ?
My parents ?
Primo.
If it wasn't for me,
you wouldn't even be here.
Juan, what are you talking about ?
**
I built that raft !
I know that.
To get us here.
I know.
To get us here ! Us !
They sent me back.
- Everything's gonna be okay now, Juan.
- No, it's not !
It's not.
You want to know
what they did to me in there ?
Every time they broke my arm,
they laugh at me.
Se reyan de me !
We got a single,
and we got a triple !
And we got a home run !
- Juan... Juan.
- They took my arm.
They took my arm away !
I have nothing.
I have nothing !
No tengo nada !
Primo, no tengo nad...
Primo ?
Gonzalito ?
Gonzalito !
Primo. Primo...
Somebody help me !
Primo. Primo. Primo. Primo...
"Vida Mas Simple"
by Nil Lara.
................
* Un palmar Baion con
las brisas del mar *
* Y al amanecer
Se oy solo tranquilidad  *
* Tu latido pide volver.
Tierra de mi amor *
* Tu recuerdo vive sin poder *
* Oh, mi Dios,
Desde el cielo escucha mi voz *
* Cuanto mas tengo que
rezar pidiendo mi regreso y ? *
* Vida mas simple la de ayer *
* Vida mas simple la deyer *
* Un cafa Era al precio
de la amistad *
* Sin tener que hablar
se ofrecia una mano fiel *
* La ninez respetaba sin preguntar *
* Y siempre al comer *
* La familia unida en el hogar *
* Oh, mi Dios Desde el cielo
escucha mi voz *
* Cuanto mas tengo que
rezar pidiendo mi regreso y ? *
* Vida mas simple la de ayer... *
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly
Presents