So two years later,
there's a knock on the door.
Guy opens it,
and there is the snail,
who says, "What the heck
was all that about?"
I don't really get it.
Well, see, it took two years
for the snail to...
Not important.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
Where do you think this is going?
To be honest, I was hoping
at least second base.
You're so funny.
You're like a stand-up comedian.
A Jewish stand-up comedian,
that'd be new.
Actually, I think a lot of them
are Jewish.
No, I was just...
Never mind.
Look, Howard, this is our third date
and we both know what that means.
We do?
Sex.
You're kidding.
But I need to know
whether you're looking
for a relationship
or a one-night stand.
Just to be clear:
there's only one correct answer, right?
It's not like "chicken or fish"
on an airplane?
Maybe you need to think
about it a little.
It's not unheard of
for a one-night stand
to turn into a relationship.
Call me when you figure it out.
Three dates means sex?
Who knew?
Greetings, homies.
Homette.
Why are you back
from your date so early?
In romance, as in show business,
always leave them wanting more.
What exactly does that mean?
He struck out.
Episode 309:
The Vengeance Formulation
Sync: Jess, Lin
www.subbercafe.fr
Did either of you guys know
that three dates with the same woman
is the threshold for sex?
I've never had three dates
with the same woman.
With Penny and me,
it took two years.
Now that I think about it,
that was three dates.
Before you and Penny hooked up,
did she ask
for any kind of commitment?
No, she was pretty clear about
wanting to keep her options open.
I have something to announce,
but out of respect for convention,
I will wait for you
to finish your current conversation.
What are you talking about?
The cultural paradigm
in which people have sex
after three dates.
I see.
Now, are we talking "date"
the social interaction,
or "date" the dried fruit?
Never mind,
what's your announcement?
Oh, good, my turn.
Well, this is very exciting
and I wanted you to be
among the first to know...
I hear you're going to be on the radio
with Ira Flatow from Science Friday.
Thank you, Kripke, for depriving
me of the opportunity
to share my news with my friends.
My pleasure.
My "thank you" was not sincere.
But "my pleasure" is.
Let me ask you a question:
At what point
did National Public Radio
have to start scraping
the bottom of the barrel for its guests?
Don't answer.
It's rhetorical.
Why are you such a stupid head?
That is also rhetorical.
I'm sorry you had to hear that.
Are you really going to be on NPR?
Yes, they're interviewing me
by phone from my office,
regarding the recent so-called
"discovery"
of magnetic monopoles in spin-ices.
It's pledge week
and they're trying to goose the ratings
with a little controversy.
Very cool, congratulations.
Thank you.
My mother is very excited.
She's convening
her Bible study group to listen in,
and then pray for my soul.
I was on the radio once.
I called in
to Fever 104 FM New Delhi
and was the fourth person
to say the phrase that pays:
"Fever 104, aajke naye
acchha sangeetka ghar."
That means: "Fever 104,
home of the really
good current music."
It's much catchier in Hindi.
All right.
These are the talking points
for my NPR interview tomorrow.
I need to make sure
they're simple enough
for the less educated
in the audience to understand.
Howard, look this over
and tell me what's unclear to you.
Excuse me, I have
a master's degree in engineering
from the Massachusetts
Institute of Technology.
It required the completion
of 144 units of grad work
and an original thesis.
Look this over
and tell me what's unclear to you.
When Sheldon gives you homework,
you don't have to do it.
In fact, it's better if you don't,
or it makes the rest of us look bad.
Talk to me.
I'm sorry, just screwing with you.
Why haven't you called Bernadette?
Did she say something?
She said she hasn't heard from you
in a week. I thought you liked her?
I do, but she wants a commitment
and I'm not sure she's my type.
She agreed to go out with you for free.
What more do you need?
Look, Bernadette is really nice.
I just always thought
when I finally settle down
into a relationship,
it would be with someone,
you know, different.
Different how?
Well, you know, more like
Megan Fox from Transformers.
Or Katee Sackhoff
from Battlestar Galactica.
Are you high?
You'd have a better shot
with the 3-breasted Martian hooker
from Total Recall.
Okay, now you're just
being unrealistic.
Anyway, that movie was 20 years ago.
Imagine how saggy those thing would be.
Howard, you're going to throw away
a great girl like Bernadette
because you're holding out
for some ridiculous fantasy?
Hey, just because you settled
doesn't mean I have to.
Excuse me, I'm sitting here.
Hey, I did not settle for Leonard.
I mean, obviously, he isn't
the kind of guy I usually go out with...
you know, physically.
Again, I'm right here.
I do not judge a book by its cover.
I'm interested in the person underneath.
I am here, right? You see me.
I'm interested
in what's inside people, too,
but why is it wrong to want
those insides wrapped up
in, say, the delicious caramel
that is Halle Berry?
Yes, you're delicious caramel, too.
- I will tell you why it's wrong...
- Excuse me, may I interject?
What?
Biologically speaking,
Howard is perfectly justified
in seeking out the optimum mate
for the propagation
of his genetic line.
Thank you, Sheldon.
Whether it's in the interest of humanity
is an entirely different question.
This is Ira Flatow and you're listening
to NPR's Science Friday.
Joining us today by phone
from his office in Pasadena, California,
is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
This is gonna be a riot.
Thanks for being
with us today, Dr. Cooper.
My pleasure, Ira.
Now, let's talk about
magnetic monopoles.
Can you explain to our audience
just what a monopole is?
Of course.
First, consider
an ordinary magnet which has,
as even the most uneducated
in your audience must know,
two poles.
A north and south pole.
If you cut that in half,
you have two smaller magnets,
each with its own
north and south pole.
Dr. Cooper, I think there might be
something wrong with our connection.
No, I hear you fine.
As I was saying,
an ordinary magnet has two poles.
The primary characteristic
of a monopole
is that it has only one pole,
hence, monopole.
A requirement for string theory,
or M-theory, if you will,
is the existence of such monopoles.
I, myself, led an expedition
to the Arctic Circle
in search of said particles.
Kripke, I found the nozzle!
I'm going to kill you!
So nice you could
join me this evening.
You're looking lovely as always.
Thanks, Howard.
Always nice to be part
of your masturbatory fantasies.
Come on, Katee.
Don't make it sound so cheap.
Sorry, fiddling
with yourself in the bathtub
is a real class act.
Thank you.
So, shall we get started?
Sure.
But can I ask you a question first?
Do you want to play
Cylon and colonist?
No, I want to know why you're
playing make-believe with me
when you could be out
with a real woman tonight.
Bernadette?
No, I mean Princess Leia.
Of course Bernadette.
She's a wonderful girl
and she really likes you.
I know, but she's not you.
I'm not me.
The real me is in Beverly Hills
with a tall, handsome, rich guy.
- Really? Tall?
- Six-four.
You've got
a wonderful girl in your life,
and you're ignoring her in order
to spend your nights in the bathtub
with a mental image
and a wash cloth.
What are you doing in there?
I'm taking a bath!
I hope that's all you're doing!
We share that tub!
Don't remind me!
Oh, man.
All soaped up and no place to go.
How ya doin', buddy?
I was humiliated on national radio.
How do you think I'm doing?
Come on, it wasn't that bad.
What do you want?
We represent the Lollipop Guild,
and we want you.
Okay, so Kripke
played a joke on you.
It wasn't funny.
I thought it was funny.
You laughed.
Did you laugh?
I fell on the floor.
All right, he got you.
You can get him back.
I refuse to sink to his level.
You can't sink.
With all that helium in you,
you're lucky you don't float away.
Are you really admitting defeat?
I never admit defeat.
Good.
However, on an unrelated topic,
I'm never getting out of this bed again.
What if you could make Kripke look
even sillier than he made you look?
- I don't think that's possible.
- You're not helping.
I didn't come to help,
I came to mock.
What you need to do
is figure out a way
to exact vengeance
on Kripke, like...
like, how the Joker got back
at Batman for putting him
in the Arkham Asylum
for the Criminally Insane.
He didn't just talk about his feelings
with the other psychotic villains.
He broke out and poisoned
Gotham's water supply.
Well...
I suppose I could poison Kripke.
It's a simple matter.
There are several toxic chemicals
that'd be untraceable in an autopsy.
Okay, uh, that's the spirit,
but let's dial it back
to a non-lethal form of vengeance.
How about we whoopee cushion
on his office chair?
He'll sit down,
it'll sound like he's flatulent,
even though he's not.
Let's keep thinking.
Gee, you're too late.
Scarlett Johansson and Wonder Woman
were just in here trolling around
for neurotic, little weasels.
I came to talk to Bernadette.
She's working today, right?
But I don't think
she wants to see you.
Why not?
Come on, you hurt her feelings
by not calling her all week.
Plus, I've kind of been
talkin' some smack about ya.
Hello, Howard.
Wait, Bernadette,
I need to talk to you.
- I can't now, I'm working.
- This will only take a second.
You asked me to think about where
our relationship was going, and I did.
Will you marry me?
Is this more comedy
that I don't understand?
No. I'm serious.
I'm never going to find
another girl like you
who likes me and is, you know...
real.
So, this isn't a joke?
Then you're insane.
I prefer to think
of myself as quirky.
Howard, we've only
been on three dates.
We haven't even had sex yet.
Fair enough.
When's your break?
Don't you just hate
when this happens?
All right, how's this for revenge?
A solution of hydrogen peroxide,
and one of saturated
potassium iodide.
- What's this?
- Mountain Dew.
Refreshing.
Now, we're going
to combine these chemicals
with ordinary dish soap,
creating a little exothermic
release of oxygen.
Foamy vengeance.
Yes, exactly.
This is brilliant, Sheldon.
How are we gonna deploy it
in Kripke's office?
Already taken care of.
Observe.
This is a live shot
of Kripke's lab via a mini webcam
I was able to install,
thanks to a dollar bill
discreetly placed
in the night janitor's shirt pocket.
At the same time,
I also secured large quantities
of these chemicals
above the tiles in the drop ceiling.
You remind me of a young Lex Luthor.
You flatter me, sir.
Let me guess: motion sensors?
The reaction will be triggered
when Kripke reaches
the center of the room.
I gotta say, I am really impressed.
This is truly
the Sheldon Cooper way to get even.
It may be low-tech,
but I still maintain
the whoopee cushion has comic validity.
Here comes Kripke!
Who is that with him?
I believe that's the president
of the university.
- And the board of directors. Abort!
- There is no abort.
- How could you not put in an "abort?"
- I made a boo-boo, all right?
I think the board will appreciate
how well we're using
that NSA grant, President Seibert.
Right here we have
a micro-controlled plasma...
Looks like the Ganges
on laundry day.
At least they don't know it was you.
Hello, Kripke.
This classic prank comes to you
from the malevolent mind
of Sheldon Cooper.
If you'd like to see the look
on your stupid face,
this video is being
instantly uploaded to YouTube.
And a hat tip to Leonard Hofstadter
and Raj Koothrappali
for their support and encouragement
in this enterprise.
Well, I'm going back to India.
What's your plan?
Here's your tip from table seven.
Thanks.
Testing. Check.
Check two.
Now what?
You want me to throw him out?
No, that's okay.
Are you sure? He's small.
I bet I can get
a nice, tight spiral on him.
I want to dedicate this number
to a great gal who I've done wrong.
Bernadette
I am so sorry for
Trying to propose to you
Bernadette
You found it creepy
But that's just
the kind of thing I do
I know now it was too soon
to talk of love
It was just a crazy idea
that came to me in my tub
But, Bernadette,
give me one more chance
Sweet Bernadette
I'll get the hang of this thing
They call romance, Sweet Bernadette
I dream to once again
Kiss your lips, Sweet Bernadette
Sincerely yours
Howard Wolowitz
Oh, I am so sorry.
Are you kidding?
That's the most romantic thing
anyone's ever done for me.
Bernadette!
Thank you, Cheesecake Factory!