* I don't ever want to feel *
* Like I did that day *
* Take me to the place I love *
* Take me all the way *
* I don't ever want to feel *
* Like I did that day *
* Take me to the place I lo... *
Fellas, please.
Penny, come on.
We were just finding our sound.
You found it.
It's the sound of a cat
being run over by a lawn mower.
I'm really very busy.
Is there any way
that we can put this off
until I have
more time to prepare?
Of course.
But, uh, you understand
my trepidation.
What's that about?
Not a clue.
Can't we just postpone it
till the spring?
Maybe next summer?
This should be fairly
easy to deduce.
He's holding the phone
to his left ear.
Ears do not cross hemispheres,
so he's using the analytical
rather than the emotional side
of the brain, suggesting that
he has no personal
relationship with the caller.
No, I didn't realize
it had been so long.
Sure, I guess
there's no other choice
but to just go ahead and do it.
He's referring to an
activity he has done before.
It's unpleasant and
needs to be repeated.
This suggests
some sort of
invasive medical test,
like perhaps a colonoscopy.
Aren't there any
other options?
There's not a lot of room.
It's gonna be uncomfortable.
Yes, yes.
I'm definitely going
with colonoscopy.
Okay, bye.
My mother's coming to visit.
How about that,
you were right.
* Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state *
* Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! *
* The Earth began to cool *
* The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools *
* We built the Wall *
* We built the pyramids *
* Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery *
* That all started
with a big bang *
* Bang! *
It's out of order.
Yes, I can read the sign.
I'm just pondering
the implications.
I think it implies that
the elevator doesn't work.
Again, I can read the sign.
But the sign and the tape are
coated with a layer of dust,
which indicates that the
elevator has been nonfunctional
for a significant
amount of time.
Which suggests either
a remarkable passivity
among the, I assume,
24 to 36 residents
of this building,
based on the number of mailboxes
and given typical
urban population density
or a shared delusion
of functionality.
You must be Leonard's mother.
Oh, I don't know
if I must be, but yes.
Uh, I'm Penny.
I'm his neighbor.
Oh, Dr. Beverly Hofstadter.
Oh, nice to
meet you.
Oh, you're a hand shaker.
Interesting.
Uh, why don't you
come with me.
I'll walk you to the apartment.
Oh, all right.
Would you like to exchange
pleasantries on the way?
Yeah, sure, I guess.
All right, you start.
Okay.
You know,
I've always been curious.
What was Leonard like
when he was little?
Oh, I think
you mean young.
He's always
been little.
Right, okay.
What was he like
when he was young?
You'll have to be
more specific.
Um, okay, like,
five or six.
Five.
Oh, well, at that age,
he was well enmeshed
in what Freud would call
the phallic stage
of psychosexual development.
An outmoded theory, of
course, but the boy did spend
most of his waking hours with
a tight grasp on his penis.
Yeah, Leonard mentioned
you were a psychiatrist.
Well, that is
one of my degrees.
My primary field
is neuroscience.
Well, I'm an actress.
Why?
What do you mean why?
Well, there are studies that
suggest that many who go into
the performing arts suffer from
an external locus of identity.
Yeah, I don't know
what that means.
Well, it means
you value yourself
only as others value you,
which is often the result of
unmet childhood emotional needs.
Oh, well, I had a
wonderful childhood.
Tell me about it.
I know my dad
wanted a boy.
I just, I tried
being good at sports,
but I hated
getting dirty!
And then, I'm assuming,
you entered adolescence.
He called me Slugger until
I got my first training bra.
And then he just stopped
playing catch with me.
I wasn't Slugger anymore.
Your mother's here!
If you want to have intercoue
with that girl,
find out what kind of cologne
her fathore.
Good to see you, Mother.
Here's your
tea, Mother.
Oolong?
Yes.
Loose, not bagged?
Steeped three minutes?
Yes.
Two-percent milk?
Warmed separately?
Yes.
One teaspoon sugar?
Raw sugar?
Yes.
It's cold.
G|G|
I'll start again.
I  s
My theory is that
his lack of focus
stems from an over-
developed sex drive.
Oh, I don't know
where he would've gotten that.
Aside from a pro forma
consummation of our marriage,
his father and I
only had intercourse
for the purposes
of reproduction.
That seems a fairly efficient
arrangement.
Yes, we think so.
We've both done papers on it.
Mine from the neuroscientific
point of view
and his from an anthropological.
Mine, of course,
was the onlyne worth reading.
Of course.
I would very much like to read
about your sex life.
Well, it's all online
or you can order it
from the Princeton
University Press.
Here's your
tea, Mother.
So, what are you guys
talking about?
The frequency with which
your parents had intercourse.
Swell.
If you're lucky,
maybe she'll show you
the PowerPoint presentation.
I'm sorry,
it's on my other laptop.
Aw...
So, Mother...
what's new?
You'll have to be more specific.
All right.
Uh, what's new with you?
Oh, well, I've been having
some fascinating
menopausal symptoms recently.
Maybe something less personal.
Oh.
Your Uncle Floyd died.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
His heart stopped beating.
I have to urinate.
What a remarkable woman.
Yeah, I-I thought you guys
might hit it off.
I envy you your childhood.
I hate to tell you,
but the only warm memories
I have of my childhood
are of my Uncle Floyd.
You're clearly misremembering.
Your mother is brilliant,
analytical,
insightful.
And I'm betting
she never hit you
with a Bible because
you wouldn't eat
your Brussels sprouts.
Sheldon, you don't give
your mother enough credit.
She's warm, she's loving,
she doesn't glue electrodes
to your head
to measure your brain waves
while potty training.
You were lucky.
When I was a kid,
if I wanted an EEG,
I had to attach
my own electrodes.
So, Dr. Hofstadter,
Leonard rarely talks about
his incredibly successful
brother and sister.
Please, don't go
there, Howard.
I understand that,
unlike Leonard,
they're at the top
of their respective fields.
Boy, you suck.
Well, Leonard's younger brother,
Michael,
is a tenured law professor
at Harvard,
and his sister just
successfully grew
a human pancreas
in an adolescent gibbon.
So, she's close
to curing diabetes?
Why else would you grow
a pancreas in a teenaged gibbon?
Wow, you must be very proud.
Why?
They're not my accomplishments.
I have to urinate.
Why are you doing this?
You know the rules.
You brought your mom to work...
you must suffer.
Leonard, I had no idea
your siblings were so much more
successful than you.
Yeah, you're like the Jar Jar
Binks of the Hofstadter family.
Oh, meesa think
yousa lookin' so so sad.
You know, rather than mock me,
my friends might realize
that this is difficult
and try to help me through it.
Nope, I think mocking you
is more fun.
Next time, don't yousa
bring mama to work.
Okee-day?
That was fast.
Oh, the middle stall
was occupied.
I'll have to try again later.
That's totally understandable.
In bladder voiding,
as in real estate,
it's location,
location, location.
So, where were we?
Howard lives with his mother
and Raj can't speak to women
unless he's drunk.
Go.
That's fascinating.
Selective mutism is quite rare.
On the other hand,
an adult Jewish male
living with his mother
is so common
it borders on
sociological clich?.
It's just temporary;
I pay rent.
He lives in the same room
where his bassinet was.
You know, both
selective mutism
and an inability
to separate from one's mother
can stem from
a pathological fear of women.
It might
explain why
the two of you have created
an ersatz homosexual marriage
to satisfy your need
for intimacy.
Say what?
That's basically
what I just said.
You brought your husband
to work.
You know the rules.
Meesa thinking yousa
looking pretty sad now
too, betcha, betcha.
Leonard, it's 1:00.
Weren't you going to show me
your laboratory at 1:00?
There's no hurry, Mother.
Tell them more about their
secret love for each other.
But it's 1:00.
You were going to show me
your laboratory at 1:00.
Her reasoning is
unassailable.
It is 1:00.
Fine. Let's go.
I think you'll find my
work pretty interesting.
I'm attempting to replicate
the dark matter signal
found in sodium iodide
crystals by the Italians.
So, no original research?
No.
Well, what's the point
of my seeing it?
I could just read the paper
the Italians wrote.
Just for the record,
we're not in an ersatz
homosexual relationship.
Well, then why didn't
you say that to her?
Why is it always my
responsibility?
It's not always
your responsibility.
I swear, this is the
same thing you did
at the comic book store
last week.
I can't believe you're
bringing that up.
I didn't bring it up.
You did.
We'll talk about
this later.
You always say that,
but we never do.
Hey.
You got alcohol?
Your mom still here?
Yep.
Come on in.
Wait, wait, she's not gonna come
here looking for you, is she?
Relax. She took Sheldon to the
hospital to get a brain scan.
Oh, my God. What happened?
Nothing. Mother likes
looking at brains
and Sheldon likes getting
his brain scanned.
Geez, what a fun couple.
She's only been here
a day and a half
and I'm seriously
considering alcoholism
as a new career path.
Hey, I talked to her
for five minutes yesterday
and I've been
half bombed ever since.
You can't let her
get into your head.
My head, what about yours?
It's too late for me.
My head is her summer house.
She was right, you know.
The locus of my identity
is totally exterior to me.
Oh, yeah, there
she is. Hi, Mom.
I mean, do you know where
I was all morning?
Auditioning
with 50 other blondes
for some stupid
antidepressant commercial.
And for what?
So I'll finally get
my daddy's approval?
Did you get the part?
No, they said I was too perky.
You want to talk about not
getting love from a parent.
You know what I used to
do when I was little
to have some sensation
of human contact?
Yeah, you grabbed your
penis and wouldn't let go.
Your mother told me.
Of course she did.
Anyway, that's not
what I was gonna say.
When I was ten years old,
I built a hugging machine.
A hugging machine?
Yeah. I got a
dressmaker's mannequin,
I stuffed it with
an electric blanket
so it would be warm, and built
two radio-controlled arms
that would hug me
and pat my back.
Oh, that is so sad.
You know what the
saddest part was?
What?
My father used to borrow it.
Your scan data will be very
helpful to my research.
You have a remarkable brain.
I know.
Although I've always hated
how my right frontal lobe
looks in pictures.
Common complaint among men.
Nothing's ever big enough.
Except when they get a tumor.
Then you never hear
the end of it.
I'd love to see a scan
of your brain sometime.
Oh, I'll send you a link,
but its physiology
is fairly unimpressive.
Oh, I can't believe that.
Your unwillingness to accept
empirical evidence
suggests an attempt
at flattery.
My apologies.
I've been living
with your son too long.
Gotten into some bad habits.
Understandable.
Can I make you a cup of tea?
I doubt it,
but if anyone has a chance,
it's probably you.
I feel very comfortable
around you.
around you, too.
It's surprising
because I generally
don't feel comfortable around,
well, anyone.
Nor I.
What are the odds
that two individuals
as unique as ourselves
would be connected
by someone as comparatively
workaday as your son?
Is that a rhetorical point
or would you like to do
the math?
I'd like to do the math.
I'd like that, too.
Okay, now this time,
Uh-huh.
you're gonna lick
the salt...
off my neck...
...do the shot...
...and then bite the lime.
I'm sorry, I didn't hear
anything after "lick."
Neck, shot, lime.
Okay, shot, lime.
Right.
Ah!
Where's the lime?
Oh, okay, we're sharing.
So, what do you think?
I'm very tempted.
I'm just not sure
it's appropriate
with my son's roommate.
Normally, I'd feel
the same way.
But based on everything
I've observed about us,
I can't help but speculate
we'd be very good together.
True. I've had
a similar observation.
It's certainly something
I could never do
with my husband.
I was hesitant the
first time I tried it,
but I experienced
an unanticipated
and remarkable release
of endorphins.
It's quite satisfying.
I see what you're doing.
You're appealing
to the neuroscientific
researcher in me.
You see right through
me, don't you?
Only when you're in
a CAT scanner.
This is actually
gonna happen.
Honey, shush, shush,
shush, shush, shush.
You shush, I'm happy.
I want to talk about it.
You know what my mother
would say about this?
She would say because you were
not loved by your father
and I was not loved
by my mother,
that having sex is our way
of making up for the intimacy
we didn't get as children.
Why would you bring
that up right now?
I don't know.
Foreplay?
So you're saying
you're not having
sex with me,
you're having sex
with your mother?
I'm gonna go with "no."
That is the sickest
thing I've ever heard.
Come on, you're trying
to have sex with your father,
and I'm okay with that.
Get out!
She said shush.
I should have shushed.
* Ooh, all night, all night *
* Oh, every night *
* Hold tight *
* You hold tight *
* Baby, hold tight *
* Anyway you want it,
that's the way you need it *
All right, Mother.
Um, have a nice flight.
That's not really in my control,
is it?
Oh, uh, yes.
Oh, good morning.
Morning.
Look, I was just coming
over to talk to you.
You don't have to.
Ever.
Gotcha.
Good-bye, Mother.
Good-bye, Leonard.
So, Slugger,
shall we pick up
where we left
off last time?
I mean, my mom
could've just said,
"Bob, get over it,
she's a girl, move on."
But she didn't.
Not one word.
Interesting.
Would you be willing to fly
to New Jersey and discuss
your relationship with your
parents during a brain scan?
Would it help?
Well, it would help me.