How much time do we have?
T-minus five hours, 37 minutes
to onset of meteor shower.
Our position is 34.48 degrees north,
118.31 west.
That means the azimuth should be...
168.22 degrees relative
to magnetic north
with an elevation of 49.93.
Anything yet?
We have a signal, but no frame lock.
Hang on.
How about... now?
We did it.
We have the West Coast feed of HBO.
Ooh, Real Sex.
Every time I watch that show,
it's old women putting
condoms on cucumbers.
All right, let's see
what's on the East Coast feed.
Oh, hey. Dune.
Not a great movie,
but look at that beautiful desert.
Too bad Sheldon
couldn't come with us.
It's just not the same without him.
This sucks.
I'm switching back to Real Sex.
Sheldon's log.
Stardate 63345.3.
While my colleagues are off
observing the Leonid meteor shower,
I have remained behind
to complete my paper
on the decays of highly excited
massive string states.
Although my research is going well,
I do miss the warmth
of human companionship.
Episode 308:
The Adhesive Duck Deficiency
Sync: Golgi, Loky
www.subbercafe.fr
And good evening to you,
Siam Palace.
This is Sheldon Cooper.
I'm going to be dining alone
this evening,
so I'll be reducing my usual order.
I'd like to start with one quarter
of the Assorted Appetizers Plate
and one half
of the Golden Treasure for two.
For heaven's sake.
In the mid-18th century,
King Rama IV of Siam
divided a huge empire
amongst the colonial powers of Europe
in order to preserve his throne.
Surely, you,
his cultural descendant,
can handle pad Thai and dumplings.
Sheldon, help!
I need to go.
But you keep in mind
that my sharply worded comments
on Yelp.com recently took down
a local muffin store.
Come in! Hurry!
I'm back here.
For God's sakes,
I'm in the bathroom!
Shall I come back at a better time?
Get in here!
Hurry!
Don't you dare knock!
Hello.
I slipped in the shower,
and I think I dislocated my shoulder.
Not surprising.
You have no safety mat
or adhesive stickers
to allow for purchase on a surface
with a low coefficient
of static friction.
What?
Tubs are slippery.
I know. I slipped.
I have a series
of whimsical duck stickers
on the bottom of my tub.
Will you just turn the water off
and help me up?
They're holding umbrellas.
- What?
- The ducks in my tub.
They're whimsical because ducks
have neither a need for,
nor the ability to use, umbrellas.
My God.
I got to go to the emergency room.
Assuming you're correct
that your right humerus
is no longer seated in the socket,
I would certainly think so.
- Can you drive me?
- I don't drive.
I can't drive!
It seems we've reached an impasse.
I could call you a cab
or an ambulance.
I can't wait that long.
You got to help me, please.
All right. Let it never be said
that Sheldon Lee Cooper
ignored the pleas
of a damsel in distress.
No one's saying that.
Let's go.
It does seem rather ironic
that for want of 99-cent adhesive ducks,
we both might die
in a fiery car crash.
I wish Penny didn't have to work.
She loves camping.
Would have been great.
You and Penny having sex
while I sit out here
and watch Howard hump a cactus.
The best I can tell,
there are eight other campsites nearby.
Mostly science nerds like us,
but just over yon ridge are two
not unattractive middle school teachers
who reek of desperation.
- Wonderful. How old are they?
- I don't know.
50, 55.
Menopause.
Nature's birth control.
Come on.
You guys can't be that hard up.
- I am.
- Me, too.
They gave me homemade cookies.
Of course, they did.
That's what grandmothers do.
What are we waiting for?
Relax.
I said we'd stop by a little later
after they have their nap.
Good idea.
They'll be refreshed.
- Cookie?
- Yeah. Thank you.
Not bad.
Yeah, very tasty.
- Tell me more about these teachers.
- Not much to tell.
They had a VW microbus
and were wearing tie-dyed
Grateful Dead T-shirts.
Good cookies.
I see no organizational
system in here whatsoever.
Which panties do you
wear on Mondays?
I don't need panties.
I just need shorts and a shirt.
My mother always told me
one should wear clean underpants
in case one is in an accident.
One was already in an accident.
Doesn't mean one won't be in another,
especially if I'm driving.
Clothes, Sheldon.
I need clothes!
Here.
Seriously?
Those shorts with that top?
All right.
Oh, that's cute.
We should have you checked
for a concussion.
Now, you got to help me
put these on.
- All right.
- But don't look.
- Don't look?
- I don't want you to see me naked.
That's understandable.
You may be interested to know
that a prohibition against looking
is well established
in heroic mythology.
Lot and his wife,
Perseus and Medusa,
Orpheus and Eurydice...
They always look.
It never ends well.
Now you got help me get my arm
into the sleeve.
Is that my arm?
It doesn't feel like an arm.
Then, maybe you should let it go.
All righty.
Stars are pretty, aren't they?
Up above the world so high.
Like little diamonds in the sky.
That's beautiful, dude.
You should write that down
before someone steals it.
So, when do the meteors get here?
The meteors don't get here.
The Earth is moving into their path.
I can feel it.
I can feel the Earth moving.
It's moving too fast.
Raj, slow it down.
Okay, how's that?
Better. Thanks.
Stars are pretty, aren't they?
What's so funny?
It's your American accent.
Everything you say sounds stupid.
"Stars are pretty, aren't they?"
For the record,
I should let you know
this is my first time driving
an actual motor vehicle.
You have your
learner's permit, right?
And I have logged a considerable
number of hours on a simulator.
- Good.
- Didn't work out well.
- All right, can we please go?
- One moment.
According to my driver's ed book,
the side mirror is properly adjusted
when the driver's door handle
is visible in the lower right corner.
There's the handle.
No, too far.
Bringing it back.
Optimized.
Now, where is the switch
to adjust the passenger side mirror?
It's right there.
Where is the passenger side mirror?
In a parking lot in Hollywood.
Can we please go?
As soon as I adjust my seat.
Oh, dear.
I'm going to have to start again.
If I could speak
the language of rabbits,
they would be amazed,
and I would be their king.
I hate my name.
It has "nerd" in it.
Len-nerd.
I lost my virginity
to my cousin Jeanie.
I would be kind
to my rabbit subjects.
At first.
You know what's a cool name?
Angelo.
That has angel and Jell-O in it.
It was my Uncle Murray's funeral.
We were all back
at my Aunt Barbara's house.
Our eyes locked
over the pickled herring.
We never meant for it to happen.
One day, I hold a great ball
for the President of France,
but the rabbits...
they hate me and don't come.
I am embarrassed,
so I eat all the lettuce in the world
and make them watch.
People could call me Angie.
Yo, Angie, how's it goin'?
To this day, I can't look
at pickled herring
without being aroused and ashamed.
Cousin Jeanie.
Could you please drive
a little faster?
I think we're going
sufficiently fast.
What's that?
- The engine does that sometimes.
- It can't be nothing.
The check engine light is on.
We need to find a service station.
The light has been on
since I bought the car.
All the more reason
to consult with a mechanic
before it explodes.
It's not going to explode.
Just keep driving.
Warp speed ahead, Mr. Spock.
Mr. Spock did not pilot
the Enterprise.
He was the science officer,
and I guarantee you that
if he ever saw the Enterprise's
check engine light blinking,
he would pull the ship over
immediately.
Oh, God, I'm gonna lose the arm.
Red light.
Release accelerator
and slowly apply the brake.
Nailed it.
While we have a moment,
may I ask you a question?
What?
Why do you have
the Chinese character for soup
tattooed on your right buttock?
It's not soup.
It's courage.
No, it isn't.
But I suppose it does take courage
to demonstrate
that kind of commitment to soup.
How did you see it?
You said you wouldn't look.
Sorry.
As I told you, the hero always peeks.
- Anything?
- No. That was the last pudding cup.
What about Slim Jims?
That's what he used
to eat his pudding, remember?
Right. That was so good!
Sweety and meaty at the same time.
Wait. So you're saying
we're out of food?
The only thing in here
are blue ice packs.
I know they're poison,
but they look like big,
yummy otter pops.
- Oh, God, I am so hungry.
- Me, too.
Check and see
if we have any more pudding.
All right, there's no need
to bark at me.
According to the inexplicably
irritable nurse behind the desk,
you'll be seen after the man
who claims having a heart attack,
but appears to be well enough
to play Doodle Jump on his iPhone.
We have to fill these out.
"Describe illness or injury."
I dislocated my shoulder.
All right.
And how did the accident occur?
You already know that.
"Cause of accident."
"Lack of adhesive ducks."
Okay, medical history.
"Have you ever been diagnosed
with diabetes?"
Kidney disease?
- Migraines?
- Getting one.
"Are you currently pregnant?"
Are you sure?
You look a bit puffy.
Change migraine to yes.
- "When was your last menstrual period?"
- Next question.
I'll put, "In progress."
Okay, moving
to psychiatric disorders.
"List all major
behavioral diagnoses,
"e. g. depression,
anxiety, etcetera."
What the hell does this have
to do with my stupid shoulder?!
"Episodes of sub psychotic rage."
- Ass.
- "Possible Tourette's."
All right. "Moles, lesions
or other skin conditions."
"Soup tattoo on right buttock."
I am scared and in a lot of pain.
Could you please take a break
from being you
for just a minute
and try being, I don't know...
comforting?
I'm sorry.
There, there.
Everything's going to be fine.
Sheldon's here.
Thanks. That's much better.
I'm so hungry!
Will you shut up?
We're all hungry.
Okay, our objective is
the Boy Scout campsite to the east.
Easy target. Big doughy scout master,
couple of Cubs, mostly Webelos.
What score we looking at?
Hot dogs, buns, s'mores.
I mean, it's a freaking 7-11.
Everyone grab flashlights.
Oh, my God, could it be?
My mother put an "I love you" brisket
in my backpack.
- Quick, get forks.
- You don't need forks.
It's so tender,
it falls apart in your hands.
He's right.
I feel like we're forgetting
something important.
Me, too. But what?
Maybe a Tupperware bowl
of roasted potatoes and carrots?
Now remember,
you were given
powerful pain medication
and a muscle relaxer,
so, don't operate heavy machinery.
Try not to choke on your own drool.
Wait. You have
to help me get into bed.
Sheldon has to get me into bed.
Bet you never thought I'd say that.
Yes.
The charm of your drug-addled candor
knows no bounds.
You know,
people think
you're this weird robot man
who's so annoying all the time,
and you totally are.
But then it's like that movie
Wall-E at the end.
You're so full of love,
and you can save a plant
and get fat people
out of the floaty chairs.
That's a fairly labored metaphor,
but I appreciate the sentiment
behind it.
Sing "Soft Kitty" to me.
"Soft Kitty" is for when you're sick.
You're not sick.
Injured and drugged
is a kind of sick.
Soft kitty, warm kitty,
little ball of fur...
Wait, wait.
Let's sing it as a round.
I'll start.
That's where you come in.
I'll start over.
I've got all night, Sheldon.
... and the next morning,
when he woke up,
he rolled over and realized...
... she was his cousin.
That's still not funny.
And she was my second cousin.
- You're a real douche.
- Who cares? You slept with your cousin.