My father worked as a lawyer for
the richest family in New York
until his plane went down
in Long Island sound.
He left me his biggest client,
the Darlings--
Tripp, the empire builder, Letitia,
the sophisticated socialite,
Karen, the
professional divorcée...
- I want to marry Nick.
- Let me help you.
Brian, the man of God...
- What about Brian jr.?
- I'm taking him back to Brazil.
You can't just uproot him.
He has a life here now.
Patrick, the
principled politician...
The three of us are gonna sit down
together and set some ground rules.
- You, me and who?
- Carmelita.
And Jeremy and Juliet,
the well-behaved twins.
- I want a job.
- What can you do?
You will not believe the
girl whose car I'm parking.
Darling Plaza was our
first home in Manhattan.
Convince Tripp to throw
Darling Plaza into the pot.
It is Simon Elder.
He has stolen my son.
I want to destroy him.
- Good morning.
- Hey.
You ready to paint
the living room?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I love painting.
I love the mess, I love the smell.
Okay, which one?
All right, let me see.
- Crème brûlée or flan?
- Yeah, it's a custard theme.
Are you sure you're going
to be able to finish this
before Thanksgiving at my parents'?
It's only two days.
Yeah. Yeah,
I have very little to do today.
I just have to meet with Tripp briefly
and help Brian with his custody hearing,
and then I am free for the
entire holiday weekend.
Five days without
Nick George...
Won't the Darling dynasty
crumble into dust without you?
It just might.
But it would be very
expensive dust.
- Anything going on with Darling Plaza?
- Not yet.
We transferred the deed over
to Simon Elder two weeks ago.
He's given me no
indication of his plans.
Is that it, then? He just wanted
to steal my soul, rob me of...
the building where
my kids were raised,
rob me of my son? My son, Nick.
Have you heard from
Patrick lately?
Not since the wedding.
He hasn't returned any of my calls.
You can't imagine what
it's like, Nicky.
You come tthe end
of your life--
so many years of work,
so many years of achievement--
and then right in
front of your face,
it's all being spirited away by this...
capricious man.
Patrick is still
your son, Tripp.
No matter what kind
of political alliance
he forms with Simon Elder for
whatever reason, he's still your son.
Yeah. Arrange a sit-down with Patrick
and Simon Elder for me, will you?
A sit-down? Okay.
The sooner, the better.
Tomorrow evening, up at Valhalla.
Wait, Tripp. You expect him to leave
the city the day before Thanksgiving
and go 60 miles up the Hudson
river valley for a sit-down?
You handed him the deed to Darling
Plaza to gain influence with him, right?
Yeah.
So use your influence.
Cash it in.
All right. I'm on it.
You'll be there
at my side, okay?
Tripp, it's-- it's Thanksgiving weekend.
I made plans with the family.
I'll get you out really early
thursday morning. Promise.
What do you want me
to tell Patrick to--
Just tell him Simon
Elder will be there.
That'll make him feel safe.
You leave the rest up to his vanity.
How much longer are we gonna
be staying at this hotel?
Living out of a suitcase,
eating room service all the time,
it's a little tiresome.
Thank you for being so patient.
Have you set up the
meeting with Carmelita yet?
Um... I'm not sure this
is the best time for her.
Uh, she's got finals coming up.
Oh, she's in school.
What school?
Uh... uh, cosmetology.
Well, it's always something,
isn't it?
When would be a good time...
for her?
Uh, what is it you
want to talk about?
Just make it happen.
If you want to stay
married to me,
quit stalling and
make it happen.
- I understand--
- Today.
Okay.
Thank you for coming on
such short notice, Giorgio.
Anytime you get divorced,
Karen, I'm here for you.
But, you know, we don't have to do
this only after you get divorced.
Yeah, actually, we kinda do.
Was that Giorgio?
What a trooper,
always being there for you like that.
- It's really, like, inspiring.
- Mm, it takes a village.
Something was off last night, though.
It wasn't the same.
Do tell.
Well, usually when
Giorgio and I have...
meaningless post-divorce sex,
it feels a little less meaningless,
like we're somehow...
Planets whose orbits
intersect every ten years?
No. Just... hornier.
- You gonna eat those?
- No. Replenish.
- What's the matter with you?
- I miss my son.
Brian jr. left? Where'd he go?
His mother came and took
him away a week ago, Karen.
I'm fighting for custody.
Brian, hey, look,
you know how the justice system works.
Whoever has the most
money wins, right?
- You've got nothing to worry about.
- Well, thanks for the advice.
Thanks for the pancakes.
Was Brian wearing Clive
Christian number 1?
Nah, that's me. And it's number 2,
unreleased to the public.
Oh. Why are you
wearing cologne?
There's this girl who
parks at the garage.
She won't go out with me.
She thinks I'm, like, just a valet.
Oh, so you're gonna knock her
unconscious with your cologne,
and then, what, shanghai her?
Just tell her you're Jeremy Darling.
No. Natalie pretended to be
pregnant just to get my money.
I want this girl
to like me for me.
Honey, that's not gonna happen.
You're a Darling.
As soon as she finds that out,
things are never gonna be the same,
trust me.
I guess she can
never find out then.
That is a good plan.
Good plan, my friend.
He's not asking you
to move back in.
He's not asking you to do
anything except sit down with him
and Simon and talk.
Nick, that's the last thing on
earth I would ever consider doing.
I know, but, Patrick,
he is your father.
It's taken me over 30 years to muster
the courage to break free from him.
I'm not about to go ruing
back into shooting range.
Okay.
But I'll do it.
I'll do it, okay?
I just need one... little favor.
She just wants to talk.
I can't do it.
I can't face her.
I'm sorry. Tell Patrick no.
Carmelita, just put yourself in
Ellen's shoes, just for a second.
She's not asking patrick
to end the affair.
She's not asking you to vanish.
She just wants to talk.
You know, who knows?
Maybe the three of you can somehow,
- I don't know, complete each other.
- You really think that's possible?
Well, I think that life is
very creative and surprising,
and sometimes we find solutions
where we thought there weren't any.
Patrick is so lucky to have
someone like you in his life.
I'll do it.
Good.
- A sit-down?
- That's what he called it.
- Wait. And what are the terms?
- Ah, no terms.
Well, because it sounds so old-world,
I figured there must be terms.
Nope, just the three of you
sitting down to talk, and me.
Okay, does this have anything
to do with Darling Plaza?
I don't think so I think it has
to do with the fact he feels
he's lost his son to you, that's
what he's troubled about right now.
Okay, so you're being straight with
me about this little... sit-down?
You promise me that I'm
not gonna be walking into
some sort of classic
Tripp Darling ambush?
Uh, yeah, I promise.
Yeah. Okay. I'll go. Actually,
I think it could be beneficial.
- Good.
- It's not every day
two men like us sit down and break bread
together. It should be interesting.
Done.
I think we can all agree it's
in everyone's best interest
to settle this without
going to the judge tomorrow.
What you think, Mr.
George, is beside the point.
My client's settling for nothing less
than sole physical and legal custody.
- Are you out of your freakin' mind?
- I know what's best for my child.
Says the tramp who slept with
me last week to get him back.
- Brian, let me handle this.
- Then handle it!
Given Brian jr.'s
feelings for his father,
do you think that moving to Brazil
is really what's best for him?
These two have bonded since you
first deposited your son with Brian
and then
subsequently disappeared.
Was this before or after he
deposited the child with you?
Beat it,
you prissy little creep.
Brian, let's just cool it.
Okay? Let's just stop.
I think I have come up with what is a
very fair proposal for joint custody.
You will be well-compensated
provided you stay in the city,
and it puts your son's
best interests first.
I'll give you $1 million to get up
and walk out of here right now.
Excuse me?
Hey, that's not what we're here to do,
Brian. Let me finish.
- $2 million.
- Are you trying to buy my son?
- I'm trying to buy our son.
- Nobody is buying anybody.
This is ridiculous.
We're leaving.
$3 million.
We both know it's all about
the money with you anyway.
Now I remember why it
didn't work with us.
You are not a human being.
Don't look at me like that.
$3 million was more than fair.
- Hey.
How you doing, baby?
This better not be your way of
saying you're missing Thanksgiving.
I am not missing Thanksgiving.
Good.
I just have to postpone the
painting until the weekend.
And I'm gonna catch up with
you and Kiki at your parents'.
I have to go up to the Darlings'
country house tomorrow.
Tripp is having a sit-down
with Patrick and Simon Elder.
He wants me there. I'm sorry.
- You know what? It's okay.
- Okay.
Yeah, I knew you wouldn't get to it,
so maybe I'll start painting,
'cause I'd like it done
before the holidays.
Because, you know,
I actually care.
Hey, Lisa, you know what?
Why don't you come with me.
We'll drop Kiki off
at your folks' first,
and then this weekend,
we'll all paint together.
I am not going to stay in the
same house as the Darlings.
- Italy was bad enough.
- Oh, come on, Lisa.
I am not gonna stay the night at
the same place you and Karen Darling
spent a dozen magical
summers together.
You know what? How about you go,
you enjoy a nice, long weekend with her,
and I will stay here
and I will paint?
Lisa, I don't particularly want to go,
but I have to.
And since I have to,
I would like you to come with me.
- Coming right up.
- Actually...
Is it possible to leave
my car here overnight?
I think I drank a little
too much wine at dinner.
I'm so on board with that.
Both myself and the garage encourage
responsible, yet
heavy drinking.
Okay, wonderful. Thank you.
I'll just go and take a catnap.
Let me...
let me help you out there.
What do you got
going on in there?
French fries with truffle oil.
You know,
I could just drive you home.
That way you have your
car in the morning.
I don't think so.
Come on. I'll cab it home.
No muss, no fuss. In and out. Boom.
That's so sweet of you.
It would help me out a lot.
Well, I will go
fetch your chariot.
Why do I have to come to
Valhalla for Thanksgiving?
Brian's not gonna be there.
Your brother Brian
has a custody hearing.
He's presiding over two
funerals this weekend.
The holiday season
die-off has commenced.
Uh, I told you I'd help you with Nick.
So trust me. Just come.
What if daddy sends me and Nick
to India-- or, no, wait, Bali--
to set up an orphanage for
the really starving children?
And we'd have to live alone
in a grass hut on the beach.
Well, as wonderful
as that sounds,
coming to Valhalla is all
you really need to do.
But she'll be there. Won't she?
I haven't the faintest idea.
Oh, she will. Of course she will.
She's his wife.
It's so her to come along,
isn't it?
Just relax, my dear.
Everything is gonna work itself out.
Door-to-door service
with a smile.
Thank you for this.
Boy, Brooklyn is, uh, far away.
I mean--
I forgot how far it is.
It's like...
it's like a whole other world.
Are you gonna be all
right getting home?
Yeah, yeah, like I said,
I'll--I'll call a cab.
Maybe I'll hobo
and hop a boxcar.
- The subway is two blocks away.
- Right, yeah. The subway.
There you go.
- Listen, Sofia...
- The answer is yes.
- To what?
- I will go out with you.
But I don't even
know your last name.
Well-- I don't--
I don't even know your last name.
I'm Sofia Montoya,
and you're Jeremy...
I'm cool with just
Jeremy, babe.
- Eson-- Jeremy Babeson.
- Babeson?
Yeah, well, you know,
it's a common american last name.
It's right on all those lists
beside Smith, Wong and White.
Well, thank you again for the ride,
and I'll see you tomorrow,
- Jeremy... Babeson.
- Yes. Yes, you will.
Hey, hey, Clark, um,
do you mind coming to get me?
I am, uh,
I am somewhere in Brooklyn.
You're sure about this, right?
What are you gonna do,
not answer the door?
Well... isn't this something?
- Ellen... I've heard a lot about you.
- I wish I could say the same.
Unfortunately, I've been
kept completely in the dark.
I have, too, in a sense.
Come in.
Please.
You can have one
saturday night a month,
but the rest of the
weekends are ours.
You can have one tuesday or
wednesday night every other week
to do whatever it is
that the two of you do
as long as he is home in time to put
the kids to bed before he does it.
That's less than I get him now,
so why exactly would I do this?
Because it's more than
you'll ever have otherwise.
Trust me.
Starting now, this is the new normal.
Sweetheart...
- are you sure you want to--
- Please, Pat, stay out of it.
Don't you think I should
participate in this conversation?
Patrick, maybe you
should take a walk.
Um... okay.
Okay.
He'll spend holidays with us,
family birthdays and
obviously all campaign-related
events are completely off-limits.
The only way that
this is gonna work
is if I get him two
nights every week.
Or Patrick's gonna
end up sneaking out,
and neither one of us wants that,
do we?
Family is the only thing
that matters to me.
And as the arbitrator in this case,
I'm sure you can appreciate that.
And that's why I believe,
as a father and a minister,
that I should share
custody with Brian jr.
And she should not be able to
whisk him away to friggin' Brazil.
Thank you, reverend Darling,
for your forthrightness.
Mr. Mitchell?
Reverend Darling,
who is Gustav?
Go ahead, tell him.
Gustav is my, uh, pet name for Brian jr.
It's a nickname, kind of.
- Nickname, really?
- Yeah.
It's a rather unremarkable
occurrence between a father and son.
Is it true you forced Brian jr.
to lie to your wife and
pretend he was a swedish orphan
whose parents died in a car accident?
- No.
- No?
It was a bullet train accident,
not a car. Get your facts straight.
- But you did make him lie.
- No.
I offered him an
opportunity to work with me
to smooth the way towards
building a new family structure
by soft-pedaling, as it were,
the nature of his involvement with me,
and by making it a fun game.
Isn't it also true, reverend Darling,
that you kept Brian jr.
on a diet of swedish foods,
including fermented milk and reindeer?
It was once.
It was a 1-day thing.
And didn't you forbid him to
tell the truth to your wife
until he was so paralyzed by fear
and guilt of hellfire and damnation
that he had to confess
the truth himself?
I need help.
I've got this little romantic
rendezvous tonight, and, uh,
I was wondering if you could
hook me up with a place to eat.
A restaurant?
This girl I like,
she doesn't know who I am.
You know, she thinks I'm this
normal parking attendant,
and, uh, you know, I just--
I wanna keep it that way.
- Ah.
- So...
- Where do people like you go out?
- People like me?
Yeah, you know, like poor people.
Where do you eat when you go out?
You know, Jeremy,
I actually make a pretty decent
living working for your family.
I've seen you eating your bag lunch,
and, you know,
I don't know what's going on with the
whole silent-movie-star moustache,
but it seems
pretty... poverty-related.
You're right, Jeremy. I...
- can't actually afford a beard.
- Oh. that's a good one.
In the interest of full poor disclosure,
uh, Maureen and I do enjoy,
occasionally, going out for pizza or
a walk down the Brooklyn promenade.
That's sweet and simple.
I like it.
Sometimes, after, we'll take a
bottle of wine up on the roof and...
if the stars are out and
the mood hits us, well...
you know us poor people.
You do the deed Alfresco?
Yep.
Clarksdale!
You're like the fountain of
middle class romance-formation.
I been called that before.
You should prepare yourself, Brian.
We may lose.
Do you think? You're the worst.
- Did you even go to law school?
- What did you want me to do?
You've lied about this kid from day one,
Brian, and everybody knows it.
- I'm sorry I can't change reality.
- Well, then you suck.
I had a plan, and you sabotaged
me every step of the way.
Just go out there and
get them back in here
and get a retrial or a
mistrial or something.
This isn't a trial. The arbitrator
makes her recommendation to the judge
based on testimony, and your little
performance in here didn't help.
The fact is,
Andrea raised Brian for seven years,
and you had him for two months.
And you made him pretend to be swedish.
So why don't you let me
worry about the law?
Go see Andrea alone,
reason with her,
make her understand how
you feel about Brian.
She's his mother.
She wants him to be happy. Good luck.
- Hey. What are you doing?
- Hey. I don't think
there is an article of clothing Kiki
owns that she is not taking with her.
- Taking where?
- To my parents'. We'll drop her off.
I'm going with you to
the country house.
You decided to come with me?
- You sure?
- Yes.
I am not going to let the
Darling drama rob me of a chance
to breathe some clean
air with my husband.
Good.
Wow.
Yeah, and they only use it,
like, four times a year.
Buon giorno, Cari. Oh, leave those.
Albert will get them.
- Told you she'd come.
- It'll be fine.
- Hi, dear.
- Hi.
- Hi, Lisa.
Lovely to have you here.
Wow. Would you look at that?
Oh. Here we go.
Oh, hello.
- Well, you must be Simon.
- It is a pleasure to meet you.
- Patrick. Oh-ho.
- Hello, mother.
Simon, how are you?
This is my wife Lisa.
- Hi.
And this is Karen Darling.
- Karen.
- Hi.
- The Karen?
- Yes. Karen.
I'm sure everybody could
use a little drinky-poo.
Hey, you're just in time.
So what are we hunting?
Quail. Might get
a pheasant or two.
- This late in the season?
- Sure.
You're not planning on shooting him,
are you?
Come on, Nick.
You know me better than that.
The country makes
everyone so ravenous.
Everything's just terrific, mother.
Thank you.
- You're not liking that quail?
- I'm all for sport hunting
and responsible wildlife management,
but actually...
I don't eat meat.
Oh, but that's all
the yummy stuff.
Do you eat anything yummy?
- Down, girl.
- Shut up.
Well, we can have them cook you
something else. There's trout.
No, no, no,
the salad is enough.
- Everything's wonderful.
- Thank you.
Lisa, you must come with me
after dinner to the east wing.
I've been meaning to
show you something.
- A little art collection.
- Okay. Sounds great.
It's an hour-and-a-half wait.
Should we just go?
- Nah, let me see what I can do.
- Jeremy, it's okay.
No, no, hold on.
I can be charming.
Excuse me. Could you please
double-check about a table for two?
Actually, it looks like I might
have a table, Mr. Darling.
Oh, uh... one more thing.
- Should just be a few.
- Really?
Babeson, party of two?
- You got us a table.
- I told a teeny lie.
Happy birthday to you!
That was so embarrassing.
My birthday is in march.
It was the only way I could get a table.
Just, you know, pretend.
- I'm having a great time tonight.
- Me, too.
You know, it's, uh,
kinda nice going out on a normal date.
And how does this
normal date ends?
How about a walk
on the promenade?
How about we go
back to your place?
Uh, that--
that is a much better idea.
Except I can't.
I got a friend crashing at my
place for Thanksgiving tomorrow.
You know, he's, uh, he's a little
down on his luck, kinda poor, so...
Too bad.
There is another option.
Isn't there some
way that we can...
work something out,
just between us?
Brian, it's too late for that.
When that arbitrator delivers
her recommendation to the judge,
it's all over,
and I'll abide by that.
Well, of course you will,
'cause it's all gonna go your way.
Not his and not mine, yours.
Brian, that first day
that I met you at church,
you sat and talked with me for
hours about faith and solace.
Yeah, so what about it?
So you are the one who taught me to
bring my problems in life to God.
Have you thought
about doing that?
I know this whole get-together may
seem a little old-fashioned, but...
I thought it was time to cut
through the haze of go-betweens
- and talk in person.
- Hey, I couldn't agree more.
Paddy... I'm glad you came.
Thank you.
As long as everything's moving forward,
dad, I'm happy.
No hard feelings.
So... what are you
doing with my son?
- Doing?
- What?
No, what is the nature
of your alliance?
Hold on a second.
Are you kidding?
This is none of your business anymore,
dad. You don't have to answer that.
No, no, no, I'm happy to.
I'm ecstatic.
I've simply offered myself
to Patrick as an advisor and
a friend during this
time of transition.
So you're not using him as a pawn
to enact revenge against me, huh?
Um, I think...
that Patrick's pedigree
combined with his passion
for social justice
is going to make him a
very effective senator.
I'm excited to be on his team,
that's all.
Dad, try not to make a
fool of yourself, okay?
What's this all about, Tripp?
It's about the chilling heartlessness
of a man determined to tear asunder
the long-standing family ties
in the course of his vendetta.
Do you want to tell them why you want
to destroy my family, or shall I?
You know, Lisa, I, um...
I've been meaning to apologize to you,
but I keep putting it off.
You know, for the wedding,
for Karen's... behavior.
She can be so rash and
thoughtless sometimes.
And I know how proud she is,
and she'd never come to you herself.
What are you talking about?
You present yourself as a--
some sort of modern-day saint.
But that's not who you are at all.
You're not motivated by benevolence.
You're driven from
your very core
by an obsessive malevolence
against me and my family--
- I've gotta get going.
- Paddy, hear this out.
Tripp, none of this is personal.
It's business.
So... your family's history with my
family has nothing to do with it?
What are you talking
about, Tripp?
I didn't know what his
real name was before.
But as soon as I found out,
everything fell into place.
His parents used to work for our family,
for a long time.
Do you want to continue,
or shall I?
What happened?
Oh, it was nothing, really.
I'm sorry. I, uh...
Well, I assumed you knew. Um...
you and Karen have
been so chilly that--
What happened?
I would love to hear
what you think you know.
Your father was my
mother's lover.
Well, that was the rumor, and my father
couldn't live with those rumors,
true or false,
so he dismissed his parents,
and they fled to the Soviet
Union with the belief that
communism spoke more clearly to
the plight of african-americans.
But it wasn't so rosy over there,
was it?
His family ended up in
a siberian work camp,
and they died there,
leaving you an orphan.
Is that true?
It touches on the truth.
Well...
you know, Karen was in a bit of a
depression, you know, post-divorce,
and a little intoxicated,
and she...
she apparently kissed Nick and
declared her undying love for him.
- She can be so impulsive.
- No, it is the truth.
And it's the truth that you
hold me personally responsible
for the death of your parents.
See, I don't need some desiccated
old man to tell me my history.
- Desiccated?
- Especially one who gets it all wrong.
My parents didn't go
to Russia by choice.
- Your family forced them there.
- No. You've got it all wrong.
I'm not dried meat,
and your parents were not deported
from this country, and you know it.
No, no. But once their names had been
handed over to the state department,
they were, for all intents and purposes,
hounded out of this country,
so, yeah, their deaths lie at the
feet of your family, completely.
All right, I've heard enough.
Look, I don't know who's
telling the truth here, okay?
But the fact that you
lured all of us up here
for this little
performance of yours
and then get everyone else
involved with your game,
that arrogance is precisely why
I stopped trusting you years ago,
and why I will never trust you again.
Do you understand?
If you see Ellen,
tell her I've gone out.
I'll head home as well.
I wish this had ended differently.
Well, it ended exactly as I expected
it to end, with a crafty denial.
- Night, Tripp.
- Good night.
Well, at least it's out
there for everyone to know.
Excuse me.
It's so sick.
Simon. Simon.
- You told me this wasn't an ambush.
- I didn't know anything about it.
You need to stop lying to me.
I will not be played.
- No one is playing you.
- If that fossil wants a war,
that's exactly what he'll get.
That's what you'll both get.
Simon. Simon.
Simon, this was all Tripp.
I had nothing too with it.
- That's the truth.
- The tru-- oh, the truth.
Oh, the truth is pretty
malleable around here.
All right, all right.
All right. Just...
listen, if we're
gonna go any further,
I need to know one last time
whether you're with me or not.
Well, if all you're doing is
exacting revenge, then no, I'm not.
Nick, I'm not exacting revenge.
But Tripp Darling owning half the city
is not good for the people of New York.
He is a dangerous man.
I know that Tripp has made some
shady business deals, but dangerous?
Yes. Do you remember Kenneth Darling,
Tripp's brother?
Simon, come on. The only people who
think that Tripp had anything to do
with Kenneth Darling's assassination
are crackpot conspiracy theorists
on the internet and two people who
are actually suspects in the killing,
both of whom have since been
completely discredited.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Because bad things don't really happen.
It's all just a story. Right?
- Where's Nick?
- I'm not sure. Scotch?
Uh-oh. It's empty. Sorry.
Were you this drunk when
you kissed my husband
and told him that you
loved him at your wedding?
Actually, no.
I was sober, and so was he.
- Hey, there you are.
- Be careful.
She just found out about
our kiss at the wedding.
- It was not "our kiss," Karen.
- Unbelievable. You are unbelievable.
- Why do you do that?
- I didn't tell her, Nick.
I thought it was gonna
be our little secret.
How did you think to
come up to this place?
Oh, my dad works for them. He told
me they're all out of town, so...
So what does mr. Babeson do?
- Who?
- Your dad, silly. Mr. Babeson.
Oh, right.
Um, he's the limo driver for
this family, the Darlings.
- You've never heard of them?
- No, should I have?
No, no. You--
no, you absolutely shouldn't have.
You know what's so
amazing about you?
- What?
- Being with you...
I feel like it doesn't matter how
much money I have or don't have.
It's like it's just you and me,
you know?
Dear God...
I don't ask you for much.
Well, 'cause I know
I don't deserve much.
But please help the arbitrator to
understand that I love my son.
Oh! I'm so sorry.
And please give her
the good sense...
I think this is yours.
- No, it fell out of your--
- From reverend Darling.
To accept my generous donation.
Thank you. Amen.
So you're just gonna
leave right now?
I'm going to my parents' house.
I need some time to regroup.
Lisa, the only reason
that I didn't tell you
was that I didn't want to waste
our time arguing over nothing.
It was basically a peck on the cheek--
her lips, my cheek.
How many times does she have to kiss
you before you put a stop to it?
I can't control
what Karen does.
Is that going to be your excuse
when you two sleep together?
She's delusional, Lisa.
I've told her over and over
there will never be anything between us.
But she lives in this world
where she thinks she can
have anything she wants.
Yeah, well,
there is a pattern here, Nick.
And for the first time,
I feel like you are taking part in it,
whether you believe it or not.
You know what?
I have been pissed offt Karen,
but I have never worried about you.
Now I am.
Hey, baby.
What are you working on?
You went to see her,
didn't you?
Where is she?
In a motel...
a few miles from here.
Could you at least
take a shower?
We didn't... do anything.
It just-- I...
look, it's been a rough night,
and I needed to talk to someone.
I... I can...
I can tell her things.
What-- I... Ellen.
Simon left so abruptly.
How was the meeting?
Ultimately?
Wearying.
Sometimes I think I'm almost
ready to leave, you know...
this life.
I'm glad I married you.
What the hell was that?
So this was not an assassination
attempt on Patrick Darling?
No, this was a simple,
run-of-the-mill hunting accident.
Where are the wounds?
Mr. Darling sustained injuries--
minor injuries-- to his leg,
and he is expected to make
a full and speedy recovery.
- Who shot him?
- Nobody shot him, per se.
- This was an accident.
- Fine. Who pulled the trigger?
Charlie Mickelson--
a longtime Darling family friend.
He is devastated
by the incident,
and we obviously request that
you respect his privacy.
Where is Ellen Darling?
Why hasn't she been here to see him?
Ellen is resting at the Imperial,
and she's also quite devastated.
And we all hope that we can just
put this unfortunate episode
behind us and enjoy the
holiday as best we can.
Why was the attorney
general hunting at night?
No further questions.
- Jeremy.
- Clark.
Looking forward to the turkey
festivities this evening?
I am, I am.
I don't know how festive it's gonna
be with Patrick's leg in a sling,
but I finally have something to
be thankful for. Let's go, Clark.
- Jeremy?
- Sofia.
I didn't--I didn't know you
were gonna be here today.
You know, the--
Thanksgiving and all.
- What's all this?
- Uh, this? This is--
Oh, of course.
That's your father.
How sweet of him to pick
you up from your work.
Yeah, he is the sweetest.
You are--you-- thank you.
Thank you, pops.
- What the hell's going on here?
- Be cool, Clark.
Just know you're my father
and our last name is Babeson.
Got it.
Sofia... this is my dad.
Mucho gusto.
Ah, Babesons don't shake.
- Babesons hug.
- Okay. How are you?
I'm good.
- Thank you for doing this, Charlie.
- Happy to help out, Tripp.
- What did I shoot him with again?
- Double-barreled shotgun.
Purdy, 20-gauge, birdshot--
both barrels.
Right.
- Happy Thanksgiving.
- You, too.
Tell Helen we'd love
to see you sometime.
Will do.
- Thank you.
- You bet.
- How's Patrick doing?
- Doped up on sedatives.
- Ellen?
- Also doped up on sedatives.
You know, this could be...
well, you know...
I mean,
it's not going to get out, is it?
I'm just thinking of
Patrick's campaign.
Shouldn't be a problem.
He's my son.
You okay?
I said I'd never lie for the family,
and all of a sudden
I'm making up stories for the
press about hunting accidents.
Doesn't seem like a step
in the right direction.
Hey, you told Dutch you were too
busy to see him, and you weren't.
Come on.
Come on, Nick.
Life's messy.
Why didn't you tell me that Elder's
parents worked for the family?
The whole point of this
is for him to trust me.
I didn't want to put you in a
position where you would have to lie.
And I could not take a chance
that his faith in you would
be in any way diminished.
So all that was true,
about Elder's parents?
Yeah. I mean,
he got it wrong about my parents
reporting his parent to the authorities.
That wasn't them.
- It was my father.
- Yeah.
That was Dutch.
My dad, he was fit to be tied.
If he'd had his way...
I mean, you know, it was the '50s.
They were different times.
Dutch got into it,
got them safely put on a boat to Russia.
You know...
if you're looking for a motive for...
who killed your dad,
I mean, if Simon Elder knew that
it was Dutch who did that...
- What?
- Isn't that Darling Plaza?
Oh, god. That's the third
time I've seen it today.
It doesn't get any easier.
Darling Plaza was demolished
today as part of billionaire
Simon Elder's redevelopment plan
for a new, greener Manhattan.
There is nothing that that
man is not capable of doing.
I was hoping it'd be you.
- Hi.
- Happy Thanksgiving.
Such as it is.
I'm sorry I left, Nick,
but sometimes it is really hard to
deal with this whole situation.
Well, I'll quit.
Why don't I quit?
I don't want you to quit.
But I feel like
you're slipping away,
like things are just spiraling
out of control, for both of us.
Why don't I drive
up there right now?
No. We're just about
to sit down and eat.
Just take the night, relax.
We'll still be here tomorrow.
All right.
Well, I'll drive up in the morning.
I love you, Nick. And I'm...
I'm really-- I'm trying.
You know that, right?
Yeah, I know.
I'm trying, too, Lise.
We'll get through this.
I know we will.
All right. I love you.
I love you, too.
Trad: Elorri, Isilring, the_teacher
et Salomon - Transcript: Raceman
Synchro: travis - www.forom.com