Change. Please change.
Oh,please don't let me be pregnant.
Not the answer l was looking for.
- Karen.
- Nick. Hey. Hello. Hi.
Hey. Look,l'm sorry to barge in,but
your mother said l could wake you up.
l guess l'm a little late.
- You're not the only one.
- What
- Are you okay
l'm fine. l'm excellent. Why
- Come here.
- Why
- What are you doing this weekend
- l don't know. Why
Well,l thought we could
drive up to the Berkshires.
l booked a suite at the Elm Court.
Oh! Oh!
- This weekend is not ideal for me.
- Okay.
- What about next weekend
- How about next month
Next month Boy,wow,that's... Wow,we
really are taking things slow.
l know. lt's good. Let's
shoot for next month.
- Okay. Next month it is.
- Perfect. lt's gonna be sexy.
It doesn't make any sense.
Why would Simon pick you,out
of all the people in the world,
to help him fake his own death
Who cares why Simon picked me
What matters is,once l do
it,you will get your brother back
from wherever Simon's
got him hidden away,
and l will be your big kahuna.
That's all l'm thinking about.
And all l'm thinking about
is that this is a trap.
Look,l know that you
wanna be Action Jeremy,
but you are world
- famous for being a party boy.
You managed to fool everyone
with your fake amnesia,
but you're not Jason Bourne.
Hey,l am whoever l need to
be to help the woman l love.
- What are you doing here
- Karen,l'm sorry.
l didn't mean to scare you. l
was just on my way to see Tripp.
Your father and l are hosting
a gathering tomorrow night.
Rolling out our biofuel.
- Listen,is this a bad time
- Oh,any time l see you is a bad time.
Come on,Karen. You're not
still holding a grudge,are you
Why,because you sold me to my own
father on my wedding day Heck,no.
Okay,Karen,it all
worked out for the best.
l've got half of the
company and you have Nick.
Hey,listen,if you wanna let
yourself off the hook,go ahead,
but don't expect me to join you.
You may be able to forget little
things like ruining my life,
but l'm never going to,because,you
see,Simon,for me it's not over.
l'm gonna remember what you
did to me every single day
for the rest of my life.
l was that important to you l
mean,you got married four times.
l was that important to you
There's not something going on
here you're not telling me,is there
Karen,it's time for our...
Why,Mr. Elder. Hello.
- Hello,Letitia.
- Hello.
- Are you all right
- Yeah,l'm fine.
Let's just get out of here.
- Hey,wifey. What's cooking
- Not much.
l'm working on my sermon for Sunday.
The text is First
Corinthians,Chapter 1 3.
You know ''Love is
patient. Love is kind.
''Love endures all...'' What
So how does that work when you say
a prayer at a state dinner,anyway
l mean,when you went down
to Washington last week
to perform the benediction
at Patrick's state dinner,
and you looked out over
all those powerful heads,
what exactly did you say
- l started with,''Dear Lord.''
- Really
You sure it wasn't,''Oh,baby,you
look so hot''
What's your problem
This.
What,you wanna have sex This
isn't exactly setting a mood.
l found it in your suitcase.
What was it doing there
You know what l don't care.
Go and use it with somebody
else. l want you out of here. Now.
Wait a minute. You can't
throw me out of my own house.
Oh,yeah l already cleared it
with your mother,babycakes.
Watch me.
Oh,Maria,could you please
pack Mr. Darling's condoms
He's moving out.
Dr. Louis' office,please hold.
When you're feeling up to it,
l'm gonna have dinner
brought in from Artisanal.
- Osso buco.
- Hmm.
The only thing l'm gonna
want once l'm feeling up to it
is an extremely dry triple martini.
And a time machine so l can
go back to the day l met Simon
and stop this whole baby
mess before it started.
You're doing the right thing,dear.
Karen Darling,the
doctor will see you now.
So there should be a pretty
impressive turnout tomorrow.
The Port Authority is sending
people,Coastal Commissioner...
- And the press
- All the journalists
who at one time or another
came out against the biofuel
have kindly rethought their positions.
So it looks like we're ready
to roll this baby out,gentlemen.
- Yeah. Almost.
- Almost There's a problem
Well,the partnership agreement
between the two of you
has obviously been executed,but we
are still waiting on your signature
on the final transfer of the biofuel
patent to Darling Enterprises.
Oh,yeah,right. Well,that
was an oversight.
So just put the papers together,Nick,and
l'll gladly sign it over.
- All right. l'll do it later today.
- Good.
Tripp,l am proud to have you as my
partner,regardless of how it began.
- Nick.
- Simon.
All right. Take care,guys.
What's up
Mr. Elder is about to part company with
hundreds and hundreds
of millions of dollars.
l think,under those circumstances,
that he's being
extraordinarily accommodating.
l have to say,l agree.
- Well,perhaps we should find out why.
- Done.
Knock,knock.
Congressman Watley.
Sit,please.
l didn't know you were in New York City.
Yeah,wife and kids are
in town for a few days,
want to do a little shopping,kick
- start the old economy,you know
Senator,look,l wanted
to stop by and apologize
for the way we left
things the other day.
l realize that l misunderstood
your interest in me.
That's all right. lt's fine.
l do hope that you'll take
the fact that l made an advance
as nothing more than a
compliment,which is what it was.
- Thank you.
- Anyway,if you are interested,
l would love to have dinner.
Congressman,l've already
told you that l'm not...
To discuss Darling Enterprises'
new biofuel initiative,Senator.
You still do need the support
of the Energy Committee,don't you
- No.
- No
- Yes,l mean,of course,yes.
- Yes.
And we appreciate that
support,Congressman,absolutely.
Good.
Okay,l'll check my schedule,and
l'll have my office be in touch.
You do that.
- Are you sure you're all right
- Yeah,l'm fine.
l'm just... l'm a little shaky.
- What exactly went wrong
- Nothing. l just...
You know,l couldn't go through with it.
Oh,Mom,please don't
make a drama out of this.
Well,certainly not,dear. When have
you ever known me to make a drama
No,we'll get you home
and draw you a bath,
- and then we'll figure something out.
- l just...
l hate now that Simon is forever
gonna be a part of my life.
- Oh,he won't be,dear. l promise.
- Ma'am.
- Thank you.
- lt'll all be just fine.
Oh,my. lt's really coming down.
Not a good day for an abortion.
Here,l'll get it.
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-¿¨»Ò
Dirty Sexy Money S02E12
l'm coming. God.
l said l'm coming.
- Brian.
- Well,don't look so happy to see me.
You going somewhere
- Here.
- Wait,wait,wait a minute.
Don't even try.
l know you have the extra room
now that you're down a wife.
- Lucky bastard.
- Wait a minute. What happened
Andrea kicked me out. She
found out about me and Mei Ling.
Well,you didn't even
sleep with Mei Ling.
Yeah,l know. She found an
unopened rubber in my suitcase.
Well,we got to explain things to her.
That's ironic,huh
l went down there to have safe sex with my ex
- wife,
l don't have any,and l still get busted.
What are you doing
There is another bedroom in
this little doll house,right
Yeah,there's Kiki's,but she uses it.
- Okay,good. You stay there.
- Brian,come on. This is New York City.
There are dozens of great
hotels,many of which your family owns.
And l have a position to uphold,
not only as a Darling
but as a man of the cloth.
l check in someplace,and it's
gonna be all over Page Six.
Come on,help a half
- brother out.
All right,fine.
An invitation to dinner. What
possible harm could come from that
lt's a date,Dad. A man
- date.
You've made your
feelings clear,haven't you
You've established your
orientation. Have you not
Yeah,well,he's not the kind of
gay that takes no for an answer.
Guy.
l'm sorry. l'm just
a little rattled here.
You just calm down.
l mean,look,there's
got to be some other way
we can push this through the committee.
We've got other contacts
in Washington,right
Of course we do,but at this point,
Representative Watley is
still our most prominent,
our most vehemently vocal critic.
lf we could have his vote,
if we can have his public support
at the rollout tomorrow night,
that would be invaluable.
But what if he gets tipsy and he
starts putting the moves on me again
- Then what
- Come on.
lt's a crowded restaurant.
Do the best you can,would
you,Patrick Please.
My car blew up and l was
standing 20 feet away.
Yeah,right,accidents happen.
But,see,when my private investigator
finds weapons- grade C- 4
mixed in with the
remains of my bodyguard,
the old ''accidents happen'' theory
kind of goes boom out the window.
No,l'm not accusing you. l'm
asking you an honest question.
Okay,okay. Okay.
lf you say you weren't
behind it,then... l'm sorry.
l am. l said...
- Problems Who was that
- Don't you worry about it.
Now,what are you doing here
The question is what
are you doing with Jeremy
Oh!
He told you our plan.
Well,it's very simple really. He wants
to be your knight in shining armor.
You want your brother,and l have
a need to make a graceful exit.
- Saw the opportunity for some synergy.
- l know you,Simon.
Your brand of synergy
profits no one but you.
Find someone else to help you
with your little exit strategy.
Look,Nola,l'll admit Jeremy's not an
obvious choice for this kind of project,
but things are difficult right now.
l'm not sure l can trust my own people.
And Jeremy's commitment to finding
your brother is strong,to say the least.
No,he's the man for the job.
Unless you have someone else in mind.
Son of a bitch. So that's
your plan all along,right
Compromise Jeremy as a
way of forcing me to do it
ls that your way of saying yes
Tell me where my brother
is right now,and l'll do it.
Yeah,okay. Nola,listen to me.
When my death is reported
on an encrypted page
of The New York Times web site,a
file on this drive will open,
disclosing your brother's
location. Not until.
Go on.
All right. Here's a
schematic of my building.
This...
Come here. All right.
The whole shebang will
go down tomorrow night,
after the roll
- out of my biofuel.
By midnight tomorrow,you
will have your brother,
and l will be,for all
intents and purposes,dead.
- Nola Lyons.
- Nick George.
What are you doing coming
out of Simon Elder's building
Oh,l was just making sure
all the ''l's'' were dotted
and the ''T's'' were
crossed for tomorrow night.
l wanted to assure Simon
that his biofuel has Patrick's long
- term support.
And you came all the way across town
to deliver that message in person
- That's quite a commitment.
- Well,the job demands nothing less.
You of all people should
know that. Excuse me.
- So where do l sign
- Here.
Here and here.
Wow. Ten years of hard
work has finally paid off.
So what if l have to share the
credit with Tripp Darling,right
The world's a better
place,and l'm a satisfied man.
- And you must be,too.
- What do you mean
Unless l'm mistaken,l think
congratulations are in order.
l'd suggest we have a cigar,
but l don't think you're really a cigar
- smoking kind of guy.
What are you talking about
- Karen hasn't told you
- Hasn't told me what
You know what l'll let
her tell you herself.
The last thing l want
is to ruin the surprise.
Karen,come out of there.
l had Maria make some whoopie
pies,chocolate and pumpkin,your favorite.
Come out.
What am l gonna do
- Well,do you wanna have the baby
- This baby,this way
l mean,God,Mom,Nick and l,we were
finally on the verge of something,
and now l'm pregnant with my crazy ex
- boyfriend's baby.
No,l don't wanna have this baby.
- So do you want...
- No. No,l can't do that,either.
l mean,what if this is my only chance
Well,then your options are severely
limited. You can only be unhappy.
- So,what are you gonna do
- l don't know. l just... l don't know.
Being rich doesn't protect
you from anything,does it
No,dear. lt doesn't. Not at all.
- Patrick.
- Charles.
l am so glad that you could make it.
- And you must be...
- This is my wife.
This is Dana. This is Patrick.
l've heard wonderful things. You
have my Charles under a spell.
- Lovely to meet you.
- Please,sit down.
So the kids are at the
hotel with the nanny.
- They're watching a movie,so...
- l crashed. l hope you don't hate me.
Not at all. More the merrier.
What the hell's going on
You went behind my back
l am not gonna let Simon hurt you.
- l can take care of myself.
- No,you can't.
Simon walked me through the plan,
the broken window pane in the sub
- basement,
the code that supposedly
disables the security cameras.
My guess is that it goes
straight to the police.
He's trying to frame you.
Okay,fine,let's say it's a set
- up. Then why is you being the rat
in Simon Elder's maze any better than me
A,l know my way around that
building better than you do.
- Okay.
- B,his people know me.
lf they catch me,l can
justify my presence.
- That's true.
- And C,it's just the way it has to be.
Okay l lost my father to Simon.
l've nearly lost my brother.
l won't lose you,too.
- Thank you.
Manufacturing this fuel is
safer than you think,Charles.
- The environmental impact studies...
- What,Patrick What
The environmental impact studies
that you're basing your statements on
don't tell the whole
story,not by a long shot.
What about the flash point
Yeah,what about the
flash point Sounds hot.
ls there any way that you
could push the flash point up
Yeah,can you push it up a bit,Pat
When something goes wrong,this
stuff burns like crazy,
and l'm not going to have
an uncontrollable blaze
at the foot of Manhattan.
Yeah,a blaze to the foot would be bad.
Boom.
Charles,my parents are hosting
a little soiree at their place
tomorrow night for
investors,potential partners.
We would love it if you two could come.
Well,then,maybe we will.
There's Jack. Jack!
l'll just be a second.
Charles,good to see you.
- What the hell are you doing
- l'm giving you a present,silly.
Your panties
What am l supposed to do with these
- Here you go.
- Thank you,Hannah.
Only the best steak in town,am l right
Hear,hear.
Sweetheart,l'm gonna have the
driver bring the car around,okay
- Okay.
- All right.
There's something
you'd like to say to me
My husband hasn't touched
me in over 10 years.
Dana,stop it.
- Why
- Because l can't do this,
even though l would really like to.
Kiss me good night,please.
- That was a mistake.
- Best mistake l've made in years.
Here he comes.
Sweetheart,it is time
to hit the old road.
Don't forget tomorrow night,my
parents' place. Take care.
- Hi.
- Hi. l didn't see you there.
- Here l am.
- l got your message.
Sorry l didn't call you
back. lt's been a crazy day.
l see.
- Can we talk
- About what
About the good news.
Simon congratulated me,and
he mentioned good news
and cigars,and since l didn't know
what the hell he was talking about,
l thought maybe you could fill me in.
l'm pregnant.
Okay.
And you told him that the baby's mine
Because it's impossible.
- We haven't had sex.
- No,l didn't tell Simon anything.
- So,what He's just guessing about...
- l don't know.
Trust me,he's the last
person l would tell.
Because it's his,isn't it
- lt's Simon's baby.
- Yeah.
Why didn't you tell me l mean,don't
you think this is information
that l would find kind of relevant
Excuse me,l'm a little
freaked out right now,
and l'm pretty scared of
what this is gonna do to us.
- Can you do this with me
- Can l
l know. l know,honey.
lt's not easy,and l know this isn't
how something should start out.
But nothing we've ever done has
gone according to plan,has it
l've waited so long,Nick,you
know that,so long for us.
So have l,Karen. Look,l love you.
This is why l didn't tell you.
Well,this is a hell of a thing
for me to wrap my mind around.
Forgive me if l can't
just say yes immediately.
Okay.
Well,then,can you say yes ever
l don't know.
l'm sorry.
But l don't know.
Am I only dreamin'
Or is this burning
Brian.
An eternal flame...
- Brian!
- What
Take those damn things off. l beg you.
What do you want l was working.
Look,l had to listen to you sing
all night long. Just enough already.
Just helps me concentrate.
l'm working on this sermon.
Would you listen to this
lt's about love. ''Love
never seeks its own way.
- ''Love is...''
- What the hell is this
- lt's coffee. lt's your free- trade
swill. - Yeah,well,it tastes like bleach.
Well,l cleaned out the coffee maker
with bleach,'cause it was dirty.
This place is a pig sty.
Yeah,well,l'm sorry that l don't have a full
- time staff of cooks and maids
like you're used to at home,Brian.
Maybe you should have thought
of that before you invaded.
No,maybe you should have
frigging hired somebody!
Planning,Nick. lt's key!
- Look...
- Nick!
What
Will you talk to her for me
- Please Thanks.
- All right,l will,but...
Now,sometimes life surprises you
and creates a path where
there was never one before.
This partnership with Tripp
Darling,Darling Enterprises was,for me,
one such surprise.
So together,we thank you
for joining us tonight
to celebrate the launch of MPG 5000,
a 21 st century biofuel
which,with the help of visionary
friends here and in Washington,of course,
will be ready for production
at the end of the year.
To MPG 5000,the fuel of the future.
- Jeremy.
- Hey. Nick. Right
Yeah,listen.
What do you know about
Simon Elder and Nola Lyons
Nola works for Patrick,and
Simon works with Dad.
Are you sure she doesn't
have any ties with Simon
that pre
- exist both those relationships
l don't know,remember
Me got the amnesia.
- Knock it off,Jeremy.
- What
- Look,l know you don't have amnesia.
- Come on. l do. l forget stuff.
Hey,hey,hey. We don't
have to discuss it. Okay
Just tell me the truth,is there a
connection between Nola and Simon
Okay. They might both be in
Oprah's Book Club together,
- but other than that,l don't know.
- Thanks a lot,Jeremy.
Congressman. Mrs. Watley. l'm
so glad you decided to attend.
We are,too.
Miss me
Hello,Congressman.
- Hello,Tripp.
- Mrs. Watley.
l'm so pleased that my son was able
to persuade you to join us tonight.
Happy to lend our support.
Timing is everything.
Well,if you could spare me a minute,
l'd like to introduce you
to my associate,Simon Elder.
Certainly. Certainly. You
can handle my wife,right
l'll do my best.
- Be back in a little bit,sweetie.
- Okay.
- Hey,there's my favorite girl.
- Hi,Nick. How's it going
You know he's moved in with me,right
Yeah,of course. He's
the father of my son.
- l need to know where he is.
- Just take him back.
Not on your life.
Andrea,look,nothing happened
between he and Mei Ling Hwa,l swear.
- l don't care,Nick.
- Well,l can't live with him,period.
Well,you're gonna have
to,because until Brian grows up
and realizes that
being in a relationship
doesn't mean zigzagging between
saving and betraying somebody,
but that it's actually about
being continually present
and continually faithful,l'm
not gonna take him back.
Andrea. All right,fine,but
he's going to a hotel,
because l don't care
what the papers say.
Nick,he could've always gone to
a hotel. The papers don't matter.
Don't you get it
Of all the places in the
world that he could have run to
and of all the people,he chose you.
Yeah. Lucky me.
He's your half
- brother. Deal with him.
lt's very impressive. l'm looking forward to my next fill
- up.
Do not give me your panties here.
That's impossible. l'm not wearing any.
The Argyle Hotel. Room
909. Come see me later.
Everything but the
door will be wide open.
Whoa.
Scotch. Lowland. Eighteen year.
- l have a drink,thank you.
- Yeah,what is that
Mmm.
Ginger ale. That's interesting.
Yeah,l'm trying to stay sober so l
don't do something foolish like kill you.
- Excuse me.
- So how far along are we Six weeks
Oh! lnto our breakup l don't know.
Honestly,l haven't been keeping track.
How far are we into
our pregnancy Come here.
How did you know
l didn't. Not for certain.
Not until just now.
l mean,l figured it wasn't
Nick's,given his reaction.
So,what were you thinking
That you were gonna have this
baby and l would never find out
Simon,you broke my heart.
- Why don't you just leave me alone
- Because things have changed.
You're pregnant with my baby,and
you tried to hide it from me.
This changes everything.
l'm not gonna let you within
1 0 feet of this baby,Simon.
See,sweetheart,that's
not your decision to make.
l swear to you,no matter where
you go,no matter what you do,
l'll always be a part
of this baby's life,
and there's nothing you or
your family can do to stop me.
Nothing.
Where's Nola
Don't worry. She'll be
at your place,1 1 :00.
- You'll get dead. Don't worry.
- There's been a change of plans.
What,you just wanna be maimed
l've decided not to
die,Jeremy,at least not yet.
l'm calling it off. Tell your girl.
Wait a second. l thought
you needed to flee.
Well,something important
has happened now
- that makes me need to stick around.
- What
Don't you worry about that.
You'll hear about it soon enough.
Hey,to mergers and unexpected arrivals.
To your family.
And to mine.
Hey,so you spoke to Andrea.
What'd she say ls she missing me
Not exactly.
- God,she's a bitch.
- Look,she's not a bitch,Brian.
You just...
You hurt her feelings,and
now she doesn't trust you.
Hey,l know this is unorthodox,but
you are a man of the cloth.
- Can l confide in you
- Well,you can give it a shot. We'll see.
Come here.
Karen's pregnant.
- Holy...
- Yeah,l know.
- And it's yours
- No.
Well,whose is it
Well,l guess it could be
half the Fortune 500's,right
- lt's Simon Elder's.
- Oh,man,give me a...
Hey,Brian,and she still
wants me to be with her.
What And raise the devil's spawn
Yeah. Something like that.
Well,you know,l seem to remember
when our plane was about to crash,
you did say something to
her about being the one.
Look,l thought we were gonna die,Brian.
But was it true
Yeah. lt was true.
- You know what the Good Book says.
- What
Love is patient. Love is kind.
- Love endures all things.
My guess is it at least tries.
l'll see you at home.
Great news.
- Tell me. - We got
the stand- down order.
l just got word from Simon.
He's like Scrooge on Christmas
morning,bubbling with life.
- What did he say,exactly
- He called the whole thing off.
No fake break
- in. No fake kidnapping. No fake murder. Done.
Let's go back to my room and celebrate.
- Wait,no,this doesn't make any sense.
- What
My brother. This is my
only chance to get him back.
His plan may be off,but
mine is still on.
- Okay. Then l'm coming with you.
- No,you're not.
Yes,l am.
Look,Nick is out there asking
questions,and Simon is a freak.
l'm not gonna let
something bad happen to you.
l'm not saying you can't be Lara Croft.
Just let me be your Terry Sheridan.
Who
- Congressman.
- Senator. Great party.
Thank you. Got a minute
Look,Patrick,if this is about your
little biofuel thing,don't worry about it.
- You got my vote.
- l know that,
and we are all very
grateful to you for that.
But seeing as how we're
both on the same side now,
- l just don't really know how to...
- Hey,spit it out.
- lt's about your wife.
- What about my wife
The other night,at dinner,um,
she kissed me,and it
was all very innocent,
and,l,of course,l
stopped her right away,
but l just wanted you to...
- l'm sorry.
- l am serious.
l don't want this to become a problem.
No,Senator,l know that you're serious,
but believe me,this,this
is not a problem.
What are you saying
Dana and l love each
other very much. All right
We're partners in every aspect
of our lives except for one,
so we have a little arrangement.
Now,if we meet a great guy
that she and l both like,
we hope that maybe he likes one of us.
Now,you obviously were not into me,
so Dana and l had a little
talk about it and figured...
What are you telling me You
want me to sleep with your wife
She gave you the key
to the hotel room,right
- Right
- Yeah.
You use that key,Senator,
because l certainly
will not be sleeping there tonight.
Karen.
What do you want What do you want What
Hey. Hey,what is wrong What happened
Simon knows the baby's his,and he
says he's not gonna leave me alone.
He wants to be a part of the
baby's life no matter what,
and l don't even know
what l want anymore.
Hey,calm down. Karen,please,just stop.
Nick,this is not your
problem. You said so yourself.
Well,l also said that l love you,
and l do,and l wanna help. So
let me take care of this for you.
Hey,l can take care of this.
- What are you gonna do
- l will talk to Simon,
and l will let him know that it is in
his best interest to stay the hell away.
All right
Can't figure out the access code.
''Swan'' doesn't seem to work.
Try ''jewelry.''
l didn't bring you
along for comic relief.
l need to open up a video
link with my brother,
so that we can find out
where he is and then...
Jeremy,hide.
What are you doing here
Your idiot boyfriend didn't
give you my message,did he
My brother,where is he
Okay,you made a mistake in
coming here,a big mistake.
How you gonna come...
Dude.
- Good. You're awake.
- Now you glad l came along
Yeah. Just keep looking
for that access code.
You two better hurry up,because my
people will be here any minute now.
You gave your people
the night off,remember
Or didn't you Told you it was a set
- up.
Hey,Jeremy,l tell you what. lf you
untie me now l promise l won't kill her
or the kid.
- There's hope for you yet.
- Nola.
Bottom of the drawer comes out.
l found it. l found the access code.
Hello
- Dana
- Hey.
Dana,l've been going through
a bit of a tough time lately.
l recently lost my wife,as you know,
and someone else to whom l was
very close.
And,look,l know l came all the way here,
but l just... l don't know
if l'm ready for something like this.
lt's okay. You don't
need to explain,Patrick.
Thank you.
lt's just sex.
Here we go.
Listen...
Come on. Hurry up. We
got to get out of here
before his Russian
circus freaks show up.
lt's processing.
You know,for a computer gazillionaire,your
lnternet is surprisingly slow.
lt's coming on. Something's happening.
Oh,my God. Justin! Justin! lt's him.
Hello? Nola,is that you?
Hi. Hi. Are you all right
Oh,my God! Oh,my God.
- What the hell just happened,Simon
- l have no idea.
He must have been in a
hurry to get somewhere.
Where is he Tell me
where he is right now!
- l have no...
- Where the hell is he
Oh!
l swear to God,l will kill you.
Oh,jeez. Jeez Louise. This is not good.
Nick.
What the hell is going on here
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-¿¨»Ò
Dirty Sexy Money S02E12