As a lawyer for
the richest family in new york
until his plane went down
in long island sound.
He left me his biggest client,
the Darlings--
Tripp, the empire builder...
You lied to me. You said you knew
about the affair.
I didn't know.
Letitia,
the sophisticated socialite...
Your father was my great love.
Brian, the man of god...
I lied to my wife
and daughters.
I told them
that you were an orphan.
Patrick,
the principled politician,
Karen,
the professional divorcée...
Karen, do not call me
on the home phone number.
I'll always love you, too.
And Jeremy and Juliet,
the well-behaved twins.
She was my best friend
in the whole world.
- I want you.
- If Juliet found out...
She won't find out.
You think Simon Elder,
the billionaire philanthropist,
blew up your father's plane?
Simon Elder is not the man
you think he is,
and your boss isn't either.
Morning, daddy.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I have to get you some new suits.
The dry cleaner is starting to think
i have a thing for him.
I'm sorry, i stayed here
at the office again.
I been going through this pile
of donation requests.
It's okay. We know you're busy.
It's all good.
I just don't know how
i'm supposed to help people
if i can't make time
to write the checks.
The whole family
sleeps here now. Charming
I work in a sweatshop.
Pookie-kai, daisy.
Pookie-kai,
long time, no see.
Pookie-kai?
What is pookie-kai?
Secret girl stuff.
Maybe we should go to my desk.
Thanks, guys.
- How are you?
- Nestly?
I'up to my ears hanging this
new show at the gallery,
i'm reading three books,
none of which i'm making
any headway in,
and i kinda miss my husband.
Yeah, me, too.
He's a great guy.
- That's funny.
- I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
I know this is
- A big opportunity for you...
- I am really sorry about-
just for the money but to find out
what happened with your dad,
You don't have to explain
i understand
All the business you do
for the darlings during the day
and the noble work you do
with their money at night,
i just feel like
there's no us anymore.
It's all Darlings.
Tell you what. we are gonna have
dinner tomorrow night.
I'm not complaining. It's fine.
- You're doing your job.
- Tomorrow night,
just you and me, del posto.
What do you say?
Kiki can stay with your mom.
Say something.
Anything.
You've just admitted to me
that you've been an adulteress
for 40 years.
Forgive me
if i'm short on words.
- Where are you going?
- What?
You haven't been in the same bed
with me for weeks.
I've known that you've
suspected something,
and i also knew
that you'd never say it.
I mean, god forbid
that tripp Darling
should ever admit
to being...
affected by anything.
Just tell me one thing.
our children,
are they all mine?
Yes.
Absolutely.
Oh, god.
What?
The thought that you can be
so sure...
that such attention was paid
to such a prolonged,
continuous insult
that you can say "absolutely,"
as if it were a favor
you did me fondly.
My god, Tish.
It's so sordid.
- Wait, what's the place called?
- Bar known.
Like the little dudes,
bar gnome?
Not gnome, freak show.
Known.
That's too bad.
I was psyched.
I was gonna get, like,
a little red hat.
Will you just come
with me anyway 'cause
it's opening night,
and then there's this...
What are you eating?
Sausage.
What?
What's the matter? Peta?
No, i've just been
all queasy all morning
and i'm, like,
a little bit spinny.
Will you just tell me,
Jeremy,
are you coming with me
or not?
I gotta make sure Juliet's not
gonna be there. But as for me,
tomorrow night?
fo sho. I'm already there.
I gotta go.
I'll see ya then, babe. Bye.
What?
- You were just talking to her.
- Who?
- Your secret girlfriend.
- I have no girlfriend.
Oh, yeah? Then who did you spend
600 grand on at bulgari,
Justin Timberlake?
All right, Jules,
I am telling the truth,
i am... i'm pluto.
I'm cold, distant
and alone.
All right.
well speaking of planets--
Pluto is not a planet
anymore.
It will always be
a planet to me.
What is this?
An early birthday present.
Hayden planetarium!
- I got you the whole place.
- Get out.
For rizzle. The entire cosmos
to yourself.
Well, i don't have
a gift for you yet.
It's kinda
three weeks early.
Yes, you do.
You see, there's this new club
opening tomorrow night.
and they begged me,
so i promised
to make an appearance,
- and you can come with me.
- It's not bar known, is it?
Oh, i know! It's like
the worst name ever, right?
Yeah, it's
the absolute worst.
You should just bail on it,
you know?
Stay home, read a book.
Are you on cold medicine?
It's a new club.
They asked me to be there.
And for your information,
i read a book last night.
Reading's a lifestyle, though.
It's an -
Jeremy, i promised. I owe it
to them to be there.
And now, thanks to me,
so do you.
She is decided.
I found something
very interesting, Tripp.
Lookin' in
your dad's calendar?
Yeah.
In the wake of
the massive helpfulness
from the police,
I decided
to go over it again,
check all the names,
all the dates,
see if i could figure out,
you know, who gave dad
all the information
on Simon Elder and why.
And my dad
had several meetings
with someone he referred to
only by the letter "c."
- "c"?
- I have no idea who it could be.
met him once a month,
sometimes twice.
Hang on a second.
There were a few times
i asked your dad
to do some detective work
for me.
Just after Kenneth
was assassinated
was the first one.
And there we others.
When he wanted to...
maintain
a tasteful distance,
he employed the services
of that man.
"Harold Templeton"?
Well, that's not
his real name.
He was a spy in the 60s
for England...
And China...
And France.
he even did some work
for Kennedy in Cuba.
He managed to make himself
globally unpopular.
You can't mention this
to anyone, not even Lisa.
How do i find him?
Well, there's
a little vineyard in--
just outside of Milan.
It's near our summer place in Italy
where you
and your dad used to
spend some time with us.
They make
a great little wine.
Chiavennasca.
Anyway,
if i remember correctly,
you go to that vineyard...
You ask for that wine...
- Slightly chilled.
- Wait a second.
Are you asking me to go
to italy to find this guy?
Yeah.
No, i mean, that's where
dutch always started out
when he was trying
to track him down.
He keeps a very low profile.
Anyway, you ask for the wine,
then see what happens.
If you manage to locate
Mr. Templeton,
He might be able
to explain to you
the origins of the...
Elder dossier.
Who knows?
He may even be able
to tell you who "c" is.
okay.
I'll go to italy.
Nick.
Yeah.
Snag a bottle fome,
will you?
Will do.
Chiavennasca.
Chiavennasca. Got it.
Aren't those to die for?
It's like they're made
out of George Clooney.
- How much?
- $1,200.
12...
$1,200?
Do they come
with a kidney?
No, they come
with each other.
What kind of perso
spends $1,200 on shoes?
Lisa.
What are you doing here?
Picked up a suit for Nick.
We're going out tomorrow night,
- So i just kinda thought-
- Then you have to buy those shoes.
- No, actually--
- Oh, yes, actually.
And do get them in raspberry.
I have them.
- I wear them all the time.
- I can't buy shoes
that cost as much
as car insurance.
Lisa, honey, don't be
so financially resistant, okay?
It's just money.
You did a little
shopping today, huh?
No, i did
a little browsing.
Karen Darling
did the shopping.
Right after i told you
our whole world was Darlings,
- Darlings everywhere...
- Yeah.
I ran into her.
We chatted.
- 3 h later, those shoes showed up.
- Well, that was thoughtful.
Yeah, i'm sure a lot of thought
went into that purchase.
What's the problem?
she sent you a gift.
She does stuff like that.
Why would Karen Darling
send me a gift?
Hey, Lise, you're starting
to sound a little paranoid.
OK? sometimes a shoe
is just a shoe.
And sometimes
it's a bomb.
So much for
our night out, huh?
Instead of a great meal
at del posto
and a night of wild sex...
Which i was really
looking forward to...
I get leftovers and a dvd
and you get a, what,
a whirlwind trip
to some villa in Italy
to pick up one bottle
of chiave--
Chiavennasca.
Why don't you
come with me?
- I can't. It's work.
- Why not?
- This is work.
- So what if it's work? Come on.
It's a private jet.
There's room.
You know, your mom can watch
Kiki over the weekend.
- Let's go to italy.
- Yeah?
Look, it's totally free,
and for two days, no Darlings.
No darlings.
See? Reading. Happy now?
Very nice.
"Babes in toyland"?
I felt bad i didn't have
a gift for you,
- so i rented out the whole angelika.
- For tonight?
- Yeah.
- Well, that is so sweet of you.
- Oh, i know.
- But i can't go.
You have to.
The thing is set.
Well, we have to go
to the club tonight.
I gave my word.
my word is my bond.
Anyways, when i decided
i wanted to read for the remake,
i decided that
i couldn't watch the original
because Annette Funicello
is so iconic.
I didn't want to copy.
But it was a really
picturesque thought.
Thanks.
Why aren't you dressed
for school today, Gustav?
I don't want to go.
Is that how they do things
in sweden?
School's like a tea party,
you go if you want?
What happened to your face?
- Bully hit me.
- Did you hit back?
- Jesus says don't hit back.
- Says who?
My mommy.
Your mommy?
You mean your mommy
who's dead?
Yeah.
Poor kid.
She's in a better place now.
Bully or no bully,
still has to go to school.
Okay, but i'm gonna
get terrorized.
Gustav, the world
is full of bullies
and always will be.
- You can't live in fear.
- What am i supposed to do?
What do you think?
Fight back.
Like David and Goliath.
You find a weakness
and you take advantage.
There's your bible truth for today.
Because i share your passion
for the truth, that's why.
Well, what makes you so sure
the painting's a forgery?
Peter, i don't want
to do this to you.
You've been our doctor
for years.
But Tish and i were passing
through David Frank's gallery
on our way to meet Karen
about a week ago...
I don't know,
maybe it was the light.
And i saw a speck
of prussian blue
in "das kind"--
your painting.
Prussian blue? I...
Yeah, the pigment.
It had not yet been invented
in engel's lifetime.
So i became suspicious.
There's a forger in Belgium
Who's becoming quietly famous
in some circles
for this sort of thing.
I'm sorry...
But your painting is a fake.
Stretfield's guaranteed
$6 million.
That painting's our exit strategy.
You've been Tish's o.b.-g.y.n.
for over three decades.
And this is a little secret.
Trust me.
This is going to go
with me to my grave.
I am curious...
About what?
In all the years that you've
been delivering our children...
Have you ever been aware
that any of them
might not have been mine?
You might look into that for me.
Yeah, sure. I could...
get you an answer on that,
- Sometime next week if you like.
- Tomorrow would be best.
If Natalie Kimpton's
gonna be here all night
with Ryan Casdale,
this place is over
before it even began.
What is that?
The old vodka
in the water bottle routine?
That is so 2004.
Does she think
she's fooling anyone?
I'm so tired of that
backstabbing little witch.
What, are you text bombing
your girlfriend?
No. i'm--
i'm betting on polo online.
Oh, my god!
Astrid!
When did you
get back from Andorra?
About two hours ago.
- What'sith boris and natasha?
- oh, it's some sort of
You look super hot tonight.
You do, too.
I thought maybe we could...
Pee does not
go well with this dress.
I'll get you another one.
Someone just came in.
- So you want to have a three way?
- It could be my sister.
You are about to have sex
in a public bathroom,
and that is what you're worried
about, your sister?
That is so incredibly lame!
This has got to be
the best part about being rich,
- Don't you think?
- What's that, the private jet?
Yeah, no lines,
no security.
And no pesky rules
about cocktails before takeoff.
What do you mean?
in 1st class,
they practically pour
the drinks down your throat.
- Not if you're flying the plane.
- Wait a minute, Clark.
- You're flying the plane?
- Tripp sent me to flight school.
Don't worry.
It's gonna be fine.
I'm expecting a real easy trip
across the pond.
You two can just
lean back and relax.
- You guys!
- Hi, karen.
hi.
Hey, Lisa,
my shopping buddy.
What a surprise.
- Could you get the luggage for us?
- Yes, ma'am.
Yeah, daddy told us that
you guys were taking the jet,
so we thought we would just hitchhike.
you don't mind. Do you?
No, no, no, no. It's fine.
It's...
perfect.
This place is incredible.
Please tell me that we don't
have to spend the whole day
with Karen and Freddy.
I'm guessing
that Freddy's out golfing
and Karen's out cold.
we can just sneak out of here.
Buon giorno, amici.
Hey, Karen.
You're up early.
I know. The espresso
in Italy is so good.
I've had, like, four already.
You guys look
freshly laid.
Am i interrupting?
- Not at all.
- No.
- What do you want to do today?
- What do we want to do?
Well, Karen i have some stuff
to do for your dad, a little business.
We don't mind.
We're game for anything.
Absolutely anything.
Nick and i don't get
to spend much time alone,
So we're...
I get...
I get it.
"love time."
Yeah.
I hope that's not a problem.
No, not at all.
You go your way,
we'll go ours.
Italy's big, you know?
Oh, my god!
these are so good.
These are lto, molto yummy.
You want some?
- Holy crap!
- What?
I hope Ryan's taking penicillin.
That girl is septic.
Are there any pictures of me?
I haven't looked.
Listen, i think my wife
is on to us, all right?
So we're just gonna
have to be a little more...
Listen.
What is it?
Chora.
Chora?
That's your bully?
She's a girl!
Come on.
Get it together, man.
I'll pick you up
after school.
You better run, hot dog.
mama's hungry!
Right this way.
Allora, today, we have
for to taste
is the rosso di valtellina.
Also we have the pinot nero
and a very nice gragnano.
- Signora.
- Grazie.
Prego. Signore.
Thank you.
You dot happen to have
chiavennasca, do you?
Si
- Slightly chilled?
Vado lo domandare.
Okay, who's stalking who?
it's such a puzzle.
Hi.
- Hi, Karen.
- Hello.
- How are you? Freddy.
- Nick.
So i guess Italy's not
as big as i thought,
It's gettin' smaller
all the time.
Lei vuole mangiare con noi?
Do you mind if--
'cause we drove
all the way here,
and it'll be so awkward
if you're sitting next to us
but not, you know, with us.
We wouldn't want it
to be awkward.
Oh, perfect. Okay.
I love this now.
- How the hell did you get in here?
- I followed the flower delivery guy.
Don't worry. Your wife
is out getting waxed.
I'm sorry.
I meant your sister.
- What the hell is this?
- Publicity stunt.
You kissed
Ryan "creepo" Casdale.
My agent told me to.
Does your agent make decisions
for your lips?
What about us?
Jeremy, what do i want
with some actor
who looks in the mirror
more often than i do?
He's a boy.
He's a baby.
You're my man.
You're my big man.
You didn't sleep with him?
I fell asleep a few times
while he was talking,
- But that's about it.
- Promise?
I promise.
I do.
Here.
Wait, wait.
I have to tell you something.
What?
You want me to put on
explosions in the sky?
Yeah. But i have to
tell you something.
Don't you ever knock?
That's your girlfriend?
I was gonna tell you about it.
I swear.
So those tickets
to "babes in toyland,"
they weren't a gift at all?
They were subterfuge?
- They were subterfuge and a gift.
- And you!
- What?
- Weren't my bangs enough?
Oh, it was a completely
different approach-
- Get out of my house, you whore!
- Let it go.
Can't we just all talk
about this like adults?
Get her drippy butt
out of my house!
- No!
- What?
She's not leaving.
This is...
utterly mortifying.
the worst thing
that's ever happened.
Juliet, you are my sister,
and i love you.
but i can't choose sides.
Well, guess what.
You just did.
I gotta go throw up.
You know, even when we were little,
- I knew you were grounded.
- I got grounded a few times, maybe.
I don't know if i was grounded.
Yeah, when i met him
at william and mary,
he was kind of a flake.
A naughty flake.
Well, you know,
I've just always seen him
as such an old soul.
I don't know if you know him
as well as you think you do,
Karen, really.
I don't think
you do either, Lisa.
I've known him for a long ti--
longer than you, and i--
Well, i remember Nick and i
walking on the beach
And the way the sun
hit your hair. It just...
glistened.
Signore George.
Yeah.
Would you follow me,
please, to the tasting room?
Yeah, i guess
You asked for
the chiavennasca.
Yeah, i did.
If you'll excuse me,
i just have
some family business.
All right.
you all keep bonding.
Will do.
Come il tuo italiano?
Non buono.
Mi dispiace.
What a pity.
To speak english
puts me in mind
of irretrievable times.
ah, well.
This the chiavennasca?
No, no. It's vin ordinaire.
So you're dutch's boy?
Yeah.
I guess so.
For what do you seek?
When my dad died, his briefcase
was full of information
about Simon Elder.
Incriminating information.
Elder, as in
the techno-philanthropist?
Yeah.
Any idea why he might have
had a file like that?
Did i do something wrong?
I'm sorry.
If you are who you say you are,
i will find you.
If not, well.
Those are your bad dreams.
Arrivederci.
Me wearing
the superman underoos
and he's wearing
wonder woman.
I'm not kidding.
There he is.
Hi, baby. Just in time.
- What's going on?
- We can go.
No. We've moved on
to spirits.
Nick,
we're drinking grappa.
Maybe the two of you
have had enough?
Loosen up, baby.
We are in India.
We are?
What did i just say?
You said we were in India.
Nick.
It's grappa.
Remember?
Remember what?
What about grappa?
We had a couple of bottles
the night
that Nick proposed to me.
Nick proposed to you?
- You didn't tell her?
- When would that have come up?
When did he propose to you?
When we were 19.
Why didn't you tell her?
You're so secretive.
Because we were 19.
Exactly. We were 19.
It's ancient history.
It was down by the lake,
just down--
down the hill
from where we're all staying.
And we...
I don't know, we'd been,
like, sailing all day
or playing tennis.
I just remember him saying
that he--
He knew it wasn't
gonna be easy
because i was so rich
and he wasn't.
But he knew we were
supposed to be together.
Hey, Karen, can we...
Oh, let her finish.
Let her finish.
And then we, you know,
we drank a bunch of grappa.
- And, um...
- Lisa.
- You know, just spent time...
- Lisa, i should've told you.
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
God,
you are a bitch sometimes.
I know.
It's a problem.
Lisa come on. I was 19.
I was in Italy.
I was drunk on grappa.
Everyone proposes
when they're 19.
- It didn't mean anything.
- Well, it meant something to her.
and it certainly
would've meant something
if she'd said yes.
Lisa, it was a thousand years ago.
When we started dating,
we exchanged plenty of stories
about our old boyfriends
and girlfriends, remember?
- Yeah, So?
- There must have been some reason
you decided to leave
this particular one out
unless maybe you forgot.
Did you forget?
I don't understand
why you don't just go
to the headmaster
and tell him this bullying
is taking place.
Because the little orphan
is never gonna learn
- How to stick up for himself.
- Like you learned?
18 years of being beat up by girls,
and what's his revenge?
The ministry.
- That's awful.
- Every summer, your uncle Brian
would come back from vacation
with aunt deirdre
and cousin derinda
covered in bruises.
it was tragic.
What did they call you again?
The princess?
What did they call you again,
fatty-paddy?
I wouldn't mind
a change subject.
I swear, sometimes i don't know
where you children come from.
Why did you really enter
the church, uncle Brian?
I didn't see anywhere else
in the world i fit in.
I didn't want to pursue business
or politics.
I never...
felt really well liked.
So a life of leisure
didn't seem appealing.
You need friends
for that kind of thing.
So, you know, i guess
i really never felt
a part of the human family.
Well, thank you
for your honesty.
Ellen, thank you.
Take it easy, sailor.
You're gonna overheat
your blood.
Sorry.
I haven't seen a child
pepper food that vigorously
since you were a boy, Brian.
Bon appetit.
You should probably
answer that.
I'm sure
it's your girlfriend Karen
calling to invite you
for a midnight swim...
or maybe another romantic
grappa party or something.
Pronto?
Mr. George.
Harold Templeton.
May we convene?
I apologize for my abrupt exit
the last time.
But you can never be too sure
who's who in my line of work.
Your father
would've understood.
He was...
also a complex man.
What happened?
Three months ago,
he asked me
compile information
on Simon Elder--
anything vexing.
What for?
To blackmail him?
I never asked.
It was not my concern.
But when your father
came to me a 2nd time
and asked me to perform
similar due diligence
on Tripp Darling,
well, i realized
he was wking
for someone else,
so i washed my hands
of it.
So who was my father
working for? Do you know?
Did he ever mention someone
that he referred to
by the letter "c"?
No.
Not that i recall.
and there's your chiavennasca
for Mr. Darling.
- Hey.
- Hey
I'm really sorry
about earlier.
You know what?
Save it for someone who cares.
I don't want these shoes
anymore. You know why?
- They don't fit?
- No, actually, they fit fine.
I don't want these shoes
because these shoes--
these $1,200 shoes--
and for everything that is
selfish and foul
and consumptive
and creepy about you.
Nick and i have...
a daughter.
And, you have this dream,
and it's never
going to come true.
So stay away from my husband
and...
stay out of my way.
- Who was that, baby?
- Nobody.
Make me a drink,
would you?
Go away.
We need to talk.
I'm not speaking to you,
traitor.
Juliet... I love her.
Love?
Okay, i really like her.
Like?
I'm moderately interest--
Why can't you be cool
about this?
Because she doesn't care
about you.
She's only using you to get at me.
Now i get it. yeah.
It's about you. Right?
- Everything is just all about you.
- I'm just trying to protect you.
You don't have to!
You're the one running around
telling everyone
you want to be independent.
You want your own career,
to move out.
You can't even let
your twin brother date someone
you had a stupid fight with
over bangs? why?
Because it makes you feel so lonely
and freaked out and threatened.
I mean, bangs?
I feel
so far from home.
Yeah,
I know what you mean.
I hate that we can't just get on
a plane right now and go.
Well, we could,
but we'd have to fly
with Karen and Freddy.
Well, they have
their private jet.
We are flying back like--
like normal people
with... lines and security
and peanuts and back pain
and... life.
God...
it's...
weird being married.
It's so weird.
Yeah...
it is.
Promise me something.
What?
Promise me that we are never
going to have to come
all the way to italy for a stupid
bottle of wine again, please.
Lisa...
We didn't come here
for a bottle of wine.
I needed to meet with a guy
who did some work for my dad.
When did you do that?
When i went down
to the wine cellar.
He's a spy.
It's a long story.
I look forward to hearing
about it halfway over the atlantic.
You know, i count on you
for so much, Lise.
You know that?
- A little.
- When i look at you,
here's this perfect line
from me through you
to the center of the earth.
You keep me connected
to everything.
You do the same for me.
And kiki does it
for both of us.
it's a...
it's a beautiful thing.
You know, i don't think my dad
felt that way about anyone.
You don't think he felt
that way about you?
I don't know.
I really don't.
Lei vuole fare l'amore?
You picked up
a little italian?
Enough to get by.
yeah?
Victoria,
would you excuse us?
Yes, sir.
Thank you so much...
For all you do.
Silver up to snuff?
It's getting there.
We need to talk.
What's that?
D.n.a. results.
You lied to me.
What the hell
have you done?
I found out
what i needed to now.
the only way that i could
give the fact that my wife
doesn't tell me the truth.
So...
So you know?
I haven't read
the results.
I won't.
I want to hear it
from you.
Which of our children
isn't mine?
Which one is Dutch's?
I'll tell you.
But you've got to promise me
nothing will change...
As far as the children
are concerned.
I don't have to
promise you anything.
You took my life--
You took my life
that i placed in your hands
to help me carry it
safely to the grave,
and you laid it on every bedside
table you could find
while you pursued
whatever it was
you were pursuing
all those years.
I hope it was
the obliteration of yourself,
because, my god,
that's what you've achieved.
Just tell me the truth...
Or leave right now.
I mean it.
You're the only woman
in the world for me, Tish.
But can't live every day
with my face being pushed
into this filth.
If you want me
in that bed tonight...
Tell me.
All right.
I'll tell you.
No, Chora!
You're hurting me!
What's the matter?
You gotta be nicer to me,
or else
- I'll tell mei ling hwa the truth.
- What is this, blackmail?
You told me to find
a weakness.
You cunning little turd.
What do you want?
Get off of me!
Help me. please.
Hi, Chora.
Those are nice hair clips.
what are those, bumblebees?
Hornets.
You know god, Chora?
Well, He's sorta my boss.
And you see that boy
over there?
God told me
you're not being
very nice to him.
And god is so disappointed.
So from now on, He wants
you two to be friends.
Otherwise you're gonna burn
in hell for eternity,
and eternity's
a very long time.
Are we clear?
Good girl.
So i'm assuming you met
our friend--Mr. Templeton?
Yes, i did.
And what did he have
to say?
Well, you were right.
He put the elder file
together for dad.
Yeah, i figured.
To your good health.
Cheers.
So what do you think?
Be honest.
My father was working
for someone else.
Could it be that "c"
that was in his calendar?
I don't know. Maybe.
But he was gathering
that information for someone.
And Templeton stopped helping
when he found out about it.
So that dossier,
all that information
on Simon Elder,
that wasn't just Dutch
doing... diligent work
on my behalf?
No, it doesn't look like it.
He was gathering information
about you as well.
- About me?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
- Why? You didn't do it.
- I know, but he--
- No, you're you.
and you're good.
that's true.
Well...
Anything happen
while i was gone?
Nothing unexpected.
Things continue
to reveal themselves.
Reality.
I like looking
at the stars because...
You know, they're so...
Hot and fiery
and explosive,
but it feels totally safe
and totally exciting
all at the same time,
you know?
I never thought a girl
could make me feel that way.
But you do.
Looking at you is like
looking at the stars.
You make me feel like i'm--
i'm a part of everything,
like i have a place.
Are you being for real?
Natalie, i'm "for realer"
with you
than i've ever been
with anybody.
Me, too.
Maybe we're in love.
I think we are.
Jeremy.
Yeah.
I'm pregnant.
That's wet.
Nicholas George?
Yeah.
Simon Elder.
Want to go for a ride?
Sure.
Transcript : www.swsub.com || Synchro : Grischka
~www.SeriesSub.com~