Previously on The Vampire Diaries...
For over a century,
I have lived in secret, until now.
I know the risk,
but I have to know her.
She's a dead ringer for Katherine.
You have no idea of the
future I have planned for us.
You, me, and Damon.
Our love for Katherine wasn't real.
Katherine never compelled
me. I knew everything.
It was real for me.
I'm going to bring her back.
- Tell me how to get into the tomb.
- The grimoire.
- Where is it?
- Check the journal, Jonathan Gilbert's.
- Can I borrow your ancestor's journal?
- I gave it to my history teacher.
So the grimoire,
that as Emily's, right?
That's what you need to reverse
the spell? I'll help you.
I told Damon that I'd help
him get Katherine back.
But it was a lie.
I can't let him do it.
Then don't. And I'll help you.
Whatever it takes.
Please!
Please, help us!
Please, my husband,
he's been hurt! Please help him!
What are you doing out here in
the middle of the night? It's not safe.
No, sir.
It's not safe.
And that's how it's done.
What happens to the bodies?
I'll take them into the woods and
the other animals will finish them off.
Are you sure you're ready for this?
I'm ready.
I want you to turn me.
When it's time.
Kiss me.
You should get a taste.
- Sorry.
- Don't be.
Soon you won't be able
to get enough.
Mystic Falls Team
1x13 - Children Of The Damned
Croutch, Dark_Chii, McFly,
MiniBen314, Paulp, Thirteen & WoLF971.
Good morning.
I could get used to this.
Rise and shine, sleepyheads.
- Please!
- What are you doing?
- Stop being smutty.
- Seriously, get out of here!
If I see something I haven't seen before
I'll throw a dollar at it. Now listen,
we have some very important
business to discuss.
- And it has to be right now?
- We have lots to do,
now that we're all friends and
working toward a common goal.
So, in order to open the tomb,
we need to find the journal,
to get the grimoire
to undo the spells.
First things first,
since you are Elena Gilbert,
- you're on journal duty.
- Since when am I helping?
Well, Stefan's helping, and you've
taken up residence in Stefan's bed,
ergo...
You don't have to do
anything you don't want to do.
- I'll look for it tonight.
- Good.
How do we know that this journal
will hold the location of the grimoire?
We're really going to take
the word of this vampire?
- He seemed like a bit of a dimwit.
- In lieu of any other options.
What exactly is a grimoire, anyway?
It's a witch's cookbook.
Every spell that a witch casts
is unique unto itself,
so every witch
would document their work.
- Cookbook.
- What about our mystery vampire?
Dimwit obviously
wasn't working alone, so,
whoever's out there
knows who we are.
And I don't like that
disadvantage, so...
chop, chop.
You know, I really like this whole
ménage-threesome team thing.
It's got a bit of a kink to it.
Don't screw it up.
He does have...
Right, yeah.
No, come here.
We shouldn't...
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Make me.
Yes?
Excuse me, miss Katherine.
Miss Pearl is here to see you.
I'll be down soon.
Please ask her to wait.
Thank you, Emily.
Fun's over.
Good to see you, Pearl.
Perhaps we could talk outside.
Would you please tell Mr. Salvatore
that I've stepped away?
Which one?
Both.
How long do you plan on
staying with the Salvatores?
People talk, Katherine.
You, carrying on with both brothers,
doesn't help the situation.
The salvatores have been
kind to take me in.
As far as everyone here knows,
I'm a poor orphan girl from Atlanta,
lost her family in the fires.
A match you lit, no doubt.
Honey, please be careful.
Honorea Fell came by
the apothecary yesterday
with a case of this elixir.
She asked that it be
sold at a reduced rate.
- I don't follow.
- Try it.
What in hell?
- Vervain.
- Why is there...
They know.
They're trying to find us, and
they're getting crafty about it.
The townspeople ingesting vervain?
Well, that's inconvenient.
It might be time for us
to move on again.
I like it here.
I'm not interested in leaving just yet.
Can we go, mama?
Is something wrong?
It's me again.
Soccer chick and foosball champion.
I'll be at the grill
later, if you want,
you know, a rematch, or whatever.
Who are you calling?
You're not, like, into him, are you?
I need him for something.
Get over it.
- Damn it!
- Dude, you gotta stop doing that.
I know. I just... I keep forgetting.
You're new.
You'll get it.
You found the Gilbert journal?
Does that look like
the Gilbert journal?
Well, it's old and musty, and
how am I supposed
to know the difference?
I don't know, I figured
maybe, just maybe,
you've been paying a little
bit of attention since we met.
You know, you don't have
to talk down to me. I'm not stupid.
Here.
Drink.
I don't want you getting itchy around
the witch. She can sense if you're weak.
When can we go hunting again?
This tastes old.
I want fresh blood.
When we get that tomb open,
you can kill anyone you want.
For now, just stay focused on Bonnie
while I try to get the journal
back from Jeremy's teacher.
Why did you choose me?
I needed someone in a position
to be my eyes and ears.
Small town bartender fit the bill.
There are plenty of
bartenders to choose from.
Why me?
You were sad then.
You lacked purpose.
You needed me.
Do you think Damon
really believes us?
That we're both trying to help him?
I don't think Damon
knows what to believe.
Trust isn't something that
comes naturally to him.
You know...
I really think that Damon believes
that everything he's done,
every move that he's made,
he's done for love.
It's twisted, but...
kind of sad.
There are other ways
to get what you want.
You don't have to kill people.
Damon has no regard for human life.
He enjoys inflicting pain on others.
For 145 years,
every single time
that I have let my guard down
and let Damon back into my life, he's
done something to make me regret that.
I'm not gonna make
that mistake again.
So what do you think will happen
if the tomb gets opened
and Damon gets Katherine back?
I think that no matter what Damon
promises, a lot of people will die.
That's Jonathan Gilbert.
What's this?
What are you guys doing?
Just going through some stuff,
feeling sentimental.
Dad had this whole family journal from
years ago. I thought I'd dig it up.
Jonathan Gilbert's journal?
- Yeah, what do you know about it?
- I just did a history report on it.
So where is it now?
I gave it to Mr. Saltzman.
He wanted to see it.
I met Barnett and
Giuseppe this evening.
I saw the skepticism in their eyes
when I showed them the compass.
We're supposed to believe
that can track one of them?
What is it, magic?
- It's science.
- I'll believe it when I see it.
I've been thinking about this church
idea. I believe it could work.
Excuse me, father.
- I didn't know you had guests.
- We'll be done in a few minutes, son.
I'll come back. Forgive me,
Mr. Gilbert, Mr. Lockwood.
- Have you told them?
- Not yet.
We need all the men we can get.
I'll tell them.
You can count on both my boys.
Someone there?
You shouldn't have done that.
Have a seat.
What is this, compressed air?
Did you make it yourself?
Who are you?
I'm not going to hurt you...
unless you try that again.
Now...
Who are you?
I'm a teacher.
Are we going to have
to do this the hard way?
I'm also a historian.
And while researching Virginia, I...
made a few discoveries
about your town.
So you show up like Van Helsing.
Come on.
Tell me the truth.
My wife was a parapsychologist.
She spent her life researching
paranormal activity in this area.
- It was her work that led me here.
- Where's your wife?
Dead.
A vampire killed her.
Where's the Gilbert journal?
- What do you want with it?
- Where is it?
- It's on my desk.
- No, it's not.
It was on my desk.
Anything?
Not yet.
Just a lot of gibberish.
Yeah, some people
just shouldn't journal.
I thought this Gilbert
was the brains.
Don't you have a date?
Wish me luck.
I saw her again today.
The most beautiful woman in town,
with a name just as pretty, Pearl.
Have you thought any more
of what I've said?
We'll leave soon, Pearl, I promise.
I need to take care
of a few things first.
You're going to turn
both of them, aren't you?
Katherine, please.
Be careful.
We'll all be safe, I promise.
Mr. Gilbert's coming.
Quick, your cheeks.
Perfectly rosie.
May I have a moment?
Yes Mr. Gilbert.
I'm still waiting for you to
explain that comet in the sky.
Your mother has an admirer.
As descendants of
the founding families,
they'll want to know that
they can count on you.
Of course they can.
Is there any doubt?
I'm not sure your bother Damon
understands the importance of duty.
Damon left the confederacy
on principle.
It was his choice and
should be respected.
You'll forgive me if I have
trouble respecting a deserter.
- I never asked for your respect.
- Good for you, Damon.
Because all I have
is disappointment.
You said the town is in trouble?
There's been too many deaths.
It is time for us to fight back,
stop these killers.
- Killers? What are you talking about?
- We live amongst demons.
You're being cryptic now, father.
Why don't you just say the word?
Vampires.
They exist.
And they live amongst us.
But we have a plan to kill them.
And you're going to help us.
My father never approved
of anyone I dated,
which only made me want them more.
Of course.
- What about you?
- There were a few guys.
Logan isn't the only
loser I've dated.
They ever find him?
Or is he still missing?
He's not missing.
He's in the Bahamas
working on his tan.
Very entitled, that one.
Marches to his own drum.
He's a Fell.
They're all snooty.
- Where have you been?
- We're cooking dinner.
Is Stefan with you?
He'll be here soon.
How long have you been aware of me?
I learned just recently.
- What about your brother?
- You met Damon.
Who do you think killed my wife?
You certain it was Damon?
I witnessed it.
If you're here for revenge,
this is going to end
very badly for you.
I just want to find out
what happened to my wife.
I thought you just said
that Damon...
I saw him
draining the life out of her.
He must have heard me coming.
He just...
disappeared.
So did her body.
They never found her
Damon can never know
why you're here.
He'll kill you without blinking.
I can take care of myself.
No, you can't.
I can help you.
If you let me.
Don't do that.
Do what?
You know what.
That move was deliberate.
I was deliberately trying
to get to the sink.
Speaking of Stefan, where is he?
He's missing family night,
which I am enjoying immensely.
Is it real?
- Is what real?
- This renewed sense of...
brotherhood.
Can I trust him?
Yes, you can trust him.
I'm wearing vervain, Damon.
It's not going to work.
I'm not compelling you.
I just want you to answer me.
Honestly.
Of course you can.
You can trust me, Mr. Salvatore.
I would never cheat.
I'm losing over here.
Again!
She's good.
I almost believe
she genuinely likes him.
Perhaps she does.
She knows father would have
her killed if he knew the truth.
Not if we talk to him,
explained how we feel.
- He could help us keep her safe.
- Have you gone mad?
No, father would
drive the stake in her himself!
- That's not true. We can trust him.
- Not with this.
Please, promise me
you won't tell him, Stefan.
I promise.
There was a time when
I trusted him more than anyone.
Trust breeds trust.
You have to give it to get it.
Are you lecturing me?
Do you need to be lectured?
I just want her back.
I'm sure you can understand that.
I can understand that you
would do anything for her, yes.
Then you understand
what I will do
if anyone gets in my way.
You said you never
played this thing before.
I'm a fast learner.
Quick reflexes.
Who are you dodging?
This girl Anna.
She can be... persistent.
Is she hot?
Yeah yeah, but she can be weird.
Hot trumps weird, trust me.
He is ridiculously hot!
He's an ass.
What are you doing
with all this stuff?
I thought there might be something
about my birth parents.
Have you told Jeremy?
I will.
When the time is right.
That's Stefan.
Dude!
Well?
Admit it.
I can't sing.
You were great.
Come on, totally trashed
a Metallica song.
Well, first mistake,
Metallica karaoke?
Well, at least I could admit it.
The woman with
the tattoos loved you.
Next time,
I'm going to throw out my Pearl Jam.
Next time?
So...
- what are your friends up to tonight?
- They're all doing their own thing.
Caroline's at her dad's,
Elena's with her boyfriend.
Elena Gilbert, right?
- I remember. You guys used to hang out.
- She's my best friend.
Yeah, my friends, they all moved away
after graduation, and I didn't.
So we just kind of drifted apart.
Elena and I are bonded for life.
I can't imagine it either way.
- That tight, huh?
- She's my...
sister. I mean, I'd die for her.
- Who took it?
- I don't know.
You know what, it's that teacher.
There's something really off about him.
He doesn't know anything.
- Somebody got to him right before me.
- Who else knew it was there?
- Damon, leave him out of it!
- Why, what's the big deal?
So...
I heard you found a really
cool journal from back in the day.
- Who else did you show it to?
- Huh?
Don't ask questions, just spill.
- You're kidding me, right?
- Jer, did you tell anyone
other than Mr. Saltzman
about Jonathan Gilbert's journal?
Why is everybody
so obsessed with that thing?
Who else did you tell?
- Just that girl Anna.
- The hot weird one?
- Wait, who is Anna?
- That's what I want to find out.
How do you know her?
I just know her.
She wants me to meet her
at the Grill tonight.
Perfect.
I'll drive. Come on.
Okay, I'm alone.
Give me all the deets,
Bonnie. I'm dying.
It's going great.
He's a perfect gentleman.
- Gentleman, huh?
- I know!
Boring, huh? I just want to
grab him and lay one on him.
- So, why don't you?
- 'cause I'm a chicken.
You're a powerful witch goddess.
Come on, seize the day, Broom Hilda.
I'm going to text you later
with more details.
You better.
Where's Damon?
He left to track down Jeremy's friend
Anna, see if there was anything there.
Aren't you gonna go with him?
If he gets to the journal
- before we do then...
- Doesn't matter.
- What is that?
- It's a copy of it.
How did you get it?
Well, Mr. Saltzman
made a copy and was
- kind enough to loan it to me.
- He did?
Not exactly, but I got it.
You just couldn't
live without me, huh?
I kinda miss my daily dose
of cute stalker chick.
Funny.
Let's play.
The sheriff was here earlier.
He bought large volumes
of the vervain elixir.
Did he try to put his hands
on you again?
Doesn't he always?
She's saving herself
for Jonathan Gilbert.
I'm beyond saving. We know that.
How can you be so calm?
They're getting closer
to you every day.
We are the respectable ladies
of Mystic Falls.
Thanks to Emily,
we walk the streets in daylight.
- No one will ever suspect us.
- Not unless a human tells them.
I'd sooner die.
And soon enough, you will.
Mrs. Fell is approaching.
Thank you, Annabelle.
Here's a reference that
he wrote about Emily.
"The Fell family
believed it should be I,
"not them, who protected
the witch's spell book.
But I feared she would
haunt me from the hereafter.
They mocked my fear, but
it was Giuseppe Salvatore who..."
Is that your father?
"It was Giuseppe Salvatore
who removed my fear.
He told me he would protect
the secret of the spell book.
He said he would carry it
to his grave."
To what do I owe this pleasure?
Did I interrupt your writing?
These are the dull musings
of my troubled mind.
A great mind.
Still. I will carry
the real secrets with me...
To your grave.
And a full grave it will be.
Now, speaking of troubled minds,
what's on yours?
I have concerns about
your plan for the vampires.
And why is that?
We are making the assumption
that all vampires are
as evil as they've been characterized,
but what if that's not true?
Do you have any evidence
to the contrary?
Do you know of any vampires?
No, of course not.
But are we to take what others say
at face value?
You always taught us so differently.
These creatures
are of the darkest parts of hell.
They have the ability
to control your mind,
seduce your spirit.
They are deadly.
They must be destroyed.
Those who stand with them,
those who bring shame to their
families will be destroyed as well.
I know where it is.
Okay, I give up.
Damn.
You're strong for a little thing.
I was wondering how long it
would take you to find me.
Why isn't your father
buried in your family's tomb?
It wasn't built
until well after he died.
Are you sure the grimoire's
in there with him?
As sure as I could be.
Great.
I can do this on my own.
And I said I would do
whatever I can to help.
- I know, and I appreciate that, but...
- This town is my home, Stefan.
My friends and family
are here. You're here.
I don't want that tomb
opened any more than you do.
I'm sorry that you have to do this.
What is that?
A gift.
From Damon?
From Emily, actually.
And when will you stop
worrying about Damon?
I want you all to myself.
Just as he wants me,
but I'm the one who gets
to make all the rules.
- And why is that?
- Because I'm spoiled.
Yes, you are.
And selfish.
And because I can do this.
And this.
What?
- What?
- Vervain.
What?
Go get the sheriff.
Tell him we have a vampire.
- What? No!
- Do as I say, son!
Nothing that you feel
for her is real.
She's a vampire, Stefan!
A monster!
I fed you vervain hoping
it would expose her.
- How did you know?
- Your sympathy for their plight.
I didn't raise my sons
to be so weak.
The sheriff, now.
Go, quickly!
Now, son!
How long have you been here?
I arrived around half-past comet,
watching you screw up every
chance you had to open that tomb.
How did you know about the spell?
I didn't say much back then,
which means I heard everything.
If you've been here the whole time
then why are we just
crossing paths right now?
I like to use others
to do my dirty work.
Like Logan Fell?
Thanks for that, by the way.
Little bastard shot me.
Logan was an idiot.
We slipped him some blood
when he started getting
all poser slayer with that compas.
I needed his family's journal.
I couldn't let him die.
- What'd you want with the Fell journal?
- I thought it contained the location
of the witch's spell book.
I was wrong.
According to her journal, Honorea gave
the grimoire to Jonathan Gilbert.
And, according to this...
He gave it to your father. So now
you're gonna help me find it.
Why would I help you?
'cause you and I both
want that tomb open.
Sorry.
I work alone.
Well the check's paid.
I'm all yours tonight.
What do you want to do?
This.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing. Sorry.
I just should have waited until
the end of the night to do that.
I didn't mind.
- You know, I'm starting to get tired.
- Do you wanna go?
I was going to say let's
have some more coffee,
get a caffeine buzz,
and, I don't know,
- go out, do something crazy.
- Like what?
Like anything.
I'm gonna run to the restroom.
All right.
What?
Not many girls
can say they've done this.
Is that it?
Well, what do you know?
This is an interesting
turn of events.
I can't let you bring her back.
I'm sorry.
So am I.
For thinking for even a second
that I can trust you.
You're not capable of trust.
The fact that you're here
means that you read the journal
and you were planning on
doing this yourself.
Of course I was going
to do it by myself,
because the only one
I can count on is me!
You made sure of that
many years ago, Stefan.
But you...
You had me fooled.
So what are you gonna do now?
Because if you try and destroy that,
- I'll rip her heart out.
- You won't kill her.
I can do one better.
Give me the book, Stefan.
Or I'm snapping her neck.
And you and I will have
a vampire girlfriend.
Let her go first.
The Book.
I'm not going to give this to you
until she is standing next to me.
The problem is, I no longer trust
that you'll give it back!
You just did the one thing
that ensures that I will.
No don't take her!
Do you know what they'll do to you
if you're branded a sympathizer?
You'll be killed along with them!
Then let me be killed!
Aspirin must be donwstairs.
Is my head supposed to hurt like this?
You'll be fine. That was just a
small amount of blood.
It should pass out of
your system by tomorrow.
Are you okay?
Damon was right. This is...
This is my fault.
I'll help you. We'll get her back.
Help me?!
Don't you think you've done enough?
You promised you wouldn't tell him!
I didn't think this would happen.
You did this.
This is your fault.
I put my faith in my father,
but Damon
put his faith in me, and...
I destroyed that.
This is my fault.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Don't forget that.
I'm gonna get you that aspirin.
You know you're not
staying the night, right?
We're just going to hang out
for a little while.
You're lucky I like you.
Keep the door open.
You got it.
Do you have any aspirin?
- Where'd she go?
- She went to the bathroom.
- Where'd who go?
- He has a friend over.
What's happening?
Get Emily.
And stay hidden.
I'll get us out of here.
Do you see all this? The town's
gone mad running after the demons.
You!?
Please.
I beg you!
I've got another one over here!
This way!
It'll be all right.
You're going to see her again.
I already know how protect them.
I'm going to protect them
There's gotta be more!
Mystic Falls Team
www.forom.com