Previously on
"the vampire diaries"...
Stefan: for over a century,
i have lived in secret
Until now.
I know the risk.
But i have to know her.
The original
johnathan gilbert
had an invention
That was stolen
by a vampire.
Her name was pearl.
I gave your device to damon.
Why don't you
ask him for it yourself?
Mom! Mama!
My wife isobel
spent her life
Researching paranormal
activity in this area.
What have you done to my wife?
I turned her.
Why do i look like her?
You were adopted.
This girl showed up,
16 and about to give birth.
What else do you know
about her?
Just her name--Isobel.
Stop looking.
She doesn't want
to know you.
She's alive?
Does that mean
she's a--
Woman: hello, rick.
Isobel.
It's good to see you.
You look good.
I hear that you're
a high-School history teacher?
How--How is that?
Where have you been,
isobel?
I don't have any reasons
that are gonna comfort you.
I don't have any explanations
that are gonna satisfy you.
I wanted this.
It's that simple?
Yeah.
You were supposed to
mourn me and move on.
You were my wife.
And i loved you.
How could i not
search for you?
Because i wasn't lost, rick.
I understand that you know
my daughter elena.
Oh.
And i hear that she's been
looking for me.
So...
I want you to arrange for
a meeting with us.
You want me...
[clears throat]
To deliver a message?
Heh.
Yeah.
Screw you...
You selfish bitch.
What do you want
from me?
I told you.
I'm not gonna
do anything for you.
You better tell elena
that i want to meet,
Or i'm gonna start
killing the citizens of
this town one by one,
And i'm gonna start with
your history students.
Got it?
http://www.addic7ed.com
I'm supposed to help build
the miss mystic float
For the founder's day
parade.
If i don't, i get
the wrath of caroline.
But i wanted
to check in first.
Well, i'm doing great.
Thanks for asking.
I'm checking on stefan.
Oh, him?
Oh. He's--He's terrible.
What's the matter?
He's just back to boring,
Strait-Laced, off the junk.
You've successfully cured him of
Anything that was interesting
about his personality.
Don't forget who helped me.
I hate myself.
Hey, did uncle john
mention anything to you
About my field trip
with the history teacher?
No, i've still been
avoiding him.
Why? What's he up to?
I don't know.
But i'd love it if you
could find out for me.
I gotta go. I'm late.
Have fun
with the mystic queen.
I know i did.
Elena called.
These are the specs
for the history
department's
Founder's day float.
We're gonna be recreating
the battle of willow creek.
Tyler's been nominated head
of the production design.
By who?
By me.
I've seen
your sketches,
and they're good.
Look, i'm not really
into the whole--
Yeah, well, you just
pick your team,
be creative, and...
And don't screw up.
Great.
You want
to help me out with this?
Not really, no.
Hey, mr. Saltzman.
Come with me.
We need to talk.
Let's reference
last year's
miss mystic float.
This is
what they did last year.
And it's exactly
what we don't want to do.
Ew.
Yeah.
Ok. So, what are
we doing?
Southern classic elegance.
"Gone with the wind"?
How did you know?
You channel
scarlett daily.
So true.
Yeah.
Uhh. Where's elena?
She's supposed to
be helping.
I don't know.
Ok, what's the deal?
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb.
You and elena
are fighting. Spill.
It's nothing.
It's not nothing.
You know, this whole float
Is supposed to be about friends
creating something together,
And everyone is fighting.
Matt and tyler
hate each other.
You and elena
are on the outs.
I--I don't like it.
And i can't fix it
if i don't know what's wrong.
I can't talk about it,
caroline. I'm sorry.
Damon.
Thanks for coming.
Sorry i'm late.
The dog ate my, uh...
Never mind.
What's all
the furrowed brows?
I saw isobel
last night.
Isobel's here?
In town?
You're late.
I didn't realize
there was a schedule.
What's with the side show?
Cherie is a little
jazz singer
That i picked up
in a blues bar
in brooklyn.
And i got the cowboy
at a gay rodeo
in amarillo.
He's gay?
Not right now.
He's very good
to me.
Hey, cherie?
[Speaking french]
I'm teaching them french.
Ooh. I can smell
the judgment
coming off of you.
Well, they're people, isobel,
and you're treating them
Like they're dolls.
If we're gonna be partners,
You really have to stop
being such a hater.
We're in a partnership together
because we share a mutual goal.
Don't ever confuse that for
an acceptance of your lifestyle.
My lifestyle?
So, i assume that you still
don't have the invention.
I'll get it.
I said i would.
Uh, you threatened to
expose damon salvatore.
That didn't work.
You killed
that pearl lady.
Still no invention.
I really don't think
that your plan
is working, john.
Well, you being here
isn't going to help anything.
You failed, john.
I'm gonna take it
from here.
Damon: did you ask
about une john?
Are they working
together?
No.
No, they're not?
No, i didn't ask.
What about the invention?
Didn't ask.
Does she know
about the tomb of vampires?
I don't know.
Did words
completely escape you?
No, i was a little
too distracted by
my dead vampire wife
To ask any questions.
What did she want?
She wants
to see me, damon.
Alaric is supposed to
arrange a meeting.
We don't know why
or what she wants.
You don't have to see her
if you don't want to.
I don't really have
a choice.
She's threatened
to go on a killing spree.
I take it that's...
not ok with you guys.
I want to do it.
I want to meet her.
If i don't,
i know i'll regret it.
Thanks.
Can you hear me?
Thanks for coming.
I'm nervous.
But i'm happy
that you're here.
Love you.
Hello, elena.
You look just like her.
It's eerie.
You've met katherine?
She found me
after i turned.
Genetic curiosity,
i suppose.
She would be fascinated
by you.
Is that how you can
walk in the day?
Katherine helped me
obtain it.
Who's my father?
Not important.
He was a teenage waste of space.
A name would be nice.
It would, wouldn't it?
You ask a lot of questions.
Why did you compel
that man to kill himself
Right after he told me
to stop looking for you?
Traumatic impact.
Wish it would have been
more effective.
Human life means
that little to you?
Means nothing to me.
It's just part of being
what i am.
No. It's not.
I know other vampires.
That's not true.
Your boyfriend over there
by the pool table?
Stefan salvatore.
Why stefan?
Why didn't you go for damon?
Or do enjoy them both?
Like katherine did?
we should be in there.
No.
Isobel made it clear
We're not to
step foot inside.
I'm not gonna kill her
in a crowded restaurant.
You're not gonna
kill her, period.
She ruined your life,
and you still want
to protect her?
She's my wife.
Was--Was my wife.
I looked for
the woman i married,
but she wasn't there.
Whoever that is is...
Cold and detached.
[Scoffs] yeah.
She's given up
her humanity.
Yeah, see,
i don't get that.
Stefan has his humanity.
He's a good guy.
Oh, you're a dick
and you kill people,
but i still see
Something human in you.
But with her,
there was...
There was nothing.
You can turn it off...
Like a button you can press.
I mean, stefan's different.
He--He wants the whole
human experience.
He wants to feel every episode
of "how i met your mother,"
So he shuts his feelings out.
The problem is,
As a vampire,
your instinct is not to feel.
Isobel chose the easier road--
No guilt and shame...
No regret.
I mean, come on.
If you could turn it off,
wouldn't you?
You haven't.
Heh. Of course
i have, rick.
That's why i'm so fun
to be around.
Elena: why did you
want to meet me?
It can't be to just
catch up.
Because i'm curious
about you.
But the real reason is
I want
what your uncle wants--
Johnathan gilbert's invention.
How do you know
my uncle?
I used to spend a lot of time
here when i was younger.
John had a crush on me
for years.
He was the first one
that told me about vampires.
So, what made you
want to be one?
It's a very long list
of reasons, elena,
All of which i'm sure
you've thought about.
That was your first lie.
It's inevitable.
You're gonna get old.
Stefan won't.
Forever doesn't last very long
When you're human.
I'm sorry,
But i don't have
what you're looking for.
Sit down.
And tell your boyfriend
to walk away.
I want the invention.
I don't have it.
I know that.
But damon does.
And you're gonna
get it for me.
He's not gonna
give it to me.
Then the blood
will be on your hands.
It was nice
meeting you, elena.
Hey, anna.
Uh, where are you?
What's up? Uh...
Give me a call
when you get this.
How is anna?
I like that girl.
She has fire.
Uh, i--I don't know.
She won't return
my calls.
Girl trouble?
No, no trouble.
Anna just owes me
a call. That's it.
Is it the girl
that i saw you with
at the founder's pageant?
You two are gettin'
pretty hot and heavy, huh?
When was the last time
you saw her?
Why?
I'm just
making conversation.
No one else in this house
likes me.
At least i can talk to you,
especially if you need someone
to talk to about girls.
Ugh. Please.
So, seriously,
how well do you know anna?
I know anna
extremely well.
Well, know that you can
talko me about anything.
I'm here to answer
any questions that you have.
I'll help you
in any way i can.
Why?
'Cause your dad
would want me to.
I'm, uh, i'm good.
[Music playing]
uh-Oh, cherie.
You won again.
Hope i'm wearing
my good underwear.
Heh heh.
It's just on
blast from the past
After another.
No, no, no.
cherie.
Damon: it's good
to see you, isobel.
I was just having fun with
your naughty little minion.
How'd you find me?
Searched all
the neighborhood
bank-Owned foreclosures
And found
the most expensive one.
Oh, i should have known.
You were the one
who taught me that.
Mm-Hmm.
What are you really doing here?
Well, you caused
quite a stir when
you blew into town.
Oh.
So, everyone except for
me you would have hurt.
I'm so sorry.
Did you bring
the device?
What are you doing
with john gilbert?
We dated a few times
when we were young.
He was a little bit
in love with me.
I'm sure one of the many.
You know,
this little invention,
what do you want with it?
Oh, me personally?
I don't want anything with it.
I'm just doing what i'm told.
You know, damon,
we're on the same si..
[Scoffs] oh, yeah?
Which side is that?
Katherine's.
She wants john gilbert
to have the device.
And i think that you know
that she's not happy
When she doesn't get
what she wants.
Why are you doing
her dirty work?
Don't kill the messenger.
We both know that you can't
control katherine.
She does what she wants.
[Scoffs] so do i.
Oh, really, damon? You do?
What should we do now?
Oh, yeah.
Resurface.
Now that i have
your attention, listen up.
You do not come into my town,
threaten people i care about.
Going after elena--
Bad move.
You leave her alone,
or i will rip you to bits,
Because i do believe
in killing the messenger.
[Whispering]
you know why?
Because it sends a message.
Katherine wants something
from me,
You tell that little bitch
to come get it herself.
Hi.
Hey.
I couldn't sleep
last night.
You were
obviously upset
about something,
And i just
walked away.
That's not me.
That can't be us.
You're my friend,
elena.
If you need me,
i'm here for you.
And i'm sorry
i couldn't show you
that yesterday.
I met my birth mother.
Oh.
Was it...
Are you ok?
Uhh!
Hey, man.
Yeah?
So, caroline
tells me
You've been
on your own
the past 2 weeks.
Is everything ok?
You're asking me
about my mom. Seriously?
Look, man, why don't i just
have her give you a call when
she walks back through town?
Dude...
That's not
what i meant.
Ok? I'm just
trying to...
I don't know
what to say.
Well, good, man.
Don't say anything,
'Cause you're a dick.
End of story.
I know...
Whatever.
Bonnie: thanks for
meeting me.
I wanted you
to see this.
Is that emily's
spell book?
I've been going through it
since grams died.
Check this out.
That's the vampire compass.
Yeah.
According to emily,
johnathan gilbert
Never actually
succeeded in
inventing anything.
Emily secretly
spelled them all
with magic--
Compass...
Rings...
And the mystery device
you told me about.
Yeah, that's it--
Well, part of it.
Damon only has the one piece.
Emily pledged
her loyalty to katherine.
But she couldn't stand by
and watch innocent people
get killed.
This was the only way
she could think of
to help--
To let johnathan gilbert
believe he'd actually
invented these devices.
Does it say what it does?
Are you sure this is
what isobel wants?
Yeah, i'm sure. Why?
This is a weapon...
Against vampires.
Elena!
Hey. Um...
have you seen stefan?
I need to find him.
No, not lately. Listen.
Um, you have a second?
Uh, yeah. What's up?
What's going on?
Well, it's anna.
I left her
all these messages,
And she hasn't
gotten back to me--
Not even a text.
Anna?
I didn't know that you guys
were still friends.
We're more than friends.
Look, something could be
seriously wrong.
And if you know anything,
you gotta tell me.
I haven't talked
to her, jer.
Are you lying to me
right now?
Why would you say that?
'Cause that's what
you do, elena. You lie.
You lie about everything.
I know what anna is.
And i know
that you know.
So, tell me.
Do you have any idea
where she is?
No.
But jer...
Jeremy. Wait.
Jeremy!
Isobel.
What are you doing here?
I'm your mother, elena.
I want to be
more involved in your life.
I don't want you in my life.
I understand that.
You already have
a lot of people
that you care about.
But i've been studying.
Let's see if i got this right.
There is the witchy
st friend bonnie.
Gonna stay away
from that one.
Oh...
Sad little brother jeremy.
And there's caroline--
Obnoxious caroline.
I got all of my info
from her, by the way.
She had no idea
who i was, and she
wouldn't stop yapping.
Oh.
There's matt--
Friend, ex,
yappy's future ex.
Lots of connections there.
Matt's not involved with us.
He's involved with you.
Isn't he?
Look, you shouldn't
be here.
You need to leave.
No.
I have some friends
here, too. Look.
See that man over there
standing next to matt
by the float?
His name's frank.
He's very handsome.
And he's also very handy.
And he noticed that the axle
was kind of rusted,
Which is very dangerous.
So, all you have to do
Is apply a little bit
of pressure, and--
No!
Aah! Uhh!
Boy: hey, get this trailer up!
Come on, guys,
lift it up, please!
Give me a hand!
Uhh! Aah!
Come on, lift.
Oh!
Come on!
Aah!
Call for help.
Caroline: ok.
Why are you doing this?
I'm showing you how easy it is
To hurt the people
that you care about.
You're doing this
just because of
Johnathan gilbert's
invention?
Hand it over
and the fun will stop.
I told you, damon's not
gonna give it to me.
And i think that you
underestimate how much
damon cares about you.
He'll kill you
before he gives it up.
Is that before or after
i kill your brother jeremy?
Elena: jeremy?
Jeremy!
The ambulance is saying
15-20 minutes.
I have my car. I can take him
to the hospital.
Caroline can take me.
I didn't drive.
Then i'll wait.
It's fine.
You will not wait!
Ok, you need
to see a doctor.
Tyler's driving.
End of story.
Go!
I'll bring my car around.
I see you're packing.
That's a good sign.
Won't be long now.
Did you get the missing piece?
Where is it?
I don't have it yet.
Then why did you
call me here?
'Cause i have
the next best thing.
What the hell are you doing?
Getting what i want.
Yeah, but he's my nephew.
And you're gonna let him go
right this second.
The gaudy ring
on your finger--
It comes off.
Come on.
Come on, isobel.
I--I know you.
Ok?
It's me, john.
You can't hurt a kid.
I'll kill him
to prove you wrong.
Really?
Are you that far gone?
Look, i know you've changed.
Ok? But the old isobel
is in there somewhere still.
Isn't she?
Come on. Let him go.
Ok.
Isobel: nice try.
We'll see how you do
without this.
Where's the device?
Damon has it.
He's gonna be difficult
to reason with.
Then we'll--We'll
go go him.
I'll talk to him.
He's not just gonna
hand it ov, , pecially if
it's harmful to vampires.
What if it's not?
Damon: absolutely not.
Just hear me out.
I'm not gonna give the device
To isobel so she can give it
to john who's gonna
turn around and kill me.
I like being
a living dead person.
But it'll be useless.
Bonnie can take
its power away.
I don't trust her.
I can remove
the original spell.
John and isobel
will never know.
No.
No, i'll get jeremy my own way.
Mm-Hmm.
Stefan: really?
How are you gonna
do that? H?
Because isobel
is a vampire,
And jeremy can be dead
the second you
walk in the door.
Are you even up for this?
I mean, no offense.
You're no emily bennett.
Emily knew what she was doing.
I've been practicing.
It's not piano lessons, honey.
What's your
favorite book?
What?
Name a book,
Any book.
Name a book.
How about...
"Call of the wild,"
jack london?
Jack london.
Great parlor trick.
Elena:
we're doing this, damon.
And we're gonna do it
my way.
Now, give me the device.
We're wasting time.
I don't trust you.
I tried to kill you.
Hmm. You're right.
You can't trust me.
But you can trust me.
Thank you.
Here you go.
What is she after?
Your ancestor
invented a weapon--
A device that's extremely
harmful to vampires.
We've been trying to get it.
Why?
'Cause there's a group of
vampires from a long time ago
That wants revenge
on this town.
But why--
Why would a vampire
help you kill
other vampires?
She has her own reasons
for wanting them dead.
Look, jeremy,
No one ever thought
vampires would return
to this town--
Not in modern times.
But they have.
And we have to destroy them.
All of them?
No--There are some
good ones out there.
There's no such thing.
I don't believe that.
Well, your dad did.
And as his son, that should
mean something to you.
How did my father
know about all this?
Who do you think taught me
about the family history?
Done.
Damon: great.
Now what?
Now we give it
to isobel.
[Bell ringing]
Where's the device?
Where's my brother?
This isn't
a negotiation.
Where's
the invention?
Where is my brother?
Do you really think
that i came alone?
For god sakes,
call home.
What?
Call home, ask to speak
to your brother jeremy.
Hello?
Jeremy. Are you ok?
Yeah, yeah, i'm fine.
Uncle john, uh,
hit his head.
It was an accident.
And we're all laughing.
[Chuckles]
Yeah, but, um,
i'm ok.
I'll be home soon,
all right?
Yeah.
You were never
going to hurt him.
No. I was going
to kill him.
Don't look
for any redeeming
qualities in me.
I don't have any.
But you took
a risk with damon.
How did you know
that he was going
to give it to me?
'Cause he's
in love with you.
Thank you.
For what?
For being such
a monumental disappointment.
It keeps the memory
of my real mother
perfectly intact.
Good-Bye, elena.
As long as you have
a salvatore on each arm,
You're doomed.
Katherine was smart.
She got out.
But we all know that
you're not katherine.
Sorry.
Hey, it's anna.
Leave a message.
Jeremy, we have
to talk about this.
No, we really don't.
I don't know
what anna told you,
But there are things
that you need to know.
Yeah?
Because...
I'm pretty sure
that your journal
covered it.
You read my journal?
And save me
the speech about
invasion of privacy,
Because i read
a section about damon
erasing my memory,
About what happened
to vicki.
Jeremy, please,
you don't understand.
The night that vicki died,
It was like mom and dad
died all over again.
It was all over your face.
And it hurt so much
to see you like that.
I just wanted
to take away your pain,
I'm so sorry.
Just get out.
No, jeremy--
Elena!
Just get out.
Please.
Jer, i--
What do you want?
I totally get it.
You here as a history teacher.
It's good.
What the hell
are you doing?
You act like
you don't care,
And yet here you are
hunting me down.
I'm leaving.
I just thought
i'd say good-Bye.
Well, you couldn't be
bothered the first time,
So why now?
You hate me, good.
Does that make it
easier for you?
I mean, what is
the whole point
of this exercise?
What did you expect?
You spent alalalisyingngngngngn,
What did you think
you would find?
The woman
who gave me this...
I mean, you act
like you don't care.
But you cared enough
to protect me
after you left.
I was a different person
back then.
Coffs] right,
right, right.
And that person is gone.
The woman i married,
the woman i loved,
she's just--She's gone.
You expect me
to believe that?
What are you doing?
Well, i'm ring-Free.
I'm vervain-Free,
So either kill me
or compel me,
Because...
I don't believe it.
Not for a second.
[Grunts]
i wanted this.
I needed this.
And i'm going
to regret it forever.
This was my mistake.
Not yours.
You are not going
to remember this.
When you think
of our marriage,
You are going to have
such fond
And beautiful memories.
But that's in the past now,
And your heart's
free of me.
It's better this way.
Good-Bye, rick.
Anna? Hey,
what are you doing here?
My mother.
She's dead.
What?
She was killed.
Oh, my god, anna...
Hey.
Hey, i'm so sorry.
I know i'm not supposed
to be here,
But i don't have
anywhere else to go.
Hey, it's ok.
Would you like one?
Ahem.
Say it.
Whatever it is,
purge, get it out.
It's about what isobel said.
What about it?
Well, i know that
you and elena bonded,
And i know that
she cares about you, and, uh,
I know you care about her.
Well, this is going
in an interesting
direction.
I'm just concerned
about elena being hurt.
She considers you a friend.
Same here. Elena's
a very good friend.
Actually,
she might qualify
as my only friend.
Is that a problem?
So, at the risk
of sounding like a, um,
Like a jealous boyfriend--
Oh, there's no risk.
You do.
History will not be
repeating itself
Where elena's concerned.
Do you understand
what i'm saying?
Sure.
Do you...
understand?
Hey, whatever you say, man.
I mean, honestly,
we're just friends.
And as her friend,
i wasn't looking forward
To telling her
the truth, anyway.
So, i'll let you do it.
What truth?
About john.
'Cause i know you guys
don't like to keep
secrets from each other.
What are you
talking about?
Am i the only one
around here
Who has the ability
to put two and two together?
Isobel. Hello?
She dated john
when she was 15.
She gets pregnant,
and ends up
At the doctor's office
of john's brother.
Now, what do you think
is john's role is
in all of this, huh?
I mean, go ahead,
think about it.
I'll wait. You get it?
You there yet? Hmm?
So, you think
that john
Is elena's father?
Ding ding ding!
[Scoffs]
What proof
do you have?
I don't need any proof.
I have the dna tests
For john, elena,
and [indistinct].
But i know how well
you deal with these
big bombshells, so...
Sleep tight.
Oh, and when you do
tell elena,
And she needs a friend
to talk to about anything...
I'm here for her.
Hello?
On your doorstep,
You'll find what
you've been looking for.
And my ring?
Don't screw this up.
I got it.
I won't fail.
You better not.
Katherine wants
All of those
tomb vampires dead.
And i want to add
two more to that list.
Let me guess.
Stefan and damon.
I don't want
this life for her.
Well, it was always
a part of the plan.
Consider them gone.
She's our daughter, john.
We owe that to her.
I know.
So you're not going
to tell me what happened?
I did something bad,
caroline.
And i lied about it.
To who?
To elena.
I pretended
to do something
I didn't really do.
What are you talking about?
I couldn't do what
she wanted me to do.
It wasn't right.
Grams would have
never done it,
So i couldn't,
either.
But when elena
finds out...
She's never going
to forgive me.
http://www.addic7ed.com