Previously on The Vampire Diaries...
For over a century,
I have lived in secret until now.
I know the risk
but I have to know her.
- What are you?
- I'm a vampire.
- You said you don't kill to survive.
- Animal blood keeps me alive
- but not strong as Damon.
- Hello, brother.
Stefan finally fessed up.
Stay away from me.
That necklace contains
an herb called vervain.
It protects you
from being compelled.
I will keep your secret,
but I can't be with you.
- What is that?
- It's a very important crystal.
- Are you psychic or clairvoyant?
- Technically, gran says I'm a witch.
There was a time when this town was
very much aware of vampires.
- Five bodies all drained of blood.
- They've come back.
- You just don't wanna die, do you?
- She's transitioning.
- Into what?
- A vampire.
- I don't know what's wrong with her.
- She'll be fine.
It'll all be fine.
I'll make sure that she doesn't hurt
anybody. I promise you.
- Later, man.
- See you, bro.
- Everyone's looking for you.
- I know.
- What's wrong, Vic?
- I'm so cold.
Are you on drugs? Everyone thinks
you're off on a bender.
I wish.
What happened in those woods?
Those kids that were killed,
what did you see?
- I'm so scared.
- Come here.
It's okay. I'll take you home.
- I can't control it.
- Control what?
I am so...
hungry, Ty.
And it won't go away.
What are you on?
What drugs did you take?
I want it. I'm so hungry, Ty.
Okay, look,
I'll get you something to eat.
Just sit back.
Let's just get you home.
What is wrong with you?
Let go of me!
What's going on here?
What's wrong with her?
- You don't talk.
- Screw you, dude.
"Dude"? Really? "Dude"?
- Damon, don't.
- Come on. Who's gonna miss this idiot?
Don't you hurt him.
Forget what you saw here tonight.
None of us were here.
Mystic Falls Team
1x07 - Haunted
Croutch
Humanidyne
McFly
MiniBen314
Thirteen
Vaern
WoLF971
- Sorry.
- No, it's cool, I'm done.
You're up early.
Where are you going?
Police station. They're organizing
the search party for Vicki so...
Wait.
Shouldn't you be going to school?
You're kidding me, right?
You shouldn't skip school.
If they find her, we'll know.
That's what phones are for.
Your lips keep movin'.
I don't know why.
Vicki, where are you?
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Tell me where you are,
and I'll come get you.
I just need some time to
figure things out.
Just know that I'm okay.
Please don't worry about me.
I don't understand
why I gotta stay cooped up here.
- Why can't I just go home?
- Because you're changing.
And you don't wanna it alone.
There's nothin' about that
Logan guy I killed in here, not a word.
- Someone's covering it up.
- What is that?
This is a very special,
very old compass.
What was Logan Fell doing with it?.
Aren't you curious?
If you're so worried
that somebody's onto you,
- why don't you just leave town?
- We should all be worried.
I'm hungry.
Do you have anything to eat?
Here.
- What is it?
- It's what you're craving.
Don't lie to her.
It's so not what you're craving,
but it'll do in a pinch, right?
- What is it?
- Yeah, what is it? Is it skunk?
Saint Bernard? Bambi?
Go on. Give it a try.
She's new. She needs people blood.
She can't sustain on that stuff.
Why can't I have people blood?
Because it's wrong
to prey on innocent people.
You don't have to kill to feed.
Just find someone really tasty
and erase their memory
afterwards. So easy.
There's no guarantee
that you can control yourself, okay?
It takes years to learn that.
You could easily kill somebody
and you'll have to carry that with you
for the rest of your life,
which if I haven't made clear,
is eternity.
Don't listen to him. He walks on
a moral plane way out of our eye line.
I say snatch, eat, erase.
Look at me.
We choose our own path.
Our values and our actions,
they define who we are.
Okay, Count Deepak.
I am outta here.
Can I have some more?
Is Stefan here?
Where is he?
And good morning to you,
little miss "I'm on a mission."
How can you be so arrogant and glib
after everything that you've done?
And how can you be
so brave and stupid
to call a vampire arrogant and glib?
- If you wanted me dead, I'd be dead.
- Yes, you would.
- But I'm not.
- Yet.
- Where is Stefan?
- He's upstairs
Singing "the rain in spain."
Knock yourself out.
Where is Vicki?
She's upstairs.
What happens now?
Because my brother is out there
searching for her
with the rest of the town.
- What I tell him?
- I'm working with her but
it's gonna take time.
She's a very volatile
and impulsive personality.
She's a drug user. All that's gonna play
a part in how she responds to this.
So she's a vampire with issues?
What am I supposed to do?
Because I am lying
to everyone that I care about.
What's gonna happen to her?
I'm gonna keep her here with
me until I know that she's safe.
How long is that?
We can talk about that later.
- How are you?
- How am I?
You're kidding?
Was our family burned
in the witch trials?
No, the girls that were persecuted
in Salem were entirely innocent.
You have to have more than
ignorance to trap a real witch.
How did we end up in Mystic Falls?
Our family fled Salem in 1692
and relocated here.
Our ancestors lived in secrecy
for over a hundred years.
It's important that we still do.
Gran, everybody knows
you're a witch.
They also know it's absurd,
it can't be true.
I'm just a kooky lady
that teaches occult at the university.
No one really believes.
They just poke fun.
And let 'em.
Don't let 'em know the truth.
Where's the witchcraft?
I mean, you've been
talking history for two days.
I wanna get to the fun part.
It's not meant to be fun.
It's real, and it's serious,
and you must understand
it before you practice it.
Aren't you late for school?
We shouldn't have
trusted that Logan.
- Weasel with the watch.
- How many are we dealing with?
The coroner thinks one. Something about
the wound radius and the jaw pattern.
Are we in danger?
If it found the watch
then it knows we know,
and could it come after us?
And should I even be saying, "it"?
Or is it a he or a she?
If it has historical town's knowledge
then it'll know where the watch is from.
So, yes,
we could very much be in danger.
So what do we do?
Just keep it quiet. We can't have
the entire town aware of this.
We need to find him
before he finds us.
I heard they're putting together
a search party for Vicki.
She just called. She's okay.
Good. It's great.
I figured you must have been
- going out of your mind.
- Little bit, yeah.
I was just gonna offer.
You know,
if there's anything I could do.
I appreciate it.
I have got your costume.
It's all here.
- Seriously?
- Come on.
Can someone please be
excited that it's Halloween?
I just wanna have fun,
you know, just some
silly, fluffy,
Damon-free fun.
Isn't this the one
you got from Damon?
Wear it. Toss it. I don't care.
I just want it gone.
Have you seen Elena?
Do we know what she's wearing?
I was with grams all weekend.
I haven't talked to her.
Maybe she's with Stefan.
Riding to his castle
on his white horse.
Don't be bitter.
It provokes wrinkles.
Coffee is our friend.
It's the caffeine.
It circulates through our veins
and it warms our body so
we're not so cold to the touch.
What if I wanna drink human blood?
You're gonna have to learn
to live with that urge
and fight it on a daily
basis one day at a time.
Don't start with that
whole 12 steps thing.
School counselor has
been down that road,
- and it doesn't work for me.
- It can work. It's your choice.
So you've never tasted human blood?
- Not in a long time.
- How long?
Years and years.
I'm not proud of my past behavior.
Does this sketchy feeling
ever go away?
It's like I have a massive hangover.
This daylight thing is a bitch.
I need more blood.
Where's your bathroom? I have to pee.
Why do I have to pee?
I thought I was dead.
I'm going to...
I'm gonna get her some more.
All right.
I'll be quick.
False alarm.
My body's feeling really funky.
It's a good funk, but it's weird.
Who are you calling?
- You can't see Jeremy anymore.
- Come on. Don't you start.
- I'm gonna see whoever I wanna see.
- Even though you could hurt him?
- I would never hurt Jeremy.
- I know you think that
but I can't take that risk.
You're gonna have to let Jeremy go now.
Really?
And how long have you been preparing
a "you're not good enough" speech?
I'm assuming it predates
the whole vampire thing.
All I'm saying is
Jeremy is not getting
involved in any of this.
I mean it, Vicki.
Or what?
Let's get one thing straight,
you perky little bitch.
You had my brother whipped
for 15 years,
15 years, and then you dumped him.
When I look at you,
that is all I see,
just so you know.
And I'm gonna see Jeremy whenever
I wanna see Jeremy, because
I have some fun
new toys to play with
and I won't think twice
about ripping your little head off.
You got it?
- She threatened me.
- She's on edge.
Imagine every sense in your
body operating at super speed.
She's uncomfortable
in her own skin and then
- when you throw in her other issues...
- How long before it settles?
- Hours? Days? Weeks?
- There's no rule book.
How long before
you learned to control it?
A while, but I didn't have anybody
helping me. I had to do it on my own.
The thing is it's hard
to resist certain people,
especially when you're new. It's
difficult to separate your feelings.
Love, lust, anger, desire...
it can all blur into one urge, hunger.
- What does that mean?
- It means that Jeremy can't see her,
not now. She might not be able
to resist him and she could hurt him.
Or worse.
I'm not gonna let anybody get hurt.
I need to get going.
Please, Stefan.
There's only so much I can take.
What are you doing?
Just contemplating
the next hundred years.
Why did you do it?
I was...
bored.
You did this to me out of boredom?
It's one of the pitfalls
of eternity.
Now I'm bored.
And all I can think about is blood.
I just want some blood.
I can't think about anything else.
- What is that about?
- That'll ease up.
You've just been cooped up all day.
Let's go.
Where?
Your life was pathetic.
Your afterlife doesn't have to be.
What are you doing?
She's been cooped up in your room
all day. She's not Anne Frank.
Now's not the time for this.
If you're gonna teach her, teach her.
Show her what it's all about.
She could hurt someone.
I'm not takin' her to Disneyland.
We're goin' in the front yard.
Come on.
Bad idea, Damon.
She's a vampire, Stefan.
She should know the perks.
Like what?
Like...
How did you do that?
Come on, Vicki. Live a little.
No pun intended.
My bad.
Is that you?
Get in here.
In a minute. I...
Please come inside.
I've been worried.
Thank God you're okay.
Where were you, Vic?
It's no big deal. Drop it already.
Three people
were murdered in the woods.
The cops were lookin' for you.
They wanna question you.
- They know where I live.
- Everyone was worried about you.
I'm back now. Just let it go.
Are you kidding?
I had a freakin' search party out
lookin' for you while you were off
on your crazy drug trip
and you want me to let it go?
- My head hurts.
- You think?
- What are you doing here?
- Is Vicki home?
- Yeah.
- Can I see her, please?
Don't let him in.
I don't want him in here.
- Did he do something to you?
- I just don't want him in here.
Just let me come in so
I can explain myself.
I don't know what's going on
but I think you should leave now.
Please, now, Stefan.
You gotta call me, Vic. I don't get it.
What's going on with you?
Just call me, please.
So... do you wanna hang out tonight?
We could go to
the Halloween thing at school.
Could be fun.
Cool. Sure. Sounds... sounds fun.
Can't wait.
I know you're upset about Vicki.
I heard she called Matt.
But you can't be with her.
She needs to get better.
The best thing you can
do for her is let her go.
What does that even mean,
"Let her go"?
Okay, sure. Since we're such experts
on letting people go, right?
I know you may not see it
but trust me, Jer.
It's for the best.
For months after mom and dad died,
I felt like crap, like,
"nothing really even mattered" crap.
Now all of a sudden, I get these
moments and things started to feel
just a little bit better and Vicki
was in every single one of 'em.
So you may not see it but trust me.
Keeping me away from
her is not for the best.
Cider for the ladies?
It's a Lockwood special.
No way. Last year,
I was hung over until Thanksgiving.
Lightweight. I am going to drink
until someone is hot enough
to make out with.
Sounds like a plan.
- How many martinis have you had?
- Don't start with me.
Can we go now? We're late
for the Halloween party. Let's go.
So go ahead.
I'd like to finish my drink.
Let me guess.
Daisy Buchanan.
I love a good "Gatsby" look.
I've met you before.
Aren't you
Caroline Forbes' boyfriend?
She had
a schoolgirl crush on me but...
it was cute
but I had to let her down easy.
It's Damon, right?
You remember.
Well, you have a face
that's hard to forget.
What's your last name, Damon?
- Are you any relation to Zach?
- Zach's my uncle.
How do you know Zach?
Are you okay?
I think there's something in my eye.
I know Zach from
the Founder's council.
You know, the Salvatores were
one of this town's original settlers.
Yes, they were.
I wasn't aware that Zach was a member.
I just recently moved back home
and haven't really had a chance
to meet many of his friends.
Will you tell him to return my calls?
I've left several messages.
Zach went out of tow for a bit.
But if it's about the vervain...
You know about the vervain?
I'm a Salvatore.
- Of course I do.
- Of course.
Cheers.
You went
with last year's costume too.
I didn't know that I was coming
till an hour ago.
Me neither.
And you're going as...
you?
He's not talking to me right
now. We got into a fight.
I got into it with Vic too
when she got home.
I'm trying not to smother her
tonight but part of me
- didn't wanna let her out of my sight.
- She's here?
You can't miss her. She's a vampire.
Where did Jeremy go?
- What's the matter?
- I've gotta find him.
What, you're following me now?
You didn't really give me
much of a choice.
- Let me out of here.
- You shouldn't be here.
Crowds like this it makes it even harder
for you to keep yourself under control.
- I'm fine.
- Really?
No headache?
Your stomach's not screamin' at you?
You're not feeling lightheaded
or anxious or cranky, like if
someone looks at you the wrong way
you could just rip their head off?
Do you wanna know what that's called?
It's called hunger
and it's only gonna get
worse and worse
every minute that you pretend
like it's not controlling you.
So you need vervain?
My husband and I only have left
what his parents left him
and Zach had promised
that he could supply us with more.
Well, I talk to him all the time
so why don't I just ask him?
How much do you need?
I mean, how many people, you think?
Well, there's our children
- of course.
- Of course.
And... friends, family,
and everyone on the council.
The council?
Zach knows how many.
But, you know what, I am so late.
My husband is not going
to be happy with me.
Well, are you happy
with your husband?
- You're flirting with me.
- You flirted with me first.
True.
Let me escort you to the school.
It's not safe out there alone.
I mean,
I've seen ten vampires tonight.
Well, if only the real ones
were as easy to find.
How's that search goin'?
We had the Founder's party and
anyone who arrived during the day
was eliminated as a suspect.
And all the rest were
just dead ends, so...
I gotta go.
- Thank God.
- What's the matter?
I lost track of Jeremy.
I was worried.
What's goin' on?
Everything's fine.
I told you to quit bothering me.
- No. Vicki, don't do this.
- He won't leave me alone.
- You need to back off, man.
- Matt, it's okay.
It's not okay.
What the hell is your problem?
She's gone.
I'm trying to help her.
- You scared the hell out of me.
- I'm sorry.
Come on. Come on.
So...
Where'd Caroline run off to?
Do yourself a favor, Damon,
and don't ask me about Caroline.
- So loyal.
- Just stay away from her.
Where'd you get that?
From a friend.
- You know that's mine, don't you?
- Not anymore.
Funny.
- I'd like it back, please.
- I'm not giving it to you.
I'll give it to Caroline
and she can give it to you
- if she feels like it.
- Or I could just take it right now.
I was so worried about you.
I'm fine now, but...
I gotta leave.
What? Where?
I gotta get out of here, Jer.
I can't live at home with Matt.
He just doesn't get it.
No, you can't. You can't just leave.
Come with me.
If you come with me, we
can be together forever.
You're taking that
costume a little too far.
What? What is it?
What the hell?!
Go.
Get inside.
Go!
Get him out of here.
What?
I need your help.
- What happened to you?
- I did something. I don't know.
It came from my necklace.
Where'd you get that?
It's part of my costume.
It's a piece of junk.
That piece of junk belonged to one of
the most powerful witches of our family.
Let me show you.
There she is.
Emily Bennett,
your
great-great-great-great-grandmother.
And there's your necklace.
You should go. I got this.
You did this.
This is your fault.
You confuse me
for someone with remorse.
None of this matters to me,
none of it.
People die around you.
How could it not matter?
It matters, and you know it.
You need to leave.
Your wounds are bleeding
and you need to leave.
Have you seen...
What happened?
Nothing.
Some idiot with some fake blood
got me. I'm gonna go home and shower.
I can't find Vicki.
She totally bailed on me.
I don't know where she is.
Is this what I'm in for,
a lifetime of worrying about her?
You're a good brother, Matt.
Maybe she went home.
Maybe.
Where is he?
Inside.
Do you understand
what happened tonight?
I don't understand.
I mean, I know what I saw but...
She was going to kill me...
Now she's dead. Vicki's dead.
I'm so sorry, Jer.
Make it stop. It hurts.
It's okay. It's okay.
Why does everybody
have to die on me?
Oh, my God. Come here.
Are you okay?
I wanted to help her.
But instead...
How's he doin'?
He's a mess.
I don't want him going
through this again. He's just a kid.
Elena, what can I do? What can I do
to help? I'll do anything.
Can you make him forget?
Please.
I don't know how he'll
ever get past this.
I just want him to forget
everything that happened.
If I did it, there's no
guarantee that it would work...
because of who I am,
because of how I live.
I don't have the ability
to do it right.
I can do it.
If this is what you want...
I'll do it.
It's what I want.
What do you want him to know?
I want you to tell him
that Vicki left town
and she's not coming back,
that he shouldn't look for her
or worry about her.
He's gonna miss her, but
he knows it's for the best.
Part of me wishes that
I could forget, too...
forget meeting you,
finding out what you are and
everything that's happened since.
If that's what you want.
Yes...
it is.
Because...
I don't want it to be like this.
I don't wanna feel like this.
But I can't.
With everything that's happened...
I can't lose the way
I feel about you.
It's done.
Mystic Falls Team
www.forom.com