Previously on The Vampire Diaries...
For over a century I have
lived in secret,
Until now. I know the risks,
but I have to know her.
You didn't tell me
that you had a brother.
It's complicated.
- She's a dead ringer for Katherine.
- Which one of you dated her first?
Katherine is dead, and you hate me
because you loved her.
- I was hoping I'd see you again.
- She's not a puppet. She doesn't exist
for your amusement, for you
to feed on whenever you want to.
They're whatever I want them to be.
Wear it for me, for... good luck.
You want to kiss me.
Vervain in the necklace.
It's been a while
since anyone could resist my...
- compulsion.
- There's nothing human in Damon.
No good, no kindness, no love.
Only a monster who must be stopped.
This is Logan Fell coming to you live
from the streets of Mystic Falls
with breaking news of another
deadly animal attack.
The wild animal terrorizing
the citizens of Mystic Falls
has claimed another victim,
Local high school student...
Police are certain that
forensic evidence will confirm
that this is the same animal
responsible for recent attacks.
You know it's coming next.
Bad dream?
Do you know how easy it was
to get into your head just now?
You really need some human blood.
It might even the playing field.
Football reference.
Too soon.
All right, I deserved that.
But I just wanted to let you know,
they caught the culprit.
The animal responsible for killing
coach Tanner and all those people.
What are you talking about?
It was a mountain lion.
Really big one.
It attacked a hunter this morning.
It's all over the news.
"Deadly beast captured.
All's well in Mystic Falls."
Why would you over your tracks?
I've decided to stay a while.
I'm just having way too much
fun here with you and Elena.
- Can't touch her now.
- The vervain keeps me out of her head.
Maybe that's not my target.
Believe it or not, Stefan,
some girls don't need my persuasion.
Some girls just can't resist
my good looks,
my style and my charm and...
my unflinching ability
to listen to Taylor Swift.
This is John Varvatos, dude.
Dick move.
Mystic Falls Team
1x04 - Family Ties
Croutch, Humanidyne,
Illyria, McFly,
MiniBen314, Thirteen,
WoLF971
I can confirm that a 12-foot
puma mountain lion
attacked a hunter and was
subsequently shot and killed.
The hunter is in stable condition.
The real animal is still out there,
Waiting for me,
challenging me to fight back,
to stop him.
But how do I stop a monster
without becoming one myself?
To repeat, the animal terrorizing
Mystic Falls has been caught.
Scum ball.
Scum bucket.
- Who are you talking to?
- Him.
- The news guy?
- Also known as Logan "scum" Fell.
Did your mom ever tell you
why I moved away from Mystic Falls?
No way.
You and him?
- He's cute.
- He is not cute.
There's nothing cute about him.
What are you doing with that?
I went yesterday and got it
from the safe deposit box.
Mom had told Mrs. Lockwood
she would loan it
to the founder's council
for their heritage display.
Is that grandma Beth's wedding ring?
Originally it was great-great-grandma
Mary's wedding ring.
How much do you think this stuff
is worth? You know, like on eBay?
- You're not gonna find out.
- That stuff is mom and dad's.
- You can't just give it away.
- I'm not giving it away.
It's called a loan, Jeremy.
Are you okay?
I'm good.
- Sorry.
- Maybe we should press pause.
Yeah, you're probably right.
That was...
getting a bit...
How do you look in a suit?
- I can pull one off.
- How about tomorrow night?
Will you be my date
to the Founder's party?
- They still do that?
- Have you been before?
No, the Salvatores...
don't get invited anymore.
Well, this year, there's this
heritage project
that meant a lot to my mom.
She was really involved
in the Founder's Council, and...
it was her favorite party.
I know it sounds really boring, but...
I would be honored
to accompany you, Miss Gilbert.
The pleasure is all mine,
Mr. Salvatore.
No yellow. Jaundice.
Go for the blue.
- I don't like the blue.
- Well, I do.
- And if I'm gonna be your date...
- You cannot be my date.
My mother is going to be there,
and she is a very proud gun owner.
I went through a lot of trouble to
make sure this party wasn't canceled.
It's very important I be there.
Please take me.
You should come
to the Founder's party with me.
Not if you're wearing that dress.
What's so special about this
Bella girl? Edward's so whipped.
You gotta read the first book first.
It won't make sense if you don't.
I miss Anne Rice. She was so on it.
- How come you don't sparkle?
- Because I live in the real world,
- where vampires burn in the sun.
- Yeah, but you go in the sun.
I have a ring.
It protects me. Long story.
Will these bites
turn me into a vampire?
It's more complicated than that.
You'd have to feed
on my blood, then die,
then feed on a human's,
it's whole ordeal.
This book, by the way,
has it all wrong.
You can be very sweet
when you want to be.
Yes, I can be sweet.
Are you going to kill me?
But not yet.
Why not?
Because there's something
I need you to do for me.
Anything.
How good are you at getting this
little nose where it doesn't belong?
I'm excellent.
So what happens with the season?
One big forfeit?
- Are they looking for a new coach?
- I don't know, dad.
I doubt anybody's
thinking about that right now.
Founder's party, focus.
- How are y'all doing over here?
- We're doing great, sweetheart.
- Is there anything else I can get you?
- We're fine, thanks.
Just the check, honey.
- Here you go, Mayor Lockwood.
- Thanks.
You're taking Damon
to the Founder's party? What about me?
- Go with Elena.
- She's asking Stefan.
Okay, go by yourself.
Gee, thanks.
What about your mom? Is she okay
with you bringing Damon?
And I'm supposed to care why?
He's older sexy danger guy.
Older sexy danger guy?
Is that an official
witch Twitter tweet?
No more witch jokes, okay?
That whole Mr. Tanner
prediction thing has me freaked.
And Damon's not dangerous.
You know, he just...
has a lot of issues
with his brother.
You know, like major,
deep-rooted drama.
Like...?
I'm not really supposed
to say anything.
Caroline Forbes, when have you ever
kept a secret in your life?
But you can't tell Elena.
So what you gonna buy me?
Some class.
Your parents are gone.
I guess we can be close now.
What the hell does that mean?
You treat me like trash.
I'm sick of it.
I don't think you're trash.
Really? Then who are you taking
to the Founder's party?
Do you want me to ask you
- It'll be stupid and lame.
- True.
But it'll be less stupid and lame
if you were there.
You realize you had to ask him
to ask you, right?
You figure if you dress up like
a respectable young lady,
he'll finally treat you like one?
Screw you, Jeremy.
You know you're making the wrong
choice, yet you make it anyway.
It's sad.
- I didn't know you were here.
- Just going through Stefan's homework.
Boy, this country sure has dumbed down
in the last hundred years.
Why he wants to go
to high school is beyond me.
I mean, in the seventies, he went
Ivy League. Harvard, I understood.
Actually, no.
I didn't get that either.
Go ahead, purge.
Get it out.
What's on your mind?
Why are you here, Damon?
To spend time with you, Zach.
Family's important.
I know you.
You always have a motive.
So tell me, what is it this time?
You are in no position
to question me.
I didn't mean to upset you.
This is not upset, Zach.
What's going on?
Having a family moment.
Spending some quality time.
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not.
And neither are you. How many more
people have to die before you see that?
I see it.
All right, Zach, I see it.
Then why aren't you
doing anything about it?
I can't, Zach.
I can't.
It would take human blood.
It's the only way
that I could stop him,
and I can't do that.
Vervain could weaken him
If he ingested it.
It would help you to the upper hand.
Vervain hasn't grown here
since 1865.
Damon saw to that.
The little I had, I gave to Elena.
What?
You've been growing it.
It's just something that's been
passed down through the generations.
Blood only runs so deep
when you're related to vampires.
Damon would kill me
if he knew that I had it.
But you're telling me.
Why?
Because I trust you.
And you're gonna need it
if you want to get rid of him.
I'm here for my mom. I was supposed
to pick up a box of stuff.
Right here.
Please be careful.
Be careful with it, dick.
- Not now, okay, guys? Please?
- I'm fine. He's just being a punk.
- I got your punk.
- Look, Tyler,
Maybe you should go. Tell your mom
that I'll see her tonight.
Would it make a difference
if I told you I actually like Vicki?
Not even if you meant it.
Delicate flower
versus naughty vixen.
Tough call. Can we mix them?
Look at you,
getting all pretty for your date.
You seem happy-ish.
I am... ish.
Tonight's going to be a good night.
But don't let that stop you
from telling me whatever it is
you wanted to tell me
as soon as you walked in the door.
What if I tell you in the morning?
I don't want to ruin the night.
Out with it.
Okay, but it has to go in the vault,
because Caroline will kill me
If it gets back to Damon
that she squealed.
Apparently Stefan has
a very interesting back story.
Do you know what happened
with his ex-girlfriend?
I know that they both dated her
and that's why they have issues.
They both dated her,
only she chose Damon.
And that drove Stefan mad so,
he did horrible things
to try and break them up.
He manipulated Katherine.
He filled her head with all these lies
until finally it worked,
and she turned against Damon.
That sounds like one person's side
of the story, meaning Damon's.
I just wanted you to know.
Anyway, his past relationships
are none of my business.
Unless he's a calculating,
manipulative liar.
- That is your business.
- Stefan is none of those things.
How do you know?
They still wear ties at this thing?
- Why are you even going?
- It's only fitting.
We were at the very
first one, remember?
I think it's better if we don't draw
attention to ourselves.
So you should stay here.
I'll see to it Elena has a good time.
My goodness,
I've driven you to drink.
Can't seem to rid myself of you.
What else am I supposed to do,
besides go about living my life?
Go about living my life.
See, there in lies
your eternal struggle.
You're dead, dude.
Get over it.
What do you think?
Hello?
Hi, Mrs. Lockwood.
What do you mean? It is?
Are you sure?
Cause I saw it.
Let me check.
I will find it and bring it.
What's wrong?
- God, what now?
- The pocket watch. Where is it?
What watch?
The one you stole from mom's box.
Look, Mrs. Lockwood just called me,
freaking out.
It was on the list. And she can't
find it, and she thinks
- she's the one who lost it.
- Maybe she did. Maybe Tyler took it.
Don't even play that card.
You took it. If I go online,
am I going to find it on eBay?
- Is that how you pay for your pot?
- Screw you.
- I would never sell this, okay?
- Then why did you take it?
Because it's supposed to be mine.
Dad said it goes
to the firstborn son.
His father gave it to him,
and now what?
And he was going to give it to you.
Look, Jeremy,
it's still yours, okay?
Mom promised Mrs. Lockwood.
What do you want me to do?
Just take it and get out.
It's cool not growing old.
I like being the eternal stud.
Yes, being a 150-year-old teenager
Has been the height of my happiness.
You cracked a funny, Stefan.
I should have a drink to celebrate.
1864.
You and Katherine
were the perfect couple.
It was hell watching you
dance with her.
My happiness was short-lived,
as you well know.
I remember.
I left the party early,
I was waiting for her.
The night you dropped her off,
I was waiting just inside.
You were such a gentleman,
gave her a kiss on the cheek.
And what she really wanted was...
Here's to history
repeating itself, huh?
I admire your effort, Stefan.
Pouring yourself a drink
Then spiking the bottle with vervain.
I'm not some drunk sorority chick.
You can't roofie me.
But I can't help but feel a little used.
I thought we were having a moment.
I have to go to the party angry.
Who knows what I'll do?
Hi, nice to see you.
- Let's go this way.
- Why?
Line's too long.
We can go around back.
Come on, party's in the back.
That was his favorite scotch.
I'm sorry, I thought it would work.
I wasn't counting on it.
- You knew it would fail?
- Did what I wanted.
It lowered his guard. He won't
expect me to try again so soon.
I doubled what I put in the scotch.
- You look smashing.
- Thank you, Mrs. Lockwood.
This is my boyfriend Damon.
Oh, well, come on in.
Lovely to meet you. I've been looking
forward to this party for quite a while.
Well, enjoy.
Let's get a drink.
Wait here.
Really, you couldn't even change
out of the badge for this?
I'm working, honey.
Who's the date
you just tried to sneak past me?
- Just some guy.
- A little old for you, don't you think?
Cause otherwise you'd approve.
Yeah, I doubt that.
- Hi, Mayor Lockwood.
- Hey, guys, come on in.
Thank you.
Where's your dad?
- Memphis.
- Good.
With Stephen.
Your parents?
There's a lot of history here.
It's good to see you.
I thought I might see you here.
- You knew it.
- I dreaded.
But were secretly hoping.
And now that I have...
Not so fast. I know you. You have
a lot more insults in you, I can tell.
- Your hairline's receding.
- It's not. You want to have lunch?
- You haven't changed a bit.
- Yes, I have.
I'm meaner now.
"The founding families
in mystic falls welcomes you
to the inaugural
founder's council celebration."
It's the original guest registry.
Look at all these familiar names...
Sheriff William Forbes,
Mayor Benjamin Lockwood.
Is that Damon Salvatore?
And, Stefan Salvatore.
The original Salvatore brothers.
Our ancestors.
Tragic story, actually.
We don't need to bore them
with stories of the past.
It's not boring.
I'd love to hear more
about your family.
Well, I'm bored.
I want to dance.
And Damon won't dance with me.
Could I just borrow your date?
- I don't really dance.
- Sure he does. You should see him.
Waltz, the jitterbug,
the moonwalk. He does it all.
You wouldn't mind, would you, Elena?
It's up to Stefan.
Sorry, but I'm not
gonna take no for an answer.
I want to apologize to you for...
being such a
world-class jerk
the other night when I tried
to kiss you. There's no excuse.
My therapist says I'm...
acting out, trying to punish Stefan.
For what?
It's all in the past.
I don't even want to bring it up.
Let's just say that the men
in the Salvatore family
have been cursed
with sibling rivalry.
And it all started with
the original Salvatore brothers.
Damon told you to ask me to dance.
Didn't he?
Why would he do that?
Would you like one?
Thank you.
Okay, just tell me
if you see my mom.
The Salvatore name was
practically royalty in this town.
Until the war.
There was a battle here...
- The battle of willow creek.
- Right.
I know, we talked about it in class.
Confederate soldiers fired on
a church with civilians inside.
What the history books left out
was the people that were killed.
They weren't there by accident.
They were believed to be
union sympathizers. So
some of the founders
on the confederacy side back then
wanted them rounded up
and burned alive.
Stefan and Damon had someone
they loved very much in that church.
And when they went to rescue them,
they were shot.
Murdered in cold blood.
Who was in the church
that they wanted to save?
A woman, I guess.
Doesn't it always come down
to the love of a woman?
Look, I'm sorry that you and Stefa
have this thing between you,
but I can't get in the middle of it,
Damon.
I just...
I hope you two can work it out.
I hope so, too.
So you want to dance?
Me dancing? Not pretty.
Maybe you could show me around.
I mean, this place is amazing.
If you like living in a museum.
Maybe I should just
strip naked and give
pastor Bill a lap dance.
I mean, that's why we're hiding
in a corner all night, isn't it?
You're scared of how
I'm going to act?
You afraid of what your parents
are going to think about your date
from the wrong side of the tracks?
- I don't care about what they think.
- Great.
Let's go say hi.
Knock it off, Vick.
Or we could just, you know,
sneak up to your bedroom.
As long as nobody sees us, right?
- Vicki, I swear...
- What's a matter, Ty?
You scared to stand up to your mommy?
It's pretty pathetic.
Let go!
We didn't get a chance
to say hello earlier.
It's Vicki, right?Matt's sister.
Yes, ma'am.
You'll have to forgive my son's
rudeness. He gets it from his father.
Well, that's okay, Mrs. Lockwood.
Tyler and I were just
saying good night.
That's what you get when you bring
the trash into the party.
What'd we miss?
We were just chatting.
Drink, Damon?
No, thanks, I'll pass.
Stefan, do you have
another dance in you?
Absolutely.
They look so cute together.
Don't talk, please.
Don't shoot!
I'm going to need a refill.
Shooting implies caring.
Feigned indifference. I like it.
I'm over the banter, Logan.
I'd really rather
you just left me alone.
I'm sorry, Jenna.
About your sister.
Thank you.
I came to the funeral.
I know.
- I saw you.
- I didn't want to push my way in, but,
I wanted to be there for you. And...
when I heard you were staying
in Mystic Falls, I thought maybe...
Well, maybe I could have
a second chance to make things right.
Her name was Monica, wasn't it?
I hope Damon didn't
drive you too crazy.
No, actually,
he was on good behavior.
He even apologized, and...
explained why he is the way he is.
And it all goes back to Katherine.
So tell me about her.
What happened?
It's not something
I like to talk about.
I get that.
I do.
I just want you to
know that you can.
I mean, I burden you
with all of my drama, and,
I want you to do the same.
I know.
Thank you.
The truth is, Stefan...
I don't really know
that much about you,
and I'd really love it
if you would open up to me.
Damon said something, didn't he?
He likes to play games
and cause trouble, Elena.
This isn't about Damon, it's about
me trying to get to know you.
Look, you're the mystery guy,
and I like that.
But with mystery comes secrets,
And this thing with Katherine.
Let it go.
- I don't want to talk about it.
- Well, then, say something
about yourself. Anything.
Otherwise, I'm left with nothing
but what other people tell me.
Don't you see what
Damon has done here?
He's trying to get you
to turn against me.
Well, then I guess it's working.
This is my fault. I planted doubt.
- I'm a doubt planter.
- It's not your fault.
I feel terrible because I said that
I wouldn't get in the middle of it,
and then, that's exactly what I did.
I got all snotty.
Elena, honey, there you are.
I notice the watch
still isn't in the collection.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Lockwood. I...
I couldn't find it.
I guess it's still packed up
in my parents' stuff somewhere.
I see.
Please let me know
if you do find it.
Where have you been?
Looking for you.
Your brother barely danced with me
for five minutes...
Okay, just a minute.
Stand right... there.
You're not supposed to touch.
What is that?
A very important crystal.
Well, how did you know
that it was there?
- Because I put it there.
- When?
A long time ago. Tonight,
I'm taking it back, thanks to you.
- Well, what's it for?
- Never you mind.
You can't just steal it.
It's not stealing if it's mine.
Come on.
Vodka tonic.
Okay, I know that this is probably
going to be strike 3, but,
I hope you can see it
for what it is.
- And what is it?
- Persistence.
Groveling, commitment.
Take your pick.
I fled town because of you.
- Fled.
- I was young and stupid,
and...
then things changed. Life got...
real.
You'd know that better than anyone.
Hypothetically speaking, if allowed,
- how would you make things right?
- Well, more groveling, of course.
A recap of the past few years
spent soul searching.
Cheese fries.
Obvious.
I know my audience.
Yes to lunch. Call me.
Look around.
What's missing?
The flames, the candles.
Why aren't they lit?
There's matches in the kitchen.
Bitch.
So how are things with Stefan?
Great. Just great.
Really?
Well, my radar must be off, cause
I was getting all sorts
of other vibes,
What is that?
Don't!
- Oh my God, Caroline, what happened?
- Nothing, okay?!
That is nothing.
Did somebody hurt you?
No, okay, nothing. It just...
My mom would kill me.
Did Damon hurt you?
Of course not!
Just leave me alone, okay, Elena?!
God!
There is something
seriously wrong with you.
You stay away from Caroline
or I will go straight to her mother,
The sheriff. You got it?
Stay away from her.
I'm sorry.
I take it all back.
You're completely right about Damon.
What did he do?
There are bruises
all over Caroline's body.
Bite marks, and he has her all confused
and messed up in the head.
You don't... look surprised.
- I'm handling it.
- Handling it?
Stefan, you should be
having him arrested.
Please. I...
I don't expect you to understand.
I don't understand anything, Stefan.
So why don't you just
clear it up for me?
There are things
that you don't know, okay?
Things that I want
to tell you, but I can't.
And I may never be able to.
And I just need you to trust me.
Trust is earned.
I can't just magically hand it over.
I'm so sorry. I have to go.
You look amazing.
What are you doing here?
I was thinking maybe I could make
one more wrong choice today.
I still have 17 minutes.
Don't!
She took it off
and I got flustered, okay?!
I didn't know what to say.
But I swear, okay, I did not tell her.
I just told her that
you didn't mean to hurt me.
You make me crazy, you know that?
It's okay. I forgive you.
I swear I didn't say...
Unfortunately...
I am so...
over you now.
What the hell?
I knew, I couldn't
spike your drink...
So I spiked hers.
There you are. I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Caroline, what happened?
- You're shaking. Caroline... what...
- I'm fine!
Come here.
I did what I had to do...
to protect Elena,
to protect everyone.
Yes, Damon, the headline reads
"Deadly beast captured.
All is well in Mystic Falls."
Thank you for staying so late.
Did you get the Gilbert watch?
She claims it's packed away
in her parents' things.
I can get it.
Good. We're going to need it.
- Are you sure?
- Five bodies all drained of blood?
I'm certain.
They've come back.
Mystic Falls Team
www.forom.com