Nice car.
I thought it was a waste
To leave it sitting in the garage.
I didn't kno you were
coming back today.
You know, I woke up this morning
And I was feeling great,
And I figured it was time for
me to get back into things.
Does the mean you're ok now?
With all the cravings?
Yeah. I mean,
the worst part is over.
So...now all I want to do
Is just spend as much
time with you as possible.
I'm ok with that.
Hey, thank you.
For helping me get through the--
The rough patch.
You're welcome.
We're going to be late.
Ok, um, you know what,
I'll catch up with you.
I'm gonna grab my stuff.
I'll be right behind you.
Ok. Ok.
There was a disturbance at the
hospital blood bank last night.
Some of the supply
was compromised.
Compromised? You mean stolen.
We almost missed it.
The inventory records
were altered,
But when the night
manager was questioned,
He had no recollection
of changing them.
Meaning the vampire
who stole the blood
Used mind control
to hide the theft.
I know what she meant.
We wouldn't have noticed
if John not alerted us
To recent discrepancies
At other hospital blood
banks in the county.
How lucky for us, we have John.
We're stepping up
security at the hospital,
Giving the guards vervain
To prevent this from
happening again.
Sheriff, might I
offer a suggestion?
Why don't Damon and I
put our heads together?
We can track down
whoever's doing this.
Truthfully, I could
use the extra hands.
Is that something you'd
be willing to do?
Well, of course, I mean,
if it'll help.
I think we'll make a good team.
Don't you, Damon?
John, whatever I can do to
help keep this town safe,
Even if it means
spending time with you.
Ok.
This week we're going
to set aside our
Regular curriculum for a
lesson in local history
As we approach founder's day.
Apparently the community leaders
Feel that's more important
than world war ii,
But hey, what do I know?
Sorry I'm late.
Looks like we will be
at full occupancy today.
Welcome home, Bonnie.
Right, founder's day.
What does it mean to
have a founder's day?
Well, if you'll turn
your attention to this
Exquisite diorama over here
That I spent all night...
I suppose I should be grateful
You learned how to use the bell.
I'm here on behalf of my mother.
On behalf of or in spite of?
I'm sorry about what the
other vampires did to Stefan.
Abducting him, torturing him.
It wasn't supposed
to go down like that.
You were playing house
with half of a tomb
Of really pissed off vampires.
What did you think
was going to happen?
My mom is devastated.
They tried to overthrow her.
Why isn't she here
telling me this?
She doesn't really do apologies.
Well, that's a coincidence,
'cause I don'to forgiveness,
So just run along.
And if you're going to continue
Playing house with your
little vampire pets,
You might want to stop
robbing the blood bank dry,
Because they're onto it.
I haven't been to the local
blood bank in at least a week.
Then it's one of your others.
The other ones are gone, Damon.
Well, where'd they go?
They weren't cut
out for this town.
After what happened
with your brother,
My mom kicked them out
and they took off.
It's just us and Harper now.
Bonnie.
Hey.
Hey, I, um, I tried to
grab you after class
But you'd already taken off.
How are you? How's your family?
We're dealing. It's been hard.
Everyone here really missed you.
Yeah, I just had so
much to deal with
After grams' funeral,
And honestly after you told me
that the tomb's spell failed,
I just didn't really
want to come back.
I hope you understand
why I called.
I wanted you to know
before you came home.
Yeah, I understand why.
I just wish I didn't know.
I know it's been really hard--
Bonnie!
Bonnie! Thank God you're home!
I know we talked every day,
but I missed you!
How are you doing?
Better. Just better. You know,
Just glad to be back,
And try to keep myself busy.
Well, I can help with that.
Major wardrobe confab needed asap.
You need to help me
pick the perfect dress
For the founder's court. Oh.
The founder's court?
Did I miss something?
The founder's court.
You know, miss mystic falls.
They announced it today, and, um,
You and are both on it.
Oh, my God, we signed
up for that so long ago.
I completely forgot.
Yeah.
So are you dropping out, then?
I can't.
No?
Her mom is the one who
wanted her to enter.
How was school?
Fine.
Yeah? Same old, same old?
Nothing new?
No stories to bring home?
You're making small talk, why?
You seem awfully chipper lately.
Less doom and gloom,
a little more pep in your step.
And you think it's because
I drank human blood again.
I mean, I don't want to brag,
But I would definitely
take responsibility
For this new and improved you.
Right, right. Well,
I hate to burst your bubble,
But I'm clean.
Yeah, not possible.
Not only is it possible,
but it is quite true.
Stefan, let's be
serious for a second.
You spent the last
century and a half
Being a poster child for Prozac,
And now you expect me to
believe that this new you
Has nothing to do with
human blood, nothing.
I'm clean.
You're lying!
Believe what you want.
I'm sorry for the short notice.
I didn't even know that
the contest was coming up,
Much less that I would be in it.
Well, I'll be happy to
escort you anywhere.
My mom was really into
this founder's day stuff.
She was even miss
mystic in her day.
I kinda wanted to do it for her.
Well, it'll be great.
We'll have fun.
Ok. I'll see tomorrow. I love you.
Love you, too.
Well, well.
He's a liar and a thief.
So...
When were you going to share?
Go ahead.
Help yourself.
No, no, I'm talking about
The fact that you're
a closet blood nknk.
So I'm drinking blood again.
You're the one that
shoved it on me.
What's your problem?
I have it under control.
Under control?
You robbed the hospital.
So what's your point?
Fine. Whatever, man. Drink up.
Just remember we're trying
to keep a low profile.
Why don't you just walk up
To sheriff Forbes,
ask her to tap a vein.
Have my actions
negatively impacted you?
Ooh. I can't imagine
what that must feel like.
Yeah, what's Elena think
about the new...you?
Noing's changed.
I'm still the same person.
Clearly.
Elena doesn't need
to know anything yet.
You've been off the human
stuff for years, Stefan.
If you're having
trouble controlling--
I'm not having any trouble.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
I know what it's like.
That Jekyll and Hyde feeling.
There's that switch,
sometimes it goes off and you snap.
Right now is not a
good time for me
To be worried about you snapping.
I know that it pains
you to see this.
Hmm.
But I'm fine, ok?
I'm fine.
So please,
Do me a favor.
And back off.
This year's queen will have
The special honor of
taking center stage
AT THE 150th FOUNDER'S DAY GALA.
Before we crown our winner,
We'd like to get to know
A bit more about each of you.
I'm on the m.F.
Beautification committee.
I volunteer at the rec
center soup kitchen.
I recognize that I haven't
been as involved this year
As I used to be.
I implemented this year's
go green campaign at school.
I've been distracted,
and I let a lot of things slide.
I don't think it's wrong for
me to win 2 years in a row.
I was surprised to
have been selected.
Since I'm not from one
of the founding families.
But I'm aware of what
an honor this is,
And I want you to know
that I take it seriously.
Worked with the county's
recycling program
And was in charge of the
policemen's yearly raffle.
Just because my DUI made my
community service mandatory,
Doesn't mean I was
any less committed.
This was really
important to my mother.
She believed in community,
Family, honor and loyalty.
It's the legacy e e ft for me.
Hey, partner.
What do you want?
You haven't returned
any of my calls.
Most people take that as a hint.
Why don't we start
looking for vampires?
Why the act, John?
I mean, you obviously don't
care about catching vampires.
You're here talking to me.
Actually, I care very much.
What did Isobel say about that?
I mean, considering
that she is one.
Isobel and I share
a mutual interest.
The originalJohnathan
Gilbert had an invention
That was stolen by a vampire.
That vampire was then burned alive
In fell's church,
or soJohnathan thought.
And the invention
was lost forever.
Hmm.
But then the vampires
weren't killed, were they?
They were trapped.
And now they're free,
thanks to you,
Which means the invention
is retrievable.
Well, what is it?
The only thing that matters
is that I want it back,
And you're going to help me
if you want your secret safe.
I mean, why bring
me into it, John?
I mean, I don't even know
what you're talking about,
Much less who has it.
Oh, come on, Damon.
You were around back then.
Yoknow who these people are,
what they look like.
He was friendly with a woman
Who turned out to be a vampire.
Her name was pearl.
Does that ring a bell?
I'm not playing anymore.
Get out.
I beg your pardon?
You know, I only entertain
This whole blackmail
scheme thing of yours
Because I thought that you and
Isobel could lead me to Katherine.
But see, now I know you have
no idea where Katherine is,
Because if you did, you would know
That Katherine and pearl
Were best friends.
See, you don't know everything,
Do you, John?
I'll tell the entire
council what you are.
Go for it. I'll kill
every last one of them.
Then I'll sever your hand,
pull your ring off,
And I'll kill you, too.
Do you understand that?
Honor your partner.
Let's focus. Right hand around.
Flirt with your eyes.
Left hand around.
This is ridiculous.
Both hands.
You're only saying that
Because you don't
know how to do it.
Sorry only one of us was around
When the dance was invented.
Ouch! Oooh!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
There's no touching
during this part.
It's about the simple
intimacy of the near-touch.
Very nice, Amber.
Thank you, Mrs. Lockwood!
If you ask me,
the near touch is overrated.
You seem to be in a good mood.
Is that a bad thing?
Would you prefer me to
be brooding and tortured?
Hey, I'm not complaining.
Oh, no touching.
The fell cousins
don't have a shot.
And Amber Bradley
is only on the court
So the pageant doesn't look like
it's founding families only.
Which, of course, it is.
So that leaves Elena.
She totally has the sympathy
vote since her parents died.
How can I compete with that?
Very nice.
Very sensitive.
Oh, I'm sorry. This must sound
Really unimportant in
light of everything.
It's ok. I get it.
You want to win.
Well, my grandmother
was miss mystic.
And both of my aunts.
My mom's the only one
who didn't get the gene,
And I want this.
I mean, I actually deserve this.
Bonnie.
Hey. Hey.
How are you?
I begged Bonnie to
fill in for Matt.
He had to work today.
Bonnie, do you have a minute?
We only have 30
minutes for rehearsal.
It'll only take a minute.
Please?
Bonnie, you have to
tell me what's wrong.
It's not worth talking about.
What do you mean, not worth it?
You've barely said 10 words to me,
And you won't even look at Stefan.
Is that what it is, is it Stefan?
Listen.
Elena, I can't just pretend
Like everything is ok.
Everything my grams
did was to protect us
From those vampires in the tomb.
And now they're out,
which means she died for nothing.
I'm so sorry, Bonnie.
What can I do to make it better?
That's just it.
There's nothing you can do.
I blame him, Elena.
Him and Damon.
And I'm not going to
put you in a situation
Where you have to choose sides.
I'm just having a
hard time with it.
Ok?
Dude, are you ok? You're bleeding.
Ahh, Stefan!
Are you ok?
Yes. I'm sorry.
I was just...
I was feeling a little sick.
I'll be fine.
Hey. Hi.
I heard you're driving.
Yeah, I am.
Let me get that for you.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Um, how, uh--
How is Stefan?
What do you mean?
You know, he seems on edge.
He went through a lot,
He was in bad shape for a while.
But he's bouncing back now.
Alaric.
Hey, buddy.
What are you doing here?
Well, I'm the chauffer.
Oh, I thought I was driving.
Oh, no need.
We're going with Rick.
Are we ready?
Jeremy can ride with you.
In the running for
miss mystic falls?
Somememis you have to wear
uncomfortable heels to blend in.
I remember this event from 1864.
I was supposed to enter,
Before everything happened.
Ahh, nostalgia's a bitch.
If you're just going to mock me,
Then you move along, please.
John Gilbert thinks your
mom stole an artifact
FromJohnathan sr.
Sr. Back in 1864.
What are you, his errand boy?
I don't know what it is,
But I don't want him to have it.
I could ask her.
But, you know,
you've made it pretty clear
That you don't trust us,
So why should I even bother?
Because you want to
stay in mystic falls,
And John Gilbert's in town,
making that impossible.
Find out where it is.
He leaves, you can
buy a welcome mat.
Thanks for helping me.
Don't thank me
Until you're sure your hair
isn't going to burn off.
You know, I remember
When my mom and I were
first applying for this.
She was so excited.
So were you, if I recall.
I was.
She just made it sound
like so much fun.
Lots has changed since then.
Well, I hate to break it to you,
But it's a little
late for cold feet.
I don't have cold feet. I just...
I think I'd be enjoying it
a lot more if she was here.
I'll tell you one thing,
Your hair would have a
better chance if she was.
Ok, I should go put my dress on.
Be careful with that thing.
Don't hurt anybody.
You look miserable.
Are there really a whole
month of these events
That I'm supposed to show up at?
You can fight it if you want,
But it's part of being a Gilbert.
Yeah, you, uh, you mentioned you
know a lot about the family.
Do you know anything about our
ancestorJohnathan Gilbert?
Prolific writer, crazy inventor.
Why do you ask?
Well, I read his journal.
Is that right?
Yeah.
I actually found it
in all dad's stuff.
Well, that's surprising.
Most of them are locked away.
There's more of them?
Johnathan Gilbert
journaled his whole life.
Right down to the bitter,
insane drunken end.
Guy had a lot of demons.
And did you read 'em?
I browsed, yeah.
What'd you think
about what he wrote?
Crazy ramblings of a mad man,
of course.
Well, she's very pretty.
Yeah, yeah, she's a, uh,
A friend of mine. Excuse me.
Are you ok, Amber?
I hate being the
center of attention.
I get panic attacks.
Do you need some privacy
so you can change?
Actually, I'm just-
I'm just going to go get some air.
You can't be back here.
We need to talk.
Does it have to be right now?
Normally I would have a
completely different outlook
On what I'm about to tell you,
But since it could
really inconvenience me,
I'll squeal.
What are you talking about?
Stefan's still
drinking human blood.
What? Yeah.
A month ago,
I would have rejoiced.
But with the council
back on the alert,
It is not a good time for
Stefan to fly off the handle.
I know he's been a little edgy,
But he said that was normal.
He has a fridge full of
stolen blood bank contraband
In the house.
Oh, my God.
He has no idea what normal is.
His entire existence isn't normal.
Normal to a vampire is
drinking human blood.
But he spent all
this time fighting it
When he should have been
learning how to control it.
And now it's controlling
him instead.
I can't believe this.
I mean, it's Stefan that
we're talking about here.
Stefan on human blood, Elena.
He'll do anything,
he'll say anything,
Because he's not going
to want to stop.
Trust me.
Anna!
What is it?
Come on, don't be like that.
Why not?
You're basically using me
to turn you into a vampire
So you could be with someone else.
No, I wasn't using you.
Really?
Then how would you
like to define it?
Look, I don't think it's any worse
Than becoming friends with me
So you could give
your mother my blood.
How do you know that?
That's not important.
Seriously, Jeremy.
What do you know?
Everything. I know everything.
This is all my fault.
I'm the one who fed him the
blood in the first place.
What's going on in here?
Just filling Elena in
On your extracurricular
activities.
What are you talking about?
I know about the blood, Stefan.
I'm gonna-- I'll be downstairs,
Drinking.
I was going to tell you.
When?
I'm fine.
I'm fine. The blood,
it doesn't change anything.
It's changing you.
Why, because I kept
it a secret from you?
Come on, Elena.
Look, given the way that
you're reacting right now,
Can you really blame
me for doing that?
Are you hearing
yourself right now?
You've been stealing
blood and lying,
And you say that
everything's fine?
Everything's not fine, Stefan.
So what, so you and Damon
All of a sudden have
everythgg figured out then?
It's not about Damon.
It's about what's
happening to you.
I know, and I'm telling
you that I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Please, come on.
Elena, I thought you...
I thought you believed in me.
Elena? Let's go.
The line up's starting.
I just--
I need a minute.
You're not even dressed yet.
Escorts wait downstairs, Stefan.
God!
Oh, God, sorry!
Ms. Tina fell,
Escorted by bartholomew Whitmore.
Has anyone seen Amber?
Do you see Stefan down there?
Nope.
Just my boring fill-in escort.
What happened to Matt?
They wouldn't let him out of work.
Hey, what happened to Stefan?
I don't know. He just
disappeared somewhere.
I don't know.
What am I doing?
I never should have
gone through with this.
What do you mean?
I need to find Stefan.
This isn't me.
I'm not this person anymore.
Uh, no, no, no, no way, no.
You had your chance to drop out.
And believe me, I was all for it.
Because there is no way
that I can beat you.
Elena, you're doing this because
it was important to your mom.
Ms. Caroline Forbes,
And her escort Jeffrey
lockwood Hamilton.
Elena, you're next. Come on.
You're missing
Elena's introduction.
I don't care.
So she has no idea
you read her journal?
She keeps things from me,
I'm going to keep things from her.
What are you going to do now?
Now that you know everything
that she's been hiding from you?
I don't know.
There's a part of me
that's so angry, you know,
That she covered up
what happened to vickie
And erased my memory,
But there's this other
part of me that's glad.
I--
I don't want to remember
vickie like that.
As a monster?
No, as someone who
wanted to hurt me.
When I met you,
You were just a part of my
plan to get my mother back.
But then things changed.
All the time we spent together.
I would never do anything
to hurt you. Not now.
You know that, right?
Yeah, I know that.
Where are we going?
I don't know.
I'm in the ceremony.
Not now, you're not.
You're standing in the
parking lot with me.
I'm in the parking lot with you.
I'm sorry.
I'm not very good to
be around right now.
I'm a little bit on edge.
I've--I've been
drinking the human stuff
And it's really
screwing with my head.
Oh! she knows now.
God, she wasn't
supposed to find out.
I didn't want her to find out,
now everything's ruined.
You seem sad.
I'm not sad!
I'm freaking hungry!
Ms. Elena Gilbert,
Escorted by Mr. Stefan salvatore.
Where's Stefan? I don't know.
What is she doing with Damon?
I have no idea.
What are we going to do?
Right now we just have
to get through this.
I don't hurt people.
I don't do that.
I'm the good brother.
Do you want to hurt me?
I want to kill you.
I want to rip into your skin,
And I want to feed on your blood.
Under your skin,
Pulsating, flowing.
Your carotid artery, right there.
If you puncture this just right,
You can control the blood flow.
It takes practice,
But it doesn't have
to make a mess.
You don't have to waste any.
What's stopping you?
If I do this,
If I give in,
there's no going back.
Then don't.
I just want one taste.
That's all I need.
Just one more tast
One taste?
Where's Amber?
I don't know.
Before I crown the winner,
I'd like to offer a
personal thank you
To all of these young
ladies for their efforts
To better our communities.
So, without further adieu,
It is my honor to announce our
very own miss mystic falls,
Ms. Caroline Forbes!
Congratulations!
I actually won!
??
Get me Damon salvatore.
I can't do this!
What's the matter?
I can't do this.
It's ok.
It doesn't hurt that much.
Just not so hard next time.
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
I can't stop.
Why aren't you afraid of me, huh?
You told me not to be.
What?
What's your name?
Amber.
Listen to me, Amber.
I need you to be afraid of me.
I need you to run like hell,
Do you understand me?
Run, run, now!
What is it, did you find h?
There were signs of struggle
in the upstairs bathroom.
There was blood.
And that Amber girl is missing.
Oh, my God.
He wouldn't hurt her.
He won't.
Let's just find him, ok?
Let's get your coat, come on.
You said to run!
I changed my mind.
Stefan! oh!
Stefan.
Come on. Get control of it.
Come on.
It's ok. Come on.
Breathe through it, man.
Stefan, stop it!
It's ok.
Stefan.
She doesn't remember
what happened.
It's a good thing the girls
got here when they did.
She lost a lot of blood.
You didn't see anything?
No. We just found her
And then called Damon.
She gonna be ok?
Looks like it, yeah.
Why don't you girls
get back to the party.
Damon and I can take it from here.
Yeah. Ok.
They didn't see the bite mark?
No, I got here before
they got too close.
There was too much blood,
they couldn't see it clearly.
Bonnie, can we talk about this?
There's nothing to talk about.
Bonnie, please.
I told you I wasn't going
to make you choose,
But I need to make the
choice for myself.
Please just leave me alone.
Jer.
You ready?
Uh, just a second.
Who's that girl with Jeremy?
His friend Anna.
What's her story?
Why so nosy? I'm just curious.
He really seems to like her.
She's new in town, I think.
She and her mom, pearl.
The family you're so
rudely trying to prevent
From buying Grayson's building.
Her mother's name is pearl?
Yes, so?
Well, I believe I already
know all about her.
Oh, good, there you are.
Jenna wanted me
To get the car.
What happened?
All right, now this
is getting weird.
We're here to talk.
I'm not in the mood. Today's been
A no-good, very bad day.
Annabelle tells me you're
looking for something
I took fromJohnathan Gilbert.
I'm listening.
What is that?
Johnathan was passionate
about his inventions.
He confided in me that he had
created a detection device
Meant to track down the
town's vampire element.
It was a pocket watch.
That's what it turned
out to be, yes.
But that's not what I stole.
I discovered my mistake when I
saw the watch in Johnathan's hand
The night they took us.
Its dial pointed at me.
So what is this? I have no idea.
But now it's yours.
What's the catch?
There's no catch.
My daughter wants to stay here.
I want to stay here.
You refuse to trust us,
and for good reason.
Consider this an apology.
You shouldn't be here.
I know.
Now you know.
That wasn't you.
Oh, it was absolutely me.
I'a monster predator.
It's who I am, Elena.
That's what the blood makes you.
The blood brings out
what's inside of me.
And if you think any differently,
then you're an idiot.
I know this isn't you, Stefan.
I wanted to drain
Every ounce of blood
from that girl's body.
- No.
- It's who I am, Elena.
No. You can't scare me off.
Why would you risk it?
Why would you come here?
Because I did this.
This is my fault.
I'm the one who made you
drink the blood.
All you did was expose
me to who I really am.
This isn't you.
Stop saying that!
Don't get any closer to me.
I'm not going
to let this happen to you.
Stop.
Stefan, I'm not going
to give up on you.
Stop!
I'm so sorry.
It's ok.
I don't know what's
happening to me.
It's ok, Stefan, shhh.
It's ok.
You're gonna be ok.
Sure you want to do this?
I'm sure.
There's no guarantee
this is going to work.
It has to.
You comin'?
I'm gonna stay here.
Sync by YYeTs.net
www.addic7ed.com