Previously on Mad Men.
I wanted you to come to me.
- And why is that?
- Because you're married.
- So you're missing here?
- Are you asking if I miss you?
- What's your name?
- It used to be Dick Whitman.
I didn't want to go
to her wedding, but I did.
The least you can do
is not come to mine.
You're not even
giving Jane a chance.
I wanna take you in that bedroom, And
give you a go round like you never had.
I wanted to inform you
that you're now the head of accounts.
- Excuse me?
- We're making you head of accounts.
Spectacular.
Synchro: zelda-zelda
Season 3 Episode 12
The Grown-Ups
I've got your hot cocoa.
Wonderful.
I just got back from lunch,
and Mr. Pryce wants to see you.
- It's instant.
- It's from the diner.
- How you can tell ?
- You can tell
because they use water
instead of milk.
It's warmer outside.
It's ridiculous.
The building will take care of it.
They always do.
Sorry about that.
This really is hitting the spot.
Come in.
Have a seat.
I believe I have what is
rather disappointing news.
It's been decided that Mr. Cosgrove
will be made senior vice president
in charge of account services
and you will be made
head of account management.
Really?
This is not to ignore
that you've distinguished yourself
and been of great service
to the company.
What is it based on?
Our billings are neck and neck.
I think I've done a lot with what
I was given in this arbitrary scheme.
It's become apparent taht
you are excellent
at making the clients feel their needs
are being met, but
Mr. Cosgrove has the rare gift
of making them feel
as if they haven't any needs.
I see.
I improved your title.
And you tell your clients
there'll be no need
to be deprecating.
- Bert and roger know about this?
- This is under my authority.
And I have to commend you
on taking it as well as you have.
I hope this was
a difficult decision.
It was.
There you go.
- Where are you going?
- I don't feel well.
Why did you pick that place?
I don't know why a lunch counter
is any better than eating at your desk.
You could've joined me for a drink.
I can drink at my desk if i want to,
and i'm not out $1.25.
I'm sorry i'm not
asstimulating a lunch
companion as doug.
It's duck, and I work most lunches.
I don't like his aftershave.
I can smell it on you and I can smell it
in the bathroom in the morning.
What's wrong with him?
Nothing.
I don't even know why I'm weighing
in on men right now.
I think it's good that
you're being picky, finally.
Well, there's nothing around
but married ones,
I mean, we can't all
throw caution to the wind.
Duck's not married.
Then why are you with him?
Well, this is me.
- Are you working late tonight?
- I don't know yet.
Van cleef.
How very Janie Siegel-Sterling.
They're blue and they're new.
She's trying.
You always take her side.
I do not.
She started giving me advice,
"don't go to bed angry.
Let them do what they want.
Dress sexy".
And all I kept thinking
about was daddy.
It's disgusting.
Doesn't she know that?
That she ruined my life?
Your father had a part in it.
You don't think i know that?
Brooks is different
than your father.
I don't want to get married.
Everything's pointing
to the fact that I shouldn't,
and everybody knows.
Brooks knows.
His mother knows.
Do you know what she said to me?
She said in India...
if the wedding doesn't take place
at the appointed hour,
they burn the bride.
Just because she went to india,
doesn't mean she's not an idiot.
And jane...
if she's coming,
I'm not going.
She's coming because
your father's coming
and he paid for everything.
You're having the wedding.
The bride will not be burned.
Turn those earrings into
a tea service or something.
- Aren't you listening to me?
- I am, and you're babbling
- like a little fool. Go to your room.
- What?
You heard me. You want to act
like a child, I'll treat you like one.
Would somebody get that?
Daddy.
Are you alone?
- Yes, what's wrong?
- Nothing's right.
My bridesmaids are supposed to give me
something blue and something new
- or mommy. She should know that.
- Who?
I don't like her, daddy,
and I've told you
I don't want her to be there.
- Honey, put your mother on the phone.
- He wants to talk to you.
Keep Jane under control.
First of all, tell the bride that
everything is copacetic.
We both agree that she's nuts
and she should shut up.
Your father said that he's sorry,
that jane will stay out of your way
and that we're both tired of the drama.
He said all that?
I'm not playing chicken anymore.
If she wants to cancel the wedding,
I'll take the deposit
out of her inheritance.
- He said the wedding's off.
- Fine.
You men that.
You are not worried about India ?
- Why are you doing this?
- Do you want to cancel it or not?
No.
Then go eat something.
I'm not taking that dress in again.
Why did jane get her
such an expensive gift?
- I didn't know they saw each other.
- Of course you didn't.
I forbid it.
I can't wait to get her out of here.
Is everything okay?
Goodbye.
Yeah, goodbye.
Get in here now.
I didn't know you were home.
I overdid it at lunch,
as did you, I heard.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I just wanted to make amends.
I got her a beautiful present.
Why the hell are you even talking
to her? You're screwing things up!
I'm tired of the awkwardness
and i'm trying to be nice.
I don't know what kind of world
you live in, but
- I am the good person here.
- You're not good
because you didn't listen to me
and you really upset her.
Everything you do is for her.
I'm yourwife.
And guess what. I live here
and I get to do what I want to do,
so stop trying to tell me
that you know better.
You'd better not have
locked that door.
Go away!
Or what? You'll commit suicide?
Peter, what are you doing home?
I got fired.
What happened?
Lane told me kenny is
senior something
of something accounts and i'm not.
I'm account something.
I couldn't even hear him.
All I saw was his froglike
mouth flapping.
So did he ask you to leave?
No.
I have to ask this,
but did you lose your temper?
No, i didn't.
That's good.
That's very good.
Do you rember if he said anything
about how much they want you to stay?
No.
That's good too.
So it didn't come up.
Stop it with the ellery queen.
- I'm going to call duck.
- No, you're not.
They would have fired you
if they wanted to fire you.
You need to wait
and see how it goes.
He basically said I care too much
about my clients and they notice it.
How could that be bad?
You hold all the cards.
It's going to be fine.
I thought you had left.
I'm here.
I see.
Well, thank you.
I've done it before.
Go back to bed.
- Do you want anything?
- No. I'll be in in a bit.
It's got to be 100 in here.
You ask the building
for heat, you get heat.
Mr. Herman on line one.
- Can you give me a minute?
- No.
I'm right around the corner
at the elysee, room 531.
I'm in the middle of something.
Peewee sweetheart,
it's been three weeks.
You can get room service.
I think they have a Monte Cristo
sandwich. You love that.
I'm having lunch
with kurt and smitty.
They're a couple of homos.
Tell them you have plans.
- It's kind of short notice.
- Come on, creative,
be creative.
I have to go to the printer.
I know a nooner when i hear one.
You're disgusting.
I was hoping to catch you
on your way to lunch.
Too late.
I found out yesterday
that head of accounts
is going to kenny and his haircut.
I heard.
- Can you turn that off?
- Not really.
- Were you consulted?
- After the fact.
What does it mean?
It's not good.
I know it's not good.
There's no future for me here.
How did you do it?
You made your job up.
I didn't.
I looked at other agencies,
saw that they had tv departments
and wondered why we didn't.
There's no such thing
in the accounts field.
- There's marketing.
- That's a research job.
- Is this official?
- Yes.
I'm afraid we can't hire
Mr. Charcot.
Well, at least you had the guts
to send me a memo.
He's far too expensive.
Salvatore Romano is gone. There is
no one in charge of the art department.
I haven't heard a complaint from
any of the clients.
Jesus! It's hotter
in here than in my office.
That's because you're overexcited.
Do you want me to walk you through
a delivery schedule?
This is Walter Cronkite
in our newsroom and
and there has been an attempt,
as perhaps you know now, on the life
of president Kennedy.
He was wounded in an automobile
driving from Dallas airport
into downtown Dallas
along with governor
connally of texas
They've been taken to Parkland hospital
there where their condition is as yet
my god, how much have
you been smoking in here?
Sorry about that.
I'm, uh, glad
you ran over.
Me too.
I don't understand. I can't run
my department without an art director.
Do you want to call Saint John?
Bert Cooper still has
a say around here.
Quoi ?
If they wanted to fire you,
they would've fired you.
I'm gonna die at this desk,
unnoticed.
Do you have any idea
what I've done for this company?
- What are you doing?
- They shot the president.
What?
...top of the president's
car was down
they drew their pistols,
but the damage was done.
The president was slumped over
in the back seat
of the car, face down.
Then governor Connally, after slumping
to the left for a moment,
lay on the floor of the rear seats.
- Oh my god.
- Is he dead?
What the hell is going on?
Every person listening at this moment
has flashed back
to that day in april, 1945,
when
Franklin Delano Roosevelt...
excuse me, chet, here is a flash from
the associated press, dateline Dallas.
Two priests who were
with president kennedy
say he is dead of bullet wounds.
There is no further confirmation,
but this is what we have
Is he okay?
They just said he died.
Who were with president kennedy
say he is dead of bullet wounds.
There is no further confirmation.
This is the only word we have
indicating the president may,
in fact, have lost his life.
It has just moved on the associated
press wires from dallas.
The two priests were called
to the hospital to administer
the last rites
And it is from them we get the word
that the president has died,
that the bullet wounds
inflicted on him as he rode
in a motorcade through downtown Dallas
have been fatal.
We would remind you there
is no official confirmation
of this from any source as yet.
Just moments before
you brought the flash,
I had word from the hospital
that the vice president,
Lyndon Johnson, and his wife
had just left the hospital...
Did you give me a hickey?
- I don't think so.
- I told you I don't like that.
I get questions from my mother.
Listen. There was
a news story that was on right
before you came in.
It's been distracting me.
You didn't seem distracted.
I just want to see what's going on.
What's going on?
...it was only on october the 24th
that our ambassador
to the united nations, Adlai Stevenson,
was assaulted in Dallas leaving
a dinner meeting there.
From dallas, texas, the flash,
apparently official:
president Kennedy died at 1:00 p.m.
Central standard time,
2:00 eastern...
- Jesus.
- Oh my god.
What happened?
Vice president Lyndon Johnson has
left the hospital
I've gotta call my kids.
...to where he has proceed.
Presumably, he will be taking
the oath of office
shortly and become
the 36th president of the united
President johnson
is under heavy guard...
it's ruined.
It's over.
It's gonna be ruined.
...five-year-old boy and myself were
by ourselves on the grass
there on palmer street.
I asked joe to wave to him.
All right, sir.
Go ahead and tell it.
As he was waving back,
he was...
the shot rang out...
- where's your mother?
- She's not feeling well.
He was slumping down
and the second shot went off
and just knocked him down.
I can't stop crying.
No, sir, I did not see
the man who did it.
I...all I...
all i did was look
why are the kids watching this?
What am I supposed to do, Don?
Am I supposed to keep it from them?
...that it hit him and he went
all the way down in the car.
Take a pill and lie down.
I can handle the kids.
...fell on him in hopes
there wasn't a maniac around.
I'm sorry
I can't help you more,
but I won't forget it.
Turn this off.
I'll make us some dinner.
A polaroid picture taken by another
witness, Mary Norman of Dallas,
showing the president
slumped over in the car.
Just as mary started
to take the picture,
the president came
right even with us,
two shots, we looked at him...
You two, look at me.
Two shots rang out
and he grabbed his chest.
Everything is going to be okay.
We have a new president
and we're all gonna be sad
for a little bit.
And then on monday
there's gonna be a funeral.
Are we going to the funeral?
...shots rang out, but by that time
the motorcade had sped away.
...fair play for cuba,
a pro-castro organization,
where he had been arrested
on disturbance of the peace charges.
He denied
he was a communist, said he was
a marxist and claimed there was
quite a difference between the two.
Police in Dallas
have just announced...
you should get ready.
It's almost 2:00.
Really, don?
...gunpowder traces on both hands,
indicating he'd recently
used a rifle.
The type of weapon that killed
Mr. Kennedy yesterday.
As we told you a short time ago,
oswald has refused...
he's 24 years old.
In washington, the body
of the late president lies...
Come on, betts.
Are you sure they haven't canceled it?
In "the times" they were doing that.
I'm not gonna
call roger to find out.
If we go in and it's off,
we'll grab dinner or something.
I can't sit in front
of the tv all day.
Fine.
...ailing Mr. Kennedy
stricken by a stroke two years ago--
just stay here until Carla comes.
...greatly increasingly
failing health for the last--
after the terrible news
had reached us...
Can you see bags?
I don't understand this.
And here we are...
Lyndon Johnson, more of the same.
Nobody voted for him.
It felt for a second like everything
was about to change.
You should get
your coat and your scarf.
I know it's far, but I really feel
like walking.
Why are we going?
Because it's your boss's
daughter's wedding.
It's business, Pete, and there's
a system. You always say that.
It's one thing to go to this wedding
and act like I don't hate them.
It's another thing to go and act
like the President hasn't been murdered.
Maybe they'll cancel it,
but we have to show.
- Have you been drinking?
- The whole country's drinking,
and not to celebrate some
spoiled brat's wedding.
We are mourning together
with his widow...
They'll never cancel.
You know why?
Because they're happy.
You should've heard some of the things
people said yesterday.
Like what? What did they say?
"The man made a lot of enemies,"
things like that.
That's awful.
I don't care what your politics are,
this is America.
You don't just shoot the President.
Chet Huntley was talking about
Jackie and those kids,
how she just lost that baby,
and Harry Crane was looking at
his paperwork,
calculating how many commercials
weren't going to be aired.
I'm not going.
You can go and say I'm sick
if you think it's that important.
... Demonstrates the internal threat
that can never be underestimated.
No, you're right.
Our sympathy
for the Kennedy family is no less
that it is for the millions of people
who have sustained equal losses
in the fight for freedom.
I got a call from Leona, the girl I used
to work with at the phone company.
My friend Francine called me.
Don couldn't get through.
The system was
completely overloaded.
It's annoying that people think
the operators were watching tv.
They were as frustrated as anyone.
The maitre d' has reorganized
the seating.
If you are at an even-numbered table,
take these first six.
If you are at an odd-numbered table,
the left side of the room.
Maestro, do you mind?
Thank you.
Look, everybody, grab your plate
and come on up to the front here,
sit wherever you feel like.
And please feel free to have
the prime rib and the fillet of sole.
Help yourself.
I mean that. There are no waiters.
Three months after Roosevelt died,
we bombed Hiroshima.
That's how we got over it.
I say we hang Lee Oswald
and then we take care of Texas...
Hell, the whole south.
What did everyone
think of the sweetbreads?
You were right, mommy. Okay?
Problem solved.
Hardly.
They just told me
the cake's not coming.
Shit.
I have to say on some level
Harry has a point.
I think he wanted attention.
He obviously didn't fit in.
Congratulations.
You are so beautiful,
like Natalie Wood or something.
Daddy, I really wish you could've gotten
to see the ceremony.
It's okay. We understand.
We're honored you're here.
- I heard the church was packed.
- Those weren't our guests.
Have a seat.
Just...
sit anywhere.
I'm so happy for you.
I would like some
legal representation,
but these police officers
have not allowed me to have any.
I don't know what this is all about.
- Did you kill the President?
- No, sir, I didn't.
How would you know that's
what a monster looks like?
Naturally, if I work in that building,
yes, sir.
- Did you see "The Times"?
- He lived in Russia.
- I thought he just visited.
- Would you visit?
I'm just a patsy.
There you are.
What are you doing here?
They're about to interview Oswald.
Hey, somebody go buy a cake.
Has the gentleman been identified?
I need you out there.
I'm about to give my toast.
I've heard your toast
a million times.
The President is dead.
And I'll tell you something else
our table has no one at it.
I consolidated the tables.
Would you keep an eye on her?
Absolutely.
We'd better get back in there.
This toast is going to be much shorter
than it was supposed to be.
Obviously,
we're all in a different mood.
Can someone get my
wife out of the kitchen?
I have something very nice
to say about her.
But while we're alone...
...I want to say something
nice about my ex-wife.
You're a lioness.
And thank you for resisting
the urge to eat your cub.
This could've been an awful day,
but here we are...
Not watching tv
but, together,
watching the two of you.
To Margaret and Brooks Hargrove.
The adults, we all wanted to be
strong for you,
but your spirit your love, your hope
is giving us strength.
And I promise you now if you can
make it through a day like today,
marriage is a cakewalk.
To many years of happiness.
Cheers.
We invite the father of the bride and
the bride to share the dance floor.
Sorry about that.
Now if there are any other fathers
and daughters...
You know what?
Everyone, please, join them.
Do you want to dance?
I don't know.
Want me to teach him how to dance?
He's a great dancer.
She's happy.
That's because she doesn't know
his net worth just dropped by half.
Stop it, daddy.
Everything's gonna be fine.
How do you know that?
You'll see.
Why do you keep
looking at that woman?
What are you talking about?
- Are you ready?
- Did jennifer fall in?
She'll be right out.
See you tuesday.
He was so handsome,
and now i'll never
get to vote for him.
You want me
to cut you out of that dress?
I'm making a phone call.
Hello.
So what's new?
It's incredible, isn't it?
Yes.
Margaret got married today.
That's right. I forgot.
Poor thing.
I wish you could've seen it.
Oh my god, what a disaster.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, she pulled through.
They pulled through.
I pulled through.
I can't believe how
quiet it is out there.
Not everywhere.
Greg just called. He's working
the night shift at the E.R.
People are still getting sick.
Car accidents are happening.
Babies are are being born.
Well, i'm glad he's not home.
I had to talk to you.
Nobody else is saying
the right thing about this.
My god, you're really upset.
What's that about?
Because there's nothing
funny about this.
Well...
- Hang in there, red.
- You too.
Bye-Bye.
Goodbye.
Put him on a standby of
indeterminate length, will you?
Let me have it.
I want it.
Being led out by Captain Fritz.
Clearers are pushing.
There is Lee Oswald.
He's been shot.
- Oh my god. Oh my god.
- What happened?
They shot him.
The police were walking him through
the building and some man shot him.
What?
Detectives have their guns drawn.
What is going on?!
There is no question about it.
Oswald has been shot.
Don, please leave me alone.
What happened?
Nothing.
Go upstairs.
The family, incidentally,
asked that there be no flowers
But there nevertheless
have been flowers.
People either didn't hear
or chose to ignore it.
And one room or two rooms
in the white house
have had to be set aside to...
To host.
I'm going out.
- Where?
- For a drive.
Let me drive.
I'll get the kids. We'll all
go somewhere.
That's a good idea.
No.
I need to clear my head.
I'm so glad you could see me.
Where does your husband
think you are?
I don't care.
He's been lying to me for years.
I couldn't be in that house.
Then I saw you yesterday.
I didn't know
you were going to be there.
I hoped you would be there.
Derby day...
It seems like 100 years ago.
And then this morning,
seeing that man shot to death...
what is going on?
It will be okay.
We've lost a lot of presidents
and we're still standing.
I wish I could believe you.
I can't believe anything right now.
Have you thought that
there are other ways to live?
Listen. I'm not in love with
the tragedy of this thing.
It's not "Romeo and juliet."
I want it to happen.
I have three children.
I'll know more when the primaries
start to shake out in spring,
But I can leave the campaign
right now.
I don't want you to do that.
You don't have to answer me now...
But I want to marry you.
I don't know what to say.
You don't have to say anything.
I told you.
But if you search your heart,
You'll know that
I can make you happy.
I should go.
I wish I could take you
to the movies right now,
Some theater that's playing
your favorite movie.
"Singing in the rain."
Well,
just think about that.
...it was made possible
by a special equipment,
it will move at one fourth speed,
so we would like
to show you in slow motion
the shooting
of Lee Harvey Oswald now.
They just stood there.
No security for the most
wanted man in America.
He didn't even have a trial.
Just throw him over the mob.
You can see the two detectives,
one in a light suit, one in a dark,
bringing Oswald out.
The camera changes its length,
for a close up of Oswald.
The shot has been fired,
you cannot hear it
in this version of the tape.
Oswald falls
and the man with the hat moves in on him
and he's grabbed by the man in light.
- Do not go in to work tomorrow.
- No, of course not.
It's a national day of mourning.
You're going to go on Tuesday.
That's another happy thought.
Those people don't care about you.
And honestly, what's the difference?
What are you saying?
You did everything
they asked you to do,  but
You don't owe them anything.
You should start
gathering your clients.
They'll follow you wherever you go.
The only other president buried there
is William Howard Taft.
Though of course, there are many
other heroes of perhaps
lesser renown.
Francine has the kids.
I don't know where to begin.
What?
I want...
To scream at you.
For ruining all of this.
But...
Then you try to fix it and...
There's no point.
There's no point, Don.
You're very upset, I understand.
I know it's painful.
But it's going to pass.
I don't love you.
Betts, don't.
- You're distraught.
- It's true.
But I don't love you anymore.
I know that.
Stop it.
I kissed you yesterday.
And I didn't feel a thing.
You'll feel better tomorrow.
You'll see.
You can't even hear me right now.
You're right.
Morning.
- Morning, daddy.
- Morning.
Where are you going?
I have to go to work, I'm sorry.
It's cold outside.
I'm fine.
What are you doing here?
I don't know. Aqua Net.
It doesn't shoot till after
Thanksgiving.
We'll be ok.
What do you have?
What are you doing here?
The bars are closed.
My roommate invited over half
the building so they can watch TV
and write condolence letters
to Jackie.
Then I went to my sister's
and my mother was crying...
and praying so hard.
There wasn't room for anyone else
to feel anything.
The funeral has already started.
I was gonna watch it in Cooper's office.
Is it ok?
Are you coming?