You can't keep avoiding me.
Really? I thought I was doing a good job.
I know what you can do.
I heard you the first time.
That doesn't make it any funnier.
It's not a coincidence
that there've been fewer deaths...
since you started working here.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Tru, I've watched you.
I've seen how you behave.
You can do things.
Things that others can't.
I don't even know how to....
Tru, it's okay.
You can talk to me.
They ask me to help them.
I wake up, the same day starts over and--
You save them.
Try to. Sometimes I can't.
You don't think I'm crazy?
No, do you?
Sometimes.
You're not.
Why isn't this just
completely freaking you out?
I've seen a lot of strange things here.
Very little shocks me.
I can't. I can't live like this.
I keep secrets from people that I love.
I can't have a normal relationship.
You're saving lives.
It's a gift.
No, candles are gifts.
Boots, bath salts maybe, but this is....
I don't know what this is. Do you?
I don't. Not yet. But tell me, Tru.
How does it feel...
to know that somewhere out there...
someone is about to die...
and they're gonna ask you for your help?
Hello?
Yeah, I'm ready.
I know we have to do this.
I love you, too.
Help me.
No, reaIIy,
who do you think I am?
Baby, I think you're my girI.
Anything wrong with that?
You shouIdn't be so certain.
Can't heIp it if I'm certain.
Come on, Iet's take a waIk, huh?
No, I'm not faIIing for that.
You're faIIing for somebody.
Tru, love is never like it is in the movies.
I mean, when was the Iast time you kissed
and music sweIIed?
You're lucky if you can find
a guy that can tell time.
I'm not asking for much, Linds.
Just a solid guy,
some decent conversation.
Maybe when he smiles,
he'll have this little crease above his lip.
Oh, God, who is he?
His name is Luc.
And he's a crime scene photographer.
But what's the point?
With the hours I keep,
we'll never have time together.
That'll lead to issues and....
You're planning the breakup...
and you haven't even
gone out with the guy yet.
Look, I'm just saying,
know what you want, and act accordingly.
For example, what I want
is out of my cube at the office.
So tonight, over drinks...
I am gonna show the big boss man
my take on a new account.
I don't want a promotion.
I just want a first date.
Fine.
But if it's romantic settings...
and movie moments that you're after...
my advice, keep them a mystery.
Because real life is not like the movies.
Sorry.
Okay, I really hope you like my take on this.
Let's take a look.
You've put a lot of work into this, Lindsay.
- Nice job.
- Thank you.
It's exactly this kind of motivation
that moves you forward.
Knowing what you want, and going for it.
That is so funny.
I just said that exact thing
to my friend today.
I just got back from a pickup...
so just make sure there's nothing
left in the truck, okay?
- No problem.
- Good.
Hey.
Hey. What are you doing here?
One: I work here.
Right. And two?
Look, um...
I was thinking how we've been
seeing a lot of each other...
here in the morgue.
I was thinking how maybe it'd be nice
to see each other outside of the morgue.
I know this isn't
the most appropriate pIace to ask...
but would you be interested
in going out sometime?
I know this isn't
the most appropriate place to say yes...
but, yeah, I'd really like that.
How's tomorrow?
Tomorrow might be risky.
I never really know
how my days are gonna go.
Look, you got an hour.
Okay, so take it.
I got it covered. Don't worry about it.
You guys have been doing
the mating dance for weeks now.
Get it over with.
You got an hour?
Yeah.
Thanks.
So....
You grew up wanting
to take pictures of dead people?
I grew up wanting to take pictures.
The dead people...
came later.
- I know the feeling.
- What'd you say?
- I said, I know the feeling.
- What?
I said, I....
Never mind.
How's it possible that you're still single?
My friend Lindsay always says:
"If the wrong guy's in the room,
I'll find him."
I mean, not now. I mean, not you.
I didn't mean....
Just a minute.
Sorry.
That's all right.
What's up?
Total disaster.
Tell me about it.
Okay, I will.
I just got busted down to receptionist.
You're kidding. What for?
My boss made a move,
I said no...
and he said,
"Maybe you'd enjoy answering phones."
Okay, don't worry, we'll fix this.
I'll call you later, okay?
Okay. Bye.
You okay?
Are we having fun yet?
Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
- No, I got it.
Yeah?
Yeah, you've got a pickup on- site.
It's two bodies and Gardez needs help.
No, a pickup?
I didn't know that was part
of the job description.
Great.
Surprise.
This was going so well.
Sorry.
So, how'd it go with photo boy?
You know those nights where things
click and you never want it to end?
That bad, huh?
I'm surprised we didn't get called out
to Lakewood Cliff sooner.
Looks like the guardrail finally gave way.
Hey, you got any advice
for a first- timer?
Thanks. Yeah, don't think so much.
Any theories?
Young love.
How many times have you seen a death...
that doesn't have
something to do with love?
You see that neckIace there?
Not something a high- schooI girI
wouId buy for herseIf.
It probably came from him.
Do we know who they are?
The guy's name's Adam Whitman,
a student at Highland Prep.
The girI's name's Jen DeLuca,
just a Iearner's permit.
See that tattoo? It means"ambition."
Looks like his was cut a little short though.
Damn, the bodies
are all jacked up.
We need a coupIe of stokes.
I'll be right back.
You were in love, weren't you?
Help us.
So you're saying yesterday a guy and a girl
went over a cliff in a car accident?
Yeah.
Was I wearing this shirt?
Unfortunately, yes.
License plate was....
689- TYH.
You memorized the license plate?
I memorize everything I can.
Once they ask for help,
I lose the body, any evidence.
The only thing I can go on
is what I remember.
Okay, the car was Adam's,
so I'II find him first.
I guess I'm going to Highland Prep.
Slow down there.
Yeah, I'm kinda in a rush.
That's funny, I was just thinking...
how we've been seeing a lot of each other
here in the morgue.
Yeah. Funny.
Then I was thinking...
how maybe it'd be nice to see each other
outside of the morgue.
I'm right in the middle of something.
Come on. It'll be fun.
No, I got it.
Yeah?
It could be.
I would love to. I would.
I just....Not right now.
I can't right now.
Let me just get back to you, okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Keys?
You be careful with her.
I know. You won her in
the best poker game of your life.
Come on, I'm in a hurry.
Hold up. Is this one of your crazy days?
Keys? Yes, or no?
I just want her back, that's all.
Without a scratch.
Not the car. My sister.
Yeah?
Where are you?
Oh, God, Linds, I'm sorry.
I had to bolt. Something came up at work.
lncoming call
from Planet Bitch. Come back now.
Harrison says,"Hi."
Is it visitation day at the penitentiary?
She sends big hugs.
Can we hook up later?
Can't. I have to meet up
with my boss for drinks.
I'm showing him
my take on a new account.
I just got busted
down to receptionist!
You know, Linds, I really think
you should cancel.
You know,
maybe keep work meetings in the office.
Thanks. But I really think
he's gonna be impressed. Trust me.
I'II caII you after? Bye.
Harrison.
I'm gonna need one more favor.
So I'm a mature 17.
Excuse me.
Do you know
where I can find Adam Whitman?
Thanks.
I don't get you.
You're dating the hottest girl in school,
and you're sad.
I don't love her'cause she's hot, Cole.
Come on.
You know what? You don't....
Just forget it.
What?
You don't think I understand
the plight of star- crossed lovers?
I got a C- plus on that paper.
- Ambition.
- Good luck.
Nice ink.
Hardly any bleed- off.
Good work, too.
- Adam.
- Tru.
lmpressive.
What's your deal? You new?
Checking it out for the day.
My family's thinking of moving here.
Run, don't walk.
We're all stuck here,
but you still got an out.
That bad?
Not if you find the right person.
This is my girlfriend Amy.
Your girlfriend?
Young love.
This is Tru.
Prospective student.
Amy. Nice to meet you.
We hitting the café or what?
Yeah. Whatever you want.
I couldn't give the okay to a school
without checking out the grub first.
A girl after my own heart. Tag if you want.
Cool.
So where you from, anyway?
Does it matter?
Not to me, but to some.
Most of us pay to go here.
Some of the other kids,
they're here on scholarship...
so they actually have to
work their way through.
What's the big deal?
It's stupid, really.
It's like this decades- old thing.
The two sides of the town just don't mix.
So it seeps into the school.
We avoid them, they avoid us.
Boy, it's fun to grow up
in the middle of a cliché.
Let me get this for you.
First meal's on me.
I'm just gonna get us a table.
Hey.
- Do you know that girl?
- Who?
The one at the register.
Not really.
She's on scholarship.
Like I said, oil and water.
It's Romeo and Juliet.
Kinda. Two worIds.
He's rich, she's poor.
Things wouldn't be kosher
if they were dating.
Are they?
Neither of them are fessing up.
And he's got a very public girlfriend.
This is kinda cool.
We're like a team.
A team?
Yeah, like the Wonder Twins,
except we're not twins...
I don't have any super powers.
Yeah. I should get back.
Romeo's getting me nowhere.
I'll try my luck with Juliet.
Good luck, because you know
how well that turned out.
Yeah.
I was wondering
if you could help me. I'm lost.
Who isn't?
Not a fan of this place?
Of high school?
I see your point.
I saw you in line in the cafeteria.
- Tru.
- Jen.
DeLuca.
I caught your name tag.
Adam was showing me around.
He seems to have a way with the ladies.
Yeah. I wouldn't know.
He's not really my type.
Yeah, not my brother's either.
That's one headache I don't need.
Your brother doesn't like Adam?
No. Derek hates everybody.
You ask a lot of questions
for a prospective.
See you.
Who's your new friend?
Shut up and drive.
Morgue.
Run a DMV check for me.
Someone nicked my brother's car
and didn't leave a note.
The guy's name is Derek DeLuca.
The guy who stole your car gave his name?
Look, not a lot of time here.
AII right.
Bingo. Derek DeLuca.
Looks Iike he's got a coupIe
of outstanding speeding tickets.
You wouldn't
happen to have an address?
Hey.
Aren't you the girl from the school?
I was giving myself a tour around town,
and I saw you in the driveway.
What are you working on?
I'm just tweaking the air mixture.
How come you don't go to Highland?
You've seen
those trust- fund casualties.
Why do I want to hang out with them?
What, you don't like chilling with rich boys
and their expensive rides?
Can't say I'm a fan.
Of expensive rides,
or the boys who drive them?
Like Adam Whitman?
Don't tell me you're a friend of Whitman's.
I'm not a friend of anybody's yet.
But why, what's your issue with him?
His dad runs the glass factory out on 22.
He fired about 300 people last month.
My dad was one of them.
You seen Adam's new ride?
Probably bought it with the savings
from the layoffs.
I think you and I both know
it's not about the car.
It's about the driver.
Guess we'll see tonight.
What do you mean?
I'm racing Adam.
You should come see for yourself.
Car race.
Where?
Lakewood Cliff. Two hours.
I've got a where, but not a how.
If it happens at the race,
it'd explain Adam's death but not Jen's.
I don't know how they ended up
in the car together.
Maybe they weren't.
What do you mean?
'Cause it Iooks Iike an accident...
doesn't mean that it is.
You should know, in our business...
things aren't aIways
what they appear to be.
Thanks, Davis.
I've never had anyone help me before.
I've never had anyone to help.
Do you have a booth?
Something quiet? We have work to do.
All right. Right this way.
Lindsay, is that you?
Harrison.
What a surprise.
Tru told me you were gonna be here.
Come here.
It is so great to see you!
It is?
What's up, my man? Harrison Davies.
I'm an old friend of Lindsay's.
You are?
Are you guys eating?
Because I am starving, and they have
this little shrimp thing...
that is just to die for.
So when I finally stopped,
everyone behind me was covered.
I'm talking head to toe.
And everyone was just glaring at me,
like I meant to do it.
So anyway, that's the most I ever puked.
What about you, Greggers?
Excuse me.
What the hell are you doing?
You are deliberately sabotaging drinks
with my boss.
Apparently, I'm doing this
for your own good.
Giving him every reason
to demote me to phones?
No. Preventing it.
At least that's what I'm told.
Not that I know what to believe anymore.
Harrison, I swear to God....
Look, let's just say I have this friend.
Yeah, you got friends?
Okay, more like a friend of a friend.
Anyway, she used to work for Greg
until she found out...
that"after- hour drinks" were a quick way
for him to get into her--
Okay, stop, please.
You're the only one
that would take it there.
Gregory and I are here to work.
Whatever you say.
How much horsepower?
Hitting 425, going for 12 seconds.
108?
You don't have to do this.
It'll be over before you know it.
And then we'll have
the rest of the night for us.
Hey.
Got a minute?
I didn't know
you were gonna be here.
How did you know we were gonna....
You can't do this. This race.
I'll be fine.
No, you won't.
Something's gonna go very wrong.
This thing Derek has against you--
Is that what this is about?
Don't sweat it. I'm way ahead of you.
Yo, Derek.
Ready to go?
Only if I'm riding with insurance.
lnsurance?
Yeah. He takes one of mine,
I take one of his.
Make sure you know
no one's pIaying around.
Fine. I'll take him.
I'll take her.
No, you can't do this. I'm serious.
Just watch. You'll love it.
You look worried.
How should I look when someone I love
is doing something stupid.
I'm sorry, I can't watch this.
You ready for the ride of your life?
Go, Derek. It's your birthday.
Watch out!
What's she doing?
She's crazy!
Come on! You just cut me off!
You jumped out
in the middle of the street.
Are you insane?
There's no way
I was gonna go over the cliff.
Let it go. You're alive, and you won.
I'm happy, you're happy.
Fair enough. Look, have you seen Amy?
I can't believe she just took off like that.
Here's a hint:
Girls in the movies like guys for their cars.
But girls in real life like guys
for who they are.
Thank you.
Hey, where you going?
Back to real life.
Hey. What are you doing right now?
So, nice work. The table.
I usually get stuck by the kitchen.
Yeah, I do what I can.
Since our time always gets cut short...
I want to skip all the work talk...
and move right to anything
other than work.
Good call. But first, no interruptions.
Okay.
All right, I'll start.
What sport did you play growing up?
- Track. You?
- Baseball.
Red Vines or Twizzlers?
Twizzlers, of course.
I'm strictly a Red Vines guy.
It's hopeless.
Tragic. I'm dating a Red Vines guy.
My turn. First kiss?
Mandy Banks. Fifth grade.
Worst gift you ever gave a girl?
To Adrian O'Malley when I was 13.
I didn't realize that a gold necklace
should cost more than $3. 95.
Necklace.
You see that necklace?
She wasn't wearing it.
Not after it turned
her entire neck green, no.
This isn't gonna make any sense at all,
but I have to go.
Are you okay?
No. Really, I'm insane...
because I'm about to walk out
on a date that's working.
But it's just
there's somewhere I have to be.
Right now?
There are times when I do this.
Take off. I really wish I could explain why...
but I guess I'm just not
your average 22- year- old girl.
Whether you believe me or not,
I'll call you...
and if you're willing
to give it another try, that's great.
If not, I'll understand.
No, I won't.
I'll be completely crushed, but I'll get it.
Thanks. Really, I had a good time.
Yeah, right.
Where's Adam?
He's around somewhere.
What about Jen?
I saw her over there a few minutes ago.
What the hell is going on?
Amy.
- What are you....
- Adam, I'm so sorry.
I knew things weren't great between us,
but how could you--
- Adam, why don't--
- Okay, shut up.
I wanted to tell you.
I didn't know how.
Looks like you figured it out, huh?
I'm so sorry.
For what?
They're all gonna know.
Everyone's gonna know.
Then we'll deal with it.
Remember what we always said
we'd do if people found out?
I don't know.
I've lived here my whole life.
I mean, it's messed up, but it's home.
How they'll look at us?
It won't work here.
We won't work here.
We have to leave, Jen.
Please.
All right. Go home and pack.
I'll pick you up in half an hour.
Everything is gonna be fine.
Remember how I said
this was Romeo and JuIiet?
I was wrong. It's Juliet and Juliet.
Are you joking?
No. Amy and Jen.
They're the ones in love.
They didn't die during the race.
I don't know what's gonna happen, but....
- Hello?
- I gotta go.
Tru.
Okay.
My round. Lindsay?
Greggers, my man?
No, thanks.
Fine. Keep my seat warm.
I am so sorry.
This is not what I wanted for tonight.
Neither did I.
We have a few minutes.
I could at least go through
some of the proposals that I--
If we've only got a few minutes...
then let's not waste it on work.
He was right?
You should--
You should call it a night.
It's getting late.
You're an important guy.
You want to be fresh
for those morning meetings.
You're probably right.
See you tomorrow.
Gregory.
Don't forget this.
We can discuss it tomorrow at the office?
Right.
Good night.
Wow. This is a first.
Thanks, Harrison.
Hello?
Are you ready?
Yeah, I'm ready.
I know we have to do this.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'II be there in a few.
Meet me out front.
What are you doing?
Who were you talking to?
Nobody.
No? You said,"I love you."
It's none of your business.
Where are you going?
Get out!
It's Adam. I knew when he
picked you there was something.
You have no idea
what you're talking about!
He picked me because I'm your sister.
Just tell me where you're going.
Out of my way!
What are you doing here?
- Please, just, can you get in?
- No way.
Come on, Jen, just get in.
I've chilled. Seriously.
I just want to talk to you.
About what?
Look, I can't find Amy.
So the Ieast you can do
is give me a minute.
You owe me that.
One minute.
Exactly!
Damn it, Harrison!
Change your oil once in a while!
Derek.
Babe, I'm kinda busy!
I know it's none of my business...
but your sister's with Adam,
and we gotta stop them.
You read my mind. Hop in.
He's upset. And with the way he drives,
I think something might happen.
You said you wanted to talk.
You don't have to drive fast.
How long has this been going on?
- A few months.
- A few months?
I wanted her to tell you.
No.
I can't believe he thinks
he can bag my sister.
She's not sleeping with him.
What do you think they're doing?
Playing Candyland?
Adam, can you slow down?
I'd just like a few answers.
I got in the car
because you need to know something.
Talk fast.
It's not your fault.
ReaIIy, Adam.
She didn't know how to teII you.
She loves you.
But she's in love with you.
The necklace.
I was gonna get it for her.
She was looking at it in the window
of this jewelry store forever.
Now I know why.
She wanted to give it to you.
You're her best friend, Adam.
That's why it was so hard.
She didn't want to hurt you.
Thinking he's all hard, huh?
What are you doing?
Trying to tap my sister in daddy's car?
You gotta get out of the car.
I can't! It won't. The door's jammed.
Your sister's in that car! Stop it!
Just shut up!
You're gonna kill her!
I'm not gonna hurt my sister.
She needs a little scare.
Stop, you'll push them over!
There's a guardrail. I'm just bumping them.
It won't hold.
The guardrail gave way.
Stop! It won't hold!
Poor little rich boy!
Derek, your sister's not in love with Adam.
She's in love with Amy.
That's who she's running away with.
What?
I saw Derek's car.
So you're saying that at exactly this time...
you were with those two dead kids
at the crash site?
That's what I'm saying.
So the girls aren't running away?
No. But it's not like it's all wrapped
up in a neat little bow.
They've still gotta deal with life
now that their little secret is out.
If it weren't for you,
they wouldn't even have that.
If it weren't for us.
Sometimes just being able to talk
to someone can make it a lot easier.
Who are those for?
Amy and Jen gave them to me...
for helping them deal with their secret.
And I'm giving them to you...
for helping me deal with mine.
Yo, Bro.
Tru?
How you doing?
Fine.
Aren't you gonna ask me about your baby?
What baby?
Your car.
Thought that'd be
the first thing out of your mouth.
Yeah, right.
Sorry, I'm just a little busy right now.
Just real quick,
tell me how things went with Lindsay.
Great. No worries. Mission accomplished.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Look, where are you?
My apartment.
I gotta change to go meet someone.
I don't know if that's the best...
idea.
Oh, my God.
Harrison.
You know, when most girls get up
and run away during the first date...
it's usually a bad sign.
I said I'd call.
Yeah. I thought you meant, like, Tuesday.
Yeah, my timing's been a little off lately.
Can you handle it?
I think I can.
'Cause maybe I'm not looking
for an average 22- year- old.
So you're free all night?
Not going anywhere?
I'm all yours.
You know, a friend of mine was saying...
that real life can't be like the movies...
that maybe sometimes
things are better left to mystery.
What good is a mystery
if you don't try and figure it out?