Did Harrison call?
Hi. No, was he supposed to?
He was supposed to give me a lift.
But, never mind.
I'm not gonna let anything
ruin my mood today because....
Look at me, Davis.
It's the new woman.
And she would be different
from the old woman because?
I won't put everything on hold anymore...
just because a few corpses
get conversational with me.
From now on,
I'm back in control of my own life.
But....
How you doing? You look a little tired.
I've got this thing tomorrow
at my apartment.
- And I haven't unpacked.
- When did you move in?
Three years ago.
Yes, some people are coming over,
because a guy I know from JPL...
is feeding us images
from the Mars Spirit Rover, and--
Why don't I help you unpack?
Really? All right.
Then it'll be me, you, and Jack.
Jack? Why is he--
Because he volunteered
before you showed up.
Honey, I'm home.
Shot through the heart,
found in an alley downtown.
FamiIy's on the way.
Still got her lD and wallet.
Not your average mugging.
Melissa Sumner. 19. College student.
I like a girl
who pays attention to the details.
It's my job.
But not everyone does it so well,
or so thoroughly.
Help me.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah.
I got to go. Just one sec.
That body that just came in,
she asked for help.
- Just now?
- Just now.
But you're still here.
That's because nothing happened.
No rewind. Nothing.
Help me.
Are you sure you didn't imagine this?
Davis, please. I may be overworked,
but I'm not hallucinating.
So is this it?
Am I never gonna rewind again?
- We may never know.
- Did I do something wrong? Or--
No. Don't start that now. You put yourself
on the line for these people.
You've done nothing wrong.
Maybe it didn't happen for a reason.
Something specific to this case, this girl.
A college student. You think
there's something special about her?
Hey. Melissa Sumner's parents
are here for an lD.
I guess we'll find out.
Mrs. Sumner, I'm sure
this is of little comfort to you now...
but I am truly sorry for your loss.
We always told her
how dangerous the city is.
How she should just hand over her wallet
if someone wanted it.
Actually, Mr. Sumner,
her wallet was still with her.
$20 inside.
Can you think of anyone who might have
had animosity towards your daughter?
No!
MeIissa was....
She got aIong with everyone.
She was aIways a good girI.
She was so bright.
She had a brilliant future and....
Honey.
Honey,
you shouldn't be here, okay?
We'll go outside.
The worst part of not rewinding
is watching the family.
All that pain every day,
how do you stand it?
You get used to it.
Where're you going?
I can't just leave it like this.
I mean, I can try and find out...
what happened to Melissa
and why she asked for my help.
I know, I am sorry, okay?
I forgot to pick you up...
- but something unexpected came up.
- A girl or a bet?
Hey, it was an emergency of a kind.
Okay, so I boxed a trifecta at 3- 4- 7.
It was 3- 4- 6.
I was only off by one.
But who would've thought that
Vanilla Custer wouldn't pass a urine test?
- You know what, just forget it.
- What's your hurry?
My hurry is
that a body just asked for my help.
This is a do- over day,
and you let me lose $200?
It's not a do- over. The body asked for help,
and nothing happened.
What, were you fired?
I was Melissa's roommate,
but we really didn't talk much.
She always had her head in a book.
She was doing
a math and engineering double major.
And she was a teaching assistant,
and had a 3. 9 grade point average.
Any arguments, disagreements?
I mean, was she upset about anything?
She seemed fine. Everything was normal.
- I'm sorry I can't be more help.
- No, I appreciate it.
You know, it's not like Melissa and I
were really friends.
But I go back to the room now,
and all of her stuff is still there.
- Like she'll walk in any second.
- Yeah.
But I guess this is just another day to you.
Good. Thanks for coming.
No problem.
This is it. How'd it go?
Actually it didn't go very far.
The roommate backs up the parents.
Nobody has any clue
why anyone would shoot Melissa.
At least you're starting to build
a picture of who she was.
- Hey, Tru.
- Hey, Jack.
I put all 13 episodes of I, CIaudius...
on the same shelf as The X- FiIes videos.
Is that wrong?
What, you were serious
about alphabetizing?
Wow. Davis is a dedicated employee,
isn't he?
He really takes his work home
with him.
I'm trying to imagine
a first- date scenario.
Why don't you come to my apartment?
I'll show you all my books on death.
- Kind of a mood killer.
- Unless you're dating a serial killer.
Hey, Davis. We were just checking out
some of your books.
I thought you guys were here
to help me unpack.
Who's this?
- Someone special, I presume?
- We were together, now we're not.
Look, Harbor Marina. She's pretty.
Yeah.
You still talk to her?
Look, I think I can take care of the rest
of this if you guys want to take off.
He's a funny guy, isn't he?
- Funny?
- Yeah.
He lives alone, he makes death his career.
Have you ever noticed how
he always avoids talking about himself?
Come on, he's just eccentric, that's all.
- How much do you know about him?
- Plenty.
Really? Then tell me this.
Is Davis his first name or his last name?
I'll bet he knows a lot about you, though,
doesn't he?
I got a pickup.
I'll see you back at the morgue.
Yeah, see you there.
Why?
What do you want from me?
How can I help you?
Talking to yourself?
Occupational hazard in a place like this.
You know what I always say.
When they start answering back,
then it's time to worry.
Look at this guy.
Swallowed a whole bottle of downers.
What have we got?
Check this out.
No lD, but he picked up
a lot of business cards.
Maybe he was a salesman.
And the piece de résistance.
"Jean, I'm sorry, please forgive me."
Signed, Geoffrey.
Short, concise, to the point.
Got to admire that.
Save me.
Davis. Two bodies, one day. We got to talk.
Davis, where are you?
No lD, but he's picked up
a bunch of business cards.
You're here early.
I need to talk to Davis. A personal matter.
You rely on him a lot,
for someone you know nothing about.
Or am I wrong about that?
See you, Tru.
Look, Harbor Marina.
"H. Clarke."
I got here as fast as I could.
You want to go talk in the office?
Could these two people
be connected in some way?
What does a murdered coIIege student...
and a businessman's suicide
have in common?
We don't even have a last name
on the suicide.
He signed the note"Geoffrey."
No lD, no address?
We didn't find any.
But I did find a bunch
of different business cards in his pocket.
I checked the company names
on the computer. Get this:
they all had the same address.
It sounds like a place to start.
Two people to save, double workload.
You gonna be okay?
I'll be fine.
I got a head start on Melissa yesterday.
Can I help you?
Yeah.
Does the name H. Clarke
mean anything to you?
Why do you ask?
Tru was looking it up on her computer...
and I was just wondering
whether I'd lost a body.
I mean, H. Clarke wasn't on the list,
but maybe....
It probably doesn't mean anything.
Okay.
I need to borrow your car.
- That's so weird. I was coming--
- No, you weren't gonna come and get me.
And if I were you,
I'd stay away from the trifecta, too.
That is so not fair.
You know what I did and I don't.
You let me down again. Nothing you
haven't done a thousand times before.
And you know what? Lindsay says
the same exact thing about you, too.
Well, excuse me. I made a mistake.
I'm not lucky like you.
You screw up, and it's:
"What am I gonna do?
You know what, I'll just redo it."
That's right, I'm lucky, right?
Because I have two lives to save today
and I have no idea how I'm gonna do it?
You know what? Let me help you on this.
Help me?
You forgot to even come pick me up.
Look, I know about that, but look...
I'm good with people, you know that.
And I've helped you before.
You don't have a lot of options.
You got two lives, right?
You got to trust somebody. Why not me?
I swear, Tru, I will not let you down.
Okay, I'll tell you everything I know
about Melissa Sumner...
but I need you to pay attention...
because you never know
what's gonna be important.
Okay, drive to Hudson,
its uptown campus, Waverly Hall.
She's gonna TA a math class at noon.
All right, that's it for today, class.
Just remember, when you think
something is random, it isn't.
It's aII about patterns.
As Einstein once said,
"God doesn't play dice with the universe."
I liked that little lecture thing there,
especially the end part.
I'm not sure I agree with it, though,
about God not playing dice.
You feel up to arguing with Einstein?
Well, gambling's fun, right?
It just stands to reason that God would
wanna have a good time with His creation.
Probabilities are fun for you and me,
because we can't see the future.
But since God already knows all the cards...
he probably doesn't get
the same kick out of it.
No, that's where you're wrong.
I actually know
a little bit about the future myself.
You do?
Yeah.
I see you. I see me.
We're having lunch together.
Nice try, but I see separate tables.
Right.
"368 West 1st Street."
Hello, Harry.
It's a little harder than I thought.
I've known bail bondsmen
who are friendlier than this chick.
Right. So listen, you have to get
into this girl's life, Harrison.
Whatever her pIans are for today,
you've got to change them.
You can do it. Just be yourself.
I was myself.
- You hit on her?
- No.
Well, not in so many....Yeah.
Then be your other self.
- Lie?
- Bingo.
Got it.
You committed to 6, 000 pounds
of bison meat.
This pIace isn't even refrigerated.
Okay, damn it, you can't get mad cow
from freaking buffaIo.
That's why they caII it"cow."
All right, hold on a second,
just hold on.
Hello? Jean, hi,
it's so good to hear your voice.
No, it's great timing.
Yeah, it's not even
midnight here.
No, that's right, Hong Kong doesn't sIeep.
Listen, honey, I'm right in the middIe
of finishing dinner with some cIients.
No, it's going really well. It's going great.
I miss you, too.
Yeah, I'II be home in a few days.
Okay. I love you, sweetheart.
Hello?
Damn it.
- Man of many names?
- Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm here to see Geoffrey.
I'm from the bank.
I just talked to your manager.
I told him I'd get the money today,
and I will.
I'm working on something right now.
Always a scheme?
I have a brother like you.
Look, the bank's gonna get their money.
I've got everything under control.
- So, thank you for stopping by.
- No problem.
You know, I come up here to be alone.
I can see why, it's a great spot for it.
If you're looking for a girl,
this campus is full of them.
Look, no offense, and....
This is so embarrassing.
I need some help with some math tutoring.
Really? What do you need help with?
Advanced calculus? Beginner?
Ah, um...
Fractions. I need some help
with some fractions.
Come on.
Okay, you multiply, divide, and...
one goes over the other...
and those little slashes?
What is that about? It's confusing.
No, the thing is...
you look like you need a break.
You're all
about patterns, right?
Why don't you break out of yours?
Look, I'm sorry.
You seem like a really nice guy, but...
I've got a lot to do.
Right.
Harbor Marina?
Yeah, I'm looking for H. Clarke.
The owner of a boat called The Comet.
Yeah, I'll hold.
Doctor's office.
Try getting a human being on the phone.
Yeah, I'm still here.
You here for the poker game?
It's high stakes players only.
I'll be right back.
Harrison, what do you know
about a poker game...
at a place called The Countdown Club?
That place. Once a month
they have a high- stakes game...
where they throw out all the small fries.
I don't know,
I've only heard rumors about it.
It looks like Geoffrey's gonna lose
and kill himself sometime tonight.
He's desperate for the money.
Think you could get into the game?
lnto the game?
What about Melissa? And besides...
you need $5, 000 to have a stake.
Right. Just stay where you are,
I'll get the money and bring it to you.
We're gonna switch.
Poker's your worId.
You take Geoffrey,
and I'll take care of Melissa.
Where are you gonna get that kind of cash?
Tru?
Vanilla Custer flunked the urine test.
Or so you told me yesterday.
You pick winners for perfect strangers,
but not even your own bro?
Where is Melissa?
She's in her dorm.
That's the only entrance, right over there.
And, hey, good luck.
Hello?
I ran one of those aliases you gave me
through a credit bureau.
Harold Smith co- signed a loan
for, get this, Geoffrey Pine.
Pine? We finally got a last name.
I think Geoffrey creates
new identities to open new Iines of credit.
And probably get away from those people
he owed money to when things got bad.
He must be deeper in the hole
than he's ever been...
if he's committing suicide over this.
His wife has no idea.
She thinks he's in Hong Kong.
He's been living a lie.
You know what the crazy thing is?
He's not a bad guy.
With all of his schemes and everything,
he reminds me so much of Harrison.
Mirror images, duality, life and death.
That's a way a lot of religions
see the universe.
Davis, I got to go.
Hello.
I'm at the game.
And I'm just checking in.
Great. Don't lose track of Geoffrey
while you're staring at your cards.
No, come on, Tru.
I wiII not Iet you down. I swear.
Everything is under controI.
Tru?
Did you follow me here?
How could I follow you if I was here first?
Now that you mention it,
I think you should leave. Like now.
- All right, who the hell are you?
- Maybe I'm a friend of your wife's.
Not with that tell.
"Tell?"
It's a giveaway.
You looked away when you lied,
and you pushed your hair back.
No, seriously,
I think you should get out of here.
What is it with you?
Why are you obsessed with me leaving?
I just have a feeling that you
might have some bad luck here tonight.
Yeah, nice try at psyching out
your competition.
But I need this money, and I'm not moving.
Come on.
What does a young, pretty,
smart girl like yourself...
need with that kind of money?
Your wife doesn't know
about your secret life, does she?
Guess what, when they take your house
away, I'm sure she's gonna figure it out.
You don't understand.
My wife told me to straighten up my act
a long time ago.
She thinks I did.
I've been putting my theories
of probability to practical use.
I've been gambling, okay? A lot.
Got it.
Over the long run, I tend to win.
But over the short run, I....
Hmm?
I lost my tuition money.
You mean all of it?
Look, I can fix this, okay?
I can win. I just need one good streak.
That's why I'm here.
Consider me your good luck charm.
In a few days, the school
is gonna write a letter to my parents...
unless I head it off
by getting this money tonight.
Look, this is my last chance, Harrison.
I like you, but I'm gonna have to beat you.
Flush beats the pair.
How about a break?
Yeah.
No offense, but as a good luck charm,
you're not working hard enough.
Damn, she's a hell of a player.
She probably won last night, too.
That's why she was killed, for the money.
So, Geoffrey lost, offed himself,
and Melissa won and--
And was robbed and shot
in the alley outside.
If she leaves broke, it'll keep her alive.
But then she gets kicked out of school.
We have to think of this as an ER.
We have to save their lives.
You have to beat her, Harrison.
Not to shock you or anything,
but I'm trying.
- You have a tell.
- I do not!
You pull on your collar
whenever you're bluffing.
You playing?
Yeah.
Just remember who
the experienced poker player is, okay?
Straight beats two pair.
The ace.
Yeah!
Congratulations,
you were faking the tell.
Well, you know...
it was only the last one, so....
Um, this is, uh...
This is really awkward for me.
I got to warn you.
I'm in a serious relationship and--
Look, Harrison, the truth is
I really need this money.
Do you think that you would consider
loaning it to me?
I mean, I would pay you back
with interest and everything.
If you'd just give me a little bit of time....
I'm sorry. I can't do it.
Yeah.
Thanks.
This whole knowing the future thing....
- It can really suck.
- Yeah, sometimes.
That was just step one,
because step two is...
now you lose all that money to Geoffrey.
Why don't you just stick a bullet
right through my heart?
Start losing, Harry.
Hi, I'm looking for H. Clarke.
I'm Hope Clarke.
Are you the owner of the boat
registered out at the Harbor Marina?
Well, I'm not the sailor in the family.
My daughter, Haley, bought it.
Then can I talk to Haley?
May I ask you what this is about?
Two lousy pairs. I'm out.
Good luck charm says cash out.
Are you crazy?
A little friendly advice, pal.
Leave while you're ahead.
You got to be kidding me.
I'm on a streak
and there's still money on the table.
There's always
money on the table somewhere.
So, I guess I'm never gonna know
who the hell you are.
Guess not.
Well....
I think I'm gonna go surprise my wife
with an early return from Hong Kong.
Thank you.
I can't believe
I voluntarily lost all that money.
Welcome to my world.
Now, I've got to go to work.
What about you?
Melissa left here
thinking I'm some kind of jerk...
so might as well try to find her...
and make sure
she knows it wasn't personal.
Hey.
You did good.
You ain't so bad yourself.
He was great, Davis.
I mean, two people saved,
and he didn't just leave it at that.
He's gone to see Melissa
to try to make things right with her.
What's with Geoffrey Pine?
Just this feeling I have,
like there's unfinished business.
The truth is,
I may have saved his life this time...
but if he doesn't make some changes....
The man reminds me so much of Harrison,
I can't just....
HeIIo?
Can I speak to Geoffrey?
He's stiII in Hong Kong.
Can I take a message?
No message. Thanks. Bye.
Bye.
His wife says he's still in Hong Kong.
He left to go see her.
He should be home by now.
I better go make sure Geoffrey's okay.
Tru, it may be nothing.
- We talked about duality, mirror images?
- Yeah.
Murder and suicide on day one.
If that were a complete mirror image,
you know what would happen.
Hello? Melissa?
Mel? Hey, you in here?
Hey, Harrison.
I'm at the campus.
Melissa left a suicide note.
My God.
You need to get down here.
I can't.
I'd never make it there on time.
Geoff's still in danger.
He never went home.
You know where he is.
Where does any gambler go?
- He went back to the game.
- Just forget him, okay?
I know where she's got to be--
I have to reach Geoffrey.
He has no idea what he's walking into.
She's going to kill herself, Tru!
You are there. You can do this, Harry.
You can do this.
Melissa, I....
Look, I know why you're here and....
Melissa, I can help you.
Are you giving me the money after all?
Look, I would, but...
Um...
I don't have it anymore.
You lost it?
Hey, no, don't.
Hey, look.
Losing money
ain't the end of the world, right?
I mean, take it from me.
I can help you.
You can tell your parents.
No, I can't. I can't face them.
They work 16 hours a day
so that I can have a better life.
They gave up everything
for me and my sister.
How could I possibly tell them
I gambled away all my college money?
- They would never understand.
- There has to be another way out, okay?
No! It's hopeless. I would have to get
the money to school by tomorrow...
before they write a letter to my parents.
Hey, hold up.
Hey, look, uh...
my car.
My car. It ain't worth but $5, 000, but...
it's yours.
It's yours.
Huh?
Will that give you time?
You would do that for me?
Of course.
Come here. Come on.
Yeah.
What a night.
Looks like I don't need
my good luck charm after all.
I'm still on that hot streak.
That's tough luck, man. Maybe next time.
Hey!
Just stay calm
and hand me the money.
No!
You know, I don't know why
you keep looking out for me.
And I'm not sure I know how to thank you.
Well, if I was really looking out for you,
what do you think I'd say?
Tell my wife.
Harder than a high- stakes game.
Think you can handle it?
No. But it's time.
Hey. I got a pickup down in the van.
How do you get so banged up
on this job? The dead don't fight back.
You'd be surprised.
Hey, did you know that Davis was married?
His wife's dead.
Dead? He tell you this?
Davis? Volunteer personal information?
Are you kidding me?
I got an ear for gossip.
You got to come out with me.
I'm serious.
Don't know.
Get out of here.
Dude, live it up a little.
Hey.
Hi.
I rescued a pizza
on the way back.
After saving a damsel.
Yes, sir.
Is something wrong?
Yesterday, at your apartment,
there was a picture of a woman.
Maybe we should discuss that.
You know what, no,
it's none of my business, actually.
It is.
You know,
should I just go and--
No, stay, Harrison.
You deserve to hear this, too.
Okay.
We were married for a year.
You're married?
And I was supposed to meet Haley
at her mother's.
We were going to a restaurant
for our anniversary dinner.
I'd been working late here,
and I was going out to my car and...
the gas had all been drained from the tank,
the tires were flat.
There was this crazy woman there,
telling me I had to call my wife...
and prevent her from getting in her car
and getting on the freeway.
- Crazy woman?
- Our mother.
But I knew
the evening could be salvaged.
Haley knew if I was running late,
I could meet her at the restaurant.
Our mother didn't know where she was.
And you didn't call Haley.
To tell her that there was a lunatic
claiming she was gonna die that night?
I thought, yeah, that'd be a great way
to say happy anniversary.
What happened?
The autopsy said
that she had a seizure at the wheel...
and her car drifted over three lanes
before she was hit by a semi.
So on day one?
I died with her.
That's why you know so much.
That's why you understand.
Our mother saved you.
Davis, I'm so sorry.
It happened a long time ago.
And, you know, today is a celebration day.
Yeah.
Two lives saved.
Cheers.
So that's it?
No more shocking revelations?
No more secrets?
You officially know what I know.
Well, not everything, Davis.
- First name or last?
- Yes.
It's my middle. Actually, it's a funny story.
Hey, Jack? Hey, my man.
Why don't you come in here,
join the party? You work too hard.
Actually, it's a slow night.
I only had this pickup on campus.
What?
Harrison, let's just go sit down.
We'll figure out what happened.
She was all right when I left.
The suicide was a friend of his?
Everything was fine.
Hey, man, it's easy to misjudge
when someone's depressed.
Who knows
what's going through their head?
- Where are you going?
- What difference does it make?
Lindsay was right about me.
You were right. I'm not like you.
I can't save anybody.
Not even myself.
Look, don't go. Just stay with me.
We can talk.
I got to get out of here.
I know this is of little comfort to you now...
but I am very sorry for your loss.
Why?
Why'd she think she had to Iie?
It was only money.
We put too much pressure on her.
Honey,
you shouldn't be here, okay?
We'll go outside.
Could you be any more specific?
We got a phone call.
A man said that Melissa had lost
all her tuition money playing cards.
Somebody told them.
Somebody told Melissa's parents.
They must have called her
after Harrison left.
They wanted an explanation.
That's why she killed herself.
But that doesn't make any sense.
On day one, they didn't know.
What changed?
Who couId've done such a thing?