Daddy, I'm leaving.
But you won't even
let me finish.
Sweetheart, please don't go. Not like this.
Paige, I promise you,
there's nothing wrong with my baby girl.
I'm not a baby. And I'm not your girl.
Paige....
Don't touch me.
God, have you ever considered
that nothing happened?
That this is all just
a figment of your imagination?
I give myself more credit than that.
Because pretty soon,
the truth is gonna come out.
And when it does,
I can promise you one thing.
I'm not the only one
who's gonna have to deal with it.
You are, Daddy.
Paige!
Okay, hotshot. Bonus question.
You ready?
Hit me.
Riddle me this: The odontoid ligaments
serve to limit the extent to which?
The cranium's rotation can be carried...
which is why they're also known as
check ligaments.
- You gonna eat that?
- It's all yours, smarty- pants.
I am finished with
cramming for your MCATs.
Davis, come on.
We haven't even started
on the sympathetic nervous system.
You know the secret for acing the MCATs?
Quit cramming. Get some sleep.
Go home, Tru.
I'm just so excited.
If I ace the MCATs tomorrow,
I get into medical school.
I do that, I become a doctor.
And if I become a doctor,
I can finally say goodbye....
To working here?
Come on, I didn't mean it like that.
Don't worry.
I got a feeling it's not gonna happen.
You think I won't pass?
I nailed every question you asked.
Plus the ones you made up.
No, that's not what I meant.
I'm sure you'll ace them.
I just meant that...
sometimes I get the feeling that
some people don't belong here.
And some people do.
So which am I? I belong here or not?
What do you think?
Help me!
Hello?
Bitch Cakes. Hey, it's Lindsay.
I guessed.
So listen. I found a guy.
I'm shocked.
Not for me. For you.
His name's Jeremy.
I haven't met him, but he's your type.
If you've never met him,
how do you know he's my type?
Tru, it's my gift.
So stop asking questions...
and start looking for that
black Dolce & Gabbana dress...
I got you last Christmas.
Lindsay, we've been through this.
I'm not on the market,
and I'm taking my MCATs this afternoon.
Perfect. You'II meet him after.
And don't worry, I'll be there to chaperone,
so now you're all out of excuses.
Say you'II be there.
I'll be there.
Smart girI.
Good luck on your test.
Thanks.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but you look like crap.
Thanks, Harrison. Very sweet.
I told you I've been up studying all night,
because in 45 minutes...
I'm gonna take the biggest test of my life.
- Right. The Top Cats.
- MCATs.
I just want to know you're okay.
Outside the big test jitters,
I'm fine, thanks.
Is everything else copasetic?
Feeling good? Having fun?
Look, you know me.
I'm always looking out for you.
Because I know you'd do
the same thing for me.
- All right, what do you want?
- Nothing, man. What?
A guy can't worry about his own sister...
without being
accused of working an angle?
Jeez. I'm offended.
How could you actually say that to me?
It's about what I told you, isn't it?
About me....You know, what I can do.
Okay. A: I don't even believe you.
And B: Even if I did,
I would still need some cold, hard...
proof.
The racing form?
You want me to believe you, right?
WeII, here's a way.
I go to the track, I see who wins.
I call you up on the phone,
tell you the horses' names...
and tomorrow should you, you know,
do that voodoo you do so well....
- You make money.
- Yeah.
Harrison, I don't think that's how it works.
I'm not even sure it works at all.
But I've heard of weirder systems,
so I say, what the hell, give it a shot.
Are you down with this,
or do I have to go work for a living?
I'll see what I can do. But now I gotta go.
I love my sister.
Go. Go take your MCATs.
Kick much academic ass.
Thanks.
Time.
Time's up, people. Pencils down.
To my best friend, Tru,
who just aced her MCATs...
and who will make
a wonderful doctor someday.
- Cheers.
- I'm not done yet.
And who will always squeeze me in
on short notice...
and accept
whatever health insurance I carry.
- Of course.
- Okay. Cheers.
Is that him?
It's gotta be.
God, can I pick them, or can I pick them?
Hey, Jeremy?
Yes.
Hi.
Jeremy.
That's me.
But you can't be Tru,
you're too good to be true.
Yeah, my name does lend itself
to more obvious puns.
I spent all day thinking that up.
Do you mind?
I don't usually go on blind dates.
Who knows what you're gonna get?
So at first I was aII, Iike, wait,
she works in a morgue?
'Cause I mean, come on,
you're too hot to work in a morgue.
You ought to switch jobs.
You ought to be in, like,
videos or something.
- I have to go.
- Right. Night shift. Creepy.
So, I'll call you.
Wait, you forgot to give me your number.
- Luc. Hi.
- Hi.
- Have we met?
- Yeah.
In the we've- never- actually- met
kind of way.
I heard there might be a new guy.
That would be me. Luc.
Tru.
- Dress code?
- Blind date.
Bad one.
Well, is there any other kind?
My friend, Lindsay,
thinks it's her life's work to fix me up.
She worried you can't meet a nice guy?
Worried I can't meet a living one.
She shouldn't worry.
- I mean....
- Why? Know someone for me?
Give me some time.
Anyway, I gotta run.
My folks are in town,
but it's nice to meet you.
Yeah.
Tru.
Luc.
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
And I hold in my hands
the key to financial freedom.
A job application?
That's very funny.
But no.
What I have are the winning horses
from the last race at Del Mar.
Great.
It's a 40- to- 1 trifecta, Tru.
So write this down.
Today's lucky ponies are...
Cherry Top, Sky Marker, and Whirligig.
You know, I have no idea
why I can do what I do...
but I'm pretty sure
it's not so I can pick the ponies.
TeII me you got them.
I got them, okay, you happy?
No. But I will be tomorrow...
if my big sister's
as lucky as she claims to be.
I gotta go. I love you.
Tru?
I didn't hear you come in.
Hi.
I meant to tell you,
you got a call from County Records today.
Something about
an autopsy report you requested.
Yeah, my mother's.
Stupid.
- Is there a problem?
- I'm sorry.
Had I known,
I would've authorized delivery.
- But since I didn't know, I just didn't--
- It's okay. I'll get them tomorrow.
No, not likely.
The clerk went on vacation tonight
for a couple of weeks.
With aII the red tape downtown...
you'll probably have to wait
till he gets back.
It's okay. I've waited ten years.
Another few weeks won't kill me, right?
Still, I can't help but wonder...
if those are the answers
you're really looking for.
Why, what are you--
We got a cold one.
The name's Paige Sanders.
Medical student at Hudson.
Well, until 4:31 today.
Hudson? That's the top medical school
in the state.
Didn't do her any good.
How'd she die?
Here's a guess.
Knowing the high- pressure world
of most med students...
I would posit this one worked hard.
But apparently played
a wee bit harder.
Overdose? God, that makes no sense.
Hudson gets their pick of the best
and the brightest. She had it aII.
What can I tell you?
Some students
can hack the pressure.
And some can't.
Yeah, but why would she--
Never met a newbie as curious as you.
Relax. You can't help her now.
Come on, Davis,
what more can you tell me?
It looks like we have
a little petechial imaging in the eye.
UsuaIIy associated
with some sort of trauma.
Could be a side effect of the drug intake.
Coughing, vomiting,
internal pressure of some kind.
Wow. Someone's gonna do well
on their MCATs.
That's good.
Just to be sure, we should prepare
the body for a toxicology report.
I want to know exactly what chemicals
were in the student's body when she died.
Hey, wait up, Davis.
You have no idea how lucky you were.
Save me.
Hello?
Bitch Cakes. Hey, it's Lindsay.
Too tired to taIk? Okay, fine.
'Cause I found a guy. His name's Jeremy.
And he's totally your type.
Good morning.
You ever have, like,
one of the greatest days of your life?
I mean, a really truly great day...
and then just feel like
the whole thing got erased?
You're assuming
I've ever had a great day?
What are you doing?
I'm just checking for something.
Hey, did we get any
medical students last night?
The only medical student here is you
in a couple of hours.
- Aren't you taking the MCATs today?
- I did.
I will. I just have to do one thing first.
You have quite the life, don't you?
Unfortunately, yeah.
And, Davis,
if County Records just happens to call...
go ahead and authorize the delivery.
I want those files.
My God, Luc, I'm sorry.
Here, let me help you.
No, thanks. Really. I got it.
Tell me it's fixable.
Well, I would.
But then I'd probably be lying.
How did you know my name?
What?
You called me Luc just now,
but we've never met before.
I'm a lucky guesser.
Yeah, well...
nice running into you.
Tell me this day gets better.
Check again. My records have to be here.
Are you sure you're using
that thing right?
Hello?
Tru? Where are you?
Oh, God. Harrison, breakfast.
Why did you blow me off?
I've been waiting half an hour.
It's not my fault.
I'm having one of those mornings.
So, you're telling me what?
We already had this conversation?
Do you have the racing form
in front of you?
It proves nothing.
Except that if you're having
one of your so- called lucky days...
you should be telling me
today's winning horses.
I don't remember.
What?
They were horse things.
How am I supposed to remember them?
You know, you talk a good game,
but I knew you couldn't do it, Tru.
I knew it. See you.
It's Hansen. Jessica Hansen.
The transfer should've come in hours ago
from Harvard Medical.
I'll be sure to let you know
the moment they come in.
You do that.
Hi.
Just a thought,
but when her files come in...
you should bounce them back
to Harvard just for laughs.
Don't give me any ideas.
What can I do for you?
My friend, Paige Sanders, is a student.
I want to surprise her.
Do you know where I can find her now?
- I'm not allowed to say.
- I get that.
Too bad, though.
She just got a residency
at the Mayo Clinic...
and I'd love to see the look
on Harvard's face...
when she learns my friend got in
and she didn't.
Goddard Building, Theater C.
- But you didn't hear it from me.
- Didn't hear what from you?
Mr. Taggert, would you tell
your fellow surgeons in training...
what exactly you're doing
to this poor dead man's heart?
Like you taught, sir...
I'm just making a cut
between the inferior vena cava....
And the what? Anyone?
Eustachian valve.
Good.
Taking particular care not to sever....
Miss Sanders?
Name's Paige Sanders.
Save me.
Miss Sanders?
The....
Anterior margin.
The answer I'm looking for
is the anterior margin.
Right. No, and I knew that. I just--
We all knew the answer, Miss Sanders.
The question is time. Time matters.
To us, time is the difference
between Iife and death.
Time has value, Miss Sanders.
And please do not waste our time.
For those of us
who may actuaIIy become doctors...
our minds are the most valuable tools
we possess.
And we must keep them sharp
at all times.
Thank you. See you next week.
Take your notes.
"The mind's the most valuable tool."
He should know.
He's the biggest tool on campus.
He acts like he's Zeus or something.
I hate that.
Well, the least he can do is realize
that he's not a god.
I am.
Hey, Sanders.
Nice work in there. Very impressive.
Give me a break, both of you guys, okay?
I'm not in the mood.
Relax, Sanders, it's us.
Excuse me?
Hi. You guys are second- years, right?
Yeah, that's right. Who's asking?
The name's Hansen. Jessica Hansen.
I just got in from Harvard today.
Jessica Hansen.
- Yeah, I saw you inside.
- You were observing us.
Yeah, what can I say?
I'm just naturally curious.
Good for you. Welcome to Hudson.
But as you've observed,
we are second- years...
which means we're busy.
Hey, is it true what they say
about you guys?
Don't know.
What is it exactly they say about us?
- That you're good.
- They'd be right about that.
What else do they say?
That you throw the best parties,
well- connected...
got some heavy- hitting careers
lined up for yourselves.
But that's not the whole story, is it?
Look, I'm cool with it, you guys.
I came here to hook up
with some color- outside- the- lines types.
Maybe we are. Maybe we aren't.
My question would be, what's it to you?
Like I said, I'm just trying
to make some new friends.
By the way, that professor
had no right to talk to you that way.
The name's Paige,
and I can take care of myself.
I believe it.
Listen, I just got out of
one Alpha Boys' Club.
I'm new in town.
Come on, heIp a sister out.
Just welcome me to campus.
I'll buy you a meal.
- I can't. We....
- We're busy.
- Doing what?
- Nothing that concerns you.
But go ahead, enjoy your meal.
We're not doing anything without you.
Okay.
I can't remember the last time I sat down
and ate a solid meal.
I thought you might need a break.
You got that whole"overachiever"
thing going for you.
Yeah, right. I'm doing everything I can
just to keep up.
You seem to push yourself pretty hard.
Yeah, but I mean, who doesn't?
You, me. I mean,
it's the whole med school thing, right?
You pass your MCATs...
always busting your ass
trying to max out your potential.
It must be nice.
I just, you know, have to stop
and appreciate it sometimes.
Not everyone's so lucky. We got in.
So let me ask you.
Is everyone here
as uptight as your friends?
Those guys, you know, they're all right.
You know what
the competition can do to you.
Sure. But that doesn't mean...
we have to hurt ourselves
just to keep up with them.
What are you talking about?
Sorry.
Hello? Now?
Yeah. No, I'll be right there. All right.
Listen, thanks for lunch,
but I gotta run.
Paige. I know.
You know what?
About the drugs.
I don't know if you do it to keep up,
or to wind down--
Drugs? What are you talking about?
What kind of freak are you?
- Okay, now I'm confused.
- Don't touch me.
Don't come near me.
I don't know what your psycho agenda is,
but screw you.
Stay away from me.
Finally.
Yeah, we are up and running.
Congratulations, Doctor. We did it.
He's dead.
Looking good. Keep him steady.
Time?
Eight seconds.
Death looks good on you, Steve.
Twelve seconds. We're getting close.
All right, 20 seconds.
Time to do your thing.
Clear.
No change.
Now, that was a trip.
Did it work for you, Steven?
I've got a better question.
What the hell is she doing here?
I could ask you the same thing.
I'll bet your answer's a lot more
interesting than mine.
- Guess again.
- I'm guessing what I just saw...
could get you all kicked out of med school
by lunchtime.
Or we could talk.
So let me get this straight.
You got this little hobby.
- You kill yourselves?
- For starters.
And then you resuscitate.
That's the plan.
But what's the point?
The point, Jessica, is that
when you come back, you're not the same.
You know the urban myth about
how the moment you die...
your whole life flashes before your eyes?
It's true.
Memories. You're unlocking
repressed memories.
And what are they, anyway, memories?
Just chemicals locked in the brain...
between your occipital fissure
and the temporal lobe.
And the best part is, they're just
lying there, waiting to be tapped into.
You guys are good.
Too bad your little experiment kills you.
Almost kills you.
I saw my father's face the day he left me.
I was two- and- a- half when it happened,
and now it's as clear as....
Let's just say hi- def video can kiss my ass,
'cause I have clarity.
Crystal clear memory of that day,
and so much more.
I'm next.
No. Paige, you can't.
You want to dig into your past, I get it.
But there's gotta be a better way.
You can deaI with this.
All you have to do is go to the source.
Find out whoever it is
you have unresolved issues with--
And what,
have a good long talk with them?
See their point of view? Reach closure?
You think I haven't already tried that?
You think this isn't my last resort?
Fine, if you know so much,
you go talk to my father.
Because nothing is gonna stop me.
Hi. I need just one more thing.
Mr. Sanders?
Right block. Wrong house.
Mike Sanders lives right there.
Thanks.
My pleasure.
- Who'd you say you were?
- A friend of Paige's.
We go to school together.
Mr. Sanders, I'm really worried about her.
I think Paige is gonna hurt herself.
No. My daughter would never do
anything like that.
I wish you were right,
but I don't think you are.
And you're the only one who can stop her.
Why am I the only one?
You're her father.
You have a history with Paige that--
Look, whatever she told you
about me isn't true.
Touch my own daughter?
It's sickening just thinking about it.
And the craziest part is,
Paige doesn't remember anything.
Just some nonsense about
the moon and the stars.
The moon and the stars,
what's that mean?
You're her friend. You tell me.
Tru Davies?
Is Tru Davies here?
I thought
you were taking your test.
I am. I'm just going a little late.
I have to find someone first.
I'm gIad I caught you.
Look, I need you to concentrate.
And the names of the horses are....
Harrison, I told you,
I can't remember them.
Look, I'm really sorry, but--
Hey, Hansen?
I gotta go.
Tru!
Were you just talking to my father?
What's wrong with you?
First you force your way into my life,
and then my group, and now my home?
How SingIe White FemaIe are you?
I know I'm butting in,
but just give me one minute to explain.
Okay, one minute.
I was 12 when my mom died.
You were just a kid.
I watched it happen, right in front of me.
I have questions about
my mother's murder...
that I may never be able to answer.
As much as I'd like to know the truth,
it's not worth dying over.
- Yeah, but why do you think I would die?
- Because I've done the research.
The heart can't withstand it,
and if the heart does, the brain can't.
Sure, some people get lucky
and come out okay.
But not everyone. Not you.
Look, do yourself a favor. Call it off.
It's suicide.
I mean, it's not like I've never had doubts.
I mean, I just....
I have these feelings about my past...
and I don't know what else to do.
Talk to your father again.
Or a therapist. Anyone.
Just don't go through
with the experiment.
Fine, I'll call it off.
I don't know why I trust you, but I do.
- I'll tell the guys.
- That's great.
You have no idea how relieved I am.
Harvard, how's it going?
Hey, Dan. I'm glad you're here...
because I wanted to talk to you
about something.
Sure, great, love to hear it.
There's just someone I met
at the sign- ups for Molecular Bio.
I really think that you should meet her.
Hi. Jessica Hansen.
Is this the one you toId me about?
And will the real Jessica Hansen
please stand up?
I don't understand.
Paige, I can explain.
Allow me.
I'm Jessica Hansen.
I transferred from Harvard yesterday...
and this woman here
is trying some lame- ass identity scam.
Which, sorry, honey, it won't work.
And now that's over with.
How about you tell us
who the hell you really are?
Paige, I--
Don't.
Because as far as I'm concerned,
everything you've told me is a lie.
I bet you're not even
a real medical student, are you?
Paige, just wait.
Two hours and counting.
- Steven? Steven, wait up.
- What do you want from me?
- You've got to talk her out of it.
- No way.
It's going to kill her.
No, it won't.
Look at me. I've never been better.
Look, we all have questions
we need answered.
But Paige is gonna make
the biggest mistake of her life...
in just a few hours,
unless you talk her out of it.
A little late for that.
Why?
She's doing it right now.
Okay, ready to come back.
Come on.
I can't get her back. She's not responding.
Got dobutamine?
No.
Dopamine?
No, none of that, either.
She's been under too long.
She should've been out by now.
It's amazing, isn't it?
How thin the line between life and death
can be?
The nearIy instant recovery time.
That's why I designed this
the way that I did.
That's great, Dan.
What wouId you have done
if I couIdn't revive her?
Hey, are you okay?
You saved my life.
You feel like telling us who you really are?
Sure. I just gotta do one thing first.
You've over three hours late.
Better get started then?
Thank you.
Thanks.
It looks like we have
a little petechial imaging in the eye...
usually associated with
some sort of trauma.
My God.
She didn't die from the experiment.
- I'll be right back.
- No.
Once you leave, you're done.
You understand?
You, your test, your future.
I'm sorry, I have to go,
but I can reschedule, right?
Sure.
Just be back here bright and early
first thing next year.
Guess I'll see you next year.
She unlocked a memory, didn't she?
Yeah. But it's none of your business.
Besides, Paige is fine,
and you're not even a medical student.
Well, pretty soon you won't be either
unless you tell me where she is.
You want to play chicken?
Because you're right.
I'm not a med student.
I have nothing to lose, but you do.
Especially with those track marks
on your arm.
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
All she remembered is a man.
He hurt her, touched her.
She wasn't that specific.
And then some crap about
the moon and the stars.
I don't know what it means.
I do.
Paige!
- Where is she?
- I told you, she's not here.
- I really have to find her.
- All right, I've warned you once.
I don't know who you are,
or what you think you're doing...
but this is harassment.
She's in trouble.
You don't understand.
Paige did something tonight.
What'd she do?
A really stupid and dangerous experiment,
but now she remembers everything.
And you think this would
bring her back to me?
Her car's parked out front.
You said something about
the moon and the stars.
That has to mean something.
Go. Just get out of here.
That doesn't make sense.
- Hello?
- Did someone forget her blind date?
No, I didn't forget.
I just couldn't make it this time.
This time?
There was a time
when you could make it?
I'm sorry.
Okay, look, I'll cover.
You're the best.
Bye.
Jeremy, hi.
I'm so sorry. I don't think my friend's
gonna be able to make it tonight.
You're not Tru? Of course not.
You're too good to be true.
Oh, my God, did you just make that up
right now?
That's hilarious.
The moon and the stars. It's the neighbor.
You don't know what you're saying.
For the first time in years,
I know exactly what I am saying.
Paige. You've always been a smart girl.
Be smart now.
I was a child, you son of a bitch. I was 9.
All right, this is ridiculous.
I'm calling your father.
Good. Call my father.
Call the police. Call the District Attorney.
I'm pressing charges.
You are gonna pay for what you did to me.
Just hush.
Don't touch me.
Just be quiet.
Quiet, please!
Don't touch me!
I said, quiet!
Get off me!
Be quiet!
No one's gonna believe you anyway.
I'll believe her.
Get out!
There's a statute of limitations, you know.
It's been years.
Go ahead, go tell the whole world!
Who's gonna believe you?
Oh, God! I'm so sorry, Daddy.
So, how are you feeling?
I thought remembering would be the end.
But it isn't.
It's just the first step.
A lot to be said for a good first step.
So who are you, anyway?
And please don't say Jessica Hansen.
I had to take on her name
so I could talk to you.
I mean, if I told you I was really
just some med school wannabe...
who works in a morgue,
would you have listened?
Probably not. So why'd you help me?
I'm still trying
to figure that out for myself.
I guess you could say it's sort of my job.
Well, if you ever figure it out,
you know where to find me.
I'd like that.
Med school gets a little cold sometimes.
I'll take your word for it.
Good luck.
Hey, Tru?
You'll make one hell of a doctor someday.
Someday, yeah.
So, how'd the MCA Ts go?
They didn't. How did my date go?
Not bad.
Until he used the same line
on the waitress that he used on me.
HonestIy, you didn't miss much.
I had a feeling.
But still, Tru, I'm telling you,
the perfect guy is out there somewhere.
You just haven't met him yet.
That, or I've met him too many times.
ExactIy.
Wait, how's that work?
See you, Linds.
- Hello, again.
- Hi.
I'm gonna try and get past you here
without any hard contact.
Don't want to break anything.
I was thinking
about our little accident earlier.
Maybe it wasn't such a bad thing.
Because otherwise,
we never would've met.
And I'm glad we did.
Yeah. Me, too.
At least this time, you won't forget me.
I don't think I could ever forget you.
Anyway, I gotta go.
- To be continued?
- Absolutely.
Say hi to your folks.
Like I said, lucky guesser.
Hello?
Tru.
Harrison, please.
For the last time, I can't remember--
No. Listen.
I didn't go to the track today after all.
And you know what? I had a great day.
Really?
Yeah, I had some fun.
I read a book.
I can't remember the last time I did that.
And, you know, plus other stuff.
The point is,
I had a hell of a day.
And I didn't need a boost
from my big sister to do it this time.
I'm not surprised. You've just gotta
believe in yourself a little.
Kind of like you?
Just like me. Good night, Harrison.
I knew you didn't need this.
Hey, you were right.
County Records called.
It's your mom's file.
Whenever you're ready.
Thanks, Davis.
You gonna open them?
Later.
I was kind of hoping to live
in the present for a little bit.
Sorry about the MCATs.
I guess that means you'll be
sticking around here a little bit longer.
Maybe that's not such a bad thing.
It's funny, I met a girl today.
AII she reaIIy wanted to do
was understand...
why she feels the things she does.
Maybe that's all any of us want.
Just to understand.
And you don't?
Not lately, no.
It's not easy, is it?
Carrying the burden you do.
Excuse me?
Some would call it a blessing.
Others a curse.
I see it more as a calling.
Davis?
I know more than you think I know, Tru...
about what you can do.
About how you help the dead
get another chance at life.
Have a seat, Tru.
It's time I told you what I know.