[Fast-paced instrumental music]
ELlSE: Hurry.
ELlSE: Tru, come on.
TRU: What's wrong, Mommy?
[Elise panting]
ELlSE: Come on, sweetie.
TRU: ls everything okay?
ELlSE: Shh!
Stay quiet now, Tru.
[Tense instrumental music]
MAN: Are you alone?
Yes.
MAN: Where's your daughter?
ELlSE: She's not here.
MAN: Good.
[Gunshot]
[Gasping]
TRU: l see Mom's face.
And then l hear it.
A man's voice and....
lt's 'cause Daddy's coming to town.
-The dream has nothing to do with Dad.
-Right.
Besides, Meredith says
he's only in town for a conference...
so the odds are
we won't even hear from him.
TRU: But there's something else.
HARRlSON: And that is?
[Slow instrumental music]
What l do...
going back, trying to save
these people from dying...
l think Mom could do it, too.
HARRlSON: Where did you get this?
TRU: Davis.
He was an assistant
the night they brought Mom in.
How does this freak-fest from a morgue...
become such an expert on our mother?
He talked to people, did research.
Besides, the question isn't how he knows,
but if he's right.
TRU: And if he is...
what am l going to find out next?
[Theme music]
Help me.
[Stomping]
DAVlS: There's this new technology
everybody's talking about.
lt's called a bed.
TRU: Sorry.
l haven't been sleeping very well lately.
Your shift's over. Why don't you go home
and get some real rest?
How ''over''?
l'm meeting Harrison and Meredith
at the diner in three minutes.
Rumor has it our father's in town.
This is Meredith's way of dealing.
DAVlS: Your father?
TRU: Yeah.
Just because none of us
has seen him in five years...
doesn't mean he still can't make us crazy.
So, you want to talk
about our father, right?
Actually, l was going to see
who wants to split the French toast.
WAlTRESS: Here you go.
TRU: Expecting someone?
Right. About that.
Well, you asked if l had anything
to say about Dad...
and so l brought someone...
who l thought could say it better.
His wife.
Jordan.
Well, it ain't breakfast, it's an ambush.
Don't blame Mere. This was my idea.
Anyway, l'm sure you all remember
this weekend is your father's birthday.
And since he's in town for a conference...
l convinced him
to let me throw him a party.
-Yeah.
-Here in his hometown.
And l thought
what could be more special for Richard...
than to spend his birthday with his kids?
-From which marriage?
-Harry, she's trying. Why can't you?
JORDAN: lt's just a small get-together.
TRU: l work nights.
Well, they let you out to eat, don't they?
[Rock music playing]
Just come tonight.
lsn't showing up the least you can do?
Funny, l thought the same thing
about my dad my last 10 birthdays.
JORDAN: Tru, l'm sorry, that's not--
TRU: For what?
For breaking up my parents' marriage,
or pretending it never happened?
You know, l just remembered
l got to be somewhere.
MEREDlTH: Tru.
You wouldn't believe it, but we get some
pretty questionable job applicants.
But you, on the other hand...
good school, six years of EMT experience.
This is pretty good.
-Some would say that you're overqualified.
-Some might say l'm late paying my rent.
Yeah.
Look, the reason l'm here is because
they say this is a decent place to work...
reasonable on-call hours, steady turnover.
[Slow, rhythmic instrumental music]
Well, you have done your homework.
l do have some other candidates
coming in...
-but l'll show you around the place.
-Great.
So, this is the sign-in room.
The hub of most of the activity.
DAVlS: Not today, obviously, but....
JACK: Right.
Do you guys use LFD
as your primary filing system?
DAVlS: Yeah.
Slow week.
Probably a good thing in our business.
You mind if l take something to drink
before l hit the road?
-No, not at all. lt's right there.
-Thanks.
DAVlS: Perfect timing.
Odd and compIeteIy off scheduIe,
but perfect.
l forgot these
when l took off this morning.
This is Mr. Harper.
He will be interviewing to replace Gardez.
Hey. Jack.
Hey. Tru.
You had to write it down?
Just so the functional illiterate
wouldn't drink my soda.
Right.
[Soda can pops open]
JACK: Can't be too careful...
what with the big soda shortage
l've been reading so much about.
And here l was thinking you didn't read.
Okay, you know what? l'll probably
make my decision by this afternoon.
JACK: Great.
Well, you know where to find me.
Excuse me.
Thanks.
DAVlS: That guy's going places.
TRU: Yeah.
Let's just hope
somewhere far, far away from here.
Are you all right?
Fine. l just don't get why
you'd want to hire someone like that.
l know you have a lot on your mind,
but are you sure...
that it's Jack that's bothering you?
[Slow instrumental music]
[Knocking on door]
Hey, Claire.
lt's Tru.
-l know who you are.
-lt's been a while, l wasn't sure.
Anyway, l'm looking for Jordan,
your mom.
She's not here.
Do you want to talk to my daddy?
TRU: No, that's okay.
CLAlRE: Dad.
RlCHARD: Yeah?
[Slow instrumental music continues]
Tru.
Hi, Dad.
lt's good to....
l was sure you'd be at your conference.
l was actually just looking for Jordan.
Claire, do me a favor.
Go keep an eye on your brother, will you?
Come in. Or are you in a hurry?
Jordan's actually running errands.
But she'll be at the party tonight.
Can it wait until then?
TRU: l don't know if l'll be able to make it.
You know, work.
Right.
Jordan told me
about your breakfast this morning.
And it will mean a lot to her
that you came here to apologize.
TRU: Apologize? No.
l might have been a little out of line.
l was upset.
With Jordan or with me?
l should go.
RlCHARD: Come tonight, okay?
TRU: lf l can.
Look at you.
You are so much like your mother.
lt was your mother.
What you can do, she could do, too.
Jordan, it's me again.
l don't know if you're still out...
or if you even have your cell phone
with you. Should l worry?
Call me.
Thanks.
[Jazzy instrumental music playing]
-Thought l'd make an appearance.
-l'm glad you did.
l can only stay for a minute.
Where's Jordan?
l'd still like to have that conversation.
Running late, as usual. She was supposed
to meet me here after her errands.
RlCHARD: Typical Jordan.
l'm sure she's just out
getting you a last-minute gift.
Yeah.
Come on.
[Exclaims]
RlCHARD: Look who's here.
LlNDSAY: Come on.
Harrison.
Hi.
l want to introduce you
to my lovely girl, Lindsay.
-Hi, Mr. Davies.
-You're Tru's friend from school, right?
Yep.
l don't think Harrison has ever formally
introduced me to anybody he's seeing.
lt wasn't really necessary before.
[Lindsay laughs nervously]
-Lindsay, let's go get drinks.
-Yeah. lt was good to see you again.
Seems like a nice girl, Lindsay.
-And here it comes.
-Don't get defensive.
l look at you,
and you've got so many options.
Why limit yourself?
Usually you save the advice
for the occasional Christmas card.
Don't waste
all your good material tonight.
What l'm trying to say, if you'll
let me finish, is that you're doing fine.
Just don't let this thing
with Lindsay confine you.
You're young. Keep your eyes open...
for what might otherwise pass you by.
[Slow, rhythmic instrumental music]
Well, just so you know...
it's kind of a now thing. lt's no big deal.
[Groans]
Good to know where we stand.
DAVlS: Hello.
TRU: Hi.
DAVlS: How was the party?
TRU: A bust.
The only reason l went was to apologize
to Jordan, who never showed up.
Listen, about your mother.
-l just wanted to say that--
-lt's okay.
l think l've had enough
big conversations for one day.
So how about the new guy?
When does he start, Mr. Mooch?
DAVlS: He doesn't.
l checked his references and....
He didn't check out?
DAVlS: No. lt turns out that Mr. Harper
has a nasty habit...
of not showing up for work. Permanently.
DAVlS: Until l called, his last three
employers had no idea where he was.
TRU: You're kidding.
DAVlS: So it looks like it's just you and me.
TRU: Who brought this one in?
DAVlS: Copland from County.
DAVlS: He's helping me
until l find a replacement.
DAVlS: Must've dropped it off
when l was on break.
DAVlS: lt looks like a mugging.
lt's multiple stab wounds.
Oh, God.
Jordan.
[Dramatic instrumental music]
[Somber instrumental music]
TRU: Dad, l'm....
l know.
You probably don't remember this,
but when your mother....
This is where we....
We could have her moved somewhere else
if it would make it easier.
lt's my fault.
RlCHARD: l shouldn't have let her go.
TRU: There's nothing you could've done.
Mugged.
God, if l could just have it
to do over again.
You should talk to them.
l will.
You know, there are pieces l remember
from the night Mom died.
Things I wish I didn't.
And they don't have to be here.
We're ready for you.
l'll keep an eye on the little ones.
lt's all right. l'll do this.
You can wait out here.
Let Daddy handle it.
[Somber instrumental music continues]
All right.
RlCHARD: Now what?
TRU: l'll take it from here.
-You sure you can....
-lt's my job.
Yours is to be with your children.
They're going to need their father.
What are you doing? Go home.
l'll cover this. l'm serious.
No one's giving out extra credit
for the bravest girl in the room.
Go on. Go home.
You cannot save everyone. Go.
Victim suffered multiple stab wounds
to the upper torso.
FEMALE VOlCE: Tru.
TRU: What?
l didn't say anything to you.
Sex.: FemaIe.
FEMALE VOlCE: Tru.
[Tense instrumental music]
[Dramatic instrumental music]
Stop him.
My God, Davis, l'm so sorry.
DAVlS: The coffee's just really hot.
This is the third time this week
you've crashed out during your shift.
DAVlS: Why don't you--
TRU: Can't.
l've told you about my father's wife,
Jordan, right?
She's in town and sometime today,
she's going to be murdered.
-One of those days again.
-And about the Jack guy...
check his references before the interview
so you don't get your hopes up.
Okay. Where are you going now?
Believe it or not, l'm going to
spend the day with my stepmother.
Tru?
Jordan, hi. This is unexpected.
She wanted to see us
to talk about some things and--
That's funny,
because l was just telling someone...
how l thought it was time
you and l got to know each other better.
MERE: You were?
JORDAN: l would like that, Tru.
Which makes what l came to ask you
much easier.
Your father's birthday is this weekend
and l'm throwing a party for him.
TRU: l'll be there.
You said she'd probably walk out on me.
l'm thrilled, Tru. Thank you.
Excuse me, l'm going to wash up.
Okay, what's going on? Those are the first
polite words you've ever said to her.
l guess we're all full of surprises today.
HARRlSON: Hey, kids. What's cracking?
Jordan came by and told us she's throwing
a party for Dad tonight, and Tru--
-Told her off?
-Actually, Tru said she'd be there.
[Rock music playing]
She was killed? Come on, get out of here.
Why else do you think l'd hang out
with her? l don't have a choice.
She was killed, she asked for my help,
the day rewound...
and l'm stuck with her for the entire day.
We're going to go pick up Dad's cake.
l guess we'll see you guys later?
Mind if l come along?
You know, help with the party planning?
Of course. That'd be nice.
What do you know?
Could you excuse us for just one sec?
You can't tell me something like that
and just run off to some bakery.
-Do you need me to do something?
-l don't think so, not yet.
But when Dad asks you
about Lindsay tonight...
tell him how you really feel,
not what he wants to hear.
You'll be glad you did. Okay?
[Cell phone rings]
My office. l'll be right back.
So, Jordan, where to after this?
Back to the hotel
or you may be meeting someone else?
lt depends on how much time l have.
What kind of cake do you think
he's going to want this year?
Honestly, you've got the wrong girl...
if you're looking for intimate knowledge
of Richard Davies.
Then we have something in common.
What do you mean by that?
Tru, l love your father.
[Soft instrumental music]
And l might even understand him.
But that doesn't necessarily mean
that l know him.
l think that he only ever let
one person in completely...
and that was your mother.
So the rest of us,
we just take what we can get.
CLERK: Can l help you?
JORDAN: We'll take the big chocolate one.
CLERK: Sure thing.
DAVlS: l see the bulk of your work
experience has been as an EMT.
DAVlS: Why the sudden desire
to change teams?
The truth is, l think l'd accomplished
everything l wanted to in that line of work.
l contacted all your previous employers...
and they all said the same thing,
that you were good at the job...
but one day you didn't show up.
Just disappeared.
DAVlS: ls there anything you want to say
about that?
A couple of years ago...
l died.
Excuse me?
l was at a scene working on a kid
about nine years old.
He had a gunshot to the back.
We'd just gotten a pulse...
and l guess someone didn't want the kid
to make it.
He started firing.
l caught the bullets instead.
l remember...
it felt like a bee sting
on the back of my neck, right here.
Three minutes and 28 seconds.
That's how long my heart stopped.
And then, l came back.
And what was that like?
You know, they say an experience
like that changes you.
lt should make you want to live every day
to the fullest.
But for me, it just....
[Melancholic instrumental music]
l lost it.
l knew something had to give.
lt just didn't feel right....
lt just didn't feel right
entrusting lives to my unsteady hands.
l thought a change of location would help.
lt didn't.
l'm hoping a change of vocation will.
Some would say once you survive
something like that...
that you were brought back for a reason.
l guess we'll see.
l love cutting through the park.
lf it stays like this,
it may be nice living here.
Are you sure
you don't want to just take a cab?
l know you have a lot to do today.
No, we're just going a few blocks.
[Lightly suspenseful instrumental music]
l just want to let you know l really
appreciate you giving me a chance today.
You know,
your father and l don't fight very often...
but when we do, it's usually about
his relationship with the three of you.
Really?
For what it's worth,
l think his distance comes from guilt.
About how he dealt with what happened.
But he's different now.
JORDAN: He wants to make things right.
He's changed.
[Suspenseful instrumental music]
JORDAN: He's a different man, Tru.
TRU: Jordan, go!
[Man grunts]
[Fast-paced instrumental music]
[Gasping]
[Dramatic instrumental music]
Now we know why we left the city.
They can talk all they want
about the shrinking crime rate.
You know, l think l'm going to lie down
a bit, before the party.
Close my eyes.
Hey.
JORDAN: Thank you.
Who knows what couId've happened
if you hadn't been there?
-l'm just glad you're okay.
-Thanks.
[Sentimental instrumental music]
RlCHARD: Boy, never a dull moment.
RlCHARD: lf not the little ones, it's Jordan.
-Luckily, she's fine.
-Luckily, you were with her.
She's sweet, Dad.
l probably should've noticed that sooner.
TRU: l'd probably better get going--
lt's nice that you stopped blaming her.
Blame her? For what?
Me and your mother.
Look, Dad, l'm glad that l could
help Jordan, but now is not the time.
No, it's not the time.
lt's long overdue. Sit down.
When l met Jordan, yes,
your mother and l were still married.
l'm pretty clear on that part.
But we had already decided
to get a divorce.
What?
Why didn't l know this before?
Because you didn't want to.
RlCHARD: l loved your mother, Tru,
but the fact is...
we grew apart.
She became distant, unreliable.
She'd run off at a moment's notice...
at very odd hours, flimsy excuses.
lt was like she was living some....
Secret life.
The truth is, when l met Jordan,
l'd been alone for years.
[Sentimental instrumental music
continues]
But l've said enough.
Too much, probably.
RlCHARD: Today is not a day
for living in the past.
I'II see you tonight, won't I?
lt would mean the world to Jordan
if you would make an appearance.
And it would to me, as well.
[Jazzy instrumental music playing]
-Hey, you made it.
-l did.
-Hi, you look beautiful.
-So do you.
Please, l stopped looking beautiful
two children ago.
So, this is Tru. Richard's daughter.
The one l told you about.
Jordan's been singing your praises
all night.
So, if you'll excuse us,
l have a lot of people l want you to meet.
Come here.
Harrison.
Dad.
l want to introduce you
to my girl, Lindsay.
-Mr. Davies.
-Aren't you Tru's friend from school?
LlNDSAY: Yeah.
There's Tru. lt was nice to see you again.
She seems like a nice girl.
She is.
One of the nicest ones l've met
in a long time.
That's good to hear.
But at your age, Harrison--
Yeah, at my age, you met Mom.
Now you wouldn't consider that a mistake,
would you?
No, absolutely not.
Think about it.
You have three wonderful kids.
lf you haven't noticed.
Yeah, l see your point.
[Slow, rhythmic instrumental music]
God, you are so unexpected sometimes.
[Lindsay chuckling]
[Glasses clinking]
[Suspenseful instrumental music]
TRU: Dad?
RlCHARD: What?
-He's here.
-Who? What are you talking about?
The man from the park
who attacked Jordan. He's here.
Or at least he was.
He's here now?
That means it wasn't random.
He's looking for her.
l'm going to call the police.
Don't let Jordan out of your sight.
[Suspenseful instrumental music
intensifies]
TRU: Excuse me.
You...
what do you want with her?
The daughter's always the last to know.
MAN: Where's your daughter?
[Gunshot]
lt was you. You killed my mother.
What do you want from us?
HARRlSON: What's up?
Dad said something was going down
with Jordan.
-He was here.
-The man who mugged Jordan is here?
-The man who killed Mom.
-What?
lt's the same person.
Go find Jordan, make sure she's okay.
Harrison, go. Hurry up!
[Harrison grunts]
[Fast-paced instrumental music]
RlCHARD: You've gone way too far
this time.
RlCHARD: l told you the last time,
this is over. You understand?
RlCHARD: l never want to see you again.
[Fast-paced instrumental music continues]
[Dramatic instrumental music]
Tru!
RlCHARD: Wait.
-Will you give me a chance to explain?
-You knew him.
This is not what you think.
You don't want to know
what l think right now.
Yeah, l know him. He's an ex-con,
and his name is Carl Neesan.
-And you know that because?
-l was the one who convicted him.
l was an ADA 15 years ago.
He was a kid up on a murder rap.
He said he was innocent,
which they all do.
The evidence was flimsy, but l was out
to impress, so l went after him.
And was he guilty?
The jury said he was.
That was good enough for me.
At the sentencing, he swore revenge...
and he said if he ever got out,
he would make me pay.
Why today?
Why today, of all days, does he show up?
You think this is the first time?
This has been going on for years.
He shows up, he demands money.
He threatens retribution, so l pay him...
and he goes away. Until the next time.
And today?
RlCHARD: Today l told him it had to stop.
l wasn't going to pay.
l never thought that he would
follow through with his threat.
God, l never wanted to get you involved
in this. Not you, not Jordan.
And what about Mom?
What does your mother
have to do with this?
He killed her.
-He killed Mom.
-Why would you say that?
l was there.
[Somber instrumental music]
-No, sweetheart--
-l heard his voice.
l will never forget that voice.
He killed Mom because he was angry
with you. He wanted revenge.
Tru, no.
Don't tell me no, l saw him.
l was there, l saw him pull the trigger.
That's not what happened.
-How can you tell? He said he--
-lt's not!
[Suspenseful instrumental music]
You don't think his was the first name
l thought of?
RlCHARD: The police investigated this
thoroughly, and said this was not the man.
Airtight alibi.
''Not your man, Mr. Davies.''
But l heard his voice.
But did you see his face?
No.
[Melancholic instrumental music]
We live with the question long enough,
we want an answer.
So our mind plays tricks on us
and makes us think we've got one.
But we don't.
-Come on, it's cold. Let's go inside.
-No, l can't. l've got to go to work.
-Tonight?
-They're expecting me. l should go.
[Melancholic instrumental music continues]
Happy birthday, Daddy.
Don't you think
you've been through enough?
Why don't you go home
and get some sleep?
Sleep. That's a novel concept.
lf Neesan didn't kill my mother,
then is it true?
What?
That her death had something to do
with her calling.
Despite what you might think...
l don't have all the answers.
But l'll promise you this,
l'll help you find them.
Thanks, Davis.
But for now, l'm going to take you up
on your first offer.
l'm going to go home, draw a bath,
and try and get some sleep.
l guess you didn't hire Jack after all.
Actually, l did.
l decided to go with my gut.
-That's weird.
-What's that?
Well, yesterday he took my soda.
This one with my name on it.
And today, it's still here.
You know how many ways
you can alter fate.
Yesterday you met him, today you didn't.
lt's impossible to predict
how that might alter things.
Yeah, l guess.
Just give him a chance.
l think you'll be happy that you did.
He's next door.
TRU: lt'll get easier.
JACK: What's that?
This. Doing what we do.
TRU: All these people.
Taken before their time.
Sometimes it just doesn't seem fair.
Never really thought about it.
That's one way to deal, l guess.
But if you ever want to talk,
sometimes it helps.
You know what l think is unfair?
When tubes and machines
keep people alive.
When life is prolonged
beyond its usefulness.
That's what's unfair.
-Yeah, l guess.
-l'll be honest with you. For my money...
l think that death
was one of the fairest things...
that ever happened
to some of these people.
You said you hadn't thought about it.
You caught me.
Anyway, l just wanted to say welcome.
l'm Tru.
-Like the name on the soda can.
-Yeah, that's right.
Jack.
[Slow instrumental music]
And, um...
And thanks for making me feel
so welcome.
lt's never easy being the new guy.
[Dramatic instrumental music]
[Fast-paced instrumental music]
[Crashing]
lt feels familiar, doesn't it?
[Neesan screams]
[Fast-paced instrumental music continues]
[Tense instrumental music]
[Tense instrumental music intensifies]
[Tru gasping]
-You okay?
-Yeah.
-Don't move. Stay here.
-Dad, no, he'll kill you. He killed Mom.
l don't care what the cops say,
l swear it's him.
l believe you.
And that's why this has to end.
TRU: No, Dad.
RlCHARD: Lock the door, wait here for me.
[Fast-paced instrumental music]
[Both grunting]
You're growing a conscience
in your old age, Richard?
-Who the hell do you think you are?
-The man you paid to kill your first wife.
-At least, if l remember correctly.
-We had a deal. l pay you, you go away.
You didn't honor it, so now it ends.
Now, l mentioned the letter, right?
The letter detailing everything
that's sent to your daughter...
if l meet an untimely death?
[Tense instrumental music]
[Footsteps running]
Tru, go!
Go!
Now!
[Fast-paced instrumental music]
[Gunshot]
[Tense instrumental music]
When we meet next,
there won't be any warning shot...
there won't be any chase down an alley.
lt's just going to be
a bullet through your heart.
Goodbye, Carl.
Did you.... ls he....
[Shushing]
RlCHARD: lt's over, sweetheart.
lt's over.
RlCHARD: Daddy's taken care of it.
[Ominous instrumental music]
[Rock music]