Daddy, the first time that you saw Mommy
Did you know that she was the one?
I sure did
I saw your mother cross a crowded room
and the second I looked into her eyes...
everything else just fell away.
That was it.
Bang, I was gone.
Wow.
Where were you?
Fat Bobby's Sports Bar
and Grill.
That's where all
the magic started.
You guys met at a place
called Fat Bobby's?
Mmm, well, we were in college.
ARIEL:
Still...
Hey, you want to hear
something funny
Daddy and I almost met
three years earlier.
Really?
JOE:
Yeah, that's right.
I was a junior in college
and I had a project on display
at the Mesa University
Science and Engineering Fair.
Won third place.
Yeah, we didn't put it
together till years later,
but I was also at
that science fair.
And you guys didn't
see each other?
I guess not.
I like to think
I would've remembered.
Well, that's a
much better story
than meeting at a place
called Fat Bobby's.
Too bad it didn't
happen that way.
Yeah, then I could be older now.
I could be 11.
Hey, Ariel, where's your sister?
What are you talking about?
She's right here?
Joe, did you see her
go to her bedroom?
Who?
Our daughter, Joe.
She's right over there.
Ariel, what's going on?
Where are your sisters?
What are you talking about, Mom?
What sisters?
Okay, this isn't funny.
Will you talk to your
children about...
Oh, my God.
What's happening?
WOMAN:
Hey, lazy bones.
Wake up! Are you planning
on getting up
and dressed at any point today?
Mom?
I just had the strangest dream.
www.1000fr.com Present
Capture:FRM@Donale
Sync:FRM@Linda
Allison.He's out catting around.
He'll be back.
You have exactly two minutes
to find something to eat
for breakfast.
I'm not hungry.
What if he gets
hit by a car?
What if he gets lost?
I'll buy you a puppy.
You ready?
Mm-hmm.
When I get married,
I'm staying married.
I'm never getting a divorce.
Ally, cut your
mom some slack.
It's not like the
divorce was her idea.
I know. When I get married,
it's going to be forever.
Married?
How 'bout we get someone to ask
us to the junior prom first?
Which reminds me.
The Mesa University
Science and Engineering Fair
is this weekend.
You want to go?
That's so weird.
Why, because it's
a science fair?
Girls are allowed to want
to go to science fairs.
And I'll let you in
on a little secret.
You know what they have
a lot of at science fairs?
Boys.
No. I mean that
you're asking me.
I had a dream about this.
About the science fair?
About us going, but...
it wasn't really about that.
I was married and I was
telling my kids about it.
Kids?
Three. All girls.
And I was telling them
about how I almost
met their dad
at this science fair.
There's a dad? A husband?
Ally, you are such a tramp.
No.
He was really kind
of cute for an old guy.
He had really great hair.
Well, that's nice.
Look, I hate to
burst your bubble,
but scientifically speaking...
Dreams are just random firing
of neurons in your brain.
They don't mean anything.
They certainly can't
predict the future.
What are you trying to say?
I'm trying to say, I don't
think you're actually
going to meet
Mr. Fabulous Hair
at the science fair
this weekend.
Still want to go? Say yes.
Yes.
Later, 'gator.
While, 'dile.
JOE:
Milk.
Pink or brown?
Both. Okay.
Fruit wraps...
(carts crashing)
I'm so sorry. I...
That's okay. No harm, no...
Ally?
Allison Rolen?
Is that you?
I can't believe it!
Hey.
Stephen!
Hey! When did you
get into town?
I heard you were
living in New York.
I was. I... New York,
Fort Lauderdale,
Lititz, Pennsylvania.
You move around a lot
in my line of work.
You know, I don't even know
what it is you do.
Have I even seen you
since high school?
Are you married?
Do you have kids?
No wife. No kids. No dogs.
(chuckles)
Did I mention I move around
a lot in my line of work?
Marketing. Telecommunications.
Cellular phones.
You must do very well.
Everyone I know has one.
Hi. How're you doing?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Stephen Campbell,
this is Joe Dubois,
Hi.
my husband. Engineer.
Hello.
Wife. Three kids.
High school.
Next-door neighbor.
Comic book freak.
You still?
Still.
Oh, hey, let me
give you my number.
Let's get together and
have lunch or something.
That sounds great.
And, uh... how's Izzy?
You're still close?
No, we sort of
lost touch.
She went to Harvard
and I went to Mesa.
So I'll call you?
Yeah, you better.
Good to meet you.
Yes. So long.
Hmm, so what are we talking?
Friend? Boyfriend?
Unrequited love?
Hmm...
All of the above?
Crush. I think.
Him on me. Junior year
of high school.
Aah.
He was pretty shy back then.
Oh, that was not a shy hug
that he gave you.
Well, I guess he's not
as shy as he used to be.
Hello?
An hour.
Yeah, sure.
Okay, bye.
Why do I get the feeling
that I'm gonna be unpacking
all these groceries
by myself? Huh? Huh?
Looks like she was raped
and then strangled to death.
And here's the weird part.
After she was dead,
we think the killer
took the time to redress her
and wash her face
and wrap her up
before he dumped her.
Tow truck driver
working in the area
saw a white sedan
stopped on the shoulder
sometime after midnight.
Afraid that's about
the closest thing
we have to a real clue.
Her name's Nancy Claymore.
Her parents reported her
missing two days ago.
Oh, my God. How old is she?
She just turned 13.
YOUNG ALLISON:
Have you ever seen
a dead person?
Oh, my God. You found
a funny cigarette
in your mom's purse
again, didn't you?
I had another dream last night.
Like the last one.
Set in the future?
I explained
this to you.
I just... it felt so real.
I mean, it was so specific.
No, it wasn't.
It just seemed that way.
You were in it.
I mean...
we had lost touch.
We weren't friends anymore.
Well, see, that's
what I mean.
That's never gonna happen.
I was, like, a cop
or something.
Oh, future cop. Cool.
There was this girl.
Nancy Claymore.
She was 13 and she
had been murdered.
Allison.
Come on.
Future cop?
Future dream?
You really think
any of this is gonna happen?
I don't know.
When I dream it...
it all seems so plausible.
You know?
There's nothing about it
that couldn't happen.
Although...
Actually, in the dream...
I did run in this guy.
His name was Stephen,
and I think he was supposed
to be an old friend.
From high school.
I don't know no
stinkin' Stephen.
And I don't know
no stinkin' Stephen.
Ah, praise the Lord.
Hallelujah!
The girl was blind,
now can see!
Looks like you're
getting a new neighbor.
YOUNG ALLISON:
Hi.
What's going on?
Somebody new moving in?
Uh... just me and my dad.
I'm, uh, I'm Stephen.
Stephen Campbell
...and we've got
the mountains.
And the deserts,
obviously.
A lot of seniors,
after they get their license,
will, like, rent a dune buggy
and just spend the day up there
getting trashed.
Well, what, uh...
what about comic book stores?
You guys have,
you guys have comic book stores?
In Chicago,
they're...
they're all over the place.
You read comic books?
Uh... I collect
graphic novels, yes.
What? Come on,
have you ever seen one?
I mean, come on,
you have, you have,
you have Watchmen,
you have Secret Wars,
you have The Dark Knight.
(laughing)
You got to know... you got
to know The Dark Knight.
Come on.
No, the guy, this guy... ah...
the guy who does them,
Frank Miller,
he's just-- he's this,
he's this genius.
IZZY:
Genius?
Like Isaac Newton?
Like Galileo?
I'm talking about
a living genius.
Okay, I'm talking about someone
who makes a difference
in my life,
not some guy who just had
an apple fall on his head
like a million years ago.
Oh, don't mind her.
If you say he's a genius,
I'm sure he's a genius.
(whispers):
Thank you.
But, you know, you don't have
to take my word for it.
Saturday, there's a, uh,
comic book convention
at the Civic Center.
This Saturday,
that's the science fair.
At the college?
I mean, that was the plan.
You know, why don't you just...
why don't you just think
about that?
Yeah, we will.
What goes in here?
Oh, um...
that is my...
dad's collection.
Collection of what?
No, it's okay.
It's, it's...
it's not loaded.
ALLISON:
Pablo.
Here, kitty.
(dog barks in distance)
DIANE: Did that cat
run off again?
He'll be back.
Were you at the Campbells again?
Izzy and I were just hanging out
with Stephen.
He's nice.
You're not over there
drinking or anything?
No, Mom, nothing.
I don't even think they
have liquor in their house.
I think Mr. Campbell
is kind of... strict.
Well, what about
Mrs. Campbell?
They moved in a week ago.
I still haven't caught
a glimpse of her.
Oh, there is no
Mrs. Campbell.
I mean, I think
they're divorced.
Really?
So he's raising
that boy all alone.
Mom.
I don't think
it's a good idea
for you to get involved
with Mr. Campbell.
Who said anything
about getting involved?
There's nothing wrong
with baking them
a batch of cookies,
is there?
To say "Welcome
to the neighborhood."
I'm going to sleep.
DEVALOS:
I appreciate everyone
coming together this afternoon.
I know that since we've formed
this Nancy Claymore Task Force,
we've all been taking a lot
of criticism in the press,
and while there
haven't been any major
breakthroughs in the case,
there is some new information
we wanted to share.
Lee?
Um, the police psychiatrist
is saying
this is probably the first time
the perpetrator killed.
According to him, the
murder scene and the methodology
are riddled with wt they call
"indicators of remorse."
Taking the time
to re-dress the victim,
wash her, wrap her
in a blanket.
They feel all of these
things are indications
that the killer felt
badly about what he did.
Not badly enough, unfortunately,
to pick up the phone
and turn himself in.
DEVALOS:
The doctors feel
that while he's never killed,
he'll probably have
a long record of inappropriate
conduct with minor girls.
That's why we've supplied each
of you with a complete file
of all the registered
sex offenders
here in the Phoenix metro area.
Study the sheets.
Feel free to conduct
any interviews
if you feel there is cause.
And what a wonderful
coincidence.
Here come the latest sheets.
Add these to
your binders.
These would be for
anyone who's relocated
to our jurisdiction in
the last four weeks,
and as ordered by the courts,
have registered their
whereabouts with the police.
Oh, my God.
You know this man?
I knew him... in high school.
Suddenly last week,
there he was in the supermarket.
Says here he raped a
14-year-old girl
back in Pennsylvania.
You've got
some interesting friends.
STEPHEN:
Hey, Allison.
Wake up.
Allison.
(dog barking)
I've got a surprise for you.
What are you doing here?
It's the middl
of the night.
Yeah, I couldn't sleep,
and I saw this little guy
sneaking through my backyard,
so I chased him down.
I know how worried you get
when he's out all night.
thanks for bringing him home.
Yeah, no problem.
you should, um...
you should
probably get going.
Yeah, I don't want my dad
to figure out I'm gone.
But I'll, I'll
see you tomorrow?
Yeah.
What's the matter,
Future Cop?
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
Don't make fun.
I had another dream.
Oh, boy.
Just give me
your opinion.
What if I saw something,
dreamt something
about a person?
Something horrible, something
that they were going to do
in the future.
Even if I couldn't prove it,
shouldn't I tell somebody?
Shouldn't I try
and stop it?
Um, in my opinion, no.
No?
No, people will
think you're nuts.
I'm your best friend,
and I think you're nuts.
But I'm talking
about something--
it's so awful,
it's so evil...
Hey.
You want to know what
I really believe?
You don't like the
way the future looks?
Change it.
It hasn't happened yet;
it's subject to alteration.
You believe someone's going
to do something awful.
Then don't let them.
For that matter,
if you believe we're going
to stop being friends,
don't allow it.
The next time someone wants
to do something with you,
and you already
have plans with me,
don't tell them that
you'll think about it.
That's my future.
I've got to go.
Well, Izzy...
I got class.
Hey. So, uh,
what have you decided?
About Saturday,
the, uh, comic show?
Yeah, I know.
I, I just... I can't.
Wh-why?
Because I can't.
I mean, I don't
want to.
I'm going to the Science
Fair with Izzy.
I told her I would,
and she's my best friend
and she's counting on it.
All right.
Okay, well, then maybe
we can, uh,
maybe we can do something
Sunday.
I don't think so.
I mean, I'm
kinda feeling that
maybe it would just
be better if...
I don't know.
Well, why?
What, what...
have I done something wrong?
No, it's just... it's me.
I'm going through something.
Trying to figure something out.
Maybe, maybe I can help.
I don't think so.
Not right now.
You sure I haven't, I haven't
done anything...
to make you, make you mad at me?
No, you didn't do anything.
I'm not mad at you.
Yeah.
Right, I mean, how,
how could you be?
All I did was bring back
your cat, right?
I really do appreciate that.
Yeah, sure you do.
Really, I'm sorry. It's...
really, it's me.
Yeah, sure it is.
SCANLON:
It's right this way,
Mr. Campbell.
This should only take
a few moments.
Whatever you say.
I'm just, I'm completely baffled
as to why...
Stephen, it's nice
to see you again.
Allison.
I didn't get
a chance to tell you
I work for the District
Attorney's office.
I asked the detective
to contact you.
I was hoping you
could help us with
the Nancy Claymore case.
I'm sorry. Who?
SCANLON:
A 13-year-old girl.
She was kidnapped
and murdered last week.
We're conducting
preliminary interviews
with several persons
of interest
based on their histories
of sexual assault on minors.
Stephen, please, have a seat.
SCANLON:
Two years ago you
pleaded no contest
to a charge of sexual battery
on a 14-year-old girl.
Yes. I made an error
in judgment.
You want to tell us about that?
She told me she was 20,
and I believed her.
According to her deposition,
she asked you several
times to stop.
It looks like
the charges were
reduced from rape
to battery to avoid a trial.
Because they couldn't prove
their case,
because there was no case.
It was all lies.
When her parents found out
about us, they got angry at her,
so she lied to them
about what happened.
She lied to them
the way she lied to me,
and now because of her lies,
I'm considered a predator
in the eyes of the law.
So what do you want to know,
Detective?
Allison,
how can I convince you
of my innocence?
SCANLON:
You can tell me
where you were on the
afternoon of the 15th.
I... I was at home.
Can anyone else
confirm that?
No, I don't think so.
What color car do you drive?
White.
Would you be willing
to provide us
with a sample of your DNA,
or are you gonna make me, uh,
fetch it from Pennsylvania?
Uh, I have nothing to hide.
Okay.
You'll understand, right,
when I don't call you about
getting together for lunch?
Pablo,
is that you?
Here, kitty.
Here, boy.
I know you're upset.
Sometimes
in nature these things happen.
A bigger animal
comes along and...
Mom,
I don't think
an animal killed Pablo.
I think...
I think maybe
the Campbell boy did it.
Oh, I know you're upset.
Allison...
He was mad at me.
He likes me, and...
and I've kind of
been avoiding him.
So you think he killed your cat?
Allison.
And that's not the only thing.
I've been having dreams again.
You know this is crazy talk,
and you know it upsets me,
and it has nothing to do
with the cat being torn apart
by a dog or a coyote...
Mom, I'm trying to tell you.
I've had dreams about him
in the future,
doing horrible things to girls.
Girls younger than me.
Well, I-I... I got
to tell you something.
That says a lot more about you
than it does him.
Why would you dream
about anyone doing anything
to young girls?
Well, you know who
I blame for this?
Mom, we're not talking
about Grandma now.
For filling your head full
of this nonsense about dreams,
about the future.
It was bad enough
I had to endure it
growing up when I
was under her roof.
But now?
Mom...
You grandmother does not know
the future.
She does not have visions
or dreams.
She's crazy.
Mom, what are you doing?
I need you to listen.
You're upset.
Please.
I just want you to take one
of these pills
and get some sleep.
Mom, I need you
to listen to me!
No. I won't listen.
Not when you're
talking crazy.
I don't want to listen
to anything about dreams,
about special feelings, about
predictions.
Are you gonna take one
of these or not?
IZZY:
Hey.
I'm so sorry about Pablo.
Your mom told me.
It's really awful.
Anyway, I want you to know,
I totally understand
if you don't want
to come with me today.
What are you
talking about?
To the science fair.
Oh.
Right.
I mean, I...
I know you're upset.
I know you're depressed, so...
relax.
We don't have to go.
We can just stay here.
Besides, we don't
want to risk
running into
your future husband accidentally
and messing up everything
that's supposed
to happen in the future,
and completely screwing up
the balance of nature,
and changing the course
of human development
on the planet Earth.
Actually...
I think I
want to go.
IZZY:
Okay.
I'm totally confused.
Now we're looking
for Mr. Goodhair?
Yeah.
Don't you see?
He's part of the future
I've been dreaming.
In my dreams, I don't
meet him until college,
unless right
now, right here,
I make it a point
to meet him.
(camera shutter clicking)
I change
the future.
And then maybe,
just... just maybe,
all the bad things
I've been dreaming
about won't happen.
Allison?
You are in dire need
of psychological help,
or, I don't know, a...
conk on the noggin
with a big hammer or something.
You're not gonna meet
this Joe guy today.
He's not in here.
He's in there.
He doesn't exist.
Well, we'll just
see, won't we?
(laughing):
Oh!
Come here for a second.
How would you
pronounce that name?
Joseph Duboys?
Yoseph Dew-bwa?
I think
this is it.
I think this is his.
Looks like the future's safe.
Did you see that?
What are you guys
looking at?
Hey.
You know, I've been looking
for you two everywhere.
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
Um, it was kind of a...
a spur-of-the-moment thing.
You know, I knew
this was where
you really wanted to be,
so I thought,
if Allison wants to go
to the science fair,
then, you know, the hell
with the comic book convention.
That's so sweet.
So, you guys want
to grab some lunch after?
I'm, uh...
I'm buying.
No. I just... I really
want to go home after.
Oh.
I guess, um,
you didn't hear.
Pablo was killed last night.
In her yard.
Like, a dog
or something.
Oh, that's terrible.
That's terrible.
Allison, I am so sorry.
This is really awful. Allison...
IZZY:
Allison,
what are you doing?
It's okay.
She's just...
She's-She's upset.
You stay away from me.
I know all about you.
I know who you are.
IZZY:
Allison,
what's wrong with you?
Nothing.
She's upset.
That's all. She just doesn't
know what she's talking about.
I have to go.
I have to go home.
I need to be by
myself for a while.
SCANLON:
Do you know why you're here?
Because
there's been a screw-up
somewhere.
Because somebody,
someplace has made a mistake.
SCANLON:
Well, should
that turn out
to be the case,
then you're absolutely
within your rights
to file a complaint
th the proper authorities.
But I suspect
you'll be a little busy
finding yourself
a good defense attorney.
What's this?
Who are these people?
ALLISON:
These are
the faces
of the seven
young girls
that you raped but
chose not to kill.
The seven that
we know about.
we can prove.
You believe this?
You believe
that I raped all these girls?
I believe in
science, Stephen,
and the science
says you did it.
SCANLON:
Not only were we able
to make a DNA match,
but no matter what part
of the country
these abductions
and rapes occurred in,
it coincided with your arrival
and departure from that region.
ALLISON:
It's just a
matter of time.
We're faxing
your photograph
to the local police
in each jurisdiction.
These girls will
identify you.
They will testify.
But that's the least
of your problems,
because we're charging you
with the murder
of Nancy Claymore.
I see.
And...
what is it you want from me?
A confession
would be nice.
It would save
us the effort
and the expense
involved in a trial.
I am authorized
to offer you
life without the
possibility of parole.
My goodness.
Your mom must be awfully
proud of you.
I'm trying to help you
avoid the death penalty.
Again?
Do you remember...
the day your Mom had you bring
some cookies over to my house?
Of course you don't.
It wasn't a particularly
important day for you.
All you did was walk over
to the new neighbors' house
and knock on the front door.
Okay...
But, see,
what you didn't know
was that right before you
knocked on that door...
I had a gun in my mouth.
And I was determined
to kill myself.
I remember it so clearly.
Across the street..
the McElroys were getting ready
for their family reunion.
And down the block,
some guy was washing his car
and he had his car radio
blasting "Sister Christian."
My dad had just kicked
the crap out of me for
leaving a jar of jelly
out on the counter overnight.
So I sat down
on the couch.
I put one of his precious
antique revolvers in my mouth,
and then...
there was a knock on the door.
And who did I find standing
on my doorstep...
but the girl next door...
Allison Rolen.
My secret crush.
And wonder of wonders
we talked,
and...
started thinking that maybe
she likes me.
And maybe life is worth
living after all.
I need a confession, Stephen.
Are you prepared to do that?
Do I call a stenographer?
Or do I call my boss and tell
him that we are having a trial?
You hear that knock?
Isn't she something?
She's going to save
my life again.
Hey. What's going on?
What did he do to you?
I don't know... he just...
one minute we were
just talking, and then...
he tried to kiss me...
and then he was...
on top of me and...
I said, "No," and then...
he got really angry.
Izzy, did he hurt you?
No.
No. We heard
his dad come home.
And then he let go of me,
and I just ran out the back
door and I came over here.
(dog barking)
I just...
I can't let my mom
see me like this.
Can I come in?
Please? Can I just...?
Of course, you can.
Sure. Come on.
(sobbing):
Allie...
I don't know what
would have happened
if his dad hadn't come hom
I really don't.
Yeah, well... I do.
I know.
Can I throw these
out somewhere?
I don't want to
take a chance on
my mom seeing them.
Yeah, sure.
I really think we
need to tell someone.
Tell them what?
Tell 'em... that he scared me?
That he's a jerk?
Last night, you
said that...
Yeah. Well...
Last night I was upset.
Today I see that I'm fine
and that nothing
really happened.
Not really.
But Izzy...
what if you knew he was
going to do it again?
But worse.
What if you knew other girls
were going to get hurt?
Is this dream talk again?
Listen to me.
I don't know anything about
the future, Allison,
and neither do you.
This is about me.
This is about something that
really happened to me.
And that means I get to decide
what to do about it.
I'm sorry.
Promise me.
Promise me you won't tell anyone
about this.
Allison, promise me.
And promise me
we'll never talk
about this again.
Izzy...
Promise me!
I promise.
Okay.
Well, I guess I better go.
Izzy?
This is it, isn't it?
We're not gonna be friends
after this, are we?
Why are you saying that?
Isn't there enough bad already?
Why do you say that?
I don't know.
It's just a feeling I have.
Oh, good, you're here.
Uh, Stacey called in sick--
lazy, hung-over tramp--
so I have to cover her shift.
And, uh, can you bring
these cookies over
to the Campbells' house
along with that note
inviting Mr. Campbell
over for dinner next week?
Mom, the last place
in the world I want to go
is the Campbell house.
Why, did you and
Stephen have a fight?
No.
What's the problem, then?
I can't talk about it,
but I'm not going over there.
I'm asking you, please.
No.
I don't ask
for much from you.
Tips are lousy, your dad's
child-support payment is late,
and the car needs new
brake pads
I can't pay for.
So do this one
thing for me,
okay, without
giving me any attitude.
Okay.
I talked to the police.
He shot himself.
I'm so sorry, honey,
but he's dead.
I'm-I'm... I'm sorry.
I know you cared
about him.
I did.
I really did.
I know.
Would you like me to give you
something...
help you sleep?
Actually, I'm...
I'm kinda scared to dream.
That's silly.
The thing a person needs most
at a time like this is sleep.
And the thing a person
needs to do the most is forget.
Bye!
Bye, Mom!
Oh, I forgot. I'm supposed
to stay after school
and work
with my new lab partner,
so can you pick me up at 4:30?
Well, this is a heck of a time
to mention it, Ariel.
I have the meeting
this afternoon.
I know. I'm sorry.
Um... wait.
Nancy!
Do you think your mom
could drop me at home
after we're done working?
Sure, I guess
that'd be okay.
Mom, this is Nancy Claymore.
She just started here this week.
Hi, Mrs. Dubois.
So her mom's
gonna drop me
at home later, okay?
Well, sure, that's okay.
Nancy, you look so familiar.
Have we met before?
Um, I don't think so.
Must be my imagination.
Welcome to www.1000fr.com