???
??
????
???
??
????
???
Sleep in the living room.
Come here.
What are you doing?
What if I'm contagious?
Shh...
WOMAN:
Oh, baby!
Let me have it.
Let me have all of it.
Oh, baby, let me have it!
Let me have all of it!
Oh, baby, let me have it.
Let me have all of it.
Oh, you okay?
I don't know.
What were you dreaming?
Huh? I wasn't
dreaming anything.
I was sleeping.
It w nice.
Sorry.
www.1000fr.com present
Hey, Allison,
we both overslept.
Oh, you're kidding!
BOY:
Help!
Please!
Somebody, anybody!
JOE:
Allison?
(gasps)
You okay?
I'm fine. I'm just trying
to take a shower.
Well, you got
to turn on the
water first.
???
Capture:Donale
sync:FRM@¹Ûº£ÎÀ
Allison, you
doing anything?
Are you familiar with State
Assemblyman Henry Rykoff?
I know he's a
state assemblyman.
I know his first name
is Henry.
Died in his sleep
last night.
Apparently, his widow
is fiercely protective
of her late husband's legacy.
Okay.
After she discovered
the assemblyman had passed,
she called EMS.
I don't know what's
going on over there,
but Emergency Medical
called the police
and everyone's been there
since before 7:00
this morning.
It's past 10:00.
What do you think's
going on?
I have no idea.
But whatever it is,
the governor asked me
to get over there
and make it go away.
What am I doing?
Oh, I don't know.
The assemblyman died.
Isn't that your area?
Mrs. Rykoff,
I'm District Attorney
Manuel Devalos.
This is Allison Dubois.
She's a bereavement
counselor who works
with my office.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
The governor asked us
to come by
and see if we could
be of any help
during what he knows must be
a very difficult time for you.
Help? Absolutely,
we could use some help.
Those idiots with the ambulance
called the police,
and the police won't let me
call a funeral home.
My husband is lying dead
in his bed.
He's been there for hours.
I would like to get him
where he belongs,
so we can move on with
the business of his funeral.
I understand.
Mr. District Attorney,
my name is Casey Frank.
I was the assemblyman's chief
of staff, also a family friend.
This is Scott Brittenham,
the family attorney.
Apparently, the maid
discovered the body
and immediately dialed 911
before Mrs. Rykoff here had
a chance to make contact
with the funeral home.
I think you'll see
it's all a big
misunderstanding.
All anyone wants really, is to protect
the assemblyman's dignity.
Of course.
Let us see what we
can find out, please.
Excuse us.
MAN:
Look at his neck.
What do you mean?
All the ambulance
guys wanted to do
was lift him up and
get him out of here.
I don't get a bonus for saying
something smells fishy.
Just go upstairs,
look at his neck.
This man did not die
in his sleep.
I've taken a look at your
late husband, Mrs. Rykoff.
We have a problem.
No, there is no problem.
My husband served
the state for 32 years.
He's entitled to privacy
with regard to his life
and dignity with regard
to his death.
Buhe did not die
in his sleep.
We're not even convinced
he died in that bed.
Is my client being accused of something here,
Mr. District Attorney?
Not yet.
My husband and I
were married for 37 years.
In 37 years, a couple
can grow very close
and very distant
at the same time.
Henry got up in the middle
of the night.
It wasn't unusual.
He liked to use the bathroom
down the hall.
I heard him get up,
make his
way down the hall in the dark.
I even heard him cough
and wheeze through the wall.
He had that cold
that's been going around.
I must have fallen back asleep,
and when I woke up again,
I realized that Henry
still hadn't returned.
Finally,
I came down here.
He had taken the belt
of his robe...
used that beam,
put it around his neck.
I kept screaming his name...
but I think he was already dead.
Mrs. Rykoff, I will do
everything in my power
to be sure that when a death
certificate is issued...
He did not commit suicide.
Nothing could have been further
from his mind.
And you know this how?
I know this
because Mrs. Rykoff called me
to help her get the body
down from the ceiling.
I know this
because when I came in the room,
his computer was on.
There was a pornographic
Web site on the screen.
His pajama bottoms
were around his ankles
and was clear from the state
of the rest of his body
exactly what he was doing,
exactly what his intention was.
And it had nothing to do
with killing oneself.
And you helped Mrs. Rykoff
move the body?
Yes.
Up the stairs
and down the hall
and into the bedroom.
I beg of you all,
let my husband be remembered
for his great work
and not for some foolishness
no one was ever meant
to know about.
BOY:
Help me!
Do you hear that?
Somebody!
What are you doing?
Put your head
on the pillow,
close your eyes and let's get some sleep.
You didn't hear that either?
Shh.
BOY:
Help me! Please!
Help me!
Please! Somebody!
Look Like he was
in some kind of a hole
or maybe it was a cave
or some kind of a well, or...
Whatever it was, it looked
like it was natural,
not man-made.
That's great, but, Allison,
there are no missing children
of that approximate age
who match anything close
to that description.
What do you mean?
I mean, you may
have dreamt it,
but it doesn't appear
to have happened--
not yet, not
around here anyway.
Well, maybe his parents
haven't reported it yet.
Maybe they don't realize
he's missing.
You said he was dirty,
you said he looked like
he'd been wherever
he was for a while.
I mean, come on,
if your child was missing
for long enough to be beat up
by the elements like that
you'd notice, you'd report it.
What are you saying?
I'm saying there's nothing
more I can do.
I can't mount a search until
I have someone to search for.
And honestly, I've got
about ten other fires
I got to put out
this morning, including...
one that you might
be interested in.
What's this?
The coroner's report
on Assemblyman Rykoff.
What am I looking at?
"High levels
of dexohyphrodan..."
Dexohydrophan.
"were present
in the deceased's system."
What's that?
It's a libido inhibitor.
It's like anti-Viagra.
Kills the sex drive.
I don't get it.
Neither do I.
Dexohydrophan is a drug
usually reserved
for chronic sex offenders.
You're saying Assemblyman Rykoff
was a sex offender?
Of course not.
But I got a better question.
Why's a guy who's loaded to
the gills on libido-inhibitors
hanging from a belt with his
John Thomas in his hand,
looking at Internet porn?
Girls down?
All except Ariel,
who just asked me
what "clubbing" is.
And when will she be
old enough to do it.
I feel like
I looked at a million files,
stared at a billion pictures.
All of those kids.
I just know he's out there,
scared and alone.
If one of our girls...
Shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh.
They're fine.
They're in bed.
All except
for Ariel.
She wants to know
what "clubbing" is.
I see you.
I see you up there.
Hey, where are you going?
No, please, you can't leave me.
No! Please don't leave me!
Allison, hey, what
are you doing?
I saw it, the place
where the boy is.
It's this hole, this glowing
hole in the ground.
I've got to call Scanlon.
Hold on a second.
You're not making
any sense.
What...
what do you know today
that you didn't know yesterday?
A hole?
You're going to wake the man up
in the middle of the night
to tell him about
a hole in the ground that glows.
Allison...
I got to do something, Joe.
He's drinking green muck.
He's dying out there.
The whole thing
was green.
It glowed green.
Wait a second. Green?
Like phosphorus?
Have you ever heard
of the Living Caves?
No, the Living Caves--
what are they?
Well, they're these
naturally occurring
holes in the ground
and people say
they're living
because they still
have big pools
of acidic water
at the bottom of them.
So they're still eroding
away the soil,
forming new passages,
growing, living.
Okay.
Here they are.
Okay, what made you
think of them?
Uh, well, they're
filled with phosphorus,
so at night they glow.
Okay, show me exactly
where they are.
Allison, there's over 200 square
miles of these caves.
There's no way
to narrow it down.
Wait a second. What's this?
Railroad track?
Railroad track...
Hey, you think you could take the girls
to school?
You're going there?
You're insane.
ALLISON:
Hello?
Hello?!
Is anyone in there?
BOY:
Hello? Is
somebody up there?
I'm down here. Somebody,
anybody, can you hear me?
Yes, someone's here.
Yes, I can hear you.
Keep talking. There's a lot
of holes around here.
Oh, please, get me out!
Get me out! Get me out!
I'm coming.Keep calling out.
???
Can you hear me?
Get me out!
Oh, please, get me out!
Get me out! Get me out!
I am.
Here, let me throw you down
some water.
I have some food.
I need to call people.
What's your name?
Jimmy... James.
Jamison Nessler.
Hi, Jamison Nessler.
I'm Allison.
How bad is your leg?
It hurts. It's hard to climb.
Okay, I'm not going anywhere.
I'm going to stay right here
and use my phone
to call for help.
You just eat.
I'll be right here.
He's here. He's in this hole.
Young man...
if you can hear me,
I want you to...
Shine a light down there.
No.
No, I just saw him.
I spoke to him.
???? how much it costs
to land an emergency helicopter
with three Forest Service
Rangers in the Arizona desert?
Hmm, no, no, I don't.
$1,700.
$1,700 to pick up a skeleton.
He kept saying,
"A skeleton
"is not an emergency, ma'am.
Do you have any idea
how much this is going to cost?"
Of course, now I do.
Aren't you going
to say anything?
What am I going
to say?
It's absurd.
I don't have $1,700.
I mean, I have it,
we have it,
but not to spend on unexpected
emergency skeleton pickups.
I mean, what are they going
to do if we don't pay?
Cut us off?
Not show up the next time we
have bones that need rescuing?
I'm sorry.
WOMAN:
Oh, baby...
Let me have it.
Let me have all of it.
Oh, baby, let me...
ALLISON:
Something
doesn't add up.
I'm talking about the suicide
of Assemblyman Rykoff.
You want to close
that door, please?
That fact that Henry Rykoff
committed suicide
is supposed to be
a closely held secret.
It's not something
we want to talk about
where others can hear.
Of course. I'm sorry.
I'm already pretty far out
on a limb with this thing.
Hiding the material facts
of this man's death,
walking his death certificate
through channels.
For what it's worth,
I don't think he actually did
commit suicide.
You remember Mrs. Dubois
from the other day?
And this is
Detective Lee Scanlon
who works with my office
on a regular basis.
I've taken them
into our confidence.
He's someone
you can trust.
Well, I'll have to take
your word for that.
Now, what am I doing here?
Frankly, Mr. District Attorney,
I have a funeral to plan.
I appreciate that this
is a difficult time.
But if I'm going to get you
a death certificate
that indicates your husband died
in his sleep of natural causes,
I'm going to need your help
answering some questions.
Mr Rykoff, did you
know your husband was
taking dexohydrophan?
Do you know what
dexohydrophan is?
Well, you people are
just determined
to wake up every sleeping dog
in the village, aren't you?
Yes, I am familiar
with the drug,
and I was entirely aware
that my husband was taking it.
He had been taking it since...
some time in the early '90s.
Mrs. Rykoff,
it's my unrstanding that
this drug is normally prescribed
to registered sex offenders.
Why would the assembly...?
Years ago, I became aware
that in addition
to Henry's voracious ambition,
he also possessed
a seemingly endless
appetite for...
What's the polite way to say it?
Companionship?
Not that he didn't love me.
I never doubted that.
But, apparently, in addition
he needed something
more dangerous,
something more...
varied.
And you knew about this?
I sensed it.
We had no children.
He was extraordinarily
busy with his career.
I still couldn't account
for all his time.
One night,
he came to me.
He was terrified.
Something had happened.
He never told me what,
and I never asked.
Someone got pregnant, I suspect.
Whatever it was,
whatever he had to do
to clean up after himself...
it changed him.
He confessed to me
that he just had these
compulsions, he called them.
That he hated himself for it.
So he found this place
in Minneapolis.
He spent two weeks,
intense counseling,
medication.
And it seemed
to work for him?
It certainly worked for us.
It became our secret...
our deep, dark secret.
Until today.
Actually bound us together
in a way
that old-fashioned intimacy
never did.
So now you know everything.
I'm sorry.
I still don't understand.
When you found your husband
the other night,
it appears he was trying
to get a kind of a, um,
heightened...
The drug kills the ability
to get aroused,
but not the instinct.
The way you sometimes
see a neutered dog
Oh, I felt so horrible
for him sometimes.
Is there anything else?
I-I really would like
to put him, this,
all of this to rest.
I'm good.
I think we're
all good.
That's him.
That's the boy from my dream.
Ain't modern science amazing?
Just like on TV.
You give those guys
a bag of bones,
a day later, you get
a name and a school picture.
Say hello to Jimmy Nessler.
Jimmy Nessler.
He just turned 12 at the time
of his disappearance,
which his parents first reported
to police in 1991.
1991?
My God, his parents--
I can't imagine their pain.
One of those nightmares
you hear about
from time to time.
Only child.
Kids gets on his bike
to go to school one morning,
never comes home.
Nobody saw him,
never left any clues.
Just, uh, vanished.
It was an exhaustive search.It went on for months.
Has anyone called 'em yet?
I mean, his parents?
Left the state in '94.
The father died in a car
accident two years later.
His blood-alcohol level
was through the roof.
Mother had a series
of mental problems.
In and out of homeless shelters
through the late '90s.
After that...
So nothing's different?
If I'd never seen what I saw,
if I never found what I found...
everything would
still be the same?
MAN:
Time to wake up, Jimmy.
You doing all right?
That was quite a little nap
you had for yourself.
Can I get you
more to drink?
Where's my clothes?
You wanted to take a swim.
Do you remember taking a swim?
They're over there.
Did you have a good time?
I hope you had a good time.
And don't worry.
I'm not going to let
anyone know you were here.
I know how much trouble
a kid your age can get into
by skipping school.
Did you put
the dirty magazines back?
Can't have my wife
finding those.
But if you ever
want to look at 'em again...
I can even make you
one of my special drinks.
Nice meeting you, Jimmy.
Go after him.Make sure he's okay.
He's okay.
He's drunk.
He's young. He's sweet.
You know, I'm only
a couple years older.
It's not about that.
Just go after him.
???
Look at you.
I'm impressed.
There's nothing impressive
about a 55-year-old man
who gets up before dawn
to trudge a mile and a half
just because he's convinced
if he doesn't
he'll die ten years
before his time.
I beg to differ.
I'm impressed.
Duly noted.
What brings you out
at this ridiculous hour?
I called your house
and your wife said
you already left.
Henry Rykoff, the dead
assemblyman,
knew Jimmy Nessler.
Okay.
Allison, Jimmy Nessler's
been dead almost 15 years.
He died from a combination
of starvation,
dehydration and exposure.
Assemblyman Rykoff
died several days ago
and in my opinion,
by his own hand.
What do the two have
to do with each other?
I don't know. Something.
I think when
Mrs. Rykoff was talking about
the assemblyman's... appetites,
And I presume all of this came
to you the way that most things
come to you?
I'm sorry, but I don't see
how any of this is relevant to anything.
The boy is dead.
Rykoff is dead.
Since we can be
reasonably certain
that the dead boy
didn't kill Rykoff...?
What if it's
the other way around?
I just like to confirm, in fact,
the assemblyman knew the boy.
Why?
i'm sorry.I know why.
I guess what
I'm really trying to say is would it be
such a terrible thing to just let sleeping dogs lie?
Yes!
Isn't Jimmy Nessler
entitled to justice?
If someone stole his life,
isn't it our job
to find out who did it?
Of course, it is,
but the victim is long dead
and the man you think might
be responsible is dead, too.
And frankly, I'm dubious
that any of  is true.
And I strongly doubt
that even if it were,we could prove
any of it.
What I am convinced of,given the times in which we live
and the climate
in which we work,
if you go swimming around
in all this muck,
you will definitely stir up
some kind of dirt
and it may reflect badly
on a man who isn't alive
to defend himself.
So where does that leave us?
I'd still like to try
and find out if he knew the boy.
And how do you hope to do that?
Ask!
No, I am not bringing
his widow back here.
She wasn't out the door
ten minutes
and the governor was
on the phone lecturing me
about decency and fairness
and respect
for the grieving.
Can I talk to his attorney?
Or what about that aide of his?
The one that his wife called
to help move the body?
Sir?!
I have to take
a shower.
Just stay away from the widow.
And if the governor calls,
I'm putting him on with you.
I'm sure he knew him
or at least knew of him.
We all did. I did.
It was a big deal
when this kid went missing.
I mean, our school
organized search parties.
I think I was in
the tenth grade
and he was in,
like, seventh.
Yeah, definitely
the assemblyman
was almost certainly
aware of him.
No, I mean,
before he went missing.
Do you think they knew
each other, Mr. Frank?
Casey. Call me Casey.
I don't know-- this
is all before my time.
I didn't start working
for Mr. Rykoff
until I was out of college.
Hmm. But you knew him?
I did yard work
for the Rykoffs.
And Mr. Rykoff was very much
a father figure to me.
Really pushed me
to go to college,
which I was not
inclined to do.
Introduced me to politics,
or "public service,"
which is what
he liked to call it.
But again,
back then,
I was in high school.
I have no idea he knew Jimmy.
I mean, why would he?
Let me ask you a question.
I read just this morning
that you were being asked to run
to fill the assemblyman's
vacant seat.
You're young.
You're at the beginning
of your career.
You get a call in the middle
of the night
to move a dead body,
to disturb what may be
a crime scene.
At the very least,
you must know you're putting
your future on the line.
Why did you do it?
Same reason you and your
bosses are working
so hard to cover it up.
Because he's earned that.
Because it's the
right thing to do.
Because I was asked.
You make it sound like
a privilege, fudging the truth.
Maybe I've been in politics
too long, but yes,
I consider it an honor
to be asked to help a great man
maintain his dignity at a moment
when he doesn't have the
strength tdo it for himself.
So you really admired him?
I like to think
I understood him.
You know, with all
he accomplished,
Henry Rykoff was actually
a very lonely and
disconnected man.
But I'll tell you something,
when I was a kid,
when I was constantly
being told
that I was not the smartest boy
in the room or the best-looking
or the strongest
or the fastest,
Henry Rykoff--
and I don't know why--
was the first adult to sayto me "Y
"There's a future for you
if you want it,
if you're willing
to work for it."
He wrote letters
of recommendation
to get me into school,
loaned my mom money
for tuition,
and when I graduated,
he immediately took me
under his wing,
made me part of his staff.
Why?
I think he sensed I might
have been a bit lonely,
a bit disconnected, too.
Jim!
Jimmy...
You okay?
No, I'm not okay!
I don't feel good!
I feel sick!
And now I'm going to get in
trouble for skipping school.
And I think you
and that old guy,
I think you're a couple
of pervs.
What are you talking about?
You know what I'm talking about!
How'd my clothes
get off of me?!
You wanted to swim.
No, I didn't!
I don't even know how to swim!
I feel so sick.
I need my mom.
You're a perv and that
other guy's a perv.
And I'm telling my mom.
You put something in my soda.
Nobody's telling
anybody anything.
You understand?
Nobody is telling anybody
anything.
Now you sit back down
and I promise you
you'll feel better soon.
I'm going home.
And I'm telling...
No, you're not!
Now don't be stupid.
You're not going anywhere.
Not until you calm down.
What do you think you're
gonna say to your mother?
Do you know who
that old guy was?
Do you know how important he is?
There!
What are you doing?
I'm getting my bike.
Getting your bike?
What are you, nuts?
You can't even see the bottom of...
Shut up! I'm getting it.
You don't seem to be
making much progress.
This was dumb.
Help me out.
What, so you can
run home to Mommy and tell her all kinds of lies?
Just help me out.
Give me your hand.
What are you going
to tell Mommy?
Just give me your hand!
Swear to...
Oh...
Jimmy!
He's dead.
What?
These are his books.
They're the only thing left.
He fell.
I mean, he was climbing
because I threw his bike
and he asked me for help,
but I-I couldn't help.
Put those in here.
Casey... my Casey.
Casey.
CASEY:
So, how can I be of help?
As you may or may
not be aware,
when we recovered
Jimmy Nessler's remains
earlier in the week
from the bottom
of that living cave
we also recovered
some other artifacts
that apparently
had been down there
as long as he had.
Okay...
A bicycle, that
apparently was his,
some microscopic
bits of fiber
that we believe is all
that's left of his clothes
after 15 years
in the elements,
and a Saint Christopher's medal.
This is all fascinating, but...
The back of the medal was
engraved with the initials
"C-E-F."
Those are your initials,
aren't they?
Casey Edward Frank.
Also the date,
11-15-74.
That's your birthday.
So you're suggesting...?
That perhaps it might
just be your medal.
Okay, I'll concede that.
It just might be.
What's the point?
No point.
Not a big one anyway.
Just that, you told Mrs. Dubois
only yesterday
that you really didn't know
the Nessler boy,
not personally.
And I didn't. Did I play
near those caves?
Horse around there?
Sure. Everyone did.
Is it possible that I
dropped or lost my medal?
Sure. Where are you
going with this?
Not going anywhere.
Just, now that you're going
to be running for public office,
now that you're going to be
under some scrutiny,
we just want to give you
a chance to revise
your statement
with regard to how
well you knew
the Nessler boy,
if... you chose to.
I don't need
to revise my statement.
I stand by what I said.
Are we through here?
Just one more thing,
uh, as you know I'm...
working to get the coroner
to issue a death certificate
for Assemblyman Rykoff
that would indicate he
died of natural causes,
and I almost had
him there, but...
then he realized that
the trauma to the back
of the assemblyman's neck
was as severe as the trauma
to the front.
I'm sorry.
You're losing me.
If a man wereto hang himself,
even if it
was only a botched attempt
to heighten sexual sensation,
the trauma would only occur
to the front of the neck--
the place where the noose
and the throat meet.
It would take someone coming up
from behind the assemblyman,
strangling him with great force,
to create the kind of trauma
apparent at the back
of the neck.
Wh... what are you saying?
We're saying that
it appears that someone
murdered Henry Rykoff,
then staged it to make it
look as though
he accidentally
caused his own death.
And you think
that someone is me.
With any murder case,
we look for means,
motive and opportunity.
You certainly
had the means.
You have the physical
strength to strangle
the assemblyman and lift
him into that noose.
You had the opportunity.
We're very
aware that you
had a key
to the Rykoff residence
along with their alarm codes,
that you frequently took care
of their home
when they were away.
And as far as the motive,
congratulations
on running unopposed
to fill the assemblyman's seat.
That's absurd. This
whole thing's absurd
Everyone knew I was being
groomed as Henry's successor.
Everyone knew he was
planning to retire
after this term.
Do you honestly believe
I would kill a man
to take something
he was prepared to give me
a year and a half from now?
I'm going to remember
this moment,
Mr. District Attorney.
When I'm sitting in the
state capital building
staring at your budget,
contemplating anything
to do with you
or your office, I will
remember this moment.
I thought you were
a smart man.
I thought you were smart people.
But smart people don't make
absurd allegations.
And they certainly don't
make absurd allegations
they can't prove.
I'll see myself out.
He's right. We can't
prove a damn thing and he knows it.
(sighing)
ALLISON:
I know what happened.
I know who did it.
I just can't prove it.
And I'm never
going to be able to.
Well, you know
what you need?
A good night's sleep.
Trust me. Just
close your eyes,
get some rest and
everything will look better in the morning.
(groaning)
That's easy for you to say.
You're right.
In fact, I think I'll say it again.
Close your eyes...
Shut up.
CASEY:
Hey, you wanted to see me?
Casey, my Casey.
Thanks for coming over, um...
I've been thinking a lot
about the plans we made,
my...
not running this term,
endorsing you.
Truth is, I just don't
think I can do it.
What?
I'm gonna run again.
And I'd very much
like your help.
Are you forgetting
I know things?
I know things that would
make it very difficult
for you to get reelected.
That's a silly threat,
young man.
You know things.
And everything you know about me
involves you, too.
So while you might
be able
to tarnish me at the end
of my career,
you'll destroy your own
in the process.
Well, I might do it anyway.
I don't want to wait
another four years.
I can't.
You can.
And you will.
Now let's not forget
who has what on whom.
You have nothing on me.
I'm the victim in all this.
That's not the way
I see it.
The Nessler boy's book bag.
Covered with your
fingerprints all over it.
Maybe not enough to prove
you killed him,
but you'd certainly have
a lot of questions to answer.
So... let's calm down.
It's only four more years.
And who knows?
Maybe you'll get lucky.
I could die in office.
Everything okay?
Everything's fine.
Everything's great.
You were right.
I closed my eyes
and suddenly
everything was better.
Who are you calling?
A locksmith I know.
Sorry to wake you,
Mr. District Attorney.
Uh...
there's a safe that you
and I need to crack right now.
welcome to www.1000fr.com