Hey guys, I saw your mom pull up.
So, put down your juice boxes,
close up your tabs You know,
let's go to your mom's house.
But you got to get the heck out of here.
You know, dad, you forgot all
about my cello practice yesterday.
Or did i?
And you forgot to remind
me about my science paper.
Sorry, hammer.
I talked to you about it last night.
You told me you finished it, so we're
gonna have to tell mom about that one.
Or do we?
Hey, guys, would you go wait in the car?
I got to talk to your dad for a second.
If we're gonna talk,
I need one of them as a witness.
I just wanted to remind
you that starting tomorrow
is that thing I told
you about last week.
Yeah, the thing.
You have no idea what I'm talking about.
The thing. No. I don't know. I told you.
You want me to really
remember something, you have to
make it rhyme and turn it into
a Catchy tune.
I was hired to be a research
assistant on a project that's cool,
so I need you to drop off and
pick up the kids at their school
- for the next 6 weeks yeah.
- I can't do it.
What?
I'm renovating the mckenzie house,
big job.
That's a historic Landmark.
I got to be on site the whole time
and keep an eye on the workers.
This could really lead to
a lot more work, so, sorry,
you're gonna have to find somebody else.
That's too bad. Maybe you know
someone who could help me with these.
Yeah. I won them in a raffle.
- Laker tickets.
- They are. Yeah.
Of course, I don't think
they're very good seats because
they're behind a bench of some kind.
You win, you win, you win.
Lakers-cavaliers. You totally win.
Look. I'll drive the kids around
whenever you need me to,
I'll keep my ears open and my eyes open
for anybody that can help you part-time?
There are your tickets. It's never
a pleasure doing business with you.
I got to bring my air horn to the game.
Not you. I mean the actual one
that used to come in a can.
Well, have fun
with Dennis at the lakers.
All my orgasms were fakers
for the last 15 years
- = 114 =-
" Gary and Dennis' Sister "
VO : ¤Aka & YaYa¤
Subs-Addicts"
[Sub-way. fr]
Look at these seats. These are way
better than the last time we went.
I know. Remember?
Our seats were terrible.
You put your binoculars
in front of my binoculars,
and we still couldn't
tell which dot was kobe.
We're gonna sit behind the bench.
Good morning, mr. Brooks.
Hi, Miss Peters.
I like to make all my workers feel good.
I give them a motivational
hug every morning.
That...
I'm not gonna let you down,
Miss peters. I appreciate the work,
and you're gonna find that my crew
is top-notch and professional.
Deja vu.
No. It's not deja vu, dad.
It's your fifth trip into the room.
That's not it. It's something else.
What is this place?
It's the Mckenzie house.
It's an historic Landmark.
This was owned by Hamish Mckenzie.
He was a shipping magnate
in the late 19th century.
The house was restored in 1975,
and before that,
it was a flophouse
for indigents and hippies.
That's it.
I lived here in'71.
You still got that big orgy room out
in the back yard with the giant doors?
You mean, the carriage house?
No. I'm pretty sure it was an orgy room.
I get a tax break by hiring him.
Pardon me. I'm looking for my...
- Gary, this is amazing.
- Yeah. I can't disagree.
- How long has it been?
- I don't know.
Probably since like, the last time
we saw each other which was when?
You don't recognize me, do you?
Throw a drink in my face.
See if it jogs my memory.
Anna! You're an...
Oh, my god, Anna!
You're Dennis' little sister Anna.
- It's good to see you again.
- You, too.
Anna, you were supposed
to be here an hour ago.
When you're late, you got to call me.
I'm sorry, Dennis, OK?
I was out looking for a job.
You want me off your couch, don't you?
On your couch? What's the matter?
You're not still living in Chicago?
No. I moved back after my
Jerk boyfriend dumped me.
Come on.
Who would dump you?
- Lots of guys.
- Really?
No. She's serious. Lots of guys...
lots.
Now, how'd the job search go today?
Well, I got one offer, but I don't want
to dress up like a cell phone
and hand out coupons at the racetrack.
Hey, hey, I might have a job for you.
Allison is looking for someone to
help out around the house
- part-time and with the kids.
- Really? That would be great.
How are Louise and Tom?
Fantastic and easily distracted,
in that order.
Allison, it's Gary,
the answer to all your problems,
except for you stretch marks
and your screechy voice.
We must've gotten
disconnected or something.
Here. You talk to her, OK?
Allison, hi. It's Anna Lopez.
I hear you're looking for somebody.
- What's wrong, Dennis?
- What's wrong?
Anna iback in town. You see,
I'm the oldest brother, and it's
my responsibility to look after her.
My dad said he'll murder me if
anything ever happens to her.
Your dad is not gonna murder you.
Latinos are very protective and literal.
I wasn't always
the oldest brother, Gary.
I'm starting later this afternoon.
Can you believe it?
- Hey, that's great.
- Thank you, Gary.
That's great. Save some
of that hug for Allison, OK?
Well, bye, Gary. See you, stupid.
Sorry to bother you, Gary. Louise
wanted me to come by and feed her fish.
She said you would forget.
Louise has fish?
- Come on in.
- Where's her room?
Right down the hall on the right.
It's the girly one.
How's it going over there?
Fantastic. Thank you so much
for getting me the job.
Of course. Come on. You're Dennis'
sister. I got to look out for you right?
Remember when you and
Dennis drove me to college
and you took me to the wrong Carolina?
Yeah. I still think you would've
done great at Clemson, though.
Yeah, but I didn't apply there,
and I didn't have anyplace to live,
so it would've made for
a rough freshman year.
But the job is great.
Allison is awesome,
and I guess I'll be over here a lot,
assuming the goldfish stay alive.
I don't know. We're having a bad
run in the fish world.
My toilet is known as
death's water slide.
So, this is your new house?
Yeah. It's kind of like my old house
took a dump and this one came out,
but it looks a little better with
a buzz. Can I get you a beer?
Well, I'm off the clock, and in a way,
you're my boss, so I guess I have to.
Well, congratulations.
Your first day with Allison.
You know, she's no picnic to work for,
and she's no picnic to be married to,
and she's certainly
not easy to go on a picnic
with when you're married to...
My gosh, am I speaking way too loudly?
I thought you were still the other room.
I thought I was supposed
to follow you in here.
Well, I'm glad you did
because I'm lazy. Here.
- Here's to getting to know each other.
- Here you go.
You know, I had a huge crush
on you when I was younger.
Really? I didn't know that.
I used to kiss my pillow
and pretend it was you.
What a coincidence. I used to kiss
Allison and pretend it was anyone else.
Are you nervous?
- You're trembling.
- I'm standing in the refrigerator.
Let me warm you up.
Wait. Come on, Anna. This is wrong.
You're Dennis' little sister. Come on.
Well, technically,
I'm not his little sister anymore.
I'm a grown woman,
or haven't you noticed?
Yeah. Boy, I noticed, OK?
I noticed. I noticed, I noticed.
Look. If we did go through
with this and this did happen.
Which I'm sure would be
one of the greatest things
to ever happen to me in my life,
and I am including
the time I rode behind Chuck Norris
on an escalator.
What if we broke up? Then Dennis,
his heart would be broken.
He's my best friend. I can't
let that happen to him. I'm sorry.
OK. You're right. You're a good friend.
I just wanted to fulfill an
innocent little fantasy where
I turned Gary Brooks
inside out with wild sex.
Well, that's not gonna happen.
Is there any way you can
pretend for one little minute
that you're not my
brother's best friend?
Just one minute,
and I'll never bother you again.
Anna, you have to realize something. OK.
We should probably stop now.
No way. I got 48 seconds left.
I'm counting in my head.
45... 4 Hey!
I don't know how that snake
bit you on your tongue,
but I think I sucked out all the poison.
Whew! I better go find
that little bugger.
Dennis, I can explain.
You don't have to explain. I have eyes.
- Gary and I were just.
- Just
making me the happiest
older brother in the world.
Oh, my god...
I'm not following you. This is great.
Everyone in my family has been praying
that Anna would find a decent guy,
- and she finally did.
- Really? Who?
You, you knucklehead. Come on.
I'm gonna get out of here,
and you guys go back to doing
whatever it is you were doing.
That was weird, and you know what?
Now that the sense of danger
is out of it, it's really not even
that interesting anymore.
Oh, my gosh, Anna, last night
was amazing. I can't even believe it.
Morning, hon. I let you sleep in,
but you better get moving.
I did the laundry. Little thing, honey.
Would you mind emptying your pockets
before you throw stuff in the hamper?
I've been fishing change
- out of the dryer all morning.
- You did the laundry?
And the doctor called confirming
your appointment on friday.
Sweetie, could you let me know
when you make appointments
so I don't schedule stuff for the same
time? We're a team, right?
How long was I asleep?
This parlor room is
currently under renovation,
but this is where Mr. Mckenzie
took his breakfast,
drew up contracts,
and met with local merchants.
Yeah, and Dennis Hopper played
backgammon with frank zappa right there.
Pay him no mind.
That rumor is unsubstantiated.
Now, if everyone could just
head into the kitchen there...
Where.
Where tommy smothers
never made hash browns!
Hash brownies...
And yes, he did.
I think she's starting to dig me.
What's wrong?
Dad, it's Dennis' sister.
She's kind of making me a little crazy.
We hooked up like, 3 days ago, and she's
acting like we're a married couple.
That's the second
weddingi missed of yours.
No. We're not married, dad.
And that's the second divorce I missed.
Excuse me.
Hey, Gary, look who I found.
Sweetie, you forgot your lunch.
You'd forget your head
if it wasn't screwed on.
You know what? Thank you, but I'm gonna
go out to eat with the guys today, OK?
Restaurant food is full of salt,
and I like my Gary not puffy.
And I bought you some new underwear.
I thought you might like to try
a pair where the elastic band
is attached to the fabric.
How adorable are you guys?
I just want to eat you up.
I talked to mom and dad. They want all
to get together at grandma's for easter.
I can't wait for you to
meet our grandma, man. Me?
She's just gonna eat you with a spoon.
All right. What's with you people? Can't
you like somebody without eating them?
Stop it. I'll see you at dinner, OK,
and don't be late.
I'm making something special.
Bye, honey.
See you, stupid.
I've never seen Anna this happy before.
It's so great that she's with somebody
that's gonna treat her right,
- not like all the other guys.
- Yeah. You know what? To be fair,
we never heard all those
other guys' stories.
What are you doing here?
You don't have the kids today.
What, I have to have the
kids to walk into your house?
According to the court, yeah.
Look. I know you're working super
hard with school and everything, and
I really forced Dennis' sister down your
throat, so if it's a big inconvenience
it's not working for you,
i'm really sorry about that.
No. Anna is amazing.
I couldn't get along without her.
So, if she was to get angry and suddenly
leave town, that wouldn't be cool?
No. That wouldn't be cool. I mean,
I love her, and the kids love her.
The only thing that isn't cool is,
she started dating some crepy older guy.
You might know him. He's you!
Are you insane?
I finally find a perfect nanny.
Mary poppins comes floating down from
the sky. You're looking up her skirt.
She's smothering me, Allison.
She leaves "i love you, Gary"
post-its all over the house, right?
She draws hearts
on my mirrors with lipstick,
and she runs baths for me.
She rubs my feet.
What a bitch.
Look, Gary.
You cannot break up with her, OK?
If you dump her, she will dump me, and I
need her whole lot more than I need you.
- Well, find someone else.
- You are stuck, Gary, OK?
The only thing you could hope for is for
Anna to break up with you. That way,
Dennis won't be pissed at you,
and she won't leave me.
She's not gonna break up with me.
Who would leave this?
Me and any other woman with legs.
Why did you leave me?
Why did we get a divorce?
OK. There are boxes of transcripts,
Gary. You can read them?
Look.
If you want her to break up with you,
just stop being
first-date Gary, you know?
Be 10-years-Down-the-road Gary
with the open boxers at breakfast
and the peeing in the shower...
I get it.
And the gassy, scratchy, burpy, slurpy,
cutting-your-toenails-on-the-sofa Gary.
I get it! I'm a disgusting man!
How you doing?
Hey, sweetie, where you been?
At a bar. I know you probably
made dinner and everything,
but I already filled up on wings and
beer, and if you're mad, I don't care.
I'm not mad. I'll just put it in
the fridge, and you can have it later.
Don't feed it to me as left over
because I don't eat leftovers,
all right, and if you're mad about that,
I don't care.
I'm not mad.
You should eat whatever you want.
You know what? Maybe I don't
want to eat whatever I want.
What's with you? It seems like a totally
different guy just walked in the door.
Yeah. He did, OK, baby doll?
The real Gary Brooks just
walked in that door, all right?
Get used to it,
and if you're mad, I don't care.
Are you kidding?
I love it.
This means
that you are comfortable enough
in our relationship to be yourself.
We just took a huge leap forward today.
OK. All right. OK. I give.
- Timeout.
- Great.
I don't want to take a leap forward.
I just got out of a marriage,
and with you, it's like
I got back into another marriage.
It's like you're acting like my wife.
You mean, because I cook your
favorite food and take care
of you and make love to
you whenever you want?
Yeah. You're nothing like my wife.
It's been 3 days. Don't you think
this is a little intense?
Wait, wait. What are you saying?
Are you breaking up with me?
No. I'm not.
I would like you to break up with me.
- Well, that's not gonna happen.
- OK. Then, I'm breaking up with you.
Why?
Don't take this the wrong way.
You're beautiful, and I really like you,
but you're a teeny bit banas.
Here we go.
I'm getting the bana talk again.
Again? You've had the bana talk before?
Lots of times, and the bana talk
is the very first warning sign
there's something wrong.
- Anna, I didn't mean any...
- No. You blew it.
There's no coming back from banas.
- Hey, there he is.
- Talk to your sister?
Guess you didn't hear the big news.
I knew this was gonna happen, but I just
didn't think was gonna happen so soon.
- Dennis, Dennis...
- Wait, wait.
I'm gonna remember this moment forever,
and I want to make it perfect.
Wait.
Say the words I've been dying to hear.
- I dumped your sister.
- Those weren't them. Try again.
It didn't work out. I broke up with her.
That's all there is to it.
It's no big deal?
But you know what? You can't just treat
her like some toy and toss her aside.
You know, a real friend wouldn't
do that. You suck, and I quit.
We go somewhere and talk about this?
Anything you have to say to me
you can say in front of my friends,
- Your real friends?
- my real friends.
We picked 3 of these
guys up this morning.
Well, you know what? I trust them
a lot more than I trust you, Gary.
Dennis, look. It didn't work
out with me and your sister.
I tried to tell her that,
but she wouldn't listen, all right?
So it's her fault. Can you believe this,
guys? He's blaming my sister.
El Gary la hecha la culpa
a Anna porque se dejaron.
I knew that if we broke up,
it would break your heart,
and I don't want to do that to you, OK?
So it's my fault.
Can you believe this guy?
Creen este guey?
Ahora, Gary le hecha la culpa a Dennis.
To be fair,
there's two side to every story,
and I'm not sure my side
is being represented here.
Scusi, amigos.
Hermana de Dennis muy bonita pero
always aqui, aqui, aqui.
"Aqui, aqui, aqui."
I'm out of here.
Dennis, wait a second.
You said your sister was a handful,
- didn't you?
- Know what you're talking about.
You told me she got dumped by
"lots of guys, lots," your words.
We're a passionate culture.
That's all I know.
Didn't a part you want me
and your sister to work
out so you wouldn't have
to worry about her anymore?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
- Maybe.
- Maybe?
I got carried away. I got excited about
you being a part of our family.
Dennis, you're my best friend.
We already are family, OK?
Can't we just go back
to being you and me?
I don't know. What do you guys think?
4 of us think you should stay together,
3 are against,
and one of us thinks the
whole thing is kind of gay.
What do you think? That's 4 for staying
together 3 against, and one kind of gay.
I still got the laker tickets. We got
purple and gold paint here. We could
paint a big "l" on my chest.
Will you paint a big "a" on your chest?
Now it's unanimous.
We all think it's kind of gay.
- Oh, my gosh, dad!
- Hey, Gary.
You know Miss Peters.
- Yeah. Hi, Miss Peters.
- Mr. Brooks.
Yeah. Is my dad bothering you?
But you are kind of harshing my mellow.
Yeah. I'm gonna take a sick day.
Team Subs-Addicts"