Previously on "One Tree Hill"...
"Congratulations. Your designs have been selected
to appear at this year's Rogue Vogue showcase."
It's like a competition for emerging fashion designers in New York!
It is my job to come up with a routine for the tournament.
The tournament's the same weekend as Rogue Vogue. You'll be in New York City.
You made me realize I was ready for you.
I love you, Brooke.
I want to be with you, not Peyton.
I need you to talk to me about your cancer.
It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
Ellie? Ellie?
I read a poem once about a girl who had a crush on a guy who died.
She imagined him up in heaven with all the beautiful angels.
And she was jealous.
Ellie is gone.
I imagine her with the badass angels now,
hanging out with them in their black leather jackets, causing trouble.
But I'm not jealous.
I just miss her.
You ready to talk about her yet?
I'm dealing with Ellie's death the way she would have wanted me to --
by really living life.
What better way than road-tripping to New York in this sweet ride
and then hopping on a plane nine hours later and flying to Charlotte?
Ellie would have loved it.
And Rachel is gonna hate it.
Win-win.
Are we on schedule, navigation girl?
Well, yeah, except that we promised to switch seats once we hit Pennsylvania.
Hmm. So, H. James-Scott, what are you more excited about?
The fashion show or the cheerleading competition?
Sharing a hotel room with Nathan.
You are so Brooke's roommate.
Whatever.
- Oh, slug bug!
- Ow!
This year's Classic will not be a repeat of last year's debauchery.
There'll be an 11:00 curfew.
That means there will be no late-night hot-tubbing,
no spinning the bottle, no truthing or daring.
And that includes the chaperons.
Your mom playing grab-ass on the bus isn't as humiliating
as Dan assaulting me in the locker room.
Where is Dan?
Official mayor stuff in Tree Hill.
Probably planning an invasion of Raleigh.
More pressure off you, then.
Actually, I play better when Dan's there.
What, some kind of twisted good-luck charm?
No, more like a gun to the head.
Okay, my turn.
Oh, wise radio, what is gonna happen to me in New York
at the Rogue Vogue fashion show?
That was the first question you asked, and you can't ask the same question twice.
I didn't like my answer.
And it's not like only one thing can happen at a fashion show.
Yeah, but it defeats the purpose of the radio game.
It's like magic eight ball -- you have to take the first answer.
Yeah, I didn't get a do-over when the answer to my question,
"what will happen with me and Nathan?" was "highway to hell", okay?
Fine, I will accept that at some point this weekend
someone will pour some sugar on me.
But my next question is, "what is Lucas thinking about?"
Right now.
# Torn between two lovers #
Okay, new game.
How about movie quotes?
I'll go first. Um...
"if I ever start talking about these as the best days of my life, remind me to kill myself."
"Dazed and confused."
Oh, my god, you guys. Look!
Whoa!
Oh, it's just like the movies.
Where's the iPod? Plug in the iPod.
Cue the soundtrack.
All right, girls, one hour to check-in.
Everyone, assembled for practice at 3:00, break at 6:00, final rehearsal, 8:30.
Lights out at 10:00.
You know, Brooke was never this strict.
She let us do what we wanted before the competition.
Do I look like Brooke to you?
Thank god no.
Well, I don't feel good.
I'm gonna go try to squeeze in a nap.
How stinkin' great is this?
Thanks for coming with me, team.
Guys, guys, this is Rogue Vogue, not prom.
Would you please get rid of those astoundingly repulsive streamers
before  I hang you by them?
- Um, hi.
- Hi.
Excuse me. I'm Brooke Davis, and I just wanted to check on my time.
We're trying to hop a flight tonight back to North Carolina
for a cheerleading competition tomorrow.
My two best friends drove down with me, and I'm in love with them for it,
- but we want to fly back together--
- You know, the schedule has changed.
Okay. Good change or bad change?
Your clothes don't show until tomorrow.
That's a bad change.
Yeah. Looks like you have a cheer-cision to make.
Well...
I cannot believe that director lady. I hate her.
She was wearing white, and it is way after veterans day.
Labor day.
Whatever,  almanac girl.
What am I gonna do? Could we get me a radio so I can make up my mind?
Okay, Donatella, get yourself together.
You've never worked so hard at anything in your life except your fake I.D.
It's your big chance!
You guys should go without me.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Peyton's right.
It's my big shot.
So just go before I change my mind.
Have fun.
Good luck.
Oh, wow. Keith.
These are gorgeous.
And  you should see the view.
Oh, and the bathroom, it comes with one of those...
Crusty old men?
Oh, that jacuzzi's gonna do wonders for my back.
Whitey, what are you doing in our room?
Don't you mean our room?
Oh, the two of you shacked up together in sin -- that's a bad example for the children.
You ought to be ashamed of yourselves.
But, uh...
Don't worry, Karen. I'll take good care of him.
Well, what have we got here?
Mmm!
Truffles.
Isn't that romantic?
Paper covers rock.
Two out of three?
Room service.
Wrong room. Sorry.
Man, if you don't come open up this door before I kick it down...
Big time.
Tony Battle. What are you doing here, man?
I live in the town next over, man.
So now I get to beat your ass in a tournament, not just one-on-one.
Well, hey, man, this is Lucas.
What's up, man?
Heard about you.
Jump shooter, right?
Went to see Nate's girl, lied about it?
Oh, god.
So I know you're all down to kick it tonight, right?
Uh, I don't know if we can do a wild night, man. We got a curfew.
Okay. Cool. So then we'll make it an early wild night.
Get your stuff. Let's roll.
Bevin, let me in.
I can't. I have an enormous fever.
You're gonna have to stay with someone else.
Thanks for driving up for the weekend.
Damn, baby, you look hot.
Oh, no, I don't really have a fever.
That was a lie.
Hi. Excuse me.
It's just a little crazy in here.
Um, I'm looking for the model for my clothes. I'm a designer.
My name's Brooke Davis. I have --
I'm your model.
Solaris.
Solaris? Cool!
Um, sorry I'm a little overwhelmed.
I'm still in high school, and this is all really new to me.
Oh, I know. Everyone here is like 30.
I am literally half their age.
So you're 15 or just really bad at math, like me?
Both.
I'm really bad at math and 15.
I thought you were like 25.
Yeah, you and every bartender in the city.
Nice.
I am really excited that there's another kid here, though.
I totally miss my friends already.
You should be psyched.
Your line is so awesome. I would actually wear it.
Like, my friend Jessica has to model a shirt made of tacks.
Ouch.
Do you have plans tonight?
Well, you do now.
Get for ready for a wild night, designer Brooke.
You took me to some pretty wild parties this summer, Battle,
but I think you're outdoing yourself here.
Hey, you'll see.
He don't look like he got game.
Bevin, quit making an "L" before you do that move.
It's the only way I can remember it's left and not right.
Well, stop. It looks like you're making the "loser" sign.
Hey, you guys, I'm sorry we're late.
Oh. Thank god you guys are here.
Where's Brooke?
Um, Brooke got delayed at the fashion show. She's not coming.
We'll just have to forge ahead without her.
All right, team. Everyone to your rooms. Let's get some rest for tomorrow.
Got to rest! So sleepy. Bye.
Oh, hey, give me a call if you need anything at all, okay?
Thanks, Haley.
I know you're excited about spending time with Nathan, so don't worry about me.
Okay.
Well, look, um, I'm not much of a listener,
but I do have some tequila in my room.
You interested?
Perfect.
Solaris, I love you.
You look fantastic.
Oh, this is Brooke Davis. I'm modeling her line tomorrow.
Do you have a cigarette?
No. I quit.
Oh, you bitch. Love you.
It's sad.
Ever since she got a rib taken out a year ago and those horrible collagen lip injections,
she's totally washed up.
Cheers.
Kind of weird, us hanging out.
Nothing personal. I just never imagined the two of us kicking it.
Well, we probably have a lot more in common than you think.
Then again, we'll probably never get the chance to find out.
I mean, I'm not Brooke's favorite person, and you are.
She just doesn't trust you.
And you do?
Not really.
I just wanted a drink.
Hey, it's Bevin.
Peyton's not in her room right now, unlike me, who's, like, totally asleep.
Anyway, if you see her, will you tell her she's bunking with you?
Why?
Because Haley switched rooms with Lucas so she could be with Nathan.
Now Lucas is in Peyton's room because Brooke's not coming.
But, of course, we can't put a girl in with Lucas, especially Peyton.
So Lucas goes there, Peyton goes in with you.
Chelsea's staying with Ashley because I'm really sick.
Long story short, Peyton's in with you, Lucas is alone in her room.
Okay, yeah, fine. I'll tell her.
Oh, and, uh, tell Skills hi for me.
What's up?
Oh, Bevin wants me to remind you to bring your flatiron to her in the morning.
Rachel says hey.
Wait a minute.
Oh, well.
You ready for a swim?
Yeah. The jacuzzi looking real good.
Well, let's swim first.
No, I'm -- I'm good.
Skills, come on.
Oh, my god.
Do you not know how to swim?
What the hell kind of question is that?
Do I not know how to swim?
It's 'cause I'm black, huh?
So you think all black people are just scared of water?
I'm so sorry.
Of course you can swim.
Actually, I can't, but... you know.
Well, I'm getting in.
Swimming, huh?
Well, how hard can it be?
Damn, baby, you smell like a candy shop or something.
Vanilla body spray.
Sparkle Classic swag bag.
You sure you want to wash off all that sweetness, baby?
We can go somewhere and just stay dry.
Skills, come on.
You have to trust me.
I'm not gonna let anything happen to you.
Do you remember when we saw "Titanic"?
"I'll never let you go."
That's easy for you to say.
'Cause the girl lived, but the dude...
his ass drowned.
Come on.
This food looks amazing, Mrs. Battle.
Well, I hope you boys are hungry.
If you're anything like Tony, that's not gonna be a problem.
Mom!
Nathan, we say grace in this house.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, that's okay.
Aliyah, would you like to say grace?
Thank you, dear god, for the lasagna.
Thank you also for sending Lucas here
and having him sit next to me 'cause he is really, really fine.
Now, that was heartfelt. Let's eat.
Best grace ever.
So, pops... I was telling these guys I'm gonna have to
light them up in the Classic tomorrow night.
Well, you know who holds the all-time record for points in the Classic?
All right, here we go.
You played ball, Mr. Battle?
Son, I lit 'em up in high school.
That's cool. What happened?
Life  happened.
I had this knucklehead.
Hey, man.
Was  it hard letting go and wondering what might have been?
Not really.
At a certain point, it's not about what might have been, but what might be.
On the drive out, did you see all those guys hanging out on the street corners --
just  them and what might have been?
Honey, do you need me to get you your soapbox,
or are you doing okay from your seat?
Let's hear about you two.
What's your father do?
Well, he hangs out with what might have been.
Well, it's a tough thing,
but I bet deep down, he wishes the best for both of you --
a good education and the hope that you'll find your way.
That's what every father hopes for his child.
Not yours.
Whoa. Fall back, little man.
My youngest son is referring to the father I never knew,
but I bet somewhere out there he is thinking the same thing.
That's what fathers do.
Ready to hit the lanes?
Uh... I kind of had plans, Whitey.
You disappear for four months,
and then you can't find the time to take an old man bowling.
I...
Go ahead.
You two have a great time.
Thanks, Karen.
Carry that, will you?
Hey, Travis, have you seen Solaris? I lost her.
She's in the V.I.P. room.
No. I was just in there.
Not that one. The real V.I.P. room.
Upstairs.
Solaris?
Brooke?
Are you okay?
I just snorted too much "H." I'll be fine in a minute.
As in heroin?
Oh, look.
The princess fell off her pony.
Is she okay?
She's more than okay, sweetie. Trust me.
You're so pretty.
Isn't she?
Whoa. Hey. I'm only 17.
Didn't know you were so old, sweetie.
I thought you were more Solaris' age.
That's disgusting.
Watch yourself, little girl.
You're swimming in the deep end now.
That's a nice jacket.
I had one like it once that I got from this vintage store
but left it at this guy's house one night.
Loved the jacket, hated the guy.
So I never went back for it.
It was my birth mother's.
Yeah. I heard about that.
Sucks.
Yeah.
I'm sorry. I'm not so good at the shoulder-to-lean-on thing.
You're in luck. I'm not looking for one.
I am, on the other hand, looking for another drink.
Works for me.
Try this. I call it "sympathy."
Hey, well.
Here's to sympathy.
For the devil.
Uh-oh. Someone is in trouble.
Why? It's not even past curfew.
Oh, Haley, uh... you're always such trouble.
Oh, my god. You thought I was Keith.
Okay. Um, Nathan's M.I.A.
I just thought I'd stop by for a girls' night in with pay-per-view,
but if you've got big plans...
No, of course, of course. Get in here.
You sure?
I'd love the company.
All right, um... movie guide.
Romance, adventure.
Nothing too scary.
Yeah, I can't really watch scary movies anyway.
Oh, I could totally be down for John Cusack -- "Must love dogs."
Oh, yeah.
That means you want to watch it, right?
Yeah!
- I love Diane Lane.
- Me too.
Did you see her in "A walk on the moon"?
"Must love" -- oh, I missed an "N." I thought it said "dogs." I'm sorry.
We can't watch that.
What do you got, big time? I got you, buddy. Shot.
Oh!
Wait. Now, don't shame me out there, son!
"T" is getting schooled!
Man, you see I have the home-court disadvantage here?
My whole family, man.
Uh, I'm not sure blue's my color, Aliyah.
Trust me. It brings out your eyes.
Come on, A.J. Let's school these two. Come on.
Okay, now we got a game.
Me and my man. All right? Me and my man.
Let's go, let's go.
And how is the most beautiful girl in New York City doing?
Oh, that hurts.
Doing great.
But I miss you so much.
I miss you too, baby girl.
You must be having the greatest time, huh?
Yeah, it's crazy!
Listen, I got to go, but I can't wait to see you.
I love you, babe.
I love you, too.
Show him your moves, baby. Show him your moves.
I got him.
What's the matter? Too low to grab the ball? Got a bad back, old man?
A.J., that's my baby.
When you finish your makeover, you should take over for me.
I'm headed out, kids.
All right, pop. Don't work too hard, man.
- Ooh, love you.
- I love you, pop.
Thanks a lot, Mr. Battle. Appreciate it.
You got a great family, sir. You must be proud.
I am.
You boys go strong, now.
Come on, sweetie.
Battle, man, you have an awesome dad.
Yeah. He could have played D1 ball but just ended up being a dad instead.
He's not bitter about it at all.
No. My dad's in love with life, man.
I mean, we're doing good now, but when we were little...
man, we came up broke as hell.
What changed?
Nothing. He just kept working the same two jobs.
He was happy then. He's happy now.
You know what he says?
"Regret makes you old, and bitterness poisons the people around you."
Your father's a smart man.
Um, excuse me, Mr. Cabdriver?
What's your name?
You can call me Daoud.
Okay, I don't think I can call you "dad."
No, "Daoud."
Sorry.
Daoud.
Would you mind doing me a favor and turning on the radio?
I have some really important decisions to make.
Of course.
Would you tell me what he's saying, please?
It is the story of a young girl who is very sad.
She's torn between two men.
One man is very rich and offers to take her away from her home
and show her all the wonders of the world.
So why is she torn?
Because the other man...
this man she's known all her life...
she loves him very much.
Yeah.
See? It's not so bad, is it?
You want to try it by yourself?
Actually, I'm not ready for you to let me go just yet.
Okay.
But we can go upstairs whenever you want.
You know, I am kind of tired from all this floating.
Well, just so you know, there's only one bed.
I hope you're cool with that.
It's not a water bed, is it?
Oh, God.
So A.J. and I roughed you guys up tonight, huh?
Yeah. You might want to wipe your eye shadow off before you start talking smack.
Nah. It's working for me.
I ate the food before saying grace.
How was I supposed to know?
You're kidding, right?
You always say grace before dinner.
Granted, every time I did it, I was sitting at the counter at my mom's café,
and every time it was, "thank you for the chicken fingers."
But still...
Dinner for me was always a TV tray and whatever game was on.
I guess we can both thank Dan for those solo dinners.
Well, then there's Chuck Battle.
Never had a father in his life.
One generation just changed everything.
You could do the same with Haley.
Look, I'll catch up with you inside.
And do yourself a favor.
Take a bath, dude. You stink.
But I don't understand how you think you can trust, uh, Lucas this time around.
It's a long story that frankly paints me in a really bad light.
Hey, the meter's not still running, right?
I shut it off when we parked.
But feel free to tip generously for my brilliant advice.
I just don't understand why I'm so sad
when I'm so young and this great thing is happening for me.
You have a lot of life ahead of you, you know?
So what are you saying? Why rush it?
I mean, I can be a fashion designer when I grow up. I don't have to be one tomorrow.
No. I'm saying the opposite.
Time passes you by, young lady.
You have a long life, and you can start by making it great right now.
My life would be very different if I could have the chance you've been given.
Would you rather drive a cab or design clothes?
I see your point.
Thank you so much, Daoud.
And good luck with everything.
Here's, um...
here's triple the fare.
You have a very generous heart, Brooke Davis.
Hey, what happens with that song --
the one about the girl torn between two lovers?
There's much happiness, I assure you.
No cheerleading for you?
No, I guess not.
Well, if you do well in this show, there won't be time for things like that.
You'll be the talk of the town.
It's just hard to let it go.
There are designers here who have been struggling in the fashion world for years,
and yet overnight, this could be the start of your career.
And the end of being a kid, right?
Being a kid ends for all of us, Brooke. Trust me.
Having an apprenticeship with Donna Karan and your own label makes things easier.
Good luck.
Yeah, very funny, Lucas.
Your ass is still sleeping on the floor.
Surprise.
I switched rooms with Lucas. I don't have to sleep on the floor, do I?
How'd you manage to switch rooms?
Well, believe it or not, Bevin "mastermind" mirsky arranged the whole thing.
Any room in there for me?
I thought you'd never ask.
Nathan! Oh, my gosh!
Come here.
And the stars are -- what are they doing?
They're... crying for what we could have had
Okay.
No, I like that line. It reminds me of Luke -- of Jake.
Jake.
Are you sure you don't mean Lucas?
No.
It's Jake.
Well, whatever you say.
Okay, look. I have to go to sleep now, okay?
But, oh, thank you. Thank you for hanging out with me.
You're not the manipulative psycho I thought you were.
Well, enjoy.
Good night.
Are you drunk?
Are you wearing eye shadow?
Working through the pain?
Kinda.
Everything's gonna be all right, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, it is.
Oh, god.
How drunk was I last night?
Drunk enough to puke six times.
Let me guess.
Rachel.
Yeah.
Rachel's probably not the best person to use the buddy system with.
I feel like you're always rescuing me.
Also, like there's a giant elephant standing on my head.
Yeah, well, I can't rescue you from the routine you have to do in three hours.
I'll wake you up in a half-hour.
Oh, god, this bed was so comfortable.
Ooh! That was attractive.
Room service?
Actually... let's have a proper sit-down breakfast somewhere...
family style.
Family style sounds perfect.
If it's the maid service, we're good. Thanks.
Brooke...
I cannot believe I flew all the way back from New York for this.
I am the dumbest girl alive.
Brooke, don't freak out. Okay, look. Hey!
Peyton was drunk.
She crashed in my room by accident.
It wasn't her fault. Our rooms got switched.
She didn't get the message. I slept on the floor.
By the way...
I'm thrilled to see you.
Come on.
What did we say about trusting each other?
You know Peyton needs both of us right now.
I missed you.
Well, well.
Looks like somebody had a rough night.
Says the girl who poured drinks down my throat
and then dropped me off in my best friend's boyfriend's bed.
Look, I just led you to the door, sweetheart.
We're not giant pandas, you know?
You can't just put us together and expect us to mate.
And do me a favor. Talk soft.
You've got a terrible voice.
Look, I was trying to help you out.
I'm sorry if it's not what you wanted.
You know what? You can't see it, but underneath my sunglasses, I'm rolling my eyes.
Huh! Speak of the devil.
Look, don't take that.
We have to get ready.
Brooke is not a part of this.
You are so happy you're not me right now.
You sound level-10 hung over.
Yeah, well, you should see me.
Yeah, you look like ass, too.
Brooke, what the heck?!
Hey!
What about the fashion show?
I have the rest of my life for that stuff.
Not so much to be 17 with my friends.
How sweet.
Unfortunately, my routine only needs 9 girls, not 10.
Which means you're gonna have to sit this one out, captain.
Well, I think we can manage. Right, girls?
Yes.
Yeah.
And watch me for the changes.
Come on, girls. Let's stretch.
You okay?
You can't be out here with me.
No, it's okay.
I talked to Brooke. She knows what happened.
It's not okay.
I mean, it is, but...
it's hard on Brooke.
I'll be fine.
You know, Peyton, you can learn a lot from Ellie.
She struck me as tough.
Yeah. Yeah.
And that's important.
But...
I also think you can learn a lot from her mistakes.
Don't live your life alone.
Let us in.
I'm still trying to figure out which was more fun last night --
sleeping on the floor or Whitey snoring the theme song to "M.A.S.H."
Top that.
Well, let's see, um...
I took a bath.
Uh, I hung out with Haley and watched an adult movie.
Hmm. Haley is a bad influence.
But most of all, I missed you.
Okay, Peyton, focus.
Brooke, try to keep up. And, Bevin, don't be an idiot.
We're winning that trophy. All right, let's go.
One last thing, girls.
Have fun.
And next up in this year's Secret Sparkle Classic --
when you're strong, you sparkle --
the Tree Hill Ravens cheerleaders.
What are you doing here?
And what the hell do you smell like dessert for?
Vanilla body spray.
Plus Bevin teaching me how to swim.
Skills, you're the best swimmer I know.
Right. I swim-lessoned her, dog.
Had to get her back for notebooking me.
You know.
Pick it up, Peyton.
Can't help it. Someone got me drunk last night.
Go, Bevin!
Solaris, you're wearingt wo different shoes, you moron.
You might want to lay off the drugs,
considering you don't have many brain cells to begin with.
It doesn't matter anyway.
Brooke Davis checked out this morning.
Can you believe she walked away from all this?
If the rest of my days are like this, I'm gonna die a happy man.
Marry me.
You can't propose to me.
I was gonna propose to yo--
I'm telling you, I did not order any... pornography.
Most of our life is a series of images.
They pass us by like towns on the highway.
But sometimes a moment stuns us as it happens
and we know that this instant is more than a fleeting image.
We know that this moment --
every part of it --
will live on forever.
Transcript: Raceman - Synchro: Amariss
- www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net