previously on the 4400...
a comet cannot change course.
this one has.
then it's not a comet.
we're not sure what's just happened.
there appears to be something out there.
the light is gone,
and thousands of people have just suddenly appeared.
diana skouris. tom baldwin.
you two will be one of the teams
that's responsible for investigating
what happened to the returnees?
-we're letting them go. -we're letting them go?
we don't have a legal right to hold them.
why disappear a little girl from the 1940s,
hold her for 60 years,
and then send her back with the ability
to predict the future?
can i go home?
home? with you.
i don't like being here alone.
shawn farrell...
uncle tommy. hi.
he's all yours.
hey, what about kyle?
kyle's in a coma, shawn.
what the hell did you do to kyle?
i don't know what happened.
i put my hands on him.   that's it.
he woke up.
you're talking about   some kind of ripple effect.
diana skouris    to the head of the class.
the incidents themselves are just catalysts for change.
i swear to god.
i'll ask you one more time...
where's my son?
-kyle! kyle! -no! tom, don’t!
you're not my son.
who are you? what are you?
i'm human.  i come from a different time.
your future.
in my time, humanity is dying out.
only those we took can prevent the catastrophe from happening.
that's why they've been altered
and seeded back into the timeline.
you mean it's all going to end?
you have to help them.
help them? how?
dad?
kyle...
i intend to provide a safe haven
for any 4400 in this country who needs one.
you goddamn freak!
danny, stop it!  stop blaming me  for nikki!
i guess what i'm asking is if i could stay here for awhile.
tell me a little more about this...ability of yours.
i wasn't pregnant  when i was abducted,
but i was when i got back.
that baby could be the key to the future,
and it has to be protected,and i can do that.
go ahead! run!
i will find you.
that baby belongs with me.
isabelle...
what is it,baby?
bad dream?
same one.
she's fine,richard.
we're all fine.
come back to bed.
it's probably just a raccoon--
who was it?
they took off  before i could ask.
they left something behind.
someone tracked us down.
who?
ntac?
collier?
this look like their calling card to you?
i don't know who it is,
but someone knows we're 4400s.
start packing.
i'll drive into town    tomorrow morning
to pick up my last paycheck,
and then we're out of here.
can't we just go now?
we're gonna need that money,lily.
mr. and mrs. sumlin.
peter.
if you'll follow me.
forgive our appearance.
as you know,
the center doesn't officially  open until tomorrow.
peter doesn't have time to wait.
that's where you're wrong,mrs. sumlin.
peter has   all the time in the world.
hi,peter.
my name is jordan collier.
just this way.
our medical lab isn't quite ready,
so we thought peter would be more comfortable up here.
hello,peter.
i'm shawn.
what do you say we get started?
yeah?
okay,buddy.
i want you to take my hands.
try and relax.
okay?
you're okay.
you're doing good.  you're doing so good.
it's okay.
oh,my god.
is he okay?  he's fine.
just watch.
it's okay.
you're okay. you're okay.
peter?
how do you feel,honey?
son?
thank you for your   generous donation.
we tried everything.
radiation,bone marrow transplants...
is he really cured?
take him back   to his doctor.
run some tests.
peter's leukemia is gone.
this is a miracle.
for now,it has to remain   a private miracle.
may i remind you that the confidentiality agreement
you've signed is strictly binding.
but people should know  about that young man.
and they will.
in time,they'll know everything.
very nice.
floating the five.   floating the five.
you nervous?
aren't you?
no,not at all.
well,maybe a little bit.
okay. a lot.
now,you really want to do this,right?
right.
let's go.    okay.
says here    she registered an ability
under the dinstman-lenhoff bill.
some kind    of precognitive insight?
yes,her visions stopped about four months ago.
we're not sure why.
oh,too bad.
i was going to ask if teledex will hit its quarterly projection.
well,we'd like to get started,if that's all right.
certainly.
if you'll just sign  where indicated.
diana skouris,
your adoption of maia rutledge is hereby complete,
legal,and binding.
so witnessed by me,henry biederman,
10th circuit family court of seattle.
you know,some of us have to look far and wide
to find the people  we'll call "family."
you two had to look   clear across time.
diana,let me introduce you to your daughter maia.
maia,say hello  to mommy.
i'm not doing it.
i mean it this time. no way.
it's just    a cat scan,kyle.
you've had them before.
this one's gonna tell them the same thing
the last 150 told them--nothing.
there's nobody in here but me.
i know that,
and sooner or later,
they're going to stop looking.
when? when?
i wish i knew,
but with ntac,the government,
they've got bigger issues  than you or me,okay?
just--
kyle,they're still  trying to make sense
about what happened that night   at highland beach.
that's all.
they're afraid   if they let me out
i'm gonna spill the beans about their big secret?
well,they can relax,
because i just want to get out of you and be normal again,
and normal people don't go around
sounding off   about future humans
and the end of the world.
besides,i don't even remember what happened.
i know.
you listening?
i don't remember!
just calm down.  just calm down.
dad,get me  out of here.
talk to someone. anyone.
please,'cause--
shh. okay,okay.
okay. okay.
tom.
been awhile,huh?
yeah,you know how it is.
us desk jockeys don't have much cause
to mingle with you hot-shot field agents.
someone feeling a little sorry for himself today?
"the path to oblivion  starts here."
the 4400 were sent back to save humanity,
and i'm supposed to help them.
i was there on the beach,remember?
they gave me a mission,
and what's my biggest accomplishment of the week?
i convinced my son to take another cat scan.
somehow,i don't think that's what they had in mind.
diana,you ready to roll?
in a minute.
it's just we have to check in on three more returnees.
i want to make sure we get our reports in by 5:00.
okay,why don't you keep the car warmed up?
and i'll be right there.
you bet.
vic hubbard's the best lead investigator you could find?
oh,no,he's the fourth one this year.
two more,i break a record.
we've got to get you out from behind that desk.
i'm lucky to have a job here.
i put a gun to another agent's head,remember?
yeah,well,
i never said it was going to be easy.
it's obvious what really happened.
are you going to start in with your negative energy again?
white holes.    see,they're the answer.
that's how they took them,
and that's how they brought them back.
yeah,but white holes--  the second law of--
yeah,because i'm right.
switch it up.    switch it up.
guys! what's it like to not be right?
am i interrupting?
brady's back on his "white hole" kick again.
well,one day you'll explain to me the difference
between the white ones and the black ones,right?
well,how about tonight?
how about you just give me  that thing that we discussed?
can't.
why not?
i already sent it upstairs.
i wonder    if anyone's read it yet.
when they do,i'm sure you'll hear about it.
i owe you one,handsome.
h.p. lovecraft's
the mountains of madness.
are you trying  to tell me something?
which orderly did you steal it from?
matt?
arlo?
you're so sweet.
you're the only  person here
who doesn't    want me dead.
i wish i could take you with me when i go,
but i can't.
they only want me.
but i'll be    leaving soon.
very soon.
joanne? paul?
what are you doing?
sex maniac.
don't go flashing    those bedroom eyes at me.
joanne,i'm serious.
put that stuff down before you hurt yourself.
we're building something.
i can see that.
can you really?
it's gonna be gigantic.
humongous.
rival the pyramids.
but some things are better left to the imagination,joanne.
besides,
you two   have physical therapy now.
let's go.
building something...
building nothing.
help me get rid of this junk.
i'm sorry. too hard?
oh,no. hey,go ahead.
give it your best shot.
whatever you do,
you must be pretty good at it.
uh,yeah,i work with my hands.
same as you.
my apartment doesn't look   anything like this.
well,it helps to have friends in high places.
i'm always open to making new friends.
come in.
speak of the devil.
give us a moment.
has anyone ever told you your timing sucks?
if they did,i probably fired them.
for you.
it's in bookstores   tomorrow.
jordan,this is gonna sell,like,a million copies.
people are gonna freak out  when they read this.
big ideas make a loud noise when they land,shawn.
you wanted to see me,nina?
are you sleeping    with tom baldwin?
should i come back in?
maybe we could start over--
answer the question.
never even held hands.
do you owe him money?
okay,what game  are we playing here?
because if i knew the rules--
i am playing   the theory room paper game.
i don't know that one.
well,let me give you a hint.
"the necessity for the immediate reassignment
of thomas baldwin to active field duty."
catchy title.
did you come up with it    yourself,
or did the big brains    in the basement pitch in?
let's just say that i agree with the sentiment.
tom is the best agent i've ever worked with,
maybe the best  you've got in this division.
in the three months that baldwin was investigating the 4400,
this department learned more,far more,
than it has in the entire year   he's been shuffling paper.
he threatened  another agent's life.
he was trying   to protect his son,
who these future people,whoever they are,
chose as their spokesman.
that's not to mention that his nephew shawn is one of the 4400.
all of which sound like major conflicts of interest to me.
that's not  what dennis ryland believed.
dennis ryland  is no longer in charge here.
maybe you should call washington    and talk to him.
i don't have to call washington.
they've got me on speed dial.
congressmen,senators,
committee chairs,subcommittee chairs,
all of them looking   to this department,to me,
for answers.
which is why you can't keep an agent
like tom baldwin on the shelf.
he's a major player  in this case.
he's maybe the major player.
see,funny,that's exactly what it says in this paper.
maybe marco had me check it   for typos.
uh,the next time that you want  to send me a message,
put your own name on it.
mr. walcott!
get down from there!
arlo!
mr. walcott,get down from there!
you heard the man!
mr. walcott,
get down from there this instant!
i'm calling security if you don't come down right now.
arlo!
this is your last chance.
what the hell are you    doing up there?
i got it.
arlo!
arlo,this is your last warning.
arlo,please!
be careful!
i'm coming down.
arlo,be careful!
watch what    you're doing.
i got it.
oh,oh--oh,my god.
oh,my god!
no!
lily,i'm home.
lily,relax.
we don't   have to leave.
some nut papered the entire town   with these things.
he wasn't singling us out.
well,i still think  we should go.
i was scared  last night too,
but did you read this?
it's a rant,not a witch hunt.
maybe,but richard,
we still don't feel safe here    anymore.
you mean   isabelle doesn't feel safe.
richard,we've gone over this a dozen times.
i don't know why she talks to me and not to you.
"talks?"
communicates.
whatever.
did she happen to mention    where we should go?
does she have a place   picked out,
or will she know it    when she sees it?
we can find the town.
we already did.  right here.
isabelle is six months old.
i know she's   a special kid,
but we're still  her parents.
we make decisions for her.
she doesn't make them for us.
i know.
it's time we get out of here.
you're right.
you're absolutely right.
we're staying put.
maia?
party time.
macaroni and cheese,mashed potatoes,
and white bread.
everything i like.
the only things you'll eat.
you've got to promise me
that you'll    outgrow this phase soon.
mommy,how do you make this taste so good?
well,it's a hidden talent,i guess.
you just called me "mommy."
you're my mom now,right?
now and forever.
i like that.
me too.
so do you think  i'll ever go back to school?
weren't you just telling me you got,
like,a 97   on your math test?
not home-school.
real school,
with a playground,and recess.
well,sure you will...
you know,when you get  a bit older.
how much older?
i'm not seeing things that are going to happen anymore,
so it should be okay for me to be around other kids.
i think i'd be happy at school.
aren't you happy now?
i'm glad you're my mom for real,
but i could still use a...
like,friend or two.
more mac and cheese,please.
just a little.
sign this.
what is it?
your letter of resignation.
i thought i was being reassigned to field duty.
you are,effective immediately.
i need results.
we have a high-priced collection of sheepskin in the basement
that tells me you're the best way to get them,
so i'm willing to take a risk,
but i need  some insurance.
this.
i left the date blank.
you cross the line,i fill it in.
fair enough.
good.
here,look at this.
tess doerner.
diagnosed with paranoid schizophrenia at the age of 15.
disappeared from abendson psychiatric hospital in april of 1955.
let me guess,they sent her back without bothering to cure her.
curing people was not part of their agenda.
we just got a call from the c.a.  over at the hospital.
one of their orderlies is dead.
he claims that there's    some kind of connection.
so...
we'll check it out.
hold on.
there's still one piece of business we need to get straight.
you're setting conditions?
this is your new house?
it's yours too.
well,all your stuff is here.  i...
kind of looks like  our old place,huh?
well,i tried,anyway.
only one thing missing.
mom.
yeah,i know.
sometimes i can't believe she's not here,either,
but we tried,kyle.
you know,we really tried to make it work.
i wish you both would have tried    a little harder.
i'm sorry. it's just...
you know,when something terrible happens to a family,
like when you were in the hospital,it can...
bring people closer together,
or drive them apart.
your mom and me...
i'll have to call her,
let her know i'm out of quarantine.
yeah,you should do that.
you know,it'd make her really happy.
shawn's gonna freak out too.
what?you know i'm gonna go see him,right?
you're a good cousin.
just don't expect too much.
you know,people change in four years.
i can't believe  you're standing here.
i've been looking forward to this moment for too long.
hey,you remember how we used to love to go to the batting cages?
you never could hit that curve ball.
me?no,it was you,
and i got plenty of quarters saved up,so...
maybe we should stop off    at the driving range too.
you want to learn    how to play golf?
i used to beg to teach you.
lot of things i want to try now,dad.
you make a list.
you want it,and we'll do it.
anything.
you can show me  tonight,okay?
you're leaving? i just got here.
it's my job,buddy.
now,get started on that list.
you people take your arts and crafts seriously,don't you?
you're sure tess drew this  before they started building?
she made her first sketch two weeks ago.
that thing started going up yesterday.
and you think that the orderly who died
is connected  to all of this?
arlo was on the ledge of "b" building,
prying loose a weather vane.
i believe it was this weather vane.
so why don't you just confine all the other patients to their rooms?
well,i've been tempted,
but this kind of cooperative behavior,
it's unheard of with these illnesses.
besides,i wanted you to get a look at that thing
before we tore it down again.
it's all right,kevin.
they're just here    to talk to tess.
he's very   protective of her.
she's his only friend in here.
really,it's okay.
i'll just let her know you're coming.
great.
we saw some of the pictures you did,tess.
they're really good.
they'll hear you.
there's microphones  in the walls.
they broadcast by satellite   to the submarines.
who does?
the doctors.
the doctors  here in the hospital?
some of them  are in the hospital.
some of them are stationed    on the submarine.
all right,we'll just talk really softly.
they took my crayons away,but they're too late.
yeah? why's that?
because it's gonna get built anyway.
they want me to  get in touch with them.
that's why they put the plans in my head.
uh,now,are we talking about the doctors here in the hospital
or the doctors under the sea?
neither.
we're talking about the people  who took me,stupid.
so the people who took you...
they want the patients here  to build that tower?
they'll do anything to get me back.
they like me.
did you ask the other patients for help,tess?
i don't like talking to them.
they're crazy.
was arlo crazy?
i never thought he was...
but maybe crazy is catching.
so my first day back,and what's going on?
nothing much.
just a bunch   of mental patients
building a machine   to contact the future.
well,that's what tess thinks,anyway.
she also thinks there are doctors
stationed under the pacific ocean,
listening to a radio broadcast
of her private conversations.
could be some kind  of collective hysteria.
doesn't explain   this guy arlo,though.
he's a middle-aged hospital orderly whose wife just left him.
it could have been suicide.
lost his nerve  at the last minute,
tried to grab    the weather vane.
i wonder how long it is since marco got some sun,you know?
i was thinking we could bring him down to have a look
at that thing they're building.
a road trip for marco?
he goes outside,tom,
but,you know,we could    have some sunblock handy.
it would be something,though,huh?
if she could actually do it.
contact the future.
tess is right.
maybe crazy is catching.
he was dictating a letter.
i don't know what happened.
he just grabbed his head and started screaming.
wait outside. now.
hold still. hold still.
thanks.
thank you.
they're getting worse.
jordan...
they're coming more often too.
you okay?
i'm fine.
i don't get it.
i don't get why these attacks    keep coming back.
i've cured...
emphysema,leukemia...
broken bones...
that baby really kicked your ass.
well,you just remember that when we find richard and lily.
you u und pretty confident,jordan,
but it's been a year.
sometimes i forget they're still out there.
i never forget,
and neither do the men i'm paying to find them.
okay,but if i were you,
i wouldn't want to be in the same time zone
as that kid.
if you two meet up again,it might just finish you off.
i have my reasons.
now,get some rest,okay?
all right.
big day tomorrow.
in breaking news,
a revelation  about the origins of the 4400.
in his newly published  autobiography,
former real estate mogul  jordan collier
claims that the 4400  were abducted
by human beings     from the future.
the book contains copies
of classified   government memoranda
that collier says    prove his claims.
the documents     are said to come
from an anonymous source
within the national   threat assessment command.
according to collier,
the 4400 were returned  to avert a catastrophe
that threatens     the survival of mankind.
why didn't you tell me?
collier charges
that the government has  had this information
for more than a year,
but has kept it secret
in an effort to avert    a public panic.
the government claims
that the documents  are purely speculative
and have been quoted  out of context.
don't care   who took them.
don't care who sent them back.
the government should have   kept them behind bars.
didn't you hear what the man said?
they're here to save the world.
what do you expect him to say?    he's one of them.
you're awful quiet.
i deal in facts...
and the fact is,
i've got to flesh the ... before lunch.
you'll be happy to hear that mr. collier's anonymous source
is anonymous no more.
agent hubbard will be prosecuted to the full extent of the law.
so,what about collier?
guy bought national secrets  on the black market.
i'm sure we'd all like to see collier charged with treason,
but it's unlikely.
i doubt we'll be able  to trace the payments directly to him.
now,as for this so-called "4400 center,"
round-the-clock surveillance  is in effect
until further notice.
i want pictures of everyone
who comes within a hundred yards of that place.
is it true that collier's filing for tax-exempt status?
apparently.
he's turning the 4400 into some kind of religion?
more like a cult.
well,"cult"is what the big congregation calls the little congregation.
cult,religion,whatever.
what's he basing it on?
have you read this thing?
collier claims that he can unlock the 4400 within anybody.
so he expects a guy punching a clock in pittsburgh
to believe he has some kind of latent superpower?
most of the 4400
don't even have    those kinds of abilities.
not yet,anyway.
no,but if you thought there was a chance
that you had an ability    locked away inside you...
you sound like you're ready to sign up.
no,
but i wouldn't blame anyone for being curious.
we keep telling the public that biologically,
the 4400 aren't any different  than the rest of us.
they haven't been altered  genetically,neurologically--
as far as we can tell,
but if collier thinks people are just going to sign their lives
and their life savings over to some metaphysical pyramid scheme,then...
he's in for    a rude awakening.
welcome to the center.
my name's devon.
what's yours?
kyle.
nice to meet you,kyle.
can i sign you up for a tour?
uh,thanks.
i'm just looking for my cousin.
shawn farrell?
i'm sorry.
mr. farrell's    not available right now.
could you tell him kyle's looking for him?
he does live here,right?
i'm afraid policy prohibits me from discussing our membership.
i'm not looking    for a discussion.
i just want to say hi to my cousin.
if you'd leave your name--
i'm not leaving anything.
what is the problem here?
there's no problem.
then tell shawn i'm here!
if he doesn't want to see me,fine,
but that's up to him,right?
would you lower your voice,please?
look,i've got nothing against you.
personally,
i hope the pod people return your body to you someday.
if it's all the same,i'll find shawn myself.
this way,sir.
get your hands off me!
you have    to leave.
you guys didn't tell me this thing was so big.
it wasn't.
not yesterday.
and those don't look like patients to me.
they're not.
dr. clayton.
i know what you're going to say.  we're falling behind.
we'll make up the time   this afternoon.
so is the entire hospital working on this thing?
it's the only way to get it done.
excuse me.
uh,randy,winston,we need a little help here.
dr. cho's back there with the satellite dish.
okay.
so first the patients,now the staff.
if this is some kind of mass hysteria,
it's spreading.
who does daddy love?
mommy...
and isabelle.
yes,he does.
you know what he sees  when he looks at you?
a beautiful baby. yes,he does.
but mommy sees  much more than that,
and you know why?
because you communicate   with mommy.
but you never talk to daddy.
so how about it?
anything you want to say    to daddy?
huh?
because i'm listening.
okay,then.
guess i'm left to muddle along   all alone.
richard.
we got to get  a copy of that book.
i want to read it.
you and me both,but i checked in town.
they won't have any copies till tomorrow.
i don't know about you,
but i kind of got used   to the idea
we'd never know  where she came from.
well,if we went to the future,
at least we came back    with a souvenir.
the people who took us,
they made all this happen,right?
they saw to it  that we got isabelle.
they must have   something in mind for her.
i have something in mind  for her too--
a normal life.
sounds good,
but we left normal behind    a long time ago.
this is outrageous!
we have work to finish here. important work.
the doctors want to work.
tell them to make their rounds.
no one's stopping them from taking care of their patients.
but the courtyard and the tower   are off-limits,you got it?
got it.
man,look at the size of that thing.
wouldn't mind having one of those  in my backyard,huh?
road trip's over. wait in the car.
so yesterday,
a few patients were compelled to work on this thing,
and today it's the entire hospital.
if we get tess out of here,
do you think   this compulsion will fade?
i don't know.
it's worth a try,isn't it?
all right,i got you.
it's okay.
i'm not a bad person.
i'm not.
no,no,no one's saying you are,tess.
then why are you going to    stick wires in my brain?
i promise,tess.
no one's   going to hurt you.
that's what everyone says,right before they hurt you.
why am i being punished?
i'm a good person. really.
i'm only doing what they want.
guys! guys! get over here!
kevin!
kevin...
okay,tess. let's go. come on.
come on.
it's all right.    kevin...
do you have a seven?
go fish.
i am   so sorry i'm late.
who do we have here?
this is carrie. she lives downstairs.
the u.p.s. man left their package with us by mistake,
and when her mom came to get it,carrie was with her,
and now i'm invited to her birthday party,
and it's a sleep-over.
i can go,right?
hi,carrie.
i'm diana.
it's nice to meet you.
nice to meet you.
i already said it's okay.
well,i think we should probably   talk to carrie's mom first,
don't you?
oh,look,you know what?  it sounds fine to me.
thank you,thank you,thank you,thank you.
you never told me    i was a prisoner.
have you ever seen a prison cell,shawn?
it looks nothing like your apartment.
goddammit,jordan,since when do you decide
who i see and talk to?
this is about your cousin,isn't it?
so you did know  he was here.
i know he was rude and aggressive,
and had to be escorted from the premises.
you mean thrown out.
it might have been handled more smoothly,shawn,
but all in all,
i'd have to say it was for the best.
kyle is my friend.
he was your friend.
look,a year ago,
you came to me looking for a new life,
your old one in shambles.
kyle,friend or not,
is part of that old life.
so what do you   want me to do?
you just want me to cut him loose and forget he exists?
he's no different    than your mother,
your brother,or your friend nikki.
don't you-- they do not understand
what it is we're trying to accomplish here.
you know,maybe i don't either.
well,then,i suggest    you pack your bags and...
leave.
so,what happens next time you start screaming out in pain?
do what's right for you,shawn.
i'll take care of myself.
i just got the full medical workup on tess.
let me guess--
physically normal across the board.
you can say this for the 4400--
they're consistent.
tess draws a picture of a...
a tower,or a monument...
yeah,or a beacon...
and the people around her drop everything and start building it.
well,they can't help themselves.
they have to work.
it's like ants.
come here.
the queen secretes a chemical,
tells the other ants what to do.
the drones don't stop working until the job is done.
doesn't matter if one of them dies,
or if a storm comes  and washes away the anthill.
they just keep working...
unless you take the queen away.
let's hope our drones respond the same way.
right,so the future sent back    a schizophrenic queen ant
with a blueprint for what,some interstellar walkie-talkie?
let's see what tess can tell us.
we'd just better not get too close,
because if your  theory's right,
anyone who gets exposed to her  could be vulnerable.
all right,i'll talk to tess.
you check in with garrity    at the hospital.
these friends of yours,
the ones who took you,
what do you think they want to talk about?
they're so much smarter than you,
it isn't even funny.
yeah,well...
yeah,i don't doubt it.
i mean,they figured out how to take you
and how to send you back.
sending me back was a mistake,and they know it.
i'm supposed to be there.
where exactly is "there?"
there were doctors there too.
they were nice. all of them.
they were nice.
you remember  where you were taken?
we slept a lot,but not all the time.
we wore gray clothes.
there was a giant building.
the doctors wore shiny jackets.
i miss it so much.
go on.
i really like hearing you talk about it.
our rooms had round windows.
high doorways with arches in them.
the stones had writing in them.
math symbols or something,
inscriptions,
jars of purplish metals,
and rods with stained tips.
these symbols,tess,what did they look like?
tess?
tess,do you remember   what the inscriptions said?
they're waiting to hear from me.
i need to get in touch   with them.
tess. tess.  just wait--
tess,just wait.
garrity,why haven't you been   picking up your cellphone?
i'm sorry.
it's been kind of crazy  down here.
so is everything all right?
yeah. fine.
we're just about  done here.
done?
well,the satellite dishes are a bitch to hook up,
but we'll get 'em.
come on,people.
let's get those dishes secured.
we don't have all day.
i just had the most unbelievable conversation with tess.
well,it couldn't    have been any more unbelievable
than the one i just had  with garrity.
can't say   i see it that way.
no other way to see it.
that book is blasphemy.
well,don't buy it  if that's how you feel.
"the third angel blew his trumpet,
"and a great star fell from heaven,
burning like a torch."
revelations 8:10.
i'll take your word  for it.
the day they came back
was the beginning    of the end times.
sounds like you've done  a little more thinking on it than i have.
either remove the book from the store,
or my boy here will remove it for you.
like hell he will!
do you know what  you're carrying there,woman?
it's just a book.
it's the doorway to hell.
that child yours?
that's my daughter.
abomination begets abomination.
richard!
what's going on?
we've got to get out of here.
now.
these new guys you sent us  are no good.
park told me he had experience with a welding torch.
experience at what? starting fires?
now our schedule's in the toilet.
did either of you call the fire department?
time to go.
hurry,richard.
hurry!
as of tonight,abendson state hospital
is officially    under quarantine.
the patients will remain locked down.
hospital staff and affected ntac personnel
will be confined to the site
until we've isolated  the source of the compulsion.
that sounds like a good plan,
but who's going to watch over them?
the last group we sent was compromised within hours.
which is,quite frankly,
a little disturbing,
if you think of this like an epidemic...
in the cdc,
we'd call tess   "the sole disease vector."
you remove her,you remove the urge to build,
except as far as we know--
none of those agents   had any contact with tess.
so it's like the flu,
or any other  airborne virus.
you catch it,you can pass it on.
what is this thing supposed to be,anyway?
my guess,
and i cannot emphasize the word "guess"strongly enough,
is that tess is telling us the truth.
it's some kind of communication device.
to contact who?
the future?
the only way to find out
is to let the patients   finish building it.
that night on highland beach,
they were trying  to tell us something.
the conversation was cut short.
which is why we've been stumbling around in the dark this last year.
tess is the only 4400
who remembers  where she was taken--
no,claims to remember  where she was taken.
she's also the only paranoid schizophrenic,
and it sounds to me like you two
have been spending a little too much time around her.
well,maybe i caught    the bug too,
but,uh...
i agree with them.
the quarantine orders at the hospital remain in effect
until further notice.
the guards will rotate shifts to minimize their exposure.
so where does that leave us?
until we're sure the compulsion's not spreading anymore,
you two aren't going  anywhere near that facility.
isabelle's asleep.
rainy day came sooner than expected.
do you think we lost them?
i'm not ready to stop    for pie just yet.
i got 1,200 here.
another 300    in my pocket.
i'm carrying two.
we're going to have to get those back windows replaced in the morning.
this should be enough to carry us through  to montana.
what did eric say when you called?
he was a little  surprised to hear from me,
but even back   in quarantine,
he used to say how us 4400s should stick together.
yeah,we didn't have much choice back then,
though,did we?
the bank will  wire us our savings when we get there.
if things get really bad,we can sell these.
i put that ring on you forever.
guess you and isabelle   were right.
we should have taken off when we had the chance.
it's gonna be a long night.
you want me to drive a shift?
get some sleep.
maia,what's wrong?
i'm sorry.
i know it's late,
but maia really wanted to come home.
why is that,sweetie?
i don't want to talk about it.
some of the girls,not my daughter,
but some of the other girls,
were teasing maia.
i guess she said she has a crush on frank sinatra.
well,ol' blue eyes.    do you blame her?
most nine-year-olds don't even know who frank sinatra was.
i want to go to bed.
i guess it got   pretty nasty.
i feel terrible.
maybe maia can come back  another time?
just her and carrie.
yeah. we'll talk about it.
thank you.
good night.
maia.
i know you didn't fall asleep   that fast.
it was awful.
you were right.
well,i didn't want to be right.
i don't need any friends.
everyone needs friends,maia.
come on,i really think   we should talk about this.
well,i don't.
buck's burgers.
good as i remembered.
kind of a strange thing to have on top of your list,
but hey,you know what?
i'm glad i could make   your dreams come true.
kyle,shouldn't you  be in bed?
dad,i'm 21.
so i have to keep    reminding myself.
i'm making some popcorn. you want some?
you're kidding me.
you could eat more?
i've been eating quarantine food for a year.
you guys might be keeping the country safe,
but your cafeteria sucks.
hello?
kyle.
we got to get the baby out of the cold.
i don't think there's any motels on this road.
i was thinking we'd head south,catch the 35.
guy should lose his high beams.
that's the first car we've seen in,what,like,15 miles?
get your head down.
ah... oh,my god,richard.
it's them.
hold on! hold on!
everybody okay?
yeah,i think so.
okay. let's go.
spread out.
hey,maia,sweetie.
it's wake-up time.
okay.
huh?
it was a late night,huh?
all right. 15 more minutes.
you know what?
frank sinatra is the coolest,
and don't you let anyone ever tell your dear friend.
so you didn't read any of it?
no.
i wouldn't want my daughter reading my diary.
you keep a diary? am i in it?
oh,come on,don't flatter yourself.
so,really,you don't even know
if "what she sees" means...
things during the day,
tv shows,ponies,whatnot...
or it could be "what she sees,"
a week,a month,a year down the line.
she hasn't had  one of those visions in,like,four months.
well,that's what she tells you,anyway.
why would she lie?
she wants to be normal,right?
every time she makes a prediction,
someone calls her a freak.
look,i understand.
you're her mom now.
there are certain protocols.
next time i'm over,why don't i take a peek?
you think that'd be  any less of a betrayal?
respecting maia's privacy   is no small thing,
but you've got to weigh that against the information
that could be in that diary.
you know what?
when you stop   trusting a parent,
it's really hard to start again,
and yes,i'm speaking    from experience.
hey.
i'm glad it's not my decision,
but if maia's having visions,you should know about it,
and you should know what they are.
is it bad?
i just jammed it    when we spun out.
just need to walk it off a little more.
we'll follow this stream south.
hike through the water a bit,
throw 'em off our trail.
it'll be cold.
it'll keep us awake.
after a mile,we'll...
we'll double back west.
head straight for the highway.
sounds easy when you say it.
we can do it.
we're going to do it,right?
keep her quiet.
she's going to bring them right to us.
does the name "gene pecusa"  ring a bell?
yeah,returnee 927.
oh,let me guess.
he still has the ability
to turn 20 bucks into a crushing hangover.
and a night in  the drunk tank.
we've got to ferry him   back to his halfway house.
give it to mortimer and falcone.
we got something else    on our plates?
everything's quiet   at abendson.
no one's been allowed    near the tower.
that's the problem,isn't it?
tom... tom,no.
you do remember
that jarvis has still got   your letter of resignation.
she wants results.
i'm going to give them to her.
and besides,you want to know
what that thing is as badly as i do.
i'm trying not to    think about it.
yeah,well,i can't think of anything else.
so it sounds like tess    has got her hooks in you.
i don't have the urge to pick up a tool belt.
i'm coming with you.
it's all right,tess.
we're taking you back to abendson.
we signed you out,tess.
no one from ntac is coming after you.
not you people. the doctors in the submarines.
they're watching us.
what,you're having second thoughts?
no,just get in.
so you still owe me four or five dollars
for those   two six-packs?
something like that?
i've got a 20 right here,
if you think you can take it from me.
look at you,man.
back among the living.   you look great.
i walk. i talk.
i seem to have full control of my limbs.
you still hit    like a girl.
nothing's changed.
four years? plenty's changed.
what are you talking about?
we saw each other right when  you got out of the hospital.
i don't remember any of that.
you don't?
so you don't remember sitting naked in the sprinklers?
no.
sounds like something you'd do.
well...
thank you.
i never got a chance to say that.
for getting me out of the coma...thank you.
you know,if it  hadn't been for me,
you wouldn't have been  in that stupid hospital
anyway,so...
no,i'd have been the one who disappeared into 4400 boot camp.
maybe i'd have come back with the magic hands.
all right,all right.    okay.
speaking of disappearing,you jerk...
oh,kyle,don't go there yet.    come on.
don't go there?
your mom   is so freaked out.
you haven't seen her in a year.
you haven't seen anybody.
your brother.
my dad.
what was going on  with you and nikki?
kyle,i don't want to talk about nikki.
we're all really worried about you,man.
you don't need to be.
i mean,i'm fine.
i've been to that place  where you're living.
there are some serious   stepford wives vibes
going on there,you know that,right?
all that stuff about "unlocking the 4400 inside everybody..."
yeah?
you don't really believe  collier can do that,do you?
kyle...
look around us,man.
the world is in a total freefall.
these centers,
they're a chance    to bring people together,
maybe our last chance.
i don't just believe that he can do it.
i believe that he has to do it.
sounds like someone  got inside your head.
he said you wouldn't understand.
collier?
i got to tell you,man,he was right.
richard!
god. what happened?
guess i wasn't looking   where i was going.
okay. we just need to rest.
you think they're stopping for breaks?
come on,richard.
five minutes.
all right,people,come on!
everyone out to the tower.
come on.
we've got a lot of work to do,and not a lot of time to do it,
so let's go,come on.
go,go.
come on,you heard me. let's go.
this one's mine.    stand over there.
hey,kevin!
look. i escaped.
always thinking of me.
kevin's a genius,you know,
but he doesn't brag about it.
i bet in a couple of days all these berries will be ripe.
don't eat them now.
the last thing we need    is to start cramping up.
look.
i thought you said   they weren't ripe.
they weren't.
well...
isabelle?
had to be.
way to go,little girl.
they're going to   have to work fast.
i'm going to help them.
that's not funny,diana.
i really want to do this.
no,you'd only be    in the way.
you don't understand.
i really need to do this.
have these sent to my house.
shawn,i've been looking for you.
yeah,i took a walk.
we have a special visitor    tonight.
she has pancreatic cancer.
her husband is willing   to donate real estate
for a 4400 center    in los angeles.
well,tonight doesn't really  work for me,jordan.
well,you have five...
no,six hours  to get in the mood.
mood's   got nothing to do with it.
i'm just not working tonight.
richard,please.
don't do this.
we don't have another choice.
there's three of them.
they're going to kill you.
not if i get my hands on one of those shotguns.
you can barely walk.
it's our only chance.
i've got to do it now,
while i still have the strength.
if i'm not back by sundown,
take the baby and walk due west.
it's that way.
just keep going in a straight line.
understand?
i'd give up another 50 years if it meant finding you again.
you knew about this,didn't you?
knew about what?
baldwin and skouris signed tess doerner out of here
and took her back to abendson.
they're rebuilding the tower.
that would be one theory.
no crying. you can't cry now.
drop it.
i'll cut you in half.
turn around.
i taught you boys    better than this.
get up!
diana,how's it going?
well,it turns out we're in better shape than i thought.
the fire missed  most of the wiring.
so how soon till it's ready to go?
well,we've got to finish    triangulating the dishes,
and then we're good.
just get it done.
baldwin.
we've got your man!
either you come out,
or the next sound you hear
is him being blown straight to hell!
i told you,she's miles away by--
open your mouth again,
i'll cut your tongue out.
watch him.
lily! run!
are you sure you don't want to say goodbye to me?
..
last time,bowen,unlock the door.
can't do that
you said you want results.
listen to me bob,when you are not in your right mind.
it's not the results that we was talking about.
you step awey before you get hurt.
take
no,no,just wait
we need a
just listen,listen to me
it's a risk,i know.
it's sometime you want to get the tureth
you have to take a ...
just listen to me.
you want the trueth?
tess sdores the memery...
they are not memeries.
she read the short...
step awey from that tower.
where are you?
let's get everyone back in their rooms.
we need a full head count before the next round of medications.
where are you?
i did what you wanted,right?
talk to me.
come on,tess.
we all could use a little rest.
but they lied to me.
or did i lie to you?
well,somehow   i wanted more.
i don't know what i expected.
another ball of light,
a booming voice from the sky...something.
could we have built it wrong?
maybe.
all i know is that i don't feel like  picking up a hammer anymore,
and 10 minutes ago,
that was all i could think of.
i want to be updated as soon as there's    new information.
norad said the pulse dissipated before it left the atmosphere.
could be all this sound and fury   was for absolutely nothing.
now,our first priority is to help the hospital personnel
restore order here,okay?
and then i want all of you who were infected    with this thing
to be checked out    by ntac medical.
you including me in that order? because i'm not sure--
you were infected,
because if you're standing here telling me you weren't,
i'm putting a date on that letter of resignation.
i was definitely infected.
i thought so.
we could use a little help policing the area here,
and we need to get rid   of these tools
before  one of the patients hurts themselves.
you heard the man.
excuse me. dr. clayton?
kevin...
did you just speak to me?
i guess i did.
i haven't said anything    for a long time,have i?
try six years.
i can think again too.
i don't know   what happened,
but...
i feel...
better.
you had me followed?
i could have had your   conversation recorded.
i just thought    that might be pushing it.
god,kyle's right.
i am some kind of prisoner.
shawn,i've told you,
you can leave here   any time you want,
and i meant it,
but until you do,
i will not allow these shadows   from your past
to alter your perceptions
of what it is we're trying   to accomplish here.
you're too important.
no,no,you mean you need me
to help bring in the big checks.
shawn,the money...
is a means to an end.
the goal is what matters.
ensure the future.
save the planet.
i can't do that without you.
you want proof the future works   in mysterious ways?
look no further than mr. kevin burkhoff.
yeah,instead    of contacting the future,
we got him.
well,not as disappointing as it might seem at first blush.
burkhoff was a tenured professor of neurochemistry at stanford university.
neuroscience.
only class i ever got a "b" in.
yeah,you're not alone.
only a handful of people work at the top of the field at any given time.
our mr. burkhoff was the heir apparent,
until he suffered his first delusion at the age of 30,
and he was institutionalized two years later.
what was he working on?
you want a ripple effect?
how's this?
burkhoff specialized   in dormant neural pathways.
he was trying to wake up   parts of the brain
that we can't use.
parts that would do what?
well,parts that could lead to all kinds    of special new abilities,
like...precognition.
right,marco?
precognition,
telekinesis...
stop me if any of this sounds familiar.
maia rutledge.
orson bailey.
you're saying that burkhoff is the father of the 4400 technology?
it's possible.
and we just woke him up.