We're not a threat.
We're salvation.
The world
will have to deal with us.
I'm not your little brother
anymore.
Then stop acting
like a two-year-old.
You're my brother.
She's your girlfriend.
It's all good.
You goddamn freak!
Danny, stop it!
Stop blaming me for Nikki!
Diana Skouris,
your adoption of Maia Rutledge
is hereby complete.
He's gonna die.
I saw it. He's gonna die.
Jordan Collier?
Someone's going to kill him.
No!
His body,
it's not there!
This is
your new house?
It's yours too.
I've been looking forward
to this moment for too long.
Only one thing
missing--
Mom.
We really tried to make it work.
How was your first day
of college?
I didn't have one.
Nobody paid my tuition.
I'm sorry, Kyle.
I must have forgot.
You've been talking
about this for months.
How could you forget?
You spent three years
in a coma.
You have no business
drinking anything!
You told me everything
that happened that night, right?
Yeah.
Any coffee left?
Help yourself.
Couldn't find a clean t-shirt?
This is what I wear
to school.
I like it.
You're looking sharp.
Thanks.
So...
How you doing, dad?
Good.
Fine. Why?
No reason.
Just, uh...
... you know, good luck.
Okay?
I'll be thinking
about you.
I'll call you.
See how it goes.
Okay?
See you.
Hey,
there he is!
What's all this?
Welcome back.
The prodigal son returns.
Returns from where?
Get your gear on.
We got to roll.
Tom, I am so glad
to see you.
Yeah, you and everyone else.
As soon as we take
Doherty down,
we're going to
pop the champagne.
Doherty?
Who's Doherty?
Diana, stop.
Fill me in here.
Who's Doherty?
Does he have something
to do with Collier's murder?
What, governor Collier?
What are you talking about?
He's not dead.
This was
Garrity's idea, right?
Got to admit,
it's creative,
but "screw with
Tom Baldwin day" is over.
Hey, listen, Tom,
don't do this.
The doctors gave you
a clean bill of health.
Doctors?
What doctors?
Where is everybody headed?
And what the hell is going on
around here today?
I think you should
probably just stay here.
We'll talk
when I get back.
Diana, just--
So, this guy, Doherty,
is he a 4400?
What's a 4400?
Please, stop this.
Four thousand, four hundred
missing people...
... the future sent them back
in a ball of light.
Any of this
sound familiar?
Diana,
I'm not laughing,
so whatever game
you're playing,
stop it, and stop it right now.
Tom, whatever
you've been through
in the past few months,
I can't even
imagine it,
and everyone here is pulling
for your recovery,
but you've got to
listen to yourself.
You sound delusional.
The future?
I mean, I've never
heard of the 4400,
and I can promise you
that nobody ever came back
in a ball of light.
Tell me one thing.
According to you,
what have we been doing
for the last year?
You're serious.
Humor me.
It's your case,
Tom.
Dirty bombs,
remember?
You went undercover
and infiltrated
an Aum Shinrikyo terror cell.
None of this means anything
to you, does it?
Of course not.
Why should it?
Well, your cover
was compromised.
They held you
for three weeks.
Sleep deprivation,
torture--
They'd have killed you
if you didn't escape.
So how does Doherty
fit in?
Aum Shinrikyo's been planning
an attack on the U.S.
since they've been sneaking
radioactive material
into the country
in museum pouches.
Doherty's the curator.
He's been in bed with them
all along.
Tom, he sold you out.
You spent three weeks in hell
'cause of this guy.
You've been
on medical leave
for two months,
recovering, and...
... obviously,
it should have been three.
Jordan Collier
museum of contemporary art.
Tell me you recognize
this place.
I recognize it, all right...
Well, that's a start.
But everything's different.
This is the spot.
This is where Collier got shot.
Do me a favor.
Don't let anyone else
hear you say that.
Tom?
Tom!
Is he in there?
Yeah, I think so.
You want to do
the honors?
Did you find
anything?
Somebody's been messing
with my computer.
All my case files are gone.
I type "4400"
into a search engine, and...
Nothing.
How could there not be
a single mention of them?
I don't know.
Maybe because...
... none of it ever happened?
Something has obviously changed.
This is not the same world
that it was yesterday.
But I'm still Tom Baldwin,
and you're still Diana Skouris,
which means that the people
they took,
they exist too, right?
Gary Navarro.
We worked with him last month.
He could read thoughts.
Read thoughts?
Tom, come on.
Played for Cincinnati?
Lifetime. 317 batting average.
Isn't it 300?
When you know what
the pitcher's thinking?
But... he was never taken!
Richard Tyler.
What did he have?
Heat vision?
No, some of them
can do... things.
Some of them...
some of them can't.
He's dead.
He's plane was shot down
over Sinanju in 1951.
So that's two down.
Are we going to go through
all 4,398 more?
I'll take my boots off
if we are.
Diana, your daughter.
Your daughter!
Your daughter, Maia Rutledge.
You adopted her,
right?
She's one of them.
Tom, don't include me
in your fantasy life.
You know I don't have
a daughter.
Yes! Right here.
It's a Seattle address
for Maia Rutledge.
It's right here.
Right here.
Oh, thank god.
Maia, it's me.
It's me, Tom.
Tom Baldwin.
I don't know you.
Don't say that, please.
- Don't say that.
- My name is Ella.
Maia's my grandmother.
Ella, who is it?
Oh, here she is.
This is my grandmother.
You're Maia Rutledge?
Can I help you?
Didn't expect you home
so soon.
How'd you do out there
today?
Glad to see you, too.
Everything okay?
Just tell me one thing.
You were in a coma
for three years, right?
If I have one more of these,
I could wind up in a coma
right now.
Come on.
I want to show you
something.
Come on.
Uncle Tommy.
We can eat, finally.
How you doing?
Shawn, what are you doing here?
Well, the band
got delayed in Berlin.
We're not going to start
recording until tuesday.
Besides, I couldn't miss
your big day.
Or Danny's.
Come on, tell them.
Believe it or not,
she actually said "yes".
We're getting married.
Look, he bought me this!
Oh, I told him
I didn't even want one
till he was
out of law school.
I like that.
You like that?
Are you all right, Mr. Baldwin?
Dad, do you
need to sit?
It can't be a joke.
There's too many people
in on it.
Sit down.
So then either
I'm cracking up,
or the world is.
Dad, the doctors said
you were okay.
I don't want to scare you,
but something's wrong.
I don't recognize
this place.
I mean,
I sort of do,
but everything's
been tweaked.
Dad, dad,
look at me.
You're not making
any sense.
You know that,
right?
You guys started
without us?
Just as well.
Airport traffic was insane.
Hi, guys, Nikki.
Can you believe my kid,
my youngest kid,
is getting married?
When the hell
did we get so old?
So you're back in the saddle.
How'd it go?
I don't think it went too good.
Really? I was just
telling your wife
that you were going
to be fine.
My wife?
I'm still married to Linda?
I said wife, not ex-wife.
Alana, over here.
Come here.
I've never seen this woman
before.
I think we need to be alone...
Go upstairs. Talk.
No. I don't know who you are.
Dad, Alana's
your wife.
You've been married to her
for two years.
She lives here, dad.
I don't know what any of you are
talking about, but it's over.
It's over,
it's over.
How'd you find me?
Guys downstairs called.
They said you've been
here four hours.
Yeah.
Sad, isn't it?
The only place
I feel normal
is hiding
in a storage closet.
I guess that's what it must
feel like to be insane--
You're not insane, Tom.
You just need a rest.
Everyone keeps telling me
I was tortured.
Maybe they broke my mind.
You're going to come back
from this, Tom.
It's just going
to take some time.
And I'm going to help you,
I promise.
So tell me again
about this ball of light.
When did you first come
to believe it happened?
August 14th, 2004.
That's when they came back.
Maybe not in the world you know,
but it happened in mine--
Get her out of here!
No one's plotting against you, Tom.
I did what I had to do
to get you better.
His wife's here.
She's asking to see him.
I am not married.
I am not married...
Look, lady, I don't
know who you are,
and I don't care
what you have to say.
You have to
play along.
I need you to
get out of here
so we can figure out
what's going on.
What are you talking about?
None of this is real
to me, either.
I know we're
not married.
I've never seen you
before yesterday.
The things you talk about--
The ball of light,
the 4400...
You know about the 4400?
Know of them?
I am a 4400.
I know my behavior
was totally out of line,
and I want to apologize.
I got fixated
on getting back to work,
and obviously,
the strain, the, uh...
The excitement,
it was just too much.
We're going to extend
your medical leave
by another six weeks,
and then we will see about
getting you back out in the field.
I'll circle the date.
Okay.
So I can go now?
Your psych hold is over.
Great.
I'm...
I'm sorry for the ambush.
Desperate times,
desperate measures.
I'll see you
in six weeks.
Tom Baldwin.
Alana Mareva.
So I guess we're married.
So I'm told.
Let's go home.
See if we can figure out
what the hell is going on.
- Where do you think we are?
- I don't know.
Maybe we crossed into
some kind of...
... alternate reality,
a different dimension.
I know.
It sounds insane.
It sounds impossible.
Impossible
isn't what it used to be, and...
... you're a 4400.
You think I'm doing this?
It's an explanation.
A pretty simple one, actually.
Simple, but wrong.
If I were making this up,
why would I put myself
in the middle of your life?
I'm sorry. This can't
be easy for you, either.
Yeah, easy.
My friends, my family,
everything I know is gone.
Erased.
I'm trapped
in the middle of your life.
How do I know it's not you
making this up?
Erased?
What do you mean,
your life has been erased?
I used to own
this place.
I bought it
four years ago,
a few months
before I was abducted.
And none of this
looks familiar now?
I was my own buyer.
I flew all over the world
And bought
mostly sculptures,
primitive art.
Excuse me.
Can I talk to the owner?
He's not here today.
Any idea
when he opened this place?
A long time ago.
15, maybe 20 years.
It only gets worse.
You're sure
that's the right bench?
I used to come here
every week.
Believe me, I know which bench
I dedicated
to my husband and son.
So back in the world
we came from...
They died.
In a car accident.
Shortly before I was abducted.
There's a way back home.
We're going to find it.
If you need anything,
I'll be right down the hall.
What, you're sleeping
in the guest room?
Under the circumstances,
yeah.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
We have to play along.
We're supposed to be
happily married.
We don't want your son
asking questions.
Okay, I'll, uh, find a spot
on the floor.
Are you sure you wouldn't be
more comfortable in the bathtub?
I'm kidding, Thomas.
It's a big bed.
I'm sure we can keep
in our own sectors.
Do you think
we're the only ones?
Are there other people out there
like us,
wondering how
they got here?
If there are, we'll find them.
We'll take out
classified ads
in every major city paper.
"Remember the 4400s?
Drop us a line".
We'll check out every returnee
we can find.
Tell me
something about yourself.
What do you want to know?
Favorite records?
Where I went to school?
How about your husband and son?
What were they like?
Paul was a radiologist.
We met while he was on vacation
in Tahiti.
That's where I'm from.
Linda and I thought about
going there for our honeymoon.
We picked Haiti instead.
Two years later,
after we were married,
we had Billy.
He was so quiet and sweet.
This is unbelievable.
I think this was
the interview
where I said I wanted
to go into medicine
because nurses
are sexy.
You did not
say that.
I got into medical school!
Stanford, baby!
Congratulations.
The real Kyle used to talk
about being a doctor all the time.
Right up
until he went into a coma.
"The real Kyle..."
I know
that's not exactly your son,
but he seems pretty real to me.
He gets happy
when he hears good news,
cranky when he gets tired,
and he forgets to put
the toilet seat down.
He's a good kid.
He was raised well.
I got a response
from our ad in the post.
Philip Kendrick.
He wants to meet us.
Philip Kendrick?
Tom Baldwin.
What do you remember
about the 4400?
It was the best sedan
Citroen ever put out.
Hydraulics came standard
on every model--
You're talking
about a car?
Yeah!
Mine's parked outside.
Where's yours?
It's in the shop.
I'll send you a picture.
Uh, Tom,
I don't have your address.
Well, that was
productive.
Yeah...
Should we check out
the Blake exhibit
while we're here?
Uh... yeah,
why don't you...
Why don't you
go ahead?
I'll catch up with you
in a minute.
No, it's...
Thomas...
Thomas?
Thomas!
It's gone.
What's gone?
That door. It was back.
And I opened it this time.
It was some kind of
operating room, I think.
I didn't see
anything like that.
You were just standing
there like a statue.
That room's the answer.
It has to be.
It's the only thing
that doesn't fit.
It's not part
of this reality.
If it even exists.
You're the only one
who can see it--
I have to get back there.
Hey, partner.
Black, two sugars.
So the guards tell me
That you spent...
Five hours here yesterday,
three the day before that,
and, one saturday,
you logged up 12.
Yeah, so I like art.
It's a nice,
functional door, Tom,
but I wouldn't call it
a work of art.
Now, maybe if it were made
of black obsidian...
I read your psych file.
You planning on having me
locked up again, Diana?
You know, this other reality
that you're anxious
to get back to?
I mean, even if you could
get back to it,
it doesn't sound
that great, Tom.
Back there,
you were divorced.
Here, you have
a beautiful wife.
Back there,
you son, Kyle,
spent four years
in a coma.
Here, he's about to spend
four in medical school.
Back there, your sister's family
is completely dysfunctional,
your nephew is in a cult,
and the future of the world
is in jeopardy.
You make it sound so... bleak.
It's just a...
Just life.
This is life,
and it's a better life for you
and for everyone you care about.
Just accept
what you have.
Because if you don't,
well, you're going to spend
the rest of your life
just sitting in this hallway.
Alana?
What's the matter?
Have you seen
these pictures?
Look at all the things
we've done together.
You know, you'd think
if we're trapped here,
they would give us
these memories.
You know?
Look, we've been to China.
I've wanted to go
my entire life to China.
Look, Alana, I don't know
how long it's going to take
for us to get out of here.
I don't know.
Who says we will?
You keep talking
about that door.
It's been a month already.
What if
it never comes back?
Then we're trapped, okay,
then we're trapped.
I don't...
But if we are,
Alana,
I promise you,
we will make new memories.
Just as good as these.
Better.
Oh, I believe we could, Thomas.
I like it
when you call me that.
"Thomas".
And this goes up, and then...
Ugh, I can never get
these things right.
Let me take a shot.
Come here. Hold still.
You got to remember
to make big loops.
Leave yourself
a little room to work with.
Hands
of a surgeon.
Hands of a resident,
more like.
No, you'll get there.
So how do you like it
over at St. Bede's?
The hours are killer.
Doctors treat me like
a glorified candystriper.
A good night's sleep
is a distant memory.
I love it.
Well, I look
like I belong
on top of a wedding cake.
Hey, you brought this
on yourself.
Some people go to Fiji
for their 10th anniversary.
You two wanted
to renew your vows.
Yeah, well,
the first time
just felt like
pictures in a book.
This one...
This one is for me and Alana.
Ready to go, champ?
And do you,
Alana Baldwin,
also renew your
commitments to honor, obey,
and love
your husband, Thomas,
till death
do you part?
I do.
Then by the power
vested in me,
I now pronounce you
still man and wife.
Go ahead. You may kiss
your beautiful bride.
I'm getting in here.
Oh, I love you guys.
So how do you feel,
Mrs. Baldwin?
Married. Finally.
Feels real now, huh?
Well, it felt real
for a long time.
It's hard to believe
we resisted it.
Do you miss it?
Your old life?
I still think about it,
but after
all these years,
that life, that world--
That feels
like the delusion.
I know.
I have to concentrate
to even remember
a life without you.
See, I'm good that way.
Like a cellphone
or TiVo.
Once you've got me,
you can't imagine
not having me.
I love you, Thomas.
It still kills me
when you call me that.
Come here, woman.
You're resigning?
I'm moving on, Tom.
I've been here
11 years.
The private sector beckons.
Dennis Ryland offered me
a partnership
in his consulting firm.
Nice gig.
So you're moving to Virginia?
Three weeks.
Look, D.C. has asked me
to submit a list of names
as potential replacements.
I'm giving them one.
Yours.
Well, I'm-- I'm flattered.
I, uh...
But you might need
a backup or two.
I mean,
somewhere in my personnel file
are measurements
for my straitjacket.
Nah, you were
convalescing
from injuries
received in the line of duty.
Your service in that case
was heroic.
I think you can talk your
way around the fallout.
That is, if you want the job.
A chance to sit
in the big chair?
I want it, all right.
Good.
Then practice saying,
"nice to meet you too, senator".
Best way to prep for
your confirmation hearing.
I'll spring
for a new suit.
My last act
as head of this division
will be to make sure
that this happens.
Congratulations, Tom.
You've earned this.
Thank you.
Guess what.
Don't tell me.
You just spoke to Jarvis.
You knew?
She might have
mentioned something.
And you didn't
tell me?
I'm transferring you
to Greenland.
Oh, look,
he's not even confirmed yet,
and he's mad with power.
Baldwin.
Hey, you're not
going to believe this.
They've just asked me
to join the board of directors
at the Collier museum.
Wow. That's... quite an honor.
Do you think I should take it?
The best museum
on the west coast.
You got to take it.
There's a benefit
at the "Seattle Inner City
Arts Council" on friday night.
They want
to introduce me around.
I didn't put my tux
back into storage.
So it, um...
Looks like we both got a little
surprise at the office today.
What do you mean?
Are you sitting down?
Just tell me, Thomas.
Honey, I'll see you
at home tonight.
Glendon Ritter,
C.E.O. of Stradwick Pharmaceuticals.
Isn't he president
of the arts council?
Well, you should go
say hello.
You come with.
No, no, you...
you go.
I'm all out
of small talk.
Go ahead.
Mr. Ritter.
So happy
you could make it.
Thomas?
Do you see it?
No.
Why? You do?
It's been gone
for eight years.
Why now?
Come back downstairs with me.
That's the way out. It...
... it has to be.
And if it is...
... and you walk through it...
... what happens to all of this?
To us?
I don't know.
And I don't want to find out.
I want to go to Washington
next month,
and I want to watch you
get promoted.
I want to see who Kyle marries.
So do I...
But this door, it's...
... it's back for a reason.
It's like
it wants me to walk through it.
But do you want
to walk through it?
I don't want you to, either.
Come on, Thomas.
Let's go home.
Kyle!
No, Kyle's my son!
Leave me alone! He's my son!
Kyle!
Stop.
Let go of me!
What...
Congratulations.
You made it.
Where are we?
I think you know.
This is where
they brought you...
... and the rest of the 4400.
Yes, this is where
they altered us--
Gave me the ability
to create the world
we've been living in
for the last eight years.
So it is you.
You've been doing this
the whole time.
We've been living
in my mind,
but the instructions
for your reality
came from them.
They created
a sanctuary for you,
an easier,
less complicated world.
But none of it's real.
You are.
I am.
The feelings
we have for each other are
as real as anything
we've ever experienced.
Is that why they did this?
Kept us here for eight years?
Because they wanted us
to fall in love?
Moments.
That's all that's passed,
but in those
few seconds,
we've accumulated
years of memories
that will bond us
in the real world.
I thought they were worried
about saving the world,
not playing matchmaker.
They're worried
about you.
Your life
is about to plunge into crisis.
Your mission
will be threatened.
They can't allow this to happen.
They gave you this relationship
as a source of strength,
to sustain you
in the trials
that lay ahead.
What crisis? What--
What is it?
Why can't they just tell me
what it is?
I can stop it from happening.
It's already begun...
... but now you won't have to
face it alone.
No, if it's started,
I have to get back there.
Only your wife
can get you home.
You are my wife.
No.
I'm part of the program
they placed in her mind.
She has no idea
she's creating this.
If she did,
it would interfere
with the bonding.
So, what, I'm supposed
to just fill her in
and tell her what?
Whether she knows it or not,
she's willing this world
into existence.
She can will it
out of existence.
Yeah, and what if
she doesn't want to?
You have to
convince her.
That will be the first test
of your relationship.
They've created a damn near
perfect world for me.
What if I don't want to leave?
Then the future
picked the wrong man.
What about Kyle?
He spent nine years
becoming a doctor.
What, am I supposed
to get rid of him?
Wish him away?
It's not really Kyle.
Don't say that!
If it's not Kyle,
who's moving around
downstairs in the kitchen?
Kyle. Shawn. Danny.
None of them are real.
They're just projections.
You've spent eight years
with these people.
They're as real to you
as they are to me.
I love my family.
I really do love them.
It's not that I want to do this.
It's that we have to do it.
But they're my family, too.
Back there,
I'm just a stranger to them.
What about you and me?
Our life?
Is that a projection, too?
No.
What we have, our memories,
they'll carry over
into the real world.
But it won't be the same.
It can't be.
Maybe not,
but whatever we have,
it'll be real.
What are you doing?
Make it go away.
What do I do?
Stare at it until it disappears?
No, just believe
it's not there.
Well, thanks
for coming, everybody.
Alana and I just wanted
to tell you all that...
... we're going to be
leaving.
We're taking
a vacation.
We'll be gone
for a while, and, uh...
I know it's sudden,
but we just decided
this morning.
Well,
how long is a while?
I mean, you just got the biggest
promotion of your career.
It'll have to wait.
We wanted to see you all
one last time before we go,
and tell you...
How much we love you.
That's so sweet.
Careful, Alana.
She's going to be crying
in a second.
It's something
we have to do.
It's a...
It's a trip that we've been
talking about for a long time.
Where are you going?
Not far.
Well...
Send us a postcard...
At least.
To the people we love.
You have no idea
how much we will miss you.
We will miss you, too.
Don't look back.
Tom?
Are you with me, Tom?
Can you email me
the Mareva file?
Alana Mareva?
Yeah, A.K.A. returnee 2155.
She was just here
doing her med eval.
It's my week
to do reports,
remember?
Diana, the 4400,
the ball of light,
it happened, right?
Should I be worried about you--
- Just tell me it happened.
- Yes, of course it happened.
What else have we been
doing here the last year?
That's great.
My god.
Thank you.
Alana. Alana!
Alana!
Alana, wait!
Thomas.