Previously on the 4400...
Kevin's a genius, you know,
but he doesn't brag about it.
Kevin, did you just speak to me?
I haven't
said anything for a long time.
Try six years.
You're saying that Burkhoff
is the father of the 4400 technology.
I can think again too.
Kyle never came home last night.
Kyle said he blacked out.
You could've come to me, told me what was
going on. He's your cousin, your friend.
Kyle thinks he did something during one of
his blackouts. He seemed really freaked out about it.
If it happened during one of his blackouts,
he wouldn't need a reason.
I don't remember them telling me
to turn my son into a murderer.
I kept hoping
I was wrong about it.
This is not Kyle's doing.
You've got to hold onto that.
Kyle...
you weren't in control
of your actions, Kyle.
You did not kill Jordan Collier.
Forget about the flight.
Bring Kyle home.
They just arrested
a suspect in the Collier killing.
We caught that man, the one that
we were looking for. It's all over.
Not yet.
Thursday, July 28
5:37 pm
Mommy,
I'm scared.
I know, baby.
I'm scared too.
But it's going to be okay,
because mommy's here.
Okay?
Whatever's coming through that door...
I'll protect you.
Thursday, July 28
7:22 am
Ten Hours Earlier
Today is Jordan Collier's Birthday
He died on NTAC's watch
What does that mean?
What's what means?
Nothing.
Just some crank...
it's nothing.
Guess it's Jordan Collier's birthday.
The state of Washington gave him
a birthday present. Did you read this?
They're talking like
it's an open-and-shut case.
He made threats against Collier.
Two witnesses picked him out of a lineup.
But they're wrong.
Roy Marsden didn't kill Jordan Collier.
And neither did you, Kyle.
You told me he'd never see a courtroom.
They want to execute this guy.
It's not going to happen, Kyle.
No one can put him up on that roof. Any...
any public defender will have a motion to dismiss
in front of a judge by this time next week.
What if you're wrong? What if they find him guilty?
What am I supposed to do? Nothing?
Marsden has been in and out of jail since
he was 15. Theft, assault, attempted rape...
but he didn't kill anybody.
And he's not going to be convicted of it, Kyle.
I'm not going to let it happen.
Neither will I.
Kyle, it's not going to be easy, but you're going
to have to start putting all this behind you.
It's your first day back at school,
and I want you focused
and fierce,
and thinking about As.
Okay.
All right.
Sweetie...
Mrs. Benke's going to be here
any minute. It's time to get up.
I don't feel good.
You've got a real fever, young lady.
Hey,
how long have you had that?
Dishonest? No, no, no.
I don't think we're being dishonest at all.
Human beings use less than
20% of their brain capacity.
Everything else is just...
collecting cobwebs.
Here at the 4400 center,
we're trying to tap into
that unused potential.
So your own ability, you believe it
stems from increased brainpower?
Show me another explanation.
Look, whether you believe that
we were taken to the future or not,
somebody did change us,
and they used technology to do it.
We're just trying to figure out
how and share it.
But "first keys", "second keys",
"unlocking the ability inside you"...
you have to admit that the terminology
is more religious than scientific.
Well, the movement
is part faith, part science.
It's a potent combination.
So what time was
your appointment for?
They told me 11:15...
but they always tell me 11:15.
I never get in before 12:00, 12:30.
Hey, free health care, right?
So what if they're so slow?
Compulsory free health care.
You don't show up for a quarterly checkup,
you've got the goon squad knocking at your door.
You don't like it?
Don't show.
Doubt they'd slap the cuffs
on someone's grandma.
Does it itch at all?
Here.
103.1.
No wonder you wanted
to stay in bed.
Is it some kind of flu?
Most likely.
Is it okay if we keep her
here for a few hours?
I want to go home.
I know you do, honey, but dr. Hudson
is going to take very good care of you,
and I'll look in on you as often as I can.
I wish I brought Lemon.
That's her stuffed dog.
Let me guess.
He's yellow.
Yeah. Well, I could go
back and get him.
You have a very nice mommy.
I try.
About this rash...
... now, I worked at the C.D.C. for seven years,
and I never saw anything like it.
It's kind of a weird shape, huh?
Yeah.
Don't read too much into it.
It could still be
hives... an allergic reaction.
We'll take care of it.
Sweetie, you'll be okay here...
... if I go get Lemon?
Okay, my darling.
Bye, darling.
When daddy's away, he misses Isabelle so much.
But traveling around the country,
talking to all sorts of people,
clueing them in about my life...
it's kind of fun.
Shawn's amazing.
This woman comes in.
Her C.A.T. scan says she's got
a brain tumor the size of a walnut.
20 minutes later, she's on
her way. Good as new.
Hmm.
I'll feed her.
She's not hungry yet.
How do you know?
She told me before you came in.
So she's...
... talking to me.
Communicating.
Same as she does with you.
- Since when?
- This morning.
I thought you'd be happy.
First time she ever said anything to me.
That's great.
It's just...
she hasn't said anything
to me for weeks.
I wouldn't worry about it.
It's just how you used to tell me...
kids always alternate
between parents. It's normal...
Just with Isabelle,
it comes with a twist.
This is major Charles Culp of the National
Security Agency's field enforcement división.
D.C. has loaned us his services.
Effective immediately, the major
and his team will be providing backup
in any 4400 cases
requiring armed intervention.
We know this office bears
a heavy caseload,
and we're here to help when needed.
Welcome aboard.
Hope you guys are up to it, 'cause
I'm going to have you on speed dial.
We'll stay out of your way,
let you do your jobs.
When the time comes,
we hope you'll return the favor.
Well, the last lady that we went up against
released poison spores from her palms, so, uh...
if you want to track her
down instead of me...
by all means.
My men and I are used to
unique challenges.
How long have we been asking
for tactical support?
Eight months.
I guess someone up
there likes us.
You guys check your emails
this morning?
"Happy birthday, Jordan Collier"?
Everyone in the building
got that one.
Maybe Marco should have one
of his guys try to backtrack it.
They already did. It came from
a public terminal in an internet cafe.
It was a new email account.
Nice to know
Collier's still got his fans.
What's that?
It's Valerian root or...
... something. I don't know, Alana swears by it.
They calm me down a little.
My suggestion?
Double your dosage.
The Baldwin trigger has been
a little "hair" lately.
My girlfriend agrees with you.
I need you to cover me
for an hour.
Maia's got the flu or something, and
Hudson wants her to spend the day here.
She okay?
I'm sure it's nothing.
I mean, I was sure that it was the bubonic plague,
but her doctor tells me that it's nothing.
So you plowed into some guy
and got away with it?
That's kind of a weird way to put it.
Well, the perks of having
a dad at NTAC, I guess.
And this guy you hit,
how messed up was he?
I can't really talk about it.
You know, it's lawyer stuff.
Who am I going to tell?
I broke both his legs
and his collarbone.
That's it?
He was in a car, Danny.
It's not like I mowed over a pedestrian.
Yeah, but you kept talking about this "awful thing"
you did. I thought you killed somebody.
What?
Well, thanks a lot, man.
So did Shawn.
Well, sorry to disappoint you guys.
Well, look, do me a favor, okay?
If you get in trouble again,
tell somebody.
There's nothing you can tell me
or Shawn that we can't handle.
Next time I black out and have a car accident,
you'll be the first to know.
Yeah, long as I'm not riding shotgun.
Oh, hey, listen, you want to go see
Arcade Fire with me on friday night, or
do you have to stay home
and nurse your guilty conscience?
No nursing. I'll go.
- Yeah?
- I'll go.
- All right.
- Yeah.
It's good to have you back.
Good to be back.
I got to go.
Okay. See you.
You hear that?
That buzz?
What is it?
What?
Is that coming from your gadget?
Is what coming from my gadget?
That noise.
I don't hear anything.
Neither do I.
What is that noise?
You hear that?
What's going on?
I've got, like, a headache.
Did you hear that?
A gift from me to you
Have fun trying to survive the day
Why is my signature
on this requisition?
Because I had to get it in!
Do not sign my name
on another report.
They sit on your desk for weeks.
If there's a space for my signature,
it should be my signature!
Foster and McCenahan are tearing
each other apart by the elevator.
Right before this started,
there was a noise.
I didn't hear anything.
Yeah, well, the rest of us did!
There was some kind
of high-pitched whine,
and we got another one of those emails.
It said, "have fun trying to survive the day".
Show me.
Okay, everybody try to stay calm.
If this noise or signal did something
to you... you've got to fight it.
What she's talking about?
What did I just tell you?
- Nina.
- You saw it.
She pulled her weapon first.
I was defending myself...
How is she?
Breathing.
She's bleeding pretty bad.
Get her to medical.
Park is under arrest.
Crowley, restrain him.
Baldwin, what are you doing?
Until we know what's going on,
nobody gets in and nobody goes out.
What's going on?
Security procedure enabled.
Who's a very good girl?
Isabelle is.
Isabelle's a smartie.
Glad to see you guys are having fun.
Lily. I didn't expect to
see you till 5:00.
Well, I'm taking an early lunch. I thought
I'd take Isabelle out to the garden.
That sounds fun.
Doesn't it, little girl?
Oh, I use flash cards with her
all the time.
Let's see if I can find an apple.
It's her favorite.
What is this?
Someone's been mixing up our cards.
I've told them a million times.
What do you use these for?
These don't belong in the nursery.
I think they use them for the applicants.
Part of their psych profile. Sorry.
Okay, Isabelle.
Going to go with mommy.
Okay.
See you real soon.
Well, the movement
is part faith, part science.
It's a potent combination.
The movement's 100,000 members
would certainly agree,
but Kevin Burkhoff, a neuroscientist
at Western Washington University,
thinks otherwise.
Uh, I don't question anybody's faith.
Why should I? Faith is a good thing, right?
But what they're doing over there at the center
has nothing to do with science. I mean,
you tell me how fasting,
meditation, and chanting
can alter, in any way, your
neurochemistry. It's preposterous.
It's a good scam,
but still preposterous.
"Scam". That's a strong word.
It fits. They're taking
this kernel of truth
about the brain's potential, and using it
to bilk people out of their life savings.
A lot of people might be surprised
by your stance. After all,
you suffered from paranoid
personality disorder for years.
Wasn't it a device engineered
by a 4400 that cured you?
Yes, and I'm grateful,
but you need to make the distinction
between the 4400 and the 4400 center.
4400s have remarkable abilities...
everybody knows it...
but the center is co-opting
that phenomenon for profit.
Those machines they're hooking
people up to over there?
They might as well not
even be plugged in.
If you ask me, he still
looks rather demented.
He seemed pretty sane to me, Matthew,
especially when he was ripping us...
Shawn, don't overreact.
It's just one interview.
Oh...
You did good, though.
Yeah.
Garrity, give me the gun.
Look, this is crazy, Baldwin.
How are we going to
defend ourselves?
Whoever's doing this wants us
to attack each other.
If we stay armed, we're dead
by the end of the day.
If we don't, we'll be slaughtered.
Look, everyone in the building
is under the effects of this thing, okay?
The cafeteria staff could be
forming an army right now.
Which is why I'll find out
who's doing this and stop it.
They're doing checkups in the medical lab today.
That means there's 4400s in the building.
You think that one of them
is behind this?
I...
I don't know,
but right now,
it's all I have to go on.
You?
Who put you in command?
He's not. I am.
This building is the target
of a 4400 terrorist attack.
It is now a military situation.
This is great, Baldwin.
Why don't you explain to these guys
why they should just lay down their arms, huh?
Major Culp, the signal, whatever it is,
it's like someone set off a rage bomb.
It's pumping up the aggression of everybody
in the building. The men, anyway.
We cannot be walking around
with loaded firearms.
My team's trained to resist
psychological pressure tactics.
This is a 4400 ability.
You can't resist it.
There's 4400s down in the med lab.
It's probably one of them doing it.
Baldwin was just headed
down there right now.
Cartwright, watch them.
Everyone else, with me.
Just wait. Wait.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to find out which one of
them's responsible for this.
And then what?
I'm going to make sure that it stops.
Be careful.
There's a little girl down there.
If it's not her,
then she has nothing
to worry about.
You have to let me out!
We got to get out!
We're going to get killed!
Would you stop saying
that already?
It's not helping.
An "a"?
That's great.
But what's my name
doing on here?
Well, we're lab partners, right?
This is our presentation.
But I haven't met with you in almost three
weeks. I didn't type a word of this.
Well, it's not like you didn't do anything.
You said you wanted to do a paper on mitosis.
You stained the slides.
One or two of them, maybe.
Look... you were in trouble, right?
I just figured
that whatever it was,
you could probably do without
an "incomplete" in bio.
I still don't know if I deserve this,
but thank you.
What can I say?
I have a soft spot for stray cats.
I look that pathetic?
Hardly.
You're shooting up?
Doesn't exactly fill me
with confidence.
It's a sedative.
If I lose control
and become like everyone
else in this place,
I can't help you anymore.
What's happening to my agents?
I don't feel any different,
but they're all going crazy.
Dr. Hudson?
I feel worse.
You shouldn't be out of bed.
Sweetie, what's that on your arm?
Skouris, NTAC.
I need to get past.
Building's locked down.
Well, what's going on?
Security breach from the inside.
That's all we know.
- I have to get through.
- That's not going to happen.
You don't understand.
My daughter's in there.
Thursday, July 28
3:19 pm
Well, I can't do it myself.
Turn around.
Hold still.
I can't believe you
broke my nose.
Yeah, well, you broke
my knuckle when I hit you.
But I'm still right.
The signal is constant.
It doesn't matter if you can hear it
or not. It's like a dog whistle.
It's one pulse, and it'll wear off.
We just have to wait it out...
Both of you guys shut up!
I'm trying to get work done.
Not a good time, Diana.
Marco, what's going on in there?
Depends on who you ask.
Somebody's definitely
set off a whammy in here.
Something's pumping up
our "fight or flight" instincts.
Heavy emphasis
on the "fight" part.
Well, Marco, I need to get inside,
and I need your help.
Every male in this building has got a gallon of
adrenaline coursing through his veins right now.
And most of them are armed.
If you're on the outside, stay there.
Listen to me, Marco. Maia is inside,
and I need to get to her.
Do you have access
to the building schematics?
Uh, yeah.
I can pull them up.
Do it.
And what do I get in return?
Well, we can talk about that later.
Good. Good.
I'm going to hold you to that.
Get off me.
You're in my space!
Hang on.
- You're in my space!
- Guys!
Settle it later!
We've got to get
Skouris into the building.
I said get on your knees.
I just need to take these.
They're keeping me calm.
Little late for that.
You sure you don't want one?
They might help.
Cut us loose. Come on.
Cut me free.
Get some cuffs.
Put them on commando-boy.
Then you can let everybody else go.
Hey, hey, where are you going?
I'm going to the med labs. Hopefully
the major met some resistance along the way.
What kind of tests?
You mean like an I.Q. thing?
I don't know, Richard.
Those flash cards were weird,
and after we got back,
I was changing her.
She has these marks on her skin.
Marks? Bruises?
No. Like irritations.
Like someone had her
hooked up to something.
Let me see.
They faded.
Richard...
don't look at me like that.
I'm not imagining things.
She's not going back
to that nursery.
Lily... all you've been talking about
is how much you love Ruth
and the nursery, and how much
Isabelle seems to love it there.
I wish you'd been there.
I mean, Ruth, she had
this weird smile on her face.
Think about what you're saying.
Nobody's doing tests on her at the nursery.
You know, I know you feel
like she's shutting you out, and
no offense, but maybe
this is an overreaction.
- Can I take her for a second?
- No.
Lily, what are you doing?
I'm sorry.
It's just this place.
I feel like it's changing everything,
like it's changing us.
We're okay.
Everything's okay.
The meditation courses, the synaptic potential
readers, and our purification seminars...
that's half our curriculum
you're putting on the chopping block.
We don't need them, Matthew.
Jordan seemed to think we did.
Jordan's not here anymore, is he?
Besides, that Burkhoff guy is right...
a bunch of chanting is not going to
unlock the 4400 inside of anyone.
Whether it will or it won't,
the product is selling.
Wait, wait, wait.
"Product"?
This is not a pyramid scheme, Matthew.
People are coming here, they're looking to be
changed. They're looking for answers.
And we'll find them,
but if we change, we look weak.
For now, all that matters is that
people believe in what we're doing.
I need to believe in it, too.
Nobody move!
They're gone.
They all took off.
Who are you?
Roger Wolcott.
I'm just here for my checkup.
The 4400?
Why else would I be here?
Now cut me loose!
Thursday, July 28
4:22 pm
That's not going to hold anybody.
Not for long. Let's hope no one finds us.
What do you think
our chances are?
The calmer we are,
the longer we stay alive.
How are you doing, sweetie?
I feel all sweaty,
and it's getting hard to breathe.
Poor baby.
I have something for you.
- Lemon.
- Yeah.
As soon as this is over, I'm going
to get you to the hospital, okay?
All right.
I'm guessing you don't have
a stuffed animal for me.
Maybe a fifth of Jack Daniels?
Sorry.
Looks like it's starting to clot.
You need another shot for pain?
No.
You need the sedatives
more than I do.
How many shots have you taken?
Three.
And you're still on your feet? Shouldn't that
have knocked you on your ass by now?
Well, on a normal day, I'd be out
for the next 12 hours, but today,
it's barely enough
to keep me sane.
Well, thank you...
for keeping Maia safe.
She's a sweet kid.
Listen, Diana...
Iook, I've only got
three shots left.
They're wearing off a little
faster each time, so...
I don't want to hurt anybody.
I don't want to kill anybody. So if I...
... start to go...
Oh, don't worry.
I'll take care of you.
Do me a favor...
... back of the head, okay?
You'll never see it coming.
Now, listen, Hudson...
Look, I just gave you permission
to blow my head off.
Why don't you call me Max?
All right, Max.
About this signal...
Which one of these bitches
do you think is sending it?
I don't see what this
has to do with anything.
Hey, you wanted to
know my story.
Well, right now, you're living it.
Open your eyes.
Now, imagine three years went
by while you had them shut.
Can't do it.
Neither could I...
but they were gone.
I missed senior year of high school,
which is supposedly the best year ever.
I got robbed. The rest
of high school just sucked.
So this blackout that
you had behind the wheel,
that was some sort of
after-effect of the coma?
Yeah.
Wow.
God, you've been through so much.
You're jealous?
What part sounds good?
The coma?
The hit and run?
I'm jealous
because you have all
this experience under your belt.
It makes you interesting.
But I didn't do it.
It wasn't me.
Great, so now someone
can kill me in my sleep.
How do you know it's one of us?
Well, I don't,
but none of you are talking,
and so I'm about out of options.
This isn't going to make
a damn bit of difference.
That's it.
No more sedatives.
Can you still function as a doctor?
For now.
Kind of busy here, Diana.
We just put the 4400s under, but we're
not sure if that's killed the signal.
Do you still feel amped up?
Yes, I do, okay?
I'm working on it from my end.
What's that noise?
I'm trying to counter
the effects of the signal.
If you'd just shut up for a second,
maybe I could find the right frequency...
Okay, calm down, Marco.
I need you to do this.
It always has to be me,
doesn't it?
Old, reliable Marco
does whatever you want.
I truly believe in what
we're trying to do.
The 4400 are the template
for the next stage in human evolution.
Do you mind backing up?
You're standing a little close.
We can recreate the technology
they used to change us.
Not by chanting "om"
three times, you can't.
Agreed...
But if you come to work with us,
we could get somewhere.
You know,
the government
has approached me
half a dozen times.
They seem to have
this bizarre theory I'm
the father of this new branch
of science. I turned them down.
I don't like working
with people with badges.
Listen, you can't blame
them for being curious.
You were in a mental hospital
for... six years?
The future busted its ass
to get you working again.
I haven't forgotten my debts.
Oh? What's that?
Signing bonus?
Fancy car?
Me.
I'm the poster boy, right?
Healing hands.
Unlimited access.
Can you really turn that down?
Mommy,
I'm scared.
I know, baby.
I'm scared too.
But it's going to be okay,
because mommy's here.
Okay?
Whatever's coming
through that door...
I'll protect you.
Tom.
Tom... put the gun down.
It's me. It's Diana.
No, you'll... you'll shoot me
if I put it down.
No, Tom.
I don't want to hurt you.
Well, I want to hurt you, Diana.
Tom... I said calm down.
My mom always wanted me
to hit it off with a cute doctor,
but make another move,
and I will pull this trigger.
What is that?
That'd be Marco
earning his paycheck.
I feel like an idiot.
It's just... Isabelle and I
were so close for so long.
And you still are.
I know.
It's like you say...
She's a baby.
It isn't personal.
Yeah, you just have
to remember that.
Hey, Ruth, look who's back.
That was a long lunch.
Yeah, sorry.
Time got away from us.
Come on. Here you are.
We'll be back in an hour for her.
- We'll be here.
- Thank you.
Bye, Isabelle.
I'd still like to do
a little house-hunting.
We could take a look around,
see what's out there.
You're in charge until I'm released.
Pool whatever manpower is still up walking.
Start picking up the pieces.
- I'll handle it.
- Mm-hmm.
All right. And you get
that head looked at.
How are you doing?
Well, for a slender lady,
you pack a punch.
I can't take all the credit.
Culp softened you up a little bit.
Hmm.
It's the final tally.
Three agents dead, two N.S.A.
operatives, a 4400...
concussions, broken bones,
stab wounds... yikes.
It's tough to swallow. It was
a major attack, and we weren't ready.
Yeah.
How are you, baby?
Okay.
Not so good.
I've got her on glucose
and erythromycin.
We're going to get her over to St. Michael's
and see if we can bring that fever down.
And the rash?
I'm going to bring in a specialist.
Should I be worried?
Brett Kellerman is one of the best dermatologists
in the city. I'm sure he'll figure it out.
You're coming with us,
right?
Of course. I'll be right there
in the ambulance with you.
All right, I'll get to the hospital
as soon as I can.
Okay.
- Oh, Max...
- Yeah.
Thank you... for everything.
No, thank you, for...
well, for not putting one
in the back of my head.
Uh, so those 4400s
Diana was protecting...
they're not going to see daylight until NTAC's
sure they're not responsible for this.
That's going to be
a marathon debriefing session.
Yeah, I bet you they'll
both be up all night.
Both?
I thought Diana said
there was three of them.
Tom?
She's gone.
A 4400 nearly took down
a fortified government facility,
and walked away
without breaking a sweat.
Do they even have
a name for that?
Yeah, "terrorism".
Payback is a bitch.
Welcome to the center.
Would you like to sign up for the tour?
No.
Tell Shawn Farrell that Kevin
Burkhoff is here to see him.
I'm sorry. Mr. Farrell's
busy at the moment.
Is there a message
I can pass along?
Yes.
I want to get
started immediately.
You can stay over if you like.
Get some dinner,
do a little studying...
Kyle?
Are you okay?
I don't deserve you.
That is so sweet.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Shawn...
this is Olivia Cohen.
Take a seat here.
Mm-hmm.
That's good.
She lost her eyesight to macular
degeneration 10 years ago.
The foundation was
very moved by her story.
Hi, Mrs. Cohen.
Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
So, uh,
what we're going to do here
is going to feel
a little weird, but
when we're done,
you'll be able to see again.
Oh, I can't wait.
I have to admit,
I'm a little nervous.
You don't have to be.
I'm going to take
your hands now, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Here we go.
So when does it start?
When do I see again?
Just give me a moment.
Shawn?
Oh...
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Is it warm in here?