We're not a threat.
We're salvation.
The world
will have to deal with us.
Previously on the 4400...
They just arrested a suspect
in the Collier killing.
Roy Marsden didn't kill
Jordan Collier.
And neither did you, Kyle.
Son of a bitch!
You go and you
tell your daddy
that he didn't kill anybody.
If Maia's having visions,
you should know about it,
and you should know
what they are.
Mommy's bosses
will be punished
for betraying us.
I want to go home.
I know you do, honey,
but Dr. Hudson is going to take
very good care of you.
Don't tell anyone
I can't heal.
Sure.
What are you going to do?
What I have to.
If you're sick,
the responsible thing
is to report to NTAC,
but if you are well...
walking into quarantine
is an easy step,
but walking out, that might be
considerably more difficult.
There's a synthetic substance
present in the blood
of every 4400.
They even gave it a name.
They call it...
... "Promicin inhibitor".
Every time
they came to NTAC medical,
every checkup.
Your daughter
is the Rosetta Stone
for understanding
what happened to the 4400.
We're her parents.
We decide.
Are you sure
you want to do this?
Just get me and Isabelle
someplace safe.
But if it comes down
to a choice
between the safety
of the American people
and the welfare
of the 4400,
Tom...
that's no choice at all.
We tried being reasonable.
In 10 hours,
we start rounding them up.
Easy, McCullough.
Let me go! I'm not sick!
There's nothing wrong with me!
We know that,
but you're a 4400,
and everybody's
got to go in.
Come on...
Now, I don't want
to cuff you,
but if you run again,
you're going to
give me no choice.
"Quarantine"
is just a word to you guys.
Try living it.
Come on.
What are we
doing here, Diana?
This is so wrong.
All right,
what do you suggest?
We walk into
the middle of NTAC,
and shout out,
"We did this.
We made them sick".
Yeah, yeah, that's good start.
We've got the medical records.
We can take them to Dennis.
You really think that Max Hudson
and a couple of rogue doctors
hatched a covert plan
to poison the 4400?
I mean, you really think
that they could do that
without approval?
Whose approval?
Dennis Ryland's, for one.
He was the head
of this division
when this whole thing
started.
I mean, you think
he didn't know?
Until we know
how far up this goes,
we've got to stay calm,
work quietly...
and watch our backs.
Don't tell me to calm down,
Lily.
How am I supposed to be calm
when my wife and daughter
left in the middle of the night?
We didn't leave you, Richard.
I just didn't feel
like Isabelle was safe there.
You've turned this
resisting quarantine
into your
personal mission.
NTAC turned it
into my personal mission
when they started
rounding us up.
And I admire
what you're doing,
but it's not my fight,
and I sure as hell won't let it
become Isabelle's fight.
Just tell me where you are.
Put my mind at ease.
I'll come see you.
Lily?
I'm sorry.
I just feel like
it's better this way for now.
I'll call soon.
That didn't go as well
as mommy hoped.
911. Please state
the nature of...
I need an ambulance.
I'm... I'm sick.
I've got this...
Hello?
Miss, are you there?
Never mind.
Think they're sharing
trade secrets?
Either that,
or she's asking
for her office back.
After you.
Thanks.
Nina.
Good to see you.
Thanks.
I wish the circumstances
were a little better.
We lost the first 4400s
to this thing
overnight.
Seven dead.
There'll be more
by day's end.
No word about a vaccine,
a cure?
I just got
off the phone with Hudson.
He said that they've worked
on a few things overnight.
I'm going to quarantine.
Diana...
I know this is frustrating,
but we've got
the best minds in the country,
in the world,
working on this.
Well, they better work fast.
Seven people are dead.
Alana could be next,
or Maia,
and still,
nobody has any idea
where this came from, do they?
We'll get it figured out.
Hey, sweetie.
It's me, Tom.
Who are you?
She was awake earlier.
Only for a few
minutes, though.
Did she say anything?
She talked about you.
Said you were going to
make everything okay.
I hope she's right.
Me too.
Let's go.
Where are we headed?
We've got
an appointment
with the good doctor
Hudson.
Diana, what...
what the hell
are you doing?
We've got some things
we need to talk about.
This guy your agents brought in,
Orson Bailey,
I think I can explain
how he developed this...
Jesus,
I can't even say the word.
Telekinesis.
Thank you.
The body produces four
main neurotransmitters.
They're like traffic cops
to the brain.
They control everything,
regulate everything.
Tell me something I don't know.
Bailey is producing
a fifth neurotransmitter.
We've never seen it before.
Nobody has.
I'm guessing
it factors into Bailey's ability
to bend spoons with his mind.
Let's just say Promicin
is basically a backstage pass
to the V.I.P. section of the brain.
He is using
parts of the cerebellum
no human has ever had access to.
I ran some tests
on the 4400s
who are still
in quarantine.
Every single one of them
is producing trace amounts
of Promicin.
So it's just a matter of time
before every 4400
develops telekinesis?
Promicin's behavior
is unpredictable.
They might not get telekinesis,
but they'll get something.
Put everything on paper.
I want to get
my talking points straight
before I try to explain this to D.C.
D.C. panicked.
I was ordered to work on a drug
to suppress
the production of Promicin
in the 4400.
Once I synthesized
the inhibitor,
we gave it to every 4400,
every time they came in
for a checkup.
But it doesn't even work.
4400s are developing abilities
all the time.
A small percentage of them are,
but if it wasn't
for the inhibitor,
they'd all have them.
I know it didn't
work perfectly.
"Perfectly"?
Seven 4400s died last night.
It was your inhibitor
that did it.
You made them sick!
You think
I don't know that?
We weren't trying
to kill anyone.
We were preserving
the status quo,
doing a good thing.
I guess it backfired.
I am trying to undo it,
but if you want to
pull that trigger,
please, be my guest.
Maybe then
finally I'll get some sleep.
All right.
If you're not going to shoot me,
let me get back to work.
I don't want anyone else to die.
Alison?
What are you doing here?
They're going to
give Roy life.
give him life,
and he's
going to take it.
What are you
talking about?
The state was going to go
for the death penalty,
and the public defender
convinced Roy
to take a plea bargain.
But they've got no case
against him.
My dad told me.
I don't know.
This lawyer,
he's handling, like,
10 different cases,
and he just
doesn't want to see
the inside
of a courtroom.
I don't know.
But he didn't do it, okay?
He didn't kill Jordan Collier.
You keep saying that.
Does your dad know something?
What?
Is there evidence
that they're hiding?
What?
You have to tell me.
If Roy takes this deal,
he can't even get parole
for 20 years.
He's not going to prison.
Why?
The 4400 came back August 14th.
Hudson discovered Promicin
October 11th.
So they probably gave
the first doses
of the inhibitor
sometime around
the end of the month.
But we have every
internal document
for october.
There's nothing
about any of this.
There's hardly even
a mention of Orson Bailey.
We both wrote reports
about him, Diana.
They're gone.
They were hoping
that was going to be
the only extrahuman ability
ever developed in a 4400.
If they destroy
all records of it...
nobody would ever know.
But this went to the top
of the food chain.
Here.
Britain, France, Korea...
... everywhere there's a sick 4400.
There has to be a paper trail.
Does it even matter?
I mean,
we could find a memo
signed by the entire
United Nations security council.
It's not going to cure anyone.
Diana, we delivered
confidential medical records
to Dr. Burkhoff.
We've got the so-called
"father of 4400 technology"
working on the case,
and you just
stuck a gun
to the head of NTAC's
medical director.
We've done everything we can
to get the right people
working on a cure.
That's if NTAC
even wants a cure.
Ryland's been talking
about people in D.C.
Who've been on a wartime footing
for months.
This is nothing
but a stroke of luck for them.
You think
they want them all dead?
I told you!
I told you
I wasn't safe here.
It's just a precaution, Kevin.
We think
you'll just be safer
if you move to
a less exposed location.
It's because
I told you
about that inhibitor
thing, right?
I spent six years
in a psychiatric hospital
suffering from paranoid
personality disorder.
As soon as I get out,
you two put me
smack in the middle
of a massive
conspiracy.
Dr. Burkhoff's been spinning
all kinds of stories about NTAC.
Very interesting stuff.
Well, he can spin
all the theories
he wants,
just not here.
I'll make sure
he has a safe place to work.
I figured out what Promicin is.
That's the name they gave
the neurotransmitter,
right?
The one that gives the 4400
their abilities?
And if I can find
one 4400
that hasn't been exposed
to the inhibitor,
I think I can neutralize it.
Hey.
You scared me.
Why didn't you use
your key?
Oh, sorry.
My hands were full.
I brought you guys
some supplies.
You still like chocolate cherry?
That sounds great. Thank you.
Oh...
... you okay?
Yeah, just jumpy.
It's so quiet out here.
Yeah, a lot of places
have closed up for the season.
Oh, I thought that, uh...
maybe I could stay for
a little dinner or something.
You don't have to
get back home?
No, not really.
Carol's gone.
She found out
that you and I were talking.
Don't worry,
she doesn't know you're here,
but she got mad.
Brian, I'm sorry.
She'll stay away
for a few nights.
I'll stay on the couch
for a while...
but in the meantime,
Heidi's staying with a friend,
and I figured,
why eat alone?
Sure,
but I hope
you're not expecting much.
I haven't made pot roast
in a while.
You know, Lily,
the truth is...
I never
should have married Carol
in the first place.
What are you doing, Brian?
Come on.
I'm alone.
You're alone.
You and Richard aren't happy.
That's not true.
We could have it back, Lily.
Don't, brian.
Why are you
fighting it?
Brian, stop it!
Let me go!
I don't want to hurt you, Lily!
Stop it!
You little bitch.
Hello?
Lily?
Are you okay?
Brian?
Yeah, I was going to
bring by some food.
Don't.
Something's not right here.
I haven't heard
from the safe house
in wheeling
for a day.
We have to assume
it's been compromised.
That's the third one
that's gone silent.
They're picking us off
one by one.
We might want to think
about fighting back.
We can do that, Richard.
We certainly have 4400s
that can do some damage,
but once
we take that step,
there's no turning back.
Excuse me,
but shouldn't there be
bars on these windows?
The point is
to be unobtrusive,
Dr. Burkhoff.
Well, this seems
a little lax to me.
Most of you are 4400s.
I'm a collaborator.
You know what they do
to collaborators?
We need to get him working.
It calms him down considerably.
We cleared out a room for you.
Anything you need,
just let us know.
What I need is a clean 4400,
one that hasn't been exposed
to the inhibitor.
I don't guess
you've got one of those, do you?
Actually, I might.
20 years,
I've never seen you pour a drink
on government property.
I never supervised a round-up
of innocent citizens before.
Conscience bothering you,
Dennis?
Hell, yes...
... it is...
... and given the circumstances,
I'd say that's a good sign...
... but I'm trying to focus
on my job, Tom...
... and I need the same from you.
But sometimes when you...
you look for one thing,
you...
you learn something else.
You know how it is, Dennis.
I know exactly what you mean.
I've learned some things
myself.
Open it.
Knowledge is a burden, huh, Tom?
Did you think
that I would release Kyle
from quarantine
and not keep an eye on him?
Why didn't you stop this?
Because I didn't know
exactly what Kyle
was going to do.
I just sort of let the future
play out.
Isn't that what
you're always talking about?
You set up Roy Marsden.
That was my gift to you, Tom.
Would you rather
I just turn these over
to my bosses?
I would rather
you be the friend...
you be the Ryland
I worked with for 20 years.
I haven't changed.
I have a tough job,
and I'm doing my best,
and as your boss,
and as your friend,
I expect support.
Kyle hated quarantine.
I wonder what you think of prison?
They know.
NTAC knows
you shot Collier.
What? How?
They've known all along.
They let it happen.
I need you to be ready
to get out of here.
I'm going to call
Alana's friends.
You're sending me to Spain?
If they come after you,
I need you to be ready
to leave right away.
Did you hear Roy Marsden's
being sent to jail for life?
They set him up.
But if I run...
... just one thing at a time, Kyle.
Let me worry about you,
then I will deal with Marsden.
So you want me
to start packing?
Yeah, Kyle!
Aren't you hearing me?
He committed suicide?
I know that Max was under
a lot of strain, but...
He had
all those people's lives
in his hands.
Maia's...
I know,
but Dr. Pinero's been
Hudson's number two
from the very beginning.
He knows everything
that Hudson knew.
We're still going to
beat this thing.
Good morning, Tom.
Nina.
Here.
I grabbed this
out of your mail cubby.
Did you hear
about Hudson?
Yeah.
You okay?
They're calling it
a suicide.
What are you calling it?
Tom, look at this.
It's from Max.
"Firewall memo".
What is that?
I don't know.
Why are you doing this,
Isabelle?
Mommy needs to know.
I brought you here
so we could be safe.
Don't you want that?
Lily, what's going on
out here?
You okay?
No. Go away!
I told you not to come here!
That's why I'm here.
Lily, please, let me in.
How do I know you're real?
What are you
talking about?
Of course I'm real.
Did Carol leave you?
Why would she leave me?
Lily, I'm coming in,
okay?
No. No!
No!
Lily... whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Lily...
put down the knife. Please.
I just came
to check on you guys,
make sure
you were okay.
Look, it's me.
Brian.
Put the knife down.
Lily, we're all going to die.
Is that what you want?
No!
Stop it, Isabelle!
Lily, I heard screaming.
What is going on?
Brian...
if you're real,
you've got to get me out.
Isabelle
doesn't want to be here.
Firewall...
it's a program,
a safety net.
That's how
you keep viruses
off your hard drive.
Okay, did you ever see a memo
with the word "firewall"
written in the subject line?
No, but I don't read
most of the memos
that circulate
around here anyway.
Look, how long
are you guys
going to be
working in here?
What, are they painting
your offices?
We need a little privacy, okay?
Tom, this memo,
whatever it is,
I doubt it ever went out
on a general distribution,
and every copy probably went
through the shredder
months ago.
So if there's no hard copy,
and if Marco is the only one
we even trust
to even
talk about it with,
then we're at a dead end.
We could always
march into Ryland's office
and ask him about it.
The guy does know memos.
When he was working here,
I must have thrown away,
like, 15 every day.
More like 20.
He liked to
keep his keyboard burning.
Who, Ryland?
Yeah.
He didn't type.
He used to
call me in sometimes
when he froze up
his computer.
Hunt-and-peck city.
Took him 10 minutes
to type in an email address.
Ryland dictated everything
to his secretary.
She had "L" level
security clearance.
Look.
"D.R. /J.O."
Everything says
"D.R.", Dennis Ryland.
And "J.O." is Jane Orman.
She worked for him
for 22 years.
Did she stay in Seattle?
Say hi for me.
Lily.
You came back.
Are you all right?
I thought I was doing
the smart thing,
but Isabelle...
What happened?
She just wanted to be with you,
and this place...
I don't know.
Hey.
Did you miss daddy?
Yeah?
Well,
he missed you.
Both of you.
Listen, I'm, uh...
I'm going to take off.
Brian...
thank you...
for everything.
Hey, uh...
... do me a favor...
... forget this address...
... forget about all of us...
... and I'll forget...
... you drove off with my wife...
... in the middle of the night.
Good luck, Lil.
Hey, I've been
calling you all day.
There's a guy here
who thinks that Isabelle...
... excuse me.
Didn't anyone hear
that car pull up...
Is that her?
I think
there's somebody here
who wants to meet you.
This is Isabelle.
What are we
supposed to say?
"You know that
massive conspiracy
to suppress the abilities
of the 4400?
We were just kind of hoping
you would fill us in
on the particulars".
Yeah,
"And don't be nervous,
but we had to shake
a government tail
on the way here to do it".
Yeah, sounds
like a start.
Tom Baldwin.
Long time, Jane.
Do you remember my partner,
Diana Skouris?
Of course.
Yeah. Hi.
I always wondered
who would show up.
I should have figured
it'd be the two of you.
You're here about firewall,
right?
The inhibitor
hasn't been tested.
It is not ready.
One of the 4400
is a serial killer
who was using,
I don't know,
some kind
of mind control
to get people
to commit murder.
The inhibitor's ready.
This is wrong, Dennis.
We are beyond
right and wrong here!
There's no precedent for this.
Now, D.C.'s been advised
of the operation.
It's been approved
at the highest level.
There is nothing further
to discuss, is there?
I am not doing this.
I took it home with me
that night.
The next day,
I put in my notice.
I mean, you have to understand,
for two decades,
I thought that Dennis Ryland
was the finest man I ever met,
and after I read this,
I couldn't work for him anymore.
I kept telling myself
I should send it somewhere...
... the newspapers, or...
... I don't know...
... but the names
that signed off
on this...
... I was just a secretary.
What could I do
against those names?
It's all here.
Did you see the names?
When Maia said,
"mommy's bosses are
going to be punished",
I had no idea she meant
all the way up
the chain of command.
We can't go public yet.
What?
Listen, the faster
this gets exposed,
the better it is
for Maia, Alana, Shawn...
... all of them.
No more secrets.
No more relying
on the people who did this
to find a cure.
At the very least,
they're going to
have to rescind
the quarantine order.
Diana,
Ryland's got something on me.
Ryland?
This entire memo
is over his signature.
What could he possibly
have over you?
He knows
Kyle killed Jordan Collier.
What?
That night on Highland Beach,
they put someone inside of him,
or some program...
... I don't know...
directing his actions,
and Ryland has evidence.
I'm sorry, Tom,
but I can't just sit on this!
Maia's getting sicker!
Just give me one hour, Diana.
Just one hour.
Please.
Stop saying that.
It's not okay, Kyle.
If I go through
with this,
they're going to
come after you,
and it doesn't matter
if you're in Spain
or Siberia.
I know, but with all those lives
at stake,
you have to do it.
Okay, I'm taking you
to the airport.
Dad...
I'm not going anywhere.
This actually makes it easier.
I didn't know
how I was going to tell you.
Tell me what?
I can't live like this anymore.
I can't live
knowing that guy is in jail.
I go through every day
trying to pretend
it's all normal,
but it's just a cover-up.
I can't let you do it, Kyle.
Marsden shot at me.
He, uh...
he shot at other cops too.
Even if you confess, Kyle,
he is still going to jail.
You try to bury stuff like this,
it changes you.
Look what it did
to your boss.
Ryland used to be your friend.
It's over, dad.
No more lies.
I can't do it anymore.
I just can't do it.
Okay? You can't stop me.
Okay?
Don't you do anything
until I get back.
You hear me?
This is the right thing,
the heroic thing,
and being a hero
comes with some perks.
You tell me
what I need to know,
I'll see that
you're transferred
to a private
quarantine facility
this afternoon.
You can
walk the grounds,
you can choose
your own meals...
what's wrong with that?
139 Lebanon Street.
That's where
they told me to go.
The inhibitor
is piggybacking
on glucose.
It enters the brain
through facilitated
diffusion.
It's a binding protein.
That's how
they did it...
I'll take your word for it.
But this serum
has pure Promicin in it.
It can neutralize the charge.
The inhibitor won't be able
to cross membranes anymore.
We can flush it
out of their systems.
So once it's gone,
the disease goes away?
Please.
Stop saying "disease".
For the last time,
it's a side effect.
Remove the inhibitor,
the immune system functions.
It'll happen
virtually instantly.
So this substance...
Promicin.
It's what makes you people
unique.
How did you get it
out of my daughter?
She has trace amounts of it
in her bloodstream.
Before the inhibitor,
you all did.
That's how they found it...
... in the first place...
... but...
... she's an infant.
I could only draw
enough blood...
to make one shot.
If you can get that
into quarantine,
one shot might be all you need.
Nina, where's Ryland?
A 4400 gave up
the Seattle safe house.
They're on their way
to take it down.
Excuse me.
Please don't shoot.
Dr. Burkhoff,
why would we shoot you?
I have no idea,
but I'm feeling
a little insecure right now.
I brought something
for you.
Whatever you do, don't drop it.
Everybody in this house
is subject
to quarantine and arrest
under emergency order 74.
You have five minutes
to come out peacefully.
If not,
we'll come in and get you.
There's an army out there.
Ryland!
Call it off.
It's over.
Quarantine. Everything.
Agent Baldwin
is obstructing justice.
Arrest him.
I don't think so,
Dennis.
I know about firewall.
Keep your weapon on him.
You're really willing
to give up your son?
Kyle's turning himself in.
He can't live with the cover-up.
When I wrote that memo,
we had no idea where
the 4400 were from
or why they were
brought back.
Dr. Hudson
gave me information.
I acted on it, Tom.
If you were in my chair,
you'd have done the same thing.
Hi.
I've got some
medicine for you.
To be honest with you,
I'd rather be giving this
to Maia,
but a crazy neuroscientist
told me
that that was not
the right thing to do,
so if you don't mind
holding still
for a minute...
you saw Orson Bailey
up close and personal.
Oliver Knox.
You know what these people
were capable of.
Hell, I attached your reports
to the memo
when I sent it to D.C.
But we learned better, Dennis.
Highland Beach?
"Save the future"?
Heartfelt message, Tom,
and while they were
giving it to you,
they were
programming your son
to commit murder.
Does that sound to you
like they were
guiding us toward eden?
I don't know,
but I sure as hell
don't want to go
where you're taking me.
Goddammit, Tom!
What does it even mean,
"save the future"?
Save the future how?
Kill us all?
Start over
with a smaller,
more evolved
population?
Is that an outcome
you can live with?
What can you
live with, Dennis?
Was Max Hudson really a suicide,
or did you pull
that little string too?
And what about me,
Dennis?
Because if you're
holding on to any hope
of keeping this covered up,
you're going to have to start
by putting me in the ground
right here and right now.
Tom, you're reducing
the fate of the planet
to a question
of your personal faith.
Without the inhibitor program,
who the hell knows
what'll happen?
Who the hell ever knows?
Very wise.
Pithy.
But if the world
turns out to be a place
of unchecked
4400 abilities,
I hope we don't live
to regret it.
Stand down!
We're done here.
You can all go home now.
Thomas.
Alana.
What happened here?
A miracle.
Welcome home, baby.
Home...
I never even unpacked.
We'll take care of that
right now.
Where's Kyle?
I can't wait
to see him.
Yeah, I told him
you were coming home.
Hey, Kyle!
We're back!
Hey, Kyle.
Man, I never thought
I was going
to see you again.
You're okay, right?
I feel like I did
15 keg stands last night,
but yeah,
pretty much.
We all are.
Dr. Burkhoff
took blood samples
from the people that I healed.
Every sample he gets
cures someone else, so...
hey, you guys
kind of lucked out, huh?
"Lucked out"?
There's 23 of us dead,
and they don't even have
a final count yet.
I don't think that was
part of the plan,
you know?
That's not why
they brought us back.
This whole idea
that there's some kind
of plan...
I don't know.
I wish
I could believe that.
Just trust me when I say
that there's a plan,
it's important,
and every 4400 is a part of it.
Shawn...
I killed Jordan Collier.
What?
I bought a rifle,
I went up on that roof,
took out two government agents,
and then I shot him.
Remember
when I was in trouble?
Losing chunks of time?
That's what I was doing.
Planning out an assassination.
Why?
You think I know?
There's something inside me,
Shawn...
or someone.
It takes over.
Those people
who took you?
If they have a plan,
it includes
me killing Jordan Collier.
That's not true, Kyle!
Then why did they
make me do it?
Why did they
ruin my life?
I'm about
to go to prison
for the people
you worship.
You murdered Jordan?
I didn't mean...
I didn't even know
what I was doing, Shawn.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Kyle...
Stop... Shawn...
what are you doing?
Stop it.
You're killing me.
Shawn...
I'm freeing you.
Freeing.
Freeing...
Just hold on.
It's working.
Hold on.
I'm going to get it out of you.
Just hold on.
Hold on, Kyle. It's working.
You really
didn't have to do this,
you know.
Actually...
I really think I needed to.
What?
Well, you're supposed to say,
"I wanted to".
Yeah.
Don't push your luck.
Whoa.
Uh, looks like they're talking
about charging these people
with murder.
Ryland. The whole crew.
Looks like
mommy's going to get
a whole bunch of new bosses.
Well, I hope they go away
for a very long time.
I'll be in the front row
at the hearings.
Guess I have to buy a suit.
I'm going to be
sitting next to you
until the whole thing
is over.
Nothing's over.
It's just starting.
Sweetie,
what are you talking about?
What's starting?
The war.
Kyle...
I'm ready.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I'll come with you.
Isabelle?
Hello, Shawn.
I'm Isabelle.