Torchwood, outside the government,
beyond the police.
Tracking down alien life on earth,
arming the human race
against the future.
The 21st century is when
everything changes...
and you've got to be ready.
This programme contains
some strong language.
Hello there.
Apologies for the
unplanned touchdown,
just hit some rotten turbulence.
I'm Captain Jack Harkness.
Diane Holmes, pilot.
Is this some sort of secret base?
You must show me round one day.
Everything all right?
How long before we head off again?
My Uncle's expecting me.
When did you leave?
About half an hour ago. Which date?
Today, December the 18th.
Which year?
Which year? I need to know.
1953.
There's no need to be frightened.
Who are you exactly?
The least you know about us,
the better.
Meet the team. Toshiko.
Gwen. Doctor Owen Harper.
John Ellis.
Emma Louise Cowell.
Diane Holmes.
Please, follow me.
At least it wasn't a spaceship
full of aliens.
That might have been easier.
But how can you travel
50 years in half an hour?
Your aircraft slipped through
a transcendental portal. A what?
A door in time and space.
It's some kind of trick,
it has to be. Tosh?
Celebrations of the Millennium
in your respective home cities,
photographs documenting the
development of Cardiff Bay
from the '50s to the present day,
blueprints of modern day aeroplanes.
But if all this is true...
then how do we get back? You don't.
According to history, your plane
never returned. I'm sorry.
What's going to happen to us?
Never mind about us.
What happened to everyone else?
Our families.
Your father died in 1959. He was 48.
Dad said he'd die young.
All the men in the
munitions factory did.
Your mother lived
till she was 81 though.
I know this is hard to take in.
But is there anyone else?
My son, Alan Ellis.
He was born on the 6th of April,
1937, 14 Park Place, Grangetown.
He might still be alive.
The archives in the '50s
weren't that well documented.
We'll try again tomorrow.
Right now,
you need to get some sleep.
Friends?
Boyfriend?
Not really. Never stayed
in one place long enough.
It's a bit basic.
Not when you've slept in barracks.
I was going to close a deal
on a shop in Dublin tomorrow.
What do you trade in?
Food, knick-knacks, essentials.
What are you after? Bit of music.
RADIO PLAYS
BEETHOVEN'S MOONLIGHT SONATA
There's photographs
of my family in here.
I'll see what I can do.
Don't worry, Captain Harkness,
I'll look after the ladies.
Call me Jack.
DISTANT LAUGHING
Who else is here?
Couple of young girls. Pretty dress.
Thank you. I made it myself.
Where are you from? Bristol.
What were you going to Dublin for?
Auntie Nora's ill and Uncle Finn
can't manage the children.
It will be good practice for when
I have children of my own, Mum says.
She's gone next door
so Uncle Finn can telephone...
She'll know I'm missing by now.
Emma, she found out in 1953.
Over 50 years have passed, remember?
What will she think happened?
It must have been like one of those
murders where they never
find the body.
They seemed to think the plane
went down in the sea.
These will be your means
of identification.
We've set up bank accounts for you
but we'll give you
an allowance so you can practice
with the currency and
money management. David Ward.
Sally-Anne Hope.
Deborah Morrison, and it's
spelt how Deborah Kerr spells it.
Your background stories
should incorporate your skills.
John, you could have run
a corner shop.
No. We can fake references.
You can't take away our names.
For God's sake,
it's all we've got left.
It's my son's name,
it's the name above my shop.
You're right.
I didn't think.
You should keep your name.
I'd suggest you use £25 for your food
and then £20 for luxuries like
cigarettes, magazines.
My dad only made £10 a week!
Things are a lot more expensive now.
How did it do that? It's automatic.
It knows you're there. But how?
There are wave bouncing detectors
which emit radio waves
and then look for reflections...
Bananas! Of course,
bananas are far more interesting.
Look at all this!
We'd just come off rationing in '53.
Yes, sorry,
we are a consumer society.
It's bloody fantastic.
How much food money have I got left?
£15.40.
£12.10. You'll ruin your teeth.
You sound like my mum.
They sell films in boxes
and you can watch them at home.
I love going to the pictures.
Good God.
Welcome to the wonderful world
of scantily-dressed celebrities.
"Super Excel Waterproof
Luscious Lashes Mascara".
I've got to have that.
There's children around.
She's a children's TV presenter.
So you like the musicals?
My best friend, Kate, and I
saw Calamity Jane five times.
I've got the LP.
You all right?
What does that mean?
I'm just going to take a look
at the stadium.
You girls stick together now.
I'll be back for supper.
Excuse me. Do you know a man called
Alan Ellis? He used to live here.
No, sorry, mate.
I'm going to check on the plane
this afternoon.
Want to come?
I'm going to watch this.
And maybe make some paper chains.
Wonder what work
I can get in aviation.
I'm going to have to find a husband.
LAUGHTER
All right?
I'm Alesha, this is Jade. All right.
I'm Emma. Diane.
Excuse me, have to get ready.
Where d'you get those shoes?
They're lush.
Thanks.
Hello, old girl,
d'you miss me?
I've been reading up on you.
England to Australia in four days,
1952, that is impressive.
Yeah, terrible wind
across the Bengal Bay.
Something you ate?
So, how did you get into this?
Ferried planes during the war.
Of course, when it was over,
we were supposed to revert to
being dutiful wives and daughters.
But I'd got the taste for it. No
pig-headed man tells me what to do.
Ah.
"Sky Gipsy"?
After the engine.
The de Havilland Gipsy Six -
a work of genius.
Tuned with a higher compression
ratio to squeeze more energy
from its fuel mixture.
Can I take her up?
No, you could get arrested.
You haven't got a licence.
But I...
Bugger, it's no longer valid.
I guess I'm just another
pig-headed man
telling you what to do.
Well, you'd better make it up to me.
I want to learn
all about this new world.
Blackpool were 3-1 down, then
Stanley Matthews worked his magic -
scored two goals
in the last 20 minutes.
Bolton lost 4-3.
My boy was on his knees,
punching the air...
The FA cup final
live in my own living room.
I charged the lads a shilling each
to come and watch.
Ever the business man, eh, John?
That's an American accent, isn't it?
That's right.
So how did you end up here,
doing whatever it is that you do?
It's a long story.
I'm a slow drinker.
You know everything about me.
What's the problem?
Gets kinda complicated.
What, did you fall through time too?
Yeah, you could say that.
Sorry, mate,
you can't smoke in here.
What are you doing Christmas Eve?
We could go carol singing.
THEY ALL LAUGH
I'll be getting hammered.
Where are your families?
No idea. We grew up in care.
Like a children's home?
I haven't got anyone else either.
What happened to you?
My parents are dead,
so I came down here to start afresh.
So they didn't leave you
a house or anything?
No.
I've got nothing.
Were you close to them?
Yes.
I loved them very much.
Must have been an awful Christmas
for them, thinking I'd drowned.
I just want to know
what kind of life he had, my son.
He might have kids.
I could be passing my own
flesh and blood in the street.
Find him, Jack,
he's all I've got left.
Cheers.
What? I'm waiting for you
to pull out my chair.
Let me get this straight.
You expect equality AND chivalry?
I don't see why they should be
mutually exclusive.
Well, if it makes you happy.
Your chair, ma'am.
Thank you.
So what other strides
have women made?
Well, on the strange but true,
how about this,
you don't have to have sex
to have kids any more. What?
How come?
Get yourself inseminated, with a sort
of syringe, cheery little process.
Seriously,
men donate sperm anonymously.
A little shuffle into a pot
at a sperm bank.
And they say romance is dead.
Oh, come on,
I wasn't born yesterday.
No, but for a bird who's going on 90
you look pretty hot.
What was your favourite song?
Well, it's hard to say.
I know what mine was.
# I just blew in from the windy city
The windy city is mighty pretty
# But they ain't got what we got
I'm tellin' ya, boys! #
What do you think you're playing at?
I thought I could trust you
to behave.
Where do you want to go now?
Well, I'm in your hands.
Well, we could go back to mine.
You could read up
about yourself on the net.
That sounds like a line.
It's not a line,
I'm not chatting you up.
Not because I don't think you're
attractive,
but because I wouldn't want you to
think I was taking advantage of you.
Got any Scotch?
I don't see why she got you
involved. She was upset.
She was drinking.
I only had half a glass.
Enough to make a show of yourself.
We're not meant to draw
attention to ourselves.
We're not the same as them.
We can't trust anyone.
Will you be OK now, Emma?
Don't worry, I won't let
her out of my sight again.
I don't like liver.
Sit down, young lady, and be
grateful for what you're given.
And why should I listen to you?
Emma? Only my dad
gets to talk to me like that...
and I'm never going
to see him again, am I?
Or my mum,
or my best friend,
or my dog and I miss them...
and I hate this filthy,
stinking place!
I never had this sort of trouble
with my son.
Woman have been to space too, y'know.
You've got a lot of
catching up to do.
Do you have a girlfriend? No.
So who do all those beauty
products belong to? Me, actually.
No?
Oi, real men can moisturize too,
you know.
It's not very homely here.
No, I'm not here that much,
it doesn't seem worth the effort.
You smoke too much.
So I gather.
Amelia Earhart...
she disappeared in 1932.
Do you think she's
still out there somewhere?
No, doubt it.
One in a zillion chance,
you ending up here.
A whole new world.
Oh, it's not so bad,
once you get used to it.
I reckon you'll fit in just fine.
I'm glad you haven't got
a girlfriend.
Me too.
# ..Come around
and knock me down again
# Worry
# Oh, worry, worry, worry,
worry... #
I take it that
wasn't your first time?
I had a lover.
He was married.
And you didn't care?
Well, I was free to do what I liked
and I didn't have to cook
and clean for him.
It suited me.
I'm not exactly marriage material.
I always thought the '50s were
uptight, sexually repressed and...
You didn't invent it, you know. Oh?!
Can we do it again?
Don't see why not.
We could have an affair.
We could be fuck buddies.
What's a fuck buddy?
It's, um,
it's a friend that
you have casual sex with.
There's nothing casual
about what we just did.
Oh, no, no, I didn't mean that.
Sex shouldn't be devalued.
Both parties should give it
100% concentration.
Because when you
take off together...
It's the next best thing to flying.
SHE SCREAMS
Emma is my auntie's step-daughter.
She meant to spend Christmas in
Cardiff with a friend
but they had this awful argument
last night and she rang me.
Got my number from Mum.
The thing is, she doesn't really
want to go back home so I thought...
I thought maybe, she could stay with
us. We've got a lot to catch up on.
For Christmas?
GWEN MOUTHS
I'd better get a bigger turkey.
Thanks. This is Rhys,
my long-suffering boyfriend.
He lives here.
Don't your parents mind?
Emma's parents are a bit religious.
Oh, better not tell them
you saw my morning glory then, eh?
The thing is I couldn't tell him
your parents were dead.
He'd ask too many questions.
The thing is, he doesn't know
exactly what I do.
We can't expect John and Diane
to look after her.
They're strangers.
I had to take her in.
Diane didn't even come home last
night. I think she was in a B&B.
I'll take her job-hunting later.
Jack, John's son.
I think I've found him.
Come and meet Alan, though I'm not
sure how much help he'll be to you.
Alan,
there's someone here to see you.
He's a nephew on your father's side.
He's been tracking down
the family history.
Is Sally coming?
Sally's his wife.
She passed away a while back.
Sorry, this isn't
one of his better days.
What's wrong with him?
Alzheimer's.
What's that? He's senile.
He doesn't remember who he is
most of the time.
Couldn't live at home any more.
He'd leave hobs on,
forget to dress, you know.
He never had any children so there
was no-one there to look after him.
That's you and your dad
playing footie out the back.
That's your dad and your mum
and your new television set.
When can I go home?
You're not well enough, love.
I don't like it here.
They took my clothes.
I'll have a word, they're in the
wash. Keeps me going, this one.
What did he do, for a living?
Was he in retail?
I think he was a fireman.
That's what I did.
In the war.
£60 for half an hour!
No worries. I'll pay.
A Cessna!
Oh, it's my first plane.
I bought one after the war,
they've hardly changed.
Dream to fly.
We'll soon get you back
behind the...throttle.
Thanks, Owen.
Matthews did three set-ups
in 20 minutes,
then Bill Perry
cracked home the winner.
You said he had wings on his feet
and that's why he was
called a winger.
You used to say clever
things like that. Blackpool won.
Yes!
Alan, it's me, your dad.
I bought you that football annual
you wanted for Christmas, Alan.
It was in my desk drawer.
Alan, please...
Everything all right?
He remembered who won the FA Cup
final when he was a boy.
He sometimes remembers
snippets from his childhood.
It's quite common with dementia.
When's Dad coming, Mum?
I'm not your mum, love.
Alan?
Who are you?
John's witnessing the end of
his world, the end of his line.
And we can't help.
There's no puzzle to solve,
no enemy to fight...
just three lost people who have
somehow become our responsibility.
Best I can do is Friday 29th,
three o'clock.
Can't you take her up today?
Fully booked.
It's all right, I've flown
for years. I can go on my own.
Not without a licence, sorry.
Maybe you could cancel someone?
We'll pay extra. I couldn't
do that do my regulars.
Look, it's fine.
Book me in for the 29th.
It's Diane Holmes.
Diane, I'm really sorry.
I should have called ahead.
Oh, for goodness' sake,
this is so silly.
It's just I was
really looking forward...
Ignore me. Let's get out of here.
MUSIC: "I See You Baby"
by Groove Armada
Do you think
she'll be all right though?
I don't think she's even had a proper
boyfriend. Stop fussing.
She'll be fine, man.
What was that for?
For putting up with me.
I deserve a lot more for doing that.
Oi! Hands off!
Go back to your friends, good boy.
What are you playing at?
I wouldn't let him do anything.
You might not have had much choice.
Gwen, you're over-reacting.
I was just having a kiss
and a cuddle.
He was after a lot more than that.
This is...disgusting.
I just want you to know that people
are more sexually aware these days.
Then maybe you'll be more careful.
Mum said that no man wants to marry
soiled goods. Attitudes have changed.
As long as it's safe and between
two consenting adults, no-one cares.
So...how many men have you
done it with?
A few.
Were you in love with all of them?
No. Sex can just be about
having a good time together.
If you're in the right mood,
with the right guy, it's the best,
no big deal.
So if I meet a boy and we get on,
and he wants sex,
then you think I should let him?
No, no, that's not what I said.
What are you saying?
Sex...is nothing to be ashamed of.
And as for you, well, your first
time should be with someone special.
Do you wish you'd waited for Rhys?
He's your special someone, isn't he?
Yes... Yes, I suppose.
And I bet sex with him
is better than with the others.
Well...
I will wait for Mr Right, I think.
I'm really not the kind of girl
who sleeps around.
I'm going to brush my teeth.
Thanks for the chat.
Not a problem.
Leave it.
I can't if I want to fly
a jet plane,
because that's all flying is now -
pressing buttons.
You used to have to know
how to fix an engine,
how to gauge the wind but...
Leave it.
Open this.
Oh!
It's beautiful.
Well, how did it go?
This coat I'm wearing is their
latest fashion, '50s inspired.
They offered me a job on the spot.
Oh, that's brilliant. Oh!
Now we need to find you a flat
near here.
The shop's in a new branch in London.
I've always dreamt about
working in a London fashion house.
They open the day after Boxing Day.
I'll be a shop girl
and a trainee buyer.
I can house share. They've given me
numbers.
London's a big city.
That's what my mum used to say.
There's no rush.
There's nothing to keep me here.
I'm sure we can find you
something in Cardiff.
You keep looking.
Need to make a plan, get work,
get my driving licence.
It will all help. Thanks, Jack.
I was looking for a bus timetable.
Want to get out to the DIY stores,
see if there's any work going.
Best of luck! Thank you.
Where are you taking me?
We're here.
Bear with me.
We have had such a girly day
shopping.
What's up?
Your mum rang.
Funny thing,
she's no idea who Emma is.
No? And I'm thinking back
to you and me on the couch...
Work calls, you go out
in the middle of the night
and come back with
a surprise relative.
So, let's have it,
who exactly is Pollyanna?
Ah, is it to do with work?
It's so hard to explain.
Do you even know her?
She was lost.
I'm sorry.
What worries me is how easy it is
for you to lie to me.
It's my fault.
I'll leave by tomorrow.
You don't have to go.
She's 18 years old.
I couldn't turn my back on her.
It's like two separate worlds -
there's Torchwood,
and then there's real life.
That's why you've got to let me go.
I, er,
couldn't help noticing you standing
out here in that beautiful dress.
This beautiful dress
is a gift from my lover.
Then he is a fool
to let you go out in it alone.
What shall we drink to?
Chance meetings.
# Oh, the good life
# Full of fun
# Seems to be the ideal
# Mm, the good life
# Lets you hide
all the sadness you feel
# You won't really fall in love
# For you can't take the chance
# So please be honest
# With yourself... #
Let's go home.
# It's the good life
# To be free
# And explore the unknown... #
MOBILE RINGS
# Like the heart aches
# When you learn
you must face them alone... #
Hello?
My car keys are missing.
John was behind the counter
earlier on
and I can't get hold of him.
He's gone home.
John!
Let me go!
You can't just throw it away,
not without trying.
I'm not as strong as you.
You don't understand.
I do. I was born in the future.
Lived in your past.
My time is gone too.
Why are you doing this?
Speaking to me in bloody riddles,
keeping me here when my wife
is dead, my son is a shell.
John, you're still young.
You can get work, make friends,
start a family.
I did all that, Jack.
Years ago.
When I was meant to.
I wish I could say something.
There's nothing to say or do.
I can't leave you here.
Then we'll wait.
The sun will rise,
we'll have some breakfast,
take a walk.
Yes.
A new day.
And I'll suffer it all
and smile and wag my tail.
And then,
as soon as your back is turned,
I'll make sure I do it properly.
Because I want to die.
You don't get reunited, John.
It just goes black.
How do you know?
I died once.
Who are you? A man,
like you, out of his time,
alone and scared.
How do you cope?
It's just bearable.
It has to be.
I don't have a choice.
But I do.
If you want to help me,
let me go with some dignity.
Don't condemn me to live.
Are you scared?
Yes.
You're very quiet.
I don't know if I can
do this anymore.
This isn't how it works for me.
I've slept with enough women,
I've done the fuck buddies thing.
This is not it.
I can't concentrate.
All I see is you,
all I can think about
is what you're wearing,
what you're thinking, what your face
looks like when you come.
It's been, what, a week?
And it's like,
when I'm not with you,
um, I'm out of focus.
How have you done this to me?
I'm scared.
I'm fucking scared.
I love you too.
The thing about love...
is that you're always
at its mercy.
Emma, these are your tickets, OK?
On the back is your seat number,
keep this with you at all times.
I've also got you
a return just in case.
Now don't go talking to any
strangers and phone me as
soon as you get there, OK?
No!
I'm not letting you do this.
I'm not a possession, Owen.
You can't do this, it's madness.
If I listened to everyone
who told me that,
I wouldn't have broken any records.
You don't have to go.
If I don't, then I'll always
wonder what it's like.
London, Gwen.
You're not thinking straight,
let's talk about it.
No, I'm sorry.
We can make this work.
You belong here now, with me.
I belong in the sky.
Well, we can get you up in the sky.
Soon you can fly whenever you want.
Look, weather conditions are
the same as the day we arrived.
That rift will open again,
I can feel it.
Diane, listen to me,
there is no way back.
You cannot get home.
Then it will take me somewhere new.
Merry Christmas!
I'll come with you.
I fly solo, Owen.
I go faster and further than others.
We have no idea how this rift works.
You can end up anywhere.
That's the beauty of it.
It's too dangerous! It's what I do.
What about me?!
Please, please, don't go.
What memories I'm taking with me.
Merry Christmas.
'Because
when you take off together,
'it's the next best thing
to flying.'
Somebody's not only kidnapping
weevils, they're causing them pain.
These guys are using weevils
to carry out the perfect murder.
You want to release a weevil
in the middle of Cardiff?!
I've been having sex
with someone else. His name's Owen.
Who are you, Owen Harper?
We're gonna hunt you down
and we're gonna make you surrender
that creature that you kidnapped.
Out there in the darkness,
something is coming.