This programme contains
some violent scenes.
'Torchwood - tracking down
alien life on earth, arming the
human race against the future.
'The 21st century is when everything
changes and you've got to be ready.'
Suzie Costelloe. Why did you
kill those people? The more I used
the glove, the more I control it.
If I could get it to work all
the time, it could resurrect...
I loved this job. I really loved it.
At last. You must be Torchwood?
My team bitch about
you all the time.
And you are? Detective Swanson.
I'm Captain Jack Harkness.
So I've heard. Are you always this
dressy for a murder investigation?
What, d'you rather me naked?
God help me, the stories are true.
So who's the victim?
That's victims, plural.
Yesterday, a man was murdered at
96 Oakham Street, Alex Arwyn, 28,
single, estate agent, here we go,
that's from the scene of crime.
Today, in here, we get two more,
Mark and Sarah Brisco, both 33,
married, he's a surveyor,
she works in education.
What about the smears of blood?
Is that writing?
Work in progress. Come inside
and see the finished thing.
Oh, my God...
Looks like somebody
wants your attention.
They've got it.
We found a few of the killer's
hairs from the first murder.
Lab results should be in soon.
Good, we'll need that.
Now, if you could just clear
the room? Some of this equipment
is strictly need to know.
It was only a matter of time.
What was?
Torchwood walks all over
this city, like you own it.
Now these people are paying
the price - ordinary people,
ripped apart, with your name
written in their own blood.
From where I'm standing, you did
this, Captain Jack Harkness.
You did it.
Still, at least
we've got a head start.
If it's someone we've pissed off,
that narrows it down to...
ooh, four or five million.
And that's just the humans.
Tosh, how we doing?
There's no record of Mr and
Mrs Brisco on our database.
Nor yesterday's victim, and no
link between him and the Briscos.
No connection between any of them.
Jack? They've got the results
on the killer's hair.
Initial findings say,
Caucasian male, early 40s,
smoker, drinks tequila.
Doesn't match any DNA profiles.
Only thing of interest
is a compound we've never
seen before. Recognise it?
Oh, we're in trouble. What is it?
Compound B67.
You're kidding? Retcon.
He's got Retcon in his blood.
B67, aka Retcon, aka the magic
ingredient of the amnesia pill.
And this belongs to us?
This killer is somebody
we gave the amnesia pill to?
Is he remembering
that he's a serial killer?
Or is he becoming a serial killer
because of the Retcon?
Wait a minute. I've taken Retcon.
Then better stay away
from sharp objects.
Ianto, how many people have
we given amnesia pills to?
2,008. Hey, what if they
all become psychotic?!
D'you have to sound so happy?
I'm just saying. Mean Streets!
Tosh, narrow the list
down to fit Swanson's profile,
start checking them out.
You two, there's got to be a link
between the victims, find the link,
find the killer. Get to it!
Jack? If there is a link, why don't
we just ask the victims ourselves?
Not the right time for a seance,
thank you very much. The first time
I met Torchwood, you had that glove.
Heh-heh, no way!
Not after what it did to Suzie.
It brings people back to life. We
could question the murder victims.
That's exactly what she said.
She was one of us, we trusted her
and she's dead cos of that thing.
The glove stays in
the safe where it belongs.
These murders are happening
because of Torchwood.
So Torchwood has got to
do something.
It fell through the Rift
about 40 years ago.
Lay at the bottom of the Bay
till we dredged it up.
I always figured,
this wasn't just lost.
Whoever made it,
wanted rid of it.
You know, we never
gave it a cool name.
I thought we called it
the resurrection gauntlet?
COOL name.
What about the Risen Mitten?
I think it's catchy.
Jack? You OK?
Don't forget, the maximum
resurrection time is two minutes,
and that was only cos Suzie
had practice.
The most we're likely to get
is 30 seconds. Tosh, ready?
Ready.
And, recording.
This man was victim number one.
Name - Alex Arwyn.
Come on, Alex. Come back.
How does it work?
You just sort of feel.
Like reaching into the dark.
Finding the dead.
I can't... I don't...
Ah.
Damn! Ah!
Ah! Nothing!
Sorry.
Never was very good
with this thing. Owen?
I tried last time.
We all had a go, it only responded
to Suzie. Well, I never had a go.
It's cold.
It warms up.
The glove relies on some sort of
empathy. Maybe compassion and...
Just be yourself.
BEEPING
SHE GASPS
Somebody help me!
Oh, my God, help me,
help me, help me! Alex!
I need you to listen to me.
Somebody help! HELP ME!
Alex, you were attacked. Do you
know who it was? Who attacked you!?
Who are you? How long?
- Where am I?
- 15 seconds.
Who are you? I'm trying
to help, sweetheart.
I want my mum.
Please! Let me see my mum...
REPETITIVE BEEPING
FOLLOWED BY PROLONGED BEEP
He's gone. Let me keep trying.
Gwen, he's dead.
I can bring him back. The glove
only works once. I can do it,
let me try. Gwen. Look at me.
He's gone.
That was amazing,
she's a natural. 24 seconds!
Give Ianto a stopwatch, and he's
happy. It's the button on the top.
What d'you think, Gwen?
D'you want to stop?
Recording.
Victim number two - Mark Brisco.
Oh God, I can feel him, it's like a
rope from my heart to the glove...
Oh, it's so warm.
Hey, there. Just look at me.
Look me in the eye. That's it.
(Where am I?)
You've been hurt,
we don't have long, we need
to know who attacked you.
(Is my wife all right?)
We're looking after her.
Now Mark, who was it?
(It was that man. He belonged
to Pilgrim, he went to Pilgrim.)
What's Pilgrim?
(Oh my God, he had a knife.)
No, Mark, he's gone, we don't have
long, quickly, what was his name?
35 seconds.
(Max.) Never knew his surname.
Trying Pilgrim and Max,
get a description.
You gotta give us something more
so we can catch him. He's going.
There was...
There was someone who knew
him better... That woman...
She was always talking to him...
What was her name? Where's my wife?
Her name! Suzie.
REPETITIVE BEEPING FOLLOWED
BY PROLONGED BEEP
One minute five seconds.
Jack? Did I hear that right?
Could be anyone,
there must be lots of women called
Suzie. Not connected to this case.
We've been talking
to the wrong corpse.
Pilgrim. A religious support group,
more like a debating society,
meaning of life, does God exist?
All that stuff. The point is,
it was tiny, more like a hobby,
run by Mark Brisco's wife, Sarah.
She had all that
stashed in the wardrobe.
Handwritten and photocopied,
that's why we couldn't find any
records, she wasn't even online.
No mention of Suzie, or Max?
Not a word.
She didn't even keep a register.
It wouldn't be our Suzie, though.
She wouldn't go to that support
group bollocks. How do you know?
I mean, were you friends?
Any of you?
Who was her best friend
in this place?
She sort of kept herself to herself.
Well, then.
If she needed to talk, maybe
that's exactly where she'd go,
a group of complete strangers.
Could be. You've got a point, Gwen.
Time we got to know our deceased
colleague a little better.
Have I got this right?
When I die,
you get to keep all my possessions?
My whole life's gonna
get stashed in a locker?
Rules and regulations.
What if I leave all
my stuff to Rhys?
We'll stash him away, too.
Tread carefully, people.
With respect.
This is the life of Suzie Costello.
That's all we are, in the end.
A pile of boxes.
Is her father still alive?
Don't know.
But you must've looked him up?
To tell him his daughter was dead?
When Suzie left Torchwood,
she was on the run.
She wiped all her records.
I couldn't retrieve her files,
she was good at computers.
Huh... She was good at everything.
She was good at murder too.
Laugh a minute, that was Suzie.
What's that?
A book.
Emily Dickinson.
Poet.
Jack.
Pilgrim.
She's part of it.
That proves it, then. No choice.
It's time Suzie came back.
Do we all get frozen?
Torchwood staff, when we die,
do we all get kept?
Rules and regulations.
How long for?
Forever. Recording.
Have you got your stopwatch? Always.
I'll record from my station.
I'm sorry, but I don't want to look
her in the eye. Sorry.
Anyone else?
Any advice?
Yeah, I know. Empathy.
Even though she did try to
kill me. You and me both.
SHE GASPS
I'm getting a reading.
No, it's gone...
SHE BREATHES HEAVILY
Just...memories.
Nothing living. She's too far gone.
What do we do now? Nothing we can do.
That's it.
We're out of options.
There's always the knife.
When she killed all those people,
she always used the knife, it's made
out of the same metal as the glove.
We've seen it before,
metallic resonance.
The glove works better if
the knife's part of the process,
like closing a circuit.
Then let's use it. Small detail.
The knife was used to kill people.
She's already dead.
So we kill her again.
Ianto?
Life knife.
Anything?
No, there was just a sort of
spark and then it was gone.
I'm sorry, Jack.
You're gonna have do it properly.
What the hell.
SUZIE AND GWEN GASP
Suzie? I've gotta go!
I can't stay, they know.
Just look at where you are.
Think back, try to remember...
Suzie! Suzie! Look at me!
Jack. Oh, my God.
There's a knife in my chest,
did you kill me?
You killed yourself, remember?
But... Oh my God, I shot myself.
We've got to ask you about Pilgrim.
No. Wait a minute.
Didn't I kill you?
Never mind that,
we need names and details.
Who's using the glove? I'm sorry.
Oh, wouldn't you know it,
Gwen bloody Cooper. 30 seconds.
When you were in Pilgrim
you gave the amnesia pill to
a man, Max, do you remember?
What? You brought me all
the way back, just for Max?!
We need to find him. Who is he?
What's his surname?
He was...
some loser... We're losing her!
Stay here. Damn you!
Don't force it, Gwen. She's not
getting away this time, stay here!
No! I told you to stop!
It's all right, I've got her,
I've got her...
Hold on... OK, pulse. She's all
right. We need to get her out of
here. Can you give me a hand?
It's the glove,
I told you they get hooked.
All right, don't make
a fuss, it's over now.
Um, excuse me. I'm still counting.
There's not much point, she's dead.
No, according to the
equipment, she's unconscious.
What the hell's going on?
Oh, my God. He's right.
She's alive! Suzie's still alive.
Look at her, she's bloody breathing!
She can't be...
Nope.
Still breathing.
No stopping her. She won't die.
One minute thirty and counting.
MACHINE BEEPS
How long's it been?
Three months.
When can I die?
I just want to go.
Can't you leave me alone?
You seem to be stuck.
But...
Am I gonna stay like this?
For how long?
Don't know.
Can I see my father? No.
You wiped your records.
We had no trace of him.
So, he doesn't even know that I'm
dead? Well, you're not any more.
This is sick.
You started it.
Right now, we've got an
investigation underway.
Pilgrim.
You visited these Pilgrim meetings
and gave an amnesia pill to someone
called Max. How do we find him?
What for? What did he do?
He was just an ordinary bloke.
We think the Retcon
triggered a psychosis.
He's started killing.
How many victims? Three. Same as you.
We need to know, how much
Retcon did you give him?
Owen. Hello.
Scared to face me?
(SIGHS) You frighten
the shit out of me, yeah.
What about Toshiko?
Is she still here?
Yeah, she's here.
All the gang. Happy days.
But the amnesia pills,
how many did you give him?
One a week. Every week.
For two years.
Christ! No wonder.
What the hell did you do that for?
I just...
I wanted someone to talk to.
About this place.
It was driving me mad.
And he was just...
He listened, that's all, he listened.
Every week, as soon as I'd finished
talking, I'd give him the pill.
You overdosed him.
I didn't know that!
Keep getting it wrong, don't I?
Is that why you brought me back? Did
you think I wasn't guilty enough?
What was his surname? I don't know.
All I ever did was talk about me.
It's all my fault, isn't it?
Never bloody stops being my fault.
Can't you just let me die?
You don't get off that easy.
Yeah, you did warn me,
right at the beginning.
He said, "This is the one
job you can never quit."
Then let's get to work.
Come on, Suzie!
Just like the old days.
There's gotta be something.
Hold on... There's someone missing.
This girl came every week,
student, blonde...
She's not in these photos.
Who was she? Lucy.
Lucy Mackenzie.
Said she worked at a club.
Which one?
Uhhh...
Come on, Suzie?
Which club?
For God's sake, this Max is killing
every single member of Pilgrim.
Now tell me, Lucy Mackenzie,
where did she work, which club?!
Wolf.
The Wolf Bar.
POUNDING ROCK MUSIC
Cover the exits.
Bloody hell, like I didn't have
a banging headache already.
That's the glove, Gwen.
Gets inside your mind.
Yeah, all right Suzie, stop
creeping me out. Just tell us, any
sign of Max or this Lucy Mackenzie?
Nothing yet. Keep moving round.
Keep alert, people.
To repeat, Max is described as 40,
six-three, six-four, stocky, short
dark hair, tattoo down his left arm.
That narrows it down.
Can't even look at me, can you?
It's not like you
to be so judgemental.
Not like you to go
on a murder spree.
All right, so it
drives us mad, this job.
God knows, I've done
some stupid stuff.
But now, I've got to keep
on working, every day,
in a job that's got a bit
less honour, because of you.
Wait, I've got a match on that guy.
Where is he?
Northwest Bar. Show me.
Owen, get in closer,
which one do you mean?
Wait, he's going over for the...
Wait, I've got a match on our
girl, Lucy Mackenzie, the student.
That's her, that's definitely her.
It's too late, he's going over.
Got the bastard!
That isn't him.
Gwen! Behind you!
That's one for Ianto.
Risen mitten, life knife
and that old classic,
stun gun. Come on, let's get him
out of here. You saved my life.
Maybe I came back for a reason.
SIRENS WAIL
OK, so your name is Max Tresillian,
can you confirm that?
You live at 106 Endeavour
Terrace, is that right?
Parents, Sandra and Dave, yeah?
You're inside the
Torchwood facility.
GROWLS
And five, six...
Keep watching.
Soon as we reach ten...
Just stops dead.
If this is a drug-induced psychosis,
it's a very specific one.
Like he reacts to
the word Torchwood.
Thanks, Jack.
Sorry.
But if that's caused by
Retcon, we've got a million
more problems on the way.
Let me know what the scan says.
But, what about Suzie?
What are you gonna do with her?
No idea.
What do you think?
You're the boss.
Torchwood!
GROWLS
Can't you ask Jack?
Just one favour?
I want to see my father.
Tell us where he is,
we could bring him in.
I'm not letting him
anywhere near Torchwood.
If he's still alive.
What's wrong with him?
Cancer.
All that waiting, and
then I go and die first.
I could contact him on your behalf.
And say what?
So, tell me. Since I've been gone,
you enjoying it?
Yes. Well, you know,
this place is sort of...
It's mad, isn't it? Insane.
Bloody nuts. Best job I ever had.
Me too. And the worst.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Funny thing is, you always
imagine when you're dead,
they're gonna miss me at work.
Indispensable!
But look what happened.
I got replaced...
..by someone better.
You got that glove working,
better than I did. Just got lucky.
No, it's more than that.
The others, they prefer you.
Don't say that.
You got my job.
Almost like you planned it.
Except I didn't.
And I'm sorry, but I've got
my own function at Torchwood
and I'm a lot more
than just a replacement.
Have you slept with Owen?
There you go,
replaced me completely.
I had a boyfriend who used
to walk into rooms like that.
The grand entrance.
It got kind of boring.
Although, he was one of twins, so
I put up with it. Twin acrobats.
Man, I gotta write that book.
Maybe even illustrate it. I can talk
for a long time, a very long time.
Takes me a while to piece
things together. Meaning?
Suzie had the glove.
You put her in charge of it.
But tell me, Jack, did you
ever ask about her father? How do
you mean? He's got cancer.
He's been dying
slowly now for years.
And what do you do? You give
his daughter the one device that
brings people back to life!
Is it any wonder she got
obsessed? Oh, so is this all
my fault?! Well, isn't it?
Did you ever stop and think?
Did you...
Did you ever look at Suzie?
Did you ever...
think what that glove
would do to her, did you?
Right from the start,
you thought that Suzie's
death was because of you,
Cos it happened when you arrived.
Then you brought her back
to life, all the way,
because you wanted it so much. OK!
We're both responsible!
Now, what the hell are we going
to do with her?! I don't know.
What if she never dies?
Have you thought of that? Like...
Undying, forever. Just you and her.
No way. Could be.
I wouldn't wish that on her.
I'd sooner kill her right now.
Could you, though? Kill her?
Yeah. Really? Oh, yeah.
'Jack, can you come to the
conference room? Something I need
you to see. Kind of urgent.'
I was going over Suzie
and Gwen's medical records.
I ran them through the filter.
Watch the footage.
This is the moment when Gwen brought
back Mark Brisco, the husband.
See?
Now look at his death. See?
The energy flow stops
just as he's about to die. But...
have a look at Gwen with Suzie.
Whoa.
What is that?
Energy.
Life.
But with Suzie, it's a permanent
connection and she's getting
stronger. It's still going, now.
She's draining the life out of Gwen.
There's always a price.
More coffee? Is that all you do?
Just leave me alone.
Have a biscuit, at least.
Go on.
Just for me.
The wearer of the glove
can bring somebody back, but
loses their own life in return.
How do we stop it?
We've got to kill her.
Suzie's got to die.
Again. Who's gonna do it?
Like you said.
I'm the boss.
Toshiko! Where the hell's Suzie?
And where's Gwen?
Interrogation Room.
No they're not... Find them, fast!
I can't see them.
Hold on. Scanning. Nope.
Nothing on internal scans.
What's going on, where've they
gone? Just keep looking... Bring
up the SUV. Still there.
I'll try exteriors...
What about Gwen's car?
What's she doing?
Getting herself fired.
Unbelievable. How stupid is that?
Thinking she could just drive off.
Come on. Let's go get them.
What the hell...
Ianto?
Ianto? Captain!
What happened?
I thought you must've done it.
We've gone into lockdown.
Then reverse it! I can't.
It's 100%.
The doors are sealed.
We're locked in! I'm taking you
to see your dad and that's it, OK?
Sorry.
I must be mad.
Jack's not stupid.
He's gonna catch us.
Oh, you never know.
We might get lucky.
Everything's gone. Computers,
mobile coverage, the lifts,
everything... We're sealed in.
How long does Gwen have
before she dies? Two hours,
maybe less. Come on! Think!
If Suzie set up the lockdown, how
did she do it? Entered an override?
She's officially dead,
she wouldn't get access.
Then how did she do it?
What the hell did she do?!
There's got to be an answer.
Suzie couldn't physically
start the lockdown,
Gwen wouldn't have let her.
But there's no-one else! Wait
a minute... We've got a guest.
..Stopped for me
The carriage held but just
ourselves and immortality
Because I could not stop
for death... Is that a poem?
I wonder. Emily Dickinson?
But what does it mean?
It's a verbal trigger.
Say it out loud, maybe repeat it 100
times over and the Hub locks down.
But if that's part of the system,
Suzie must've installed a vocal
command programme, way back.
Back when she was alive, yeah.
Max is just a Trojan horse. Suzie
planned this right from the start.
'Do you see? Max, the Retcon,
everything, it's all been a hoax
to get us to resurrect Suzie.'
She gave Max a whole complex
of subconscious triggers.
Like, she dies,
Max becomes a time bomb...
He doesn't see her for three months
and, wham, the orders kick in.
He follows Suzie's program,
and starts killing.
And the whole chain of events
forces us to bring Suzie back.
And then she escapes! That is not
bad! I'm picking her for my team.
If she could lockdown the Hub,
she must've installed
a way of reversing it.
A bit more colour in your cheeks.
It's all thanks to you.
That night...
my last night on Earth,
or so I thought...
..before I shot myself, I shot
Jack right through the head.
I killed him, stone dead and
then he just stood up and lived.
Am I right? Did that happen?
Gwen? Yes, it did.
So he can survive a bullet
through the head? Yeah. How?
I don't know.
He won't explain it properly.
Said something happened
to him a while back. He said...
He said he can't die.
Not ever.
And he makes judgments about
whether I'm allowed to live.
It's all very easy for
Captain Jack, isn't it?
Do you ever wonder? What?
Who is he?
All the time.
DIALLING TONE
I've got reception, sir.
How do you do that?
We're sealed off! Just used
the Water Tower as a relay.
Nice work, Ianto!
But who the hell do we phone?!
PHONE RINGS
Detective Swanson.
Who is it? Torchwood.
You'd better not be wasting my time.
I was wondering if you could
do us a favour. The humble police,
helping the mighty Torchwood?
Why don't you just help
yourselves? Like you normally do.
Because we can't. Why's that?
Why don't you just help
yourselves? Like you normally do.
Because we can't. Why's that?
We're sort of busy.
Well, I'm busy too,
try someone else. No, no, no...
It's just because we can't at the
moment because we're sort of stuck.
In what way? We're locked in.
You're locked in?
Just a bit. Locked in where?
Um. In our own base.
You're locked inside your own base?
And it's not funny.
And how am I supposed to help you,
exactly? We need a book of poetry.
'It's NOT funny!'
Oh, God, driving at night...
GWEN SWITCHES RADIO ON
# Just a little... #
Oh, my God.
I don't know this one.
It's ancient.
My Mum used to sing this,
when I was a kid.
All those years ago...
# O-o-o-oh, soleil, soleil... #
..before I died.
# Soleil, soleil
# O-o-o-oh, soleil, soleil... #
All right, Captain Jack,
just say that one more time.
Nice and clear.
LOUDSPEAKER: We're locked in our
own base and we can't get out.
LAUGHTER
OK, you've had your fun.
Listen, Detective Swanson,
one of our team is in danger.
Right, you lot, back to work...
OK, we've got it.
The Complete Poems,
it's gonna cost you 20 quid.
What does the book say? Er, I don't
know, what am I supposed to do?!
Find I Could Not Stop For Death.
Read out the next verse.
What if it doesn't work?
Read out the whole book.
It's gonna be a long night.
Tired?
I'm fine.
Don't want you falling
asleep at the wheel.
One corpse is enough for this
car, thanks. Don't say that.
What? Corpse. Cos you're not.
What am I, then?
I dunno, you're just not, though.
When you're dead...
I mean, when you die...
What happens?
What do you want me to say?
The truth. Really?
Tell me.
You religious? Just sort of
in passing, you know.
Do you believe in Heaven? I dunno.
Yes, you do. What do you believe?
Stupid, but I always
sort of think...
Like, you know,
white light and all that.
And I think of my Gran.
Like she'll be there.
Waiting for me.
The smell of carbolic.
Your faith never left primary school.
So what's out there?
Nothing.
Just nothing.
But, if there's nothing,
what's the point of it all?
This is.
Driving through the dark.
All this stupid, tiny stuff.
We're just animals,
howling in the night,
cos it's better than silence.
I used to think about Torchwood,
all those aliens, coming to Earth...
What the hell for?
But it's just instinct.
They come here cos
there's life, that's all.
Moths around a flame.
Creatures clinging
together in the cold.
So when you die, it's just...
Darkness.
And you're all alone?
There's no-one else?
I didn't say that. What do you mean?
Why do you think I'm so
desperate to come back?
There's something out there...
in the dark...
..and it's moving.
Parting is all we know of
heaven and all we need of hell.
No, try another.
Success is counted sweetest
by those who ne'er succeed.
Christ, she was a bundle of laughs.
Success is counted sweetest by
those who ne'er succeed. Nope.
Wait a minute, just had a thought...
If words cause the lockdown,
maybe numbers reverse it...
Try the ISBN, every book's
got a different number.
You getting this? Yup, hang on,
I'm looking... Read it out.
The keyboards aren't working. The
membrane might recognise the code.
OK. Got it!
ISBN 019 8600 585.
That's it! Everybody,
move, move! Cathy, thank you.
Pleasure!
I've got the tracker on
Gwen's car. It's a hospital.
Giving you the co-ordinates now.
On the way. How long's she got?
It's only a guess, but I'd give
Gwen about 40 minutes.
Kathy, I want the road
ahead clear. I'm gonna break
the speed limit, big time.
All units, give Torchwood priority,
repeat, give Torchwood priority.
MACHINE BEEPS
Suzie... I don't, em... I'm not...
Oh, my God, this headache, it's...
What's happening to me?
I'm sorry, Gwen.
You're getting shot in the head.
Slowly.
And believe me, it hurts.
Almost better.
Completely gone, soon.
No!
No, no, no...
Dad?
GWEN CRIES
It's me, Dad.
Wake up!
Dad? It's Suzie.
Hello, Dad.
Ow!
And goodbye.
What are you doing?
BEEPING
Oh, that's worth coming back for.
Sending him into the dark.
Just what the bastard deserves.
They're moving again. Can't predict
a specific destination, not yet.
Keep feeding it through,
we're catching up.
PHONE RINGS
Hello?
Did you like the poem, Jack?
Suzie, don't let her die.
The glove is killing Gwen
and keeping you alive. I know.
Then stop. But I get to live.
Why would I stop? For Gwen's sake.
She replaced me.
Now, I'm doing the same
to her. Isn't that fair?
Suzie, we've got a tracker
on that car, we're gonna
catch up, I promise.
And what happens then?
If she's dead, then I'm gonna
kill you, Suzie Costello.
I promise, I'm gonna kill you
for the last and final time.
But would you?
When there's a part of her
that's now me?
Could you really do that
if I'm the only thing left of her?
Why are you doing this?
Because life is all, Jack.
You should know.
I'd do anything to stay.
Anything.
Suzie. Please. Just stop.
She's a real find, this one.
Gwen Cooper.
She's better than me.
She's so much better.
I was never any good.
Jack, I'm sorry.
SUZIE!
Jack, she's heading for
the coast line on the B587.
It's a place called Hedley Point,
there's some sort of ferry, goes
out to the islands. Get a move on.
Owen, how long we got?
Minutes.
It's beautiful, Gwen.
Can you see?
We'll take the ferry.
Go out. As far as we can.
Keep on running
cos he won't hurt us.
We'll keep on going, you and me...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Have you gone? Gwen?
Can you hear me? Gwen?
Poor Gwen Cooper.
Safe journey.
Let her go.
I can't.
Let Gwen go. I can't.
Owen, how is she?
Owen! Report!
I think we're too late.
If I kill you, does she live?
But you can't, Jack.
Cos look at me.
I'm the last thing left of
Gwen Cooper, can't you see it?
Just the smallest bit of her?
Not one bit.
Owen? Anything?
Nothing. But I broke the connection.
I killed you. Can't die.
Never gonna die.
How much more of this do you want?
It's all your fault, Jack.
You recruited me.
The glove. Tosh! Destroy the glove!
It's keeping them connected!
Ianto, armaments, code five.
Captain, my captain.
Do you want to know a secret?
There's something moving in the dark
and it's coming,
Jack Harkness.
It's coming for you.
Whoah! Whoah! It's OK.
It's OK, it's OK, it's OK.
SIRENS WAIL
# If I should die this very moment
# I wouldn't fear
# For I have never
known completeness
# Like being here
# Wrapped in the warmth of you
# Loving every breath of you
# Still my heart, this moment
# Or it might burst
# Could we stay right here
till the end of time?
# Till the earth stops turning?
# Wanna love you
till the seas run dry
# I found the one
I've waited for. #
Thanks for doing this.
Part of my job, sir.
No, I should be doing it, but...
One day, we're going
to run out of space...
If you're interested...
I've still got that stopwatch.
So?
Well. Well, think about it.
Lots of things you can do
with a stopwatch.
Oh, yeah.
I can think of a few.
There's quite a list.
I'll send the others home early.
See you in my office in ten.
That's ten minutes and counting.
Oh, Jack?
What do you want me to say
on the death certificate?
Good question.
She had quite a few
deaths in the end.
I don't know.
Death by Torchwood.
I'll put a lock on the door,
just in case she goes walking again.
Nah, no chance of that.
The resurrection days are over,
thank God.
Oh, I wouldn't be too sure.
That's the thing about gloves, sir.
They come in pairs.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd