This programme contains some
strong language.
Torchwood. Outside the
government, beyond the police.
Tracking down alien life on earth,
arming the human
race against the future.
The 21st century is when
everything changes
and you've got to be ready.
MOBILE RINGS
Dad? I dunno, hour and half, tops.
I'll be there soon as I can.
I can't hear you.
The signal's going.
Hello?
Are you all right?
Come on!
CLATTERING
METAL SCRAPES
Leave me alone!
BANG
SHE SCREAMS
SCREAMING CONTINUES
I hate the countryside.
It's dirty, it's unhygienic.
And what is that smell?
That would be grass.
It's disgusting.
Seventeen disappearances
within the last five months.
Police are clueless.
Now there's a surprise.
No offence, PC Cooper.
The last known whereabouts of
each one is somewhere around here.
All within a 20-mile radius.
Anything else linking them? None
of the bodies have ever been found.
These people just fell off
the radar. No patterns in age,
sex, race.
One minute they're here, the next...
boof. Gone.
The rift doesn't spread
out this far. Does it?
We don't know that much
about it to be certain.
And it's increasing in
activity all the time.
Come on, aliens aren't gonna
bother hanging around out here.
Probably some sort of
weird suicide club with people
choosing the same spot to end it all.
God knows, if I had to spend too
long up here, I'd want to top myself.
Here you go.
Careful, they're hot.
Sure you don't want anything, Tosh?
Really sure.
A friend of mine caught
hepatitis off a burger
from one of these places.
We'll start with the most
recent victim, Ellie Johnson.
We last have record of
her making a phone call.
She dropped out of signal mid-call.
The coverage map has her placed...
somewhere about here.
Looks as good a place
as any to set up camp.
Sorry, did you say camp?
What's the matter with a hotel?
People are going missing round here.
D'you really wanna stay in
a place run by strangers?
Cos sleeping outside
is a lot safer(!)
No other race
in the universe goes camping.
Celebrate your own uniqueness.
What am I supposed to do with this?
Need a hand getting it up, Owen?
If I did, I wouldn't ask you.
Some pieces are missing!
No. I checked.
HEAVY BREATHING
Oh, come on! It's just a bit of fun!
Who was the last person you snogged?
See! You even sound
like an eight-year-old!
Who the hell says "snog"?
Mine was... Rhys!
Yeah, well, there's a surprise.
Tosh, your go. It's easy for you!
Oh, come on! Spill the beans!
Owen. What?
Really? Tosh, in your dreams.
3am, Christmas Eve,
in front of the Millennium Centre.
Waiting for a cab. I had mistletoe.
Christmas?! You've not had
a snog since. No.
Well.
Lucky me, eh?
So who was yours?
Gwen, actually.
When was this?
It was complicated.
Didn't take you long to get
your feet under the table.
What?
So was it just a kiss, or...
Tosh, leave it.
Jack?
Are we including non-human
lifeforms? Oh, you haven't!
You're a sick man, Harkness!
That is disgusting!
I never know when he's joking.
It's my turn, is it?
It was Lisa.
Ianto, I'm sorry...
Sorry she's dead?
Or sorry you mentioned it?
I just didn't think.
You forgot.
We should get some firewood.
I'll give you a hand.
Couldn't you have kept
that to yourself?
What's the matter, you embarrassed?
You're such an arrogant
shit sometimes, Owen!
That was a good kiss. It was
borderline great. So good, you've
been avoiding me ever since.
Country air's making you delusional.
How long did it last? Ten seconds?
But the things I can tell
from that kiss. Oh, like?
Like your sex life ain't up to much.
You what?!
Y'see old Rhys makes the
earth rumble, but he don't
make it move, does he?
You might want to shut
up before I lamp you one.
When was the last time
you screwed all night?
When was the last time you
came so hard, and so long,
you forgot where you are?
Doesn't happen with him,
does it? You're too familiar.
Whereas, you and me,
we're not cosy at all.
We'd be amazing!
And that scares the shit out of you.
Someone's watching us.
Through the trees.
50 yards north.
I just saw them move.
You got your gun? Yes.
You go to your left.
I'll go right.
Three...two...one.
BIRD FLIES OFF
Bollocks! How did we lose them? Owen.
Well, it's not Ellie Johnson,
that's for sure.
This is a male, late 40s, 50s.
Wasn't killed here. No blood
spatter or signs of a struggle.
Must have been brought here after he
died. Why do that? It's not like
they've tried to bury him here.
Maybe you disturbed them and they
ran away. Maybe it's a warning.
Whoever's responsible
marking out their territory.
Cause of death? Impossible to say.
The body's been stripped of
the flesh and bodily organs.
Could the Weevils
have come out this far?
No, Weevils don't finish
off their victims like this.
CAR ENGINE STARTS
Is that ours? Yeah.
All right! I've said I'm sorry!
Basic security protocols, Owen!
Oh, get off your high horse, Tosh!
I was carrying that stupid gear.
What, the whole time? and then I was
trying to put that bloody tent up.
And then... Yes, I sort of forgot
that I'd left them in there.
But I'm sorry.
I'm human. I ballsed up. Looks
like that body wasn't a warning.
More of a decoy.
That would mean we've been
watched since we've arrived.
Tosh, can you get a tracking signal?
Already done. I took the liberty.
It's currently 3.4 miles
west from here.
Gunning at ninety, no doubt. You
steal a piece of equipment like that,
you drive straight on till morning.
Actually, no. It's been stationary
for the past four minutes.
I'd go so far as to say it was
parked. There's a small
village in that area.
Other than that, nothing for 30
miles. Call me suspicious, but this
has all the hallmarks of a trap.
Yeah, I was just
thinking the same thing.
Anyone fancy a walk?
Why would anyone want to live
out here? Has the SUV moved?
Not for an hour now.
HEAVY BREATHING
Tosh, Ianto - follow
the signal, find the SUV.
Owen, Gwen...
Let's see
if there's any room at the inn.
Pint of best please, love.
And em, yeah, get one for yourself.
Where is everybody?
SHE RETCHES
You OK? In there.
That burger coming back to haunt
you?
Oh, my God...
Gwen!
Jack please...
something's going on here.
Let's take a look in here?
Come on.
One, two, three...
What is it?
There's another body in there.
Same as the other?
What did this, Jack? Cos whatever
it is, it can't be human.
How far is this going to spread?
Stay focused. I should be
having dinner with Rhys.
What am I doing here with you?!
Don't you ever get scared, Jack?
Huh?
There's another two houses.
We'd better take a look.
Whatever they were,
I hope you put up a good fight.
It's just half a mile up here.
Least we've still got this.
Rest of my stuff was in the vehicle.
DISTANT YELP
What was that?
Just a...fox
or something.
Check round the back. Yeah.
ANIMAL YELP
We should carry on straight up there.
Tosh!
Locked? Locked.
Gwen! Gwen!
Gwen! Gwen.
Put the gun on the floor!
PUT THE GUN DOWN ON THE FLOOR!
I thought you were them!
I thought they'd come back for me!
Thought who had come back for you?
WHO?!
Gwen...Gwen!
Gwen, what's happened?
A kid hit her with a shotgun.
I got you, I got you.
Move, move!
Get in.
OK, I'll check upstairs.
Owen! Owen! Bet you thought
you'd never be glad to see me!
Right... Help me!
Listen, listen, I'm going to
have a look at your wound now, OK?
Just keep calm.
Hands off, hands off. OK.
No, don't please!
Right, it could've been much worse.
Hold this apply pressure.
Oh, Jesus! The bullets are lodged
near the surface.
You've been bloody lucky, girl.
Another inch to the left
and any one of your vital
organs might've been... Anyway.
D'you want a quip about
feeling a small prick?
No, but thanks for offering.
Here we go.
All done. GOD!
Let's get these pellets out, eh?
Right, there's gonna be
a certain amount of residue.
So just lie back
and think of Torchwood.
D'you miss being a doctor?
Excuse me,
I still am a doctor.
I just don't deal with
patients any more, that's all.
It's ideal.
That was the bit I always hated.
You beauty.
Come on. I'm good.
Not bad.
What's taking Tosh and Ianto so
long? Jack, the SUV might be locked
up. Or they could be dead!
Well, everyone else is. Sit down!
Tell us what happened here.
It's not human. Look,
my mum won't know what's happened.
They're expecting me
back for the weekend.
Look, we'll get you home OK.
What are you going to do?
You can't fight them.
They're too strong. The only thing
we can do is barricade the door.
No! We'll make base at the pub.
Should we go after Tosh and Ianto?
Not till we know what we're dealing
with. But what if it's too late?
They're not children.
They know what to do.
Let's go.
It's all right. I've got her.
Owen, I want to do it on my own.
Look, I'm sorry about your friends.
You know, I never liked camping.
Don't bother. They took the guns.
Charming place they've got.
Judging by
the sound reverberations...
and the air quality,
pretty deep underground.
Chances of rescue? We won't need
rescuing. I haven't met a cell yet
I couldn't get out of.
What were they? I don't know.
It happened too quickly.
Are you worried?
A little. Only...
that body we saw, in the forest.
Don't think about it.
See if you can get
that light to work, huh?
You're used to this, aren't you?
That facial expression you all share.
When things get a bit...
out of control.
Like you enjoy it.
Like you get a high from the danger.
You want me to apologise for that?
Don't you ever wonder how long you
can survive before you go mad,
or get killed, or lose a loved one?
It's worth the risk.
To protect people.
And who protects us?!
God, I'm hungry. You should
have had that cheeseburger.
Not THAT hungry.
What's that?
You've found something?
It's just a shoe.
Wait, there's another.
There's dozens of them.
Oh, my God...
How many people have been down here?
And what happened to them?
Is that a fridge?
Tosh, what is it, what's in there?
Tell me!
Ianto, don't. I want to know!
That's why there was
nothing left on the body.
They need to eat.
We're food.
So, if we barricade ourselves in,
what happens to Tosh and Ianto?
Why are we still talking about this?
Tosh and Ianto can look after
themselves.
The kid is our first responsibility
and they've already been for him
once. They're not going to give up.
So have we ever heard of a species
who strip human bodies of flesh
and organs? You need to rest.
I'm compiling what we've got.
Seeing if it helps.
We have to assume the others who
disappeared have been killed.
17 deaths? At least.
These aren't casual killers.
OK. So all this means
is the rift is spreading.
Dumping aliens and psychos
wherever it fancies. Looks like that.
Great. This conversation's
cheered me up no end.
Did you see that? Something outside?
Was that the same one or different?
He said they'd come back.
Let's not jump to conclusions.
We don't know who they are
or what their intentions are.
I'm thinking that's not a good sign.
They've come back.
Kieran, listen to my voice, OK.
Just come back. Kieran!
OK, so we didn't check the cellar.
You can't let them in! Come back
from the door. Don't let them in!
Sit down! We've got this under
control! You don't understand, you
don't know what they're like.
No, please...please, no, not me...!
Kieran! HELP ME!
It's pitch black. You don't have any
tracking devices! Wanna get yourself
killed? Get out of my way!
Look whatever's in that cellar
took three bullets. I heard it fall.
Once we know what it is, we'll know
how to deal with it. You do that.
We'll go after Kieran
and the others. You are wounded!
Do you think that's gonna stop me?!
Be careful.
Go.
Got to be three steel bolts -
top, middle and bottom.
How are you at calculating
target stress points?
Find the weakest point,
bit of brute force...
Nice thought. But it's reinforced.
Get off! Look at me, you idiot!
I'm not gonna hurt you!
You've got a gun.
I promise, I promise.
OK, OK...give her some space.
Thank you.
Were you injured? When they took you?
Can I see? I'm a nurse.
OK, OK, OK.
Does anyone else know you're here?
Have you managed to call for help?
We don't need any help.
There's three more
of us in the village.
I can't help you.
I'm sorry.
What d'you mean?
I've been sent to collect you.
I've got to take you to them.
Tell us what's going on.
We can help.
No-one's safe.
Every ten years...
..it takes us again.
What takes you? What is it?
The Harvest.
No, please, you have to
come with me.
Help me.
Please...help. Did you attack us?
I'm dying, help me...
I'll tell you everything...
This'll help you for a short amount
of time. Now start talking.
You've got to get help.
I know where you can get some.
We had a deal.
I help you, you tell me where
they've taken the boy and what
the hell is going on around here.
HE LAUGHS MIRTHLESSLY
You don't know?
What are you doing?!
Put it back!
You need to know something.
A long time ago,
I was pretty good at torture.
Y'see, I had quite a
reputation as the go-to guy.
My job demanded
it at the time, you see.
So I know
where to apply the tiniest amount
of pressure to a wound like yours.
You've gotta stop,
you're gonna kill me. PLEASE STOP!!
It's in your power to get
me to stop.
Just tell me what I need to know.
Because in ten seconds,
I'm gonna find a sharp object.
Right.. All right.
I'll tell you everything,
just stop.
Now talk.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah, fine,
I'm fine.
That's all we bloody need.
Let me do the talking,
I'll get rid of him.
Who are you, please?
Special Ops. From Torchwood,
have you heard of Torchwood?
What's that then, a band is it?
What's wrong with her?
Mate, you wouldn't understand.
What's that light over there?
The Big House?
Sort of unofficial village hall.
Village meeting tonight, that's
why I'm here. Constabulary report.
Come on.
Where do you think you're going?
In there, please.
If you help us,
we can stop all this. Please.
I'm sorry. Get back.
Oh, God, that stench...
Tell us what these creatures are.
Do they look like us?
How else are we gonna look?
There are three more out there.
Not a problem. How are they?
They're in a good state.
I think they're the best
we've ever had. Yeah?
Oh, I forgot to tell you,
we caught the boy.
Finally.
Come on.
I won't tell anyone!
Who is he?
He's meat.
I'm afraid we're all just meat.
Get ready to run.
What're you going to do,
put us on meat hooks?
No, not yet.
You see...meat...
has to be tenderised first.
Go! Get the others!
I know you're here.
No-one's coming for you.
SHE SCREAMS
No more games.
Hush now.
SHE CHOKES
Get off her or I'll shoot!
GET OFF HER OR I'LL SHOOT!
We saw the torchlight.
They've murdered all the villagers.
They're cannibalising the bodies!
Put the gun down. You're in no
position to negotiate, mate.
S'all right, it's all right.
You're safe.
You can arrest him now.
I said you can arrest him!
You gonna arrest me, Huw?
That'd be a laugh, wouldn't it?
My own uncle.
Put the gun down,
don't you hurt him.
Shoot the bastard.
Split his skull.
Put the fucking gun down! Shoot.
I will shoot you! Put it down.
Pull the trigger, kill.
Why don't you give me the gun? Mate.
Who are these people?
This is our village.
But the villagers are dead.
They're all involved.
They've all been doing it.
This is our Harvest.
Only in the bloody countryside!
You sick fuckers.
Are you OK? Where's Ianto?
What have you done with him?
Wake up, man.
Time to be bled.
Like veal, it takes a long time.
But it definitely makes
the meat taste better.
What the fuck...?
Oh, really?
No, Jack! Don't do it. These people
don't deserve warnings.
Let me question him.
I have to understand.
I want to know why. Otherwise this,
this is too much.
They're injured,
they need to get to the hospital.
Owen you control the bleeding
and then phone the police. Jack,
please give me an hour with him.
Don't tell me you
don't want to know too.
The whole village was involved.
Every generation.
Our tradition.
Once a decade.
Target those travelling through,
those most likely to disappear.
And butcher them.
What sort of people are you
that you wake up in the morning and
think, this is what I'm going to do?
Why'd you do it?
Come on!
Make me understand.
Why do you care?
I have seen things you
would never believe.
And this is the only
thing I can't understand.
So, keep on wondering. Tell me!
I need to know why! That's enough.
Time to go.
I'll tell you something...
if you let me whisper.
OK.
(Cos it made me happy.)
Come on, out..
'I had a good job before this,
'I thought in a year
or two, perhaps a baby,
'I know Rhys would be a good dad and
I could try for Desk Sergeant and...
'Well, it was all
slotting into place...'
'And then I met you lot.
'All these things...
'..all these things,
they're changing me.
'Changing how I see the world.'
And I can't share them
with anyone.
You can now.
What is this thing? With this you
can read peoples minds, it levels
the pitch between man and God.
We'll find you.
My guess is you're not
from around these parts.
Shagging a woman on the rebound.
Wouldn't be the first time
I'd been a rebound shag.
You need to see this,
this is completely impossible.
Tell me what to do.
Get me into Torchwood.