It may not look like much now
but wait till you see Poseidonis in 3D.
- With Aquaman riding Storm.
- What's Storm?
That's his animatronic seahorse.
Amazing. Eventually you won't
even need actors, right?
In five years we won't.
Kidding.
You still mad at me
for bailing on dinner?
I'm not mad at you.
- So what's wrong?
- Who says there's anything wrong?
I know you.
I can tell.
Vince, you haven't known me
in like five years.
True. You've probably changed a lot.
I've changed a lot. I learned French.
I didn't know these two
had a history.
It's nothing.
Even if something was wrong,
I think it's egotistical
that you just assume
it's about you.
That's right.
I mean, you're right.
But I'm right too. There is
something wrong. So what is it?
Nothing.
I don't want to talk
about it with you.
We're gonna be up here for a while,
we might as well talk about something.
I had a fight with Chris.
I don't want to talk
about that.
Vince, how are we ever going
to make this movie together?
They're gonna make
this movie together
because between them
they're making $8 million.
Fucking actors, they never know
when they're miked,
It was weird,
on "True Lies"
it was Tom Arnold that said
he was gonna be governor.
Uh, excuse me,
Mr. Cameron,
- Yeah?
- Ron's on the phone.
There seems to be a small
problem with the hovercraft.
What is it?
- It won't hover.
- God damn it.
Gary?
I hope these two are not
going to be a fucking problem, Eric.
Go ahead, Jim.
Gary, I need you
at the hovercraft right now, over.
Flying in.
What happened with you
and Chris? I want to know.
- We're having communication issues.
- We had those.
- You got to be more upfront.
- Oh really?
If we're talking about
someone who's never been upfront,
we should be talking
about you.
- What?
- Well I'm going to be upfront now.
I'm not over you.
And I haven't gotten over you.
How's that for upfront?
We are so fucked.
So first you tell me your relationship
with this girl was meaningless.
Then I find out
that you proposed to her.
Then you tell me you haven't
thought about her in five years
when, as sick as it is,
you're still in love with her.
How can I trust anything
you say anymore?
How can I trust you?
You're the one eavesdropping.
Should have Gavin de Becker
come sweep the house for bugs.
You know what?
This is a bad situation.
You know what, E?
There's is no situation.
Mandy is engaged. You're acting
like an obsessed schoolgirl.
E, do me a favor. Manage my career,
not my relationships.
This is your career.
And mine too, all right?
In front of James Cameron,
stop lying to me.
I don't want to talk about
this in front of the guys. I'm serious.
Vince, Armani doesn't have
a suit for under two grand.
Don't worry,
it's all on me.
Seriously, do we
need to wear suits?
What else are you going to wear
to a bat mitzvah? A Knick jersey?
It's formal.
I was thinking home whites.
How come you're not
trying anything on?
I don't let other men
buy my clothes, Drama.
And I'm not paying two grand
for a suit myself.
Wear the suit you wore
for your high school graduation.
It's hanging in your closet.
I thought that was
his communion suit.
E didn't grow much from communion
to high school graduation.
It's probably the same suit.
Fuck you guys.
I'm going to Men's Warehouse.
Oh come on, E.
I think you can afford a nice suit.
Yeah, E.
Don't be such a chaza huh.
I'm brushing up on
my Hebrew for the affair.
Chaza means greedy,
Drama, not cheap.
- How do you know?
- E used to valet park at Ohav Shalom.
That's great, Drama.
Now you're illiterate in two languages.
Let's hit shoes.
Men's Warehouse?
Don't start.
What do you think,
red or blue?
The red's a little flashy for
a bat mitzvah, Vince. I like the blue.
Okay. How did you know we were
going to a bat mitzvah?
- You don't remember me?
- Sloan.
- Sloan McQuewick, right?
- That's right.
Good memory.
Eric, right?
Yeah, good memory too.
This is Terrance's daughter.
Terrance is Ari's boss.
- Ari's partner.
- That's right. Now I remember.
- Do you?
- No, not really.
I'm sorry,
how did we meet?
The Christmas party, last year.
You were going to Italy, right?
That's right. You were
thinking about getting engaged,
- What?
- We had a couple drinks.
More than a couple,
I think.
I take it
you didn't then.
Oh no.
We broke up.
So, will I be seeing
you both at Ari's party?
- Yeah.
- Great. We'll have fun.
- See ya.
- Nice to meet you again.
Well, Vince, what else
can we do for you today?
I'm just going to look at
some more ties and that's it.
Great.
Know what, Philip? I think
I'm going to buy myself a new suit.
What?
She's not engaged.
Don't even think about
not picking that up, Ray,
- 'cause I'll fucking kill you.
- Fuck you, Ari.
Fabulous, baby.
Fabulous.
Hey, Is it me
- or is her voice getting worse?
- Ari!
Doesn't mean that I don't love her,
but she's just awful, baby.
Hey kids.
Whose car's out front?
Terrance.
He's waiting for you out back.
Terrance is here?
Why's he here?
I don't know.
Why don't you find out?
Ari, what are you
freaking out about?
Guy lives three blocks from us
and hasn't been by in five years.
Now he shows up four hours before we're
supposed to see him. Something's up.
- Ari.
- What?
You're a partner now. You don't need
to be afraid of him anymore.
I'm afraid of him? I'll beat that
old fuck and throw him in the pool.
Only Daddy speaks that way.
Out.
- There he is.
- Ari!
Terrance,
what a pleasant surprise.
- Nice to see you, mate.
- Nice to see you.
- Sweaty.
- Ha ha.
Well, I'm looking forward
to this evening.
Yeah, well it should
be fun, huh?
Cost me enough,
it better be.
I hope you're not going
to try and expense
any of this bat mitzvah
to the agency.
Me?
Ah, so little Sarah
becomes a woman tonight.
Yeah.
Time flies.
Incredible, isn't it?
It seems like
only yesterday
that my Sloan was running around
in pigtails and braces.
- Amazing.
- Yeah yeah.
You know,
speaking of Sloan,
she mentioned that she ran into
Vincent Chase in Beverly Hills.
You know, she can't stop
raving about this guy.
She thinks he's gonna be
a giant movie star.
I've been saying
that for five years.
Yes, but Sloan
is never wrong.
You know, she saw
Johnny Depp
in "Platoon" when she
was eight years old
and she said, "Dad,
that's the guy to watch."
You showed her "Platoon"
when she was eight years old?
- Oliver did. He wanted feedback.
- Ha ha ha.
Listen, the reason
for my visit is
I'd like a little chat
with Mr. Chase tonight.
I'd like to see
into his head,
find out what his hopes
and his dreams are.
We've had that talk
dozens of times,
and I could tell you firsthand...
No, firsthand
would be him telling me.
Yeah.
So listen,
why don't you give me
a proper introduction
tonight, huh?
- I mean, make an old man happy.
- Yeah.
Oh, listen...
- this is for the little lady.
- Oh.
I didn't want my gift to get
mixed up with all the others.
Huh?
Would you stop?
- You're gonna spoil your appetite.
- You're not my mother.
If I'm not eating,
you're not eating.
I'm fucking starving!
Do you know how much food
is gonna be at this thing?
You eating right now
would be like jerking off
an hour before
fucking a supermodel.
If I was fucking a supermodel,
I would jerk off.
That way I can
go all night.
- You guys ready for a big night?
- You sure Ari wants us there?
Of course he does, Turtle.
Ari looks at us as family.
Then why doesn't
he represent me?
Oh hey!
Look at this guy!
$3,000 suit just to line up
some pussy, huh, E?
It's a good investment. McQuewick's
gotta be worth 100 million easy.
You buying that suit is like
buying Microsoft in the '80s.
That's if you can
get the girl.
- I just needed a new suit, that's all.
- Oh yeah?
- What about the hair?
- What about it?
- A little shiny.
- Mangoes.
- Don't smell me.
- Uh-oh.
Looks like we're headed
for another E romance novel.
Get your tissues ready, guys.
Seriously, if this one
breaks your heart,
just kill yourself
so we don't have to hear about it.
I'll have the Barry Manilow
CD ready for you.
- Fuck you guys.
- What are you so sensitive about?
We know you well enough
to know you're in for trouble.
Yeah? How well
do we know you, Vince?
What does that mean?
Yeah, why are you
going off on Vince for?
No reason.
- All right, what's up?
- Nothing.
I didn't want to waste a Saturday night
on a bat mitzvah anyway.
You guys don't wanna
tell me what's up, I ain't going.
- Me neither.
- Ask Vince.
I told you I didn't want
to talk about it in front of them.
Them?
Since when are we them?
Next thing you know,
E's gonna be his brother.
You're a fuckin' dick.
Fine. Tell 'em.
Vince isn't over Mandy.
He never has been.
- He's been lying all along.
- What are you talking about?
He told her he loved her today
in front of James fucking Cameron.
- I didn't use those words.
- I thought she was getting married.
- Great Mother of God.
- This is why
we told you to get her
off the movie, E!
Yeah, E, if this movie
gets fucked up, it's on you.
No, look, nothing's
getting fucked up, okay?
I am fine.
I am just living my life.
You know, in fact, I was planning
on living my life again tonight
till you decided to stake
your claim with Sloan
with your new suit
and your fruity new hair.
What?
We all know how you like
to fall in love at the drop of a hat.
Did you ever think that maybe
I was interested too?
What are you talking... you didn't
even remember who she was.
Don't worry, E.
You spoke up first.
It's okay.
I'll step down.
I don't need you
to back off.
Oh, E, don't wake
a sleeping giant.
Seriously, E. Take the offer
while it's hot on the table.
I had a connection
with this girl.
So what, she's just
gonna flip to Vice?
You have a 25-mile lead
in the marathon.
Once Vince laces up
his shoes, it's over.
At least if he bangs Sloan,
he'll get over his obsession with Mandy.
It might be worth the sacrifice
to save the movie.
Look, Vince, if you wanna
go for her, go for her.
Okay, fine, I will.
You don't scare me,
you famous fuck.
Good move, E.
You're gonna need all your facilities.
My what, idiot?
Did I say that wrong?
Mazel tov.
Congratulations.
You look beautiful.
Look at Terrance. I guarantee you
his relatives worked with Nazis.
- Ari, compose yourself.
- Compose myself? You hate Melinda too.
- Quiet. I don't hate anybody.
- Mazel tov, Ari.
Hello, darling.
You look great! Beautiful.
- Thank you.
- Hey, princess!
- Melinda, it's so great to see you.
- You too!
- You look fabulous.
- Thank you.
Being a housewife
certainly agrees with you.
Playing a raging bitch on TV certainly
agrees with you. You're so natural.
If you hadn't quit acting at 25
it might have been you on a hit TV show.
- Honey, I need a drink.
- I think I need a drink too.
Hey, I'm looking forward
to my sit down with our boy.
"Sit down."
That schnitzel-Ioving
fuck is trying to steal Vince... hi.
- Nice to see you. Welcome.
- Hello.
Speaking of Vince,
why did he bring three dates?
That's the way it comes,
a package deal.
Where am I gonna sit them?
I already talked
to the caterer... hi.
Everything's taken care of.
Don't worry about it.
Why are me and Drama sitting at table 19
and you guys are sitting at table six?
Relax, Turtle. Ari probably just
wants to spread out the celebs.
Not to mention I haven't seen
a single edible item since we got here.
We just passed a sushi bar
right there, Turtle.
- Cooked items, E.
- The yellowtail is amazing.
- Patience, Turtle.
- Hey, you boys missed temple.
We thought that was
for Jews only.
Hi, Vince. Thanks so much
for coming to my bat mitzvah.
I wouldn't miss it
for the world.
- Look at you. You look beautiful.
- Thanks, so do you.
You look great too, E. What'd you do,
raid the boys department at Macy's?
You look pretty good too.
You auditioning for "Guys and Dolls"?
Hey, boys, enjoy yourselves.
Tonight we eat like kings.
- 500 a head.
- I'm starving.
- I told you,
- Smoke more weed, Turtle.
Seriously, smoke more weed.
She is pretty, huh?
Ivy Leaguer too?
I thought you didn't remember
anything about her.
Things are starting
to come back.
I think I'm gonna
ask her to dance.
- Oh, unless, of course, you wanna...
- Fuck you.
Oh, I forgot,
you don't dance.
Great, you get a leg up on me
because you've been training
for the "Saturday Night Fever"
remake for the last 20 years.
I don't understand what you do
at these things if you don't dance.
- Why're you doing this?
- Why'd you tell the guys about Mandy
- when I asked you not to?
- So what is this, payback?
- I'm heading over.
- I'm heading over with you.
So what show did you say
you were on again?
"Viking Quest."
What did he say?
Excuse me, honey.
What time's dinner? We're starving.
Didn't you eat all
the appetizers after temple?
No, we missed temple.
Sinners.
It's going to be a while.
I wanna kill you, Drama.
So what exactly
were you doing in Italy?
A friend was opening a restaurant
and I kinda helped her manage it.
God, what a coincidence.
E used to manage
an Italian restaurant also.
Really?
- Well, yeah...
- Don't be embarrassed.
It was the biggest Sbarro's
in all of Kew Gardens.
I love Sbarro's. I go to the one
at the Beverly Center all the time.
- Great sauce, right?
- Yeah.
Hey, Vince, my dad is dying
to get a word in with you.
- Would you mind if I went to get him?
- By all means.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Already wants me
to meet the family.
You're seriously
starting to annoy me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
can I have your attention?
Excuse me, could I
get your attention?
Before I bring up
the special family members
for the lighting
of the candle ceremony,
I would love to say a couple things
about this little girl right here.
You know,
when she was born
I have to be honest,
I wanted a boy.
Easy!
Wait a minute.
Give me a break here.
Now I didn't have any sisters
and I didn't know what to expect.
But this little girl
changed my life.
And, um...
watching her blossom
into a woman
has been one of the most
remarkable things
that I have ever seen.
And from the time
she could walk
she would come into our room
and she would jump on our bed
and she would wake us up
and we couldn't sleep.
- I'd get about two hours of sleep...
- Vince, this is my father.
- Hello.
- Nice to see you.
And this is his wife
Melinda Clark.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- And, Daddy, this is Eric Murphy.
- Ah.
When was the last time
we saw each other?
Oh, it's been a while. I think
since the Christmas party last year.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
We should let them
get acquainted.
- You wanna get a drink?
- Yeah.
- We'll be at the bar.
- So, Vince, I have to say,
I finally saw "Head On."
I just have to say it was...
- fabulous. Simply fabulous.
- Yeah.
We finally found her
asleep under our bed.
And she didn't wake us.
But she wanted
to be near us.
And I hope that she always will.
Now, I would love to invite
some of the family members...
who's coming up now?
- Grandpa Manny. We've got cousin...
- Grandpa Manny,
or as Sara likes
to call him "Munchie..."
I would love
to come up here.
He's that...
he's that special...
special breed
of grandfather...
You know what?
A better idea I think
would be to bring up
Sarah's star crush,
Vinnie Chase,
to cut the challah.
Everybody put it together
for Vinnie Chase.
- Ari, what the hell are you doing?
- Vinnie Chase!
Come on up and cut
the challah.
Look at that gorgeous
piece of bread.
It's like a big baked cloud.
Imagine making
a six-foot hero out of that thing.
A little mortadella,
some gabagol, provolone.
Let's get this party started, huh?
DJ Quick. Everybody dance,
What about the blessing
and the lighting of the candles?
What more boring way to kill
a party than to get 30 people up here
and light a fucking candle?
Thank God.
What did you guys order?
Uh, we didn't order anything.
We were late.
- But we'll take whatever you've got.
- Well...
what I got is
two kosher vegetarians.
Do you need some salt?
Excuse me, sir.
I will give you $100
for that prime rib.
What'd he say?
Oh, I love this song.
Do you want to dance?
Oh, you know what?
I really... I don't dance.
Oh, come on.
It'll be fun.
No, not for you.
People will be looking at you.
- It'll be horrifying, trust me.
- What's up, kids?
- You guys having a good time?
- Well, we were,
but Eric here refuses
to dance with me.
Really? Why?
Well, he says he doesn't
like to dance.
Since when? E, come on,
you used to love to dance as a child.
You know what? He's a little insecure.
I'll talk to him.
Okay, fine.
I did lie about the past.
But I really believed
I was over her.
And then I saw her and I realized
I wasn't. What do you want me to do?
Get over her.
Go make the movie.
This coming from
my manager or my best friend?
Both. Look, she's in love with
someone else. She's getting married.
Thanks, buddy.
Hey, Sloan.
E wants you
to dance with me
so we can teach him
a couple moves.
We'll be back later.
Shalom aleichem.
That's Hebrew for
"What time do you get off tonight?"
Cute.
Ignore his inappropriate
sexual advances.
We're looking
for one thing... meat.
How stoned are you guys?
- What?
- No.
I know exactly
what you need.
Come on, boys.
Unbelievable. He's pimping
his own daughter out.
Sarah, come here, baby.
Angel, come here.
- Stop it, Ari.
- Honey, go get your star crush.
- Go ask him to dance right now.
- Shut up, Daddy!
- You're so embarrassing me.
- "Shut up, Daddy."
She's really a woman now.
I have to get used to it.
- You are being ridiculous.
- I'm being...
That's exactly what you said
at the "Bill and Ted" premiere
when Terrance said, "I'll take Keanu,
you take the other guy."
Ari, you've idolized Terrance
since you were 20 years old
and you've let him take
advantage of you ever since.
So stop it now.
You're right, baby.
- Just be a man.
- "Just be a man." Really?
You give me the whole
heartfelt pump-up speech
and then you say just go
be a man? Come on.
- I need to speak to you.
- Hmm?
I need to speak to you.
- Ahem, I'm dancing with my wife...
- Now.
Excuse me, darling.
This better be good.
- Where's my joint?
- Where's the goods?
Turn to your right.
A kids' buffet? Sweet!
- Thank you.
- We got hot dogs,
and chicken and pizza.
Mac and cheese, baby!
Vince is my client.
I took him from nothing,
all right?
And now he is on the cusp.
I ain't sharin' him.
You know, when I started
this company in 1971,
my mantra was:
"Every client
should be represented by
every agent in the building."
And, yes, all right,
technically, he is your client.
- But this is my agency.
- And I'm a fucking partner.
Well, I've had more
than a few partners.
Not all of them
have lasted.
- Enjoy your evening.
- Ha.
Mm...
Mm!
Good living, huh, kids?
No doubt.
You got a light?
You've gotta be kidding me.
Turtle, look at this kid.
Jesus Christ! What, are you 13
and you're getting high?
You're not gonna
give us a lecture, are you?
No, not a lecture,
a life lesson.
We know. You're talking
to former addicts.
Weed is
a gateway drug, son.
One day you're lighting up in full view
of a dozen adults at a bat mitzvah,
the next you're cruising
Santa Monica Boulevard
offering hand jobs
for a crack rock.
Which one of you did that?
Just put the joint down, kid.
Just give me a light,
old man,
or I'll tell my dad
you put your hand on my knee.
Enough about Mandy.
What's the deal with your friend Eric?
Eric? I mean,
Eric's the best.
He's got good values,
smart, loyal.
I highly recommend him, although
right now he's probably mad at me
because he thinks
I'm out here working you.
What, you didn't tell him
- I don't date actors?
- How would I know that?
I told you that at the Christmas party
when you were working me.
Really? Was I?
Come on.
Hello?
Cheer up, E.
It's a celebration.
- Where's Vince?
- He disappeared with Sloan.
Probably at
the tennis courts.
I hear that's where you fuck
at the Beverly Hilton.
The fact that he went after
this girl purely out of spite,
- I may never speak to him again.
- Don't be so overly sensitive.
It's like getting mad at the bull
for giving you the horns
when you shouldn't have been
in the ring in the first place.
- Fuck you guys for encouraging him.
- Come on, Turtle,
- let's go work the waitress staff.
- No, fuck that.
They just wheeled out
the dessert cart.
Do-it-yourself sundaes?
Oh, man.
Sprinkles.
- Hey.
- Hey!
Where's Vince?
Oh, he got a phone call
from Mandy and he left.
- You're kidding me.
- He said you'd react that way.
But you gotta stop
worrying about him.
What else did he day?
He said that you're
a great guy
and that you've been
his best friend his whole life,
and that I should just drag you
onto the dance floor.
Come on,
it's a slow song.
I was a little surprised
that you called. What's going on?
I... I wanted to tell you
that Chris and I are gonna
be taking a little break.
Aw, that's too bad.
Look, you know, if you need
a friend, of course I'll be there...
Vince, I have enough friends.
The truth is... if we're being
upfront with one another...
I'm not over you either.
- Really?
- Really.
You wanna go get
a cup of coffee and talk about it?
Is that Vince?
Is that Mandy?