[ Man ] We interrupt this program
for a breaking news bulletin.
[ Male Reporter ]
Ninety miles and counting.
That's how far officers
of the Nevada Highway Patrol...
have pursued the blue car
on your screen...
in a wild chase right through
the heart of Elko...
at speeds approaching
1 00 miles an hour.
Live on the scene in Carlin is Chuck
Pickering in the Fox 1 1 News chopper.
Chuck, what can you
tell us ?
[ Pickering Over Radio ] Benjamin,
we're heading west following Route 766,
where it feeds off
the I-80.
Now,just under an hour ago, troopers
attempted to pull over the blue car,
which we understand is stolen.
That occurred on the 80 east of Wells.
Now, since then,
this driver has stopped
for nothing and nobody.
[ Buckley ]
Any word yet on who the driver is ?
Not at this time.
What we do think, though,
and what we've passed on
to the highway patrol,
is that from our vantage point,
we see another person in that car.
See ? Right there.
A hand.
It-It just moved.
See in the back seat ?
Now, we could possibly have
a hostage situation here.
And obviously, the sooner
they bring this vehicle to a stop--
- [ Sobbing ]
- [ Sirens Wailing ]
[ High-Pitched Frequency ]
[ Groaning ]
Unit 6,
ready at milepost 1 3.
[ Man ]
Coming your way, 6.
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ Pickering ]
Well, that did the trick.
The, uh, automobile seems
to be coming to a stop.
[ Buckley ]
Chuck, what did they just use there ?
It looked to be a special
tire-puncturing chain.
And now, the officers
are approaching the car.
One of them has opened the door,
and he has hold of the suspect.
He's pulling him out.
He-He doesn't seem
to have a weapon.
[ Buckley ] Well, he may not be armed,
but from our vantage point,
it looks like he doesn't
wanna get out of that car.
Vicky ! Vicky !
- Vicky!
- Please get it out of my head.
Please.
Let me go ! Let me go !
Vicky !
Vicky ! No !
[ Buckley ]
The hostage appears to be okay.
The highway patrol has her now,
but Chuck,
it looks like that driver
is still fighting.
[ Pickering ] Yes, he's definitely
putting up a bit of a fight.
He seems to be a man with a few choice
words on the subject, as you can see.
They're trying to restrain him.
I tell you what.
We're gonna move back and try
to get a wider angle.
See, there's the woman.
What the heck ? She's--
Vicky !
- Vicky !
- [ Groaning ]
There, see ?
She's banging her head
against the window.
- What the hell just happened?
-[ Man ] Hey! Cut!
- Yeah ?
- [ Scully ] Uh, Virgil Nokes ?
I'm Agent Scully. This is Agent Mulder.
We're with the F.B.I.
-Jehovah's Witness ?
- No, sir.
Federal Bureau
of Investigation.
But we do have a free copy of
The Watchtower for you, if you'd like.
Uh, sir, this is just
a routine check, but, uh,
we understand that you recently
placed an order for 5,000 pounds...
of ammonium nitrate
fertilizer.
Oh, you people.
Come on in.
- Sugar beets.
- Excuse me ?
I grow sugar beets.
I figure I got better things
to do with my fertilizer...
than go around blowin'
government buildings sky high.
No, well, as we said, sir,
this is just routine.
So routine
it numbs the mind.
I've got my AG card and
my papers around here somewhere.
- [ Man On TV] ... strange death
on a Nevada highway.
- Help me look for 'em, will ya ?
As we reported earlier, a wild police
pursuit ended in tragedy this morning...
with the death of
a 36-year-old female hostage.
This was the scene west
of Elko, Nevada one hour ago,
- as the hostage died
mysteriously while in custody.
- Scully, take a look at this.
We once again want to warn our viewers,
this footage is extremely graphic.
[ Pickering ] Now, the hostage
is still inside the car.
It appears as though she's banging
her head against the window.
[ Reporter ] At this time,
highway patrol officials...
are refusing to identify the woman
or to speculate on how she died,
though they do stress it was not
the result of a gunshot.
A preliminary coroner's report
isn't expected for a day or more.
Meanwhile, residents
of northern Nevada--
Thank you, Captain. That's no problem.
We'd be happy to help.
- Mm-hmm. See you soon.
- We'll be happy to help what ?
Mulder, we're not going
to Nevada.
- Come on, Scully.
Just one quick side trip.
- No.
Sorry, Mulder.
We have a whole new assignment.
Running down people that buy
fertilizer ? This is scut work.
Bozo work. This is the F.B.I.
equivalent of being made...
to wear an orange jumpsuit and pick up
trash by the side of the highway.
They mean to humiliate us.
Look, Mulder, like it or not, humiliated
or not, we're on domestic terrorism now.
And yes, this is--
this is a punishment.
But if we wanna get back to where
we wanna be, we have to follow orders.
- We can't freelance.
- You saw that news report.
What did you make of that ?
I think that the obvious assumption
is that the woman was shot,
regardless of what
the police say.
- Maybe it was a sniper.
- In the words of their captain,
""She just sort of popped.""
And what about this guy who supposedly
tried to take her hostage ?
Her husband ? Looked to me like he was
trying to warn the cops before she died.
Now, the sun will rise
in America tomorrow,
regardless of whether or not
we're at yet another farm...
investigating yet another
enormous pile of doo-doo.
We can be in and out in a day.
Nobody has to know.
[ High-Pitched Frequency ]
[ Gasping ]
S-S-Somebody !
Please !
It's starting !
- Why can't we see him ?
- Well, hopefully later.
He pitched quite a fit
in his cell--
screamin' a bunch of nonsense
that we were gonna kill him
the way we killed his wife.
You know, he's not a particularly
stable individual.
- Captain, he may need
medical attention.
- He's getting it.
Our doctor's with him now.
I mean, after whatever
happened to his wife--
which I'd like to stress
was not our fault--
we're not gonna take
any chances, you know ?
Patrick Garland Crump
of Montello, Nevada.
[ Mulder ]
40-year-old roofer.
No history of mental illness.
- No prior record.
- He's got one now.
That Barracuda he jacked
on the Utah state line ?
He yanked some teenager
out of the window,
threw his wife in back
and took off.
Excuse me.
What do you think ?
I'm thinking while we're here,
I might take a look at Mr. Crump's wife.
I'm gonna stay here
and see if I can see Crump.
Captain, where's Montello ?
Little town right here.
So that's where it started--
that's Crump's home.
Then he headed east
in this direction on the 5...
about ten miles to the Utah border,
where he stole the car.
- You got it.
- But you caught up with him in Wells.
Where's that ?
That's here. So that means that
he started off in this direction.
Then all of a sudden, he turned around
and he headed west to Wells.
Why ?
The former
VickyJenkins Crump.
I'm hoping you can tell me
what I'm looking at,
'cause this is
a new one on me.
There's no
gunpowder residue.
No carbon stippling.
There seems to be no evidence
of an entry wound whatsoever.
There is none.
It's all exit.
But how that could be--
I'm finding what look like
fragments of petrous bone...
embedded in the remaining portion
of the auditory canal.
In fact, I seem to be
looking straight through...
to the osseous labyrinth,
or what's left of it.
It's almost like a little bomb
went off in her ear.
- May I ?
- Please.
There seems to be some kind of
tumefaction within the lateral sinus.
[ Gasps ]
Look out. Can you give us
a little room here ?
No, he just went rammy on me.
AccuChek is normal.
We did a Narcan push,
but he keeps gettin' worse.
I.V. beta blocker
and topical nitro.
I don't know if you're gonna get
to talk to this fellow after all.
Five's a crowd, buddy.
[ Siren Wailing ]
[ Monitor Beeping Rapidly ]
- [ Beeping Slows ]
- Whoa. Something must've worked.
- Heart rate's dropping.
- B.P.'s headed south.
- I don't understand.
What'd you just do ?
- Hell if I know.
But I'll take it.
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ Sighs ]
Oh, God.
[ Line Ringing ]
Come on, Mulder.
Hey, you, out !
This lab is quarantined !
Go !
- Mulder ?
- [ Mulder] Yeah ?
Mulder, it's me.
You know how to pick 'em,
I'll tell you that.
Look, I have no idea
what killed this woman,
- but I have to assume
it's communicable.
- Yeah ?
Another body has been found
just outside of Montello.
Same apparent cause of death. Some kind
of massive aneurysm or rupture.
- Uh-huh.
- And Mulder, I've called the C.D.C.
They're on their way,
but Patrick Crump may be infected.
So you need to quarantine
his cell and make sure...
that anybody who's had any
close contact with him whatsoever...
has been quarantined as well,
and that means you, Mulder.
You're to have no contact
with him whatsoever.
[ Sighs ]
Mulder ?
- Well, that's gonna be
a little tough, Scully.
- [ Sirens Wailing ]
Drive.
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
- Where are they ?
- Route 7 89, heading west.
We're keeping 'em in visual,
plus we're in phone contact,
not to mention the strings
we've pulled with stations...
- to keep this thing off local TV.
- Where are they going ?
Crump won't say. Wherever it is,
though, he ain't gettin' there.
- We'll see to that.
We'll shut him down east of Tuscarora.
- Roadblock ?
Nice, clean, remote space
we can own.
All right.
I want the C.D.C. on site.
I want the officers making
the arrest to be wearing...
level two or better
anti-contamination suits.
I want the car decontaminated. I want
Agent Mulder and Crump decontaminated,
- and I want them
quarantined separately.
- You got it.
[ Inaudible ]
Crump says that if we don't
pull back our escort,
he's gonna shoot your partner.
Just leave me
the hell alone !
Now !
How about if, uh, we just pull over
and let me out too, huh ?
I must be cramping
your style.
Just shut up.
It's you people.
It figures.
- What figures ?
- Shut up.
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
Hey! No!
No!
That is... so stupid, Crump.
- That is so stupid.
- Shut up!
You shut up and drive.
You understand ?
- What are you doing ?
- What ? What am I doing ?
- What the hell are you doing ?
- I'm composing a sonnet.
What does it look like I'm doing ?
I'm slowing down for a light.
Go !
[ Horns Honking ]
Crump ?
Is this what happened
to your wife ?
This same thing ?
If you stop moving, you die ?
I think I saw this movie.
Why didn't you tell anybody ?
Why didn't you tell the police ?
Oh, geez.
Look, I don't know how well
you recall the last 30 seconds,
but your life is in my hands regardless
of whether or not you hold that gun.
- It's right here, boy.
-Just tell me everything you know.
- That may be the only way
I can help you.
- You people put me here !
Shut up !
I'm guessing we got two or three miles
before the roadblock.
What roadblock ?
I got rid of the cops.
Check your window.
Man, if we get stopped--
[ Woman Over Police Radio ] Please be
advised pursuit now headed west on 80.
Fourteen, come in.
Fourteen, be advised
vehicle's heading your way.
[ Man Over Radio ]
Subject's turning off 789...
about a mile east of your position
and is heading north on a fire road.
- Looks like he's gonna miss you.
- Say what ?
What's the report,
Captain ?
They lost 'em.
They were last seen on
a forestry service road.
Trees were too thick.
Our helicopter lost sight of'em.
- Well, how did Crump know
to avoid the roadblock ?
- That's the question.
I was hoping your Agent Mulder would
manage to steer him toward it, but--
Well, maybe Agent Mulder
steered him away from it.
Why would he do that ?
Maybe he knew something
that we don't.
[ Man ] Agent Scully, I've got the
cell cultures from the second victim.
Anything ?
So far, I'm seeing no evidence
of infection in either victim.
So then,
we're in the clear ?
No. No, not necessarily.
- I mean, something killed these people.
- [ Cell Phone Ringing ]
I'm sorry.
Excuse me. Scully.
[ Woman ] Agent Scully, please hold
for Assistant Director Kersh.
- [ Kersh ] Agent Scully.
- Yes, sir.
How's southern Idaho ?
Agent Scully ?
Southern Idaho ?
Think carefully.
Sir, I am not currently
in the state of Idaho.
- No, you're not.
- In the course of prosecuting
our assignment in Idaho,
Agent Mulder and I came across
a situation in Nevada...
which we both strongly felt
needed our immediate attention.
I eagerly await your report.
In the meantime, agents
of our Las Vegas field office...
will be available to assist you
in tracking down Agent Mulder.
- Thank you, sir.
- Oh, Agent Scully.
I think at this point I want to
see him alive even more than you do.
[ Line Clicks ]
Can I see that
for a minute ?
This man worked at
Silver State Power reading meters.
- Yes.
- What if he read the meter
at Vicky Crump's place ?
Crump ?
Crump, what else can you tell me
about what's happening to you ?
Mr. Crump.
You call me by my last name,
you say "" Mister"" in front of it.
Mister. Got you.
Not Crump.
Mr. Crump.
I can think of something else
I'd like to call you.
I could put "" Mister""
in front of that too, if you'd like.
You know, what kind of name
is Mulder anyway ?
What is it, like--
likeJewish ?
- Excuse me ?
- Jewish.
It is, right ?
It's Mr. Mulder to you,
you peanut-pickin' bastard.
Now, Mr. Crump, what can you tell me
about what's happening--
- [ Yells ]
- What ?
- You're goin'... the wrong way.
- What do you mean,
this is the wrong way ?
- Go this way ! Go this-- Go this way !
- I can't--
I can't go left.
There's only trees there.
- [ Yelling ]
- Crump!
[ Yelling Continues ]
[ Horn Honking ]
[ Yelling ]
Crump ?
It's west, huh ? West.
You gotta head west.
It's just like you did with your wife.
You took her and you headed west.
It's not just motion.
It has to be in one direction.
Is that right ?
What the hell happened
to you ?
Okay, I want
a thorough search...
- with an eye to
the usual disease factors.
- [ Man ] You got it.
[ Screaming ]
[ Dog Barking ]
I think we're witnessing
the same pathology here.
[ Barking, Yelping ]
- We need to get a blood sample.
- Yeah.
Let's go.
- Hold him down !
- [ Dog Yelps ]
Try to hold him still.
Let me sedate him.
[ Yelps ]
[ Mulder ] One more time.
You woke up this morning. Then what ?
We have been through this.
You woke up this morning,
but you didn't go to work. Why?
It was raining.
You don't shingle in the rain.
I was up at 6:00
reading the paper.
What was your wife doing ?
Cooking, man. Breakfast.
She was just putting breakfast
on the table when the--
- You looked up.
- I looked up,
and I saw that she had this nosebleed
she didn't even know she had.
- What caused it ?
- What do I--Am I like Quincy?
How the hell should I know
what caused it ?
It just happened.
Ten, fifteen minutes later,
she just...
starts getting sick.
Said she got a headache
that just...
keeps gettin' worse and worse.
She starts...
screamin'.
I didn't know what the hell to do.
I just, uh--
I got her in the truck and--
taken her to the hospital.
But then it seemed like the faster
we went, the better she'd do.
But just as soon as
I try to slow down or stop--
I'm sorry about your wife.
Sure you are,
you and the rest
of yourJew F.B.I.
- Crump--
- Oh, yeah. You think
I don't know, huh ?
You think I'm just some
ignorant pud-knocker, don't you ?
But I get it, man !
I see what this is.
I am not sick,
and I do not have the flu.
Vicky and me
were just some kind of...
government guinea pigs.
- You think the government
did this to you ?
- Oh, hell,yeah. Who else ?
You see it all the time
on the TV.
They're dropping Agent Orange,
they're puttin' radiation
in little retarded kids gonads.
Oh,yeah. You sons of bitches
sneakin'around my woods at night.
I seen you.
You think I don't know ?
Well, on behalf of the
InternationalJewish Conspiracy,
I just need to inform you that
we're... almost out of gas.
The trailer looks clean.
No readily apparent vectors.
Dogs, housewives.
Whatever this thing is,
it doesn't discriminate.
There are zoonotic pathogens
which spread among species.
Look at that.
The Crumps
have a neighbor.
[ Knocking ]
Hello ?
Doctor ?
[ Man On TV, Indistinct ]
[ Screaming ]
Oh, no, it--
It's okay, ma'am. It's okay.
- Who are you ?
- It's all right. I'm sorry.
[ Mumbling Incoherently ]
- [ Mumbling Continues ]
- It's okay.
It's okay.
- Hey, Crump, we got
about one more mile.
- [ Dings ]
I'll make it fast.
You ready?
Here goes nothing.
Turn on the pump !
Number four ! Three !
- [ Groaning ]
- Number three ! Turn it on !
You gotta pay
before you pump, buddy.
[ Engine Starts ]
Hey, damn it, that's my car ! Where in
the hell do you think you're goin' ?
Damn it! Stop!
[ Muttering ]
We're gonna take care of you.
Watch your step, now.
We just have to
examine you.
One deaf woman
survives unscathed,
while everything else
around her dies.
Why ?
Wait.
What are you doin' ?
The pathology
of this thing--
it affects
the inner ear.
And this area right here
is ground zero.
What if what we're looking for
is some kind of a sound ?
Seriously ?
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
[ Ringing Continues ]
Excuse me.
- Scully.
- It's Van Gelder.
Agent, I don't know what the hell
your partner's thinking,
but not only is he actively evading
my officers, now he's stolen a car.
- Come again ?
- You heard right.
He left behind a crazy note
addressed to you.
You there ?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Read it to me.
""Crump sick.
Will die if stopped, same as wife.
Must head west to keep alive.
No roadblocks.""
Exclamation point.
This make any sense to you ?
Take him at his word.
- Let him through.
- Let him through ?
Look, no offense, Agent Scully, but how
about you run that by your superiors ?
'Cause frankly,
I think they'll say different.
I'll take that
under advisement.
[ Van Gelder Continues,
Indistinct ]
[ Static, Line Breaking Up ]
Faster.
- I'm doin' 7 0.
- Man, you gotta go faster.
It's getting worse.
Yeah,yeah, that's good.
Okay.
Hey, uh,
theJew stuff?
No offense.
I mean, uh, a man can't help
who he's born to.
That was an apology, right ?
Gee, I don't know
if I can see to drive.
My eyes are tearing up
so bad.
Whatever, man.
Why are you doing this ?
- Why am I doing what ?
- This.
It's not in your best interest
to make me question that right now.
How do I know you ain't doing
exactly what they want you to ?
Hmm ?
Driving me all around creation,
experimentin' on me.
How do I know it ain't that ?
I guess you don't.
I ain't saying you are.
I'm just saying
that's no way to treat a man,
take away his dignity
like that.
It ain't right.
Better just to kill him.
That's all I'm saying.
Hey, you gotta stay alive if
you wanna stick it to the government.
If you die, you let them off the hook.
Am I right ?
Huh ?
You're right.
You're damn straight.
We'll figure this out.
You'd better figure quick.
We're runnin' out of west.
Lieutenant Breil ?
My name is Dana Scully.
I called in regards to
the electrical equipment...
- the navy is maintaining
in the town of Montello.
- Right.
Listen, I don't know if there's been
some miscommunication...
between you and your Washington office,
but, uh--
- My Washington office ?
- Yeah.
I was under the impression
that I'd explained this
to the F.C.C.'s satisfaction.
Oh. I'm-I'm...
so sorry to make you
run through it again,
uh, for my official report
to the, uh, to the F.C.C.
Okay. At 6:1 7
yesterday morning...
during a test of our
ground conduction radio system,
a situation arose in which our equipment
experienced a brief power surge.
That's what interrupted television
reception in the four-state area.
However, steps have already been taken
to ensure this won't happen again.
The ground conduction radio--
that-that would be Project Seafarer ?
The specifics of what we do here
are classified, ma'am.
Sure, sure. Um...
would you happen to know what effect
such a surge might have...
on, uh, on an organism ?
Say, um,
say a human being ?
Theoretically speaking.
Theoretically speaking ?
Well, that's classified as well, ma'am.
Crump ?
- Mr. Crump.
What is it, Mr. Mulder ?
Mulder, are you okay ?
Yeah, aside from terminal
cell phone withdrawal.
That and I gotta pee.
Where are you ?
I'm just about to board
a Justice Department jet.
Hopefully, I'll overshoot you.
- Headed where ?
- I don't know, Mulder. You tell me.
I'm guessing wherever the hell
Route 36 ends.
But we can't stop, Scully, and I'm
kind of at a loss as to what to do next.
[ Sighs ] Well, I think I have a loose
theory as to what caused this.
- Well, lay it on me.
- Okay.
Mulder, you know what
E.L.F. waves are ?
- Extremely low frequency
radio transmissions ?
- Yeah.
It uses an antenna,
like, 50 miles long.
The military uses it to communicate
with the trident submarine.
Project Seafarer,
Project Haarp.
Well, Seafarer has
an antenna array...
stretching beneath the edge
of Patrick Crump's property.
Now, E.L.F. fields
have been shown...
to produce biological effects
in human tissue--
inducing electrical currents,
altering chemical reactions.
Not to mention that it's
a potential weapons application.
It's been referred to as
""electrical nerve gas,""
or may be behind
the so-called ""Taos Hum.""
What if some overload--
some-some hum from this system...
could somehow match the resonant
frequency of the human skull ?
I mean, what if it could
induce a like hum...
that could somehow exert
a rising pressure...
on the labyrinth of the inner ear,
in a sense shattering it ?
But with constant movement
somehow ameliorating that
pressure, making it bearable.
But why only
westward movement ?
I don't know, Mulder.
I don't know. I mean--
I mean, maybe it has to follow certain
lines of force, electrical or magnetic.
But the big question, Scully,
is what do we do about it ?
Well, I think I know, Mulder, but it's
nothing that Mr. Crump is gonna like.
We'll be there.
What ?
Well, whether they did this to you
intentionally or not, you were right.
They did it to you.
So what do we--
what do we do ?
Your one chance is that we meet
my partner at the end of the highway.
There, she will insert a long,
large-bore needle into your inner ear,
hopefully relieving
the pressure.
And when we get there,
she's gonna have to work fast.
She's only gonna have
one chance.
She's not gonna be able
to use any anesthetic,
and it will probably
leave you deaf.
But I'll live, right ?
Well, that's what
it's all about.
All right, man,
let's do it.
Mr. Mulder, could you go
a little faster, please ?
- Just a little more is all I need.
- Sure.
Just a little bit faster.
[ Siren Wailing ]
Get ready !
[ Kersh ]
"Justice Department jet.
""2.6 turbine hours round trip
at $ 1,400 an hour.
""Car rental. Over mileage,
out-of-state use penalties--
""$346.
""Compensation to one
Walter R. Duncan...
for unauthorized use of his 1 968
Caprice station wagon-- $500.""
Why don't you bill me ?
I'll bill
your partner instead.
You too obviously relish
the role of martyr.
Okay, so are we done here ?
Back to the bozo work investigating
huge piles of manure ?
You can always quit.
- [ Door Slams Shut ]
- [ Sighs ]
Sir, Agent Mulder
has been through a lot.
And you apologize for him a lot.
I've noticed that about you.
I'm not apologizing
for this.
Because of his work,
the D.O.D. is shutting down...
their antenna array
in northeastern Nevada.
Our participation in this case
has saved lives.
I don't see you proving that.
The Department of Defense...
admits no culpability
whatsoever.
Furthermore, they say the closing
of the facility was coincidental.
Right.
Don't misunderstand me,
Agent.
I don't care if
you and your partner...
saved a school bus full of
doe-eyed urchins on their way
to Sunday Bible camp.
You no longer investigate X-Files.
You are done.
And the sooner you and Mulder
come to recognize that,
the better for both of you.
- Big piles of manure.
- [ Door Slams Shut ]
[ Child ]
I made this!