[ Woman Groans ]
I've got mosquito bites.
- I've got blisters.
I hate those new boots.
-[ Man ] Honey.
Why are you so P.O.'d ?
I thought we had a good time.
You had a good time.
You had a fine time...
tromping around and leaving me
a half a mile behind.
For future reference, me running through
the woods after you for an entire day...
is not my idea of a good time.
I'm sorry.
I've got longer legs.
I was excited, you know--
the great outdoors,
communing with nature.
- Your head hurt ?
- Yeah.
You can hit me in the head with a rock
if it'll make you feel better.
Fine.
Go get one.
I'm taking a shower.
[ Screaming ]
You still mad at me ?
No, I'm not mad.
Come here.
So, I guess we're never
going hiking again.
It's indoors forever
from now on.
Angie, honey, what's up ?
Just hold me.
[ Mulder Groans ]
I don't know what they
did with the screen for this thing.
Now, this is Angela
and Wallace Schiff.
It's a young married couple last
seen hiking in the vicinity of
Brown Mountain, North Carolina.
That's Angie on the right.
I should add this is the condition
in which their bodies were found...
after being missing for only
three days in temperatures that
never got above 7 0 degrees.
Which rules out decomposition.
I'd say predation, but the bones
would be scattered.
Not to mention that these skeletons
are not wearing any clothes.
Right. Well, I'd say
it looks like a double murder,
possibly one with
ritualistic overtones.
The bodies may have been stripped,
then skeletonized, possibly by boiling,
or by the use of some
kind of acid solution.
Maybe the arrangement
of the bodies...
has some meaning for
the killer or killers.
But at any rate, I'd term it
""ritualistic.''
That's a pretty big operation
you're describing.
There was no evidence found
at the scene-- no tire tracks,
no footprints, nothing.
Well, what do you think this is ?
It's Brown Mountain, Scully.
That doesn't ring a bell ?
The Brown Mountain lights ?
It's a famous atmospheric phenomenon
dating back nearly 7 00 years...
witnessed by thousands of people--
back to the Cherokee Indians.
Strange multicolored lights are seen
to dance above the peak of the mountain.
There's been no geological
explanation, no scientifical
credible explanation at all.
And what does that have
to do with these two ?
As I said, there's been no scientific
credible explanation,
but there are those of us
who believe that these strange
multicolored lights are really--
U.F.O.s ?
Extraterrestrial visitors...
from beyond who apparently
have nothing better to do...
than buzz one mountain over
and over again for 7 00 years ?
Sounds like crap when you say it.
I'm just wondering if
there's a connection, Scully.
The conditions of these bodies
are reminiscent of Southwestern
cattle mutilations--
cases where there's no physical
evidence, and they've been
associated with U.F.O. activity.
Mulder, can't you just for once--
just for the novelty of it--
come up with the
simplest explanation,
the most logical one,
instead of automatically...
jumping to U.F.O.s
or Bigfoot or--
Scully, in six years, how--
how often have I been wrong ?
- [ Scoffs ]
- No, seriously.
Every time I bring you a new case
we go through this perfunctory dance.
You tell me I'm not being scientifically
rigorous and that I'm off my nut.
And then in the end, who turns out
to be right like 98.9% of the time ?
I just think I've... earned
the benefit of the doubt here.
We gave 'em adjoining suites.
I was ready to send 'em
on to Chapel Hill.
Figured the state medical examiner
should have a look at 'em.
We appreciate you holding off.
- The connective tissue
is more or less intact.
- Unlike everything else.
I'm not sure what to make of it,
considering the short time frame.
If you'll, um,
pardon an obvious question,
are you sure that these are
the right two bodies...
and not two others that have lain out
for six months ?
We triple-checked
the dental records.
Angela and Wallace Schiff--
no doubt about it.
Hmm. And they were both found near
Brown Mountain, right ?
- Where exactly ?
- I could write you some directions.
Would you, uh, happen
to know what this is ?
Well, the remains
were found in a swampy area.
It's some sort of organic material
relating to that.
- It's bog sludge.
- I'm gonna go check out
where the bodies were found.
- You coming ?
-[ Scully ] No.
You go ahead.
[ Sighs ]
[ Car Approaching ]
Wallace Schiff?
We got your gas
spectrometer results.
That stuff on the bones
I said was bog sludge ? It isn't.
Water, hydrochloric acid,
electrolytes, pepsins
and trypsins.
It's a digestive secretion.
It's stomach juices pretty much-- pretty
damn close to it, except for this.
Chitinase ?
It's a digestive enzyme as well,
but it's strictly plant,
not animal.
Hello !
I told you I'd seen this before.
These are the two
I remember anyway.
Both of these were discovered
as skeletal remains.
Right, but we saw
nothing odd in that.
Both were lost hikers found months or
years later, or whatever it says there.
Says here that the bodies were
found not far from where Angela
and Wallace Schiff turned up.
-[ Dialing ]
-[ Line Ringing ]
Oh, Mulder,
answer your phone.
[ Computerized Voice ]
The cellular customer you are trying--
Do me a favor. I want you to forward
a sample of that secretion...
over to the F.B.I. lab
at Quantico.
-I want them to run a complete analysis.
-You got it.
And, uh, in the meantime,
can I borrow your truck ?
[ Rustling ]
Please.
- Don't take me.
- Come out here.
Step closer.
I won't hurt you.
- You're not one of them ?
- One of who ?
Are you Wallace Schiff?
Well, I hate to tell you this, Wallace,
but you're supposed to be dead.
They found your skeleton
not 200 yards from here.
It's fake.
They put it there.
Who put it there ?
You know who.
The Brown Mountain lights.
They abducted us--
me and my wife Angela.
They took us on board their--
Oh, God !
Wallace ? Wallace ?
They found your wife
Angela, too,
lying right alongside
your skeleton.
No.
Don't you get it ?
They faked our deaths !
They have that kind
of technology.
Who would be looking for us
if they thought they'd already
found our bodies ? You see ?
They returned me, but Angela,
she's still up there...
being experimented on
and I-I-I-I can't--
I don't know what to--
What do I do ?
Mulder ?
First things first--
we got to find a way out of here.
Right behind you.
What the hell's going on ?
That was solid rock
a minute ago.
- Now there's nothing there.
- Oh, God.
It's them.
They're affecting your head.
Maybe mine too.
-What if I can't even tell what's real ?
-Let's get out of here.
Come on, Wallace.
They're out there, man.
[ Rumbling ]
It's them !
Wallace !
[ Rumbling Continues ]
Mulder ?
Mulder !
[ Rumbling Continues ]
Don't let them see you!
[ Rumbling Stops ]
- They're gone.
- Yeah, for now.
- Thank God they didn't find us.
- They should have.
Maybe they came
for something else.
Oh, my God !
- Oh, my God ! Angie !
- [ Moaning ]
They brought her back.
Angie, can you talk to me ?
Do you remember what happened?
Can you tell me ?
- It's all fuzzy and--
- You were with your husband--
with Wallace.
There was a light--
a bright light.
Where was that light coming from ?
From the mountain ?
Over Brown Mountain.
There were strange lights dancing
over the peak and--
and they took me
and Wallace too.
And then what happened ?
Just... it all went black.
And when I woke up,
I didn't know where I was...
and I couldn't see
Wallace anymore.
They returned me first.
This-- This place
that they took you to,
can you describe it to me,
tell me what it looked like ?
It was... white--
a white place.
It was featureless.
I was lying on a table...
and I couldn't get up.
I mean, nothing was holding me down,
but I couldn't move.
Were there men there ?
Yes, there were men...
standing over me,
but I couldn't see their faces.
Did they perform tests on you ?
Yes, they did tests--
terrible... tests.
You have a--
- You have a scar back here
on the back of your neck.
- What ?
- What scar ?
- It's fresh.
- What is that ?
- It's an implant.
I've seen this before.
Yes. The drill--
I remember the drill.
I-- I couldn't see it at first.
That was the worst part.
But I could hear it spinning...
and it was coming
out of the light--
- What did they put in me ?
- Is there one in me ?
No. Male abductees
don't usually report this.
And everything she says is textbook
down to the last detail, except for one.
- What ?
- Two skeletons identified
as yours and Angie's ?
I don't understand that.
It doesn't make sense.
Maybe they're like
the cattle mutilations you hear about.
- Maybe they're part of their tests.
- I had that thought.
But there's no precedent.
It's in none of the literature.
Well, they didn't want
anybody to find us.
I guess they didn't want you
to know the truth.
We got to get out
of here right now.
- Oh, no way.
- They're out there.
They're always watching.
If they find us, if we leave,
they'll take us again.
We're leaving right now. Gather
your things. Angie, I'll help you up.
They're coming.
I can feel it.
[ Rumbling ]
- They're here!
- Hide ! They'll take you too !
- We've got to hide !
- No !
No !
- Scully.
- Mulder.
- Why the hell did you leave
North Carolina without telling me ?
- Long story.
You disappear and then I get a furtive
call that you're back here in D.C. ?
- I'm sorry.
Does anybody know you're here ?
- No.
- Scully, this is--
- Angela and Wallace Schiff.
- But Mulder, it can't be.
- This is my partner, Agent Scully.
Mulder, I I.D.'d
their remains myself.
Yeah, I think you were meant to.
Agent Scully, the aliens planted decoys
so you would think we were dead.
The aliens ?
Scully, I want you to... put aside
your scientific bias for a moment.
'Cause what I'm about to tell you
is gonna change your life forever--
your life, my life,
the life of everybody
on this planet.
- Mulder--
- I was out there...
and I found it.
- What ?
- The truth.
This couple--
they were abducted by a U.F.O.--
the Brown Mountain lights.
They took me to a white place.
There were men there.
They put an implant in my neck.
Just like what happened to you.
Mulder, from what very little
I understand about this case,
this is not what happened to me.
There's more.
It doesn't like the light.
Who ?
I abducted him.
It's a gray.
It speaks to me.
We communicate telepathically.
He told me everything.
- I-- I can hear him.
- Yeah.
Oh, my God !
I, uh-- I don't know
what to say, Mulder--
where to begin.
I mean, you--
you were right.
All these years,
- You think so ?
- [ Sighs ]
You were right
about the grays, about--
about the abductions,
about the U.F.O.s,
the lights, the
Brown Mountain lights--
What about the skeletons ?
They were--
They were fake. They were decoys.
You're buying that decoy theory ?
What about that organic substance
we found on the skeletons ?
That goo you were
so interested in ?
It was nothing.
It was bog sludge.
That, uh, doesn't sound
like you, Scully.
It, uh-- God, I can't believe
you're buying this.
Mulder, I'm admitting
that I was wrong.
Are-- Are you all right ?
[ Water Stops Running ]
- How are you feeling ?
- [ Groans ]
- This doesn't make any sense.
- What ?
These two, their story,
their skeletons, none of it.
Mulder, if I, of all people,
can believe this, then why can't you ?
- Did you go inside the cave ?
- Yeah, I looked. It's empty.
It's as if he just vanished.
He's got to be around.
We'll catch up to him.
I know this area pretty well.
Doctor.
It's more of that
digestive material.
Looks like it's coming up
from out of the ground.
Agent Scully ?
I got tracks going in and out.
They were only going in before.
- I guess you missed him.
- How ?
I mean, this cave's not much more
than a hole in the rock.
Agent Scully?
[ Door Opens ]
The courier just arrived.
They brought your partner's charts.
I'm sorry.
I know it's difficult.
That, um-- That digestive secretion
that we keep finding,
could it-- could it
have done this to him ?
I'm not sure I follow.
Well, it's-- it's chemically similar
to gastric juices, right ?
I mean,
maybe he fell in it or...
maybe it's a product of a particular
vegetation that grows in the area.
That... all sounds plausible,
I guess,
except for one thing.
There's no sign of it
on these remains.
It was--
It was on the Schiffs.
I just think we need to look
for the simplest explanation--
the most logical.
What is the most
logical explanation ?
I'd say we're looking
at a murder--
one with ritualistic overtones.
I think his body was stripped...
and then skeletonized,
possibly by boiling
or use of an acid solution.
Don't worry, Agent.
We'll take care of the arrangements.
What arrangement ?
We'll have the remains
sent on to Washington.
I appreciate the thoroughness
of your report,
especially given the circumstances.
It might be best if you
took some time off-- a short leave.
Agent ?
Sir ?
You're satisfied with
my conclusions in this case ?
Absolutely.
- I take it you're not.
- [ Scoffs ]
I was unable to determine
a clear cause of death,
nor was I able to fully account for
the condition of Agent Mulder's body.
You concluded he was a victim
of a ritual killing.
No.
I mean that was one possible scenario
that I mentioned,
but in my mind it--
it was the least plausible.
Not only is it plausible,
it's-- it's, uh--
it's likely.
Why are you questioning
your own findings ?
My role in the X-Files
has always been to provide...
a rational scientific
perspective...
to cases that would seem
to defy explanation--
a counterpoint
to Agent Mulder.
And you have done that.
- You have performed admirably.
- Have I ?
How many X-Files
has my scientific approach...
fully and satisfactorily
explained ?
Your reports have consistently
made sense of his conclusions.
Sir, this one makes
no sense at all.
Are you suggesting this is
anything other than a murder ?
That's what Agent Mulder
would have thought.
You think he
would have been right ?
[ Sighs ]
Given Mulder's life work,
it's tempting to attribute
his death to the paranormal--
the unexplained, the unknown--
but that's simply
not the case here.
You need to see
this for what it is.
And given that,
I promise you we'll get
the bastard who did this.
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
I'm sorry.
Agent Scully,
how are you holding up ?
I, uh--
I still can't believe it.
Neither can we. I half expect Mulder
to come knocking at that door.
- ""Surprise.''
- This will dull the pain.
No, thank you.
Just so you know,
we've launched
our own investigation.
I was beginning to think that I was
the only one who was at all suspicious.
We'll find him. We'll find him
and we'll make him pay.
- Find who ?
- The son of a bitch who killed Mulder.
I hope you're not offended, but we, uh,
managed to get a hold of your report.
I must say, we were impressed
by the thoroughness of it.
- Especially given the circumstances.
- I don't understand.
We concur with your findings.
Clearly, this was a ritualistic murder.
Those were not my findings.
You guys believe that, too--
that Mulder was murdered ?
- It's the obvious answer.
- No, it is not the obvious answer !
We believe his body was stripped, then
skeletonized, possibly by boiling...
or the use
of an acid solution.
-We'll make that monkey pay.
-What the hell is wrong with everybody ?
You guys, there are
unanswered questions here !
Am I the only one
that's asking them ?
I could use a drink.
You three, of all people,
should be all over this,
not buying the party line.
Something else is going on here.
Am I the only one who thinks that ?
- [ Exasperated Sigh ]
- Are you all right ?
I think you need to go home and
get some rest. I'll call you a cab.
What have you done with him ?
Scully, you're emotionally distraught.
You need to calm down and get some rest.
Where is Mulder ?
What have you done with him ?
Listen to me. He's gone.
You need to accept that.
Something else is going on here !
Where is he ?
Where's Mulder ?
[ Knocking At Door ]
[ Knocking Continues ]
Scully.
We were in the cave
when the light came.
It was a blinding...
blue-white light.
And then they took me.
I was abducted.
I found myself
in some kind of medical bay.
It was white, featureless. It was
just as the Schiffs had described it.
- Mulder, the Schiffs are dead.
- No, actually, they're not.
Mulder, their remains
were discovered in a field.
That's-- That's what brought us
to this case in the first place.
I found your remains
in that same field.
Look at me.
I'm here.
How did you get here ?
Aliens brought me back here.
From North Carolina direct
to your apartment door ?
Mulder, you don't remember
getting here, do you ?
Neither do I.
It doesn't change
what happened.
Mulder, why did you knock ?
This is your apartment.
And you don't seem the least bit
surprised to find me here.
And what about the Schiffs ?
I mean, if they're--
if they're alive, as you say, then--
then where are they--
where'd they go ?
Mulder, five minutes ago...
this room was filled with people
attending your wake.
Well, what can I say, Scully ?
I'm here. I'm real.
Mulder, this is not reality.
This is a hallucination.
It has to be.
And either I am having it or you are
having it or we are having it together.
- Brought on by what ?
- Something that we found
in that field, Mulder,
because that's where it began.
Wild mushroom.
Wild mushrooms, Mulder.
They were growing there.
I stepped on one and it gave off spores.
Several varieties of mushrooms are known
for their hallucinogenic properties.
- If we inhaled it--
- Whatever happened
to the most logical explanation ?
This is it, Mulder.
What if we're still there--
if we're still in that cave
in North Carolina ?
That we're not here
in this apartment right now?
- Whoa, Scully.
- Mulder, bear with me.
I think this is making sense. I think
that Angela and Wallace Schiff...
were digested by that substance
that I found all over that field.
That they were dissolved
and then expelled up out of the ground.
What if that substance...
and this hallucinogen are
from one and the same organism ?
- A giant mushroom ?
- A giant fungal organism, Mulder.
We already know that they exist.
Biologists have found specimens
that range dozens of acres...
that weigh hundreds of tons.
And what if this one
needs to feed on living tissue ?
There is carnivorous plant life.
There's the Venus flytrap
and the pitcher plant.
Mulder, what if this one
puts off a hallucinogen--
- To lure its prey into the cave ?
- To make it complacent--
to keep it still
while it devours it.
[ Gasps ]
What if we're still
underground, Mulder ?
What if we're moving deeper
into the cave, or being moved?
Mulder, what if
we're being digested ?
Right now.
[ Coughing ]
The exact size of this organism
has yet to be determined ?
[ Scully ]
That's correct, sir.
We know that the organism
extends for at least ten acres.
Though it's mostly subterranean,
so it may be far larger.
We've contacted
Fish and Wildlife.
We've contacted the North Carolina State
Health Department...
as well as the local
F.B.I. field office in Raleigh.
And we've contacted a mycologist
at the Smithsonian for good measure.
We think we have
our bases covered.
The lab results determined
that the spores we were exposed to...
have a chemical structure
similar to L.S.D.
They also contain an alkaloid
which induces a state of narcosis.
It's a rare day when the two
of you sign off on the same report.
Agent Mulder ?
I'm just thinking.
Uh, I'm not exactly clear
on how we escaped.
- What's not clear ?
- Once you recognized we were
under a chemical influence,
then it simply kind of...
broke its spell ?
- That's right.
- Scully, how could we simply...
will ourselves out
of a chemical hallucination ?
- Well, the fact remains we did.
- Did we ?
Can you name me one drug that
loses its effect once the user
realizes it's in his system ?
I assume the effects wore off to the
point you were able to make your escape.
How long were we underground--
hours, half a day?
How come our bodies
don't show effects of being
burned by the digestive fluids ?
We were covered in hydrochloric acid,
yet look at our skin. Nothing.
Agent Mulder,
where are you going with this ?
Scully, we never escaped.
We're still trapped underground.
Mulder, we did escape.
- I think you're suffering
from post-traumatic stress.
- No, I'm not.
This is not real.
You--you're not real.
[ Scoffs ]
Mulder, I--
I'll prove it, Scully.
I'll prove it.
Mulder!
[ Liquid Dripping ]
[ Skinner]
Over here !
[ Men Shouting ]
Hey !
Rescue, over here !
- He's alive.
- Hurry up !
Get him out ! Get him out !
Keep digging !
She's down here !
Pull her up.
Get her out !
- Mushroom.
- We found it.
Just take it easy, Agent.
[ Child ]
I made this!