[ Mulder Narrating ]
Two men--young, idealistic,
the fine product of a generation
hardened by world war.
Two fathers, whose paths
would converge in a new battle--
an invisible war between
a silent enemy and a sleeping giant...
on a scale to dwarf
all historical conflicts.
A 50-years war.
Its killing fields lying in wait...
for the inevitable
global holocaust.
Theirs was the dawn
of Armageddon.
And while the world was unaware,
unwitting spectators...
to the hurly-burly of
the decade's long struggle...
between heaven and earth,
there were those
who prepared for the end--
who measured the size and power
of the enemy and faced the choices:
stand and fight, or bow
to the will of a fearsome enemy.
Or to surrender,:
to yield and collaborate,:
to save themselves
and stay their enemy's hand.
Men who believed that victory
was the absence of defeat,
and survival
the ultimate ideology...
no matter what the sacrifice.
- Shoot me now before it's too late !
- [ Banging On Door ]
- Mulder !
- Shoot !
Who are you ?
- What's going on ?
- Get down ! Get down on the floor !
- Who are you ?
- Get down !
[ Shouting Continues ]
On the floor !
[ Coughing, Gasping ]
- Who are you ?
- We're with the Centers
for Disease Control.
Remain calm and where you are
for your own good.
You're gonna be transported
to a quarantine facility as soon
as we can secure the environment.
- Quarantine for what ?
- A contagion.
A contagion
of unknown origin.
[ Instrument Humming ]
There must be some kind of mistake.
I signed up for
the aromatherapy treatment.
Are we gonna be able to talk to somebody
who can tell us what this is all about ?
[ Door Closes ]
Where the hell
do you think we are ?
I think based on our travel time,
probably Fort Marlene.
- High risk decontamination
and quarantine.
- [ Door Opens ]
I'm gonna beg for your
forgiveness and understanding...
and offer my humblest apologies
for the way this went down.
I didn't have a lot of choices.
I owe your neighbors apologies as well.
It's gonna be some time before
they get back in the building.
We're still acting on a C.D.C.
level 4 quarantine protocol.
Based on what information ?
That Cassandra Spender had contracted a
highly contagious vectoring organism...
which produces a spontaneous
cellular breakdown and combustion.
- What ?
- She was and remains
the only surviving victim...
of an unspecified
medical experiment...
that killed seven doctors with
violent and unexplained burning.
- Who called you ?
- Agent Spender.
Where's Cassandra ?
She's isolated, pending full
and satisfactory medical evaluation.
Cassandra Spender was in a general
hospital environment for days.
We met with her. And yet on a whim,
you call in the third battalion.
- It's unjustified and
highly suspicious as to motive.
- Scully--
What motives
are you suspecting ?
- Your isolation of Cassandra.
- She's patient zero.
No one is sick
or infected here.
I mean, I assumed that, based on you
walking in here dressed to the nines...
offering apologies
masquerading as explanations.
- Scully.
- Mulder, I wanna see Cassandra.
- I told you, she's isolated.
- Yes, and I am a medical doctor.
Who was suspended indefinitely
from her position at the F.B.I.
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
They burned our clothes.
Hey, I heard gray
is the new black.
Mulder, this stinks.
And not just because I think
that woman is a--
Well, I think you know
what I think that woman is.
No, actually. You hide
your feelings very well.
Agent Spender calling
the Centers for Disease Control ?
Mulder, this is just somebody
using their position...
to stage a high-tech
government kidnapping.
Apparently not.
I just spoke to A.D. Skinner.
He was at the hospital
when Cassandra went missing.
He heard Spender make
the phone call to the C.D.C.
But she wasn't sick, Mulder.
I mean, the remarkable thing
is she was well.
Then why did she come to my apartment
demanding to be killed ?
Because of everything
that had been done to her--
because of the tests,
because of the medical experiments
and the implant put in her neck.
The same thing that was done to me.
She just wants it to stop.
And I'm telling you, they have
taken her so that it can continue.
No, it won't continue.
It doesn't have to anymore.
She knows what she is, Scully.
That's why it's so dangerous
for her to be alive.
She knows what she is, Scully.
That's why it's so dangerous
for her to be alive.
That's why she came to my apartment
asking to be killed.
What is she ?
I think she's the one,
Scully.
[ Man ] I recovered all the medical
records from the hospital.
The doctors who examined her
before she escaped...
are telling us Cassandra Spender
may be the culmination...
of 25 years of
this group's finest efforts.
That's why the rebels struck.
They were trying to kill her.
They killed everyone but her.
They struck to keep her alive.
- To keep us from killing her.
- What do the rebels want ?
To destroy us.
They know that when the aliens learn
of Cassandra, colonization will begin.
We must destroy Cassandra.
No.
Let colonization begin.
We must turn over Cassandra.
Save ourselves.
Bill Mulder was against this. He said
this would be our tragic mistake.
Bill Mulder sacrificed his only daughter
because he knew this day would arrive.
What choice have we...
if you want to see
your families survive,
if we want to see those
we sacrificed returned to us ?
Hello ?
Oh-Oh, ma'am.
Um, these shoes, they're--
they're two sizes too small.
I was wondering
if I could get a--
a pair that fit, maybe !
I can't be seen with you.
Marita ?
If they catch me with you,
they'll kill me this time.
Who ?
The smoking man
and his group.
What have they done to you ?
Tests.
Terrible, terrible tests.
Like the tests
on Cassandra Spender ?
No. No.
Cassandra Spender is part of a program
that's been going on for 25 years.
A hybrid program.
But what were
the tests on you ?
I was infected with the alien virus,
the black oil.
My tests were on
the vaccine against it...
being developed in secret.
In secret
from the alien colonists.
The hybrid program was in cooperation
with the aliens,
but the conspirators never intended
to succeed, to finish the work.
They were buying time.
- To make a vaccine. Build a weapon.
- But Cassandra Spender happened.
She's the first, isn't she ? She's
the first successful alien-human hybrid.
If she is...
and the aliens learn
a hybrid exists,
colonization of the planet
will begin...
with no stopping it.
Jeffrey ?
Jeffrey.
-Jeffrey.
- Mom.
- How are you feeling ?
- I'm fine.
- Why are they keeping me here ?
- I'm keeping you here
because you're safe here.
- Safe from who ?
- You know who. From my father.
You can't keep me safe
from him.
I can, Mom, and I'm going to.
There won't be any more tests on you.
You don't understand.
You don't understand
about me.
I do. I understand
everything now.
You don't understand
what will happen--
what will happen to you
if they find me out.
- You've got to let me go.
- They'll just hurt you again, Mom.
Yes.
You must let them,
or everyone dies.
Everyone.
Jeffrey ?
Please. Jeffrey !
Jeffrey! Jeffrey!
[ Door Closes ]
The latest
in home security.
Hey, you get through this,
you gotta come through me.
I got a call from Scully,
said it was urgent.
I'll ask you to hear me out
before you launch any objection.
Mulder, I asked them to pull up
everything they could on Diana Fowley.
[ Sighs ]
I don't have time for this.
Mulder, she's playing you
for a fool.
- I know her, Scully. You don't.
- You knew her. You don't anymore.
I think we can
prove that to you.
She took a position in the F.B.I.'s
Foreign Counterterrorism Unit in 1 991 .
Seven years in Europe.
Yet there isn't a single piece
of information available...
on her activities
in the F.B.I. files.
[ Mock Gasp ]
I hope you've got something
more than that to indict her with.
Travel records pulled
from airline manifests...
that have been purged
from her F.B.I. records.
Extensive movement
throughout Western Europe.
Almost weekly trips
to and from Tunisia.
For the purpose of what ?
That's what we couldn't figure,
until we took a flyer and we found this.
- Mutual U.F.O. Network logs.
- U.F.O.N.
[ Scully ] Special Agent Diana Fowley
of the F.B.I...
was visiting
every European chapter...
collecting data
on female abductees.
- So she's collecting data. Big deal.
- Or hiding it.
Scully, you're reaching.
Mulder, when I was abducted,
a chip was put in my neck...
when I happened upon
a U.F.O.N. group filled with women
who'd had the same experience.
So you're suggesting that Diana
is monitoring these abductees,
monitoring these tests ?
You tell me that Cassandra Spender
is the critical test subject,
the one who could
prove everything.
And yet who
is watching over her ?
Mulder, I can prove what you're saying,
or I can disprove it.
But not when Diana Fowley
is keeping us from even seeing her.
Mulder, ask yourself why
there is no information whatsoever...
on Special Agent
Diana Fowley--
why she would suddenly
happen into your life...
when you are closer than ever
to the truth.
I mean, you ask me
to trust no one,
and yet you trust her
on simple faith.
Because you've given me
no reason here to do otherwise.
Well, then,
I can't help you anymore.
Scully, you're making
this personal.
Because it is personal,
Mulder.
Because without the F.B.I.,
personal interest is all that I have.
And if you take that away, then there
is no reason for me to continue.
Diana ?
Sorry.
Nobody home.
What are you doing here ?
The door was open.
I came in.
Interesting company
you keep.
No more interesting than
your apparent lingerie fetish.
You feeling smug,
C.G.B. ?
Yeah, I know your name.
I know your game,
and I got nothing to lose.
I remember looking over a gun barrel
at you once before, Agent Mulder.
You couldn't pull the trigger then.
What makes you think you can do it now ?
- I came here looking for my son.
- Why ?
Because he's betrayed me.
He's chosen the wrong side.
He's chosen to believe in your cause.
That presumes
my cause is wrong.
Oh, it is, Agent Mulder.
It is.
I'm not the one
using innocent people--
innocent women as lab rats,
trying to create a hybrid--
an alien-human hybrid--
so that I might save my own sorry ass
when they finally come knocking !
- You find that funny ?
- Your father was against it too
back in '73.
The lone dissenter.
But he came to his senses...
and gave up your sister,
Samantha.
He didn't give up my sister.
He was forced to. You made him do it.
You're wrong, Agent Mulder.
I can't tell you
how wrong you are--
how wrong you've always been.
We had agreed to cooperate
with the alien colonists...
by a majority vote,
taken by the group that
your father and I worked for.
A group that came together
at the State Department...
on a project dating back
to 1 94 7 at Roswell.
The vote changed that, though.
It changed everything.
We no longer cleaved
to any government agency.
We would now operate privately
on our own project.
That was
your father's objection--
that we would ally ourselves
with the alien colonists.
Toward your own
selfish end.
We forestalled
an alien invasion.
- No, no, no.
You only managed to postpone it.
- We saved billions of lives.
You put those lives on hold
so that you alone could survive.
No, Agent Mulder,
so you could.
That's exactly what your father
failed to realize.
He railed at us
and our plans...
even as the process had begun,
while the group had agreed...
to the most
painful sacrifices--
sacrifices that...
no one else would ever
be asked to make.
You gave them your children !
You gave them your wife !
You sent them away...
like they were things !
We sent them away, Agent Mulder,
because it was the right thing to do.
You sent them away
to be tested on.
We sent them so they would
come back to us. Don't you see ?
You can't think these choices
were made lightly.
They were the most painful
decisions of our lives.
Watching our families'faces--
You're a liar.
My sister wasn't taken
from any hangar.
She was abducted from our home
right in front of me.
Because your father was late
to understand the necessity--
that he too must give up one of
his children to the alien colonists.
The aliens insisted on it.
It was the only way they would give us
the one thing that we needed--
the one thing without which
we could not proceed.
See, the alien fetus
would give us the alien genome--
the DNA with which we could make
a human hybrid.
A new race, Agent Mulder--
an alien-human hybrid...
who could survive
the holocaust.
So you could survive...
and live to see your sister.
Now you've succeeded ?
Quite.
In spite of ourselves.
The plan was to stall,
- to resist.
- To work secretly on a vaccine.
That was your father's idea--
to use the alien DNA
to make a vaccine...
to save everyone,
the world.
It's the reason
he came along,
but it's too late now.
Colonization is gonna begin.
There will be
a sequence of events.
A state of emergency
will be declared...
because of a massive outbreak
of the alien virus by bees,
and the takeover will begin.
I have only
to hand over Cassandra.
You can't do that.
Our hand's been forced by
the faceless rebels. We have no choice.
Stop it now,
or I will stop it.
No, Agent Mulder,
you won't stop it.
Not if you want to see
your sister again.
No, you--
you stop it,
or everyone dies.
No.
I live.
You live...
to see your sister return.
It's what
your father realized.
It's what you'll realize
as your father's son.
Or die in vain...
with the rest of the world.
Save her.
Save yourself.
[ Door Opens ]
[ Door Closes ]
You're looking
for your father.
He's gone.
They've all gone.
- But they're coming back.
- No.
- No, they left for good.
- What do you mean ?
- They've abandoned these offices.
- But they've been here for 50 years.
- I don't think you understand.
- Where did they go ?
To West Virginia.
They'll be transported by the colonists
and begin medical preparations...
to receive the hybrid genes.
Except for your father.
- He's gone to get your mother.
- No one can get to her.
I've got her secured away.
""Secured away"" ? He's already
at his doctor's looking at her.
- I've got her under guard.
- She's probably being prepared
as we speak,Jeffrey.
[ Door Opens ]
- What do you want now ?
-Just lie back, Cassandra.
- We're just gonna remove
some of these machines.
- Leave me alone !
- Leave me-- Help !
- Cassandra, lie back and relax.
Help! Leave me alone!
Oh, no !
You're not gonna dope me !
- No, don't dope me!
- Roll her over, please. Roll her over.
[ Yelling, Sobbing ]
Don't !
- Hold her!
- Damn you !
Bastard !
The biggest bastard of all.
I need a few minutes.
- They never question it, do they ?
- What ?
Your power and authority,
when you're really
such a... coward.
I--
I came in hopes
that we might...
speak of the future,
not the past.
I'm at a disadvantage,
since you stole
the past from me.
I won't defend myself,
except--
except to say that...
we're here now only because
of what I have done.
It's due to it.
I know it now.
Only now.
But for so many years
I didn't understand...
through all the abductions
and the tests...
that it was you.
I ordered them, yes,
but it was never my intention
to harm you.
It was to save you...
and Jeffrey.
You can never save our son.
He knows what
you've done to me.
I saved you !
There's only one way...
to save him.
Only one thing you must do.
I can't do it to you.
I can't.
I must die,
or they all die.
No !
[ Sobbing ]
[ Door Closes ]
-Jeez !
- I'm sorry.
- I didn't mean to scare you.
- Fox, what are you doing ?
Nothing.
Not a damn thing.
- I came here looking for evidence.
- What are you talking about ?
Evidence that you'd lied to me--
that you had loyalties other
than to me or to the X-Files.
Nothing could be further
from the truth, Fox.
Nothing.
I didn't find anything, Diana.
- But something found me.
- What ?
Fate. Destiny.
Whatever it's called
when you realize...
the choices you thought you had
in life were already made.
Fox, what happened here ?
You were being paid a visit
by young Jeffrey Spender's father.
The cigarette-smoking man
came looking for his son,
who has now taken up the futile cause
that used to be mine...
- against his father.
- Why futile ?
Because there's nothing
to be done.
And at some point,
you just have to accept that...
the only way those you love
are gonna survive...
is if you give up.
That's where it all begins.
That's where we need to be
if we want to survive it.
Please help me.
They're going to leave me here.
Please stay away from me.
I can't help you.
They're packing everything up.
They aren't coming back here.
I know you.
- I can help you.
- You can't help me.
I know where
they're taking her.
I know how
You've gotta trust me,
Jeffrey.
[ Door Opens ]
Shut the door.
This is a highly sensitive area.
Go back. You're at a high risk
of contamination. Leave the room.
[ Screams ]
Hey, Scully, it's me.
Mulder, I was just dialing you.
Where are you ?
- I'm with Diana.
- I'm coming to get you.
No, we're coming to get you.
You're coming with us.
No, Mulder, listen to me.
I'm gonna take you to Cassandra.
Cassandra's gone, Scully.
I know, but I know where
she's gone to, Mulder.
Scully, it's no use.
Mulder, I'm going there
whether you're coming or not.
- Going where ?
- To the Potomac yards.
They're transporting her
by train car.
- Who gave you this information ?
- Agent Spender called me.
- All right.
I'm gonna send you on ahead.
- What is it ? What did she say ?
This may be our last chance
to stop them.
- [ Bell Dinging ]
- [ Brakes Screeching ]
- Turn around. Turn around, Scully.
- [ Train Horn Blaring ]
[ Train Horn Blaring ]
- [ Gunfire Continues ]
- What the hell is that ?
I think this is him.
You gonna tell me
what the hell is going on ?
- Our lives are in danger.
- Why couldn't you tell me that
over the phone ?
- If somebody overheard us,
it might create mass panic.
- Mass panic ? Over what ?
El Rico Air Base.
We waited to send
our communication.
We were worried
something had happened.
- Shots were fired at us.
- By who ?
I don't know.
We have people missing.
Where's Alex Krycek ?
[ Yelling ]
[ Spender ]
Krycek!
- I'm trying to get out of here.
- What are you talking about ?
We can't get past security.
They won't recognize my
authority to remove a patient.
My father did this to her.
She wants to tell her story.
Sorry son of a bitch.
You don't get it, do you ?
It's all going to hell.
The rebels are gonna win.
- They took it.
- They took what ?
[ Tires Screech ]
- Who sent the communications ?
- No one.
This isn't
supposed to be.
[ Man ]
What is this ?
Back. Back.
Back, back, back !
[ Chattering, Shouting ]
Back! Back!
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ Screaming, Yelling ]
The way these people died,
the loss of life here,
it is beyond words.
I can't imagine how it must be
for you, losing your mother.
Yes, sir.
But that's not why
I asked for this meeting.
Why did you ask for it ?
Because I'm responsible for
the deaths of those people...
at the air base hangar
in no small way.
I certainly didn't
prevent them.
I can assume then
you can explain how they died?
Because I've yet to hear
any explanation.
Agent Mulder can explain it.
I think Agent Scully to an extent.
They might have even prevented
what you see in those photos.
Agents Scully and Mulder
have been suspended by the F.B.I.
- Also my doing. And my mistake.
- I would ask--
I'd ask, sir, before you tell me
that it's not my business,
that you do everything you can
to get them back on the X-Files.
Far worse can happen.
And it will.
- Where are you going ?
- To pack up my office.
Agent Spender !
You have answers now ?
- Why didn't I hear
about those answers before ?
- I've had answers for years.
Then why didn't
we hear about them ?
- Nobody ever listened.
- Who burned those people ?
They burned themselves...
with a choice made long ago
by a conspiracy of men...
who thought they could
sleep with the enemy,
only to awaken another enemy.
What the hell
does that mean ?
It means the future is here,
and all bets are off.
Agent Scully,
make some sense.
Sir, I wouldn't bet against him.
Get out of here.
This picture you have,
I haven't seen it since you were born.
- You probably don't even know
who the other man is.
- I don't care. Get out.
It's Bill Mulder,
Fox Mulder's father.
Isn't that something ?
He was a good man,
a friend of mine,
who betrayed me in the end.
I know more than enough about
your past, enough to hate you.
Your mother was right.
I came here hoping otherwise.
Hoping that my son...
might live to honor me...
[ Cocks Weapon ]
like Bill Mulder's son.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Child ]
I made this!