[Morris] Once upon a time,
there were three...
how should I put this...
geeks.
Three more unlikely heroes
there never were.
[Byers]
We defend the defenseless.
I don't see any other way.
It wasn't long before
their naiveté...
- [Click]
- nearly got them killed.
So they hooked up
with an FBI agent...
[Byers]
That's why we like you, Mulder.
Your ideas
are weirder than ours.
And began publishing a...
what shall I call it...rag...
called The Lone Gunman.
[Langly] The guys at the NSA
and the CIA...
they tremble every time
we put out one of these babies.
From their cramped
basement office...
they pointed fingers at
powerful, evil forces.
And some not so evil.
In their own unique way,
the three gunmen were patriots...
fighting the good fight.
We tell the stories
others refuse to tell.
Yeah, that's one way to put it.
And provided, um, expertise...
for their friends at the FBI.
She's hot.
For a brief time,
it looked like they...
might actually make a difference
in this cold, cruel world.
They acquired an intern
who believed in their cause.
[Jimmy] You guys fight
the lost causes.
I want to help.
And a powerful
beautiful nemesis...
[Automatic Gunfire]
Who became an ally.
But the world is not kind
to idealists...
and those who fight
the good fight...
don't always win.
[Sonar Pinging]
Morris?
Morris, it's going "ping."
Oh, it most certainly is.
[Giggling]
Ping.
[Laughing]
You're going
to make me spill.
Mmm.
Morris, what is
all that stuff, anyway?
Oh, baby, don't
make me talk shop.
It is so boring.
But I want to know.
All right.
Well, where do I begin?
You know we're in
the Bermuda Triangle, right?
That place where all
those planes and ships...
have mysteriously disappeared?
Who do you think named it
the "Bermuda Triangle"?
Wait. You?
Yeah, that was in my former life...
before I joined
the private sector.
There are a lot of things
I can't talk about...
owing to matters of national security,
but I will say this:
There are powerful
forces out here.
Primal...
other-worldly forces...
- Mmm.
- Hidden beneath the waves...
just waiting to be...
plucked by man.
- [Engine Approaching]
- Somebody's coming.
Hmm?
Hey, whatever
you're selling...
we don't want any, okay?
No ganja.
[Woman Screaming]
Ho! Hey! Hey!
Wait, wait, wait...
Uh...
Oh, you want the girl?
Yeah, I can dig it.
I'm down with that.
Uh...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Guys, this is a rental.
There's a $15,000 deposit
on this...
Oh, God...
Your employer wanted
me to tell you...
you're fired.
[Engine Accelerating]
[Door Opening]
Morris Fletcher?
Finally.
What took you so long?
You must be Reyes.
Enchanté.
Yeah. Mr. Fletcher...
we've been told
you requested us by name.
We're very curious
about that.
Well, you two head the FBI's
X-Files unit, do you not?
I thought you'd appreciate
what I have to offer.
Which is?
[Chuckles]
You have no idea who you're
sitting here with, do you?
A guy who's up fudge creek
for violating The Federal Secrets Act.
How's that for starters?
Look, l-I've got
top security clearance.
I'm supposed to check in
every month...
with my former employer.
So I skipped
a few phone calls.
Big deal.
Let me give you a hint.
I used to work
at Groom Lake, Nevada.
Area 51.
I was a Man in Black!
The Men in Black.
What, you've never heard of us?
I saw the movie.
Yeah, well, there were a lot
of technical inaccuracies in that thing.
Anyway, I'm ready
to make a deal.
What deal
would that be?
The one that saves
my furry pink ass.
People are trying to kill me.
Did you hear about my boat?
Yeah, your female companion
told us what she witnessed.
My female...
Oh, you mean they didn't kill...
Brittany?
Brittany.
Well, thank God
she's still alive.
Look, I need protection.
I need to get out of here.
You scratch my back,
I'll scratch yours.
I can give you guys
the keys to the kingdom.
UFOs, aliens...
the whole 50 year cover-up.
I was there
for all of it.
Tell me, Mr. Fletcher...
these documents of yours...
are they indicative
of the kind of secrets...
you can reveal to us?
Honey... they're just the tip
of the iceberg.
This is the Jupiter 2
from Lost in Space.
Okay, yeah, th-those are B.S.,
but only those!
See, l-I was freelancing...
for this foreign billionaire.
I told him the air force
lost a flying saucer...
in the Bermuda Triangle and
that I could recover it for him.
In the Bermuda Triangle and
I just wanted to cruise
the Bahamas.
I never would've given him
the real thing.
That would be un-American.
Comin' out.
Well, he found out about it.
Now he wants to kill me.
I need protection.
Super Soldiers.
What do you know
about Super Soldiers?
A bit.
It may be... there's one I can
help you lay your hands on.
This Super Soldier,
he have a name?
Not he. She.
[Buzzer Sounding]
What in the hell
do they want?
[Banging On Door]
Gentlemen.
What happened here?
Did you get robbed?
No.
Uh, we're upgrading everything.
We gave away all our old crap
to the Salvation Army.
We're buying totally new stuff.
What can we do
for you, Agents?
Well, we were hoping
you could help us out.
You know that
for months now...
we've been investigating
this secret cadre...
these, uh, so-called
Super Soldiers.
Genetically-altered humans.
You mean the ones
that want to kill Mulder?
[Reyes] Exactly. We'd like your help
tracking one down.
This woman.
[Reyes]
You recognize her?
She's, um...
She's a fellow hacker.
Damn fine one.
[Byers] She calls herself
Yves Adele Harlow.
Uh, it's not her real name.
[Frohike]
We never learned her real name.
She disappeared a year ago,
and nobody's seen her since.
Well, we have reason to believe
that she's resurfaced...
and that she's become
one of these Super Soldiers.
[Frohike Laughing]
What in the hell...
are you talking about?
She's no Super Soldier.
Absolutely not.
Not a chance.
Who told you that?
[Morris]
This is pointless.
These three monkeys
couldn't find stink in an outhouse.
Why are we even here?
You son of a...
Hey, let me at him!
I'll kill him!
- I'll hold him down!
- Whoa, fellas...
- You've got a nerve coming here.
- Miserable son of a bitch.
Told you they wouldn't help.
[Doggett]
All right...
everybody just shut up.
This man
is a professional liar.
Every word out
of his mouth.
[Langly]
He's a scam artist.
He used us to track Yves down
a year ago.
[Frohike]
And then he abducted her.
Which is why I know
what happened to her.
[Clears Throat]
I facilitated a meeting, is all.
And the man
I was working for?
I didn't know in advance...
what he was planning to do
to her.
Not my finest hour,
I'll admit it.
Every word out
of his mouth.
[Morris]
Agents...
I'm telling you, you don't want
these three involved.
And they don't even have their
ridiculous Tinkertoy gizmos.
This place is like
How the Grinch Stole Radio Shack.
[Doggett] All right,
you three know this woman.
I want your help.
I need to track down
this Yves Adele Harlow.
Knock, please.
Oh.
My office hours are 3:00 to 5:00
Mondays and Fridays.
You'll make time for me,
Professor.
[Air Hisses]
Douglas, you ready to go?
Douglas?
[Gasps]
Airline reservation database.
What name do we look under?
Try our old standby...
different anagrams
of Lee Harvey Oswald.
"Area 51 Exposé"...ooh!
Where's your new issue?
This one's a year old.
Back off, Skeezix.
You'll never find her that way.
[Beeps]
He's right... no anagrams
for Yves Adele Harlow.
- So, who's Joey?
- What?
Joey Ramone?
Leader of the greatest punk rock
band in human history?
Now shut up.
[Snickering]
What?
What are you, 34, 35?
Why don't you cut your hair
and grow up, huh?
Need I remind you, Fletcher...
that Doggett and Reyes aren't
here to save you.
Yeah, well, get yourself
a real hero, anyway...
not some dead
teeny-bopper.
You want to know why
Joey Ramone's my hero?
'Cause people like you never
managed to grind him down.
They never stole his spirit.
He never gave in,
never gave up, and never sold out.
Right till his last breath.
[Scoffs]
And he's not dead.
Guys like that,
they live forever.
Langly...
just ignore him.
[Sighs]
Look, if we have to work
together, let's work together.
We don't have
to work together.
Well, watching you three try and
find your butts with both hands...
is not my idea of a fun time.
Now, wouldn't it be easier
tracking Yves...
if you knew her real name?
You know her real name?
Lois Runce.
Lois Runce? Aha.
I'm telling you the truth, boys.
Well, if you were,
it'd be a first.
[Knocking]
Nobody knows about that door.
That's our secret door.
Does Lois know about it?
Yves?
Jimmy?
Guys...
How you feeling, man?
[Morris]
Oh, right.
The old errand boy.
The guy used to intern
for you losers, right?
I wondered what happened to you.
Why is he here?
[Byers]
FBI business.
It's a long story.
Where the hell you been,
big guy?
Zurich. Then Malta.
Then Yemen.
And just now New Jersey.
It's been
a real geology lesson.
I ran out of money,
so I hitchhiked here...
then snuck in the back...
'cause I didn't know
if the place was being watched.
[Sighs]
I just had to see you guys.
It's about Lois.
Lois Runce?
That's Yves's real name.
I told you so.
Hey, wait a minute.
You tracked her
all over the world?
You?
[Sighs]
Mr. Brainpower here
is lucky to be alive.
Why did you send him?
Were you trying to get him killed?
He sent himself to find Yves.
We tried to talk him out of it.
Yeah, and now
I almost wish you had.
Jimmy, what is it?
Are you all right?
Last night I traced her...
to a little college
in New Jersey.
It's the closest I've been
in a year of searching.
I saw her.
I actually laid my eyes on her...
I called to her...
but she ran.
Later on, I found out...
Guys, I think
she murdered somebody.
One down.
John Gillnitz?
I'm Agent Reyes,
and this is Agent Doggett.
Is this the woman
you saw last night?
It was dark.
It could have been her.
Do you have her in custody?
We're working on it.
Sir, what can you tell us
about your friend?
Have any reason why
he may have been targeted?
Absolutely none.
Douglas was a wonderful teacher
and an even better researcher.
What did he research?
Elasmobranchii...
sharks, rays and skates.
He was a marine biologist?
An immunologist.
Sharks have a remarkable
immune system.
Toxins that would kill
nearly any other vertebrate...
pass right through them.
So he did medical research?
Douglas wanted
to save the world.
Cheer up, Gomer.
Bringing the whole room down.
This is a computer,
Langly.
Com-pu-ter.
Step away before
you embarrass yourself.
Always a pleasure, Kimmy.
Yeah, yeah.
So, then, how do you wish
to partake of my hacking genius?
Thanks toJimmy...
we know Yves's real name.
Hey, I told you
before he did.
Jimmy also told us
what kind of car she's driving...
silver X5 with New York plates.
Really? Way to go, special ed.
The New Jersey Turnpike
has video cameras...
at every tollbooth.
Langly hacked the system...
and spotted her
southbound at Newark.
Somewhat creative.
We spotted her again...
going through
the Fort McHenry Tunnel.
She passed through
not 20 minutes ago.
We're betting
she's headed for D.C.
We're going to try to intercept her
with your help.
Think you might find...
a military satellite
you could piggyback...
give us a bird's-eye view
of the Beltway?
Intriguing.
Stand aside, ladies.
We'll be on the cell.
I got shotgun.
Dream on.
You're staying here.
We need somebody
we can trust...
keeping an eye
on Fletcher.
I'm on it.
So, how'd you like Malta?
The only thing I can say
for sure is what killed him.
He was injected...
with some sort of
tiny poison pellet...
but the wound in his chest
was postmortem.
What is that?
That's what I said.
My best guess is bioluminescence...
but I'm still waiting
to hear back from our lab.
Bioluminescence, as in the stuff
that makes lightning bugs glow?
Lightning bugs, plankton,
jellyfish...
but generally
not dead college professors.
So, what? This stuff
was put on postmortem?
No, as near as I can tell,
it bled out of him.
It gets weirder still.
When I opened him up...
I found adhesions that indicate
past surgery...
so I'm figuring I'll find he had
a bypass or a pacemaker.
Instead, I find... this.
Looks like cartilage.
It is.
It was living tissue
grafted into him.
I have absolutely no idea why.
It held something.
Something that's
now missing.
Could that be the purpose
of this wound?
A little
ad hoc surgery?
Maybe that was the very purpose
of the murder.
Whatever was inside him,
she removed it.
What the hell was inside him?
I have no clue.
Seriously, this is the first
I'm hearing of it.
Weird organs?
I don't know
what to tell you.
You've never heard
of the man...
Professor Douglas Houghton?
You're looking at me oddly.
Perhaps because you've been known
to lie on occasion.
Yeah, well, I'm
not lying now.
I've said from the start...
I didn't know
what she was up to.
[Kimmy]
Damn it! Crashed again!
I cannot make magic
with substandard equipment.
What's the problem?
The problem is
it's a freakin' piece of junk.
I knew those guys
were broke...
but this is pathetic.
The guys are broke?
Are you kidding?
Look around this dump.
They had to hock
all their stuff...
just to pay the rent.
What about this?
Oh, their paper?
Deader than disco.
They haven't published
in months.
So saving the world
doesn't pay the bills.
There's a hot news flash
for you, huh? The chumps.
They were getting by all right...
till you put 'em out
of business.
Oh, and how exactly
did I do that?
When you took Yves.
They spent every last dime
trying to find her.
They're loyal
to their friends.
Hilarious, huh?
[Phone Rings]
Reyes.
[Byers]
You better get here quick.
Where are you?
The Hotel Farragut. Hurry.
[Bell Dings]
She's going
to kill that guy.
Doggett and Reyes
are on their way.
By then it'll be too late.
[Frohike]
Yves, don't do it!
Lois?
Should I call you that?
I prefer Yves.
So, we take it you're
not a Super Soldier.
Super what?
Long story.
Never mind.
Yves, you
weren't seriously...
going to smoke
that guy, were you?
I know you three mean well...
but I can't begin to tell you...
how badly you've
mucked things up.
[Door Opening]
So this guy just
up and bolted.
He hit her and then
he took off.
Nobody's seen him.
The room is registered
to one Leonard Southall...
of Darien, Connecticut.
It's an alias.
It's a stolen I.D.
The real Leonard Southall
died in 1996.
You want to tell
me who that was?
His real name...
I have no idea.
This is your bag,
isn't it?
It's quite a party
you've got planned for him.
Respirator...
surgical gloves...
scalpel.
Not to mention
this little item here.
[Reyes] You were planning
to cut him open, Ms. Runce...
just like you did the professor.
Why?
Yves, that can't
be true.
Tell them it's not.
It is, Jimmy.
Time is running short.
Unless you let me finish
what I started...
innocent people will die.
You want to elaborate on that?
First things first.
Who was it that put
you on to me?
[Groans]
Okay, guys, so she's not
a Super Soldier.
I made an honest mistake.
Ow!
[Yves]
As I suspected...
it's a tracking device.
I'm sure he meant
to activate it...
once he knew
you had me.
You've been wearing
that since Miami.
You've been running
a scam on us from the start.
Blowing up the boat.
The girl as your witness.
You planned all that.
[Doggett] That and all
the Super Soldier bull.
All that was
just to hook us.
So then you two
would in turn hook us.
And we'd track down
Yves for this slimeball...
all over again.
Well, what can
I tell you?
You three always get
the job done for me.
Who do you work
for, Fletcher?
An international arms dealer...
a billionaire...
and scum of the earth.
[Fletcher]
And...
he's also...
My father.
My father is a murderer...
and a supporter of terrorism.
I hate everything
he stands for.
[Jimmy]
Yves...
you're a murderer, too.
The man I killed
was a terrorist, Jimmy.
A zealot whose research
was funded by my father...
for its potential
as a weapons system.
Houghton was
an immunologist...
doing research
on sharks.
[Yves] Yes, and he used
his knowledge...
of their immune system
to devise a vessel of sorts...
one that kept him safe
from an engineered virus...
that he carried within him.
This man had living tissue
implanted in his chest.
Cartilage. Shark cartilage.
It contains something
which you removed.
That was this virus
you were talking about.
I destroyed it,
but it was only one of two.
Oh, man, the bald dude
at the hotel.
The one that got away.
[Yves] Think of him as
a human time bomb.
He can pass by any sniff dog,
any metal detector...
and no one would ever suspect.
What triggers
this time bomb?
Programmed cellular death...
genetically altered
to a high degree of precision.
The way the vessel
is decaying inside of him...
is virtually
clocklike.
It will lose integrity
and rupture at 8:00 tonight.
Five hours from now?
[Yves] This virus,
once it's airborne...
its kill radius is five
or six miles...
depending on the winds.
Potentially,
it could kill thousands...
tens of thousands.
Fletcher...
I know you're a dirtbag...
but, still, how could you
be a party to this?
[Yves] Fletcher's a con man,
not a killer.
He didn't know about it.
Providing all this is true,
how do we track this man down?
Kimmy,
zoom in more.
Zoom in.
Back off, kibitzer,
I'm doing it.
This thing is slower...
than Stumpy,
my one-legged granny.
Where did you get
this dinosaur turd?
Stop bellyaching
and work.
Those things will
kill you, you know.
Yeah, that's why I quit
20 years ago.
You want one?
So you're too broke
to publish, huh?
Pencil neck told me.
It's a shame.
This little rag always
was such a hoot.
I'm going to miss it.
But, hey, the world
spins on, right?
Maybe saving it is
a younger man's game.
Or a woman's.
Maybe it is.
Got to admit, Byers,
it hasn't exactly been our year.
And to top
it all off...
we screwed the pooch
pretty good today.
Maybe we should
pack it in.
And do what instead?
We never gave up.
We never will.
In the end...
if that's the best
they can say about us...
it'll do.
[Langly]
I got him!
[Kimmy]
It's my hack, Langly.
I got him.
We got him,
all right?
Our bad guy just rented
a blue Corolla...
under his alias,
Leonard Southall.
We just picked him up
on Kimmy's satellite.
[Kimmy] Yeah, hauling north
like a bat out of hell.
New Jersey Turnpike,
30 miles south of Newark.
I think I know
where he's headed.
[Nail Guns Popping]
[Phone Ringing]
Lone Gunman Newspaper Group.
Byers speaking.
Byers? John Doggett.
Agent Doggett,
do you have him?
Oh, yeah, we got him.
Listen, how much
do you trust...
this Yves Harlow...
Lois Runce...
whatever name
she's telling you?
Completely. Why?
Because the doctors here
have run every kind...
of imaging on this guy Southall
and come up snake eyes.
No virus, no cartilage vessel
in his chest, nothing.
They found nothing.
That doesn't make sense.
[Byers]
They're absolutely certain?
One hundred percent.
Agent Reyes and I
are looking like...
a couple of fools
on this one.
There must be something
we missed.
All I can tell you is,
we got the wrong guy.
There must be
a second man.
I know there is.
It's basic Terrorism 101.
Except we don't
know his name...
and we don't
know his target.
And we've got
one hour to find him.
Good evening.
You're good.
All my information pointed
to that man Leonard Southall.
He goes by an alias, he traveled
to Washington on this very day.
Clearly,
he's involved somehow.
He must be.
He made a beeline right back
to that biology department...
where the dead professor worked.
It's their base of operation.
[Langly] Yeah, so if Southall
is involved...
and yet he doesn't have
the virus inside of him...
So how exactly does
he fit into their plan?
Three-card monte.
You ever played it?
You have now.
What's that
supposed to mean?
It means these guys have
you running after the ace...
when you should be
chasing the queen.
Oh, my God.
Southall is the decoy.
That's all he is.
You were hot
on their trail...
so they gave you
someone else to follow.
I thought you didn't know
anything about terrorists.
I don't.
But, boy, do I know scams.
I wasn't a Man in Black
all those years for nothing.
They made you work
at finding Southall...
which tells me
the real guy...
is hiding in plain sight,
right out in the open.
A friend
of the dead professor?
A co-worker maybe.
The man who saw me through
the professor's window.
The one who identified me.
Ladies and gentlemen, scientists...
academic leaders
and government representatives.
Coming together
is our goal this evening...
coming together as one.
Those words are easily spoken.
But guiding our missile
into that fugitive...
and imponderable target
is hard indeed.
Sorry,
conference attendees only.
We're reporters.
What newspaper
you work for?
The Lone Gunman.
Never heard of it.
We're legit, man.
Show him
your press pass.
It's desperately important
that we get in there.
Yeah, buddy, come on.
These expired last December.
We've got five minutes.
We believe there's
a dangerous man...
in that room.
Folks, I need all of you
to step away right now.
Look, thousands
of people may die.
Mike, I got a situation over
by the main conference room.
John Gillnitz!
Step back, sir.
I'm really sorry.
Where'd he go?
Split up.
Four minutes left.
Good luck.
Hey, wait!
What do we do with this guy
once we find him?
Hold him till
I get there.
I'll do the rest.
- You mean cut him open?
- If that virus...
gets into the air stream,
we'll have failed.
People will die.
Whatever it takes.
Let's go.
Three minutes and counting.
[Distant Banging]
[Banging Continues]
Don't try to run.
I don't have to.
Yves, Jimmy, we found him!
Over here!
What do you plan to do?
By my watch,
it's two minutes to 8:00.
Not much time
for surgery.
Yves!
Jimmy!
Now you have a minute forty.
Guys.
Whatever it takes.
[Alarm Rings]
[Jimmy]
Byers! Frohike!
Langly!
Yves, come here.
Guys!
[Gurgling]
Oh, God. No.
Don't, Jimmy.
Jimmy, don't.
It's airtight.
They're already exposed.
No, guys.
Buddy, fight the good fight.
Both of you.
Never give up.
Vaya con Dios, amigos.
Arlington.
You must've pulled
some big strings...
to get those guys in here.
It's the least
I could do.
You ready?
Yeah.
Dana.
I'll catch up.
They meant so much to me.
I'm not sure
if they ever really knew.
Nobody knew...
what heroes they were.
It's not right.
It's not.
[Morris]
No, it's not.
Langly said to me...
the ones who never give up,
they never die.
I still don't know
what that means.
That means that like
everyone buried here...
the world is a better place
for them having been in it.
It means that
they're gone...
but they live on
through us all.
[Child]
I made this.