[Man] The Bible says God appeared
to Moses in a burning bush.
He came toJesus
on a mountaintop.
For Buddha, God came
while he sat under a tree.
God came to me in a vision
in the desert...
February 26, 1991.
[Gunfire]
My recon squad had engaged Saddam's army
in a small Bedouin encampment.
We'd been ambushed...
taken all by surprise,
and there were casualties.
- I can't feel my legs!
- You're gonna be okay.
- Don't worry.
- My legs!
Damn it, get on the radio!
We need some help here!
Zulu Six Two, we are under attack.
Repeat: We are under attack.
We are taking heavy
machine-gun fire.
[Man] We were holding our perimeter,
and we might've held up...
but on this day, I had
a terrible sense of foreboding.
I saw the future
of those brave men...
and they were about to die.
Death came to take my men...
but not me.
I was left as a witness
to a vision.
Angels from heaven.
[Gunfire]
[Gunfire Continues]
[Gunfire Ceases]
[Boots Thudding]
Behold, a whirlwind came out of
the north and a brightness was about it.
And out of the midst came the likeness
of four living creatures...
and they had the likeness
of a man.
I knew why my life
had been spared.
I was to deliver
the message of these angels...
of these sons of God.
To deliver the message of the god
who came before all other gods.
At 7:00 this evening,
in a Washington D.C. Alley...
a vehicle carrying the son
of Agent Dana Scully...
was forced to a violent stop
by a female shooter...
who proceeded
to kidnap the child at gunpoint.
The van was being driven
by three men...
asked by Agent Scully
to protect the child.
The three men are currently
working to I.D. The assailant.
John Doggett
was seriously injured...
by the same female shooter
as he tried to halt her vehicle.
Agent Doggett remains in a coma
under close watch...
at St. Mary's Hospital.
This kidnapping follows
on the heels of a failed attack...
on Scully's child by another
FBI agent, Robert Comer.
He remains
in critical condition...
also at St. Mary's.
Now, this man's motives...
and the motives
of the female kidnapper...
are still unknown.
Let me emphasize that the FBI
has no reason to believe...
that it cannot affect the safe
return of Agent Scully's child.
Agent Scully.
What are you doing?
I thought I told you
you didn't need to be here.
I just had to see
this for myself.
Go home.
To what?
I'm just saying,
you don't need...
to put yourself
through this, Dana.
We've got every stop pulled:
Every available agent
working to find your son.
And A.D. Brad Follmer
leading the charge.
Deputy Director Kersh asked him
to take the lead.
He knows how to run
a task force.
I think you see that
in there.
I see a man who withholds
information for Kersh.
A man who not
once but twice...
failed to prevent
an attack on my son.
You see a task
force in there.
I see a whitewash.
I know you're upset...
but you can't possibly
accuse Follmer or Kersh...
of having any part in this.
What is it going
to take for you?
How many people
have to be taken out...
for you to open
your eyes to it?
My son...
Agent Doggett...
Mulder.
Kersh protected you...
by not telling you
reports of Mulder's death.
As did Follmer. As did I.
You call it protection.
I call it a systematic
effort inside the FBI...
to eliminate us.
You accuse anyone
of anything in the FBI...
you have to accuse me
along with them.
Scully, where are you going?
To find my son.
[Heart Monitor Beeping]
Hi.
His hands are so cold.
Have you talked
to the doctors yet?
They say the good news is that
there's no swelling of the brain...
but they were very frank that
he could just never wake up.
I wonder if
he can hear us.
There'd be soldiers
in Vietnam...
bodies turned inside out.
I'd hold their hands
just like you're doing.
Tell them
it was going to be okay.
Do you think it helped?
Talking to them?
Well, I always thought
it was like...
like praying.
Even if they can't hear...
maybe... God can.
[Phone Ringing]
Hello.
How's he doing?
No change.
I need to see you right away, Monica.
Are you alone right now?
Skinner's here with me.
I'd prefer
if Skinner didn't know.
We found her.
Who?
The woman that took William.
She's a wanted felon
and a part of the UFO cult...
that the FBI was investigating.
I need anything that you
can find on her, Monica...
but I need you
to get it quietly.
"Access denied"?
Yeah, we'll see about that.
If they I.D.'d the woman...
then why isn't the FBI
investigating it?
I asked them not
to tell the FBI.
What are you doing, Dana?
I'm trying to get my son back.
- We're locked on.
- Like there was ever a doubt.
Which brings us that much
closer to finding William.
Langly's inside the system.
I'm hacked
inside the phone company.
Going to use their mainframe...
to scan the map
for a locator signal.
[Scully] Before William was kidnapped,
Byers was able...
to tuck a cell phone under the
padding of the baby's car seat.
[Frohike]
Call the phone, and Langly...
can use the signal
to find its location.
Find the phone, find the baby.
You mean, assuming the kidnapper
hasn't found the phone.
[Rapid Busy Signal On Phone]
We'll keep trying.
[Beep]
[Gun Cocking]
This is madness,
and you know it.
They failed you once
with your child.
They're going to
fail you again.
Then I'll find him myself.
You can't do this alone.
Look, what alternative
do I have...
when the FBI is all
but telling me...
they think
that my son is already dead?
[Byers]
We've got a signal...
in Warfordsburg, Pennsylvania...
off the interstate.
You coming with me?
Or am I going alone?
[Cell Phone Vibrating]
[Car Door Opens, Shuts]
[Camera Shutters Clicking]
[Cell Phone Ringing]
[Phone Beeps]
Have you got him?
[Woman]
Yes. He's safe. We're here.
[Man]
We need to go carefully now.
I want you to stay
where you are.
I'm sending someone to get you,
all right?
Yes.
[Low Rumbling]
It's moving.
It's moving!
[Rumbling And Grating]
[Rumbling Continues]
[Humming]
[All Gasp]
[Pounding]
Can you hear me?
We need some tools.
Go get some tools!
Come on, move it!
[Tires Squealing]
[Brakes Screeching]
Federal agent!
[Panting]
John Doggett... where is he?
He's not in his bed.
They've taken him
down to Radiology...
to run a CAT scan.
Would you like me
to call down to his doctor?
No. No, I was
just worried.
I'm sorry.
What?
Nothing.
I've known you a long time...
and this just seems, uh...
a little traditional for you.
Maybe when you're lost...
you knock at the door
with the porch light on.
Hey, hey.
I want you to know,
I'm doing all I can...
to find the woman
who did this.
Even though we got
people inside the FBI...
working against us.
It was foolish going
after her by yourselves.
We could have been there...
long before you, Monica.
Could have even
captured the suspect.
Instead, she got away.
This is complicated, Brad.
If you came in here
to bust me...
No. No.
I came here to ask
for your cooperation.
Not sharing information...
creates an atmosphere
of distrust...
and then I'm less apt...
to share my
information with you.
What haven't you shared with me?
This FBI agent who tried
to kill Scully's baby...
has come around.
He's got something
he wants to tell us.
What?
I need your cooperation.
You said he tried to
tell you something.
How is that possible?
He didn't tell me exactly.
He wrote it down.
I don't know what this means.
I don't know either.
But it means something.
And I want to know what.
Just tell me where you got this.
You know what it means?
Robert Comer wrote
this, didn't he?
The FBI agent who tried to kill my son.
And how did you get it?
I got it under the condition...
that I share
what I learn from you.
Take it.
What is it?
What does it mean?
If I don't tell you...
you're good on
your word, right?
That means that
you've learned...
absolutely nothing from me.
Where are you going?
To the hospital.
Hey, it doesn't work
that way.
Look, this began when the agent
lying in that hospital...
crashed his motorcycle
running the border from Canada.
Somehow, he got to Washington
without a scratch...
and he tried to kill my son.
Now, tell me,
how did he do that, Monica?
With something...
I found in his jacket pocket...
in a jacket that he wore to my
house that I put three shots in.
The artifact...
a piece of the ship.
[Heart Monitor Beeping]
[Rumbling]
[Beeping Speeds Up]
Let go.
Oh, my God.
Let go of my hand.
Turn off the monitors, or
they're going to alert somebody.
[Shuts Off Heart Monitor]
[Gags]
Now tell me who sent
you to kill my son...
or I will take that pillow
from under your head...
and make them the last
breaths that you take.
Your son has to die.
I'm not what you think.
Please...
The FBI sent me undercover...
on a man named Josepho
to get inside his cult...
whose followers believe an alien
race will rule the world.
[Gasping]
One day, God told Josepho to
lead us a thousand miles north...
to find a ship
buried in the ground.
You have a piece of that ship
in your hand.
Josepho believes...
that that ship is a temple...
which houses the physical
manifestation of God.
Are you saying...
that God asked you
to kill my child?
No.
Josepho said God spoke to him
of a miracle child.
A future savior coveted
by forces of good and evil.
Josepho believes your son
is this child.
Then why does he
want to kill him?
He doesn't.
He wants to protect him.
Josepho believes
your son will follow...
in his father's paths and try
and stop the aliens' return.
Unless his father...
was to be killed.
That is the prophecy.
You came here
to kill her son...
against this man and his cult?
To stop them?
Are you saying you believe this
prophecy but acted alone?
What he's saying is
that Mulder is dead.
That that's true.
That they killed him to
fulfill this prophecy.
And that your son must die too.
Or everyone...
all of mankind
will perish from Earth.
Please...
Please, let me...
Please... Please...
What is going on here?
What are you doing in here?
[Nurse]
They turned off all the monitors.
They removed his intubation.
What are you doing in here?
This patient
does not need support.
He's breathing on his own.
Step outside.
Both of you.
Let's go.
Get me A.D. S Follmer and Skinner.
It's not working.
You weren't followed?
No.
He's safe now.
He's safe with us.
[Loud Rumbling]
Where are Scully and Reyes?
They were told to wait out here.
Assistant Director...
we need Scully
and Reyes, now.
What are we going
to tell them?
Who?
The FBI about Agent Comer.
About what just happened.
About how he was healed.
Just tell them the truth.
They're not on our side.
They will use
the truth against us.
Dana, you don't believe
what you heard in there.
You don't believe what
that man was telling you.
How can you doubt him?
I mean, after everything
that you've just witnessed.
After what you saw
with my son.
I mean, it's-it's
exactly what I feared...
that there's something
terribly wrong...
from the very moment
that he was conceived.
Your child was a miracle, Dana.
I don't doubt that
the things I've witnessed...
are any less miraculous.
But your son
is not an abomination...
a thing that should
cease to exist.
You tell me on that ship
is written scripture...
from the world's
great religions.
Tell me a religion...
that decrees
the death of a child.
Not just your child,
but any child.
This is a man saying
these things to us.
How many religions
warn of false prophets?
Men sent to deceive us?
The only thing that I believe...
is that your son
may still be alive...
and we can find him
and save him.
And with that object
in that room...
we can save
Agent Doggett too.
You two better get out of here.
Agent Comer's dead.
What?
This man was alive.
You saw him.
He was alive.
Somebody was in here.
Where did it go?
[Follmer]
Where did what go?
This man had
something in his hand.
A small piece of metal.
It's what revived him.
L-It's why he could
be taken off life support.
A piece of metal?
I don't know
what she's talking about.
Who else came into this room?
Why are you questioning me?
Did you leave the room?
[Follmer]
Agent Reyes.
This woman came in here,
and this man was alive.
He was more than alive.
He'd been healed.
He'd been brought back to life.
This man was murdered,
but it wasn't by us.
Agent Reyes.
Who else was in here?
You were in here.
I came in and found you.
Were you alone in here?
Was he alone in here?
She went to get the doctors.
Search this man.
For what?
Monica!
Scully saw it.
Ask Agent Scully.
Agent Scully...
Where's Scully?
Agent Scully.
I never meant for this.
All that's been lost.
I never meant
to put you at risk...
to risk losing you too.
She's fighting for you.
Monica's out there
trying to find a way.
And she's not going
to let you go.
Agent Scully.
Agent Doggett. Oh!
I heard someone talking.
Yeah, that was me.
That was me talking to you.
No, it wasn't you.
They're going to come to you,
but you can't trust them.
Do you understand that?
Scully.
Oh, my God.
[Cell Phone Rings]
Scully.
Listen carefully, Agent Scully.
You want to see your son?
You come alone...
and you follow my instructions
to the letter.
[Car Approaching]
[Engine Stops]
[Car Door Opens, Closes]
Sorry to keep you waiting...
but I had to make sure
you were alone.
I only wish to protect the boy...
from those who'd harm him.
He's a very special boy.
I came here to take him back.
"Behold, a whirlwind
came out of the north...
"and a brightness was about it.
"And out of the midst...
"came the likeness
of four living creatures...
and they had the likeness
of a man."
That's the Bible.
Did you know it?
Ephesians.
The Bible...
describing giants
who walk the earth.
Who'd believe it?
Only the faithful...
and we who have seen them.
These... Super Soldiers.
The true sons of God.
I want to see my son.
You struggle to believe.
It's so incredible...
but your son will lead
this alien race.
He was put here to lead.
I'll bring you to him,
to see your son.
After you do something for me.
After you bring something
I need.
Confirmation that Mulder's dead.
You killed Mulder?
No.
I believed he was dead...
but now I have reason
to doubt that.
And if he's alive...
he's the one thing preventing
your son's true destiny.
You told me I could see my son.
You lied.
If you want to see the boy...
you'll bring me the head
of Fox Mulder.
[Scully Over Phone]
Get ready, Monica.
Hold on.
His car is wired.
Here we go.
They say he's about a mile
ahead, turning off the highway.
What about these hills?
Are we going to lose
him in these hills?
[Beeping]
[Frohike]
Yeah, yeah.
How are we in terrain?
That transponder
will track this guy...
driving under water
to Brazil.
Langly.
What just happened?
We're coming to a turn.
Is this it?
Uh, yeah.
Turn.
I think they lost the signal.
They have to get it back.
Piece of crap!
Hey, louder, why don't you?
Tell them we're working on it.
Here, you be the messenger.
[Low Rumbling]
[William Crying]
What is it?
What's happening?
The baby started crying...
and it just came to life.
Hey, guys, we lost him.
And we just ran out
of road out here.
William?
William!
[William Continues Crying]
[Low Rumbling Continues]
[Low Creaking]
[High-Pitched Whirring]
[Rumbling Continues]
William!
[Rumbling In Distance]
No.
Oh, my God!
Dana...
[Baby Crying In Distance]
Oh, my...
William?
[Crying]
Oh, sweetie!
[Footsteps]
I came to give you
a ride home.
They told me
you were in here.
Yeah.
I came in here
and prayed for you.
Yeah, I know.
This voice in my head,
it was...
it was talking to me...
telling me to get up...
telling me to warn Scully
about this man.
I mean...
was it you talking to me?
I only prayed for your life.
- [Tapping On Door]
- Uh, Deputy Director?
Mr. Follmer.
Sir, it's, um...
It's about that report
you have there.
The investigation...
of Special Agent
Robert Comer's death.
Yes?
As you know, A.D. Skinner
refused to sign it...
believing that
Agent Comer was murdered...
in his hospital bed.
But you did sign it,
isn't that right, Mr. Follmer?
Finding nothing to support...
that allegation.
Well, that's just it, sir.
I did find something.
The monitors in
Agent Comer's room...
they recorded his condition
moment by moment...
showing that his vital signs...
did improve just before
his equipment was unplugged.
They did, in fact...
return back to normal.
And you have an explanation
for that, yes?
No, sir, I don't.
And you want what?
I just want to take
my name off it.
Maybe if you weren't so busy
backpedaling, Mr. Follmer...
you might get me an explanation.
Excuse me.
I'm sure you heard all of that.
Congratulations.
It would appear now...
that everything is dead
but this case.
I'm sure I can take care
of that, Deputy Director.
Quite sure.
[Child]
I made this!