The Cylons were created by man.
They evolved.
They rebelled.
There are many copies.
And they have a plan.
Previously on Battlestar Galactica:
Congratulations, Doctor.
You've just uncovered your very first Cylon.
I'm not a Cylon.
This isn't happening.
I've been here for months.
By myself, on the run.
One step ahead of the Cylons.
You're going out there or I'm
gonna blow your brains out.
Right here, right now.
How did Crashdown die?
He gave his life in the...
in the finest tradition of the service.
You have my parole.
When I'm on duty, I'll make no attempt
to free her or sow insurrection
among the crew.
And when I'm not on duty,
I'll report directly back to this cell.
I have a few months to live.
And in that time,
I will lead the people to salvation.
It is my sole purpose.
As it appears obvious that the
government cannot function
under the current circumstances,
I have decided to dissolve
the Quorum of Twelve.
And as of this moment,
I have declared martial law.
You're sweating.
It's hot in here.
How long have you known
lieutenant Valerii was planning
to assassinate Commander Adama?
I had no idea she was
planning anything of the kind.
You were frakking her!
I ended that weeks ago,
on your orders.
You covered for her,
you lied for her.
- I admit I used bad judgment.
- You protected her at every turn.
Colonel, I had no idea she was a Cylon.
I'd like to exercise my article
21 rights at this time.
Oh, I'm sure you would.
I guess you haven't heard.
Cylons don't have rights.
- Cylon? Wait a minute.
- You know what we do with Cylons, Chief?
- I'm not a Cylon.
- Roslin came up with the execution method.
- I'm Galen Tyrol!
- She put a Cylon out of the airlock.
My father was a priest!
My mother was an oracle.
I've served on Battlestars
since I was 18 years old.
Pegasus, Columbia,
Atlantia, Galactica.
Don't talk to me like you're
a soldier!
You are not a soldier!
The old man always had a soft spot for you.
Let him decide what to do with you.
Colonel, you gotta believe me.
I am not a Cylon.
I'd never do anything to hurt Adama.
I love the old man.
That's what your girlfriend said.
Get him the hell out of here!
Chief?
I thought you were on Kobol.
Don't... you... talk to me.
Don't come near me.
Don't touch me.
If you do, I swear...
I will kill you.
Cylon-occupied Caprica
No sign of Centurions on the perimeter.
I don't like it. The human
toasters don't go anywhere alone.
- Think they're bait?
- Well, a pair of Cylons
don't just drive up here
in broad daylight.
Not after we hit that
convoy last week.
Frakkin'-A.
All right, screw it.
Pass word for everybody to sight in.
I wanna blow these Cylons away
before they ever knew what hit them.
Got it.
Unh! We gotta figure out
where the hell we are.
Why? You don't know?
You're the navigator.
You were driving.
Resistance
En subs by Laddin
bsg-cz.net
47,861 survivors
In search of a home.
Called Earth.
Earth.
All right we can head towards Gups' Point.
There's an emergency airstrip there.
No.
I've been.
I was thinking we could
head southwest.
Did you hear that?
- Drive through a lot of bad neighbourhoods?
- Better safe than sorry.
I hear that.
- We're sitting ducks down here!
- You go, I'll cover!
- Why me?
- Don't start!
Fine!
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Go!
Five of them, split up between
nine and one. 50 meters.
Ready?
Go!
Didn't see any shiny
silver out there.
I think we're dealing with
the human variety.
Hope so... they're not as
tough as mechanicals.
They do bleed good, though.
You gotta like that.
Let's get out of here!
Come on!
They locked the Chief up with Boomer.
Tigh thinks he's a Cylon.
I know.
I'm gonna see the Colonel now.
I think he wants me to find
a way to clear the Chief. Or...
Or what? Throw him out the airlock
like a piece of garbage?
If Commander Adama were in charge,
this would never happen.
Yes, but he's not in charge, is he?
No, but I've known the Chief for years.
He's no toaster.
He was involved with Lieutenant Valerii,
who most certainly is a toaster.
That word is racist.
I don't like it.
Sure... he's shown some bad
judgment getting involved with her,
but that doesn't mean he's a toaster.
- You've got to help him.
- Say something, Gaius.
Tell her you won't have racial
epithets used in your presence.
I'm very sorry. I was gonna tell
the Colonel there's nothing I can do.
The Cylon detector I developed doesn't work.
Clearly.
No!
You've got to help him.
Your child's gonna be half toaster.
How does that make you feel?
Nothing could make me happier.
I just don't know what I'd possibly say.
Excuse me.
He helped you!
He didn't tell anyone what
you did on Kobol.
What you did to Crashdown.
What I did to Crashdown
saved your life.
Are you blackmailing me?
Help the Chief to help
yourself, Doctor.
Yes, Doctor. That's what
you're best at, isn't it?
- Deck log.
- What the hell's the matter
with your Cylon detector, Doctor?
You gave the assassin a pass.
Yes, but that was a beta test, a preliminary.
Clearly I hadn't perfected my methodology,
- and she slipped through.
- Fuel report.
So that the hell are you telling me here?
That we are back to square one?
That no one's results are definitive?
That we have no way
of knowing who are the
Cylons among us?
No, I'm saying that since Valerii's te--
since the assassin's test, I've
developed a new set of protocols which
should eliminate any errors...
anomalies, that cropped up earlier--
If you let me test the Chief's blood,
I might be able to tell once and for all if--
No "if". I want a definitive answer.
No more of your weasely techno babble.
He's a Cylon or he's not. So get down
there and do something right for a change.
I am the Vice President.
Legally speaking, if the
President is incapacitated,
shouldn't I take over her duties--
Legally speaking,
I have declared martial law.
That makes you nobody.
So... unless you want to
join Roslin in the brig,
I suggest you get to work.
It's good to see you, Colonel.
Aren't you getting tired
of the continuous humiliation?
The disrespect from mechanics
and Colonels alike?
What do you think?
Maybe it's time to do something about it.
- What is this?
- The fleet Captains
are reporting protests among the civilians.
Demonstrations, petitions,
even some civil disobedience.
All over the declaration
of martial law.
Sir, there's more.
The Aturian refining vessel
has stopped refining tylium.
They say if they don't have
a voice in the government--
What?!
Their captain says they'll send fuel once
the civilian government has been restored.
And three other ships are
also refusing to resupply Galactica
until the President's reinstated.
And I got a note from combat warning
about problems with tylium resupply.
So watch your fuel burn
till further notice.
- Questions? - Yeah, when you
coming back to the card game?
I'm afraid when I'm off duty I'll be
enjoying the intimate surroundings
of the brig until...
ah, well, until further notice.
Come on back.
We miss you, Captain.
- We could bring the game to you.
- Somehow I doubt Colonel Tigh would approve.
Oh come on.
Hey, all right, all right.
Hey! Knock it off!
- Morning, Sir.
- Sergeant.
Shall we?
- Morning, Sir.
- Morning, Dee.
- Fancy meeting you here.
- I was just on my way, Sir.
- Hey, guys.
- How's it going, Dee?
Good, thanks.
- How's my father today?
- Uh, Commander Adama's the same... Captain.
He's sedated. Resting comfortably
since the surgery.
Trouble brewing in the fleet, though.
Oh, I'm shocked.
What kind of trouble?
Martial law isn't going
down too well.
Protests, demonstrations.
Some ships are even refusing
to resupply Galactica.
And this is the honeymoon period.
What's a dictator to do?
I, um, I wish...
I wish you were in command, Sir.
Dee...
He's hitting the bottle.
A lot.
Thank you for the company,
Petty Officer Dualla.
You're welcome, Sir.
- You okay, baby?
- No, I'm not okay.
My head feels like it's gonna
roll off my shoulders.
- What are you working on?
- I'm trying to figure out how to
solve our resupply problem now
that half the fleet has gone out on strike.
- You serious?
- Yes, I'm serious.
I should probably call a summit
sit-down with all our ships' captains
and explain the situation and tell
them why I had to declare martial law.
Screw them. Like you have to
explain yourself to them.
It wouldn't hurt.
It would cool things down a little.
What?
Nothing.
No, no, no, it's...
you're the boss. Far be it from me to tell
you how to do your job.
- I know that's one of your issues.
- Just say it.
I don't know, it just feels
kind of... touchy-feely
You know, "Let's all sit
down and talk about how
we feel about martial law."
Bill would never do that.
But you gotta do what you gotta do.
I mean, Bill may never get
on his feet again.
Honey... honey, you handle
this the way you want.
They'll respect that.
Eventually.
This is the XO. Mr. Gaeta, send the
following to all ships' captains
Message begins: Resupply operations
of this ship are not, repeat, not optional.
All ships to recommence scheduled
supply runs immediately.
Failure to comply will result
in... stern measures.
Message ends.
You happy now?
- I'll fake.
- I'll draw fire.
Hi.
We're not Cylons.
Right. You're human.
You have a soul.
You swim in the stream.
We heard it all before.
Hey, colonial fleet.
Notice the uniforms?
Yeah, right, we've seen
Cylons in uniform before.
- We're human.
- Yeah, right.
- Everyone on Caprica is dead.
- You're not.
I just got here.
I want to hear some names.
I'm Anders.
- Samuel T. Anders?
- Yeah, that's right.
This is Jo-man, Rally, Ten-point...
Sue-Shaun, Crip-Key, Morris Fink.
Kara, these are the Caprica Buccaneers.
- Hmm. I don't think so.
- Give me a ball, little girl.
I'll shove it up your ass.
Please... try.
Okay,
since we're all getting along so well,
can people stop pointing their guns at us.
How does a professional pyramid
team survive a nuclear holocaust?
We were in the mountains when the
Cylons attacked. High altitude training.
We've been on the run ever since.
- Doing what?
- Raiding military stores
for ammo. Anti-radiation meds.
And plugging toasters whenever
they show up.
- Same as us.
- Okay...
how many foul breaks did you
have in the playoff against Aerilon?
- You're kidding, right?
- You either have the answer,
or you have a bullet.
Three.
Wrong.
- Four.
- Three.
Three. Last one was called
back on instant replay.
He's right, Starbuck.
I lost 20 cubits on that game.
Fine.
For now.
on three.
1.
2.
3.
You know you guys suck, right?
Can't shoot, can't pass.
Sure as hell can't take the point.
Everyone's a critic.
Here's your, uh, medication,
Madame President.
And a little something from the galley.
Thank you, Corporal Venner.
Chamalla and liquorice.
Would you like some?
- I hate liquorice.
- Me too.
It's interesting he still
calls you Madame President.
You still have a lot of
supporters out there.
Something ugly is coming.
I can feel it.
Sir, refinery captain's still not
cooperating. And now seven
other container ships are
refusing to release their supplies.
- Food, medicine, even coffee.
- Coffee?
This is getting ridiculous.
Frak this. It's time to get their attention.
I'm sending in the marines.
I want a Raptor and an armed marine
boarding party for every ship
refusing the resupply order.
Sir, we're stretched pretty
thin on manpower.
I'm not sure we have enough marine non-coms
to command that many boarding parties, Sir.
Well, pull pilots and deck officers to
command the boarding parties if you have to.
Tell them to get over there and
bring back the supplies.
Whatever it takes.
- Make it happen, Lieutenant.
- Yes, Sir.
Heavy Hauler Transport "Gideon"
People, step back, all right?!
We're just here for the supplies!
Galactica Boarding Party Six
Lt. Joe "Hammerhead" Palladino, Commanding
Just stay out of the way
and no one gets hurt!
For the last
time, step back!
Step back!
Cease fire!
Four civilian dead. How the frak
could this have happened?
What'd you expect, genius? You put
a pilot in charge of crowd control.
Palladino! Did you give the order
to shoot on that crowd?
No, Sir, of course not.
The crowd surrounded us.
- Were they armed?
- No, Sir, but...
you had to be there. They were
yelling and screaming at us,
and then it got violent.
They started throwing things,
canisters.
- Coffee, I think.
- Coffee?
You shot people for
throwing coffee?
The crowd was out of control.
They were pressing in on us.
My men were getting hurt.
Somebody took a shot.
I don't know who it was.
Then all hell broke loose.
If ever we needed you, Bill,
it's right now.
Troops shooting unarmed civilians.
This is a travesty.
He has truly stepped over the line.
It'll cause an explosion in the fleet.
The press will have a field day.
The ships would begin to splinter.
The Cylons will be able to eliminate
us a few ships at a time.
We've got to get out of here now.
- Corporal.
- I am right with you.
I'm so glad you said that.
I want to take Billy and Elosha with me.
Of course you do.
I've worked out a way of
getting us in the hangar deck.
And I can get us a Raptor.
But we're still gonna need
clearance to get off the ship.
- I know how to get that.
- You do?
Question is, where do we go
once we get off this ship?
We'll have to find some place to hide
in the fleet while we rally
support among the people.
I've got an idea about that.
You're not going to like it.
I'm not cut out for this.
I never was.
Don't talk like that, Saul.
This is your moment.
Me and Bill, side by side, that was the deal.
It was never supposed to be me alone.
Well, like it or not, you're in command,
so you better deal with it.
I don't want to deal with it.
I do not want to command.
Don't you get it?
Jeez, why do I listen to you?
What are you talk? I never told you
to send troops out to that ship.
No, no, you didn't tell me to
send troops anywhere.
You just manipulate. You always do.
You put the knife in, and you twist it.
Oh, right,
you're going to blame me
for your own inadequacy?
I'm not blaming you, Ellen.
you are so frakking passive that
if I didn't push you,
you would never get your head out
of that frakking bottle and do anything.
I warned you.
I'm telling you.
- I love you so much.
- Shut up, Ellen.
I guess you really must hate me.
I don't know if it makes any difference
right now, but I'm really sorry
you got pulled into this.
You know, what we had--
Was nothing.
Nothing.
You're a machine.
I'm not.
Well, whatever I am,
I know how I felt.
- Software doesn't have feelings.
- Open the cell.
I never meant to hurt you.
I'd like some privacy, please.
I'll be fine, thank you.
And how are we this evening?
What do you want?
I'm here to determine whether
you're a Cylon or not.
Your arm, please.
His test doesn't work too well.
I mean, he gave me the green light.
The test works...
just fine.
Chief?
I lied to you, Sharon.
I covered up your true nature from
the rest of the fleet for my own purposes.
What did you do to him?
He's not breathing.
No, he's dying right now, Sharon.
I can save him
if you tell me how many Cylons
there are left in the fleet.
I don't know,
but I'm not getting a pulse.
Yes, you do. Now, buried
deep down in that thing you call
- a subconscious you know how many.
- I don't know!
He doesn't have time for this, Sharon.
His organs are shutting down.
In ten seconds time, he'll experience
complete brain stem death.
Now how many?
Do you love him, Sharon?
only you can save him!
10.
9.
do you love him?
Do you love him, Sharon?
Eight!
There are eight.
All right, let's get these
weapons unloaded. Let's go!
Hit an armory earlier today,
about 18 clicks north.
- Brought home a lot of toys.
- What is this place?
Delphi union high school.
Toasters don't patrol this area.
It's good place to get some
shut-eye, a bite to eat.
- How many people you have here?
- 53.
We had almost a hundred before the
toasters ambushed us last week.
Let's go!
- More pyramid teams?
- Nah, just us C-Bucs.
Rest are survivalists,
hikers mostly.
How's your stock of
anti-radiation masks?
Raided a couple of hospitals
down in Pilgrim Bay.
I figured we've got enough
for three months.
Let's get you some
bunk space, come on.
53...
Not exactly an army.
A hell of a lot better
than the two of us
if we're going to assault an airbase,
steal a heavy raider,
and get the frak off this planet.
I'll just be a moment.
Doctor...
I need your help.
But it's illegal, dangerous, and in
violation of your oath as
an officer.
You're a lousy salesman.
Corporal! Corporal Venner.
I, uh...
I just want to tell you how much the
President appreciates all the
little things you do for her.
Hey, anything I can do to
make things easier for her.
Great. She, um...
has a special request.
If I could just get your signature, Sir.
Why are we closing down Causeway B?
Integrity testing, Sir.
Got chewed up pretty bad when
the toasters boarded us.
And we've been getting some
pressure drops in there.
Tell 'em to get it fixed.
- Oh! Sorry.
- Lieutenant.
Things are pretty frakked up
these days, huh?
Yeah, things are pretty
frakked up most days.
If people are upset, they should
go through the proper channels.
- I'm not sure I understand what...
- I was running some maintenance checks,
detected a series of scrambled calls
going out over the past few hours.
You wouldn't happen to know
anything about that, would you?
No, Sir. Off-log calls are against regs.
Hmm... that's right.
I'm sure you won't approve.
But I guess that's nothing new.
I just want you to know that this, um...
this isn't about you and me.
Good-bye, dad.
- You gonna help out here or what?
- They're putting the Chief in there,
you know?
I don't care if they put
a giant parakeet in here.
Colonel says build a cell,
we build a cell.
This isn't right.
He's one of us.
No, he's one of them.
He always was. We just never saw it.
No, he's innocent.
She tricked him.
Wow, such loyalty.
Were you frakking him too?
You want to get pissed at someone,
you get pissed at Boomer.
She's the one who put the
Chief in the cell here, not us.
- Evening, Sir.
- Evening, Dee.
Fancy meeting you here.
- Everything set?
- Roger that.
Sorry, captain.
Can't chit-chat today.
Captain!
I'm having trouble with the ordnance
tracking on my Raptor, Sir.
I can't get it to cycle.
Oh... change of plans, boys.
Instead of getting some rack time,
I going to take a minute to do
the Lieutenant's job for her.
- Yes, Sir.
- After you.
Okay, make it look good,
but not too good.
Hold it!
Private, do you know who I am?
Good.
You and I have something in common.
We each took an oath to protect
and defend the Articles of Colonization.
Those articles are under attack,
as is our entire democratic way of life.
Now, my duty won't let me stand
here and allow that to happen.
So I intend to go through that hatch
and get off this ship.
Damn it.
They should be here by now.
You can either stand aside,
or you can shoot me.
You'll have to decide where your duty lies.
Madame President...
Madame President, this way.
Madame President.
I'm not getting on that ship with you.
What?
I understand what you're trying to do.
But it's going to divide the fleet.
At the very best, it'll create
an insurgency against Adama.
And at the worst, a civil war.
Taking part in that is a line
that I won't cross.
We do not have a lot of time.
I wish you well.
Dustoff two-seven, checkers green,
ready for launch on medical mission.
Request clearance.
Good to see you. You okay?
I think so. My feet barely touched
the ground getting here.
I know what you mean.
Dustoff two-seven. Standard port three
departure approved. Cleared for launch.
Standard port three, wilco.
Sir. Corporal Venner reports
the former President's missing.
- Missing?
- Two men down, cell's empty.
Damn it.
Alert security.
Set condition two!
No one on or off the ship!
Attention, set condition two throughout
the ship. Repeat, set condition
two throughout the ship.
Sir. Flight log records a Raptor departed
the ship two minutes ago
with Doc Cottle on
a medical emergency.
Medical? Confirm that.
Dradis has their transponder
bearing 2-8-7 carom 0-0-3. Range 2-7.
Get the cap on the horn and have them
intercept. And get Captain Adama
out of the brig.
Sir, Dr. Cottle is still inboard.
He says he was forced
to request the Raptor at
gunpoint by Captain Adama.
Son of a bitch.
Dee, put me through to that Raptor.
Cap has visual on their target.
Turn that ship around, Apollo,
or I'll order the cap to shoot you down.
- We're not turning back.
- I'll do it.
Don't think I won't just because
you're the old man's son.
Then do what you have to do, Galactica.
Apollo out.
Fire across their bow.
Hot Dog, Galactica.
- Acknowledge.
- Wilco, Galactica.
Hot Dog reports they're
not turning around, Sir.
- Where are they now?
- Dradis shows them approaching cloud nine.
Sir, if they dock, we may lose them.
Cloud Nine is one of the busiest
transport hubs in the fleet.
Shuttles coming and going constantly.
If they board one and take off,
it'll be before we can
shut down air traffic.
Galactica, Hot Dog.
Request instructions.
I need further instructions.
Do I fire or not?
Dee... tell Hot Dog to hold his fire.
Repeat, weapons
hold. Do not fire.
Hot Dog, Galactica. Weapons hold.
Repeat, do not fire.
They couldn't have done
it on their own.
Did anybody notice off-log calls?
Scrambled communications?
No, Sir.
Nothing.
Well, we're home free for now.
Good to see you, Madame President.
Captain Apollo...
what is Mr. Zarek doing here?
Once Tigh gets over his initial shock,
he'll send troops out to search for us.
If we're going to make it, we have to keep
on the move. I figured Mr. Zarek here is
the only one in the fleet with enough shady
friends around who can possibly hide us.
Love the way he puts that.
Well, Mr. Zarek, it would seem the enemy
of my enemy is my friend.
Call me Tom.
Our shuttle's waiting, ma'am.
We have to hurry.
Wow, is that the best you can do?
Nice to know installing a regulation
pyramid court was one of the
priorities of the resistance.
Well, there are some things
one cannot live without.
Let's go.
Are you kidding me?
I'll wipe the court with you.
Yeah, we'll see about that.
I was scouted for the pros.
Bum knee took me out of contention.
I see.
Is that going to be your
excuse when I kick your ass?
- "My poor knee hurts."
- At least I have an excuse.
I can't imagine what
yours is going to be.
Nice shot.
Thanks.
Thanks. Thanks, doc.
I appreciate it.
Don't thank me.
Thank her.
Why, what does she
have to do with it?
Everything.
Nothing.
Love is a strange and
wonderful thing, Chief.
You'd be happy you experienced it at all.
Even if it was with a machine.
- What are they going to do to her?
- They're setting up a new holding facility.
There will be tests.
Mental.
Physical.
Like she's some kind of lab rat?
That's the idea.
This is just great.
Bill Adama's little baby boy
pulls the wool over your eyes,
and you let him get away Scot-free.
You're a laughing stock.
You didn't want this command.
Well, don't worry about it.
You won't have it for much longer.
All because when push came to shove,
you got shoved.
It was his son.
What's happening on my ship?
Wait in the corridor.
Ellen, can I speak to my XO?
Of course.
Slowly.
What's happened?
I frakked things up and good.
- How?
- I made some bad calls.
- I've done that.
- Not like these.
You gonna pour us one
of those or what?
Never had much use for people
who second-guessed my decisions.
Especially if they've never held a command.
They don't understand the pressure.
You make a call.
It affects the lives of thousands.
And you have no one to
turn to for back-up.
Well, you make it look easy.
Well, you know that's a lie now.
A lot of pieces to pick up.
Then we'll pick 'em up together.
Where's my son?
Bitch!
Traitor!
No, no, no.
I love you, Chief.