The Cylons Were
Created by Man
They Evolved
They Rebelled
There Are Many Copies
And They Have A Plan
Previously on
Battlestar Galactica...
Colonel Fisk is the
new Pegasus Commander
The cylon's fetus
contains no antigens.
??????????????????????
Are you saying you found a
cure for the President's cancer?
Yes.
I've got ships on half rations...
when will some of these supplies
start getting out to the fleet?
Target's FTL is history
She's all yours.
He's all right.
I say again, Apollo is all right.
Let's just be glad that we both
came back alive, all right?
That's just it, Kara.
I didn't want to
make it back alive.
You're not going to shoot.
You're not like me.
Cloud 9
48 hours earlier
Hey, hey. Hey, don't go.
Sorry.
I though you were still asleep.
You should have kicked me out
of bed an hour ago.
If I hold up Galactica's raptor,...
Tigh'll have my ass.
Which me both know currently
belongs to me.
All right, let's move on to
the the next item...
Oh, no, gentlemen. Please, don't get up.
After the last few weeks, it just
feels good to be on my feet,...
thank you though.
You've made a remarkable recovery,
Madame President.
Remarkable, indeed.
But, now I'm
playing catch-up,...
and I'm afraid during my illness I
lost focus. I let some things slide.
That's behind us now.
Yes, it is.
To the point...
supplies are running
low and the people are worried.
Well, they wouldn't be civilians...
if they didn't have
omething to bitch about.
Well, I think that in this case,
they're entitled.
Our inventory levels are tight,
but they're not critical.
But all the way across the fleet,...
people are reporting
shortages of essential goods...
and what they do get
comes at a high price.
They're turning to
the black market.
Last week, one of my aides...
came down with pneumonia.
Billy had to trade liquor...
to get the antibiotics.
It's the nature of the beast.
People want what they want.
A few trades would be one thing,
Commander Fisk, that's reality.
But, I'm talking about criminals...
making outrageous
demands on the people,...
so bottom line is, I'm implementing
a new fleet-wide trade policy.
We need to be in control
of our supply chain,...
not black market thugs.
I am hoping that I can have the
military's support on this.
Admiral. If you want Pegasus
to run these dogs down,...
you just give us the word.
Our people will do whatever it
takes to get this under control.
And it's good to have you back,
Madame President.
It's good to be back,
thank you, Admiral.
Gentlemen, thank you.
Is madame President always so
"right in your face"?
Her last-minute resurrection
seems to have...
invigorated her somewhat.
Yeah, well, maybe too much.
She doesn't really
think her made-up...
plans and regulations are going
to change anything, does she?
As if we don't
have enough to do.
No, madame President sets a
great prestige by her office...
and Adama supports her,
at least for the moment.
Well then, so do I,
just for the moment.
By the way, did you
get the cigars I sent over?
I not only got them,
I enjoyed them, as well.
Oh, my pleasure,
Mr. Vice President.
Well, I've got a ship to run.
Look forward to
our next visit.
As do I.
I got them from a friend.
- Paya!
- Hey, sweetie.
Wow,...
you seem to get an inch
taller every time I see you.
What, I don't
get my handshake?
Well, it's okay Paya.
I have a special surprise for you.
And it's in here.
You wanna come see?
What's he got?
Come on.
What have we got?
Oh, Paya!
I've never been great with kids.
Maybe next time I'll
get one with, uh, two eyes.
See if I can trade her
for something else.
No, it's okay.
You just surprised her.
Well.
Well, um.
Look, I'm not sure...
when i'll be able to make it back.
I know.
I'm gonna have to ask for an extra
hundred since you spent the night.
Well,...
I wondered when you
were going to show up.
49.597 survivors
in search of a home
Called Earth
Raptor one-two-niner.
You are cleared into the break.
Galactica, raptor one-two-niner
has the ball.
Inbound
speed two-two-zero.
Admiral, Colonel,...
I'm just getting started,but...
from the looks of him,
I'd say he was garroted.
Gods. This is the
last thing we needed.
Admiral,...
you might
want to take a look at this.
Looks like our friend,
Fisk, hit the jackpot.
Cubit?
Find anything else,
let me know right away.
If I find anything else,
I may retire early.
Someone's sending
us a message.
Or running us in circles.
Maybe there's another
cylon in the fleet.
I almost prefer that
to the alternative.
We start killing our own,...
all they have to do
is sit back and watch.
Fisk.
Do we have any idea who did it?
No.
But we will do a full investigation
and I want you to lead it.
Don't you think it would be better...
if someone from Pegasus
dealt with this?
Even though Cain's gone, her
influence lingers.
I need someone I can trust.
You know, there were
times when that was in...
short supply between us.
We've both been
through an awful lot, son.
And I hope that we've
grown stronger for it.
I need your help.
I'll call up a flight
to Pegasus right away.
Anyone else been inside?
Just the medical team, sir.
Do you know who I am?
I am the vice President
of the colonies,...
let me in!
Captain Adama.
Commander Fisk didn't tell
me  you were invited.
Let him in.
They were going to let me in.
Oh, my gods!
What's going on in here?
Where's Fisk?
On a slab in Galactica's morgue.
What, he's dead?
Isn't this your brand?
Careful, Gaius.
You've bought yourself some
good will by saving Roslin.
But it's fading.
Their old suspicions
are re-emerging.
What are you doing here?
Captain.
I was about to ask
you the same thing.
Wait a minute.
Are you interrogating me?
I'm not sure I appreciate
your tone.
This isn't a diplomatic exercise.
A man was butchered.
His head was practically severed
from his body with piano wire.
You're Vice President of the fleet.
Why are you acting
like a child...
with your hand
in the cookie jar?
Wonder what she would say if
she saw you like this.
You know I can't believe
it's even necessary...
for me to explain
myself to you.
But obviously, no, I had nothing
to do with Commander Fisk's death.
For the record, I just
came here to discuss...
President Roslin's new trade policy.
Oh, I-I thought that was settled.
No, uh, Commander Fisk
had some reservations.
I'll bet.
And as the vice President,
I decided to assuage his doubts.
Of my own free will.
Is that sufficient?
Or would you like me to
provide you with an alibi?
I'm sure I can rustle one up.
Enjoy the cigars.
Escort the vice
President to his ship.
The wireless is going crazy.
Word of Fisk's murder has spread
out through the entire fleet.
When we lose a command
officer aboard a warship...
people are going to be
concerned about their security.
Crew can fall apart when
their Commander is killed.
Pegasus lost two
in a matter of weeks.
Maybe, this time,
they were lucky.
His personal log shows that he
was rerouting supply runs,...
on- and off-loading freighters
without command authorization.
He raided the McConnell,...
and at least a dozen
other ships in the last week.
I also found
a small warehouse...
of high value merchandise
in his quarters.
He was working
the black market.
Well, half the fleet's working it.
Fisk was getting greedy.
If he crossed one of
his suppliers on a deal,...
that would explain the cubits
that Cottle found.
Still doesn't tell us who did it.
Well, he's going to need
trading partners.
And they wouldn't be hard
to find, even on Galactica.
Lee.
I'm scared.
Paya's cough
keeps getting worse.
I'll bring her something
on my next trip.
Which could be weeks if there's
another cylon attack.
I keep hearing about
shortages on the other ships.
People trading anything they can
for food and for medicine.
Really?
Have you seen all the
new working girls outside?
Lee, when your baby's crying
because it's hungry,...
you'll do anything
to make it stop.
Hey.
Come here.
Mommy.
Captain.
What do you want?
Is your wife around, Colonel?
No.
Why?
Is this hers?
Oh, yeah.
She lost it a
couple weeks ago.
Where the hell
did you find it?
On Pegasus.
In Commander Fisk's quarters.
She's burning up.
What did they say
at the infirmary?
Antibiotics have
all been rationed out.
They said they might have
something by the end of the week.
We got shortages across the fleet.
People begging for scraps.
Somehow, you and Mrs. Tigh
have fresh fruit, real liquor...
All right,...
what the hell is this about?
You must have known she was
trading with Fisk.
Or maybe I'll talk to her.
She didn't give it to Fisk, I did.
I traded it for a few necessities,...
a couple of things to help
her get by, big frakkin' deal.
There's nothing
illegal about that.
Not yet.
Don't you play "holier
than thou" with me.
I haven't done anything that most
people on this ship haven't done.
Including you.
Doesn't make us right, Colonel,
just a whole lot of people wrong.
You didn't make
it to class today.
Yeah, I been pretty jammed up.
Anyway, I'm not sure you need me
holding your hand anymore.
Is that what you were doing?
Holding my hand?
I meant it as a compliment.
Permission to speak frankly, sir?
You don't need my permission and
you don't need the "sir."
Maybe that's the problem.
I don't really know
what to think anymore.
So, I'll just ask.
Is this going somewhere?
Dee...
Please don't pretend like you
don't know what I'm talking about.
You know our time
together, our workouts.
Something's
changed between us.
I'm just not sure
what you want me to say.
Then don't say anything.
Communications paging
captain Adama.
You have a priority
ship-to-ship call, Cloud Nine.
Captain Adama here.
Shevon.
Shevon, it's me.
Shevon!
Oh, my gods!
What did they do?
They said they knew
about you and me.
They wanted to know what we'd
been talking about.
I don't understand
why they'd care.
All right, get what you need.
I'm taking you and Paya
back to Galactica.
Lee, wait.
It's the only place
I can keep you safe.
What are you going to tell
them about us?
I'm not fooling myself.
I know what this is.
Lee!
Get away from us!
You listening?
I hear any more talk about Fisk,...
I'm going send your whore
back to you piece...by piece.
And then I'm going start
with the little girl.
I know who you are.
I know whose son you are.
And I don't care.
You tell Adama to let it go.
Is that when you knew
that you loved her?
I thought so.
But you hurt her.
Yes.
This is captain Adama.
I need a medic and a security
team on L deck, ASAP.
You wanted to see me,
Madame President?
Yes.
Thank you for coming, doctor.
Have a seat.
Would you like some tea?
I'd love one.
You know,...
I'm never quite sure where we
stand with each other, doctor.
Why do you think that is?
I can't imagine why.
I've never had anything but the
utmost respect for you,...
and your office.
I understand that
you and Commander Fisk...
planned to meet just
prior to his death.
As I have already
explained to Captain Adama,...
Commander Fisk had
several lingering concerns...
about your new trade policy.
What can I say?
And that's it?
Gaius, she's afraid of you.
Why...
are you asking me this?
You saved my life.
And I'm grateful.
But I sense that there is some...
unease in you about
assuming the presidency, and...
I'd like to offer you an out.
You what?
Resign.
Return to your scientific
work on Galactica.
No one will
question your motives.
You can consider it a second
chance, like the one you gave me.
Charming.
Doctor.
This is a one-time offer.
I suggest you reconsider.
You know, Madame President,...
I've never been particularly
interested in politics.
I never wanted any
lofty position of power.
I never wanted to
be the Vice President.
That is, until this very moment.
Because right now,...
I can't think of
anything I want more.
One to the head.
You didn't do this?
I was attacked.
Found him there when I woke up.
Security bulletin said...
Commander Fisk was garroted
with a wire.
Whatever happened,
looks like you found your guy.
What about Shevon...
and her daughter.
Cloud Nine's an open port.
Chances are,
they're already off ship.
I'll get a team down here.
Councilman Zarek.
Lee.
I just heard, are you all right?
What are you doing here?
Attending a Quorum meeting.
Nothing as exciting as all
this. I assure you.
I know these places are legal.
But still, the son
of the almighty Adama...
Talk to me about the black market.
Not much to say.
It's widespread,
inevitable,...
and according to
President Roslin...
illegal.
So, it's no surprise that you and
Fisk were in it up to your necks.
Fisk, maybe, but not me.
I represent Astral Queen.
I have to be careful
about the company I keep.
This is Fisk's log.
He says,...
he made three runs to
Astral Queen in the last ten days,...
and I doubt it was to discuss
prison reform.
What do you want from me, Captain?
Names of ships. Contacts.
I can't help you.
Why do you think
Fisk approached me?
To get a piece of your
black market scam.
To offer you protection.
You and your father are so
blinded by the past.
Fisk's black market...
was up and running when
he approached me.
He knew Adama would pick up on
his unauthorized shuttles,...
so he tried to force me into
taking over the deliveries,...
creating a firewall between Pegasus
and the illegal shipments.
So, you're trying to tell me
that you turned him down.
At great cost.
Check the fleet logs.
See how many supply ships
made stops at the Astral Queen...
after last Fisk's trip.
The answer is none.
So, if Fisk was trying
to starve you out,...
why didn't you bring it to the quorum?
Roslin's acting like the black
market's some sort of aberration,...
but I thought you were
smarter than that.
Did you really expect some...
utopian fantasy to
rise from the ashes?
I heard the security officer.
They gave you Fisk's
killer for a reason.
They're offering you a way out.
You know something, don't you?
Just rumors.
There's a freighter,...
Prometheus.
Some people say it's
gone off the grid.
But if you want
something bad enough,...
that's where you go.
The deals are brokered by
an ex-military mercenary named...
Phelan.
Lee.
I hope she's worth it.
Oh, Paya.
Paya!
Paya, hey.
Paya.
It's okay, it's Lee.
You remember,
it's Lee.
All right, you're going to be fine.
I promise you.
Okay, you just hang Tight.
I'll be right back.
You may find this hard to believe,
but my father was in the service too.
Strict as hell.
Probably the same as your old man.
But, when the cylons attacked,
all his duty and honor...
didn't add up to squat.
Is she dead?
I can see why you want her back,
she's one of my best.
One of yours.
A good escort...
understands it's
about a lot more than sex.
She knows when to listen...
and when to call for help.
Lee, I had to.
Don't blame her.
The only reason you're alive...
is because I was able to see
you through Shevon's eyes.
And what I saw
seemed reasonable.
Like Fisk.
Fisk was a pig.
He tried to
force us to renegotiate.
So you killed him.
No.
I gave you the killer.
The murder weapon,...
the prints.
Everything you needed to
close the case legitimately.
Despite the President's objections,
the fleet needs us.
Rationing's too tight,...
ship comes in too late, we're the
pressure valve, we provide.
When Shevon needed
antibiotics, she knew where to go.
Without us,...
people would
have nowhere to turn.
The fleet would tear itself apart.
And what about those
children outside?
How are they...
helping the fleet?
Everyone has needs.
Some settle
for cigars or liquor.
You wanted shevon.
Others are more demanding.
It's hard to find...
the moral high ground when
we're all standing in the mud.
I'm not not like
my old man, Captain,...
and you are not like yours.
I came alone.
But, Galactica
tracked me on DRADIS
All they'll need to vent this ship
into space is an excuse.
So, let's make a deal.
I want Shevon, the girl.
I walk out of here,
and you shut down this operation.
And all of you will live.
Sorry, the little girl's been
paid for. No refunds.
Oh, gods!
No!
- Wait.
- Lee, don't.
Come on, do it.
Do it.
I made you a fair offer.
So did I.
Yeah, you're probably
right about everything.
You, me, Fisk.
Nobody can stop it,...
and maybe nobody should.
But it needs limits.
There's lines you can't cross.
And you crossed them.
You're not gonna shoot.
You're not like me.
You're not gonna...
All right, it's done.
Fleet relies on the black market.
Much as we'd like,
we can't wish that away.
So, you're still in business.
For now.
But if they are any more killings,...
if you hold back
essential medicines,...
if you...
ever touch a child...
Shevon.
No, I don't want to see...
Hey, hey. It's over, it's okay,
everything's gonna be okay.
- Lee, Lee, let go.
- Shevon, it's over.
Stop!
I can't be what
you want me to be.
I don't want
you to be anything.
You want me to be her.
That's what this is about.
That's what this has
always been about.
No...
that's not what
this has ever been about.
Come on, Lee.
I know my job.
I'm a replacement.
For a lot of things.
Things that men can't
get anywhere else.
Things they've lost.
She wanted to give you a child.
But you were afraid,...
so you pushed
her away and then you ran.
And you didn't stop running
until it was too late.
Well, I'm not her!
And Paya is not,
and will never be, your child.
Commander Fisk's
murder has been resolved,...
and Pegasus' crew appears to have
accepted Galactica's conclusions.
That's all, Madame President.
Not quite.
What about the ship,
Prometheus?
I understand it's the hub of
the fleet's black market.
We will keep an eye on them.
Keep an eye on 'em?
It's not exactly
the solution I had in mind.
Whether or not we allow
a criminal enterprise...
to thrive in this fleet is not
a matter of choice, Captain.
Admiral?
I've given Lee full authority on
this issue. The decision is his.
I support your trade policies
whole heartedly madame President.
But, we are never going to
have a perfect system.
There will always be some
kind of black market.
At least this way, I know
names, I know faces,...
I know where they are, and
we will monitor the situation.
Thank you, gentlemen, I'm busy.
18, I'm starting to sweat here. 19
- You should be sweating.
- 20
Why aren't you doing any of these?
No talking, no talking. No cheating,
all the way up, a little higher.
- Sneaky.
- 8, 9,...
start again.
- You lost track.
- Zero...
No?
President wasn't very happy today.
No.
Ever since you ejected from
the blackbird, you've been different.
Harder to reach.
I'm just
trying to understand.
Well, like you said, dad.
We've all been through a lot.
Fair enough.
But you should have
told me about the woman.
-= Legendas: Fr0g (fr0g@ig.com.br) =-
-= Tradução: =-
-= Revisão geral: =-
-= Revisão final: =-
-= Grupo Legendas Galactica =-
br.groups.yahoo.com/group/leg_galactica