The Cylons Were
Created by Man
They Evolved
They Rebelled
There Are Many Copies
And They Have A Plan
Previously on
Battlestar Galactica...
Frakk me.
Are you alive?
It's probably a Cylon itself.
More of an animal maybe,
than the human models.
Maybe they genetically design it
to perform a task.
To be a fighter.
- Don't even try defending
- for no frakking reason!
Knock it off!
You get the hell
out of here, now.
I'm so sick of her.
Come on, come on, come on.
I can't do it.
What the hell happened?
Kat's made the trap 100 times.
What are these?
Stims.
By the look of it, she's been
taking them by the handful.
I was ???????????????
So I taking stims.
It's so stupid.
As soon as I get back to Galactica,
I'll send a rescue party.
Yeah, right.
If I say I'm gonna
do something, I do it.
- Count on it.
- My kind of woman.
The resistance base camp is here.
300 cliks north of the only
Cylon airbase in the area.
I respect what
you trying to do here.
However...
We have a duty to the
people we left behind.
We undestand that.
We have to find a way to
jump back to Caprica...
- and go get then
- Kara
Colonial Mining Ship Majahual
29th Day of operations
Entering section two-five-nine.
Keep your eyes open, Kat.
This is where BB and Jo-Jo
bought it.
Come on out, Scar, you ugly
cylon son of a bitch. Let's party!
Yeah, I don't think he's
gonna RSVP, Kat.
He prefers surprise parties.
Yeah, well be surprised when
I blow his ass apart.
Yeah, that'll be the day.
Cassie.
Cassie, wasn't that her name?
Whose name?
Reilly's girlfriend.
You know what Kat, I told you
I have no frakkin' idea,...
so give it rest, all right?
94 hours ago
Reilly's dead for
one very simple reason.
He couldn't
control his fear.
Yup, poor idiot cut and ran.
Gave the toaster a free
shot up his ass.
Scar spooked him.
He saw that motherfrakker's
red eye coming straight for him,...
and he panicked.
Reilly was a good stick.
A little short on guts,
but a good stick.
Beano who had plenty.
Took Cally an hour to
clean out his cockpit.
Hey, does anybody remember
the name of Reilly's girlfriend?
No.
Karen, I think.
Died on Picon. Karen.
No, was it Kather.. Kathy?
You guys, what does it matter?
Gonna hold a little prayer circle?
Good cry? The whole thing?
Actually. It does matter.
Hi.
Hey. This is Ensign Baxton.
Ensign Clark.
And I guess
we're your new bunkmates.
Welcome.
We just finished, uh,
viper training on pegasus.
Ready to kick some Cylon butt.
So was Beano.
Who's, uh, Beano?
Right here.
Ooh, Scar's gonna smoke you
like a fine cigar, my man.
Who's Scar?
Not who. What.
Toaster's top gun.
Deadliest raider in the cylon fleet.
Gimme break.
Come on they're machines.
One's the same as the next.
Yeah, that's what we thought till
Cap Thrace cut the brain out of one.
Scar's the best they got.
Lotta pilots die going
after that bastard.
Why do they call him Scar?
You'll find out soon enough.
He's got a taste for nuggets.
Easy pickings.
Starbuck, I think I got something.
Big spud, lower rim.
You see that?
Negative.
A time you'd have
noticed it before me.
Fine, you're the shooter.
Try to keep up!
Yeah, just don't screw up.
- So,...
88 Hours Ago
how does Scar take out an
experienced pilot like Beano?
- He hides...
- He hides behind an asteroid.
Or the debris field
that you've ignored.
Because it looked like a
bunch of harmless rocks.
You see, Scar doesn't
like to fight...
until the odds are
on his side.
And then, suddenly
out of nowhere, bam.
He pops out,
blows you to pieces.
And then jumps away
before you can return fire.
Well, if you ask me,
I think Scar's a coward.
This isn't dueling
pistols at dawn, this is war.
You never wanna fight fair.
You wanna sneak up
behind your enemy,...
and club 'em over the head.
You see, Scar understands that.
And so do I.
So, that's why
I'm gonna kill him.
You?
Starbuck, you can barely walk.
Look who's talking, Stim Junkie.
You know,...
I wouldn't be calling anyone a
junkie if I were you Starbuck.
Not the way you been pounding
back that booze lately.
One Tigh on the ship's enough.
Uh,
I got...
I got 200 here.
Says I nail Scar's chrome-plated
ass. And when I do?
You hand that top gun over
to me and pour me my first drink.
Your lips'll never touch
the rim, little girl.
We'll see.
Starbuck!
Maybe you should slow down.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
Starbuck! Starbuck!
Comin' in hot!
Checkers green.
Speed 250!
Oh, yeah,  it's gotta be Scar.
Found your hiding place,
you little frakker.
Starbuck, kiss your 200 goodbye.
49.593 survivors
in search of a home
Called Earth
This guy's mine.
Something's definitely wrong.
That can't be Scar.
He should be jumping,
or wheeling to gun at us.
I'll check
our tails.
Frakk!
Frakk, I'm hit
Scar got me!
I'm hit, I'm hit, I'm hit!
See, Beano opened fire too early.
You guys,...
you gotta fill the
windscreen with the sucker...
or you're not gonna hit him.
See,  look.
He's still not close enough.
Beano's already dead, he just
doesn't know it yet.
Do any of you guys see where
he went  wrong?
There, you see that glint?
There.
That's a Raider.
If beano hadn't fixated on
his target, he'd have seen that.
Was it Scar?
There he is, boys and girls.
There's the motherfrakker
I'm gonna kill.
I'm afraid this
is one of those...
good news, bad
news conversations.
Bad news first.
The mining chip's broken
another drill bit.
We need to extend again.
Another eight days.
Eight more days.
Son of a bitch.
They've just discovered an
incredibly rich vein of ore.
Enough to build two entire
squadrons of vipers.
I can't walk away from that.
What's the good news?
The Pegasus production team
has just turned out...
its first combat-ready viper.
We are beginning to
replace our losses.
Hmm. Are they going to be
able to replace pilots as well?
Let's review the tactical
situation.
Four weeks ago,...
our mining ships struck pay
dirt on this asteroid.
A pile of strategic  metals
that we need to build new ships.
Since we're sitting ducks
until the miners finish the job,...
the old man has sent the
fleet out of harm's way...
under the protection of Pegasus.
Our job is to stay
behind and protect the miners.
Unfortunately, this star system
is full of rocks and dust.
Dradis cannot tell the rocks
from the bad guys,...
so our only reliable
system of detection is...
Our eyeballs.
Which means we have to put
those eyeballs way out there.
Split up, cover a huge perimeter.
We'll be patrolling the area
in divisions of four...
at these picket points.
Twos, we're going in
sections of twos.
Are you planning
the ops for me now too?
CAG wants us to spread out to
control a larger area.
It's right here in the briefings.
All right.
So, we do go in twos.
Scar and his buddies are out there.
Looking for easy kills.
Let's not give him any.
This operation is vital...
to the long term
survival of this fleet.
Yes, it is.
And we'll
continue to support it.
They're grinding us down,
viper by viper.
Why'd they stop
coming at us en masse?
Is it because we destroyed
the resurrection ship?
Starbuck's working on that.
This guy's probably died and
been reborn a dozen times.
You may have faced him before.
So what, raiders reincarnate?
Just like you?
Yeah, just like me.
Great.
What a frakkin' world.
A raider's much
like a trained animal,...
with the basic consciousness
and survival instinct.
But with the destruction of
the resurrection ship,...
when they die,...
they're really dead.
So,...
they're not gonna
mount mass attacks...
where they could have
major casualties.
Raiders reincarnate?
Makes sense, doesn't it?
It takes months for
you to train a nugget...
into an effective
viper pilot.
And then they get killed.
And their experience,
their knowledge,
their skill sets.
They're all lost forever.
So, if you could
bring 'em back...
and put 'em in a
brand new body,...
wouldn't you do it?
'Cause death then becomes a
learning experience.
How, uh...how many pilots
have we lost?
I mean, have you lost?
You know, there are
times when I look at you
and I forget
what you are.
All I see is...
that kid...
that pooched her
landings day after day.
The kid that was
frakkin' the chief...
and thinking she was
getting away with it.
Yeah, I remember.
You were like a big sister to...
Kara, um...be careful
of Scar, okay?
He's filled with rage.
About what?
Dying's a painful and
traumatic experience.
Every time he's reborn, he's
filled with more bitter memories.
Scar hates you every bit as
much as you hate him.
A raider is a squirmy
son of a bitch.
You won't be able to
keep him in your sights...
for more than two seconds.
So, you have to deliver
a killing burst...
within that time or
he will turn and nail you.
All that yanking and banking gives
you one hell of a case of vertigo.
And that is what this chair
simulates.
All right, Jo-Jo.
Go!
Time!
Not bad.
At least you hit the target.
Yeah, but that's a lot better
than I did the first time.
I think I took out that
clock over there.
So, what's the all time record?
Four hits on the x-ring.
Are you kidding? Who did that?
I did.
Mind if I give it a
shot for old times sake?
Be my guest.
Two seconds. Go.
Time!
- Five.
- Yes!
Frakk! I'm hit, I'm hit!
Scar got me!
I'm hit, I'm hit, I'm hit.
Kat, Starbuck.
Where the hell are you?
Starbuck, I lost visual on you.
Starbuck, what's your position?
Primary and secondary hydraulics
are bent. I can deal with it.
Starbuck, I got no visual on you,
where you at?
Forget it, Kat. Scar's mine.
Don't be an idiot, Starbuck,
what's your position?
Yeah, you remember me, don't you?
You want my ass so bad,
you can taste it.
Well keep coming.
'Cause I guaran-frakkin-tee you,...
I will put you down
this time for good.
42 Hours Ago
One more.
Come on, Starbuck, let's go.
Get it up there.
Why are you pushing so hard?
Kat's just another hot shot
kid out to make her bones.
Like you were
before you met Anders.
You ever think about him?
What's the point?
He's dead.
Kara.
If you didn't think he
had a chance of surviving,...
why'd you promise to return
with a rescue party?
I thought I was...
I don't know
what I thought.
Captain Thrace. If Scar
jumps us out there, um...
Keep your eyes open so he can't.
Okay. But, if I screw up and he
bushwhacks me, what do I do then?
Come on!
They drilled this into you
over and over and over...
again at basic air combat.
I know, sir, but Scar's
something I'm not...
Scar is no different
than any other attacker.
He comes at you, turn
into him, get closer,...
pull the trigger.
Turn into him, get closer,
pull the trigger. Thank you, sir.
Don't run, or you'll die.
Right.
What are you waiting for?
Nothing, sir.
Come here.
Come here,
I want to talk to you.
Now listen me,...
you're flying Duck's
wing today. Baxton, right?
Yes, call sign BB, sir.
Okay, that's one of our best
pilots that we got.
Okay, so just do what he says,
and you'll be fine.
Just don't let the raiders
get anywhere near the miners.
- Okay.
- Yeah. Thank you, sir.
Okay, go get 'em, tiger.
Starbuck.
That kid needs more than a
pat on the ass...
and a textbook quote
about tactics, okay?
You wanna be his wet-nurse,
go right ahead, all right?
Be my guest.
His jacket says he's a
qualified viper jock.
So, I either fly him,...
or I ground him and
then we go up short.
What's it gonna be?
Your call, Kat.
Galactica, Starbuck.
Wilco return to base.
Roger, Starbuck.
BB, Duck.
Four raiders. From
behind the rocket, left ten.
Coming hard, looks like Scar.
Duck, BB. What do we do?
We don't have enough fuel to
mix it up.
We bug out, BB.
Let our relief deal with 'em.
We're going home.
Negative! Starbuck said to
turn into any attack.
Weapons hot!
You're bingo fuel. Don't
attack, you idiot.
Gods damn it, BB. This is
the frakkin' exception.
Abort and reform.
Duck, Starbuck. Position?
Four-two alpha.
Behind the big spud.
We need a hand,
right frakkin' now.
You're on your own, Duck.
Everybody's way out of range.
Duck, be there in six minutes.
Duck, Kat. Eight minutes out.
Duck, they're on
my six, oh, my god.
It's all right, Jo-Jo.
Verify pc-2 pressure zero,
throttles closed,...
oxygen, generator and master
switches off.
Check. Shutdown complete.
Nothing you could do, Captain.
You were too far away.
Nice work, Starbuck.
What the hell happened to BB?
What happened?
He did exactly
what you told him to do, Captain.
Him and Duck had bingo fuel
and a head start home,...
but instead the FNG
turned and attacked.
And Scar lit him up like a pinwheel.
Why'd he try to take Scar
on by himself?
Stupid idiot.
"Try to run and your
dead."
I heard you, you drilled that
into the poor moron's head.
You know what?
You and I both know that 99%
of the time that is the right move.
Hmm, not this time.
You know what gets me?
I know that in two weeks,...
I won't remember his face.
I can't remember any of their
faces after they're killed.
No matter how hard I try,
they just fade.
I don't even remember
their names.
Names.
Oh, let's see, there was...
there was Flattop.
Who bought it on
his thousandth landing.
There was Chuckles.
Stop it, already.
Please, not funny.
- All right.
- It's not funny.
It is funny.
You know the President...
says that we're saving
humanity for...
a bright, shiny future...
on Earth.
That you and
I are never gonna see.
We're not.
Because we go out...
over and over again...
until someday, some metal motherfrakker...
is gonna catch us on a
bad day and just blow us away.
Bright, shiny futures
are overrated anyway.
That is why...
we gotta get
what we can.
Right now.
I'll drink to that.
To right now.
So, why don't we?
Why don't we what?
Wait a minute.
- What?
- Wait a minute.
Ow. Hey, slow down.
Whoa, this isn't a race.
Kara,
what's going on?
What's going on?
What's wrong
with you, all right?
Okay, you know what? I don't
wanna know. I don't wanna know.
Hey, what about us?
There is no us, all right?
I just wanted a good lay.
There is nothing here.
Do you get that? Nothing.
Sure.
My gods.
Hey.
Well, that's just great.
Frakk or fight, huh?
Okay,...
maybe I am just a quick lay.
But, Kara, I'm also your friend.
I am hung up on a dead guy, okay?
And it is pissing me off.
And I don't know what I'm doing.
Anders, right? On caprica,
the resistance fighter.
Yeah, well, Samuel's
dead so what does it matter?
Oh, Kara please.
- I don't need your pity, Lee!
- For once in your life...
you haven't got my pity!
Listen, you are fine, you're
fine with the dead guys.
It's the living
guys you can't deal with.
There you are. I got visual
on you Starbuck.
I'm inbound
about 15 out.
Now!
All right, Scar,...let's see
how much you like...
playing chicken when
you can't download, bitch.
How's it feel,
you bastard?
One of us is gonna have
to break away first...
and it isn't gonna be me!
Starbuck, wake up!
He's a machine,
he's not gonna break.
You're committing suicide, Starbuck!
3 hours ago
In two on two engagements,...
cylon raiders like to
isolate individual vipers,...
and then gang up on one,...
hoping to kill it before his
wingman has a chance to protect him.
Captain
Which is exactly what happened
to Jo-Jo 20 minutes ago.
Frakk me,...
was it Scar?
Bastard smoked Jo-Jo and
jumped away in less than 15 s...
before his wingman
could get a shot off.
And, where were you?
What?
Flight schedule had you flying lead
for Jo-Jo on that patrol.
So...
why'd you assign
Snake to take your place?
Was it too early in the morning
for you, Starbuck?
What exactly are you trying
to say, lieutenant?
What I'm trying to say, Captain,...
is maybe if you weren't up
all night drinking,...
Jo-Jo would have still been here.
Give us the room.
What is it with you, Katraine?
Ever since I got back,...
you've been on my
ass like a bad rash.
You know, coming late for a
briefing 'cause your hung over,...
that's bad enough. But when
you back out on a mission?
I put Snake in my place because
I was in no condition to fly.
And I knew that.
You see, unlike you, I don't
take a bunch of pills,...
and then climb
into my cockpit so wired...
that I can't land the frakkin' ship.
Starbuck,...
you're an embarrassment.
You used to be the hottest
stick on the fleet.
Now,...
you're just
a reckless drunk...
that sends other people
out to get killed.
What're you gonna do, hmm?
What are you gonna do,
you gonna hit me Starbuck?
It's scares you, does it?
Actually, no.
You're afraid most
of the time, Kat.
You're afraid that
you're gonna end up...
like that picture
of Reilly's girlfriend.
Some little,...
forgotten...
picture that nobody
really remembers.
You see, that's why you're
riding my ass so hard.
So, no one will
notice that Scar...
scares the living
crap out of you.
Ten-hut!
What's going on?
Little tactical discussion, sir.
Well, it must
have been lively.
Right, I'm pairing you two up.
Kat, I want you to fly
Starbuck's wing out by the big spud.
Sir, I...
I got a hunch a
couple of raiders...
are gonna try and
sneak through that sector.
So, I want my heavy
hitters out there to greet 'em.
Skid's up in 49 minutes.
Sir
Starbuck.
Are you okay?
Colonial Mining Ship Majahual
29th Day of operations
Entering section two-five-nine.
Keep your eyes open, Kat.
This is where BB and Jo-Jo bought it.
Cassie, Cassie!
Maybe that was her name.
You know, Kat, I told you I
have no frakkin' idea,...
so give it a rest, all right?
Whoa, hold up Starbuck.
Did you see that?
Oh yeah!
It's gotta be Scar.
Something's definitely wrong.
That can't be Scar.
Frakk! I'm hit
Scar got me. I'm hit,
I'm hit, I'm hit!
Don't be an idiot, Starbuck,
what's your position?
Now, you remember me, don't you?
There you are.
Got visual on you, Starbuck.
I'm inbound about 15 out.
All right, Scar, let's see how much
you like playing chicken...
when you can't download, you bitch.
How's it feel, you bastard?
One of us is gonna have
to break away first...
and it isn't gonna be me!
Starbuck, I'm inbound your
starboard, Seven high at ten.
Starbuck, wake up!
He's a machine, he's not
gonna break!
He's a machine,
he's not gonna break!
I got nothing to lose.
You're committing suicide, Starbuck!
I'm coming back.
I said it.
I meant it.
Yeah, okay.
Gods damn it!
I am gonna put
him right in front of you.
Do not miss him,
you frakkin' stim junkie.
And that's the way it's done!
Yeah, let's go home, skipper! whoo!
Yo, Starbuck!
Hey, Starbuck!
My cup runneth dry.
Seems I recall someone boasting...
that my lips would
never touch this rim.
You earned it.
To BB.
Jo-Jo,
Reilly,
Beano,
Dipper,
Flattop,
Chuckles,
Jolly,
Crashdown,
Sheppard,
Dash,
Flyboy,
Stepchild,
Puppet,
Fireball.
To all of 'em.
So say we all.
I could have done it, you know.
Could have taken out Scar.
Head on pass.
Straight for him.
Just needed to get a little closer.
So, why didn't you do it?
Probably would have
died in the process.
The bastard was too good.
Couple months ago,...
I wouldn't have even
thought about that.
Would have just
gone for the glory...
hoping I could pull it out
of the fire somehow.
Quit kicking yourself.
You did the right thing
and called in your wingman.
Okay?
Scar's dead.
You and Kat came back alive.
It's not why I did it though.
Can't get Anders out of my head.
Can't get over this insane
hope that maybe he's alive.
You got something to live for now.
Not just die for.
He's down for the count. Uh!