The Cylons Were Created By Man
They Evolved
They Rebelled
There Are Many Copies
And They Have A Plan
Previously on
Battlestar Galactica...
CYLON OCCUPIED CAPRICA
They've got us zeroed in.
If we stay here,
they're gonna chew us up.
All right, we gotta fall back.
Position up this hill. Let's go!
All right, let's go, people!
Jaw set nicely. You're done here.
I'm kicking you out of here
and sending you back to work.
Work like this?
You gotta love a woman who can
complain even with her jaw wired shut.
You got a visitor.
I'm sorry.
What I did was... unforgivable,
inexcusable. I didn't come here to...
I forgive you.
No. Cally. No.
It wasn't you. I know
that. It wasn't you.
It was me. I... may
have been out of my mind
and not know where I was doing
or anything, but it was me.
You're in pain. You have been
in pain for a really long time.
Don't feel sorry for me.
I care about you. I always
have. And I always will.
Let's move! Let's go, let's go.
Move it, move it, move it.
Get a medic!
Sharon, take the gun!
They got us blocked
in here really good!
Frak! Can't raise the raptors.
The cylons have jammed the freq's.
Frak.
Still out there?
Watch yourself.
Yeah. They're holding back though.
Yeah, but why?
They're holding position.
Sending for nonlethal weapons.
They want some prisoners
for interrogation.
The rest they're
gonna send to the farm.
I'm not going back
to one of those farms.
Yeah, well, you won't have
any choice. None of us will.
They're gonna lob some gas in here and
then we'll all wake up somewhere else.
Damn.
So what do you want to do here?
Sit it out. Wait and
see if she's right.
If she is, then you and me,
we gotta have an agreement.
An agreement?
Not going back to one of
those farms, Sam. I'm not.
So if she's right and they throw
gas in here... you do me, I do you.
What are you talking about?
This is what I'm
talking about, okay?
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
Down two more points. And this after
hearing his notions of social policy.
Not to mention his wishful thinking
that he is calling "security policy."
Are people really
going to be that stupid?
Are they really going
to be that short-sighted?
He's got the only
issue people care about.
I know. The planet.
That's all anybody wants to talk
about is that frakkin' planet.
Excuse my language,
Tory, I'm sorry.
I know in my gut that settling on this
planet's gonna mean disaster for humanity.
And I will not say otherwise
just to win an election.
As you wish, Madam President.
So I guess I should
start packing up my office
unless you have some
super secret backup plan
for victory in your pocket.
There's always a
backup plan for victory.
Just in time for the priest.
Good. Send him in.
Eighteen hours. They're taking
their good sweet time out there.
They could've overrun us at
any point during the night.
They're up to something.
What are we up to?
Got any brilliant ideas in
that military brain of yours.
Do the same thing we always
do. Fight 'em till we can't.
What do you think?
Let's get a recon crew
together. Scout the area.
Figure out what's
going on out there.
They're gone. They just left.
Thank the gods!
It's a miracle.
Let us pray.
Lords of kobol, we trust in your
benevolence and praise your righteousness.
Give the people of this fleet
the wisdom to see the goodness
and the strength of your
servant, Laura Roslin. Amen.
Admiral?
Madam President.
The Admiral's not here.
This is my meeting.
I wanted us to talk privately
without the press getting wind of it.
Please have a seat.
Well, you must have
something very interesting
to say to resort to such
pedestrian methods of deception.
The question of permanent
settlement may well be
the most important issue
we face since the attack.
I agree.
Good. The question should be carefully
studied before making a final decision.
In the middle of an election campaign
is hardly the time for careful study.
Therefore I propose a truce. You and I
will issue a joint statement declaring
that the  question be tabled
till after this election.
We will both pledge that
regardless of who is elected,
the decision will be made
only after careful deliberation
involving all
elements of the public
and after consultation with the
military and the Quorum of Twelve.
Doctor, I know we've
had our disagreements,
but this issue transcends personal
disagreement as well as politics.
I am appealing here to
your sense of patriotism.
Let me tell you my sense of
patriotism is doing just fine.
Thank you very much for asking.
I see it as my patriotic duty to
lead this fleet to a new world.
That new world is
unquestionably New Caprica.
But thank you, Madam President,
for demonstrating to me
just how desperate your campaign
for re-election has become.
Were you with a blond woman on
Caprica just prior to the attack?
A what?
She knows.
Were you with a tall, blond
woman in the river walk
section of Caprica City
just prior to the attack?
She can see right through
you. Get out of here now.
You'll resort to anything
at this stage, won't you?
I'm afraid my affairs on Caprica
and who I chose to consort
with are none of your business.
I saved your life. I won't
save your political career.
We are not moving
down to that planet.
- If Baltar wins the election--
- Baltar won't win the gods-damn--
If he does, then what? We're
going to just sit on this ship
and rot while everyone else
gets to start a new life?
Ellen, my job is to protect
the fleet from the cylons
and that's exactly
what I'll be doing.
If you want to move down
there, go ahead, be my guest.
Go down and cat around with all the
men. Have yourself a good old time.
Saul, I want you.
XO. You gotta be kidding
me. I'll be right down.
Starbuck's back. I
gotta get down there.
You're going to be
okay. We're almost there.
Guys, take it easy
with it. Come on.
Am I good or what?
There's gonna be no
living with her now.
It's good to see you. Welcome back.
Thank you, sir. I brought
some friends with me.
I see.
Right. Right.
This is... This is
Samuel T. Anders.
I know who he is.
- Damn good to meet you, sir.
- Caprica Buccaneers.
That's right.
Hell of a player. I'm a
Picon Panther fan myself.
We enjoyed beating them too.
- It's good to have you aboard.
- Thank you.
I have news. Good news, actually.
The cylon occupation is
over. They left. They're gone.
- What are you talking about?
- It's true.
The cylons have left the colonies.
They're headed for
greener pastures.
- Security!
- What the hell?
Don't move! He's a cylon.
Back off, chief. We got it.
Well, this is an awkward moment.
Yes, he's right. I'm a cylon.
And I have a message. So
take me to your leader.
Take him to the brig.
Take that to the brig too.
What? Admiral, she didn't know.
Don't even start, Helo!
Of course she knew.
Welcome to Galactica.
Why the frak didn't
you say anything?
I don't know. Maybe
I didn't want to.
Maybe I wanted him to come
here and blow up the whole ship.
Is that what you're looking for?
You don't mean that.
Sharon, we finally got the Admiral to
start trusting us. Finally! And what?
They killed my baby.
You think I care about you or us or
whether the Admiral trusts me anymore?
Sharon! I love you!
And I'm not giving up this
frakkin' easy! Not after everything!
- You ready?
- All right.
Listen. You don't
have to get me drunk.
I will sleep with you, okay?
I figure I owe you one what
with you saving me and all.
- Little slut.
- Shut up.
Come here. Now you're
going to play hard to get.
- Yeah.
My hero.
Gods, I guess they'll let
anybody in here these days.
Hi.
Welcome back.
- Do you want to meet my man?
- Your man.
My personal property. Right, Sammy?
Don't call me Sammy.
How does it feel to be
my personal property?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And before you answer...
He loves it.
I'll bet he does.
I'm Lee, by the way.
- Hey. Sammy. I'm sorry.
- I've heard a lot about you.
- Pleasure. Shot?
- Sure. Why not?
Lee, when are you gonna
get yourself a girl?
I'm doing fine, thank you.
You're not still
frakkin' Dualla, are you?
Thanks a lot.
I mean, I'm not one
to like, you know,
lecture or anything 'cause
I'll do just about anything
to get into the pants of
some hot little young thing.
Is that all I am to you?
Yes. But you love it.
That's all right. I don't
mind doing charity work.
Where did he go?
I'm here to deliver a message.
After that, you can do whatever
you want with me. I don't care.
Would you mind telling
me what's going on?
I'm not a frakking cylon.
I'm not... Well... Okay, then.
Sorry to bust up your day, brother.
But there's been a change of plans.
It's been decided that the occupation
of the colonies was an error.
I could've told them
that. Bad thinking.
Faulty logic. Our first
major error of judgment.
Live and learn.
But the war heroes have managed to
swing opinion over to their side.
What heroes?
A six and an eight. One of the
eights you know as Sharon Valerii.
Their voices carry a lot of weight.
So when they started talking about
our mistakes and our corruption
and our need for a new beginning,
the rest of us listened.
You see, we're not like you.
We can admit our mistakes and
we're not afraid of change.
So you abandoned the colonies leaving
behind a devastated nuclear wasteland.
And we're supposed to be grateful.
Our pursuit of this fleet
of yours was another error.
That's two for anyone
who's keeping score.
Both errors led to the same result.
We became what we
beheld. We became you.
Amen. People should be true
to who and what they are.
We're machines. We
should be true to that.
Be the best machines the
universe has ever seen.
But we got it into our heads that
we were the children of humanity.
So instead of perusing
our own destiny of trying
to find our own path to
enlightenment, we hijacked yours.
You said it, brother. My
mission here is simple.
I'm to tell you that you've
been given a reprieve.
Cylon and man will now go their
separate ways, no harm done.
No harm.
You completely annihilated our race
and destroyed our civilization.
Now if you going to
start pointing fingers...
Where did the cylons go?
Back to their home world?
Well, I'd rather not say just now.
Let's just say we have other plans.
New marching orders
by your one true god.
There is no god.
Supernatural divinities
are the primitive's answer
for why the sun goes down at night.
At least that's what we've been
telling the others for years.
Can't really prove it one
way or the other, of course.
I know a way to prove it. Throw
them both out the air lock.
Let them see if there
really is a cylon god.
ELECTION DAY
Ballots from the
Adriatic. D? This way.
It's been an exciting day.
The election has been a
real roller-coaster ride.
The polls now have been
closed for about five hours.
Results have come in and
it's been a seesaw battle back
and forth between the Presidential
candidates all night long as we,
of course, expected it would be.
Uh, we're still waiting for a
few more numbers to come in now,
from the counting
room of Galactica,
which must tell you as some of
you may know, was a source of a bit
of a controversy yesterday.
Councilman Zarek had
filed a formal complaint
against the use of military
involvement in the election process.
Now it's just reached a compromise
was just reached late yesterday
allowing Galactica to provide
security for the balloting
as well as civilians to oversee
and monitor the situation.
Yes, okay. We have some
more votes coming in here.
Still not done.
But what we have so far is
6,282 more votes for Baltar,
which puts his total now
to 21,569. Is that correct?
And we also have Roslin.
Her total now is at 17,754.
We've had 2,981 more votes
come in for Roslin at this time.
So that is how things
are looking at this point.
We'll continue to bring you
up-to-the-minute coverage...
Yeah, it's me. Is this
a secure line? Okay.
There are only five ships left
to report in. We need to move now.
I'll take care of it.
Lieutenant, I'll be right back.
Are those the ballots
from the Zephyr?
Yes, sir.
All right, we'll take it from here.
We were told to take these
to the ballot room, sir.
Counting has already begun.
We'll take it from here.
Last one.
We have some more results
have come in here now.
Okay. 8,593 for Roslin,
which puts her over the top.
That's 24,265 for Laura
Roslin. Is that correct?
And 22,366 for Gaius Baltar.
We're going to check these again
because that has put her
over the top. She has done it.
She has retained the presidency
in an improbable comeback
in the final hours of the campaign.
Again, we would, of course,
like to check those
numbers, if we could.
But it appears that Laura Roslin
has retained the presidency
in defiance of the
polls, the pundits,
and the surveyors
of gloom and doom.
I've never seen a political
race end like this,
but it has just happened.
I am James McManus.
We'll check those numbers and
we'll be back to you very shortly.
Thank you.
I've seen a lot of
elections, Gaius.
Most honest, a few fixed.
And you can always tell the fixed
ones because they don't make sense.
And this doesn't make sense.
Laura Roslin is many things.
But she's not corrupt.
And she's not dishonest. It's over.
Congratulations, Madam President.
Thank you.
I hope you don't take
this the wrong way,
but are you as shocked as I am?
I'm relieved.
Well, you don't sound it.
I'm just tired. It's
been a long campaign.
Colonel, may I speak
to you for a moment?
What's up?
Sir, I'm afraid these ballots
from the Zephyr are wrong.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Doctor Baltar's name is spelled
correctly on these ballots.
But this morning, the
Zephyr called me and told me
their ballots had a misprint. They
misspelled Baltar's first name.
We didn't have time to print
new ballots, so I told them
on my authority to go
ahead and use them anyway.
Baltar's name is
spelled correctly here,
so they couldn't have come
from the Zephyr. They're frauds.
Now there's a complete chain
of custody from the Zephyr
all the way into this room.
So someone in the chain
is either a perpetrator
or at least a willing ally.
Thank you for bringing
this to my attention.
I'll take care of it from here.
Sir. We should at least
notify the civilian observers
and the press that these ballots...
I said I'll take
care of it from here.
Yes, sir.
Madam President,
you should celebrate.
It's a great victory
and you've earned it.
Excuse me.
Admiral, we'll talk
later. Thank you.
Adama.
Yes, sir. This is Lieutenant Gaeta.
Sir... I don't know
how to say this.
Fast and straight, I'd advise.
Yes, sir. Admiral, I
believe that Colonel Tigh
is involved in a conspiracy to rig
the election for President Roslin.
When I confronted the
colonel, he admitted his guilt.
He said he acted in collusion with
your campaign manager, Tory Foster.
Saul said tory contacted
him a few days ago.
He did it because he felt that Baltar
as President would be a disaster.
I said I agreed, but that
what he had done was illegal.
A judicial tribunal
may have to be convened.
Stop. I gave Tory the go-ahead.
I didn't know exactly
what she was planning.
I certainly did not
know about Colonel Tigh.
My gods. But I did know that
she was planning to fix the vote.
You tried to steal an election?
Yes, I did. And I got caught.
But Gaius Baltar cannot become
President of the Colonies, Bill.
It cannot happen.
Laura... I don't want him
as President either, but...
He's working with the cylons.
I saw him just before
the attack in Caprica
with a copy of the
tall blond cylon woman.
The same model who accused Baltar of
treason before disappearing from Galactica.
What the hell are you saying?
Why didn't you say
something before this?
Because I didn't remember
seeing him with that woman
until I remembered
it when I was dying.
I know how that
sounds, but it's real.
The same way Kobol is real,
and the Tomb of Athena is real,
and the map to earth is real.
Baltar is working with the cylons.
Even if that's true,
you have no proof.
No, I don't.
Do we steal the results of
a democratic election or not?
That's the decision. Because
if we do this, we're criminals.
Unindicted, maybe, but
criminals just the same.
Yes, we are.
You won't do it. We've gone
this far, but that's it.
'Scuse me?
You try to steal this election,
you'll die inside likely move
your cancer right to your heart.
The people made their choice.
We're gonna have to live with it.
It's the wrong choice.
Yes, it is.
All right. All right. All right.
So that's it. We just
give it up, just like that.
The battle, perhaps.
But not the war.
Well, the important thing is the
error was discovered and corrected.
You've been elected
President. Congratulations.
Thank you very much,
Admiral. Now about this error.
Exactly what kind of a tabulating
error could have occurred on your ship
that could've swung several
thousand votes away from me
in favor of your preferred
candidate, Admiral?
As soon as I have the time,
there will be an investigation.
I suggest that you take your victory
and you leave it at that, Doctor.
I think you'll find I can be
magnanimous in victory, Admiral.
And I believe the correct honorific
at this time is Mr. President elect.
Set course for New Caprica.
Jump completed. We are in
orbit around New Caprica.
We have all ships present
and accounted for, sir.
Send word to the Pegasus to launch their
initial ground team onto the surface.
Let's get a good look at our
new home. Gods help us all.
Well... well, I think
my ability to see you
will no doubt be constrained
by the responsibilities
and the requirements of my
new position. Listen to me.
My new position.
But obviously, we will
have the chance to connect,
to get together again
on New Caprica once...
I'm not going to New Caprica.
What? What are you talking about?
We're all going to
New Caprica. All of us.
Every last, single one of us!
It's our chance to be together.
To be together again.
No.
I can't do this anymore.
Stay.
If you'll raise your right
hand and repeat after me.
"I, Gaius Baltar, do
now avow and affirm."
"That I take the office of the
President of the 12 Colonies of Kobol
without any moral reservation
or mental evasion."
"That I take the office of
President of the 12 Colonies of Kobol
without any moral reservation
or mental evasion."
"That I will protect and defend
the articles of colonization."
"With every fiber of my being."
- Congratulations, Mr. President.
- Thank you.
I accept the role offered
to me by the Colonies
with humility and
gratitude. Thank you.
Wait, wait. No, no, wait. And now...
because it was the first will of the people,
I'm going to sign my
first executive order
requiring the fleet to
immediately establish settlements
on the planet we have come
to know as New Caprica.
Admiral Adama. You
have your orders.
We suspect the warhead
was stolen from your lab.
Then smuggled aboard
Cloud 9 by a Cylon agent.
I don't suppose I could interest
you in a cup of tea, Admiral?
Mr. President, this may be the first
step in a coordinated cylon attack.
I suggest our first priority would
be to focus in on internal security.
No. No, I don't think so.
Our first priority
is to the people.
See that they are safely
established on New Caprica.
Once  that's accomplished... We
can put this tragedy behind us.
You're not listening.
I don't have to listen.
I'm the President.
The settlement begins
and it begins now.
Mr. President. President
Baltar. Good morning, sir.
Good morning, sir.
Mr. President, the
Union needs their answer.
The union. If it's not
the union, it's the Quorum.
If it's not the Quorum,
it's the people's council.
ONE YEAR LATER
We survived a nuclear
holocaust, Mr. Gaeta.
And the people complain
about the weather.
- Sir, it's hardly the weather...
- Well, whatever it is.
How many cylon attacks have
there been since I took office?
- How many?
- None, sir.
None. Precisely. So why
do the people complain?
Tell the union to get
off their fat asses
and do some frakking
work for a change
or I'll start rounding
up their leaders
and holding them in detention. I
doubt they'll like that very much.
- I'll tell them, Mr. President.
- Thank you.
Morning. Where's
my, where's my pills?
BATTLESTAR GALACTICA
ORBITAL DEFENSE PATROL
DAY 380
- I'm telling you to go, okay?
- No, it's not okay.
I feel like I'm abandoning my post.
It's time to pack it
in, Saul. You know it.
More than half the crew is down
there on the ground already.
We can barely put a
squadron in the air to train,
much less fly a decent cap.
We're not really doing
too much up here anymore.
You're staying.
Yeah, well, someone has to
take care of the lighthouse.
Then I'll stay and take
care of it with you.
I appreciate that. But you know
there's only one person per lighthouse.
We both know the cylons
could still show up.
Anything's possible.
We've been orbiting New Caprica
longer than we ran after the attack.
I don't think they're
coming back anymore.
Colonel...
Good luck.
If she gives you too much trouble,
find yourself a younger one.
Attention, all
section four residents.
Please report to supply depots
to pick up weekly food rations.
NEW CAPRICA CITY POPULATION 39.192
Supplies are limited. Please
report as soon as possible.
You seen Sam?
- I think he's over there playing pyrimid.
- Thanks.
Set her up.
Sam, you idiot! I've been
looking for you everywhere.
What the hell are you thinking?
Looks like I'm in trouble.
Doc Cottle is here. You're sick.
You're supposed to be in bed.
I would rather work
this out of my system
right here than lie in bed all day.
Player 1: Sam, come on. Come on.
- Duty calls.
- You gotta be tough.
Let's go, Anders.
Tomorrow, man. Same
time, same score.
Can't believe I married
a moron. Are you okay?
Fine. I'm fine.
It's okay.
I'll be right back,
okay? Doc, wait. So?
There's fluid in the lungs.
It's probably pneumonia.
So give him something.
I'd love to. I've been out
of antibiotics for months.
So what, that's it?
I have a lot of patients to see.
But he's young and he's
strong. So make him rest.
Keep him warm. And with a
little luck, he'll make it.
Son of a bitch.
Everybody, please. Just calm down.
Please just calm down. Everybody
listen just for a second.
Please. Please. Be quiet!
Shut the frak up!
When you elected
me union President,
I promised I would keep us
working, keep benefits flowing.
But most of all,
keep this city alive.
I promised we would
stay on the job.
And well hey. And
building a better tomorrow.
- Look at you.
- Hi.
I'm so glad you guys are here.
Me too. It's pretty...
pretty exciting.
Yeah, that wears off.
- So what's going on here?
- President Baltar.
Sir, Anders is really sick.
But Doc Cottle's
giving me the runaround
and says there's no antibiotics.
And that's a load of crap.
Anything you can do to help
me cut through the red tape.
You should give Apollo a call.
Pegasus is sitting on the backup
meds. He'd spring some for you.
Yeah. I doubt that.
That was a long time
ago. People change.
Okay.
But there comes a
time when you realize
that the engine you've
built with your blood
and your sweat and your tears is
being used for something so foul,
so perverted that it makes
you sick in your heart.
And it's then that you
must throw your body
on the gears and on the levers
and on the machine itself
and make it stop. And you have
to show the people who run it,
the people who control
it, that unless we're free,
that machine will be
prevented from working at all.
Strike! Strike! Strike!
Okay. Everybody have that so far?
Yes.
Good, you're listening.
Think the President has a
bit of a problem on his hands.
I also want you to
look at chapter ten.
It's the history of the 12
colonies. It's really interesting.
The President's problems are
not our problems, are they?
That's right. Our problems are
homework for everyone tonight.
Now some of you are
going to stay and help me
with the art project
for the presentation.
Everyone else, your
parents are here.
Get your stuff, let's go.
Go on. Get out of here.
Good job. Yeah. Okay.
Bye, honey. Thanks.
Good job. Good job.
Thank you, parents.
You know what, why don't
you and the baby go on, okay?
- I'll finish up here.
- You sure?
Yes. Yes. Go ahead. Thank you.
Bubble head. A bubble
head. I love this.
Hello. Hello, Isis.
BATTLESTAR PEGASUS
LEE ADAMA, COMMANDING
What's going on?
- It's for you.
- Who is it?
Right.
What do you want?
I need a favor.
Is that right?
I hear that you're hoarding a
bunch of antibiotics for the pilots.
Where did you hear that?
Anders is sick. He has pneumonia,
Lee. I think that he might die.
Commander.
Wait. Yeah, lieutenant. What is it?
I'm not sure. Picking
up something on dradis.
Dradis? How can you see
anything in that soup?
There it is.
What is it?  Wait, what is that?
Oh, my gods, it's a cylon fleet.
They found us. They found us.
We have to get out of here, sir.
We can't just leave
all those people behind.
There's nothing we can do.
It's taken us forever just to
get to action stations over here.
We're in no shape for a fight, sir.
They'll be wiped out.
We don't have a choice. We need
to get out of here right now.
All decks finally report
condition one, sir.
Should we launch
the alert fighters?
Begin jump prep. We're leaving.
But we'll be back. Start your prep.
Mr. President! Mr. President!
- Don't you knock?
- Gaius. Gaius!
Yeah, what is it?
The cylons just jumped into
orbit and the fleet's jumped away.
Judgment day.
I'm looking for Kara Thrace.
I'm Gaius Baltar.
President of the Colonies.
I know who you are, Gaius.
I know very well.
As long as you offer no
resistance, you won't be harmed.
How do I know that?
You don't. You also
don't have any choice.
How did you find us?
It was quite by accident, actually.
We were over a
light-year away from here
when we detected the radiation
signature of a nuclear detonation.
Very well. on behalf of the people
of the 12 Colonies, I surrender.
What do you want
to do now, Captain?
The same thing we always do,
fight them until we can't.
transcript : twiz.com
subs: innuit
www.crogate.net