Weeds - Season 3 Episode 9
Release the hounds
Transcript by testexam
Synchro : Macanto / [dx]
Michvanilly / San-A
Well? I'm waiting.
- If you'd...
- Keep your body still.
Move your lips.
Make sentences.
What are those lines?
You'll get a full diagnostic
report from the doctor.
But you know.
You have a week to live.
- That's not funny.
- Tickled me.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
You want to get
some coffee or something?
You're an insane stalker person.
Why would I go anywhere with you?
To talk, to explain.
And...
Sorry if I freaked you out.
And I swear I'm not dangerous,
and I'll buy.
Latte, cookies, you name it.
You're gonna keep stalking me
unless I do this, aren't you?
I can't answer definitively
yes or no at this point.
There's a place across the street.
I'll meet you there
in an hour.
Great. That's great.
- What?
- Could you release the hounds?
- No.
- No?
I'm gonna send in another tech
to do your side angles.
Might as well
finish what you started.
Ok. Let's make this quick.
It's fucking hot, out here.
- Don't you love coffee?
- Yes, I do.
I love coffee, slept with Peter,
just like you.
We must be long-lost twins.
I have those
same earrings at home.
They're nice.
How's... Tim doing?
How do you think he's doing?
His father's dead.
I have boys too... two boys.
Dead father.
Heart attack, though,
not, well, however Peter died.
Is Tim seeing
a grief counselor?
Shane went, but I don't know
if it did anything.
I guess time and...
This is my break,
and you are not my friend,
so why am I sitting here?
Don't you want to talk
about Peter?
Not with some random woman
he was fucking,
who my son hates.
I used to think that
it was because
he wanted Peter and me
to reconcile,
but now I'm thinking
it's because
you're a crazy,
stalker, narcissist whackjob.
I started sketching again.
Jesus, I do sound nuts.
I'm not.
You're right,
this is all ridiculous.
I don't know what I expected.
I'm sorry.
Nice meeting you...
Even though
you are kind of a bitch.
Bye.
Here. You can throw it away
if you want, Ok?
I have two questions.
One, why isn't
the air-conditioning on?
I don't think it's working.
And Shane, can I play
brickbreaker on this thing?
Those are for
business purposes only.
Sanjay, your territories are colleges,
junior colleges, trade schools...
And gay bars and dance clubs,
'cause I'm a faggot.
I can call myself that
but you can't,
'cause I'm gay, and you're not.
I'm not ashamed.
This is who I am.
Good for you.
I'll sell to anyone cool who
wants some weed. I'm flexy.
Don't be too flexy. Remember we
start with people we've dealt to before,
and we only expand when
a customer has been vouched for.
You're forgetting
one key territory.
Hi, Silas. I'm gay.
You can get help for that.
Oh, I know. This guy Stuart's
been really helping me.
Stuart's the best.
Silas, why don't we talk
about this after Tara goes home?
This is about Tara.
Hear me out.
Tara is completely
active in the church,
and they have,
like, 10,000 members.
It's a totally
untapped market.
They say when christ
was anointed with oil
by John the baptist,
it was cannabis oil.
That sounds hot.
The Lord wants me
to sell pot, Mrs. Botwin.
- Really?
- Yes.
And he also wants me
to buy a new BMW...
Preferably the convertible.
The good christian people
of Majestic like to get baked.
That explains so much.
Shane,
would you get that, please?
So, am I in?
I promise I'm gonna be
your number-one salesperson.
- You work on straight commission.
- Fine.
- Never say where you get your product.
- Never.
You realize you're
doing something illegal?
I answer to
a much higher authority.
Fine, you're in.
Do I get a cellphone, too?
Take Silas's.
Then how am I supposed to
cover my territory?
You don't. Delivery requires
discretion, which you clearly lack,
so I'm gonna think of
something else for you to do.
Someone named Valerie is here.
She says
she wants to talk to you.
What am I doing here?
I wanted to apologize
for acting like an asshole.
No, that was fair.
I mean... I did stalk you.
Tim's in the car...
I got your address
from your mammogram papers,
drove over...
Drove by the house a few times.
Your neighbor on the corner
is really into gnomes, huh?
Did you call before
and hang up?
- Twice.
- Crazy stalker person.
- Call it even?
- No, I'm having you arrested...
Restraining order, the whole thing.
Little shit. All right,
look, I got you this.
It's a bath bomb -- Effervescent.
My advice is to let it bubble
between your legs.
The carbonation effect,
it's really enjoyable.
And it smells nice.
- Thanks.
- Just take it. I'm an overgifter.
Not a big deal. Oh, well...
I'm gonna go.
Thanks for the bath thing.
Oh, and your boobs are fine -- Benign.
Fine and benign.
Aren't you glad I'm not a proctologist?
Well, you have short fingernails
but a lot of anger, so...
Okay, I'm gonna go smack my kid
and take him to the shrink.
Oh, hey, um...
Are you free for dinner tomorrow?
The referendum will pass.
- I'm tense.
- Ooh, you want a massage?
Yes. In maui.
A week in wailea with you when this is
all over. What do you say?
I say I'm one lucky girl.
Hello... Isabelle...
Well, how in the hell
should I know where he is?
Have you tried his cellphone?
Well, maybe you should call
child protective services.
I'm sure he's fine.
God protects the stupid.
I'm not feeling any cold air.
I think it's broken.
When a customer calls in
to the computer database,
he or she types in a client ID Number.
- It's not working.
- You haven't even tried it.
No, the air-conditioning.
I don't think it's working.
Okay, we need to talk.
Bet your ass we do. Where's Tara?
She's at her youth group.
She's coming by later.
I'm in the middle of
explaining this to you.
Praying that they'll have her BMW
in the color that she wants?
What's your problem?
I guess we'll go over it later.
Honey I'm sorry. Go eat some cake
or watch Youtube or something.
Were you trying to impress her --
The bad-boy drug dealer
who drives all the good girls wild?
It's not like that.
She is totally, totally trustworthy.
You would know this how?
You met her three weeks ago.
In your 17 years on earth,
you've gained such great insight
and wisdom into people?
She's gonna make a lot of money for us.
We know nothing about her
except that she's a fundamentalist
who likes to smoke a lot of pot.
That does not inspire me
with confidence.
You married a DEA Agent.
also, monumentally stupid.
I would hope that my children could
learn from my mistakes.
I'd like my phone back.
No, as I told you before,
I have other plans for you.
You're coming with me
to the grow house tomorrow
Should I be excited,
or is this, like, punishment?
This is, like,
a way to learn about a business
from the ground up, literally.
This is also, like,
a way to keep you occupied
so you don't, like, go off and do
something else, like, stupid.
Like, get it?
Just a little something to say,
"thank you for all your help."
90-fucking-percent of the vote, baby.
I'm not gonna answer that.
It might be important.
Everything that's important
is right here in this room.
It's your daughter.
Tell her you're busy till tomorrow.
Then we can eat and fuck all day
without interruption.
What?
I can't understand anything
that you're say--
Stop crying.
Isabelle, stop crying and talk!
Son of a bitch.
Will you drop the "steel magnolias" bit?
He's still breathing.
Why are you such a cunt?
Please don't use
foul language, Isabelle.
People will think
you weren't raised right.
I wonder why.
Ow, stop!
Good afternoon, Mrs. Hodes.
Yeah, for who?
Is he going to be okay?
He's lucky to be alive.
Animal urine disinfected
many of his wounds.
Animals peed on him?
Apparently, several.
Hmm, that's somehow perfect.
He's gonna be all right, though, right?
The initial surgery was successful,
but he'll need several more.
Then there will be a tremendous
amount of rehabilitation needed.
We're looking down
a long road here, Mrs. Hodes.
No, not we. Him and you.
Not me. We are getting a divorce.
So, who should I speak to?
- There's no one else.
- There has to be someone else.
He was an only child.
Grandma and grandpa are dead.
There's no one else but you.
Well, what about the state?
I'm sure there must be some lovely,
state-funded institutions
that will take him.
- Dad.
- Oh, God.
Come on! Move it!
What's going on, Dwight?
Just open the gate.
Doug Wilson -- councilman Doug.
I'm here every day.
Don't you remember I wore
that pompom hat the other day?
You loved that hat. Yeah, you did.
What? This is letting
the air-conditioning escape.
Sir I'm sorry but the computer's telling
me that your membership's been revoked.
What? By who?
I don't know, but it's in red.
It's from pretty high up.
You have to turn your car around.
No, I'm not moving.
Sullivan Groff
and this whole fucking place
can kiss my black ass.
This is so not over.
I'm sorry, Mr. Wilson.
I did like your pompom hat.
Save yourself, Dwight, you're too good
for these assholes.
Go get a job you can be proud of.
We'll see who laughs last.
Conrad, teach him to grow.
This little fucker?
No, hold up.
Okay, no, this little fucker
steals our shit,
ruins everybody's life and I'm supposed
to be his mentor?
Think of it as
a big-brother kind of thing,
or scared straight.
He needs a positive
male influence in his life.
I'm the only man you know?
The only real man.
You think this shit
is gonna fly with me?
It's not shit.
You're the best at what you do.
I mean that.
Hey, watch this right here.
Your mother's smooth as butter.
Not always.
Your only lines are, "yes, I'm willing
to do anything you say,"
and, "thank you for this opportunity."
How much are you paying me to babysit?
- Pay you?
- That is what I'm doing.
You can't handle him, so you're
giving him to me, to set him straight.
$10 an hour.
Don't be cheap with me, I know the going
rate is closer to $15 in the suburbs.
After business is up and
running, I'll buy you a Rolex.
Because all black men
like a little bling-bling?
Yes.
Go on.
Make my boy your bitch.
All right, Nancy. You want
your boy to be my bitch?
He'll be my bitch.
Poor guy.
Poor wrecked guy.
Okay, tell me
she gave you a sponge bath.
Tell me she soaped it up,
and then slurped the gobbledygood.
Blink once for "yes, "two for "no,"
three for "hell, yes."
Listen, buddy, you don't
have to worry about anything.
Buddy Doug here
has got your back.
Now, in case
you turn into a vegetable,
I've taken the liberty,
of drawing up this power of attorney.
You need to sign this now,
or your cunt wife will crush
the one part of you that
hasn't already been crushed.
All right?
Just try to work with me here.
Sign your name.
There we go.
Your assets are protected.
I speak for you now.
Do you have any assets?
You've got your milf money
coming to you, buddy.
Nance is back in business. Conrad's got
a grow house three times the size.
Money's flowing in like
this morphine in your arm.
Just a little while.
Share the love?
Are you out
of your fucking mind?
He might have a disease.
Let's see if there's any clean needles.
Then we'll just pull the tube.
Fair enough.
I could use a little something.
It's so hard
to see him like this.
You think he'll be in pain
if we take the drip out?
He'll be fine. Right, buddy?
You are such a good friend.
We love you, man.
- What?
- Bingo.
Does this mean
we can't go to hawaii?
No, this means I have to
sell the majestic house,
and then I have to pay
for someone else
to take care of
"the magnificent invalid."
Baby, you can't
sell the majestic house.
What can I do?
I need the money.
No, seriously,
you can't sell it.
The mortgage is held
by a dummy corporation.
You can live in it as long as you want,
but if you try to sell it, the jig's up.
You'll go to jail
for accepting a bribe.
Shit. Can you sell it for me?
I thought dean
was out of your life.
He was... Till the handitard went
and drove off of a cliff.
You'll think of something.
You're a very resourceful woman.
Fucking rolling blackouts.
The planet's overpopulated.
Resources are running out.
The world is...
...it's doomed.
- More wine?
- Oh, god, yeah.
I have to sit down.
When Shane was little,
he called the stars "up aboves"
I Miss the simplicity
of toddlerhood.
Amen to that.
I'm failing my children.
Oh, God.
Who isn't?
Yeah.
Tim's kind of a dickhead.
- Fuck you. I love my son.
- Oh, sorry, of course you do.
I love my dickhead son.
I have ice-cream cake.
I want cake. Give me cake.
Give me cake!
Someone's yelling,
and people are sleeping.
How drunk are we?
We're not drunk, andy.
We're lubricated.
Is that the technical term?
- You got a problem with that?
- No, ma'am.
He called me "ma'am."
Get him, val, get him.
You think I'm a "ma'am"?
You are definitely
not a "ma'am." no, ma'am.
I'm getting cake and three
forks, and no one can stop me.
Thank you.
- You getting up?
- No, I'm fine down here.
Who's your friend?
Do you like her?
She's, uh... Who is she?
- She's my new friend.
- About time you got a friend.
Oh, not nice, andy.
Not a nice thing to say.
So, How do you know her?
She's Peter's ex-wife.
I'm sorry, Nance.
Are you fucking insane?
Thank you. Thank you very much.
You know, it's funny,
but if we don't succeed in life,
we run the risk of failure.
It's not pollution causing
problems in our environment.
It's the impurities
in the air and in the water.
So I say to you,
my fellow majesticans,
change is good...
because change... is change.
Thank you very much.
God bless you,
and God bless the new Majestic!
Thank you!
Holy shit.
Wow, that's a lot of sewage
that motherfucker.
I'm gonna have him killed.