I'm not waiting around for some damn kid
He's late
Your watch is fast
Hey, say... If there's something I am
is never late
I say I'm gonna be somewhere...
I'll be there like a flash
Nice car, man!
What is this, real leather?
I got places to be small fry!
What do you got for me?
I got some great stuff for you Mr Hannison
I'm talking top of the line
You've been busy
Well you know:
"idle hands, empty pockets"
So whatta you think?
- I give you 200$ for the lot
It's worth it 10 times that much!
- Yeah, I told you i don't handle this nickle dime crap anymore
wanna handle real score you come talk to me...
until then, you take what I give you
Maybe I should just take it all
That isn't a threat, is it kid?
Ah, geez!
Doctor said your doing great
- Yeah right before he gave me this new prescription
The red ones at least they'll go nicely with
my pink, blue and green ones I'm already taking
I rather have more colours in the
medicine cabinet than not have you around
I just didn't wanna have to worry your mother
anymore with this stuff, that's all
Dad, we both worry about you
What you already did because of me...
- Wow! Wait a minute, I knew what the risk was, Clark...
ANd I'll take it again in a heartbeat if it meant
keeping you safe
Didn't you and I have a game to catch?
Metropolis Sheriffs, 50 yard line...
Lex really came through this time
Look son, I understand what that friendship means to you,
but... please don't forget he had you investigated, be careful
Not going into this with my eyes closed
He wants another chance
to prove he's changed
Clark...
Dad this is my senior year, I don't want to have
to worry about Lex or Jor-El, or any of that
I just wanna lead a normal life, hang out with
my friends and play football
Alright.. why don't you go get the truck
We don't wanna miss the kick off
Dad!
Dad you're ok?
Yeah, I think so...
Your mother would be visiting me in the hospital
again if you hadn't pushed me outta the way
Dad it wasn't me
I saw someone who can move like I can
I couldn't believe it, he saved you
Whoever it is, he not only did he save my life,
Clark, he also stole my wallet
Somebody save me!
Let your warm hands break right through
I don't care how you do it
Just save...
Save...
Come on!
I've been waiting for you
I made this whole world shine for you!
Stay!
Come on!
Smallville Season 5
Episode 5 " RUN "
Hey! Aren't you two supposed to be at the game?
Well the tickets to the game were in my wallet
- Which was stolen, some kid swiped it
outside the medical building
Oh my god, your were robbed!
Are you alright? Did he have a gun?
No, he had a very fast pair of sneakers but...
I'm gonna call the credit card company
to report it stolen
Hey dad, wait!
THis kid... he was as fast as I am,
I should find out who he is
Just let me talk to Chloe, maybe she can track
down where he's been using your card
Come on dad, if I don't find anything by
the end of the day, then make the call
Alright, but I want you to be careful Clark,
we don't know anything about this kid
THat's why I've to find out who he is
Are you sure you're ok?
- Sweetheart I'm fine... I wish you wouldn't worry about me all the time
You were in a comma for 3 months Jonathan,
it's hard not to worry when you've been
through so much
With a lil' help from modern medicine I'm
planning to go through a whole lot more
Starting with a romantic evening
with my beautiful wife
Maybe we could have a lil' dinner and then...
drive on down to the lake?
I'd love that sweetheart, but I...
I'm gonna have to work late again tonite...
Running the Talon is a lot more involved than
I thought it would be but... eh...
I'll call you later, ok?
>
What is that?
IT's nothing
Looks like a very large tattoo hovering over
a very provocative spot
When did you get that?
- Hum... uh... I got it.. uh...
...Before I came back from Paris
Really? Why didn't you tell me?
I could've come with you and gotten a mermaid...
or an anchor... or a mermaid holding an anchor
I didn't plan on getting it alright?
it kinda just happened
Tattoos don't just kinda happen...
There's usually some ink and
a fair amount of pain involved
What was I supposed to do?
Ask you for permission to get it?
Wow! Hey!
THat's not what I meant...
Why are you biting me head right off now?
- I'm not
- Yes you are
Look I just... I don't want you making
a big deal outta this
I don't care about the tattoo, ok?
But what bothers me is the fact that for some weird
reason you felt like you had to hide it from me
I've seen what keeping secrets
has done to my parents...
I'm not gonna end up like that
Jason the last thing I ever wanna do
is hurt you
But there are some things that I am... just
I'm not confortable sharing with you yet
I'm sorry
>
Dude!
You lost?
You know, cause I guess you must
be because... this is my room
Technically it's my dad's since you used
his credit cards to pay for it
I didn't take anything from anybody
You can save the innocent act, I had a friend trace all the
charges you trying to stick on him after you stole his wallet
And you went through my backpack!
Man, that's invasion of privacy...
...messing with my stuff
- Your stuff? You stole all this!
Yeah?
Prove it
I saw you save my dad from
that truck this morning
Man, nobody sees me
when I'm doing my thing
Maybe you're not the only one
who can move like that...
Jake Garrick, Barry Allen, Wally West...
whatever your name really is...
It's Bart
Not that it matters cause I'll be a 1000 miles
away before you can even blink
I don't know...
I can blink pretty fast
I'm warning you man
I'm gonna give my dad his wallet, and then
you and I are going to sit down for a long talk
Not big of a chit chat,dude
Smell you later
Dad, I found the kid who stole your wallet
but I lost him out at the docks
He just took off across the water
Uhmm, son...
Hi Clark
What took you so long?
Dude, I didn't think anybody else
could move like that except me,
because, hey... fastest man alive, right?
Yeah!
You were right up my butt, man... and
You know I've always wondered if there's anyone
else out there like me and it turns out...
...to be you! Jimmy Crackcorn,
fresh from the farm
What Kind of story did you spin to con my
dad out of a free meal and a bed on the couch
No story Clark, just the truth
And what's that?
Well.. A couple of years ago...
...there was like this accident... right
...a huge flashlight...
and my body went into overdrive
And this happened in Smallville?
No
It's my first time here... and
No offense dude... but
Hopefully the last
I've never met anyone with powers like yours
that wasn't from around here
Yeah, well...
Maybe you should get out more
So, how did you get so fast?
You had an accident too or...
I was kinda born this way...
Why are you living on the streets Bart?
What happened to your parents?
Their son got zapped into a human
lightning bolt that's what happened
I mean, they made this whole big deal that
everything was gonna be ok and that...
I don't know man, you should've just seen
the way they looked at me...
I could tell that...
nothing was gonna be the same...
So you ran away?
I'm...
I just didn't fit in
Man, I guess you don't have that problem...
- Oh, you'd be surprised
I ran away once too
- Yeah, why did you come back, man?
Mow the lawn, milk the cows?
Dude, you should be out there
with me tearing it up
You mean stealing everything in sight?
It's not like I really hurt anybody...
I mean I usually just swipe a lil' bling from
stiff upper crust whenever i need some cash
How much would you call "a have-not" Clark?
I take from "the haves"
Like my dad?
Look man, don't even sweat it ok?
They don't charge you if your card's stolen
Oh, and that makes it alright?
Look man, my friends down at suicide slums...
they sure changed me...
So I had to boost your dad's card in order to get a
room I don't like spending the night out in the streets
Ok? Stuff happens there...
When I'm asleep I'm just
as slow as everybody else
Don't hit me with the big
cow eyes there stretch? Ok?
I could always take care of myself...
- Yeah you've done a great job so far
You know what man? Enough of
the poor lil' street urchin right?
Let's take a closer look at
the mysterious Clark Kent
let's see...
you like to read about
native american mythology..
you've scrolled the name "Lana"
on your notebooks
And you've one of the most
boring hobbies known to man...
Rock collecting
- I don't collect rocks...
Dude you're ok?
Put that away
I'm alergic
Man! I've heard of people sneeze around cats and dogs
and stuff but never get all weak in the knees over a rock
It's a long story
It's one I'm sure I'd love to hear
after we get back...
Get back from where?
Anywhere we want
I mean do we have
2 super power studs here?
Why else do you think i came all over
to Smellyville looking for you man?
Let's go crank it up!
Go have some fun
Did you ever seen Florida?
>
Dude, man, that girl in the black bikini she was
totally checking you out
No she wasn't - Look the girl was eyeing
you like you were a snow-cone dude...
...you should've gotten her number
- I can't just walk up to a girl on the beach and get her phone number
Yeah, well, lucky for you...
I can
She said to call her next time
you are in Miami
I can't just go running back down to Miami
- Why not?
Because it's...
- It's what?
Too much fun Clark?
Come on, nobody's ever died from it
What are you doing?
I'm eating a cookie, dude
I'm starving
You can't just take whatever you want
My mom runs this place
Look man, there's a line...
I don't do lines
What's up Kent? I thought you'd still be in
Metropolis playing detective
I thought i leave that one up to the authorities
They never whould've caught him anyway
Chloe this is my friend Bart, he's from..
- The future
Really?
- Yeah
I ran all the way back in time to tell you that
we are still in love a 100 years from now
Bart...
What's your favourite kind of flower Chloe?
Uhmmm... tulips
How did you do that?
- Magic
You wanna see some more?
Clark!
Knock it off!
Your dad called...
Is that the boy who robbed him?
Yeah, his name's Bart Allen
- Why's he here?
I think he's lonely, wants to be my friend
- Good, maybe you can talk some sense into him
I'm trying
Oh, uh... Lex is looking for you sweetheart...
he asked if you'd stop by the mansion,
he said it's important
Ok, but I probably
shouldn't leave Bart alone
I really don't think he'll notice you're gone...
I purchased this from a private collector
in St Petersburg...
convincing him to part with it required a few glasses
of vodka and a small fortune but it was worth it...
That's very nice
Take a closer look at the border design
Embedded glyphs, similar to the Kowaichi
symbols found in the cave
No one's spent more time down there than you
Any idea what they mean?
No
But I thought you weren't interested
in this stuff anymore
Oh, I'm still interested Clark,
just not obssessed,
Which is why I'm not keeping this from you
I'd like it if we could work on
this mystery together
I'd like that
So what is it?
It's the last surviving page from
a XIV century manuscript
It depicts the Grand Prince Donskov's victory over
his mortal enemy Mamaia at the battle of Kulikova
Legend has it that...
this was the only object adorning the walls of Rasputin's
chamber while he studied at the Verkhoturye Monastery
He believed this page will reveal
a path to unimaginable power
Rasputin would stare to it for days at a time
in the attempt to penetrate its secrets
It's incredible...
- Don't
I had state of the art security installed
to protect it
I'm keeping it at the mansion for a few days
before it goes into the vault at Luthorcorp
Sorry Clark I have an appointment...
Why don't you swing by tomorrow and...
we'll roll up our sleeves...
Yeah
Dude, you know Lex Luthor?
- Whatta you doing here?
Well, Chloe shut me down,
but you know, her loss...
Man this place is awesome!
Man have you seen all the cool stuff?
- You were just in there?
Yeah, I just took a quick spin
Don't worry man, he won't even have a clue
- You gotta get outta here
Clark, who're you talking to?
Dad!
Hey Clark!
Just in time son, your mom's working late again
so I thought maybe we'd have guys night
You know, catch up on the highlights
of the game we missed?
I saw something in Lex's dad, it was a page of
an old manuscript that had krytonian symbols on it
Kryptonian symbols?
Were you able to read 'em?
It had a message, repeated over and over:
" Look deeper"
I used my X-ray vision and I saw
a map hidden underneath
A map?
A Map to what?
I don't know dad, but I think it has something to do with
Jor-El, and what he said to me after he was controlling me
- I want you to leave this alone,
Clark... - No, dad... - Son!
You were just telling me how you'd like
to have a normal senior year, right?
Well, how does traipsing across the globe
on Jor-El's crusade fit in with that?
It doesn't, but hanging out with Bart
reminded me that I'm not normal, dad
Maybe it's time I stopped running
from who I really am
What you really are is a 17 year old boy
Sit down
Dad, it doesn't matter how old I am
Whatever Jor-El sent to me find I've a feeling
it's very powerful and dangerous,
especially if it falls into the wrong hands, and
I'm the only one who could stop that from happening
How?
By stealing this manuscript from Lex?
No, he's no idea of what he has... All I've to do
is to sneak back in there and get a better look at it
Clark, it's a bad idea, he could see you
- I'll be in and out before he even knows I'm there
Dude!
Lex's place was sweet!
I mean that guy's got like 20 cars!
Man, there's no way you get that rich
playing it straight
Man, I gotta step it up a notch
because that's definitively how I wanna live
Listen, Bart, there's something I've got
to take care of, alright?
Can I come?
- No, it's personal, but maybe we'll hang out when I get back
Oh dude, there's this midnight showing "Speed"
at the Min's chinese theatre...
best popcorn and Keanu rules in that one...
So d'you wanna go?
You know it sounds great, but... just don't mention it to my dad, ok?
- Ok
Clark!
Man, it's been really cool hanging out
with somebody like me, you know?
So I gotya something,
just to say thanks for everything
It's an mp3 player. That way you can download all
your favourite tunes and listen to 'em wherever we go
Where did you get this?
I got it for you Clark
It doesn't matter where I got it
- Yes it does Bart
You haven't been listening
to anything I've said to you.
You can't go around
stealing whatever you want
Why not?
- Because there are laws
For normal people!
And dude, why do you treat your habilities like
they're a curse? They're not man!
THey're a gift!
I'm gonna use' em
- I'm not saying you shouldn't
Just use'em to help people not hurt them
- Whom am I hurting?
The store I swiped this from?
Cause they're insured
- That doesn't make it right
Whatever dude, I'm not sticking around
for another lecture
Whatta you gonna do?
Run away again?
You're not gonna solve all your problems
like that, Bart
Look, I'm not running away, Clark
I'm running towards something I'm gonna have
everything I've ever dreamed of one way or another
Bart...
- Look, I thought you and I were the same but I was wrong
You are nothing like me
Bart!
Don't Move!
Clark?
What the hell are doing here?
Would you like to explain what happened here?
Just came by to say hello
Next thing I know all this alarms and lights
are going off
It's a lil' late for a...
...Social call Clark...
- Yeah, I just...
I should've called but
I just figured you'd be up
Are you sure you didn't see anyone else
when you came in?
No, I didn't see anyone
Then you don't know who did this?
No, I don't
I believe you
I know a real friend would never lie to me
I better go and let you take care of this
I'll let you in on a secret...
I'm not that worried...
You said this manuscript page
was worth a fortune
It is
And there aren't that many fences in Metropolis
that can move such a high-end item
If I put a reward at him, sure some fiscally
challenged citizen will point me in the right direction
D'you think that'll work?
Don't worry Clark
Our thief is gonna learn that there's
nowhere on Earth he can run from Lex Luthor
I'd like that too, Jonathan, but I can't
Because I still have all this work to do
I'll be home as soon as I can
that's the best I can do
ok, bye
You're working late?
Oh god, it's like this never stops, I don't know
how you managed all this and went to school too, Lana
It wasn't easy... but I don't remember
staying this late after closing every night
Well it's easier to do this here than at home
Is everything alright Mrs Kent?
Oh, Jonathan thinks the only reason I took
this job is to help out our finances
I love him... so much...
But after everyhing that's happened,
all his health problems...
The only time I'm not worrying about
losing him is when I'm here...
...working
But if you're here all the time then...
...you don't see him anyway
Isn't that like you lost him already?
That summer in Paris's really
given you some insight, Lana
Thank you for reminding me
Reminding you of what?
That it's easier to deal with your fears
if you can share them with someone you love
Sure, however you wanna handle it
No problem, it is my pleasure
well it's about time
- Well I had some things to take care of, maybe when
you grow up you'lll understand how men do business
Is this grown up enough for you?
It's a start
Mr Luthor I belive that I've something
that belongs to you
Is this the dangerous criminal
you warned me about?
Hey, it's not your problem
Come on, let's talk about that finder's fee
He's just a kid
Let him go
No
You've no idea what that freak is capable of
If I were you I'd be more concerned
about the police right now, Hannison
What did you do?
In about 5 minutes this place will be
swarming with Metropolis P.D.
Well ok, then I guess
we better hurry this up, uh?
Tony!
Look at the mess you made kid!
Let's see if you're faster than
the speed of a bullet!
You don't wanna be here!
You still think what you do
never hurts anyone?
Lex!
Lex?
I am sorry Clark
This doesn't change anything
You don't understand...
it'll kill me
You're not a murderer!
That's not who you are!
You don't know who I am!
- Yes I do
Why did I say you saved my dad?
I've seen the good in you
Bart, you gotta stop running or in the end you'll
just be alone and you don't want that, I know you don't
I know because down deep...
...we're the same
I wish that was true Clark
You've no idea of where Bart could be?
- Lex was unconscious...
I stayed with him until I heard the
police syrens then I went after Bart
By then he could've been
halfway around the world
I think it could be for the best, Clark
Dad!
- Now look, I know how much you wanted to help him about but...
...you can't force people to change
no matter how strong you are
He's not a bad kid, dad, he's just different,
at least he's willing to accept that
Clark, embracing your abilities and
flaunting them are 2 entirely different things
I know
It's just sometimes there's a part of me that
wishes I could be more like him
I mean... I've spent so much time trying to hide who
I really am, I'm starting to feel like 2 separate people
Clark, I think you'd be really surprised to find
out how many normal people feel exactly the same way
Yes, son, everybody has secrets,
yours is just...
...it's just bigger than most
I better go check on Lex
- Alright, you wanna use the truck?
No, I uh...
Kinda wanna stretch my legs
Hey!
Thought you'd be at work all day
- Well that's one of the benefits of being the boss
I promoted Linda to assistant manager so I can take a
break and spend some time with a raggedly handsome farmer
Well, you 're in luck,
there just happens to be one...
sweating in your driveway right now
- Maybe I should get the hose
and a bucket of soap
I really missed you
- Me too
This is amazing
When Clark first found this caves...
...I had no idea why was he
so obssessed with them
I always felt like he was keeping this secrets from
me because he was afraid of how I was going to react
I don't wanna live like that
I don't wanna be afraid all the time
You don't have to be, not with me,
that's what I've been trying to tell you
Ok
Remember the church we went to in Paris?
Yeah, I had to live early to make
arrangements for your birthday...
Well after you left I noticed something strange
on the tomb of Countess Thoreau
There were these symbols edged into the rock,
like the ones in this cave
How is that possible?
I don't know
And when I touched them, there was this
blinding light and then pain...
...and all I remember is waking up the next
morning to you knocking on my door
And I had this
Ok wait a second...
So you're saying...
that some strange symbols on the tomb
of a dead countess...
gave you a tattoo?
You know how odd it sounds...
Why d'you think I didn't wanna tell you?
That's why you left Paris
I had to come back to these caves
I had to find out why I was missing
12 hours of my life
But all I found were more questions
It's the same as yours
What does the symbol mean?
I don't know
Jason I don't know what's happening to me
- Ok, Ok
Whatever it is...
...we'll figure it out together ok?
ok
Clark!
It's good to see you keeping normal hours
Just came by to see if you're alright
I heard you ran into some trouble
in Metropolis..
News travels fast
- The curse of a small town
So, what happened?
I decided to play cowboy
and got my spurs handed to me
To be honest I don't know why I'm not dead
THere must be somebody watching over you
In more ways than one
How did you get this back?
I didn't
It was sitting on my desk when
I returned from the Hospital
Whoever took it must've had
a change of heart
I guess he did
Look, we'll have plenty of time
to study this later...
Right now, I'm still nursing a bit of a headache
- I'm just glad you're feeling better
Clark
I thought you'd like to know I had the manuscript page
examined by a team of experts as soon as it turned out
Do you know what they discovered?
That I payed too much for it
Thanks for checking in on me
Dude, your drawing sucks
I'm sick of the hero thing
You mean like returning a
priceless artifact to its owner?
Kinda all that money would've just
slowed me down anyway
To a dead stop if I hadn't found you
Yeah, how did you do that?
Whatta you? Fast? Strong? And psychic?
I wish
I spent a whole night down at suicide slums trying to
convince someone that I had a 1000 of these to fence
A few guys pointed me in
the direction of Hannison
Look at you,
channelling your inner criminal
So, uh...
whatta you gonna do now?
I don't know.
It's a big world
We gotta to check it out
See if there's anyone else out there like us
Maybe start like a club
or league or something
You know you could come with me...
...or you could stay...
You've a great life, Clark, but...
It's not mine
I've no reason to stay in Smallville
You've me
Thanks for being my friend
Are you sure there's nothing
I can do to change your mind?
Tell you what...
If...
you can catch me
I'll think about it
Thanks to Doranwen
www. filetopia. org
Transcription by Lacenaire
Synchronization by Lacenaire
Lacenaire ***LuMonCa***
"Láthe Biósas"
Subtitles checked and synchronized by Little Miss
For dvd-rip
www.tvsubtitles.net