9-1-1 emergency.
San francisco 9-1-1.
He's trying to kill me. Please hurry!
Ma'am, can you go outside?
He's in the living room!
Please hurry!
Ma'am, listen to me. The police are on theiray right now.
He's in the hall!
Ma'am, go into another room, lock yourself in
and try to leave out the back door.
Oh, my god!
He's going to kill me!
He's breaking down the door!
Ma'am? Ma'am?
Hey.
Sorry to inrrupt pete's going away dinner.
You got me before it started.
You hear the 9-1-1 call?
No woman is here, and that
was definitely a woman's voice.
That's definitely a man.
Fred osner, 35.
Wallet was in his back pocket.
He lived two houses down.
So the caller's a woman.
She gives this address.
The patrol guards show up
and find only him?
The caller identified herself
as corinne stevens.
She lives here. Neighbor says
her husband's away on business.
Two head wounds-
Blunt object and then
he starts in with a knife.
This guy's butchered.
18 stab wounds and counting.
Is that a crystal rabbit?
The killer picked it up
and smashed it into his skull.
That's an enraged killer.
Enraged like
a jealous husband?
Are there any drag marks around?
No.
So he took corinne with him.
Why am i here?
What-What-What is this place?
I don't understand.
Why are you doing this?
Why won't you talk?!
Please. Please.
Talk to me!
Why are you doing this?!
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
Womens murder club µú1¼¾µú13¼¯
-=Ææàãğü×öä»×é=-
·­òë£º¸öèëid
ğ£¶ô£º¸öèëid
ê±¼äöá£ºfunnylz
She's been missing ten hours.
What is this, kidnapping?
Off-The-Record?
Linz, it has been so long since we were
on-The-Record,i've put the record away.
Ten
hours and no ransom demand.
Where's the husband?
He was at a hotel in colorado springs.
He checked out at midnight
the night before last.
If he drives fast enough,
just makes it in time.
We tried to reach him on his
cell, but it's not turned on.
So corinne gets home and turns
the alarm system off at 8:02 p.M.
And the victim, fred osner,
did he come in with corinne?
Yeah, it looks that way.
Our guess-
The killer's waiting inside.
He sees fred. They struggle.
Corinne runs for t media room
and locks the door.
That's where the call
came from.
The killer drops fred with this
crystal rabbit then stabs him.
Fred's watch is smashed
at 8:11 p.M.
8:12 p.M., corinne calls 9-1-1
from the media room.
You're supposed to be home recuperating
it was a gunshot after all.
I'm recuperated.
How do you know where corinne
s when she called 9-1-1?
The doorknob-He snapped it when he forced his way in.
So what happened with pete last night?
I got the page at the restaurant
before we even sat down.
That's okay.
I got two days before he leaves.
Hey, linz.
I just brought in the husband.
Are you people nuts?
Why would i kidnap
own wife?
You have a temper.
Your wife's having an affair.
With fred? He's our friend.
He checks on corinne
when i'm away. I asked him to.
Look, i stopped in reno
on the way back, and i slept.
Talk to the hotel staff.
I- I left my cell phone there.
We're looking into it. .
Stevens, we're checking out the crystal rabbit
the killer used to hit fred.
If we find one fingerprint-
What? Wh-What did he use?
The killer picked up a crystal
rabbit and hit mr. Osner in the head.
We don't own any crystal rabbit.
Excuse me a moment.
Look,
i know what you're thinking.
She's 25, a trophy wife.
I didn't do this.
Can you think of anyone
who might have a grudge against you?
Anyone your wife mentioned?
No.
I don't-I don't know.
I... no. No one.
You have to find corinne.
Please.
A minute?
His alibi checks out.
He did sleep in reno.
Now forensics found
no prints on the rabbit-
Not the husband, the victim
or the missing woman.
So the killer must have
brought it with him.
Who brings a crystal figurine
to a kidnapping?
Maybe it was a, i don't know,
a message to the husband.
He was weang gloves.
There was no fingerprints.
That's not a message to the husband.
That's a message to us.
-==Ææàãğüàöô°çãçé·îï×==-
±¾×öä»½ö¹©ñ§ï°½»á÷£¬ñï½ûóãóúéìòµóãí¾
Your victim
has two head wounds-
One from the glass rabbit,
The other, i think, came
om the killer's right shoe.
He kicked osner postmortem.
This is from the second wound.
There's something
in the matted hair.
I think it's blue paint.
I sent samples to the lab.
What kind of knife did he use?
Serrated. And he's strong.
He stabs with tremendous force.
Is there a small indentation
at the bottom of every wound,
Like from the base of the knife
slamming against his skin?
Maybe, but how could you...
You think
it's the kiss me not killer.
Lindsay,
his only victims were women.
And he took corinne stevens with him.
Linz,
all three women had their lips sewn together,
Not him. Osner wasn't
his intended victim.
It was corinne he wanted,
and fred osner interrupted him.
And the crystal rabbit?
Well,
look at all the other crime scenes-
The-The mouse, the tub,
the-The key, the lilacs-
All symbols
of some sort of ritual,
And the crystal rabbit
was another one.
He meant it
for corinne stevens,
But he broke it
when he killed fred osner.
He's back. He's killing again,
and he's got his next victim.
I didn't hear you come in.
I was just taking
a quick shower.
I'm sorry
i didn't come home last night.
Yeah, well, martha and i
spent some quality time.
Really?
Yeah. And now that you're here,
maybe we can have some.
You have no idea
how good that sounds,
But i have
to get back to work.
Yeah. S-Sure.
No, i understand.
You know, work's work.
Assuming that that's
what this is all about.
You think i'm running away
because you're leaving.
I think you're running away
'cause i'm leaving.
Pete, believe me,
that's not it.
Is this something
i can ask you about?
We call him
the kiss me not killer.
He started five years ago.
He tortures women
and sews their lips shut.
Am i totally
freaking you out?
No, no. No, you're not.
Hunting this guy
took over my life.
I became obsessed.
I lost my marriage.
I lost perspective
on everything.
Why this one?
Why-Why bring this one home?
If i knew
why he chose these women...
If i could figure that out,
Then i could understand him.
I have to finish this.
It's the only way that
i can get him out of my life.
He's taken another woman,
pete,
And i have to find him
before he kills her.
You have to go.
Do what you have to do.
Just go.
Crime scene is clean
xcept for the paint residue in the hair.
Why in the hair
and not on the carpet?
Well, okay, look.
You see these threads?
Lab says that they're stitches
that hold the upper tohe sole of the shoe.
The paint was held in by
the threads. Lieutenant?
Yeah.
Here you go.
Thank you.
So you
kicked him in the head...
Lost your temper.
Stupid.
Stare at that board long enough,
you'll see a sailboat.
Hey, wheeler.
Hey. So the lab says
the paint from the killer's shoe is called skylar blue.
It's a specialty paint,
Uh, used for restoring old
cars and trucks.
How old?
We're talking, uh, elvis and hula hoops.
Five dealers in the bay area carry it.
Three of them
don't have it in stock.
The fourth one just got his first shipment
in six months.
You said five dealers.
No, the fifth one
has it in stock.
His name is, uh, john harris.
Let's go.
Skylar blue.
Uh, well, not much call
for it unless you own a '55 pickup.
Was it only used in 1955?
June '55 to april '58.
People
got tired of the dark blue.
This one's sort of a turquoise/robin's egg,
and then people got tired of that.
Americans and their cars.
We're picky.
Have you sold any recently?
Yeah, i can check.
How good are your records?
Oh, well, at $290 a gallon,
it's not exactly walkinout the door.
We're not talking a lot of people.
Well, please give us a list and add, uh, your employees
and day laborers for the last five years.
I'll fax it over right away.
No, we'll wait for it now.
This is serious.
Where were you last night around 8:00,
mr. Harris?
Well, gee. I was here.
We're open till 9:00. I have the
surveillance tapes.
Great. We'll take those
and the list of customers and employees.
Right away.
Hey. Still no sign
of corinne stevens.
We recanvassed
the neighborhood.
What about the paint dealers?
Jacobi and wheeler are running the customers
and the employees through n.C.I.C. So far nothing.
Hey, linz.
John harris, the paint dealer
we saw this morning?
He had a 15-Year-Old daughter.
She ran away 16 years ago.
Disappeared. A lot of cops
worked on the case on and off,
Especially after
they found her dead.
One of the cops was your dad.
Where'd they find her body?
It was five years ago.
Her remains were dug up
in a park near san mateo.
I need a minute.
It's about a case.
Must be pretty big for you
to come see the old man.
We speak twice
in the last seven years,
And suddenly
i'm your new best friend.
Can i come in?
Always welcome here.
You, uh, want some tea?
I got that scottish brunch stuff
you like. Um...
Scottish breakfast,
and you hate it.
But i stocked up on it.
I figured eventually, you'd come
to visit.
This isn't a visit.
If that's the way you want
to play it. What's the case?
It's a serial killer
i've been working a few years.
Kiss me not?
Is there
a new victim? I didn't hear.
We were trying
to keep it quiet.
He took a woman last night.
Hopefully, she's still alive.
What can i do for you?
John harris, auto paint dealer,
his daughter ran away.
Does that ring any bells?
Harris.
Oh, yeah.
Daughter's name was rachel,
right?
Yeah, i worked that case
a couple of weeks.
You were homicide, so why'd you
work it if she was a runaway?
The family said she was
a runway, but nobody bought it.
Didn't take any clothes, didn't
tell anybody she was leaving.
We expected
to find her body any day.
Only about a decade off.
Who were you
looking at for the killer?
A couple of us liked
the harris' son.
Billy.
Yeah.
He was in the file.
12 years old, strange kid.
Of course, harris and his wife didn't
want to hear it.
But could a boy that age kill a 15-Year-Old girl
and dispose of the body?
I've seen worse. We kept an eye on him.
He got into some fights,
in and out of juvie.
The kid
always just seemed wrong.
Jacobi.
Hey. What do you got
on billy harris?
Uh, he works
in his father's shop.
You know, harris didn't have him
on the employees list.
Shift manager says he's been
out sick for three days.
He works in his father's shop.
Ask jacobi where-
I know what to ask jacobi.
Whe does he-
He lives in his father's house.
Don't get snippy over the phone.
Get a warrant,
text me the address,
and i'll meet you there.
I gotta go.
Anything else i can do?
No, uh, i just came
for the information. Thanks.
Sure, kid. Hey.
Be careful.
Always am.
I don't understand.
Why are you looking for billy?
What is this about?
Take mr. Harris outta here.
This isn't right. This is
my house. Get him outta here!
Lindsay, nothing in the
basement. D.M.V. Report.
Billy harris has got
a 1956 f-100 pickup, color blue.
Thanks.
The layout of this room
look familiar?
This was the daughter's room
a long time ago,
Just like in the file photos.
Mm-Hmm.
No sign of corinne stevens
in this house.
No blue pickup truck
in the garage.
Thanks.
It's not here
because he's driving it.
You are gonna
tell me about sarah rice.
She was laid
to rest in a bed of lilacs.
They were still fresh
when we found her. Why?
Well, he leaves things
at crime scenes, like a key.
Melissa paquin-
48 stab wounds.
He left an old key in her hand
and a dead mouse at her feet.
When we saw her lips,
we knew it was the same guy.
Elaine lewis-
She was eviscerated
and left in a copper bathtub.
Is that a crystal rabbit?
Who were you
looking at for the killer?
A couple
of us liked the harris' son,
Strange kid.
Jacobi!
The crystal rabbit, the lilacs,
the brass tub-
All of these things
belonged to rachel harris when she was 15.
Billy harris
is the kiss me not killer.
How much longer do we have,
and will he keep corinne alive?
He kept sarah rice alive
six days.
I know a shrink in juvie
where billy spent time.
I just talked to him.
Now he can't tell you anything-
Doctor/patient privilege-
But he's my friend.
I know this guy. He'll help us.
Cindy, this isn't your job.
You can get in a lot of trouble.
That's half the fun.
I don't know where billy is.
Do know
that he's a good kid.
Your list of employees-
You didn't put billy on it.
I don't think of billy
as an employee. He's my son.
This is a nightmare.
Linz?
If harris knew
what billy was doing,
He didn't do it with him.
We pulled his credit cards.
The night
sarah rice disappeared,
He was in atlanta
at a car show.
Thanks.
Sure.
Billy goes hunting
and doesn't tell you where?
Maybe. I wasn't listening.
He likes to hunt.
I don't even know how to fire a
gun.
Might any of his friends know?
No, he's, uh...
He's sort of a loner.
When your daughter rachel disappeared,
We understand
that the police told you
they thought
billy might have done it.
Yeah. Yeah, and when they said
that to my wife, it killed her.
She died two months later.
Mr. Harris, we understand the feeling of needing
to protect your son,but there is a woman's life at stake.
Please think about
what you're doing.
He knows where billy is.
I don't know.
He jumped out of
his chair when i brought up rachel.
You don't think
he's protecting billy?
No, he's not.
Harris isn't protecting his son.
He's protecting himself.
Rachel harris was buried
in a vinyl duffel,
Handles on the side,
dried blood on it.
Didn't they test the blood?
Too small a sample at the time.
I had them compare the d.N.A. From the blood speck
to the d.N.A. Om billy harris' hair brush.
It's a partial match.
It's his father's blood.
So john harris killed and buried his daughter
and then claimed she ran away?
We can charge harris, offer him
a plea to help us find his son.
Okay, let's get him charged,
But if this guy's smart as i think he is,
He isn't gonna help us
with anything.
Boxer, homicide.
Hello, lindsay.
Yeah. Who's this?
Let my father go if yont
to keep corinne alive.
Billy?
You want to help corinne,
right?
Uh, yes. Yes, i do.
Uh, let me talk to her.
No games. Let my father go.
Damn it!
Not enough time
to trace the call.
What'd he say? Linz?
Uh, uh, he said that if we
didn't let john go, he would kill corinne.
I got here
as fast as i could.
I'm sorry. I probably sounded a little...
Freaked out when i called.
So you're sure
it's billy harris?
Yeah.
But you know what, claire?
It was partly a relief.
Okay.
Well, billy harris
has always been this phantom.
Now i know what he looks like,
i know what he sounds like.
I took pete
up to the attic this morning and showed him...
Crazy lindsay's
serial killer exhibit.
What happened?
He had
a bunch of questions.
I don't know
if he'll get past it.
???
It's a little early to be
talking about love.
Lindsay, he sleeps at your place
when he's not in a hotel,
He cooks, he walks your dog,
He puts up with your crazy hours
and never complains.
That's not love?
That would be amazing...
If i wasn't spending his last day here
living inside billy harris' head.
Which is what we all rely on you to do,
and i'm sure pete understands that.
Cindy called.
She said she has something
we'll want to see.
I have billy's notebks
from juvie hall.
My friend said he could lose his license,
so he needs them back when we're done.
Look at this. It's from 1993.
He was thinking about it
even as a kid.
A serial killer at age 12?
But he wasn't killing anyone.
This w in the back
of his notebook.
And here's the freaky thing-
The first drawing shows up
Two weeks
after rachel disappeared.
Why would he draw her like that
if he didn't know she was dead yet?
Unless he did.
That's what the drawings mean.
John harris killed rachel,
and billy saw it happen.
He knew his sister was dead.
He draws her
with her lips sewn shut.
That's how a 12 year old
tells us what happened.
It's about keeng the secret.
It's about the silence.
John must have threatened billy
and told him to keep quiet about it.
Why these women, billy?
Why do you choose them?
All this time...
All this time, it's been
right here in front of me.
Where?
Look at corinne
stevens and her husband,
And then look
at the past three victims.
Each victim is a young woman
with an older man in her life-
Sarah rice had the boyfriend,
Melissa paquin-Her sick fathe
Elaine lewis
and the older boss.
It's all about rachel.
With each victim, billy is
reenacting his father's crime
And the order not to tell.
That's billy's life.
That's the only thing
that's important to him.
Quiet!
Quiet.
Boxer, homicide.
Hey, beautiful.
Hi, pete. Uh... how's it going?
Uh, well, i'm at the hotel.
I'm gonna see you
before i go, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I'd, um, i'd really like that.
I'd-I'd really,
really like that.
Because we should finish
our conversation.
Uh, uh, pete, i gotta go, okay?
Oh, sure. Yeah. Okay.
I'll-I'll- I'll call you later.
Boxer, homicide.
You didn't do
what i asked, lindsay.
You still have my father.
Well, billy,
let's talk about it.
You want to be my friend.
I want to tell you
that i know what happened.
I know what your father did
to you and your sister.
Too late.
You should've listened.
I almost have him.
Billy, i'm listening now.
What-What do you want
to tell me?
You made me do it again.
What are you talking about?
Billy?
Lindsay...
By the way, nice dog.
He's calling
from your apartment.
Tom!
Where is she?
Kitchen.
Are you okay?
Lindsay?
He left corinne stevens
in my bed.
I get to go tell richard stevens
that his wife is dead...
Dead because of me.
She's blaming herself.
She's got an endless loop
in her head saying it's her fault.
Turn it off
because you're wrong.
Corinne stevens has been
in rigor for more than a day.
She was killed six to nine hours
after she was abducted,
And she was already dead
when billy asked for his father's release.
You gotta stop feeling guilty.
We need you at 100%
to catch this guy.
I don't want another woman on my table
with her lips sewn shut,
So what are we
gonna do about it?
Find the sailboat yet?
His sister's death was the single
most defining moment in billy harris' life-
Not his mother's love,
not his first home run,
not his first kiss.
Witnessing
his sister's murder
Obliterated anything and everything
that came before or after that.
That's his obsession
with his father.
Why did he wait to start killing?
They found rachel's body.
That threatened
to expose the secret.
That's what provoked him before.
That's ???
You want your father
out of police custody?
You want us
to keep your secret?
Let's see how you like it when it's plastered
all over the news.
...well over a decade
Since the initial trail
went cold,
New evidence has surfaced
that has seemingly
Broken this case wide open
for investigators.
And now this man-
John harris-
Has been arrested
for the murder
Of his 15-Year-Old daughter
rachel.
The investigation had been-
All the morning shows ran it.
Billy will see it.
He'll call back.
And if he doesn't?
Tom, he won't let it go.
"Espresso, wheat"...
We're looking for billy.
You're reupholstering?
Married to a civilian
who teaches kindergarten.
What can i say?
She thinks the job turns off
when you leave the building.
Well, that's one problem
you didn't have with me.
Hey, lindsay. Call for you.
Theythe sending it up.
They think it's him.
Billy?
Why'd you push me?
I don't want to push you.
I want to talk to you.
No, lindsay, no talking.
This time i'm not forgiving you.
You took something
that belongs to me,
Which means
i had to do the same.
4-5-4-3-5-1- That's my cell
phone. How'd you get that number?
See you soon.
My cell phone's in my desk.
Is anything missing
from your apartment?
I haven't been back to the apartment
since claire took the body out.
Okay, he said he took
something of yours.
Maybe he doesn't mean
an object.
Maybe he is talking about
a person.
I saw cindy and jill
in jill's office.
I saw claire in the hall
20 minutes ago.
No messages.
Oh, my god. He means pete.
No, no, no, no.
It's an i.P. Address.
Jacobi.
Can we run a trace
on the site?
No, it'll take days
to go through all the servers.
Oh, my god. It's your dad.
Bring me my father. I'll give
you yours in exchange.
You have five minutes
to decide, inspeor.
Or i'll blow
his brains out.
'S not a rescue, linz.
It's a suicide mission.
I tell billy it's possible
or he blows marty's head off.
Think. It was a secret.
Now it's out. Game over.
He wants to kill you, lindsay,
and then himself.
If it was your father,
what would you do?
Boxer.
What's your answer,
lindsay?
We have a deal.
Where do we meet?
15.7 miles east on midway road.
5:00. Don't bring company.
I want to speak
to my father.
You can talk
when you get here.
We have an hour to figure out how we
do this so you and your dad don't die.
Okay, i got
an idea, but we're gonna need some help.
Lieutenant hogan.
Ted thorne, fbi.
Thanks for coming.
Inspector lindsay boxer.
I appreciate
your help.
Inspector, you've handled this
as well as anyone could.
We're here to help
whatever way we can.
This is the house in solano county
where the hostage is being held.
It's an old hunting cabin.
Only structure within a 5-Mile
radius.
It's cattle country.
He'd see us coming from a mile away.
It's too far for a sniper
to get a shot.
Well, since we c't get
a bullet in there,
I was thinking of something more up close
and personal.
What'd you have in mind?
Small explosive, like a flash-Bang grenade
with a radio signal trigger.
My guys can
do that. How do you get it in his hand?
Put it in something he wants.
Can you get a grenade in that?
Sure. We'll put the bear
in a bag. You bring it to him.
We'll wire your jacket
for a mike.
You get him to hold it,
send us the signal.
Carl can remote detonate the
bomb.
How far away do i have to be?
6 to 8 feet.
6 to 8 feet at least.
If there are any surprises,
you let us know.
We'll be there in 30 seconds.
A lot can happen
in 30 seconds.
The d.A. Found
a cooperative judge.
Billy's dad pleads down to manslaughter
on the murder of rachel,
And in exchange, he agrees to go with you.
Let's go.
We just wanted to ask-
'Cause we are taking you
to dinner after all of this-
Pizza, japanese or greek?
We want
to hear all about the big adventure.
And your good-Bye with pete-
What he said, what you said.
Yeah, he's leaving at 9:00,
so i may not make it.
Not if you talk
that way, you won't.
Uh, pizza, japanese, greek-
You pick. Surprise me.
Remember, if i don't
make it outta this,
I never liked you
that much anyway.
Come on.
Head down.
These restraints
are excessive.
That's what criminals wear.
You know the main reason
parents kill kids?
Because daddy wants something
the child won't give.
That's what happened,
isn't it?
You wanted her, and she fought back,
and billy saw the whole thing.
He saw you try to take her.
He saw you kill her.
How'd you keep him quiet?
What a pretty speech.
You made your son a monster.
He is what he is
because of you.
You don't understand anything.
She's got the bear,
and it's in the bag.
Are we getting a signal from
her mike?
The signal is clear.
Everyone's set.
We have sound
on lindsay and harris now.
I n't see billy anywhere.
He's here.
His truck's behind the cabin.
Billy!
Come on.
Your father's here!
Drop the bag.
Hands on your head.
Where's my father?
In a minute.
We had a deal, billy.
Where is he?
I said shut up.
Daddy...
I'm sorry.
It's falling apart. I...
can't keep it inside anymore.
What the hell are you talking
about? What's falling apart?
I don't like where this is going.
She's okay. She knows what she's dng.
I tried to protect you.
I tried to keep the secret.
Not another word!
I did what you said, daddy.
Never tell.
Never tell. Never tell.
Never tell!
Never tell.
I was a good boy.
Then they fod rachel.
I love you, daddy.
Your turn.
Inside.
What are you doing?
I ju-I have some things
that you want.
What?
It was things
that belonged to rachel.
Carl, get ready to blow it.
Remember, on her signal.
No.
No, i don't want those.
Billy-
Move.
Okay, we gotta get her
outta there. We can't.
She doesn't have the flash bomb.
She's helpless.
If we go in now, lindsay and her dad
are dead before we get in the house.
Go inside.
Hey, kid.
No talking!
You stop right there.
Just stay.
She was beautiful.
Yeah, billy, she was.
I didn't save her from daddy.
You couldn't.
You were too young.
No, i was too scared.
I could'veaved her.
I could've saved her.
I didn't save her.
I didn't stop.
You shouldn't have come
here, lindsay.
Quiet, old man!
Wait, billy-
Stop!
This has nothing to do
with my father.
Okay? Let him go.
Oh, he stays.
What happened to rachel,
it wasn't your fault.
It was your father's.
So you know what that means?
You can stop
with all of this.
Your father is gone.
You don't have to keep
the secret anymore.
No, the secret's out.
You let the secret out.
Tell her she's a bad daughter
and this is all her fault.
Stay right there.
No.
She's a screwup. She's
a waste of... billy-
Flesh and bone.
She doesn't deserve to live.
Say it.
I love you, baby.
I love you with all my heart.
No!
Go! Go!
All units, move!
Gun.
Dad?
Daddy?!
It's okay, daddy. Officer down!
Get the e.M.T.S now!
The e.M.T. Said it was
a clean in and out.
I'm gonna be fine.
Well, i'll come check on you
later tonight.
You don't have to do that.
I know.
Thank for coming
to get me, baby.
I'll see you
in a couple hours.
Yeah.
You did okay today.
I may have to treat you
with something resembling respect.
Man, don't go overboard.
The press got wind
of what happened.
The p.I.O. Wants to know
if you feel up to talking with some reporters.
No. No. Uh, you'll-
I gotta get to the airport.
You'll handle it
for me, okay?
What are you doing?
Excuse me. Sorry.
Uh...
passport.
Uh, yeah. S.F.P.D.
I need to get to gate 24.
Sorry, ma'am. I can't let you
do that.
There's no problem.
I just need to get in there. Only be
a minute.
Ma'am, i can't let you in withouan
okay from my supervisor.
No, i can't wait.
I need to talk
to someone, okay?
He is on the 9:10 to phnom penh,
which is leaving in 18 minutes.
And look, if i don't say good-Bye to this man,
i am gonna regret it for the rest of my life.
So can you just-Can you just please let
me in? You should probably let her go.
What a-What are you
doing out here?
Waiting for you.
Uh, d-Does
this mean you're staying?
No, it means there's a flight to taipel in four
hours that gets me to cambodia tomorrow.
It also means i couldn't leave
without talking to you.
Okay, there's like...
A thousand things that i-
I want to say right now.
So... okay, for a long time,
I've beehanging on to
a lot of feelings
about... everything.
And i finally finished
this nightmare.
And... and the point i'm trying to make
is that... i think i can be happy.
Well, i-I-I want to be happy.
And...
I'm just really sorry that i didn't realize it
until you were about to leave.
And... i just wanted you to know that-That i'm gonna
miss you more-More than i want to think about.
That's nice to hear, linz.
Okay.
Now here's the thing-
This dsn't have to end.
I mean, i-I don't get a lot of time off,
but when i do, i'd like- I'd like to come back to you.
What i'm saying is that
between my vacations, yours,
Uh, cell phones, a little patience,
we can make it work.
It's-It's only a year.
Doesn't sound like
muchf an offer, but-
Yes.
I- I would like that.
Yes?
Yes, yes.
Yes.
I would like that.
I would like that very much.
Hey. Sorry i'm late.
I had to stop at the bureau and
get my stuff back. No problem.
So, uh,
how was the good-Bye?
It was not so much a good-Bye
as it was a continuation.
He's staying?
No. But he's coming back
from time to time.
Eventually.
It's better than it sounds.
It is.
The long-Distance thing
never works. Take it from me.
Hello?
A little support maybe.
She's right. He's been
pretty great so far.
Exactly. And i can take
some vacation time and go visit him.
Uh-Huh. When was, um,
When was the last time
you took a vacation?
Seventh grade, maybe?
Okay, you know what?
You people have absolutely
no faith in romance
Or two people who care
about each other. Boxer.
10 bucks says
in half-Hour from now,
We're at a crime scene.
I was so looking forward to shrimp.
I don't understand. I...
I thought he was fine.
I thought it was nothing.
N- Never mind. Yeah. I, uh,
i'll-I'll be right there.
Linz?
It's my dad.
ææàãğü×öä»×é
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==-
»¶ó­¼óèë