In the time of magic,
the destiny of a great kingdom
rests on the shoulders of a young boy.
His name...
Merlin.
Camelot welcomes you, Lord Bayard of Mercia.
The treaty we sign today marks an end to war
and a beginning to a new friendship between our people.
Why do I always get the donkey work?
You're a servant. It's what you do.
My arms'll be a foot longer when I finish.
It's characterbuilding.
As the old proverb says, hard work breeds...
...a harder soul.
There's no way a proverb! You just made that up.
I didn't!
Sorry.       That's all right.
Excuse me.       I'll give you a hand.
Hi.
I'm Merlin.       Cara.
You're Arthur's servant.
That must be such an honour.       Oh, yeah. It is.
Well, someone's gotta keep the place running.
Thank you, Merlin.       Hmm?
Oh, right! Yeah.
Uh, no problem.
It was nice meeting you.
Shouldn't you be busy running the place?!
Ugh! When's the last time these were cleaned?
Last year some time. Before the feast of Beltane.
Did it end in a food fight?       Don't all feasts?
I wouldn't know.
The airs and graces of the court are a mystery to me.
Not tonight, they won't be.
I'm gonna be at the banquet?
Not quite.
You'll be there to make sure my cup doesn't run dry.
If I have to sit through Bayard's boring speeches,
I don't see why you should get out of it.
Be sure to polish the buttons.
Do you want to see what you'll be wearing tonight?
Won't this do?
No.
Tonight, you'll be wearing the official ceremonial robes
of the servants of Camelot.
You can't be serious.
Nice hat.       Thanks.
She's pretty, isn't she?
For a handmaiden, I mean.
Pretty for a princess, let alone a handmaiden.
People of Camelot, for a great many years,
we have been mortal enemies.
Our blood stains the ground
from the walls of Camelot to the gates of Mercia.
And though we remember the dead,
we must not allow any more to join them.
As a symbol of our goodwill, and of our newfound friendship,
I present these ceremonial goblets
to you, Uther,
and to your son, Arthur,
in the hope our friendship may last.
Merlin, I need to speak to you.
What is it?       Not here, please.
I don't know who else to tell.
Tonight, we toast a new beginning for our peoples.
We look to a future free from the toils of war.
When he gave Arthur the goblet, I knew.
Whoa. Start from the beginning.
Two days ago, I was bring Bayard his meal.
He wasn't expecting me to walk in...
What are you trying to say?
If he knows I said anything, he'll kill me.
I will not let that happen, I promise.
Tell me what you saw.       Bayard is no friend of Camelot.
He craves the kingdom for himself.
Cara...tell me, what has Bayard done with the goblet?
He believes if he kills Arthur,
Uther's spirit will be broken and Camelot will fall.
What was he done to the goblet?
He put something in it.       What?
I shouldn't. He'll kill me.       Please tell me.
Is it poison?
And may the differences from our past remain there.
To your health, Uther,
Arthur,
the Lady Morgana...
...the people of Camelot
And to fallen warriors on both sides.
Stop! It's poisoned. Don't drink it.
What?       Merlin, what are you doing?
Bayard laced Arthur's goblet with poison.
This is an outrage!
Order your men to put down their swords. You're outnumbered.
I will not allow this insult to go unchallenged.
On what grounds do you base this accusation?
I'll handle this.
Merlin, you idiot,
have we been at the sloe gin again?
Unless you want to be strung up,
you'll tell me why you think it's poisoned  now.
He was seen lacing it.       By whom?
I can't say.
I won't listen to this any more.       Pass me the goblet.
If you're telling the truth...
I am.       ..then you have nothing to fear.
No  if this does prove to be poison,
I want the pleasure of killing you myself.
He'll drink it.
But if it is poisoned, he'll die.
Then we'll know he was telling the truth.
What if he lives?
You have my apologies,you can do with him as you will.
Uther,please.He's just a boy.He doesn't know what he says.
You should have taught him better.
Merlin, apologise. This is a mistake.
I'll drink it.       No, no, no. It's all right.
It's fine.
He's all yours.
It's poison. Guards, seize him!
Merlin, can you hear me?
We have to get him back to my chambers.
Bring the goblet. I need to identify the poison.
Lay him on the bed, quickly. He's struggling to breathe.
Gwen, fetch me some water and a towel.
Is he gonna be all right?
He's burning up.       You can cure him, can't you, Gaius?
I won't know until I can identify the poison.
Pass me the goblet.
Ah. There's something stuck on the inside.
What is it?
Looks like a flower petal of some kind.
He's on fire.       Keep him cool.
It'll help control his fever.
Ah. The petal comes from the morteaus flower.
It says, "Someone poisoned by the morteaus can only be saved
"by a potion made from the leaf of the very same flower.
"It can only be found in the caves deep beneath Balor forest.
"The flower grows on the roots of the morteaus tree".
That's unfriendly.       Cockatrice. It guards the forest.
Potent venom. A single drop means certain death.
"Few who've crossed the mountains of Isgaard
in search of morteaus have made it back alive
Sounds like fun.       Arthur,It's too dangerous.
If I don't get the antidote, what happens to merlin?
The morteaus induces a slow and painful death.
He may hold out four, maybe five days, not for much longer.
Eventually, he will die.
My lady,I am sorry I haven't been here to attend to you.
Don't worry.I'm all right. How's Merlin?
If Arthur returns with the antidote, he'll be fine.
Then he'll be fine.
You should be with him. I'll manage.
I know what he means to you. Go.
Thank you.
What's the point of having people tasters for it
if you're going to get yourself killed anyway?
I won't fail.No matter what you think.
Arthur,You are my only son and heir.
I can't risk losing you for the sake of some serving boy.
His life's worthless?
No,because he's worth less than yours.
I can save him.Let me take some men.
We'll find the antidote and bring it back.
No!       Why not?
Because one day, I will be dead and Camelot will need a king.
I won't let you jeopardise the future of this kingdom
over some fools servant
It's not a fool servant
Gaius says that if we...
Oh, Gaius says?! That's exactly what makes it so.
Please, Father. He saved my life.
I can't stand by and watch him die.
Then don't look.
This boy won't be the last to die on your behalf.
You're going to be king.
Something  you have to get used to.
I can't accept that.
You're not going.       You can't stop me.
That's it! Arthur.That's end to it.
You're not leaving this castle tonight.
Say what you like about the food
but you can't beat our feast for entertainment.
Morgana,sorry.Are you all right?       Disappointed.
I was looking forward to clumping a couple of run
ahead of the the label.
Guards could've handled Bayard.
Yeah.But why let them have all the fun?
Morgana,You shouldn't get involved. It's dangerous.
Spare me the lecture. I've already had it from Uther.
If it is a bit of consolation.You weren't the only one.
Not that I listen to him.
Sometimes you must do what you think is right.
Damn the consequences.
You think I should go.       Doesn't matter what I think.
If I don't make it back, who will be the next king of Camelot?
There's more than just my life at stake.
What kind of king would Camelot want?
One that would risk his life for that of a lowly servant?
Or one who does what his father tells him to?
Halt! No!
He's getting hotter.
What language is that?       None. The fever's taken hold.
None of those words are his own. His pulse is weaker.
What is it?       That can't be right.
The rash isn't supposed to appear until the final stage.
What does that mean?
It says that once a rash appears,
death will follow within two days.
You said four days.       Something's increased the potency.
It warns that "the effect will be more rapid
"if an enchantment is used during preparation".
Enchantment? Bayard's no sorcerer.       No, he isn't.
Then who did this?
It can't have been.
She wouldn't dare to come here
Unless...       Unless what?
What happened to that girl?       Which girl?
Before Merlin burst into the hall,
Bayard's servant girl took him outside.
She had dark hair. Very beautiful.       Find her. Quickly.
Arthur...
I especially ordered Arthur not to go.       Worked like a charm.
Not another word.       My lips are sealed.
Should have put him under lock and key.
You can't chain him up every time he disagree with you.
Just you watch me.
I won't be disobeyed,especially by my own son!
No. Of course you won't.
You knew about this, didn't you?
Morgana...
Don't lie to me.
Arthur's old enough to decide.
He's just a boy.       Have you seen your son recently?
You have to let him make his own mind up.
Even if it means letting him go to his death?
Let me guess, she wasn't there?
Noone has seen her since the banquet.
Who is she?       Not who she claims.
You know, don't you?       Cara.
Though, that's not her name. Not her real name.
Then who is she?       A powerful sorceress.
We should tell Uther. Maybe he could send riders after her.
She'd be long gone. Impossible to know where.
Oh, no.       What?
She knows the only place an antidote
will be found is Balor forest.
Arthur could be walking into a trap.
Arthur.
Arthur. Ohh.
Hello?
Are you all right?
Stay back.
It's all right. I'm not going to hurt you.
Who did that to you?
My master.
I ran away from him but then I got lost.
Please don't leave me.
I won't. I'm not going to.
You can take me away from here?       Not yet.
There's something I have to do first.
Why have you come to the caves?       I'm looking for something.
It can only be found here.
What is it?
I know this place. I could help you.
It's a type of flower that grows inside the cave.
It's very rare.
The morteaus flower? I know where they are.
I'll show you.
Arthur, it...it's a trap.
It's a trap.
His fever's getting worse, isn't it?
The poison's setting in.
Could you get me some wolf bean?        Yes, of course.
Merlin, you must fight it.
There they are.
Keep back from the edge.
Don't worry. We'll be out of here soon.
What are you doing?!
I expected so much more.
Who are you?
The last face you'll ever see.
It seems we have a visitor.
Very good.
But he won't be the last.
I'll let his friends finish you off, Arthur Pendragon.
It's not your destiny to die at my hand.
Who are you?!
Arthur. It's too dark.
Too dark.
Merlin.
What are you doing?
Come on, then. What are you waiting for?
Finish me off!
Leave them, Arthur.
Go. Save yourself.
Follow the light.
Faster. Go faster.
Follow the light!
Move. Climb.
Inform the King! Arthur has returned to Camerlot.
What are you doing? Let me pass.
I'm sorry, sire. You're under arrest by order of the King.
You disobeyed me.
Of course. A life is at stake. Do not let Merlin die
because of something I did.
Why do you care? The boy is just a servant.
He knew the danger he was putting himself in
He knew what would happen if he drank from that goblet,
but he did it anyway. He saved my life.
There's more.
There was a woman at the mountain
She knew I was there for the flower.
I don't think it was Bayard who tried to poison me.
Of course it was.
Gaius knows what to do with this.
Put me in the stocks for a week, a month even. I don't care.
Just make sure it gets to him. I'm begging you.
No!
You have to learn there's a right
and a wrong way of doing things.
I'll see you're let out in a week.
Then you can find yourself another servant.
He hasn't got much longer. Arthur got the flower?
I don't know. Uther won't allow anyone to see him.
Is there nothing we can do to help?
Only the leaf of the morteaus can save him.
We must find out if Arthur has it.
I could sneak into the dungeon.
That would be very dangerous.
I've got to. Merlin will die if I don't.
Be careful.
Food for the prisoner.
Set it down over there.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
I couldn't possible eat this. It's disgusting.
The state it's in, I'm not sure it's fit for anyone.
You. Wait!
Waste not, want not.
We're not all as precious as our Royal Highness.
Food for Prince Arthur.       Stay where you are!
How is he?
Have you got the morteaus?       Here.
His breathing's worse. We must hurry.
Why have you stopped?
The poison was created using magic.
We may need magic for an antidote.
But we can't. It's forbidden.
Even if we could.
I'll try and make it work without.
Oh, I need some fresh water.
Thank you.
Hold his nose.
Swallow, Merlin.
Swallow it.
He's stopped breathing.
What's happening?
Gaius?
His heart has stopped.
He's dead?
He can't be.
It can't be.
It wasn't his destiny.
It's my fault.
If I'd have got here sooner, if I'd have been quicker.
No, no.
It was me.
I should've looked after him better.
It's my fault.
You should be ashamed of yourself,
you're old enough to be her grandfather.
Merlin! You're alive!
I'm the ghost come back to haunt you.
Sorry, I'm just...
I thought you were dead.
It's fine.
It's more than fine.
Um... What happened?
The last thing I remember is drinking the wine.
Forgive the interruption. May I speak with you?
Not now.       It is important.
Word of Bayard's arrest got back to Mercia.
We're about to be attacked.
What I have to tell you may have bearing on your plans.
It will only take a moment.
I know who tried to poison Arthur.
So do I  he's locking in my dungeon.
It wasn't Bayard.
The poison was magical.
I'd recognise the hand that made it anywhere.
Nimueh.
You must be mistaken.       I wish I was.
It can't have been. We'd know her.
Her face is not easily forgotten.
She's powerful. She enchants the eye that beholds her.
We never knew it was her.       Have you any proof?
The poison used against Merlin
was made more potent by the use of magic.
You saying she conspired with Bayard to kill Arthur?
No, Bayard is innocent.
Look at what's happening? This is what she's wanted all along.
a war to bring strife and misery to Camelot.
How long before Bayard's armies reach our walls?
A day. Less. We should send cavalry to meet them.
Instruct your men not to leave Camelot
until I give the word.
Sire.
You're making the right decision, sire.
Do you think Arthur should be told the truth about Nimueh?
OK, let the bragging begin.
How'd you manage it?
I'm not sure.
All I do know is I had help.
Someone knew I was in trouble
and sent a light to guide the way.
Who?
I don't know.
But whoever it was,
I'm only here because of them.
I'm glad you're back.
Arthur?
The woman you met in the forest,
what did she tell you?
Not much.
She was too busy trying to get me killed.
It was strange, though.
In what way?
I was at her mercy.
She could've finished me off but she chose not to.
She said it wasn't my destiny to die at her hand.
You must have been scared.
Had its moments.
Those who practise magic know only evil.
They despise and seek to destroy goodness
wherever they find it,
which is why she wanted you dead.
She is evil.
Sounds as if you know her.
I do.
To know the heart of one sorcerer is to know them all.
You did the right thing,
even though you were disobeying me.
I'm proud of you, Arthur.
Never forget that.
Still alive, then?
Uh, yeah, just about.
I understand I have you to thank for that.
Yeah, well, it was nothing.
A half decent servant is hard to come by.
I was only dropping by to make sure you're all right.
Be back to work tomorrow.
Yeah, of course. Bright and early.
Arthur?
Thank you.
You too.
Get some rest.
Arthur may give you a hard time, but he's a man of honour.
There aren't many who'd risk what he did for a servant.
It all would've been for nothing
if he didn't know how my identity is.
Eat your dinner.
I don't understand why she went to all the trouble
of framing Bayard.
She could've just kept quiet and killed Arthur.
Destroying Arthur and Camelot wasn't all she was after.
She knew you'd be forced to drink that wine.
It was you she wanted to kill.
Seems someone else knows
you're destined for great things, Merlin.
I owe Lancelot my life.
I am paying for that debt the only way I can.
It's my life's ambition  to join the Knights of Camelot.
Arise, Sir Lancelot.
I shall not return...       Don't go£¬Lancelot.
OK, it's now or never.
www.tvsubtitles.net