'the destiny of a great kingdom rests
on the shoulders of a young boy.
'His name...
'Merlin.'
VILLAGERS SCREAM, MEN SHOUT
Search the place!
Find him!
MAN: Found him.
It's harvest time!
What's this?
Where's the rest of it?!
I only kept back what
we need to survive.
Survive?
I'll be back in one week, farmer,
and I want to see all of it.
You can't take our food!
Our children will starve -
I won't let you do this!
You're not taking any of it!
Hunith!
I will give you a week.
Don't you dare disappoint me.
I'll see you later, sweetheart.
Yah!
Mother?
Merlin!
What happened?
Who did this to you?
The winters are harsh in Ealdor,
and there are many children.
Some of them just
won't be strong enough to survive.
We barely have enough food
as it is,
and if Kanen takes our harvest,
our children won't live
to see another summer.
Please, we need your help.
Ealdor's in Cendred's kingdom.
Your safety is his responsibility.
We've appealed to our king, but...
he cares little
for the outlying regions.
You're our only hope.
I have the deepest sympathy for you
and would have this barbarian
wiped off the face of the earth.
You'll help us? I wish I could.
Surely we can spare a few men?
Resources are not the problem.
Then what is?
Ealdor lies beyond
the ridge of Aesctir.
For an army of Camelot to enter it
would be an act of war.
I know you're a good king,
a caring man.
I'm begging you - help us, please.
The accord we've struck with Cendred
was years in the making.
I cannot risk hundreds of lives
for the sake of one village.
I'm afraid Camelot cannot help.
I'm sorry.
If it were up to me,
we'd be on our way there now.
Well, you tried. And thank you for
getting an audience with the king.
I wish that Camelot was able
to help people regardless of how far
away they lived.
I'm going back to Ealdor.
Of course.
It's been an honour serving you.
You'll be coming back?
She's my mother.
I have got to look after her
before anyone else.
You understand?
I'd do exactly the same.
Well...you've been terrible.
Really, I mean it,
the worst servant I've ever had.
Thank you, sire.
Merlin.
Good luck.
Here.
HE WINCES
Tell me how it feels.
Yeah.
Yeah, that feels really good.
It's very, erm...you know...
swordy.
I've packed some armour for you.
I won't be able to carry all that.
You won't have to.
We're coming with you.
What do you mean? You're going
to need all the help you can get. I
can mend armour and sharpen swords.
And I know how to fight.
But you-you can't.
I mean, why would you?
If it was the other way round,
you'd help us. You already have,
you saved my life.
And you helped me get the druid boy
out of Camelot.
We owe it to you...both of us.
You've got the food
I prepared for you? Yes.
Careful with the wine.
One whiff of a barmaid's apron
and you're singing like a sailor.
I'll be fine. Sure you don't want
an extra blanket? It's OK, really.
I'll be all right.
Well, make sure you are.
Do whatever it takes.
They shouldn't be here,
especially the Lady Morgana.
Isn't she the king's ward?
Not that you'd know it.
She's the only person
who isn't frightened of him.
It won't make any difference
to Kanen that they're women.
I know.
But I couldn't talk them out
of coming.
I'm going to make him pay
for what he did to you.
Promise me you'll be careful.
No-one can find out about you.
They won't. They never do.
Get some rest.
Draca.
I'd ask you for money,
but I know you don't have any.
Arthur!
Put the sword down, Merlin,
you look ridiculous.
How much further is it?
Maybe a few hours.
How many men does Kanen have?
I'm not sure - I think from what my
mother's said, maybe as many as 40.
We should get some rest. It's going
to be a long day tomorrow.
Thank you.
Um... I know you didn't have to
come.
Get some sleep.
If you're hiding anything from me...
Kanen!
Please...
we have to eat... Oh. And re-sow
the fields for next year.
We only kept the bare minimum.
Everything else you can take.
That sounds fair.
No!
Kill them!
Ahatian.
Remembering when I'd beat you?
That never happened.
You'll pay for this...with
your lives, all of you!
You're still up to the magic tricks.
I thought I told you we didn't
want your kind round here.
I missed you too, Will.
It's good to see you again.
How have you been?
I hear you're skivvying for some
prince. No, I wouldn't say
I'm a skivvy.
Merlin! Gather the villagers,
I need to talk to them.
Yeah, in a minute,
I'm just talking... Now, Merlin.
There isn't much time.
Yes, sire.
I know Kanen's kind. He'll be back,
and when he is...
we must be ready for him.
First of all, we have to prepare...
Am I the only one wondering
who the hell this is?
I'm Prince Arthur of Camelot.
And I'm Prince William of Ealdor(!)
Keep quiet, he's here to help us.
He's made things worse.
Kanen will be back, looking for
revenge.
You've just signed our death
warrant. He saved Matthew's life.
It's all right, Hunith, this is his
village. What would you have us do?
We can't fight against Kanen,
he has too many men.
What's the alternative?
We give him what he wants. Then
what? Those of you who don't
starve to death
will face him again next harvest and
the harvest after that.
We manage, we'll survive.
MAN: How?
The only way he can be stopped
is if you to stand up to him.
No, you just want the
honour and glory of battle. That's
what drives men like you.
If you want to fight, then risk the
lives of your own people. Not ours.
Will.
I'll follow you. If I'm to die,
then I want to go out fighting.
That goes for me, too.
VILLAGERS: You can count me in.
Me, too. You can count me in!
He knows what he's doing.
You've got to trust him.
Look...when I first met Arthur,
I was exactly like you. I hated him.
I thought he was pompous and
arrogant. Nothing's changed there!
But in time I came to respect him,
for what he stands for, what he
does. I know what he stands for.
Princes, kings, all men like him.
Will...don't bring what
happened to your father into this.
I'm not.
Why are you defending him
so much? You're just his servant.
He's my friend.
Friends don't lord it over one
another. He isn't like that.
Really? Wait until the fighting
begins and see who he sends in
to die first.
I guarantee you it won't be him.
I trust Arthur with my life.
Is that so?
So he knows your secret, then?
Face it, Merlin, you're living
a lie, just like you were here.
You're Arthur's servant,
nothing more.
Otherwise you'd tell him the truth.
Have you always slept on the floor?
Yeah. The bed I've got in Camelot's
luxury by comparison.
It must have been hard. Hmm.
Like rock..
I didn't mean the ground, I meant...
for you, it must've been difficult.
Hmm... Not really,
I didn't know any different.
Life's simple out here.
You eat what you grow and everyone
pitches in together.
As long as you've food on the table
and a roof over your head, you're
happy. Sounds...
nice.
You'd hate it. No doubt.
Why did you leave?
Things just...changed.
How?
Come on, stop pretending
to be interesting, tell me.
I wanted to find somewhere
that I did.
Had any luck?
I'm not sure yet.
We'll start training
the men tomorrow.
It's gonna be a long day.
Get the candle.
Have you still not learned how to
dress yourself? You don't have a dog
and fetch the stick yourself.
No offence, Merlin. None taken.
Prince Arthur, you didn't
finish your breakfast. Didn't I?
Come on, eat up.
Mmm...
Right, let's get going.
We need wood and lots of it.
Of course.
Arthur said it was lovely.
He must care for you a great deal.
Arthur would do the same for any
village, that's just the way he is.
It's more than that.
He's here for you.
I'm just his servant. Give him
more credit than that, he likes you.
That's because he doesn't know me.
And if he did, I'd probably be dead
by now.
You don't really believe that,
do you?
Merlin! Where are you going with
that thing? What does it look like?
We need wood.
We both know that you don't need
an axe to fell a tree.
And I remember the trouble
it got me into,
I nearly flattened old man Simmons.
Well, he deserved it,
the stupid old crone.
He never did like me anyway.
Well, even less after that.
Why are you being like this?
You know why.
Why did you leave?
It wasn't what I wanted.
My mother was worried.
When she found out you knew,
she was so angry.
I wouldn't have told anyone.
I know you wouldn't.
You'd be able to defeat Kanen
on your own, wouldn't you?
Not sure, maybe. So what's stopping
you? So what if Arthur finds out? I
don't expect you to understand.
Try me.
One day Arthur will be a great king,
but he needs my help, and if anyone
ever found out about my powers,
I'd have to leave Camelot for good.
Are you saying you'd rather keep
your magic secret for Arthur's sake
than protect friends and family?
fighting with a sword,
but you can learn the basics -
the stance,
how to parry a blow,
how to land your own.
On my count - one,
two,
three,
four.
Now you may have to watch
for the feint, so keep your feet
moving and only stay in range
long enough to land your blow.
Again. One,
two, three, four...
One, two, three,
four...
There's no way they're gonna be
able to hold Kanen off. Men aren't
the only ones who can fight.
Again! One, two,
three...
Matthew, I want you to organise
sentry duty
to keep an eye out for Kanen and
his men. I'd be glad to.
If there's any sign of attack, I
want you to ride straight back here.
I don't want you fighting him
all on your own.
It looks like the battle's
already fought and lost.
They'll toughen up. They need to.
How are we doing for weapons?
There isn't much, but we should be
able to scrape together
what you need.
It's not the weapons that worry us,
it's having enough people to use
them.
We think the women
should be allowed to fight.
You haven't enough men. If they were
trained soldiers, maybe you'd stand
a chance, but they're not.
It's too dangerous.
Right,
back on your feet! Come on, let's go!
We don't stand a chance.
Arthur can't see that.
He's too stubborn.
Why do you think he came here?
The same reason we did.
Merlin.
Arthur may act like he doesn't care,
but...
he wouldn't be here if he didn't.
We're not going to be able to defend
Ealdor with sword and sinew alone.
We're going to need a plan.
We need to find some way of limiting
their mobility
and drawing them into a trap. If we
fight them on their terms, then...
WOMAN SCREAMS
No!
Get him down from there.
What does it say?
"Make the most of this day,
it'll be your last."
Matthew!
No! No!
No! You did this. Look what
you've done, you've killed him.
It wasn't his fault.
If he hadn't been strutting around
treating us like his personal army,
this would never have happened!
These men are brave enough to fight
for what they believe in,
even if you aren't.
You're sending them to their graves!
You've killed one man.
How many more need to die
before you realise this is a battle
that can't be won?
When Kanen comes,
you haven't got a chance.
You're going to be slaughtered.
Don't bother, Merlin, I'm not
interested. You should be,
because tomorrow Kanen attacks and
whether you like it or not, we'll
have to fight. Not if I'm not here.
That's up to you,
but the rest of us are staying.
Join us, Will.
This isn't about Arthur - this is
about your friends, are you going
to abandon them?
What, like you did? I'm here now.
Yeah. Yeah, you are
and you could end this.
If you used your magic, then
no-one else would have to die.
You know I can't.
Can't or won't?
I'm not the one abandoning
these people, Merlin.
You are.
William's father was killed
fighting for King Cendred,
so he doesn't trust
anyone of nobility.
Do you think the villagers
believed him? No.
He's...always been a trouble-maker.
They're used to ignoring him.
And if he's right?
He isn't.
I'm treating these men like soldiers,
and they're not.
You've seen them fight, they...
they haven't got a clue.
You need to tell them all to leave
the village before Kanen returns.
No, we're going to stay,
we're going to fight,
and we're going to win.
Merlin...it can't be done.
The odds are too great. It can.
We're going to make Kanen rue the
day he ever came to this village.
All you need to do
is get the men ready for battle,
and the rest...will
take care of itself. How?
You've just got to believe in them.
Because if you don't,
they'll sense it,
and the battle will be lost
before it's even begun.
Tomorrow morning,
the women and children should gather
what belongings they can carry
and go to the woods.
We're not going anywhere.
I know you want to help, but women
can't stay here, it's too dangerous.
The women have as much right
to fight for their lives
as the men do.
But none of you know how to fight.
The more of us there are,
the better chance we stand.
This is your home. If you want
to fight to defend it,
that's your choice.
I'd be honoured to stand
alongside you.
Kanen attacks tomorrow.
Kanen's brutal.
He fights only to kill,
which is why he will never defeat us.
Look around.
In this circle, we're all equals.
You're not fighting because
someone's ordering you to.
You're fighting for so much more
than that. You fight for your homes.
You fight for your family.
You fight for your friends.
You fight for the right
to grow crops in peace.
And if you fall, you fall fighting
for the noblest of causes,
fighting for your
very right to survive.
And when you're old and grey, you'll
look back on this day and you'll know
you earned the right
to live every day in between.
For your family!
For your friends!
For Ealdor! For Ealdor!
Ealdor! Ealdor! Ealdor!
Ealdor!
Come here.
I do love you, my boy.
What's wrong?
I should never have gone to Camelot.
I've ruined everything for you. You
haven't. Why would you say that?
I know what you're planning to do.
If it comes to a choice
between saving people's lives
and revealing who I really am,
there is no choice. You can't let
Arthur know about your gift.
Why not?
Maybe it's meant to be this way.
And if he doesn't accept me
for who I really am,
then...
he's not the friend I hoped he was.
Arthur.
Hunith made you some food.
Thanks.
I think. Food is scarce for these
people, you shouldn't turn your nose
up at it.
Oh, no, I shouldn't have spoken to
you like that. I'm sorry. Gwen...
I'm sorry, I don't know
what I was thinking... Guinevere...
Thank you.
You're right. And you were right
to speak up, I should've listened
to you and Morgana.
We're going to need all the help
we can get. We'll be fine.
How can you be so sure?
Because I have faith in you.
I mean...we all do.
Thank you.
No, not today. Put on your own.
Are you ready? My throat's dry.
Me, too.
It's been an honour.
Whatever happens out there today,
please don't think
any differently of me. I won't.
It's all right to be scared, Merlin.
That's not what I meant.
What is it?
If you've got something to
say...now's the time to say it.
Arthur.
They've crossed the river.
You ready? Ready.
Ealdor.
Are you frightened? Not in the
slightest.
Yah!
Hold.
No-one moves until I give the signal.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
Now, pull!
Now, Morgana,
what are you waiting for?
Something's gone wrong.
Merlin!
There's one, get him!
Kill him!
Give me the flints.
Baerne.
HORSES NEIGH
Pull back! Go the other way!
Now!
I didn't think you were coming.
Neither did I.
There's too many of them.
Not for me, there isn't.
Cume theoden.
WIND HOWLS
VILLAGERS CHEER
Pendragon!
Who did that?
What? Wind like that doesn't
just appear from nowhere.
I know magic when I see it.
One of you made it happen.
Arthur...
Look out!
Will!
You saved my life.
Yeah...I don't know
what I was thinking.
Come on, get him inside!
That's twice I've saved you.
Twice?
It was me.
I'm the one that used the magic.
Will, don't... It's OK, Merlin.
I won't be alive long enough for
anyone to do anything to me.
I did it.
I saw how desperate things were
becoming, I had to do something.
You're a sorcerer?
Yeah.
What are you going to do? Kill me?
No.
Of course not.
Merlin...
..do what you can for him.
I was right about him.
I told you he was going to get me
killed. You're not going to die.
You're a good man, Merlin,
a great man, and one day
you're going to be servant
to a great king.
Now you can still make that happen.
Thanks to you.
This place has been boring
without you.
It was good to see you again.
You too.
Merlin...
Merlin, I'm scared.
Don't be, it's going to be
all right.
Merlin...
I'm sorry.
I know he was a close friend.
He still is.
You knew he was a sorcerer,
didn't you?
That's what you were going to
tell me.
Yes.
It was.
You know how dangerous magic is.
You shouldn't have kept
this from me, Merlin.
You'd better be going.
I don't have to go.
Yes, you do.
If anything were to happen to you...
I know where to find you.
You have to go, Merlin.
You belong at Arthur's side.
I've seen how much he needs you,
how much you need him.
You're like two sides
of the same coin.
I've heard someone say that about
us before.
I'm going to miss you.
I'm going to miss you, too.
When you left...
you were just a boy.
Now look at you.
I'm so proud of you.
'When the time is right...
the truth will be known.
'Until then, you must
keep your talents hidden.
'It's better for everyone.'
I am Anhora, keeper of the unicorns.
Arthur, don't!
When you killed the unicorn,
you unleashed a curse.
Camelot will suffer greatly.
The kingdom is under attack.
Undo the curse.
It is not in my power.
He will be tested.
One of us has to die.
What have you done?
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk
www.tvsubtitles.net