In a land of myth and time of magic,
the destiny of a great kingdom
rests of shoulders on a young boy.
His name...Merlin.
(Spelling)
Aren't you scared?
Of What?
But you might catch whatever it is.
I need cooperation.This is part of my job.
Only a dead.There is nothing really to be scare of.
What you were saying?
People mustn't see this. Cover it up.
Dad, This is your sandwich.
What's in it?
It's smoked pigeon. But I'd say...
that's more smoke than pigeon.
You're so good a girl to me.
I've done you watercress soup tonight.
Dont tell me
There is more water than cress.
See you later
OK. Bye.
Wot are you doing?
weighting something.
Looks heavy
Something really...
Someone got you flowers
Oh, no.
Would you like one? a purple one.
purple one suits you.
er, I am saying that red doesnt suit you.
Thanks. well, er...
er, see you
Bye
You look happy.
I picked these for you.
Oh, thats so sweet.
To cheer you up. I know you're not sleeping well.
You cheer me up.
Would you like me to put them in water for you?
I've never seen anything like this before.
Some kind of plague?
No.  this could never from nature.
But who has this kind of power?
You think its casued by magic?
Merlin!
I'm on my way. Sorry I'm late.
Dont worry. I'm getting used to it.
Oh.er,Gwen, she gave it to me.
Tell Gaius my father wants him.
ok...
Gaius...
I heard.
Why not tell you himself?
Because it is the way it is.
You are a servant
If he knew who i was..
You'd be a dead servant.
right. get this covered up.
Im not YOUR servant.
No. You're my dogsbody. Come on, hurry up.
Whats happened?
I dont know, Sire, this is the Second case I've seen today.
Why not report it?
I wanted to find the cause.
and you concluded?
No hurry for conclusions. The scientific process is a long one.
Wot are you concealing from me?
sire, i have seen nothing like it.
the victim are dying in 24 hours. it's spreading fast.
so what is the cause?
I think, should say the cause, those likely cause, is sorcerer.
We have to find this.
I will, father.
Increasing your process in the town.
Double the guards at all the gates. And learn the position you served.
Dad!
We need Gaius to find the cure.
If he needs help, we'll give him.
If Gaius is right, believe me, this city will be white dead.
This is kind of magic that undermines the authorities,
challenges what we have done.
If we can not control this plague
people will turn to magic for kill.
we have to find this sorcerer and quickly.
yes father.
Gaius, Gaius. He's still alive.
I think there's nothing we can do, I am afraid.
We havn't tried!
If we dont know the diease, how can we cure him?
with magic!
Have a look. They are suspicious of everyone.
this is not the time to be using magic.
science will lead us to the source of the disease.
what are you doing?
examining the contents of that man's stomach.
will that tell you who did it?
No. but maybe how its spread.
One thing i do know - this is magic of the darkest kind.
why would someone use magic like that?
Magic corrupts. Pepole use it for their own ends.
But not all magic is bad. Iknow
It's neither good nor bad. It's how you use it.
Over there.
Sorry,guys. we're searching every room.
what for?
the sorcerer.
why would he be here?
Just doing my job.
we've nothing to hide.
Go on, then, search.
What are these books and papers?
My life's work, dedicated to science.
You are quite welcome to read through them if you wish.
what's this room up here?
It's mine.
what do you expect to find there?
I'm looking for evidence suggesting use of enchantments.
what have you done with the magic book I gave you?
Merlin, come here.
Look what I've found.
I found a place we can put things.
It's called a cupboard.
How long do you think before you find a cure?
Depends on the interruptions I get.
Of course. I'm sorry.
We are finished here.
We have to hide that book.
No.
we must use it.
Don't be stupid.
I have this legacy. What is it for?
You can tell me it's not for playing tricks.
You want to practise magic with the king hunting for sorcerers?
Are you mad?
Merlin, you're destined for important things.
What if I don't practise,
how would I become this great warlock?
In time your skills will be recognised.
when? how long do I wait?
Patience is a virtue.
Sitting by and doing nothing is a virtue?
Your time will come.
I could cure that man we saw.
I know it's tempting to use the way you find easiest.
It would save a life!
It's no good saving one person.
We have to discover how this is spreading.
Arthur is out right now looking for the sorcerer.
A sorcerer this powerful will never be found searching the town.
so what can we do?
Hope that science can find the answer before it kills us all.
we've searched everywhere the entire city.
Nothing?
I don't know where else to look.
Impose a curfew.
No one is to be on the street after the great bell.
- Father?   - Cordon off the lower town.
Why?
It's where most of the victims are.
Let's isolate it and stop this disease from spreading.
what about the people who live there?
You think I haven't considered it?
what else can I do?
I have to protect the rest of the city.
What's different about this victim?
Um...she's a woman.
Sometime I do wonder
whether your magic talent were given to the right person.
Anything else?
em...she's courtier
How does that help us?
Courtiers seldom go to the lower town.
What does that mean?
um...she hasn't spoken to any townspeople.
Yes it suggests that the diease is not spread by contact.
They probably eat different food.
Good. Anything else?
Don't breathe the same air.
what's the only thing they do share?
Water.
You think this diease is spread by water?
Merlin, you're a prodigy.
It's time to get up, dad.
Dad!
Gwen?
Gwen.
Gaius.
Who have the sickness?
My farther.
Please, Gaius, he's all I have.
Gwen, I have no cure.
I am begging you.
I hope there is something anything,
but so far the remedy is beyond what I can achieve.
I'm sorry , Gwen.
There must be something we can do.
My best. Let's hope this can provide answers.
Too late for Gwen's father.
I hear you maybe right.
What about that one?
In there.
Sentries,sir.
Father, what's happened? I can't believe it!
Don't touch it.
I have this in the water for no more than a few hours.
Where the water from?
From the people's daily supply.
We must stop using it.
The city can't survive without water!
We have to find the sorcerer!
I don't believe they are inside Camelot.
Then extend the search to the villages.
We've started, but I can't search the entire kingdom.
Any I can't stand by and watch our people dying.
How's your father?
Is he feeling better?
Yeah. It's incredible.
It's a miracle.
His skins clear? Back to normal?
Yes.
Great.
You don't seem surprised.
No, no I am. It's a miracle.
But how did you know he's well?
Er...cause is your smiling.
That's really weird.
I haven't told anyone. but you know.
How could you know?
Yep, all right.
You finally found out.
I will tell you.
I'm psychic.
No, you're not.
It's true.
All Right, what am I thinking?
That I'm not a psychic.
You're strange.
I don't mean that in a nasty way.
You just funny.
I like that.
I'm pleased for you.
Thank you.
What for?
Don't know. just for asking.
I didn't like to see you upset.
Alright, I have to go.
Get on.
The story is you were sick.
Not any more.
Perhaps you are suffering from some other ailment.
Oh, you're joking.
I feel like death itself.
Not enough to strength in me to stir the air.
And...what happened?
I don't know. suddenly it was gone.
I'm fitter than I was before.
That's Remarkable. was anybody with you when all these happened?
Just my daughter gwen.
Seize her.
No.
Guinevere,
I'm arresting you for crimes in contravention to
the laws of camelot. That you did practise enchantments.
Gwen!
I haven't done anything! help me!
What are you doing?
We found a magic poultice in her house.
That's ridiculous.
How else do you explain her father recovery?
But she's innocent. you know she is innocent.
What can I do? I can't turn the blind out.
No! please! listen to me.
Please, I haven't done anything false! Authur, listen to me, please!
I'm innocent! I swear!
Let me go! I swear!
Merlin! merlin! please help me!
Why don't you listen to me?
No, please!
-what have you done?  -what?
I warned you!
Oh, I understand, you thought you were doing good.
I couldn't let her father die,
knowing I could cure him.
But do you think it might looks a bit suspicious, curing one man!
Well, then, all I have to do is,
I'll cure everyone. no one has to know it was magic.
It's too late. they think gwen is a sorcerer and she cause the disease.
But she didn't!
And how are you going to prove that?
Please listen to me. I have done nothing. please.
I swear I haven't done anything.
Well done.
Why will no-one believe me?
He got better. he just recovered. I didn't do anything!
I believe you. perhaps this disease is not always fatal.
Have you thought of that?
Perhaps he recovered naturally.
And what of this poultice that was found?
What poultice? I don't know anything about a poultice.
It was found in your house.
Undo this enchantment. put an end to this contagion.
I can't.
I can show you no mercy.
I'm not a witch! I don't know how to stop the illness.
If you will not undo your sorcery, I must find your guilty.
But I have told you I ...
It's therefore my duty to pronounce judgment.
Under the circumstances, I have no choice but to sentence you to death.
No.
I can only hope that when you die, the evil plague dies with you.
Take her away.
No!
Please no! I'm innocent! please! please no!
Please help me! please, I beg you.
I know gwen. she's my maidservant, not an enchantress.
Have you ever seen an enchantress?
Believe me, they bear no sign, no mark.
There is no sense of evil in the eye.
I've seen the way the girl works.
Her fingers are worn, her nails are broken.
If she was a sorceress, why would she do this,
why would she kneel on a cold stone floor,
Morning after morning,
When she could make this things happen with a snap of her fingers?
Like an idle king!
You have no right...
You have a right to cast a judgement.
I have a responsbility to take care of this kingdom.
I take no pleasure in this.
You're sentencing the wrong person.
She's right, father.
You hear with the magic. you no longer listening.
You saw yourself. she used enchantments.
Yes, maybe.
But to save her dying father,
it doesn't make a guilty of creating a plague.
One's an act of love, the other of evil.
I don't believe Evil isn't in this girl's heart.
I have witnessed what witchcraft can do.
I've suffered at its hand.
I cant take that chance.
If there is a slightest chance about that girl
She must die or the whole kingdom may perish.
I can't understand that.
One day you may become a king.
Then you will understand.
Such decisions must be made.
There are dark forces that threaten this kingdom.
I know. witchcraft is an evil, faher.
so is injustice.
Yes, I am yet to be king and I don't know what kind of king I will be.
But I do have a sense of the kind of camelot I wish to live in.
It would be where the punishment fits the crime.
I fear you're right.
She's played with fire.
And sadly, she must die by fire.
I thought I was doing good.
And that curing gwen's father would help her.
I thought I was saving a life.
It seemed...so simple.
An easy solution is like a light in a storm, merlin.
Rush for it at your peril. it may
not always lead you to a safe harbour.
I can see that now.
I have warned you about the responsibilities of a warlock.
I must see her.
Gwen!
Thank you.
What for?
Coming to see me.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
Well...it's all right. don't worry about me.
There's no point crying about it.
I mean, I'm not saying you were going to cry about me.
Obviously I dont think that.
Oh, gwen, I cant have this happen.
Please, one thing.
You dont have to.
But...
What?
Remember me.
You're not going to die. I'm not going to let this happen.
What if burning this witch doesnt stop the poison?
How do I protect my people?
We've closed down the water pumps.
The emergency supply won't last much longer.
We have to find a way to cleanse the water of the disease.
But how?
Well...
It was me.
It was me who used magic to cure gwen's father.
Gwen is not the sorcerer. I am.
Merlin! are you mad?
I cannot let her die for me.
I place myself at your mercy.
He doesn't know what he's saying.
I do.
Then arrest him.
Father, please. this is madness!
there's no way merlin is a sorcerer.
Did you not hear him? Yes
He admitted it.
He saved my life, remember?
Why should he fabricate such a story?
As gaius says, he's got a grave mental disease.
Really?
He's in love.
What?
With gwen.
I am not.
Yes, you are.
I saw you with that flower she'd given you.
But...i'm not in love with her.
It's all right. you can admit it.
I dont think of her like that!
Perhaps she cast a spell on you.
Merlin is a wonder
but the wonder is that he's such an idiot.
There's no way he's a sorcerer.
Don't waste my time. let him go.
Arthur's an idot, you know
Arthur was right to do that he did.
he saved you from you own stupidity.
What else could I do? it's my fault gwen's going to die.
You dont prove her innocence by jumping into the flames.
You do it by finding out the cause of the disease.
Well, whatever it is, arthur's not going to find it.
He thinks he's so sharp.
Even when I said I was a wizard, he still couldnt see it.
It's pretty hard to spot.
Maybe I should get a pointy hat.
I dont think you'll find one big enough.
Anyway, forget that.
To save gwen, we have to find out what's contaminating the water.
This water supplies the whole town.
Take a sample.
Let's take it back and examine it.
What the hell was that?
There.
It was an afanc.
An...a what?
A beast born of clay and conjured up. only by the most powerful sorcerer.
Now we have to find a way to defeat it.
But where?
That could take days. gwen'll be dead by then.
Have you got a better idea?
Gwen?
I'm going to get you out.
I will.
Hello?
Hello.
The great warlock returns,as I knew he would.
I need to know how to defeat an afanc.
Yes I suppose you do.
Will you help me?
Trust the elements that are at your command.
Elements? but what is it I have to do?
You cannot do this alone. you are but one side of a coin.
Arthur is the other.
I dont understand.
Just tell me what it is I have to do.
No!
Please! please help me!
I have!
Oh, yeah, right, thanks.
Have you found anything more?
I have tried.
Then keep looking.
People are dying. we cant delay any longer.
We must kill the witch. bring her execution forward to tonight.
Merlin, what are you doing?
Looking for a book.
Care to tell me which one?
A book on elements.
Elements?
Yes. which one would I find them in?
Most of them. the study of base elements is at the heart of science.
How does that help kill the afanc?
The Afanc is a creature made of earth and water,
that's two of the four base elements.
What are the other two?
Perhaps they will destroy it.
You want fire. Wind and fire.
How did you find this out?
I just knew. Part of my powers.
What else did your powers tell you?
I am only one side of the coin. The brighter side, obviously.
Who's the other side?
I think it might be Arthur.
They are bringing forward the execution.
We have to prove Gwen's innocent.
We're trying.
Please. Just tell me what I can do to help.
We need Arthur.
Arthur?
There's a monster, an Afanc in the water supply.
That was causing the plague.
We must tell Uther.
I think it's a creature forged by magic.
Uther would just blame Gwen for conjuring it.
So, what are we to do?
We need to destory it.
The plague will stop and Uther may see sense.
That's why you need Arthur.
He's our best chance.
But he won't want to disobey the king.
Leave that to me.
You're alright?
Sorry about all this. Merlin's not been in today.
Poor Merlin.
Yeah.
To offer to give up his life to save Gwen's...
I can't imagine any man loving me so much.
No, I can't imagine that either.
It's because you're not like Merlin.
He's a lover.
Maybe that's...I haven't found the right person to love.
Sadly, the age of gallantry seems to be dead.
Look around and all you see are small men.
Not big enough to fill their armour.
There's not one of them able to stand up for what is right.
What do you want me to do?
You'd better be right about this, Merlin.
You should stay here.
I'm coming with you.
No.
Scared I'll show you up?
Father will slam us both in chains
if he knows I'd endangered you.
Good he doesn't know, then.
Turn back. You could get hurt.
So could you...
If you don't get out of my way.
How are we going to find it?
Just hope we do, before it finds us.
-Stop!  -What?
It's just a shadow.
Spread out.
What is it? Are you all right?
Yeah.
-Did you see it? -Yes.
-What does it look like? -It's ... it's quick.
Where is it?
I think it's gone this way.
Arthur, use the torch!
(Spell)
Merlin!
This is very good.
Good news, sire.
There are no new deaths, and the sick is recovering.
Good.
Strange, I've never heard of an Afanc before.
It's conjured from the clay by powerful magic.
The type that can only be invoked by an ancient sorcerer.
One who has the power to mirror the spirit of life.
I found this at the water source.
It bears the mark of Nimueh.
We must be vigilant, sire.
Will I never be rid of her?
Sire...
Leave me!
Dad!
Thank you!
Don't thank me. It was more Merlin.
Really?
He's the real hero here.
I don't know what to say.
I didn't do anything.
I'm grateful to you all. Come on, Gwen.
Merlin, I wanted you to know...
you secret's safe with me.
My secret?
Merlin, don't pretend.
I know what you did.
You do?
Saw it with my own eyes.
You did.
I understand why you don't want me to know.
Well, obviously...
But I won't tell anyone.
Yo don't mind me talking to you about it?
Er, no. It's...
You have no idea how hard it is to keep this hidden.
Well, you can continue to deny it.
But I think Gwen's very lucky one.
Gwen?
It's our secret.
The fish didn't come from the water, did it?
Where else would it come from?
Water's fine now. That's not your worry.
This is the work of a very powerful sorcerer.
I only hope you didn't come to her attention.
Doubt it. No-one else seems to appreciate my skills.
I just want someone to see me for who I am.
One day, Merlin.
One day.
One day what?
One day people won't believe
what an idiot you were.
Thanks.
Merlin, you will pay for this.
Merlin.
If I don't get the antidote, what happens to Merlin?
He will die.
His pulse is weaker.
His fever's getting worse.
He's dead?
www.tvsubtitles.net