Come on, let’s get those bids up, it’s the Annual Boy Toy Auction.
Alright I’ve got $25, do I hear $40? Oh come on people, this is for charity. $40?
$40. Coming up right there. Anybody got $50? How about $50? $50?
$50. And remember for the next five hours, till midnight tonight, these boys are at your call.
- How about $55?
- $55.
$55. Going once. Going twice. Sold for $55.
Pay your money and get your boy.
Look, I have credit cards, okay? Gold? Platinum, for crap sake.
I’m sorry. Auction rules say cash only. Okay?
Here’s the thing. I’m kind of coming out of a dark place right now and I could really use the distraction.
I need this boy and I need him tonight.
I understand. But by rule, I have to give him to the next highest bidder if she has the money to give.
- Oh no. No, no.
- Brooke.
- Uh uh.
- No.
- Brooke.
Thank you.
Okay that did not just happen because I had an entire evening planed,
so what am I supposed to do now?
Well, there are four boys still up for auction, and a cash machine right down the street.
Okay.
See anything you like?
I’m seeing everything I like.
Really?
But I think I’m going to bid on Jake.
You guys are really hitting it off, huh?
Just friends, really.
What about you? Ready to fight off these rabid skanks for Nathan?
Actually, I think I’m going to bid on Lucas.
Really?
Yeah, I haven’t gotten a chance to spend time with him much lately
and I get Nathan for free.
Alright folks, here we go.
Who is up next?
Oh no.
Tim.
Do I hear $30?
How about $20?
That boys going to pull something.
Can I get a ten spot?
I suppose I have some chores around the house.
- $8?
- Sold!
Oh Jake’s up next. How much money do you have?
$87.53.
Okay.
- $20.
- I have a bid for $20.
- Do I hear $30?
- $30.
- Take it off!
- $40?
- $40.
$40. Right over there.
- $50.
- $50. Going, going.
- $75.
Bet it all.
- $87.53.
- Going once.
- $100.
Going once.
- Who’s bidding on Jake?
- Going twice.
Sold! For $100 American. The highest man of the night. Good job, Jaglieski.
You dirty bird. Who bought you?
I don’t know. But whoever it is it will be fun. It’s for charity, right?
- Yeah man.
- Go get ‘em.
Okay, let’s have our next boy.
Well, here goes.
Yeah! I got you.
Alright, let’s start the bid at $20.
- $25.
- $35.
- $50.
- $75.
- $100.
- I’ll go $101.
$105.
$110. Oh what the hell. $115.
Sold!
Café savings. No way he’s worth it though.
Alright, we’re down to our last boy toy, so loosen up those purse strings,
pucker up those lips and remember, this is for a good cause.
You’re on, Nathan.
Okay, do I have a first bid?
- $80.
- Wow.
$85.
It smells like sex in here.
$90.
$91.
That’s a creepy threesome.
Do I hear $92?
$92.
How much money do you have?
Well with the five you gave me, $92.53.
- Okay bid it.
- What?
- You have to bid it, I want you to buy Nathan.
- Why?
- To keep him away from them.
- Going twice.
Please, Peyton, please.
$92.53.
$109 and 40.
- Going once.
- Where’s that emergency 20. Come on. Where are you?
Going twice.
Oh! $112.53.
- Sold!
- Yes!
- Thank you.
- Wait, wait.
I’m sorry, we’re fresh out of flesh.
I want to thank you all for coming this evening supporting this good cause.
Now  all these young men belong to the highest bidders till that midnight kiss.
Let’s try to keep things legal this year.
I’ll give $5 for the microphone boy.
- I’ll go 10.
- Do I hear 20?
I will.
- $25.
- Oh no, I’ve got $200.
Sold!
All sales are final.
I didn’t see you in detention.
Can I get you something to eat?
Actually  I was wondering if I could get you something to eat.
Unless you’ve got plans after work.
No.
Great. We could go to my place.
Karen. I’m not a serial killer.
It’s just a couple of new friends eating food.
Sure. Okay.
Good, then it’s a date.
Okay, I’ve got $50 cash on the Mouth-Boy for trade. Who wants him?
Well, Timmy. Looks like you’re all mine tonight.
How about you grab a change of clothes and I’ll meet you at the house.
Change of clothes?
Well you’ll probably want to take a shower after I get through with you.
I plan on getting dirty.
So I’ll leave the door unlocked. Just come in and get me.
Well, well, Jake.
Once again, looks like I own you.
Come on, Jake, wait up.
I’m not kidding, Nikki. I’m not falling for your crap.
At least talk to me?
About what? Where you’ve been for the last 8 months or how my daughter doesn’t have a mother?
I understand you’re upset, but there are things you don’t know. Please.
Jake, come on. I don’t want to mess with your head.
But, the least you could do is hear me out.
After that you can ditch me if you want.
What, like you did me?
This things is awesome. Where are we going first?
- Here’s the thing, Lips.
- Mouth.
I know. And I know I owe you for the whole cheerleading competition,
but I had this whole night kind of perfectly planned out and
it’s a waste of a Brazilian wax.
Okay. That’s cool. I can take off.
At least let me give you some of your money back.
Oh, no, no, no. I don’t want that. Please.
No, no I understand. I just thought the car was cool.
Um, I’ll see you later.
Wait. Fine!
I’ll take you to once place.
Really?
What the hell. It’s for charity, right?
With the night I have planned I might need you to carry me home anyway.
Sweet.
I am so excited to have Lucas all to myself for an evening.
We have not had a night to just hang out in forever.
Yeah, same goes for me and Nathan.
I know you’re still into me, but $112?
- Hey you.
- Hey.
- How about you come see me around midnight?
- Sounds good.
Don’t have fun.
I wont.
Alright, come on. Let’s get this over with.
Funny. That’s what he’d say before we used to have sex.
So you’re planning to kill me?
The painters must have left it.
So what do you think of the new place?
You really moved out, huh?
Yeah. Judge declared me emancipated.
Good for you, Nate.
Come on. Check it out.
So what, you got your big cool apartment but you don’t believe in furniture?
Where are we supposed to eat?
We got the bed.
Still doing that whole desert before the meal thing, huh?
You used to think it was cute.
Yeah. That was before you abandoned my child.
Okay. I guess we’ll do this now.
I made a mistake. I didn’t know what kind of mother I’d be.
All my friends were going off to college, my parents… well you know how they felt.
I just wasn’t ready, Jake. Is it that hard to understand?
Yeah, Nikki, it is.
She was a part of you. You held her in your arms.
I spent every night asking myself how you could just leave her behind.
I couldn’t. I hated myself for leaving, that’s why I came back.
I want to be in her life, Jake.
And yours too.
I missed you, you know?
I wanted to call you a thousand times over the last 8 months.
Yeah but you didn’t. Did you?
Well, that was a great dinner, Larry.
Thanks. Single parent cooking class.
I’m glad you decided to come.
- Not too painful?
- No, not at all.
But you don’t date much?
I don’t date at all, really.
At night I work or I’m at home with Lucas.
Sometimes with Keith.
Keith seems like a good man.
He is.
He’s a good friend.
- Well…
- Oh no. Absolutely not.
You’re  off duty and not allowed to touch anything but your wine glass.
Tour the house, make a long distance phone call, whatever, it’s called relaxing.
Well you know I do have some friends in Florence.
Maybe I should give them a call.
Haley, now this was a great idea.
I know.
Did you fill any with milk like we used to?
Yeah I did. Some of them.
I can’t do this stuff with Nathan. It just seems, I don’t know, does it seem childish?
- Well, yeah.
- Great!
But in a good way.
So, what’s your situation now?
What do you mean?
With Peyton? Or Brooke. Or bar-slut that I heard about.
Okay. What’d you hear and who’d you hear it from?
Just stuff… from people.
I just want to play ball again.
You know? Get over this damn drama.
You know it wasn’t long ago I was happy playing hoops with the guys and hanging out with you.
Yes, life was much simpler then, wasn’t it?
I think I’m going to go call Nathan.
Ohhh. You are so dead.
I guess that one was a milk balloon.
I think she likes you.
So thanks for bringing me out tonight. I’ve never been to a real club before.
I’m glad I brought you.
Yeah?
Yeah. I enjoy corrupting America’s youth. It’s kind of one of my hobbies.
So was Lucas one of your test subjects?
Can we not go there tonight?
Okay. Sorry.
That girls practically naked up there.
So you don’t like naked girls?
Well I’ve never actually seen one up close.
But from what I’ve found online I’m thinking they’re okay.
What?
Want to find out for sure?
Let’s do some damage.
Kind of severe, huh?
Kind of familiar, actually.
You know when I was a cheerleader we buried a time capsule midfield of the football stadium.
I bet if you dug it up you’d find a version of the same thing our kinds are going through now.
Well, I got a couple of shovels in the garage.
Want to find out?
Yeah.
- Sweet. You got a pool?
- Yeah. You want to go swimming?
No, you are the boy toy you do what I say tonight.
Oh, just like old times.
Please. You did whatever you wanted and most of the time it was either sucky or mean.
I know. But you let me.
Well maybe I kept thinking you’d change. Live and learn, right?
- Is this thing heated?
- I don’t know, why don’t you check it out?
Oh my god!
- I slipped.
- What?!
I slipped. Hey, at least it’s heated.
Real thing sure beats the internet, huh?
The internet sucks.
Hello?
Deb?
Miss Deborah?
Come on in, Timmy, I’m in the bath.
Ready or not, here I come.
Sorry!
Timmy!
I am so sorry. I don’t know what gave you the impression that...
It’s okay. I’m fine. I'm fine...
- It’s just that you startled me and...
- Where’s my shirt?
The lawyers are gonna love this one.
Luke?
I’m all out of balloons. Can we please call a truce?
- Is it a real truce or a trick truce?
- It’s a real truce, I promise.
Okay.
Or not!
No Luke, you’re going to hurt your shoulder.
Oh you are so lucky.
What?
- What’s on your back?
- Nothing.
- Haley, is that a tattoo?
- No. It’s nothing.
Haley.
23.
That’s great, Hales.
You see, that’s why I don’t like the guy.
- Lucas.
- No, that’s just like him!
To get you branded with his jersey number right above your ass?
He doesn’t even know about it.
I just, I just did it.
By yourself?
Yeah, by myself.
Haley, why would you do that?
Because I’m in love with him.
Look, I didn’t mean to freak out on you up there, okay?
But, a tattoo?
You got one. You got one with a girl you’re not even dating anymore.
I know.
How stupid do I look?
You hold me to a higher standard than everybody else, Luke, and it’s not fair.
Look, I know it’s not fair, okay? But that’s because I’ve seen you be better than most people.
Let me see it again.
How long ago did you do it?
A  few days ago.
- And Nathan had nothing to do with it?
- No, I told you, Nathan doesn’t know.
Ugh, God, what am I going to do, Luke? I’m so, I hate being away from him,
I think about him constantly. I was in the middle of a history quiz yesterday
and I just totally zoned out on him.
Maybe we’re not going to be together for the rest of our lives,
but right now I’m in love for the first time
and if I look at this tattoo 20 years from now,
and it reminds me of how I feel today,
I think I’ll be okay with that.
Then why didn’t you buy Nathan at the auction?
Why hide out with me?
Because, I wanted to remember for a night the way that things were.
Everything was so much simpler when it was just you and me.
And I’m used to being self-confident, and sensible and...
I just really feel like a mess right now.
You’re not a mess.
You’re just in love.
And I’m not sure if he is.
What happened to us, Peyton? We used to be good together.
No, we weren’t. We just had sex a lot.
You sure about that?
Trust me. You’re the only guy I’ve been with.
You knew that.
Yeah, I know, I just, I figured since we broke up, maybe...
No.
Yeah, me neither.
It’s just sex, right?
Okay, you know what, Nathan? Haley really deserves better than that.
She really, really likes you and she’s good for you and more than that, she trusts you...
- I know that.
- And okay, fine.
We could do it, right here in the pool, and nobody would know.
- Peyton…
- But I would know,
and you would know, but I wouldn’t do that to Haley. Or myself.
Or even you for that matter. Cause you know what?
If you screw things up with your relationship with her, than you’re a bigger jackass than even I thought.
I know it would hurt Haley.
The only reason I mentioned it, was to let you know that I’m not pressuring her.
Right. I knew that.
- You said I was good in bed.
- No, I didn’t.
- Oh yes you did.
- Oh, God, kill me.
So I left school for good by the way.
Thought I might transfer here.
Will you at least tell me how she’s doing?
Right.
So I guess asking you how you’re doing is out of the question.
You look good.
Give me the keys, Nikki.
Stop it.
Come on. I missed you, Jake.
Remember how good we were?
I know it’s been hard for you, I do.
Let me make it easier.
Come back to me.
We could be a family.
Damn it.
Damn it, Nikki.
You almost had me again.
You want to impress me with your Maternal instincts?
Get out.
Why don’t you go buy all the things you think Jenny might need. I’ll wait.
Okay.
Hey, by the way. She’s 9 months old, just incase you forgot.
I’ll be fine.
Hey.
Hey, Keith, come on in.
I saw your car. So how did pimp duty go?
That’s charity coordinator.
Right. Assuming you’d raffle yourself off, huh?
Nobody could afford me.
I’m glad you came by, Keith.
I’ve been wanting to ask you a question.
When do you plan to start living?
Well, I am living, coach.
No you’re not. You’re dying.
I for one think it’s a damn shame.
You know what I’d change in my life if I could?
I’d have Camilla back.
Just to spend one more day with her.
When we were young and in love.
You love Karen, don’t you?
Yeah, I do.
And I plan on telling her that it’s just...
things have been kind of messy since the accident, you know?
I understand.
There’s something you need to understand.
Everyday you wait,
is another day you’ll never get back again.
Trust me on that, son.
I know.
So why don’t you have a girlfriend? You’re a nice guy.
Well that’s the problem. I’m too nice.
- Girls like jerks.
- Yeah, tell me about it.
You mean Lucas?
I thought we weren’t going to talk about Lucas tonight,
but I could just throw your ass out at the next light.
Okay. So let me ask you a question.
What do girls want?
Half your paycheck.
Here’s my philosophy on dating.
It’s important to have somebody that can make you laugh.
Somebody you can trust. Somebody that, you know, turns you on.
And it’s really, really important that these three people don’t know each other.
I got the cutest little stuffed animal.
She has a purple monkey that she can’t sleep without. Anything else she ignores.
You got the wrong formula. She needs a special kind because, well she wasn’t breastfeed.
The alcohol in these wipes are bad for her skin.
I buy her a special vitamin because she was a little underweight at her six month checkup.
She doesn’t read. She sure as hell doesn’t smoke.
Oh well look, at least you got the most expensive kind of ice cream.
I got that for you.
Cause on our third date you said that all you needed for life to be good was a pint of this ice cream.
I want your life to be good, Jake.
I want to be with the boy that told me those things.
- Where did he go?
- You left him.
Damn it, Nikki, it’s not fair for you to come back here and do this.
It’s not fair to me, and it’s not fair to Jenny.
I still love you, you know?
It’s funny. I can’t tell you how many times I spent wondering
when I was going to hear you say that again.
Just hoping the next time the phone rang it’d be you, calling to say those words.
Jake.
And now that you’re here, I... I cant even remember why I needed to hear them.
You should recognize this next move, Nikki. You perfected it.
It called turning my back and leaving you behind.
I don’t know about this, Larry. We’re trespassing.
No we’re not. Our taxes paid for this place.
Oh, okay, let’s try vandalism, theft…
We loosen dirt, on a field we paid for, get property that belongs to you,
and we put the dirt back. What could they charge for us?
Immaturity.
There’s a difference between growing up and growing old, Karen.
Give me the shovel.
I can’t believe you do this every night. You have the greatest life.
Hi.
You look hot tonight.
Thanks.
So, what’s your name?
You don’t remember the last time we did this.
You were pretty wasted. You’re name is Brooke, right?
So, Brooke. Are we going to do this again, or what?
You okay?
I need to go home.
Brooke, did something happen?
Do you want to talk about it?
How long have you known Lucas?
Since 4th grade. I transferred in.
And you think he’s a good guy?
I think he’s a great guy.
Why?
Remember when I told you what girls want?
Girls just want somebody to want them back.
At least I do.
If it’s action that you’re craving, go and get yourself a Raven.
We said go. Ravens. Go mighty Ravens.
If you really want to score, gotta dig a little more. We say go, Ravens, go mighty Ravens.
Oh. We got treasure.
Oh yeah.
- Check it out.
- Oh!
Bon Jovi. I saw that tour. Scorpions opened for them.
Yeah.
Oh no!
- Check out the hair.
- Me and Dan.
Is that Keith?
Yeah. He was always very protective.
You know, I don’t think I ever noticed Keith in the picture before.
Well, the kid in the background is definitely in love with the girl in the foreground.
What in the sam hill is going on here?
Oh my God.
- Karen?
- Hi, Whitey.
Offer you a beer, coach?
We were, um, having dinner and...
Oh hey, Keith.
It’s nearly midnight. Looks like our date’s almost over.
Yeah.
I think I was hitting on you in the pool.
You think you were?
I don’t know anymore. This whole good guy thing, it’s new to me.
I guess I’ll always have feelings for you, Peyton.
But I owe it to Haley to be a better guy than I’ve been.
I just don’t want to be the kind of guy that cheats on her.
Then don’t be.
Nathan, I’m proud of you.
You know, standing up to your dad, and being a good guy for Haley.
You’re turning into the kind of guy I always knew you could be.
- So Nathan got his own place.
- Yeah this is it.
Oh crap. I left some cds for him in the car. I’ll be right back.
- No, I’ll come.
- No, it’s alright.
Um, why don’t you go ahead and go on in, apartment 11.
Hey, ask him if he’s in love with me, and if he says no, break up with him for me, okay?
- Okay.
- Great.
Hey. Seriously. Say something nice, okay? I mean, he’s really a different person.
- Okay.
- I better get going.
I guess by rule, I owe you a kiss.
I guess so.
He wasn’t there.
Are you sure? Apartment 11?
Yeah.
Voice mail. Great. I guess he’s not done yet. I told you Peyton was easy.
Come on, I’ll take you home.
Okay.
I guess I should have told my parents I’d be out late.
I’m not sure this was a good idea.
Mouth, you’ve got to live a little.
No, it’s not that. I mean, a night with you is like flying first class.
My life is coach.
It’s going to be hard going back to it.
Thanks, but this gets old, pretty quick. Trust me.
Listen, Brooke.
I don’t know what’s going on with you and Lucas but he’s a really good guy.
I’ve never been really good at sports, I mean, I’m little, you know.
But when I decided I wanted to be a sports announcer,
Lucas introduced me to the guys at the river court and it made me feel like I belonged.
He has a good heart. And as far as I can tell, you do too.
I’d be really surprised if you two couldn’t work things out.
Thank you.
Well, I should get home. That stripper might booty call me.
Mouth.
Oh right. For the charity thing.
Nah.
Just cause.
Hey, Brooke.
Thanks. This was the greatest night of my life.
Well, did you have fun tonight, slave boy? Thanks for playing along.
Look, Haley. I know we’ve grown apart a bit lately.
And I know we have a lot a head of us, but...
I just want you to know I’ll always be there for you.
And if Nathan doesn’t see how special you really are, well, then he’s an idiot.
Cause I think you’re amazing.
Thanks, Luke.
Oh, technically you owe me a goodnight kiss.
Mm. Rules are rules, I guess.
Yeah, I guess so.
Here’s the thing, though, if your tongue comes anywhere near my mouth
I’m just never speaking to you again.
Hey, Haley.
You’re going to be okay.
I promise you that.
- Nikki, don’t do this.
- Jake, please.
Keeping Jenny away from me because I hurt you is wrong.
Can’t you just forgive me?
It was a Wednesday.
What? What was?
The day I realized that you weren’t coming back.
I loved you. You knew I loved you. I would have done anything for you.
But you betrayed me. So it was that same Wednesday that I stopped loving you.
And I promised myself that my daughter would never feel the pain that you caused me.
You want to hear me say it?
Fine. You broke my heart, Nikki.
But you will never break my daughters heart because you will never, ever have the chance to.
I’m going to be in her life, Jake.
With you or without you.
So would you like some coffee?
It’s getting late, I should probably go.
I had a lot of fun tonight. I didn’t do much of this in high school.
Well, maybe next time we could do something less juvenile.
Oh well, if we have to.
Karen, I know you have some history with Keith. I hope I didn’t cause any problems tonight.
No.
But I like you. For what it’s worth.
Well, I like you too, Larry.
And you’re right. I do have history with Keith.
I’m just not sure we have a future.
Goodnight.
Keith.
It’s not too late, is it?
No. Is everything okay?
Not really. These last few weeks have been the hardest of my life.
Being without you and Lucas, on the outside of your lives.
I felt... I felt like a shadow of someone I used to be.
And I know I let you down. And I put Lucas at risk,
but you have to know, I love Lucas.
And I’ve been carrying this around with me since the night of the accident.
I love you Karen.
Keith.
I always have.
Marry me.
I need to talk to you.
Okay.
I spent the entire night trying to avoid this or ignore it,
but I cant so I’ve just got to say it.
Brooke what’s up?
I think I’m pregnant.
Synchro : Amariss
- www.forom.com-
www.tvsubtitles.net