How’s your punching hand?
A lot better now that I nailed a guy’s face.
How ‘bout you? How are you feeling?
Like an idiot.
Luke, you’re cool with us being just friends, right?
I mean, we are friends, right?
We are.
- Okay.
- And I’m cool with it.
And besides, I wasn’t ready for all that Peyton Sawyer/Girlfriend drama anyway, you know.
Hey, say hi to Brooke for me?
Alright. Talk to you later.
Haley.
Mmm, we can’t do this here right now.
We just did…
Alright, I’ll kiss you later.
When you leave this gym today,
I want each one of you to look at the sun,
because if you lose to Cove City on Friday,
I can pretty much guarantee you
that sun will not rise the next day.
That’s not a joke.
I’ve coached some great players and great teams in this gym,
but not one of those great players or great teams has finished a season undefeated.
You may be the first.
There are only two things separating you from greatness.
Number one is Cove City.
Number two… is you.
Hey, Brooke!
I’ve got something for you.
I know you do, gorgeous.
It’s that book I was telling you about.
- I though you might want to check it out.
- Oh, I definitely want to check it out.
I suppose I could read the book too. But what are you going to do for me?
What do you mean?
Well, I read the book. You do something for me.
- Like what?
- I don’t know. Something fun.
- Deal?
- Okay. Deal.
Should we shake on it or just make out now?
Who knew reading could be so much fun?
Need some help?
No. Everything is just fine.
How about a cup of coffee?
Deb, I know you claim your taking over the café’s not some sort of payback.
It isn’t. I’m trying to help Karen.
By ruining her business? That’s the worst cup of coffee I ever paid for.
If you’ve come here to mock me, Dan, save it.
I didn’t come here to mock you.
I had a few hours. I thought maybe my wife could use my help.
Clearly she can.
How’s your sandwich?
Almost warm.
Well, I’ll start cooking again. Unless your mother comes to her senses.
You know, just when I think things can’t get any weirder around here,
Mom takes over Karen’s café.
I think I’m going to invite Lucas over to spend the night.
Well, your mother hasn’t exactly been herself lately.
It might help if you tell her you’re happy.
She thinks I’ve ruined your life.
Cove City game’s coming up.
Yeah. Whitey claims that if we lose, the sun doesn’t rise.
Well, he might actually be right for once.
Of course, you know who scored the most points against the Cavaliers?
- 42.
- Yeah.
- I’m looking to top that this week.
- No. You won’t.
You want to know why? Because you’re not tough enough inside.
I got coverage buckets you’ll never get because you can’t bang down low like I did.
That plus the fact that your conditioning’s for crap. I never left the floor during a game.
Hey, guys.
I’m happy, Mom. Dad loves me.
What was that all about?
He was wondering where his mother was.
Oh. Don’t start, Dan. I’m tired and I’m hungry.
Oh, well. How about you eat first and then we argue?
- How about we just don’t argue?
- How about we just don’t eat?
What up, brother?
You do know you’re white, Tim?
What’s wrong with you?
- Is your brother still dealing?
- Why?
‘Cuz I need to tear it up against Cove City.
So how’s getting high gonna help?
Not weed, Tim. Performance enhancers.
Look, just tell your brother that I’m gonna be on the floor for forty minutes,
and I need to be in a different gear.
You sure about this?
Yeah. He’ll know what do get.
So what, you going to avoid the café for the next six weeks?
What, you don’t like pizza?
I love pizza, but that’s not the point.
Look, don’t you find it a bit strange, having Nathan’s mom running the café?
Yeah. It’s a little strange.
It’s also pretty gutsy of her.
Dan’s gotta be giving her a lot of grief about it.
You know, Luke, you really oughtta give her a chance.
Deb’s okay. And when you think about it,
when she got pregnant in college, her life changed a lot like your mom’s did.
Yeah but Dan?
Why does she stay with a guy like that?
I don’t know. Maybe she wants to protect her son.
Hey Handsome. Three more chapters and you’re all mine.
What  was that all about?
Nothing.
Well I disagree. That was definitely something.
Okay I got them.
You sure about this?
Have you met my dad?
Okay, here’s the deal.
These are basically amphetamines.
They’re like, steroids on speed or speed on steroids.
Anyway, you gotta be careful Nathan.
Whatever  gets me jacked for Cove City, man.
Here. These will definitely do that.
Anyway, if you grow breasts… I get first peek.
You’re welcome.
Hold it. That was a foul.
Nathan, you’ve got to get off his back.
Why don’t you get off my back, Whitey?
How would you like to call that a practice.
Whatever, man, that’s fine by me.
- Nathan!
- What?! Huh!
What the hell do you all want from me?
Just walk away, son.
Walk away.
Fight ball up top.
Very funny.
Hey, are you okay? Lucas said you had some trouble at practice yesterday.
Lucas needs to mind his own business.
We got a game coming up, that’s all. I just get a little intense.
Are you, uh, okay? You’re shaking, Nathan.
My heart’s racing too.
That’s what happens when I’m around you.
So your house tonight, right? Tutoring?
- Are you sure you’re okay?
- Yeah, I’m fine.
I just- I had a bad day yesterday.
- See you tonight.
- Yeah.
If you came here to lecture me or argue, I get enough of that at home with the wife.
I came here to talk about Nathan.
His behavior concerns me.
Really. You put Lucas on the team, give away his position,
kick him off the team bus 30 miles away from home,
and now you’re worried.
You forgot, uh, pressuring him and belittling him.
Of course, that happens at home, doesn’t it?
I remember when you came to me.
You were a scrawny freshman with a hell of a jump shot.
You loved the game.
What the hell happened along the way?
You happened.
There was always something for you to pick apart, something that wasn’t good enough.
But you are right. I did love the game.
- I simply despised the way you controlled it.
- Who’s controlling Nathan now?
You’d be ashamed if you learned to hate that person like you hate me.
I might be tough on him, Whitey.
But then I’m not the one who told him the sun wouldn’t rise if he lost his next game.
You really laid into Whitey yesterday.
He deserved it.
So Cove City’s pretty tough, eh?
They suck.
Listen man.
I know you’re under a lot of pressure from your dad.
Hey!
You don’t know anything about my dad, alright?
Maybe if you knocked out a shot every now and then I wouldn’t have to carry us out there.
All finished. Now it’s my turn.
Hey, hey, hey. Not so fast.
- Did you like it?
- Did I like it or did I read it?
The book’s about how a guy loses his integrity and gives into temptation.
Which is exactly what I see you doing tonight… with me.
Right.
Well, a deal’s a deal, right?
That’s right, baby. A deal is a deal.
Here you go.
Thank you… Gretchen and Henry.
Fake IDs. I used your yearbook photo.
- I didn’t know you could shoot pool.
- There’s a lot you don’t know about me.
Really?
Like what?
Like… I love it in the summer when there’s heat lightning at night.
And up until the fourth grade, I called squirrels squirrlers.
And I love beating boys at pool.
Oh my God. A smile. Is Lucas Scott actually having fun?
- I have fun.
- Sure you do.
Lucas, you’re like the most serious guy I’ve ever met.
Fine.
Does that make you happy?
A little.
Well, just as long as you don’t feel cheated.
You read a book,
I drink a beer. We’re even, right?
Wait, did you think this was the thing you have to do with me?
Well, yeah.
No. This isn‘t the thing.
This is just… drinks before the thing.
Bottoms up.
Nathan. Are you going to pace all night, or can we get started?
Are these all your brothers and sisters?
Yeah. I’m the youngest.
I don’t think my parents know what to do with the silence.
So a month ago, did you think we’d be alone in your bedroom?
Oh, but we’re not alone in my bedroom.
-  We have the forefathers with us.
- They can watch.
Nathan, can you just get serious for a minute?
Oh, I’m serious. Come here.
- My parents could come home.
- Come on…
Nathan, come on, stop it.
Come on…
- Don’t… Hey!
- What?
God…
I think you should go.
You’re kidding, right?
Haley…
Alright, Haley, I’m sorry. We can study, it’s fine.
I’d like you to go.
Unbelievable.
Don’t you love weird science?
Ah, the family jewels.
He doesn’t even have a license, Lisa.
Out of area?
Booty call?
Hey, this is Lucas’ cell phone. Please leave a message.
Where were we?
Where we were having fun.
I’m glad we did this.
Good.
So what’s your take on tattoos?
I don’t know…
depends.
Come here.
What do you think…
About…
this tattoo?
That tattoo is very, very… sexy.
Right answer.
Keith! Hey man.
You okay?
I’m perfect.
Have you been drinking?
Oh Keith. There is this girl.
Now I know how my hope and Aunt felt when I came rolling in…
You know, you had me worried sick, Luke?
Why don’t you go and sleep it off and...
we’ll deal with this tomorrow?
What are you doing, Dad? Still looking for your name in the box scores?
Hey. Knock it off and get serious. You’ve got a big game coming up.
And you think you’re gonna break my scoring record.
Come on, Tara Reid, you’re gonna be late.
What’s up?
Nothing.
What are you hiding?
Check that out.
Tell me that’s a joke.
No, no, no. Just, just… wipe it off, okay.
Keith, it’s a tattoo.
A tattoo.
- Of what?
- It’s an ancient symbol for fun.
Oh, for fun? Because I thought it was for freaking fool.
- Keith…
- Luke.
Your mom trusted me. She’s gone five days and now you scar yourself for life.
- It’s just a tattoo.
- It’s a tattoo. There is no just.
God. What were you thinking?
This is a bunch of crap. You’re out half the night, you’re drunk, and now you got a tattoo.
What, did you join the navy too?
You took advantage of me, Luke.
You’d have never would’ve pulled a stunt like this with your mom here.
What stunt?
You mean actually enjoying myself for once?
You said it yourself.
My mom’s not here. Is she?
Your ass is grounded.
Keith…
Bread and water.
Hard core grounded. Start now.
You know…
I expected more from you.
What did you do last night?
- Nothing, you?
- Nothing.
Actually I kinda made out with Brooke.
- What?
- While I was drunk.
Oh. Wow. Slow night for you. What happened.
Well, we went out as friends and things just kind of escalated.
Yeah. Sounds like.
You and Brooke Davis. Please.
- What, is that so strange?
- Yeah, it is.
You know, she’s different than people see?
You of all people should understand that.
I’ve been kissing Nathan.
If I told you not to do that anymore would you listen?
- Would you?
- Maybe.
- Probably not.
- Probably not. Yeah.
So what about Peyton?
- Yeah, you can kiss her if you want.
- I’m serious.
Look, I told her how I felt, alright? She doesn’t feel the same way.
Maybe she’s just not ready.
Nah. She just wants to be friends.
So are you and Brooke Davis like a thing now?
No. We went out. We had fun.
Alright, well, if that’s what you want. I mean, you deserve to be happy.
Yeah.
You too.
Hi, friend. Guess who I went out with last night. I’ll tell you. Lucas.
Definite  went out.
We met at a bar, shot some pool, had a few drinks.
- Lucas Scott?
- Yep.
You didn’t tell me he was such a good kisser.
I gotta go.
Hi…
So what do you think?
Uh, about what?
Long counter here, some retro books.
I don’t follow.
Deb’s Diner. The hottest little place in town.
Dan… I don’t want a diner. What’s this really about?
You tell me.
I told you. I’m simply trying to help Karen.
You hardly know the woman.
Well, that’s not true.
But for the sake of discussion, lets say you’re right.
Lets say I’m doing it to help you.
Me?
What do you feel when you see Lucas?
I mean it was different when we never saw him. But now...
- What do you want me to say?
- Anything. Something honest.
Okay, then how does this sound? I was a kid, I made a decision.
And I’m tired of you and everyone else holding it over my head every day of my life.
So if you’re running that little café so you can find absolution for me, forget it.
I don’t need it and I don’t want it.
What’s going on? You said you wanted to talk.
Do you think second chances are a lie?
Well, it depends on who you are dealing with, I guess.
Yeah…
How are things going with you and Nathan?
Not so great. I don’t know what he wants us to be.
Are we a couple? Are we just hanging out? Is it for sex because if it is…
If it is what?
That’s not enough for me.
Bad experience?
What, are you a virgin?
Yeah. So what if I am?
Good for you.
So what are you going to do?
Try and get some answers I guess.
Did Lucas tell you what happened between us?
Yeah. He just said that you weren’t ready for a relationship.
Did he tell you about Brooke?
That they went out? Yeah…
You okay with that?
He’s fair game.
Plus, she’s really not the dating kind, if you know what I mean.
Is connecting with someone really this complicated, or is it simple and we just make it worse?
For me its complicated.
You just make it worse.
Hey, I got you some tape.
For the tattoo. You gotta cover it for the game, right?
Thanks. I appreciate it.
Let me see it.
Geez, Luke. Where’d you get this thing? Some back alley in the Philippines?
You know, you can get Hepatitis, HIV from..
Does it hurt?
A little.
Well… we’ll get it checked before the game.
Keith, man, you worry too much.
I’ve got to worry once for myself and once for your mother.
Your arms are going to be dead for the game tonight.
Yeah. You wish.
No I don’t. I’d love for you to break my record, Nathan.
- I just don’t think you will.
- We’ll see about that.
Good news and bad news, Nate. Bad news is I have to be at the café
so I’m gonna miss your game. Good news is Haley can be there.
Whatever.
At least one of us will be there.
- Nathan!
- Not now, Haley.
Okay, after the game, can we get some food and talk?
Haley, I said not now, okay?
Why are you being like this?
Because I can, okay? That’s how it works. People are mean, life’s a bitch.
What is your problem?
What’s my problem? My problem’s on the other side of the wall.
And in five minutes, if I’m not perfect, they’re going to eat me alive.
That’s my problem.
That’s 38 points for Nathan Scott tonight, and we’re early in the fourth quarter.
He’s 5 points from breaking the all time high against Cove City,
set of course by He-Who-Won’t-Be-Named.
Another 4 pointer for Nathan and now he’s a basket away from the record.
Yeah, baby!
This is it.
No basket!
Oh, no basket! Nathan Scott is whistled for charge-
- He was moving at speed. What are you talking about?
- One! Two! Three! Easy, son.
- Time out!
- Keep your eyes on the game!
- Coach, you better watch your boy?
What’s he doing?
Nathan, I don’t care how many points you’ve got.
You keep this up, I’ll move you so far down the bench they’ll have to pump air into you.
Just give me the ball.
Alright, lets go fellas. Defense on three.
One! Two! Three! Defense!
You alright?
I will be 2 points from now.
Here we go, folks. This is it!
Luke waits for Nathan Scott to come free! He’s got 41 points.
Coach! Coach!
Easy, son.
You’re okay.
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
You collapsed during the game.
Nathan, how are you feeling?
I have to piss.
You were severely dehydrated.
We have you in these ice packs because you body temperature was very high.
Now, I need to ask you some questions about the supplements you’re taking.
Uh, Benzedrine, Mephedrine.
Anabolic steroids? Anadrol, Dianabol?
Okay.
What about speed? And uh, cocaine? Ecstasy?
Hey, Doc, he’s an athlete, not a junkie, okay?
And he’s also a kid.
True, but he’s my kid.
So how about you play a little more doctor and a little less detective?
Mr. Scott, could I speak with you?
Listen to me, son. You’re going to be fine, okay?
You’ve been hitting it a little hard lately, we’ll back a notch or two.
You’ll be as good as new.
Hell, the scouts won’t even remember this come to post season.
The early results tell me that your son is going to be fine, physically.
That’s great.
But they also tell me he’s taking some sort of amphetamine.
There’s got to be some kind of mistake.
Mr. Scott, these kids are under a lot of pressure to perform, and granted, it could be an isolated case,
but there could be a more serious problem.
Look Doc, I appreciate your concern, I really do. But I gotta tell you.
I know my son. And if he says he’s clean, he’s clean.
So if you label him an addict, you take away his future.
So unless you’ve got your results 100 percent accurate, you’re looking at a lawsuit you don’t want.
Now from where I stand, your job is to get him well.
I’ll do the rest.
Are we clear?
Hey. I was on my way to check on him, and then I realized you were here,
so I turned around and came back. You should go. How is he?
- Who?
- Nathan.
What about him?
I appreciate it, Keith. Thanks.
How are you doing, son?
He’s okay.
Where is he?
Hey.
I talked to Dan.
Nathan’s going to be fine.
You know why they made whiskey, Keith?
For the poor fool that wakes up after 35 years and discovers he’s a part of the problem.
Well, no more.
I’ll forfeit the damn games before I lose a boy to that.
I’ve got to be the sorriest son of a bitch on the planet.
Well, Karen left me to watch Luke.
And uh, he got drunk and then he got a tattoo.
Well, I take it back.
I tried to call you but you weren’t answering your phone.
Because I ran out of the café with nothing but my car keys and the fear that my son was dying.
Oh, and that’s my fault?
After Haley walked in… how long was that, Dan?
20 minutes after Nathan collapsed? A half hour, maybe?
My first concern was for Nathan. You’re overreacting.
Oh. Overreacting? That my son nearly died and my husband didn’t see fit to call?
Where is he, Dan? He could be anywhere. He could be unconscious.
Get a hold of yourself. The doctor said he’s out of harm’s way.
Well the doctor was wrong.
Because as long as you control him the way you do, he’ll be in harm’s way.
Ohhh… okay. Yeah, I get it. I’m to blame. It’s gotta be my fault.
Yeah.
Would you consider this, lady? If you weren’t off helping your little friend Karen and her café,
you might’ve been there for him like I was.
You smug son of a bitch.
- I want you out of this house.
- Deb…
I said get out!
- It’s been an emotional night…
- No, no, no, Dan. It’s been a night of clarity.
And it’s time for you to go.
It’s my house.
Fine, then I’ll go.
But either way, Nathan stays with me.
Don’t do this.
I’ll say it one more time, Dan.
Pack a bag and get out.
Or so help me God, I will stab you in your sleep.
And you better pray that my son is okay.
Do you really think Nathan would choose you over me?
Hey, its me.
I guess I’m just worried about you.
- I really hate the way we ended things.
- So do I.
Nobody answered the door.
They’re gone for the weekend.
How are you?
Not so good.
Can I...
I made a lot of mistakes, Haley.
Sometimes because of my dad,
sometimes by choice.
I just can’t do it anymore.
- It’s okay…
- No.
No, it’s not okay. I’m not okay.
I lived for tonight.
I was so scared.
I’m still terrified.
Then I saw you.
I promised myself that if I could just get up,
and walk over to you,
and tell you how much I need you,
and how much I want you,
that nothing else matters.
Peyton?
I heard about Nathan.
Yeah,
he’s gonna be okay.
So… what’s up?
Lucas, I made a mistake.
When you said you wanted to be with me, I got, I got scared, but...
Peyton…
But, the truth is, I want all the same things that you want, I do.
And I want them with you.
Okay, superstar, are you ready to score?
Hey…
we missed you after the game tonight.
Yeah. I just… I guess I just kind of got turned around.
Peyton…
Haley…
Can I stay with you for tonight?
What a frightening thing is the human,
a mass of gages and dials and registers.
And we can read only a few.
And those perhaps not accurately.
Synchro : Amariss
- www.foromfr.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net