Hey, lets move it lady.
Come on!
Haley.
- How long are we going to do this?
- Do what?
- Avoid each other.
- You tell me. You’re the one upset.
And you’re the one who lied to me.
I don’t know what to say to you, Luke.
Just explain to me why you were with Nathan. Huh?
I mean, considering the past few weeks and what he’s done…
I can’t.
You know how I feel about him, Haley.
Lucas, fine!
Yes. I know how you feel about him. But there is something you don’t know.
I promised him I’d tutor him if he left you alone.
What?
I’m doing it for you, Luke.
- So you and Peyton are history?
- Nah.
- I wouldn’t count on that.
- No?
Yeah. This is what she does. She freaks out, we break up;
a few days later, we make up.
So why put up with that?
Because a few days later, we make up.
Hey, ball.
Expect plenty more of that at the father/son game because we’re going to crush you guys.
Oh yeah?
You can expect more of that.
Bring it on.
I’m an idiot.
I know.
I’m sorry.
I miss hanging out with you, Hales.
Yeah. I miss hanging out with you too.
Listen. I appreciate everything you did for me.
I do, Haley, but- how about you let me handle the team from now on, okay?
Okay.
All right. So you can… stop tutoring Nathan now.
Um, no. I can’t.
- Haley.
- Lucas. I can’t. I promised him.
If I break that promise, I’m just as bad as... you think he is.
Hey, Lucas, I’m looking forward to see you play in the father/son game this year.
Good article about you and your pop.
Who would’ve known that Dan Scott’s basketball pedigree would be inherited
by his two sons, Nathan Scott and Lucas?
You’ve got to be kidding me.
That’s great, Dad. We’re all one big happy family now.
Watch it. I wonder what they’re paying this reporter to support his crack habit?
- How about some breakfast?
- I lost my appetite.
Dan, the boy exists. He’s on the team. It’s not exactly headline news.
No, Deb, apparently it is.
Well, how do you think Lucas and Karen feel about it?
Gosh, I don’t know. Maybe we should invite them over for breakfast and find out.
Alright, look. If you guys are going to argue, I’m out of here.
We’re not arguing and your breakfast is getting cold.
I’m just going to grab something at school with my brother.
You know, there is a chance that Lucas and Nathan can get along if their father encouraged it.
True. But there’s also a chance that hell can freeze over.
You’re not still mad at me, are you?
I’m not mad.
We’re just over.
Hey cutie. I saw your picture in the paper.
Personally, I didn’t think it did you justice.
- No?
- No.
Far too much clothing.
Hey, Lucas. That father verses son game’s coming up.
Considered who you want to play with.
- I figured I’d skip it.
- Oh, come on, son.
I know it’s hard, but it will be worse if you don’t play.
Besides, I thought you said you were through hiding from Dan.
I am.
Well, wouldn’t it be fun to dunk on him?
Here we go! Ravens, lets score!
Wait! Hold on, Peyton, you’ve got the arms wrong.
- It’s not brain surgery, Brooke.
- Okay, what’s with the attitude?
What’s with your life?
Seriously, aren’t you embarrassed that the most important thing in your world is some stupid cheer?
Look, I’m really sorry things didn’t work out with you and Nathan,
- but don’t go all Mariah on me, okay?
- You think this is about Nathan?
You’re not even close! You’re not even in the neighborhood of close!
- Okay, then, what’s wrong?
- What’s wrong is how… pointless all of this is.
- Stop saying that!
- No! Because it’s true.
What difference does it make if you sleep with a popular guy, or you go to the right party,
or you know the moves to some moronic cheer to do with some lame-ass game I could care less about!
- Hey. You’re not working today.
- Yeah, I have a favor to ask.
Uh, there’s this father/son charity basketball game.
Whitey says I’ve got to play, so… you interested?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Yeah, okay. Of course, I might be, you know, a little out of shape,
not to mention I… wasn’t worth a crap back in high school.
Well, it’s better for us, right?
Well. Why don’t you start coming to the court with us?
Hang with a member of the Scott basketball dynasty?
So how are you doing with that?
Well. What are you going to do?
- Sucks for my mom…
- Yeah. What about you?
Honestly… I can’t stand being connected to Nathan or Dan.
Hey, big brother!
I was getting some cardio in, ran out of water. You wanna help me out?
Yeah. Sure, why not?
So, uh, you wanna buy some charity tickets to the big father/son game?
Oh,  well, I, you know, could if I wasn’t playing in it.
Luke invited me.
Oh, great.
Well, try not to soil the Scott family name while you’re at it.
Yeah… that’s every day advice for you, huh?
Hey, kid.
Seems as though you have an obligation to the family name too.
Don’t blow it.
That article’s a lie.
You’re not my father and you never were.
You’re  right. It is a lie.
You should never have had the name in the first place.
Hey! Dan!
- You okay?
- Look! I have no responsibility to him or his name.
Just… Don’t let him get inside your head, okay?
You know what. I don’t plan on it. You know, as a matter of fact,
I think it’s about time I get out from under this guy completely.
What’s that supposed to mean?
Meaning I’m not gonna be a Scott anymore.
I’m gonna change my last name.
You’re late. I expected you this morning after that article in the paper.
I understand Lucas has asked Keith to play in the basketball game.
- Do you think that’s wise?
- Why not?
Well, Keith isn’t exactly a father.
You’re not the best father, either, Danny, and you’re playing.
What about Lucas?
You have to know this will be embarrassing for him.
Embarrassing for him?
What about embarrassing for you?
Wait a minute.
This isn’t about Lucas and Keith.
This is all about you, Danny…
and that feeling you get in the pit of your stomach when you see the son that you…
never claimed.
You were a great player.
Maybe the best I ever had.
But you can score a hundred points in this game,
and that feeling’s not going to go away.
It’ll be there until you acknowledge that Lucas is your son
and that you made a mistake.
You uncle Keith’s been working hard getting ready for the game.
He mentioned that you’re thinking of changing your last name?
I just don’t want people to read these stupid articles and think I played ball just because Dan did.
I don’t want you to have to read that stuff.
Well, you’re in the spotlight now.
The article’s come with the territory.
But I don’t want you to run away from that.
I’d rather you face your problems head on.
I just… figured it would make you happy if I took your name.
When I found out I was pregnant, Dan already had a basketball scholarship
and nothing was going to get in the way of that.
But then something strange happened.
Right before classes started, Dan changed his mind.
He said he’d finish the semester and… we’d get married.
So when I went into labor and you appeared,
the nurse asked for your name and I said it was Scott.
Keith was there,
and when the nurse brought you in she let him hold you.
I’ve known Keith my whole life,
and that’s the only time I’ve seen him cry.
Your father never showed up.
So to hell with him.
I don’t want his name.
Keith’s a Scott too, you know.
I’ve never been ashamed of you, Lucas, not for a second. Or your name.
Then I also never had to carry that name in this town the way you have,
so if you want to change it, you have my blessing.
But it’s just a name, Luke.
What you do with it is up to you.
Brooke!
Hey. Have you heard from Peyton?
Not since you two broke up and she went psycho on me in practice. Why?
Because she’s not in school.
And she won’t pick up at home or on her cell.
Well… maybe she’s out kicking the homeless.
A lot of smokers in this place.
I don’t really smoke.
I just figured since Nathan and I broke up, I’ve got room for a new bad habit.
Mind if I sit down?
She was quite a gal, your mother.
Yeah.
She used to lead cheers for my team, too.
And you’ve got her looks.
- I don’t really remember her.
- Oh, I do.
She was a wily one. Your old man didn’t stand a chance.
So what are you doing here? Making a reservation?
You better watch it!
No.
No. My wife, Camilla, is buried out here.
Right over behind those trees.
I couldn’t get in a word edgewise while she was alive so I come out here
and visit, tell her about things.
You think she’s listening?
Yeah. I know she’s listening.
I lost my wife just about the time your mother passed away.
That always make us weak and tough one.
They’re all tough.
Yeah.
The good news is you did better… and the bad news is better is a D.
Yeah. I guess I didn’t really give this one my best shot.
What’s  going on with you?
Well. You know me and Peyton broke up.
- Peyton and I.
- Oh. She broke up with you too?
Just… I didn’t know she was going to take it this hard.
She went off on Brooke at practice.
I’m kinda worried about her.
Well, maybe you should’ve worried more about her when you were together.
- I’m sorry, but come on, it’s true.
- No!
You don’t know the first thing about Peyton and I.
- Me and Peyton.
- Whatever.
Why do you do this?
If I were you, I’d get back out now.
Not until you tell me what’s going on.
Come on! Slow down, Peyton! Come on!
Slow the car down!
Peyton? Slow the car down.
She was driving to school to pick me up.
She was late, so she ran a red light.
It was one light at the wrong split second and it ended for her.
My mom ran one red light.
I run them all the time and nothing happens.
It’s not fair.
No it’s not.
You can get out now.
Or I can stay if you want.
No. You can’t.
- Hey, Keith.
- Hey.
Twice in a week. It’s got to be some kind of record.
Yeah, well, it’s this father/son thing.
- Yeah. How about a frostie?
- Nope, I’m in training.
- It’s just a game, Dan.
- No. It’s a public event.
I mean, what are people gonna think? Especially after that article?
Oh yeah. About that…
what in the hell is wrong with you telling Lucas he never deserved the name Scott?
- Well, he doesn’t.
- The hell he doesn’t.
- You fathered him, Dan.
- That’s right.
Which brings me to my original point. What do you think you’re doing playing in the basketball game?
I mean, whatever you think you are to Karen and her son, you’re not a husband. Or a father.
How much does a suit like that cost?
Because it’s gonna look like hell when I lay you out all over that greasy floor.
- Come on, big brother.
- That’s right. Big brother.
And no matter what you did on that basketball court a lifetime ago,
and no matter what you do now, I’ll always be your big brother.
So guess what, Danny boy? It was my name first. It’s Lucas’ name now.
And there’s nothing you can do about it.
Okay, Keith.
You know, you can be ashamed of me.
And you can be ashamed of Lucas.
But what makes YOU think we’re not just as ashamed of you? Huh?
Now get out of my shop.
Hi.
You never know who you’re going to see in the boys’ locker room these days.
Or what you’ll see.
I thought maybe we could talk.
Unless… you’re too busy.
No, sure. We can talk.
Still in denial?
About what?
Missing her.
It’s okay that you do.
What… are you my tutor or my shrink?
Whatever you need.
I treated Peyton pretty bad.
She had every right to walk away.
Okay, yeah, it was my fault. I screwed up.
I just wish I had another chance.
Nice work.
- That was the truth.
- No. On your practice exam. 81.
You know, it’s funny.
I think we’ve actually talked more than Peyton and I ever did.
Peyton and I… good job.
Yeah, you too.
Hey… are you coming to the game?
Um, well, it depends on how you do on your English exam.
Anything less than an 81, I’m staying home and watching The Office.
Alright.
Haley?
Yeah?
I know this hasn’t been easy for you.
I just wanted to say thanks.
Good luck.
My wife wouldn’t let me smoke in the house, so...
I got in the habit of coming up here to this bridge.
I’d offer you one, but I know you’re trying to cut down.
- How long have you been coaching?
- Too long.
- Do you ever wonder about it?
- What?
I mean, you’ve spent your whole life watching boy’s play a game.
Well, I’d prefer to think I was teaching them to play.
Yeah, sometimes I think about the conversations when I’m finished between me and my wife.
The holidays I missed because I was off coaching somewhere.
That’s when I come closest to thinking it was a mistake.
- Do you miss her?
- Every day.
Peyton, it’s hard to lose somebody.
I spent a lot of time searching for reasons or answers.
But you can’t find what’s not there.
It just happened.
So you gonna light that thing or what?
No. I used to love cigars but I haven’t smoked one since I lost Camilla.
I don’t even carry matches anymore.
I don’t guess I’ve been much help to you.
But  I do know one thing.
Your mother’s proud of you.
Take care of yourself, kiddo.
- Hey.
I really don’t want to be like this, Luke.
What is that?
This. Us skirting around each other. I mean, we’re friends.
You know, when you wanted to join the team,
I didn’t understand it and I told you that, but I supported you.
- I know.
- So… support me!
When I’m tutoring someone, and they get it,
and that light goes on, I feel good! I feel worthy.
The same way that you feel when you play basketball.
Besides, having things gotten better for you?
The team’s left you alone, the hazing’s stopped?
Yeah. So, that’s worth the risk for me.
What’s not worth the risk it us.
We’re friends and that is important to me.
You’re just tutoring him?
I am just tutoring him. That’s it.
Okay.
- Oh, game.
- I think I pulled a kidney.
- You alright?
- Yeah.
Yeah…
So you decide on the name thing yet?
Well, I downloaded the forms. But, uh… Mom’s still got to sign off on them.
Mind if I tell you what I think?
I think you just did.
Hey, I know I’m not your father, and, I’d never try to tell you what to do, but…
I just… wish you’d think about it.
I will…
and you know you don’t have to play if you don’t want to.
Oh. Why do you say that?
I know it puts you in a weird spot.
And Dan and Nathan are your family too, right?
As far as I’m concerned, you and your mom are my family.
As long as you’ll have me.
You know, Dan and I, we... we’ve never seen eye to eye. Even when we were kids.
And Nathan’s practically a stranger.
Besides,
I was honored that you asked me to play.
Good.
I was hoping you’d say that.
Listen. I’ve got to take off.
Talk to you later?
Si.
Take care, all right.
- Hey, Keith?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
How’s my boy?
Why?
Dad send you to spy on me? Where’s my drink?
You know, you’d think he organized this entire thing himself.
Just so he could get back on the court.
I know he’s been tough on you lately, Nate.
But I want you to know things are going to change around here.
I just wish he’d lay off, you know.
I wanna do good for him.
He just gets so worked up about this stuff.
Well, if you don’t want to play, don’t play.
He’ll get over it.
You know that’s a lie, Mom.
Hey.
I’ve been thinking about you.
Try a cold shower.
Sorry. You set yourself up for that one.
Yeah, I guess so.
How you doing?
Lets see.
I broke up with my boyfriend. My mom’s dead.
And my dad’s away on a job.
What’s your dad do?
Captains a drudging boat.
He’s only here for those forked anniversaries but this year, he sent his sympathies in an email.
I read your article.
I think it seemed like you guys are just one great, big, happy family.
Yeah. It’s kind of ironic, huh?
You know, I would gladly erase my dad if it would bring back your mom.
I wish I could change it for you.
Thank you.
I gotta go.
Hey, Peyton!
Don’t ruin it, okay?
Excited about your game tomorrow?
Truthfully? It’s like Christmas Eve.
And have you been naughty… or nice?
Have I been naughty? Well, which would you prefer?
Honey. I know this is important to you and I know that Nathan is talented but…
I think you push him too hard sometimes.
I worry that he won’t enjoy it anymore.
Oh, he enjoys it. If he doesn’t, he’ll regret it when it’s gone.
Do you?
Every day.
There’s nothing like it, Deb.
Walking into the arena, hearing the cheers of a sellout crowd,
knowing it’s going to be your night.
And for an hour or two, the world is yours
and there’s nothing they can do to stop it.
I wish I would’ve known you then. I wish you could’ve been there.
No decisions to make, cars to sell, bills to pay.
Just the game.
And I was good.
It’s the best it ever was for me.
Better than your life now?
Better than... knowing your son?
Or me?
It was different.
What do you call that?
Love.
What do you want, Nathan?
It’s what I don’t want.
I don’t want this for us.
Maybe you should’ve thought of that sooner.
Yeah, I know.
I’ve been thinking about how we were when we started going out.
Like that day at Rhysfield Beach.
The nights here in your room.
We haven’t been that way in a long time.
We could be.
Come on, Peyton. I’ve been thinking about you.
I know you’ve been thinking about me.
I’ve actually had a lot going on lately.
Yeah, me too.
My dad’s been going crazy about this father/son game and my mom…
it’s like ever since she came back she’s been wanting to hang out.
I really can’t hear this right now.
Alright. Well, how about you come to the game?
Maybe we could hang out afterwards.
I miss you, Peyton.
I’ll see you there.
Catch up to you later man.
- Got a sec?
- Hey, yeah, what’s up?
Check that out.
An 84! That’s so great.
Yeah, hey, congratulations!
Hey! Dan the man, are you going to carry us tonight or what?
You know it, Bruce. I’ll carry the team and Keith can carry my jock.
- Keith, it’s good to see you man.
- You too, Bruce.
I didn’t know you had a son that played ball too.
Well, actually I’m just a stand-in.
One of the boys doesn’t have a father.
Luke! Lucas!
Hey, Scott!
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
And welcome to the Tree Hill Ravens’ father and son charity basketball game.
Tonight the fathers battle the sons and the winner gets bragging rights.
Coming soon tonight, Ravens son league MVP Nathan Scott.
And for the father’s, the all-time even scorer in the history of Tree Hill,
and state championship runnerup, put your hands together for Dan Scott!
Sounds like the old man got a louder applause than you did.
Are you sure your hearing aid’s not turned up too loud?
Under a minute remaining now and the Ravens’ sons are putting on a show.
They’ve made a mockery out of this one.
28 point lead and they’re running it in on the fathers…
Lucas Scott spins the ball on his finger… over to Hamilton…
- Hamilton disgraces his father.
- Don’t try that crap with me, Nate.
Nathan Scott tries… scores and is left with an even 30 points at halftime.
You guys suck out there. It’s embarrassing.
For you, maybe.
Come on… you play house with a girl I get pregnant in high school and I’m supposed to be embarrassed?
It’s embarrassing because we’re old men, Dan, playing horribly
- and that’s the way it’s supposed to be.
- Not for me.
- Enemy approaching.
- That’s right, enemy approaching.
Are you going to bring your best game or what?
- You’re down by thirty, Dad.
- No, I’m talking to you.
You bring your best game, I’ll bring mine, and then we’ll see.
- We’ll see what?
- We’ll see who’s the best.
Or maybe you’d rather not know.
- Hey. Come on, relax, little brother.
- This isn’t your place, Keith.
Well, it’s not your place either, Dan.
It’s their game now. We should be proud they’re so good.
Like you had anything to do with it.
You walk away, Danny.
Lets see what you got.
Any of you give me your best game and...
I’m gonna hurt you.
Hey, you’re doing fine.
- Lucas. Luke. Are you mad at me? What’s going on?
- I don’t want to talk about it right now.
Okay, can you just tell me what I did, please?
- I saw you with him.
- Who Nathan?
God, he got a good grade on that math quiz. It was nothing.
I want to believe you, Haley. I do.
- But I don’t think you’re telling the truth.
- I’m am telling the truth Lucas. There’s nothing going on.
Nice bracelet.
Well folks, an impressive showing for Dan Scott. The kids are just too much.
What do you say we make this interesting?
Lets make the score 0-0, and the next basket wins.
Alright. Give me the ball.
Alright. Lets go, fellas. Ravens on three. One, two, three! Ravens.
The Ravens’ sons have the ball, and the next basket wins.
Game over, Dad.
Nathan Scott to the tape. He catches the ball in the wing. He rides to the- holy crap!
Lets hope the young man’s okay.
You okay?
I couldn’t give you the winning bucket, Nathan.
- Beat them?
- Yeah.
But I want to do it myself.
Well, good news, folks. Nathan seems to be okay.
And the Ravens sons still have a crack at it…
Lucas Scott hands the ball to Nathan.
He drives- ooh! He drops the ball. It’s moving.
That will create a turnover. The fathers have a crack at it.
Looks like its payback time.
That was a sloppy turnover, Nathan. That’s not like you.
- That’s because it was on purpose.
- On purpose? Why?
Because you don’t deserve my best game, Dad.
Look. I could’ve beat you. You know it and I know it.
You know, if you want to mess with that, go ahead. I’ll give it to you.
You didn’t beat me, Dad.
You never will.
Good game.
What? Are you kidding me? I was by far the worst one out there.
And that includes old Mr. Budieres and his wooden leg.
Oh, Keith, you know it’s never about basketball.
And just so you know…
what you did for Nathan,
what you’ve done for me…
well, lets just say I was proud to have you as my dad for the night.
You know, I’ve been thinking about what you said about the Scott name, and...
I think I’ll keep it. I just hope I can wear it as well as you.
Thanks.
Hey.
I’m glad you came.
I knew you would.
I want you to know thing’s are going to be different for us.
Did you know that my mom died tonight?
Seven years ago?
You didn’t know because you never asked.
I didn’t come here for you tonight.
Why’d you come?
John Steinbeck once wrote
“It seems to me that if you or I must choose
between two courses of thought or action,
we should remember our dying
and try so to live
that our death brings no pleasure on the world."
Synchro : Amariss
- www.foromfr.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net