Come on baby.
We need some music.
Peyton!
Sorry...
Where the hell are we?
Miles from normal.
What is she doing here?
You invited her!
Ow!
- Bail!
Nice. What's next?
- Uh, you pick.
- Alright.
Could this night get any freakier?
Nathan with Lucas.
Haley and Peyton?
What the hell is going on?
Hey stranger.
No stranger than you.
- Did you get my message last night?
- Nah. I was at the library late. Midterms.
- Yours or Nathan's?
- Both, actually.
- Well. Good luck with that.
- Luke.
You're cool with this, right? I mean, last week, when you said you didn't trust me...
I know. I didn't mean that. Alright? I meant I don't trust Nathan.
Hey, you got a second?
Speaking of...
So last week... sucked.
I just... wanted to say thanks.
- Oh, you made me a mix?
- Just trying to square my karma.
Uh-huh. Does this mean we're dating?
Listen, you've got a long bus ride tonight and I had some free time.
Don't read too much into it.
Haley!
- Hey!
- Hey.
- Coming to the game tonight?
- Um... I don't know.
You should come. We always beat the crap out of the Pickerington Hicks.
- They're called the Hicks?
- Well no. But they should be.
The place is all pickup trucks and mulch.
It's definitely worth the road trip.
I'll look for you.
Okay.
Dan! We should get going.
What is wrong with these people? Putting an SPL dinner on a game night?
Honey, it's once a year. We'll go, we'll enjoy a nice, adult evening downtown.
And tomorrow you can pour over the box scores.
I still don't understand why we booked a room. It's only a thirty minute drive.
Because you and your wife are in need of some good, old fashioned alone time.
I like the sound of that.
Well Nathan's got his cell. I can keep tabs on the game from dinner.
Dan, why don't we spend 48 hours without basketball and see where we wind up?
- Okay?
- Sure.
Thank you.
Okay.
What does this dress say to you?
Uh... beware of crazy ladies who talk to dresses.
No, come on. Really. I need your help.
Single and successful or married to her work?
- Is this for that justice league thing?
- Small business league.
And yes. It's one of the few times a year I get to dress up and I'd like to look nice.
Well, is Keith still going as your date?
He's not a date. We're just going together.
Why would you say that?
You guys hang out a lot. You get along well...
Yeah, well I get along with the guy who delivers our water.
That doesn't mean I'm gonna date him.
Yeah, but the guy who delivers our water is not Keith.
Where is this coming from?
Well, you know I've been thinking, you know, that you're not exactly old, Mom.
Thanks... I think.
I'm just saying that I'd be all right with it, you know...
if that's what you're worried about.
Well, thank you, Cupid. Now, help with the dresses, please.
- Black, I guess.
- Hmm. Black it is.
Keith didn't say something to you, did he?
Oh, you mean about the date that you two aren't going on tonight?
Not a word...
Good luck with your game.
Yeah, you too, Mom.
Safe yet?
No hostile tone, no bitter complaints,
no yelling at your best friend because you broke up with your jerk of a boyfriend?
Oh my god, a smile!
Alright. I was a mess last week. I'm sorry.
Apology accepted! A-P-O. L-O-G. Y?
Because I love you. Get your skinny ass up and lets go beat the pirates.
- What are you doing?
- What? It's a web cam. It's what they're for.
Come on.
Overweight.
- Now we're even.
- You're dead!
Dead!
Alright! Knock it off.
This is our first away game.
For those of you who are unfamiliar,
you sit there with your mouths shut and focus.
I'll choose the music.
Tonight's theme is defense.
Lets roll!
Good evening, ladies and gentleman, from the stinks of Pickerington
where the pirates always suck and the livestock is nervous,
I'm Mouth McFadden and sitting in with me at tonight's away game is Haley James.
Haley,  how do you see tonight's match up?
I'd rather not be associated with your lunacy, Mouth.
Oh, see, Lucas looks even hotter in blue. You should totally hook up with him.
- Stop it.
- What?
At the very least you're due for a little rebound action unless you're still into Nathan.
I'm not.
Alright. Since you're my pal you can have a courtesy hold on Lucas for the weekend,
- but after that he's fair game.
- He's already fair game, thanks.
So what's the story with that one anyway?
She's tutoring Nathan... supposedly.
And  hanging out with Lucas.
Right... we're supposed to believe she's just friends with both of them?
Did you see that?
- What?
- Nathan just gave her the nod.
- What nod?
- The “lets hook up after the game” nod.
Wanna know what I think? I think Nathan likes tutor girl.
But I think tutor girl likes Lucas. And I know I like Lucas.
And I don't know who the hell you like anymore.
This is all turning into one big love...
rectangle plus one, whatever that is.
So as you've heard Ravens have the big lead early in the second quarter.
Ooh. And that's a foul by Nathan Scott.
Hey. Why don't you try putting your hands up on defense, alright?
- Why don't you try not getting beat?
- Why don't I just beat your ass?
Moron...
Keep it up, punk.
Ball in!
Hey, you gonna talk or you gonna play, Daddy's boy?
Hey, Haley's looking pretty fine tonight, right? Can't wait to get with that.
Hey. So I saw Nathan in the shower...
yeah, no wonder you broke up with him.
You two! You're out of here!
You're throwing them both out of the game?
I got to, Coach. I got things rolling.
They're on the same team!
Ow! Pain!
Nathan Scott! Lucas Scott! On your feet!
Congratulations, boys.
In all my years of coaching, this has got to be a low point.
That little stunt you pulled almost cost us our undefeated record.
I don't give diddlee-squat about your issues with your daddy or your girlfriends.
As far as I'm concerned, you can hate each other until hell freezes over.
But if you're going to play on my team,
you're gonna learn how to work together.
I can't see that happening, Whitey?
Yeah? Well you've got thirty-some-odd miles to figure it out.
They can't just leave us here.
Nice work, idiot.
This is great. This is friggin' great.
- Calm down.
- You calm down, man.
My phone's on that bus. My wallet's on that bus.
Yeah, my wallet too!
So what the hell do we do now?
We start walking.
Ow, that's too tight.
- There. How's that?
- Too loose.
Ow, that's too tight.
So you're in college, right?
Junior.
Oh... you know, I love college guys.
Two more years, you'll be a doctor.
Uh, not exactly.
So tell me, Doctor College Boy.
If you wanted to give me something for the pain, you could, right?
Well, the team doctor would have to...
I could maybe do that.
Wait. You're not a cop, are you?
No.
Well, and one for tomorrow...
please.
Okay, here's the thing. Those are really strong painkillers.
So just take, like, a half of one. Every twelve hours.
Oops! All gone!
We wouldn't be out here if you never joined the team.
No. We wouldn't be out here if you weren't such a jackass about me joining the team.
Why do you want my life so bad anyway, man?
Dude, don't flatter yourself, alright? You're about the last person I want to trade places with.
Oh yeah? Well all I know is you came out nowhere and started grabbing everything you could from me.
- My game, my girl...
- What about you, huh?
I bet your grades sucked before you met me. But I didn't see you going to Haley for help then.
Who said what me and Haley's got's is about grades.
Ravens! Hey Ravens!
Want a ride?
I wouldn't take that ride if I was you.
You're not me.
You never will be.
Two little Ravens for the price of one.
Get in or the superstar dies.
What are you still doing here?
I'm thinking of transferring.
What's your excuse?
Brooke. She's been in there forever.
Peyton!
Oh boy.
Hi.
This is my best friend in the whole wide world. Don't you think she's pretty?
What is this?
She found some pills... on the floor.
She'll be fine. Just uh, let her sleep it off.
Hey! Ooh, call me!
We  should totally hang out more. What is your name?
Haley...
Yeah. I don't like that name. Lets call you... Brooke!
Hi friend!
Thanks.
Sure. I'll see you guys later.
- Where's your ride?
- Oh. I'm going to take the last fan bus back.
It just left.
That's perfect. Brookie can come with us!
Yeah, she named me Brooke.
Peyton, can she come? Please? Peyton, please!
Just don't touch the stereo. Or we'll have a problem.
Road trip.
We're going on a road trip. We're going on a road trip.
Alright. This is my stop. Thanks for the ride, fellas.
This one's funny, Thing. Lets kill him last.
Wait. Your name is Thing?
That's right. Thing.
And I'm Thing One.
Okay, wait. Let me guess.
Thing Two.
Thing Three. Because I'm the third.
Whoa. Dude...
Get your clothes off, boys. You're going shopping.
Oh, what do you know? We finally got the center aisle this year.
Guy must've thought I said Dan Scott.
No. Dan's table has one spot for Dan and five for his ego.
Well, well, well. Isn't this cozy?
Hey Karen.
Hi.
Hi Deb...
Dan.
- Hemorrhoid ointment.
- Dude, this is total crap.
These guys are morons, not killers. I bet it's not even a real gun.
Lets just play the game, get our clothes, and get home.
Okay. Ah, we need two bottles of spring feminine cleansers.
Oh, great. A pair of douche bags.
A case of beer and we're out of here.
What? How are we going to pull that off?
Would you card us?
I didn't think so.
Brooke! Come on...
Don't you two like the same guys? Or guy, or something?
I'm just tutoring him, that's all.
So you're not into him? Because he seems to be into you.
He gave her the nod!
Just be careful.
- Well, what about you and Lucas?
- What about us?
Oh, come on. Tortured artist meets tortured athlete? Talk about your obvious attraction.
- I hear birds.
- Unbelievable!
Brooke, did you not think to put gas in the car?
Answer the question, Brooke.
Why are we stopping?
- Sweet. They scored the brew.
- Where's the porn?
Hey. You had your fun. Now give us back our clothes.
Yeah, man, I'm done with these clowns. Hey, lets go somewhere and get wasted.
- With no porno mags?
- They didn't have Playgirl.
- Go back inside and get some hardcore.
- Wait! Shut up! Listen!
- Come on, roll, roll, roll.
- Go, roll!
Come on, lets go, lets go, lets go.
Move it! Come on! Lets go!
- Oh, yeah. Yeah, baby!
- Yeah, yeah, right. Alright. Yahoo!
Yeah, enough's enough. Give us our clothes.
Don't they say please in the suburbs?
He said give us our clothes, you hick.
- Can't you steal a fake gun in the suburbs?
- That's great. It's a starter pistol.
- I knew this thing was fake.
- Yeah, but our fists are real.
Look. We'll give you guys your clothes back. We'll even give one of you a ride home.
Yeah. What do you mean by one of us?
The game is Gladiator.
Basically, you guys beat the hell out of each other for our amusement.
The one left standing gets his clothes and a ride to a phone.
The loser... well he loses.
Let the games begin.
Okay, the game isn't called two punks staring at each other.
It's called Gladiator. Get to it.
Alright, you can screw yourself. Because there's no way in hell that the two of us are going to fight.
Or maybe we are.
This is great. Not only do I get to kick your ass but you get 30 miles to think about it.
What the hell are you doing, man? We should be fighting them.
- You want it?
- Yeah.
Wait, wait, wait!
You okay?
Yeah.
Pickerington morons.
- Give us the keys.
- Give us our clothes.
Fine.
You guys wanna play games, huh? I've got a little game for you.
It's called keys for clothes. You give us a piece of our clothes, we'll give you a key.
- No deal.
- Fine. We were walking anyways.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- We'll deal.
- Forget it. I want to walk home.
- It's dark.
Man, seriously.
Fine. Give him his sweats.
- That's worth a house key.
- Hey, keep them coming.
There's still no signal. Who lives like this?
Pop the trunk, will you?
Peyton, don't listen to it. It might be a trick.
Yeah, it's empty.
I saw a gas station a few miles back. If I'm not back in an hour, tell my mom I loved her?
-  Don't you mean Nathan?
- I'll go with you.
What about me?
I could suffocate in here.
- Guys!
- You did crack a window, right?
Come on! I'm scared! Please! Come on, you guys.
Don't go! Someone will come!
Scott Motor Company's been reaching a lead in new car sales for the past six years.
Pretty soon we'll be the top dealership in North Carolina.
So you two are in business together?
Uh, no. I own the company. Keith runs a garage.
I fix the junk that he sells.
Alright. Lets give credit where credit's due.
Big brother here has been tinking with cars for years. If it wasn't for his influence and...
lack of initiative, I may never have been able to realize my dream.
Hmm. Was it really my influence, Dan?
Because I thought it was Deb's money that bankrolled your dream.
True. Deb's father took a leap of faith with me.
Of course, I returned his investment ten-fold.
And every good business man knows it's a long road from seed money...
- To profit.
- To profits, exactly.
Amen to that.
So Keith. You talk about being a self-made man but... self-made into what?
Excuse me.
Last key. You got one thing left.
Give us the car key and we'll give you the shirt.
I can live without my shirt.
- Oh man, no!
- Have fun walking.
Just find the key... we're gonna kill those guys.
What did you mean before?
About Nathan when you said be careful?
I just know him, that's all.
Said the ex-girlfriend.
Look, we were crazy with drama but I'm over it.
He's not a complete waste. He just- he's really threatened by Lucas.
It could all just be a big mind game. That's how he works.
Do you like him?
I was- talk about stuff, you know what I mean?
- Like what?
- Like school or... his dad.
Oh. Dan. Danny sure did a number on his boy, right?
Yeah. Both of them.
So you didn't answer my question.
Do you like him?
It doesn't matter. I mean, that... it would be too weird around Lucas.
That's his problem. You've got a life to live too.
It just seems kind of selfish.
Why? Did he ask you if he could go out with me?
Did he ask you out?
No.
That's not the point. No. He wouldn't ask permission. So why should you?
Would you say yes if he asked you out?
It depends.
What song is playing... am I in a mood...
is he smiling when he asks or is he doing that goofy brooding thing he does?
Oh, you know I think he's definitely doing the broody thing.
He does that all the time!
It's strange. Just...
the night away from school. It feels like you and I actually live on the same planet.
Life plays trick on you like that.
Can I bankroll another drink for you?
I'm sorry about that.
I shouldn't have dragged you into it.
Sometimes my little brother has a way of getting to me...
- He has a gift.
- Yeah.
You know, you and Karen really go nicely together.
I don't think she sees me that way.
How do you see her?
She's amazing. She's strong, she's beautiful,
and, you know, she's a great mother to Lucas.
- So...
- A relationship would just complicate things.
What about you, Deb?
Tonight was just part of the course with him.
And, I know it's none of my business but why are you...
Why do I stay with him.
Yeah...
It's okay.
Believe it or not, some days he's the man I fell in love with and other days...
I don't know.
Besides, if you've got Lucas to consider, I've certainly got Nathan.
Come on. Lets go rescue Karen.
Yeah.
- Alright, it's a blue key chain.
- Dude, look over here moron. Is that blue?
Are you color blind?
- I can't believe you sucker punched me.
- I had to. It got us outta there, didn't it?
Here.
So what's your master plan, genius? Huh? You gonna hotwire the car?
Actually, we're not gonna have to.
Those idiots are gonna flip out when they find a key chain with no car key.
- Great!
- And no phone. What are we going to do?
So we'll get the car, we'll drive into town, we'll find a phone, and we'll ditch it.
Wait, what if they report it stolen?
Well I kinda think that the cops got the license plate number earlier, don't you?
Yes, but they didn't see who was driving that car.
I mean, think about it, if they pull us over they can pin everything on us.
What if we sit here and we talk about it all night, huh?
Got any better ideas?
- I'll drive.
- No. I'll drive.
Whoa, whoa!
Pickerington sucks!
Oh yeah, oh! They aren't going anywhere. Lets go get them, boys!
- Bail.
- Bail!
- We're gonna pluck you, Ravens!
- Hey, I've still got your shirt!
Shut up! They can run but they can't hide!
- Oh yes!
- So what are you doing?
Um...here, hold this.
- Or you'll stab me?
- A girl can't be too safe.
Here, try and get that gas cap open, will you?
- Does this really work?
- We are about to find out.
Had a lot of practice?
At sucking gas. What did you think I meant?
You wanna do it?
Watch out for the golf ball.
- Oh, yeah.
- Are you kidding?
Dude, who knew you were like the 4th Charlie's Angel?
Oh Ravens! Come out and play
Still out there.
They'll get bored eventually.
So that was a pretty good move with the car keys.
Yeah. It doesn't change the fact that my dad's gonna kill me for getting kicked out of that game.
You should consider yourself lucky sometimes.
Lucking out of a dad?
At least this one.
I remember this one summer, I was playing little league baseball
and I was the pitcher and my dad was the coach.
Anyway, this kid Billy Lyons, he was a great hitter.
Everything he hit was a homerun.
So, you know, he got up to the plate and there was nobody on base so I just walked him.
Four straight pitches, nothing even close to a strike.
So my dad calls a timeout, comes to the mound, and I'm thinking he's gonna say
like, Smart move or Good thinking son, something like that.
But instead... instead he grabs me by the arm,
and he kicks me in the ass as hard as he can.
I mean, he literally took me by the arm so that I wouldn't like, go flying,
he kicked me so hard.
Then he brought Stevie Planking into pitch, sat me on the bench,
never mentioned it again.
- That sucks.
- Yeah.
So just think about that the next time you're feeling sorry for yourself.
I haven't heard from you, Nathan. I'm starting to get nervous.
Uh... just call and leave your stats on my phone as soon as you get this.
You okay?
- Yup. Just a little bit hammered.
- Sorry, Karen. It was my fault.
What?
I thought we said no basketball.
What do you want from me, Deb? You leave me here with Karen and these two?
How you doing, boozy?
Alright, you know what? I'm ready to go.
Oh, there, see. Your ride's leaving.
I mean, she may not be much of a date but at least she's a reliable designated driver.
Dan, that's enough.
You know, maybe you oughtta spend a little less time
worrying about my relationship and a little more time paying attention to your own.
If you call chasing after my leftovers a relationship.
- Keith! Keith! It's not worth it.
- Come on!
Keith! Come on, come on. Please? Lets just go, alright?
Okay, I'm fine.
- It was a joke.
- Come on, please.
Man, it's been like, what? Twenty minutes?
Think they're coming back?
What?
Thing, Thing One, and Thing Three.
Well, yeah man, he was the third.
Yeah.
Hey. What are we doing hiding from these idiots anyway, huh?
Look, I can hold my own.
And I know that you could throw a pretty damn good punch.
I say lets take these fools on.
Alright. I'm in for that.
Are you gonna stay down here all night?
I made a call.
Nathan got thrown out of the game tonight for fighting with Lucas.
Fighting with his brother.
Hmm. I wonder where he gets that from?
His phone's turned off. No one's answering at home.
But he's okay?
I'm sorry about tonight, Deb.
- I don't know how things got so out of hand.
- Things didn't get out of hand, Dan. You did.
- He threw the first punch.
- You provoked him.
Nathan's prospects took a huge blow tonight. Can we just focus on him?
That's the wrong answer, Dan.
And if you don't know that, I'm not sure I know you anymore.
Well that's a two way street.
I'm gonna go upstairs and pack.
We should go home.
He cares about you, you know?
Yeah.
We need some music.
Peyton!
Sorry...
Where the hell are we?
Miles from normal.
What is she doing here?
You invited her!
Ow!
I cannot believe I let him get to me.
So did I.
I guess we both should know better by now.
Yeah, but even so...
you should be able to count on me.
It's like I can see the guy that I am in my head and I can see the guy that I want to be
and they're just... it's not the same.
That's okay, Keith.
I like who you are.
And I do count on you. More than you know.
Can I tell you a secret?
Sure.
Lucas called tonight a date for us.
And for a while, I pretended that it was.
And it felt good.
Can I tell you a secret?
Sure. Go ahead.
I pretended that too.
I love you.
Always have.
Nice. What's next?
- Uh, you pick.
- Alright.
This is so tragic. You two don't actually think you're going to be friends tomorrow, do you?
So this Haley thing...
you know, for some reason she feels like you're not full of crap.
- Don't take advantage of that.
- I'm not going to.
I know you're not. Because if you do, you're going to live to regret it.
Bring it on.
Hey, listen.
Look, man, you didn't have to get in that car when those guys grabbed me.
Especially after you warned me not to.
Right, whatever.
You know the way I see it, I mean, if they would've taken you out,
who the hell else am I gonna have to fight with, right?
Same person I have.
Car.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Lets do it.
Haley and Peyton.
Oh my Gosh. Nathan with Lucas?
As happens sometimes a moment settled...
and hovered and remained...
for much more than a moment.
And sound stopped...
and movement stopped...
for much, much more than a moment.
And then the moment was gone.
Synchro : Amariss
- www.foromfr.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net