And to another fine year of trading.
Hear, hear!
Truly, the medical supplies
you have given to us
over the past several years have made an
immeasurable difference to our people.
Not to mention your warning last harvest
that the Wraith were nearby.
You saved many lives.
Well, you know.
My favorite missions are
to do our trading.
And I've said that, I can prove it.
I'm not just saying...
You don't need to prove it.
You know, actually,
we got to get going.
So soon?
- Yeah, so soon?
- We were hoping that
you could stay...
Well, I...
I guess we could stay a little longer.
I hate to...
no, never mind.
- What is it?
- Well, I wouldn't dream of imposing...
you've been so generous
to our people already...
- What's the problem?
- Our sister.
She is in great need of your help.
- I didn't even know you had a sister.
- We do indeed.
And I imagine
she's as beautiful as you two.
Even more so.
- And she's in great need of guidance.
- Guidance. That I can do.
You are most generous.
Excuse us for one moment.
I'll get her.
- Dibs.
- What?
- I'm calling dibs on the third sister.
- You can't call dibs.
Look, we both know that Flora
and Mardola have been suckered in
by the whole cliche-heroic thing
you've got going,
but maybe this other sister, maybe
her taste in men will run more to the...
Geeky?
I was going to say "cerebral,"
but who knows. Maybe we'll hit it off.
I don't need your love life
screwing up our trade relations.
I'll try not to break her heart,
but no promises.
These are the men
I was telling you about.
Gentlemen,
this is our sister...
Harmony.
Super.
The Projet-SG & SG-66 Teams
present:
Season 4 Episode 14
Harmony (v. 1.0)
Transcription by:
SadGeezer.com
Timing by:
Golgi, Linwelin, Obusco, Ricana.
www.projet-sg.net
www.seriestele.net
As you know, our mother and
queen passed at the beginning
of this lunar cycle.
A secret, sacred ceremony was held
to determine which of her three
daughters would succeed her.
It was determined that Harmony
shall be the new queen.
Really?
Well, congrats.
Before she is crowned,
all future queens must perform
a time-honored rite of passage.
A rite of passage
normally performed alone.
It is not written one way or another.
And Harmony is so young.
- It concerns me greatly.
- I can do it.
You are very brave...
but the trail is difficult.
It would bring me great comfort to know
that you had someone
looking out for you.
What kind of rite of passage
are we talking about here?
Deep in the forest lies the ruins
of the great temple of Laros.
Every queen must take a pilgrimage
before the end of the first lunar cycle
of their selection.
Once there, she must meditate
on the journey that lies ahead of her
and pray to be endowed
with the knowledge and power
to govern her people.
How deep in the forest?
No more than a day's trek.
I see.
Yes. No.
We are very honored,
but why don't you just have
a couple of your own guards escort her?
Although it is not written so,
our people will expect their new queen
to have completed the journey
on her own.
So you don't want her to be alone,
but you don't want anyone to know
- she's getting help.
- Precisely.
Right. We'd love to lend a hand, but...
Our peoples have enjoyed
such a fruitful alliance.
Yeah...
One that has greatly benefited
both parties.
Right...
I'd hate to think that one of us
would put that in jeopardy
over a simple day's walk in the forest.
When do we leave?
I must confess...
I'm quite looking forward to this.
I rarely get to leave
the confines of the castle,
although I've had much training
in forest survival.
Oh, you have, have you?
Oh, yes.
I have completed three sessions
with Nolar Lumsbred.
He is one of the greatest hunters
amongst my people.
Three whole sessions?
With the Nolar Lumsbred?
They were all I needed.
I am a quick learner.
I'll bet you are.
Tell me,
which one of you
is the superior officer?
You mean who outranks who?
Yes.
I'm a civilian, I don't have a rank,
but basically, we're equals.
Technically, I'm in charge.
I thought so.
You have all the makings
of an excellent leader, John.
Well, thank you.
- You going to eat your powerbar?
- Yes, Rodney.
I told you, you shouldn't have
eaten yours so early in the day.
I'm starving.
Usually Flora feeds us some sort
of food when we visit.
- Come on, you hardly ever eat yours.
- No, Rodney.
Well, will you give it to me later
when you decide not to eat it?
You allow him
to question you so incessantly?
I guess I'm just used to it by now.
Would it not be easier to beat him?
We don't beat people where we come from.
Why not?
Well, we find it's not very effective
in the long run...
unfortunately.
Really?
You are a truly gentle leader, John.
I admire that.
Thank you, Harmony.
There's supposed to be
a rope bridge here.
- Maybe you're reading the map wrong.
- No, I think it's straight forward.
How old is this map?
It has been passed down from
too many generations to know for sure.
Okay, guess that bridge doesn't exist.
You two stay put.
I'm going to try to find
a safe way across the river.
Don't worry, I'll be right back.
Where'd you find that?
John's bag.
It's not yours.
- I'm hungry.
- You can't just take it like that.
- When I'm hungry, I eat.
- What's gonna happen
- when Sheppard finds out?
- Well, he's not going to know, is he?
He is, I'm gonna tell him.
- I wouldn't do that if I were you.
- Yeah, or what?
- I'm the queen.
- Not yet, you're not, little sister.
Trust me, you don't
want to be on my bad side.
Right? And what are you going to do?
Have me beaten?
All right, princess, just hand it over.
See, now, you're in trouble. You just
wait till Sheppard gets back here...
- He's gonna...
- I think I found a place for us to...
Is that my powerbar?
- She stole it.
- I did not!
What? You so did! Tell him!
I would never do such a thing!
The second you were gone,
she went into your bag.
You are a liar!
- You are a lying liar!
- Please, who are you going to believe?
Well, if she stole it, Rodney,
how come you've got the wrapper?
Well, b... I was trying to take it
back from her,
and then she wolfs it down
and hands me the wrapper.
Really?
Okay, you better come clean, brat.
It's okay, sweetie.
Sometimes... he makes me cry, too.
All right, we need to get going here.
All right? I found a path.
Can I navigate from the map?
Sure,
as soon as we get back on the path.
Now...
we go...
Right.
Correct.
- What was that?
- That's probably the beast.
Sorry, the what now?
The beast.
The protector of the ruins of Laros.
- Did Flora not tell you of it?
- I guess she forgot to mention it.
Don't worry.
When you say "beast," I'm assuming
that's a figure of speech, right?
No, it's a beast, all right...
though no one is quite certain
what it looks like.
Those who have cast their eyes upon it
have quickly perished.
But your little knife will protect us.
I'm the queen.
It will not harm me.
We may not get a chance
to tell the beast that.
It will know.
Listen,
why don't we say
we made it as far as the ruins?
We don't actually have to make it there.
They never have to know the difference.
I would know.
Yeah, but you're going to be queen,
so who cares, right?
I care.
My people care.
Listen...
Perhaps it would be best if you stopped
speaking. Your voice hurts my ears.
Well, that beast could hurt
my whole body, okay?
So I'm sorry, but this is not what we
signed up for. Back me up here.
John?
According to legend,
the beast attacks silently.
I thought you said the beast
would know you were the queen.
Well, it didn't attack me.
John?
Are you there?
It is strange, though...
the beast is supposed to only attack
enemies of the throne.
If it was going to kill anyone,
it should have killed you.
I'm not an enemy to the throne.
I'm not! I'm here to protect you.
Don't move!
So far, I'm not impressed.
Drop your weapon.
We have her.
Map grid 11 in the small clearing.
On our way.
- Hand her over.
- You're Genii.
Step aside, and hand her over.
This is obviously some sort
of huge misunderstanding. All right?
I'm Dr. Rodney McKay. I'm a close
personal friend of Ladon Radim.
You know, your leader?
I'm your greatest ally!
You don't know who I am?
I'm the genius scientist. The friend of
John Sheppard?I gave you the bomb?
No? Nothing?
- What do they teach in Genii school?
- Hand her over. Right now.
- Okay, let's just talk about this.
- I'm growing impatient.
Our quarrel is not with you.
Once you hand her over,
you're free to go.
- Really?
- Yes.
You wouldn't.
You took a sacred oath to protect me.
- Nah, I don't remember doing that.
- I'm going to count to three.
One...
- Where have you been?
- Well, my spidey senses
felt an ambush coming on.
And you couldn't mention it?
- Not without tipping them off, no.
- What took you so long?
I had to take a position so
I could shoot all three at once.
You okay?
No.
No, I most certainly am not.
This one was going to
hand me over to those men.
- No, I wasn't.
- I saw it in your eyes.
You were considering it.
To save your own worthless,
cowardly hide.
I was keeping them talking, you know,
I was buying us time.
A little thing called "strategy"? You're
too young to know anything about it.
Oh, I understand strategy.
In fact, I'm forming one right now...
the second we return to the castle,
I will instruct
- my guards to...
- All right.
Plenty of time to come up
with punishments along the way.
- But, John...
- Thumb screws, you like them?
Yes.
Thumb screws are good.
We better find some cover. That back-up
he called is gonna be here any minute.
All right, this'll work.
Those were Genii.
Yeah, I picked up on that,
Rodney. Thanks.
So...
what are the Genii doing here?
And why do they want to kill her?
I mean, aside from the obvious reasons.
Harmony?
I don't know.
I don't like the Genii.
But you know who they are.
- Are you trading partners?
- Not anymore.
- But you were.
- Yes.
But they cheated my mother
on many trades.
She banished them from our land.
What about you?
When you're queen,
are you gonna start trade back up?
No! Absolutely not.
So maybe somebody in the royal court's
a little more willing to play ball.
You know, once the path is cleared.
If I were to die,
my sister would succeed me.
But if the Genii think that she would be
more willing to trade than me,
they are sadly mistaken.
You really believe Ladon would give the
marching orders to kill a little girl...
even this one?
I don't know how these people work.
Maybe he told someone to fix that,
and this is what they came up with.
It's creative.
Knowing why they're here
really doesn't help us out.
I need to get a take on how many
are out there. You stay with her, okay?
Sure.
All right, stay here, and stay quiet.
Of course, John.
Thank you for taking care of this.
I'm not sure what I would do
if you weren't here.
Tell me something, Doctor.
The place where you sleep at night,
is it guarded?
I know what you're trying to do,
it's not going to work.
I'm not scared of you.
You're just a kid. A bratty little kid.
I don't care you're gonna be queen.
Nothing could impress me less, so
why don't just cool it with bad seed act
and just go back to ignoring me?
Surely they can't guard you
all the time?
Squad three,
take up position on the ridge.
Squad four, move to map grid nine.
Acknowledged.
Wonderful.
Stop it. What are you doing?
I'm burning your face into my memory.
- You...
- This way I can give the bounty hunters
an extremely accurate
description of you.
All right, Your Highness,
I have had just about enough out of...
I thought I said
keep talking to the minimum?
I was... she was...
How many Genii are out there, John?
If I had to guess, I'd say all of them.
What, so, a lot of them?
Yes, Rodney. A lot.
This will make the pilgrimage
most difficult.
That's funny,
I was thinking the same thing.
I find we have much in common, John.
Yeah.
Anyway, I figure we wait for nightfall
and then head back to the settlement.
Back to the settlement?
Yep, road trip's over.
But that would make
this journey a failure.
You win some, you lose some. You wanna
be queen, learn how to cut your losses.
But the lunar cycle is nearing its end.
If I do not make it to the ruins
by tomorrow's sundown,
I will forfeit the throne.
I'm sure they'll make an exception.
No, they cannot. It is our way.
It's too dangerous to move forward.
For you, perhaps.
If it's too dangerous for me,
it's definitely too dangerous for you.
We're gonna wait for nightfall, and then
we're gonna head back to the village.
- End of discussion.
- Fat chance of that.
It's not your decision to make.
I'm the queen.
No. Not yet.
And until you are, you're just
a regular kid. I call the shots.
Many would consider
disobeying the queen a treasonous act.
Well, I'm sure they wouldn't look too
fondly on letting the queen get killed.
We're heading back.
You should not be here.
I was careful.
No one saw me, don't worry.
We use this from now on
to stay in contact.
Does that mean it's not over yet?
No.
Her two guardians have
complicated things greatly.
They killed three of my men.
Yes, well,
they were an unforeseen complication.
My apologies.
Your apologies do me little good.
We will increase your pay,
don't worry.
Threefold.
Threefold?
Triple the work, triple the pay.
You want us to kill them all?
If they survive,
they'll come back and tell my sister
that the Genii were involved.
Now, we can't have that, can we?
Listen...
- I've been doing a little thinking.
- Oh, you have, have you?
I've a Wraith stunner in my backpack.
She can't weigh more than 90 pounds.
I say we stun her
and just carry her back.
Well, we can't stun a 13-year-old girl.
It's kinda dangerous.
The forest is crawling with Genii. Who
knows when she'd throw one of her fits?
She'll be fine.
She understands how dangerous this is.
- I talked to her.
- I'm sure you did, but she's 13,
she's unreasonable,
among many other awful attributes.
They say you dislike
the things in others
that you, in fact,
dislike about yourself.
So, what?
I'm just saying.
- We're nothing alike.
- Okay.
She's a stuck-up, know-it-all brat.
It's about as dark as it's gonna get.
Let's wake her up and get moving.
Oh, no.
Oh, that sneaky little...
I told you we should've stunned her!
I'm gonna kill her.
You really need to
work on your child skills.
We have been searching for her
for over an hour.
We have had not one, but two
close encounters with the Genii.
All so some useless, spoiled brat
can make her meditation appointment?
- More searching, less complaining.
- Sorry, I'm hungry,
- and when I'm hungry, I get cranky.
- And when you get cranky, you get hit.
Okay, okay.
I wish Ronon was here.
You know, you said that out loud, right?
I mean, I'm right here.
Well, it's nothing personal.
It's just he's a better tracker
than both of us combined.
That's true.
Okay, I'm starting to hallucinate.
- Why? What do you see?
- Not see. Smell.
I smell food.
Delicious, fresh-cooked food.
Roast beef, hamburgers,
hot dogs, pork on a spit.
Chicken.
- Yeah, sure, the more, the merrier.
- No, I smell chicken.
The nose that knows. Follow me.
Ah. Found it.
It's coming from down there.
Told you.
You don't need Ronon while I'm here.
What do you think?
- Genii camp?
- Give me your stunner.
All right, stay behind me.
John!
How did you find me?
We could smell your fire a mile away.
That's okay.
I was finished cooking anyway.
You ran away from us.
You didn't give me any choice.
We've been out there searching
for over an hour.
We almost were caught twice.
Yes, it's very dangerous
out there right now.
That's why I decided to seek refuge
in this cave and make camp.
You made all of this?
Yes,
and caught a loden bird.
- They're quite delicious.
- How?
You made all this with that?
I told you, I completed three sessions
with Nolar Lumsbred.
- They covered all that in 3 sessions?
- I am a quick learner.
Do you not listen?
You're mad at me.
Our first fight.
I knew it would happen eventually.
We'll laugh about this one day.
I'm sure we will,
but we got to get moving.
Right after we've eaten the loden bird.
Or not.
That sounded very, very close.
Are we sure this isn't the beast's cave?
You're so ignorant.
The beast doesn't live in caves.
We should stay here
until the coast is clear.
All right.
Half-hour, tops.
Good. I'm hungry.
I brought you the bird's heart.
My people believe
it brings you great luck once consumed.
Thanks, but no thanks.
- You're sure?
- Pretty sure, yeah.
Very well.
Are you still mad at me?
No, I'm over it.
That's good.
- I don't like it when you're mad at me.
- Well, don't give me reason to be mad.
Very well.
So you're 13, huh?
I'll be 14 in five lunar cycles.
Right.
Nervous about being queen?
No.
- Why would I be?
- Well, it's a lot of responsibility.
I know that.
You gotta put the needs of your people
before anything else including your own.
- Some of the time, yes.
- No, pretty much all the time.
I'm sure I will strike a proper balance.
Just remember... you're not queen
because of divine right,
you're queen because
they allow you to be queen.
If you're mean to the people, they may
change their minds. Just remember that.
You know much about leadership, John.
Hard-earned lessons along the way.
And I know much about my people.
I hope so.
I think we would make a good team.
As queen...
I will one day need
a king...
Listen, Harmony...
There's no need to answer now.
I know such an offer
must be overwhelming.
You shouldn't make your decision rashly.
Well, I'm pretty sure I know
which way I'm leaning.
You're a great little lady.
It's just that...
- What the hell was that?
- The Genii just had a little run-in
with the beast.
All right, be a brave girl
and stay here with McKay.
Hey, hey! How come I always
get stuck being the babysitter?
You want to check out the beast?
No, I'm good here.
Thought so. Stay here.
This is Mardola.
I want an update.
What's taking so long?
I have men all along the path
to the ruins. They've gone another way.
Well, obviously. They're not idiots.
You should be looking everywhere but
the path to the ruins.
I am, but it's night,
and this forest is vast and dense.
My men are spread thin.
What if they make it back
to the village?
There's no way that I could save
relations between our two peoples then.
We've just lost contact
with some of my men.
We're heading to
their last-known co-ordinates.
Maybe we'll get lucky. Teran out.
You're a doctor, right?
Yes. Yes. I mean,
I'm not a medical doctor...
So you're a liar?
No, I'm a...
What do you want?
- What does love feel like?
- Oh, boy...
Because I think I'm in love with John.
It wouldn't be the first time,
and I'm sure it won't be the last.
- What does that mean?
- It means that a lot of people,
particularly alien women, tend to fall
for John Sheppard's
good looks and charm.
Not like me they don't.
He's a bit old for you, don't you think?
I hadn't considered it.
He will, so don't get your hopes up.
You're not going to try
and influence him, are you?
I won't need to. Trust me.
You don't like me very much, do you?
No, that's not true. I...
I don't not like you.
What does that mean?
You have an annoying attitude,
but I'm willing to cut you some slack,
- because you're still just a child.
- Whereas if I were
grown up,
my annoying attitude
would be less excusable?
That's right. An adult would...
- Hey, I don't have an attitude problem.
- And I don't not like you.
Well, that's sweet of you to say.
So you promise not to get between
John and me?
I promise.
I'll give you this...
you're a lot more mature
than the women he usually falls for.
Thank you, Doctor.
What do you got?
Two dead Genii.
It's not pretty.
Multiple puncture wounds.
You mean like teeth marks?
I don't think so.
So... so, what? Claws?
Talons? A very sharp beak?
I don't know. It's not like anything
I've ever seen before.
Over here.
- What kind of creature could do this?
- It doesn't matter.
We don't leave this forest
until all three of them are dead.
What took you so long?
I thought for sure we'd lost you!
I ran into Genii. Had to lie low
until it was safe to move.
- So what happened?
- I don't know,
but whatever that beast thing is,
it's lethal.
I could have told you that.
Also...
the Genii have shoot-to-kill
orders for all of us.
Super.
All right, princess, let's move.
Wait!
What?
Where are you going?
Where does it look like?
We're going back to the settlement.
But we're so close to the ruins.
And it's almost daybreak.
The fact that it's almost daybreak is
a bad thing. We need the cover of night.
I can't come this far
and just turn back.
I refuse.
You know, I still have the unner-stay.
The best thing
you could do is go that way.
That sounded a little weird.
Hating to agree with the child, but...
Give me that.
The beast will avoid the ruins.
- We'll be safe there.
- How far are they?
A half hour or so.
So what do you say?
Well, it's better
than running into the beast.
I was afraid of this.
That's sacred ground. How dare he?
Hey. Hey!
We'll handle this, all right?
- I'll do that.
- I got it. It's okay.
- Really, just... just...
- Steady...
come to papa.
Let's go...
- Hey! Hey.
- What?
You have subdued him.
Now we can go.
Oh! Fascinating.
Ancient?
Yeah. Obviously.
It's weird...
this place seems strangely familiar.
It's even more beautiful
than I imagined.
Something's wrong.
What?
It's not working.
Shouldn't you be, like,
silently meditating or something?
My pendant... it's supposed to glow.
Well, I'll be damned.
- Let me guess.
- Oh, yeah, it's Ancient.
It's the Pendant of Laros.
The queen, and only the true queen,
must return it to the ruins.
Once here, it is to glow
and imbue me with great power.
Your sisters kind of failed
to mention that.
It is one of our greatest secrets.
It's the testing ground.
- What?
- I know what this place is!
I've been reading about it. We've been
looking for it for the last two years.
- I've seen the schematics.
- Share with the class.
Well, believe it or not, this place
actually does control the beast...
- if the beast is what I think it is.
- Which is?
Mini-drones, if I'm right, and
you can usually take that to the bank.
This planet must have been where the
Ancients first developed drone tech.
It was their main testing ground!
That would explain why the Genii
look like swiss cheese.
- The mini-drones went right through'em!
- And that noise the beast was making
was more like an electric
swarm than a growl.
So the pendant is...
Probably some sort of pass-key.
Ancients weren't above protecting
their research, even from each other.
You need more than just the gene
in order to activate or control
the drones, otherwise...
Yes, yes, yes, of course!
It's in auto-protect mode!
They're trolling the forest,
taking out anybody without the gene.
That's why they stayed clear of us
and went straight for the Genii.
The royal pain here must have it,
as well.
Why isn't it working?
Well, maybe because genius over there
- was messing with the crystal tray?
- All right, so?
Well, so give me a second to figure out
how much damage he's done.
The machine is broken.
That's why your pendant isn't glowing.
It's got nothing to do with machines.
If I am worthy of being queen,
the Gods will bestow the power of
pure light and make my pendant glow.
Well, who knows what kind of
wacky rules they've imposed on it.
I mean, I suppose it's possible that
once a generation, the key needs to be
reactivated here. Maybe it's the thing
that allows them to use the Ancient
- tech they have back at the castle.
- It's complicated,
but it will light up.
We just need to make some repairs.
You don't understand.
I've failed.
Maybe I'm not supposed to be queen.
Maybe...
maybe we've come all
this way for nothing.
Trust me, it'll glow.
Wake up.
What'd you do to this thing?
I'm not sure.
I just rearranged the crystals.
Don't tell them a thing. They're
going to kill us one way or the other.
Can you get it to work?
Not quickly. I can come back
with a Jumper and a small team
and get it working.
Listen.
- We're going to head back.
- No!
If I return with a darkened pendant,
I won't be allowed to...
Yes, you will be queen,
I promise you! It's just busted.
This isn't the type of thing where
you got a second chance, John, please.
I can do it. I just need to focus more.
Easy does it.
Huron, come in.
Huron. Come in.
If we don't respond,
they're going to come and investigate.
Huron here.
What's your status?
Good.
Elaborate.
- Real good.
- Help us!
Kinda busy, got to go!
Well, it was worth a shot.
You got to get that thing workin', fast.
Why can't we just run for it?
We're boxed in from all directions.
We've got to get
- those mini-drones working, or...
- Or we die.
You know, you're not exactly
inspiring confidence.
Yeah? How so?
You're hiding behind a foot of solid
rock. How am I supposed to feel out here
with only a cool breeze
between me and the Genii?
You're more than welcome
to come get cover
for yourself, as soon as you're done
with those repairs.
Do you have any idea how many crystal
placement combinations there are?
- More than seven?
- Try 7,000.
Well, that's less than infinite.
All right, look.
It's going to get very,
very noisy when the Genii get here.
Screaming?
No, these guns,
they make a lot of noise.
It's very important
that you stay put and keep
your ears covered, okay?
Shouldn't you give me a gun instead?
You're gonna stay put, cover your ears,
and you're not gonna move, okay?
Son of bitch! I think I got it!
Harmony! What did I just say?
Go, go, go, go!
You're surrounded!
You have limited ammunition,
and I have unlimited men!
We'll take our chances.
If you make this hard,
I will make your death as slow
and as painful as possible.
Okay, what's option number two?
Give us the girl,
and we'll let you go free.
Never!
They would rather die than deal
with the likes of you savages.
When my sisters hear of this,
the Genii will be finished!
Finished, do you hear?
How do you think we knew
how to find you, little one?
You lie!
Come at us with all you have!
I shall silence you once and for all!
Let us handle this, okay?
You have one minute!
It can't be true.
It doesn't matter right now,
to be honest.
How can you say that?
Did you get that thing working?
Yeah, before
they started shooting at it.
So it's broken again?
It was powered up.
50-50 chance it's still operational.
Provide me with cover.
I'll make it to the pedestal,
summon the beast, and smite them.
There'll be no smiting today,
little lady.
You've never even
used that thing before.
But I am the queen,
and the beast is my protector.
It's a little more
complicated than that.
You say anyone with
the Ancient gene can activate it?
Yeah, as long as
they're wearing the pendant.
Exactly!
50-50?
100% chance they'll kill us if
we talk about it for much longer.
- You got a full mag there?
- Locked and loaded.
On three?
Okay.
Yes. Excellent.
One...
two...
three!
What are you waiting for?
Shoot him!
You all right?
Yeah, I'm good. You?
Sure, sure.
That was the bravest thing
I've ever seen.
You're young. I'm sure you'll meet
even braver men
than me as you get older.
Not you, usurper!
You're lucky I like you,
or you would be hung for treason!
But you...
you saved my life.
- I did?
- When the Genii started firing at me,
you threw yourself on me,
- using your own body as a shield.
- Oh, no.
No, no, no. I just... I tripped and fell
on top of you. It was an accident.
And then...
you pulled me to safety.
You don't... don't not like me.
You like me!
No. No, no.
No, I'm...
Yes!
You saved my life
and restored the ruins.
You are a hero, Dr. McKay,
both to me and my people.
Well, I don't know about "hero." I mean,
exceptionally courageous, perhaps...
And modest, too.
It's time to go,
before the Genii come back.
I doubt it.
They are a simple people,
and I'm sure they were
most impressed by your actions.
I, however, was not.
The pendant still glows.
The gods have deemed me worthy.
Now we can go.
You've returned!
What are you doing?
These are my private quarters.
It's all right, Mardola.
They've already searched my room.
- You should allow it.
- Why?
The Genii attacked us.
Oh, well,
it was a good thing Colonel Sheppard
was there to protect you.
They knew the location
of the ruins, Mardola. How?
You ask as if I would know.
You're too young to be queen, Harmony!
Perhaps...
but when you're released from prison,
you'll be too old to remember.
Dr. Rodney McKay
and Colonel John Sheppard,
your contribution to my people
may never be repaid.
Well, we didn't do it for compensation,
Your Highness-ness.
Kiss-ass.
I personally owe you a debt of gratitude
for your help defeating
the regicidal Genii.
I've had one of the Court's
finest artisans feature you
in a rendering of our glorious victory.
Yeah, pretty much how I remember it.