Previously on Stargate Atlantis...
I could easily bring
another 12 ships to the battle.
12 ships,
willing to fight shoulder to shoulder?
For a chance to destroy the Replicators
once and for all? Of course.
- What did you do?
- What are you referring to?
- There's a ship on the way.
- Ah, they picked up my signal.
Subspace tracking device.
- Hello? Is anybody here?
- What happened?
My people,
they are gone.
Searched the entire planet,
no life-signs.
I will find them.
And we're gonna help you, but you
gotta rest, get your strength back.
Whoever did this will pay.
I will make certain of it.
I'm so sorry, Teyla.
Kanaan was a good man.
He would have made a wonderful father.
I really thought I could save him.
You did everything you could.
That's all anybody can ask for.
He's at peace now.
All right.
I'm ready.
Teyla...
- Teyla!
- He's still alive!
Help me, Teyla, please!
Please help me!
He's still alive!
Let me go!
- Teyla, it's too late.
- Help me, Teyla!
The Projet-SG & SG-66 Teams
present:
Season 4 Episode 18
The Kindred (part 1) (v. 1.0)
Transcription by:
swsub.com
Timing by:
Golgi, IceFre@k, Linwelin,
Obusco, Ricana, Shaft.
www.projet-sg.net
www.seriestele.net
As you know, for some time now,
we've been tracking what appears to be
a new sickness in the Pegasus galaxy.
We don't know exactly
when or where it started,
but so far we've encountered it
on seven different planets.
Make that eight.
We just came back from 447.
They got it too.
Really? The same symptoms?
Starts with respiratory difficulty,
proceeds rapidly
to fatal organ shut down.
Oh, it's... disinfectant.
We just came back
from the bio-screen, Rodney.
We were wearing a hasmat
the whole time, too.
Yes, well, it's better safe than sorry.
Do we have any idea how it's spread?
Well, that's the strange part.
Most of these planets
have no regular contact with each other,
but a few of them do have
regular contact
with other, neighboring planets
that have been completely unaffected.
So far.
How bad is this going to get?
If I had to make a projection, I'd base
it on the evidence from M1R-992.
There have been no new cases
there for some time,
which would seem to indicate
the sickness has run its course.
And?
It killed 30% of the population.
If those numbers bear out
on the rest of these planets,
we're looking at a death-toll
of about 200,000.
That's assuming
it doesn't spread any further.
Rodney, has Dr. Keller made any progress
with her investigation?
Unfortunately not, no,
but she's still working on it.
What are you hiding?
I...
Well...
I've been waiting for the right time
to give this to you,
and what with everything
that's been going on and all, I...
Anyway...
- Here you go.
- You didn't have to do this, Rodney.
Well, think of it as a...
a kind of a pre-baby present.
Back on Earth, there's this company
that produces recordings specifically
for the fetus.
The thinking is
that by listening to the works
of, say, a great composer
while still in the womb, the baby
will be born with a natural
predisposition toward musical ability,
or in this case, science.
Yeah, I recorded some of my reflections
on some of my more
ground-breaking accomplishments and
theories. Just a couple of hours' worth.
You should not have gone
to so much trouble.
Oh, it was no trouble at all.
Something wrong?
I was debating
whether or not to tell anyone.
Tell anyone what?
I believe I had a vision last night.
A vision?
I saw Kanaan,
the father of my son.
I believe that he was trying
to send me a message,
that he's alive,
and that I must not abandon the search
for him and the rest of my people.
And-and this was
while you were sleeping?
- You think it was a dream.
- Well, I...
I believe it was more than that.
It did not feel like a dream.
I knew you'd doubt me.
I should not have said anything.
Hey, I've been cocooned
inside an alien space craft,
I've had another person living
inside me, I've encountered not one,
but two different versions of myself,
so who am I to judge?
If you say it was a vision,
then I believe it was a vision.
- I seriously doubt it was a vision.
- She had them before.
She's had remote contact
with the Wraith, never another human.
Besides, those Athosians
have been missing for, like,
6 months now?
You really think they're still alive?
What do you want me to do?
Tell her to give up hope?
At some point,
she may not have a choice.
Kanaan...
Teyla?
You must help us.
- How?
- Save us.
Where are you?
Where are our people?
- You bought me this.
- Yes.
- Do you remember where?
- The village of Croya.
Is that where you are?
Come find me.
She says the pendant in her vision
is the same one she gave to Kanaan
before he disappeared.
So what's the significance?
Well...
I'm not sure.
Well, what does she want, exactly?
Well, she bought it from
some guy in a village on M2S-181.
She wants to go back and check it out.
That's a peaceful trading settlement.
I'd be very surprised
if they had anything to do with
the disappearance of the Athosians.
That's what I said,
but she still wants to go.
She thinks that Kanaan
is sending her a message, a clue.
- And what do you think?
- Doesn't matter.
It's Teyla, and we owe her one.
Okay, but we're stretched pretty
thin dealing with this plague.
We'll try to make it quick.
I purchased the pendant
from an artisan in Croya,
the village we are about to visit.
Among the Athosians,
it's quite common to present such gifts
as expressions
of admiration and respect.
Hey, maybe I'll pick you
something up while we're there.
Really?
No.
All right, so we'll ask around see
if we can get some useful intel,
but if you even begin
to sense any danger
I'll make straight for the Gate,
leaving you to deal with it.
All right, then.
Excuse me, I'm wondering
if you can tell me
what happened to the artisan
who used to occupy this space.
He specialized in handcrafted jewelry,
bracelets, pendants, chains...
He's gone.
Gone?
During the sickness
that took the village
several weeks back.
He and some 40 others.
I'm sorry, child, he's dead.
Hey, I hear you have something.
Yeah.
I found out
what's making these people sick,
and it's something
we've encountered before.
It's a unique protein originally created
by the inhabitants
of a planet called Hoff.
It was designed to interfere
with the Wraith's feeding mechanism,
making them immune to the process.
It also killed the feeding Wraith,
and half the people who took it.
That's right.
So this isn't some contagion
that spreads naturally.
No. This is mass murder.
- I think we're done here.
- Not yet.
I've given this place the twice over.
Nobody knows anything.
Perhaps someone does, and has
not yet seen fit to come forward yet.
I was guided here.
By showing me the pendant, Kanaan
was telling me to come to this village.
Look, you're going through a tough time.
You want answers,
that's understandable, but
you might want to consider it's clouding
your judgment. Just a little.
What are you questioning, John?
My interpretation of the vision,
or the vision itself?
We've been here long enough.
If there was something for us to find,
we would've found it by now.
Rodney, Ronon, we're heading out.
You sure it's the same protein?
I ran a side-by-side comparison.
It was almost an exact match.
Almost?
We're dealing with
the new and improved version.
The Hoffan drug killed roughly
50% of the test subjects,
and this one only kills 30%.
Yeah, it's still 30% too many.
How do the populations of eight
different planets get inoculated
with a drug and not even know about it?
It's possible it was administered
through their food and water supply.
- We're running some tests.
- So who's behind this?
Well, maybe the Hoffans have resumed
distribution of the drug, but
on a much larger scale.
They haven't been doing much of anything
lately. When the Wraith discovered
what they were up to,
the whole civilization was wiped out.
Maybe a few of them survived,
and they're planning a little payback.
The random nature of this drug's
distribution is clear and calculated.
It's obviously intended to throw
the Wraith completely off balance.
They have no way of knowing which of
their food sources has been infected.
So it's just a matter of time before
they become hungry and cranky.
Well, I mean, I know I would.
We need to go back to Hoff,
search what's still standing, see if
we can shed some light on the situation
before another planet's targeted.
Let's go, Rodney.
Teyla...
Kanaan...
Where are you?
I don't know.
Who took you?
How can I find you?
You already know where to go
to uncover the answers.
The village.
You stopped looking.
I went.
I found nothing.
You were close.
Please, Teyla.
Our time is running short.
We need you.
Kanaan...
And you weren't sleeping?
I was in a meditative state,
but I was most definitely awake.
There can be no doubt.
This is real.
But you've already been to the planet.
We missed something.
I'm certain of it.
I want to believe you, Teyla,
but I'm a scientist.
- I'm trained to think critically.
- There is a possible explanation.
Kanaan has the gift.
- The same ability that I do.
- The Wraith DNA.
Yes.
Among my people, the gift is considered
useful, but it also sets one apart.
It can be difficult.
Kanaan was the only one who could
truly understand what it felt like.
It brought you together.
It is something we have
shared since childhood.
But have you ever
communicated this way before?
No.
I know what this looks like, Colonel,
and I know what everyone is thinking.
She sees what she wants to see,
she believes what she wants to believe,
but I assure you, that is not the case.
All right. When Colonel Sheppard
gets back from Hoff,
- we can...
- I cannot wait.
Kanaan said their time is running short.
I must leave immediately.
I see.
I do not need your permission, Colonel.
Unless you intend to restrain me.
Major Lorne, come in.
Go ahead, Colonel.
Assemble your team. You'll be
escorting Teyla back to M2S-181.
Understood.
I'm not letting you
go back there alone.
Thank you.
Call me Sam.
Thank you, Sam.
Rodney, come in.
Go ahead.
- Did you find anything?
- Just a bunch of junk. You?
Nothing.
The Wraith did a pretty good
number on this place.
Yeah, this is more
than just random destruction.
This place used to be the repository
of all Hoffan knowledge.
I'd say a lot of it's just missing.
Who's there?
What's going on?
I thought I heard something.
Relax.
Probably just rats.
Rats?
Okay, if there's someone in here,
you better come out.
I'm not kidding.
Hang on.
I'm not going to hurt you.
I want to ask you
a couple of questions.
Now, who are you?
What are you doing here?
Okay, maybe you can help me.
I'm looking for some medical stuff.
Books, files, equipment.
I don't know anything about that.
By the time we got here, most of
the good stuff was already gone.
We're picking through what's left.
Looks like we're not the only ones here.
What do you got?
A bunch of kids going through
what's left of this place.
Scavengers. You think they got
a hold of what we're looking for?
Hoffan research wouldn't have meant
anything to them.
All right, if it's not them,
then who was it?
I don't know.
One thing's for sure, whoever it was,
they knew exactly
what they were looking for.
Kind of reminds me of the flea markets
they used to have back home.
Every sunday, stroll down
to the bay area,
find pretty much anything you wanted,
and a lot of things you didn't.
What is it?
Teyla?
Leave.
I will ask you once, and
you will answer me truthfully.
- Where did you get this pendant?
- From a trader.
If you like it that much,
it's yours with my blessings.
You recognize it?
It belonged to Kanaan.
What else did you
acquire from this trader?
You know, I don't want to be
difficult here, but I did acquire
merchandise for a price, and while I
don't mind gifting you with an item,
from a purely business standpoint, it
really doesn't make sense for me to part
- with my stock...
- This necklace belonged to Bellara.
It was a gift from her parents
to mark her coming of age,
and this ring
belonged to Halling.
This trader you say you got
these things from.
- When's the last time you saw him?
- Several days ago
but he comes
through here quite regularly.
In fact, it's more than likely
he may pay me a visit today.
It would be my pleasure to make
the proper introductions.
- Anything?
- No, the place was cleared out.
Is that what I think it is?
- It's getting to be a familiar sight.
- What is it?
Wraith subspace tracking device.
It's our old friend.
- Todd.
- Maybe he wants
to talk, and maybe he just wants
to lead us into an ambush.
There is that possibility.
Well, there's only one way to find out.
- Aw, come on, we just got back.
- Sorry, Rodney.
I haven't even had lunch yet.
Dial it.
Got some real nice merchandise
for you today, my friend.
Real nice.
Hey there,
how you doing?
You mind telling me
where you got this stuff?
Wake up.
Look,
we need to know
where you got this merchandise.
I do trade so much, it's often hard
to keep track of it all.
Oh, yeah?
Well, according to the merchant you do
business with here, the stuff you've
been bringing in lately has been a hell
of a lot nicer than your usual crap.
- He said that?
- Yeah, he said that.
Well,
there's no accounting for taste.
I can't give up my sources.
They're trade secrets.
I don't give a damn
about your trade secrets.
We want to know
where you got this stuff.
And if I don't tell you?
What are you going to do?
I recognize those uniforms,
I've heard the stories.
People from Atlantis,
do-gooders of the galaxy.
You wouldn't hurt me.
I'm wearing no uniform.
A pregnant woman.
Very intimidating.
I will inform the villagers
that you are a Wraith worshiper,
and let them mete out
their own justice.
Let's go.
Wait, wait!
I got it
at an off-world dumping ground.
Dumping ground? For what?
Corpses, mostly.
Loose ends that need
to be disappeared.
Occasionally they may still have
some valuables on them,
valuables they obviously
have no use for.
This merchandise,
you removed it from the dead?
No,
not that merchandise.
The last time
I was back at the planet,
I spotted what I thought
was a fresh grave,
a potential new opportunity,
but when I dug it up,
instead of finding a body,
I found a box
containing those items.
I suppose somebody was just
trying to get rid of them.
It was odd to me at first,
but I wasn't just about...
You will take us to this world.
You will show us
where you found them.
Of course.
Whatever you say.
Get him up.
Sheppard.
We got something.
Well, they're dead,
but there's no marks on them.
That's because they were poisoned...
and I suspect you already know how.
First thing we do when we get
to the Gate is radio back to Atlantis,
let them know
where we're going, okay?
Listen, Teyla,
I know you're looking for answers
to what happened to your people, but
I'm thinking maybe it's better
if you let us check it out, okay?
- Major...
- Look,
just let us scout ahead, all right?
- What is that?
- Dart!
Well, let me guess...
Something they ate?
Many of my fellow Wraith
have fallen victim
to this attack on our food supply.
Yeah, it's a shame,
but it's not really our problem.
From what we've been able
to surmise,
this blow against us has been delivered
at a great cost to human lives.
Something you would have
made your problem in the past...
Unless, of course, you're responsible
for the dispersal of this plague,
in which case, you may well consider
the human lives sacrificed
acceptable losses?
Actually, when we were putting a list
together of the most likely suspects,
you were at the top.
What better way to stick it
to your competion?
Effective,
yes,
and admittedly creative,
but the truth is,
all of the existing Wraith factions
have been adversely affected by this.
Our food supply
has been so randomly tainted
we have no way of knowing
if our next meal will be our last.
All right,
times are tough.
Doesn't explain
why you called us here.
I brought you here because...
I need your help.
I am aware you had a hand
in helping the Hoffans refine this drug.
I require whatever research you possess
in order that I may synthesize a cure,
for my hive
and my hive alone.
That's not going to happen.
You always say that,
but you always come around.
Yeah, well, this is different.
We're still a little upset
over the whole Earth conquest thing.
- I had no part in that.
- Actually, in an indirect way, you did.
The Wraith who led the attack
was able to access the Midway station
with information you stole
on your last visit to Atlantis.
Information
he stole from me in turn,
so, in a way, we were both victims,
but let's save our commiserations
for another time.
I have a proposal.
Let's hear it.
In exchange for this information,
I will give you
the identity of the individual
responsible for dispersing this poison
and killing both Wraith
and human alike.
A couple of minutes ago,
you thought we did it.
There are only two parties
who possess the resources
and capabilities
to launch such an attack.
If you are not responsible, then,
by process of elimination,
there can be only one.
Michael.
According to Todd,
every Wraith faction has been hit,
which makes it very unlikely
that any of them are responsible.
When we told him we weren't behind it,
he said there can only be one other.
And you think you know
who he's talking about?
Michael.
The Wraith that Dr. Beckett
converted into a human?
Well, temporarily converted.
Eventually, he became a kind
of a human-Wraith hybrid.
The other Wraith didn't want anything to
do with him so he's been kind of holding
- a little bit of a grudge ever since.
- He's not a big fan of Humans, either.
No, for him, the Hoffan drug
is the perfect weapon.
Still, this is just speculation.
I mean, do we have any proof?
Well, not really, but even if we did,
we'd have no way of finding him.
We can go back to Todd, see
if he's got something more than a name.
Wait, you're not seriously
thinking of...
giving him our research
on the Hoffan protein?
Why not?
Because we'd effectively
be giving the Wraith
the means to reproduce the drug and,
potentially infect and kill millions...
Theoretically, yes, but practically,
it really wouldn't be
in their best interest to poison
their own food supply, regardless of
whether our research helped them
come up with an antidote or not.
No, I think the more likely scenario
is that they find an antidote
that works as a short-term
solution to the existing threat,
then they work
on weaponizing the protein.
Coming up with a more
effective delivery system,
one that cuts out the middle man,
in this case, the human victims.
No, what we're doing is giving them
the means to kill each other off.
So, when you, uh...
put it that way,
giving them our research
could be a good thing.
Incoming wormhole.
Major, where's Teyla?
Why am I here?
What do you want?
Answer me!
I'm disappointed.
I was expecting a little more gratitude,
after everything I went through
to arrange this...
family reunion.
Reunion?
My people...
You took them?
Where are they?
- What have you done with them?
- They're alive and well,
and working with me
toward the common goal we all share.
What are you talking about?
The extermination of the Wraith.
I'm building an army
that will soon replace them
as the dominant race in this galaxy.
An army of monsters.
I'll admit,
my early attempts were a little...
crude,
but that's all changed now.
I've refined the retrovirus
to create the perfect balance,
ability well beyond any normal human,
but without
the one weakness
that will be the downfall of the Wraith.
The need to feed.
It was you.
You're the one responsible
for spreading the Hoffan drug.
Consider it the opening salvo
in a much broader assault.
How were you able to discover the drug?
How were you able to refine it?
I had help.
Wait! Where are my people?
Michael!
Oh, don't mind them.
They're just here to help
with the clean-up.
I assume you've agreed to my terms?
Not exactly.
You do not wish to know
who's responsible for these
unfortunate events?
We already know.
At least, we have a pretty good guess.
We call him Michael.
Don't ask why.
He used to be a Wraith. Now he's a...
I'm not sure what the hell he is.
I know the one of whom you speak,
and I believe you are correct.
Confirmation,
without us giving you anything.
That's very generous.
Obviously there's more you want from me,
or you would not have come.
Maybe we just came to kill you.
Did you?
Unfortunately, no.
Well, there's always next time.
Rodney...
One of our people,
Teyla, was taken by a dart today.
I suppose she's already made
some lucky Wraith a very tasty meal.
This was no culling.
She was targeted. Someone set a trap.
And you suspect this...
What do you call him? Michael?
Well, if not, the timing's
a hell of a coincidence.
We need you to tap your intel sources,
find something useful.
This tablet has the address
of an off-world relay station.
If you leave a message for us,
we'll get it.
It also has our research
on the Hoffan drug.
Just enough to whet your appetite.
You find something we can use,
we'll give you the rest.
Well, I'll see what I can do.
I understand
you're refusing to take food.
It's not poisoned,
if that's what you're worried about.
Take it.
You need to keep up your strength.
What do you care about my well-being?
I care a great deal.
I may not be foolish enough
to consider us friends,
but we do have a history...
And even though you've
betrayed me repeatedly,
you're still the only one,
human or Wraith,
who's ever come close to understanding
what I've been through.
Really?
We're not that different, Teyla.
You're a human with Wraith DNA.
A hybrid, just like me.
I'm no murderer.
You kill to protect yourself
and your own, so do I.
Of course, circumstances require me
to do it on a slightly larger scale,
but the principle is still the same.
You're insane.
Spite me all you want,
but don't do it
at the expense of the child.
My child...
is of no concern to you.
On the contrary,
I have great plans for him.
- How can you eat right now?
- You kidding?
This is the first decent meal
I've had all day.
Besides, it's not gonna help Teyla
starving ourselves.
I'm just trying to keep my strength up.
I suggest you two do the same.
- We'll find her.
- I've just gotta do something.
Colonel...
- Looks like Todd came through for you.
- He did?
Got a message from the relay station.
Apparently there's a rumor going around
amongst certain Wraith worshipers
about one of our people
being held captive.
- You've got the coordinates.
- I'm gonna need Lorne's team.
He's already volunteered.
You'll gate to the nearest planet,
- the Daedalus is enroute to pick you.
- Let's go.
I told you, I'm not hungry.
Kanaan...
What has he done to you?
Kanaan,
it's me. Teyla.
I came for you, just like you asked.
Like I asked.
I was the one in your visions.
Appropriately disguised, of course.
You're lying.
I reached across 10,000 light years
of space and touched your mind.
There is more of a bond
between us than you know.
Once the child is born,
the bond will grow even stronger.
Enjoy your reunion.
Kanaan, you must help me.
You must help our child.
Please, Kanaan.
The child will serve the cause,
then one day soon,
the galaxy will be ours.
- Colonel...
- Sheppard.
- Approaching target destination.
- Drop us out.
Yes, Sir.
We're unable to get a lock
on Teyla's subcutaneous transmitter.
No surprise.
Sure Michael got rid of that.
Guess we'll have to
do things the hard way.
Good, let's do it.
- All right, stay in touch.
- Yes, Sir.
Let's move out.
Sir, I'm picking up another ship.
It's a Wraith cruiser.
Shields up.
Return fire!
Sheppard, this is Daedalus.
We've been engaged by a Wraith cruiser.
How's it going?
More than holding our own,
but you could pick up the pace.
Where's your boss?
- You're too early.
- What the hell does that mean?
We're expecting him back.
He's on his way
with an important prisoner.
This is Sheppard, come in.
- Daedalus, do you read?
- Sheppard, this is Daedalus.
Do not destroy the enemy ship.
I repeat,
do not destroy the enemy ship.
Teyla may be on board.
Did you hear me?
Teyla may be on board!
- We heard you. Can you cripple it?
- It's possible, Sir.
It's already sustained
some heavy damage.
- The enemy is attempting a retreat.
- Target the engines!
I'm sorry, Sir.
Bad news.
The cruiser made
the jump to hyperspace.
It's gone.
- Any sign of her, Sir?
- She's not here.
Are you sure?
That guard was protecting something.
Finally!
It's about bloody time.
What took you so long?