You can go ahead, Rodney.
- I don't remember how it's start.
- Sure you do.
No.
Start with your name,
like we've been doing, okay?
I just go for now.
My name.
My name, is...
Mister Rodney McKay.
- No.
- Yes.
Come on, you Doctor McKay,
you remember?
No, I'm...
I'm not anymore, I'm not...
smart anymore.
- Doctors are smart, so I'm mister now.
- Okay.
I used to be
the smartest person ever...
And... And now...
Now I'm not.
That's what we're trying to fix,
right?
No, you can't fix me.
You know we're trying
our very best...
No, you can't.
You can't. Can't...
It's okay, Rodney, what's the next thing
you're supposed to say?
Where...
Where did John go?
He had to go away for a few minutes.
He'll be back...
- I'm your friend, I'm right here.
- Where are you, John?
Why the hell didn't you tell me
my brother was this far gone?
- It's happened pretty fast, Jeannie.
- No, I...
I got a message from him
just a couple of weeks ago.
He seemed perfectly fine.
He'd never been so nice.
That would have been
shortly after he became infected.
- I didn't recognize the symptoms.
- It's not your fault, Doc.
Frankly, Mrs. Miller,
we contacted you
as soon as we became aware
of the seriousness
of his condition.
In fact, Daedalus dropped you off
at the first available Gate in Pegasus
because we were concerned that you
wouldn't make it here in time.
We thought you deserved a chance
to say goodbye.
The Projet-SG & SG-66 Teams
present:
Season 5 Episode 06
The Shrine (v. 1.00)
Timing by:
Golgi, Linwelin and Pikes.
www.projet-sg.net
www.seriestele.net
Dr. Keller wanted to take a moment
to prepare him for your visit.
Yeah, I...
I think I need a moment myself.
How did...
How did this happen to him?
There was a little snafu
on the last mission.
Colonel Sheppard,
when you reach the research camp,
please remind Dr. Nichols
that he is now...
one hour and 15 minutes overdue
for his scheduled check-in.
Right, want me to smack him around
or anything?
Just the reminder, please.
Shouldn't we be concerned
for Dr. Nichols' team?
No, the settlement's a half hour away
from the Gate.
He's got them checking
in every six.
I'm sure Nichols is tired
of taking the round trip.
Still, it wouldn't hurt
to bust his chops.
That Nichols is so arrogant.
Amelia, I think I'm going to risk
heading down to breakfast
before they check in.
I just mean that...
It will probably take them some time
to get to the camp,
and then more time for Nichols
to get back to the Gate and report.
There's really no point in my...
telling you this.
- Not really, sir.
- Right.
Be back in 20 minutes.
Unscheduled offworld activation!
Activate the shield.
I'm not receiving an IDC.
This is Sheppard.
Do not lower the shield.
The entire Tower will be flooded.
I have no intention of doing that,
Colonel. What's your status?
It's cold and wet.
The Stargate's underwater.
- The entire valley's flooded.
- And it's freezing!
We need you to send a Jumper through
so we can stay warm and dry
until the water recedes.
- Will do, Colonel, hold on.
- Holding on. Sheppard out.
Rescue one is standing by.
What's taking so long?
Why isn't the Gate disengaging?
It's the water.
The constant pressure's
forcing the wormhole to stay active,
which means we're going to have to wait
the time a Stargate can stay open.
38 minutes.
We're down to 32,
and before you say I told you so,
we had no choice.
- I can't stop shivering.
- You're letting the hot air
out of your mouth.
All right, everybody,
you'll be warm soon enough.
I don't know,
I think I got wetter than you did.
I got a little damp dialing the DHD.
The research camp was farther up.
I'm a little concerned
for Dr. Nichols' team.
Right.
Anyone at the research camp,
this is Col. Sheppard, please respond.
I repeat, this is Colonel Sheppard.
Please respond.
- I'm pretty sure they're all dead.
- We can't know that, Rodney.
The research team was studying
the effects of global warming.
They set up camp at the foot
of a massive glacier up the valley.
- You think an ice dam broke?
- It fits.
The Ancients don't put Stargates
on a flood plain,
and I certainly don't think
the tide just came in.
It explains why the water's
so freezing.
Okay, so now I'm hot,
and I'm still shivering.
Were you running a fever
before we left?
I don't know, maybe.
I'm always running something.
All right,
I think the water's receded a little.
So we're going to be stuck here
all night.
In the back of a warm,
cozy Jumper, all right?
All you need to do is hold on for,
I don't know, 30 minutes or so...
- How long has he been unresponsive?
- Since he fell asleep in the Jumper.
About nine hours.
Let's get him to the infirmary.
I want to have a look at you guys, too.
We're good.
By that I mean now.
I think you've just made a case
for my proposal
to send a MALP ahead
of every single transit.
Stuff happens, Woolsey,
and by "stuff," I mean...
I know what you mean, thank you.
Why didn't you return in the Jumper
I sent you?
I ordered the rescue party to continue
the search for Nichols' team.
- There's a chance they're still alive.
- Of course.
I got to go get checked out, and then,
I'm gonna check on Rodney.
Well, how's our boy?
No fever, no hypothermia,
nothing on the scan at all.
- How about you guys?
- Like I said, we're good.
But we're not the ones
who became unconscious.
I didn't really get much sleep the night
before, and I did skimp on breakfast.
Woolsey wants to send out a MALP
before every transit now.
- That's going to get old fast.
- That's what I said.
Can I go now?
I feel a little silly lying here.
I'm keeping you for a little longer.
Besides, I ordered you dinner.
Then you can observe me eat,
because I'm famished.
- It's official. He's better.
- See you guys.
- Do you want me to send them in?
- Okay.
Rodney's all ready for you.
What am I supposed to say?
Doesn't matter.
- It's me. It's jeannie, Mer. I'm...
- You're my sister.
Yes.
Meredith's my...
real name.
It's your first name, that's right,
but you never liked it.
No. No, it's...
a girl's name.
Sometimes, yes,
but you go by Rodney.
You're crying because of me.
No, I'm crying
because I've missed you very much.
'Cause you're my sister.
That's right.
I'm... sick.
I know.
I'm here now.
Sweetie, I just need to go outside
for one second, okay?
I will be right back, I promise.
I know.
I just need a second.
I just don't want him to see.
I know how you feel.
- I felt the same way.
- I'll go back in, I will.
He needs me, and I want to be able
to say goodbye, but it's like...
- It's like he's already gone.
- I know.
There's a way.
What? How?
It's a place.
I've been there before.
He'll be himself again,
and you can say goodbye.
Then why haven't you
already taken him?
Because it's dangerous,
but I'm willing to risk it
if you are.
All set?
Remind me to register a complaint
with whose ever idea this was.
It was yours, actually.
Complaint duly registered.
It was a good idea to keep a record
of what's happening to you and how fast,
- but if you'd rather not...
- No, it's fine.
- Start by my name, right?
- Right.
I remembered something.
My name is Dr. Rodney McKay.
I'm head of the department
of science something in Atlantis
in the...
Oh, for God's sake...
- In the Pegasus galaxy.
- Okay, not bad, keep going.
Jennifer, there's...
There's something I wanted to...
While I remember, while I still can,
something I wanted to say...
Go ahead.
I wasn't expecting anyone
this late.
I'm one of those people who needs
all the information they can get.
This is his most recent scan.
This dark area
that looks like a tumor
is actually a parasitic organism.
Its tendrils spread far beyond
any hope of surgical extraction,
and it's not responding
to treatment.
Even stasis
barely slowed its progression.
There are still
a number of drug combinations that...
He was infected somehow
on his last mission?
Maybe, but not necessarily.
It was too small
to show up on a scan at the time,
but in the Pegasus galaxy,
the condition is fairly common
- among the very old.
- Right, so why him?
It's possible we're all exposed to it
and fight it off.
Rodney was already suffering
from a viral infection
when he went on the mission
at M44-5Y9, and then
- all that time in freezing water...
- So his resistance was low.
The parasite doesn't so much
as kill cells as render them dormant
for reasons
I still don't completely understand,
but the net result
is ever-diminishing brain function.
As it spreads, he'll lose motor control,
regulation of organ function...
Ronon's people call the disease
"Second Childhood."
- You talked to Ronon.
- Yes.
- Okay, I know what he's told you.
- That he's dying,
- and there's nothing you can do.
- No,
I'm doing everything I can.
I have to ask you...
Why did you tell me you didn't recognize
the symptoms in time?
Because
he was already showing the symptoms
when he came back
from the mission, and...
I didn't see it.
So?
Just what the doctor ordered.
Funny.
You want my fruit cup?
- No, no, no.
- I think you do.
Eating from the patient's tray
is kind of frowned upon.
Jennifer, we practically dated.
You bought me one drink.
So now I'm asking you
to have dinner with me.
I mean, such as it is.
I do love the fruit cup.
Not that this is exactly
the dinner I had in mind, but...
- Is that an invitation?
- Only if you promise to accept.
If I wasn't so taken
by the new Rodney McKay,
the parasite might've been
small enough to operate
without causing
significant brain trauma.
By the time he started
to forget, it was too late.
I haven't given up
on trying to find a treatment...
Ronon told me about this place
that could give Mer one more day
- as himself again before he dies.
- Jeannie, you can't possibly believe...
And that you're the one
who won't let him go.
It's on a planet called Talus, one
of the original worlds of the Ancestors.
It took us about five or six hours
to get there from the Gate,
but I was just a kid, and my grandfather
had to be carried most of the way.
We could do it in about half that time.
There's a small problem
with that plan.
The Wraith established a Major outpost
there during the Replicator war.
It's still there.
That's never stopped us from going
anywhere we needed to go before.
Well, it's not just that.
- You don't believe it's real.
- I'm not saying...
I am, actually.
- I was there.
- Yes, but you were six years old.
Ronon, listen to what you've told us...
A magical Shrine,
inside a cave, behind a waterfall...
- Did I say it was magic?
- No, but you did say
that people afflicted
with McKay's condition
suddenly revert
to their former selves for...
The Shrine of Talus
is also known among my people,
for victims of the second childhood.
It offers the gift of one last day,
and a quick death.
- That doesn't necessarily make it real.
- I'm telling you in a matter of seconds
I saw my grandfather go from someone
who couldn't speak his own name,
to the man that taught me
how to track and hunt.
You learned to hunt
when you were six years old?
For one day,
he got to hold his wife in his arms,
and share a meal
with the people that he loved,
and then he died with honor.
You can say
I was too young to remember,
but I know what I saw, and we can do
the same thing for McKay.
If you think that's not worth it,
you're wrong.
I've never told anyone this,
outside of...
My father had a disease
called Alzheimer's.
It's similar in many respects
to the condition
that Dr. McKay is suffering from.
My point is,
I had a similar moment with him
to the one you've just described.
He hadn't recognized me,
literally, for months,
and then one day,
out of the blue,
he had a moment of absolute clarity.
He said
"Richard, what are you doing here?"
And I said, "Dad, I...
I'm here to see you," and he said...
He said, "Isn't that wonderful",
and then he was gone again.
- Couldn't you be remembering a simil...
- It's not the same.
- Ronon, look...
- I owe him this!
- I'll take him.
- I'll go with him.
Hold on, hold on.
We know for a fact
there are two hive ships
and 10,000 Wraith on the ground.
If we're even going to consider this,
all right, we have to make a plan.
- Fine, make your plan.
- I'm sorry,
but he's not going anywhere
without my permission,
and you won't get that
until we talk to Rodney.
You got some visitors.
John's here.
So are Teyla and Ronon.
The whole team.
Ronon Dex.
That's right, buddy.
I want to take you to a place,
a place that's going to give you
a chance to be yourself again
for a little while.
As you were before you became ill.
Before...
Hey, pal.
Hey, John.
Truth is, we don't...
know exactly
what's gonna happen to you,
but we're willing to try,
if you are.
Okay.
Okay, okay, well,
- that settles it, then.
- No, it doesn't.
- They haven't told you everything.
- He doesn't need to know.
The planet they want to take you to
is a Wraith outpost.
You remember who the Wraith are?
It means going will be very,
very dangerous,
not just for you,
but for your friends.
- We're willing to take that risk.
- A risk for which,
and I'm sorry, even if it works,
which I very much doubt...
you might revert to your former self
for one day.
Now, forgive me if that sounds
more like torture than a blessing.
We're still coming up with new ideas
on how to treat this thing,
but if you do this,
if you leave Atlantis...
Atlantis...
It's over.
I can't help you.
Doctor...
He doesn't understand.
No, he doesn't,
which means the decision
on whether or not to let him go is mine,
and I haven't given up
on trying to cure my patient.
And you still haven't given up.
No, because I don't think the damage
to the cells is permanent, which means
- if I can safely remove the parasite...
- How long have you been at it?
Weeks?
And how many days does he have left?
Two at most?
Look, I know you've done
everything you can.
I know you feel responsible,
and you want to keep trying, but...
I'm his next of kin.
That makes the decision mine.
And we're taking him.
It's recording.
Aren't you supposed to say "Action"?
Sorry.
I'm kidding.
Okay, here we go.
My name is Dr. Rodney McKay.
I am head of the science
and research departments
here in Atlantis,
in the Pegasus galaxy,
in the local cluster,
in the universe as we know it.
The purpose of this log
is to provide a baseline
for myself, and for Dr. Keller,
to monitor the progress of my...
memory loss.
Ironic, isn't it?
By reciting the aforementioned,
as well as a list of things
I know like the back of my hand,
starting with pi,
to, say, 12 decimals.
3.1415926535...
- Rodney on board?
- Yes.
Are we clear on the rules?
We'll get in and get out
before the Wraith even know it.
If in fact
Dr. McKay does regain his...
Say goodbye for me.
- I thought you didn't believe.
- Is that a prerequisite?
He'll be glad you're here.
We're either going to get away
with this, or we're not.
If we don't,
the ride's gonna be wild,
and it's is gonna be fast,
so I need everyone prepared.
Jumper three, standing by.
Send the MALP through.
The malp is clear of the Gate,
and they're firing on it
from both sides
of what appears to be a deep valley.
It's deploying smoke.
You should have complete coverage
of the area in five seconds.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
I hope so.
That's one hell of a valley.
Do you think they detected us
before we cloaked?
No, I think the smokescreen worked.
Hopefully they think we just sent
a MALP through ahead of us
and changed our mind
when they blew it up.
I'll do a sweep of the landing area.
Shouldn't take more than a few minutes.
- You were there, and then he...
- I'm right here. What's wrong?
I woke up, everyone had left!
Buddy, I...
I'm sorry,
I thought you'd fallen asleep.
I was...
I got so scared, I was sure that...
by the morning what was left
of my mind was gonna be gone!
I'm gonna take you
back to your quarters, okay?
I've never been so scared.
I'm slipping away.
I'm slipping away,
and I don't know how to stop myself!
Look, you're still here.
All right?
You're still here.
Yeah. I am.
And I'm not going anywhere.
You know, you want to hang out,
you just...
hang out.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do with myself.
I'm...
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have
woken you up.
All right, look,
it's a nice night out.
Let's go have some beer
on the pier, okay?
- I drink beer?
- A lot.
Take this.
Come on, buddy, let's go.
- I don't know, should I have another?
- What could happen?
I shouldn't have banged on your door
like that, I feel ridiculous.
Don't.
I've been trying to remember the name
of my sister's kid.
Betty.
Betty...
Pretty sure that's not it.
It's Madison.
See?
- At least you remember what it wasn't.
- There's an underrated skill.
You may not be
as far gone as you think.
I'm hiding it.
I've already forgotten more
than most people will ever know,
and I know that sounds...
- Arrogant, is that right?
- Yeah.
That works.
I was trying to help Zelenka finish
a device that was apparently my idea.
I was...
useless.
Jennifer says it's going to get worse
now almost by the hour.
In a week or so,
I won't even remember my name.
How's about...
How about we say goodbye now?
No.
What, no?
- I mean, I'm not saying goodbye.
- I'm saying it anyway.
- I'm not listening.
- But soon I won't know who you are.
- Then I'll remind you.
- I don't want you to see me like that.
Remember me as I am,
as your genius friend, not as some...
Not happening.
- Please.
- You're stuck with me. Just accept it.
- Yeah, but...
- No!
That's final.
You're a good friend, Arthur.
All right, landing area's clear.
I'm taking us in.
Where are we going?
Up there, do you see?
Behind the waterfall,
there is a cave,
and when we get there, you will spend
a wonderful day with your friends.
I'm tired.
I know.
We'll be there soon.
So... What do we do?
We wait.
Look at the waterfall.
It's cool, huh?
I'm getting
very faint energy readings.
- What kind of energy readings?
- I'm not sure.
Look at this. Radiation?
Not that I've ever seen.
Maybe we can ask
Rodney in a minute.
- Just hang in there, buddy.
- I wanna go home now!
Perhaps he should stand
closer to this tablet.
I don't know.
I think that's the source
- of these energy readings.
- I want to go now!
- A little bit longer.
- Go now!
I'm here, Mer.
Yeah, obviously.
He's back.
Somebody please tell me
what the hell we're all doing here?
I'm head of science and...
research.
Dammit!
- It's okay.
- No, it is not.
Atlantis...
Pegasus...
It's 3.1... 4...
I don't know.
How can I not know that?
Do you wanna stop?
I keep seeing a face.
Every time I close my eyes.
I think it's my mother.
I don't... I don't...
recognize her...
It's so long ago.
She's saying words to me...
I don't know them.
Well, you can start with,
what is this place?
- It's the Shrine of Talus.
- That means nothing to me.
It's a planet of the Ancestors.
We brought you.
Thank you, Mr. Information.
Since when is he Ronon the explainer,
and why am I not in the infirmary?
What am I, better?
I am better!
No, you're not.
I am. I can feel it.
This is amazing!
Mer, we brought you here
so we could say goodbye to each other,
but you'll feel like this for a day.
- That's just how it works.
- What?
What do you remember?
You didn't want me to say goodbye then.
Why now all of a sudden?
And why one day?
What's with that?
It is a gift of the Shrine,
and from all of us who risked
great danger to bring you here,
one last chance
to be with those you love.
And then what?
I die?
With honor.
- And dignity.
- Screw that, I'll just stay here.
- Doesn't work that way.
- Why not?
One, this is a Wraith-controlled planet.
And we're detecting ionizing radiation.
- We shouldn't be standing close to...
- You've gotta be kidding me.
- How could you let them do this?
- Don't blame her. She didn't wanna.
Then whose brilliant idea was it?
- Mine.
- We all thought it was a good thing...
How could this possibly be a good thing?
Look, I'd got past the humiliation,
I've said my goodbyes.
Merdith, I'm sorry this happened to you,
but I'm not that I got this chance.
Please, just...
try to see this as an opportunity
- and not...
- Not torture?
Look, I'm sorry, I just...
I thought I was going to be okay,
and then now you tell me...
Did you have
some kind of itinerary planned?
Well, actually,
we're going to have a big feast first.
Last supper, huh?
Suits your messiah complex.
True.
Please don't be mad at me.
I guess if I had to choose the people
I would spend my last day with, then...
What is it?
Honestly,
I didn't expect it to work.
I expected nothing would happen,
and that would be that.
So why did it?
You don't believe in magic shrines
any more than I do.
Show him the readings.
- That's what I said.
- You said "hmm"?
I just meant that
I thought it was weird, too.
- What do you think, antimatter?
- Or a superheavy element
the Ancients used to use
as an energy source.
- I've never seen it before...
- Or created to power this place.
Who could tell what that is?
Must be thousands of years...
- See that spike?
- Come on.
- Let's have some fun.
- For me, this is fun.
Just... Save me some ham.
There it goes again.
It's some kind of gamma that's...
- Come with me.
- What? Why?
- I need to find out something.
- Where are we going?
Hopefully all the way back to Atlantis.
Sorry...
Why did you do that?
To determine whether the parasite
would expand rapidly back into his brain
when we took him from
the radiation source, I think it did.
The reason why his symptoms disappeared
when we came here was because
it contracted to protect itself.
What does that mean for us?
That leaving this chamber
will probably kill him.
We can't take him back to Atlantis.
So...
We're gonna have to find a way
for me to operate on him right here.
I thought you already tried radiation.
I did, but we'd never come across
this kind before.
The parasite is radiosensitive to it.
That's why the Shrine works.
You feel fine for one day
until the radiation makes you feel sick,
then you leave.
Farther away you get, more rapidly
the parasite expands into the brain.
And your day is over. I get it.
So, if we're here,
it's small enough to operate?
I guess, but it's the only thing
that would explain his sudden remission,
but I'm not gonna know
for certain until I get in there.
- How are you gonna do with a field kit?
- I don't.
- We would need equipment from Atlantis.
- That's a problem.
What if we radio Atlantis,
ask a Jumper with what I need?
- No, we can't.
- I need that equipment, John.
The Wraith are never gonna fall
for the same trick twice.
Even if somehow they don't
pick up on our radio signal,
and even if the second Jumper
makes it through the gauntlet,
they'll know we're here.
We'll never make it to Atlantis.
If we don't try, he's dead.
- What do you need?
- To operate? I already told you.
Bare minimum, what do you need?
More than I have
in my medical kit.
I mean, I need a scanner to find out
the location of the parasite,
I need the proper tools
to cut his skull open...
All right.
I've got an idea.
Keep him as far away
from this thing as he can stand.
We'll be back in 20 minutes.
You can't expect me
to operate with those.
Well, I've seen surgical drills.
They're not that much different.
Fine, assuming we can open him up,
I still have no way of knowing
where the parasite has contracted to.
We can use this.
- A lifesigns detector?
- Yeah. Why not?
Well, it's just not designed to do what
I need it to do on the correct scale.
We'll have Jeannie modify it.
No. You don't understand.
The radiation is compromising
his immune system as we speak,
which means if I don't kill him,
the infection he's bound to get
by being operated on in a damp cave
- almost certainly will!
- Look, if we don't do something,
he's dead.
You said it.
Absolutely not!
We're talking about saving your life.
Look, my brain is not some new deck
off the back of your house.
- I'm not the one doing the surgery.
- Yes, and as my parting advice,
you need to stop letting these guys
talk you into doing stupid things.
I can do it.
Really?
And I'm fairly sure
I can modify the lifesigns detector.
- Yeah, with my help...
- So help.
This isn't one of those brain surgeries
where my skull is open,
and we have a conversation...
I have anesthetic to put you out.
You're not going to feel a thing.
Yeah, it's probably a hammer.
Time is of the essence, Rodney.
You need to make a decision.
Please, Mer. Let us try.
Obviously I'd get around to consenting.
It's just... You've thrown
an awful lot at me all at once.
That's life.
All right, let me have a little ham.
No food before surgery.
Sorry I'm mean sometimes.
I'm gonna have to cut here...
Here...
And here,
and drill those points
to resect the area.
I don't wanna penetrate the dura layers
until we get there,
so hold him as still as you can.
Go.
I took too long reconfiguring
the lifesigns detector.
I haven't given her enough time
to perform the surgery
before his immune system
is compromised.
- Dammit, I went too far. Hold him.
- I'm trying.
It's the parasite... It's moving.
Maybe it knows we're going after it.
I don't think so.
I think it instinctually wants
to get away from the radiation source,
and we've just shown it the way out.
Ronon, we're going to need
that gun of yours in about 10 seconds.
You could have stepped on it.
She told me to shoot it.
It's clear.
You did a good job.
You too.
Let's get him home.
Why don't you go get some sleep?
I'm gonna be here all night.
It's okay.
I'd like to be here when he wakes up.
Well, it could be a while.
He does love to sleep, our Rodney.
You should've seen him
when he was a teenager.
Who can sleep
with all the talking?
You still all there?
There was so much to spare.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
That was scary.
For me too.
Are you hungry?
Peckish.
I'll go order you something.
There's something I wanted to...
While I remember, while I still can,
there's something
I wanted to say before...
Go ahead.
I love you.
Loved you
for some time now.
Where was I...