The question you've
gotta ask yourself, E,
- is are we family?
- Yeah, E, are we family?
What are we
if we're not family?
Just four guys who are a little old
to still be living together.
Yeah, and one guy
who's way too old.
Just share the wealth.
You made $200,000
off "Aquaman."
With another $300,000
coming in.
- That is good money.
- Meanwhile, me and Turtle,
we're living beneath
the poverty line.
In the old country everybody gets
a taste off a big score.
- I'm Irish, Turtle.
- Well, I'm not.
And this broke Guinea wants
to wet his beak a little.
A quarterback takes care of his
offensive line after a good season.
You know that, E.
Otherwise, they let him
get buried the next year.
I feel like I'm getting buried
this year.
You better forget gold and check out
something in silver, Drama.
No, bro.
Silver doesn't read on my skin.
What does that watch cost?
$10,000?
You wish.
This is gold, E.
Ooh, Saigon is gonna love
this beast.
- Saigon?
- Yeah.
I've got to get something for my client
to welcome him to my company.
You think I'm buying a watch
for your fucking client?
No, you're paying
for a gift for me.
What I chose to do with it after that,
that's my business.
- Vince?
- Family, E.
Family.
All right, fuck it.
Miss, can you give these guys
whatever they want?
Spread it out
over all of these.
So much for paying off
my student loans.
- I'll be outside.
- Told you he wasn't cheap.
Had you all wrong, E.
- Yeah, E, you're good people.
- What?
I don't have to buy
the watches?
No, I'm buying.
I just told them that you would have.
Whew.
Thank God!
Thanks.
- Can I wear mine out, bro?
- Of course, Johnny.
- Me too?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
It's 7:35 A.M.
In Senegal...
That's great, Drama.
...and 7:53
in Tikrit.
Minutes don't change, Drama.
Only the hour.
- Yeah, like you've ever been to Tikrit.
- Holy shit!
- What?
- Look!
Is that Mandy?
You've got
to be shitting me.
She's stepping out
on baby bro!
Relax! Don't jump
to any conclusions.
Maybe they ran
into each other in there.
And they just happen
to be leaving together?
Yeah, that's what
happens at Gucci...
buy a pair of shoes and they let you
fuck your ex-fiance.
Come on, Turtle,
let's trail them!
Come on, come on!
- What should I tell Vince?
- You're representation. Lie!
Let's go!
Where did they go?
Turtle had to meet
with Saigon.
I thought today was
gonna be a leisure day.
Thank you.
- They started without you.
- Ha ha, very funny.
Mr. McQuewick
is in there.
What is this?
April Fools?
...never been in better shape.
I think we have
more A-list clients now
than we've ever
had before.
Ah, Ari.
Good of you to join us.
When did the rules
change, though?
I'm not sure what rule
you're referring to,
but I'm sure there have been
some slight adjustments
in the last three years
since you last attended a staff meeting.
Well, nobody's ever been allowed
to enter a staff meeting late.
No one.
No exceptions.
Move along, Ari.
Back off a little.
You're too close.
I'm two cars back.
What do you want?
Always keep two-fifths of a block
between you and your subject.
Oh, what, have you
done this before, Drama?
Too many times, Turtle.
Too many times.
I'm thinking about taking
a trip to Paris.
Yeah.
I've got a week
before shooting starts.
It's six months
of hell after that.
- Yeah.
- I could use a trip.
I'll tell the boys.
No, not with the boys.
With Mandy.
What the fuck are you
taking pictures of?
What do you mean?
Them.
This way when Vince
goes into denial about it,
- it's proof.
- You don't think he'll believe us?
Nobody ever wants to believe
you're being two-timed, Turtle.
How many times
you been cheated on?
Too many, Turtle.
Too many.
Mr. McQuewick's on the phone.
He'd like to speak with you.
To apologize?
Send him down.
He wants you
to come up.
- He won't come down?
- He asked me to send you up.
He asked you
to send me up.
Did you tell him
that you don't send me anywhere?
Did you tell him that no one sends me
anywhere in this fucking agency?
Did you tell him
that I send myself where I want?
No. I just said okay.
You tell him
to come down.
He'd like to speak
with you.
You see that, Lloyd?
No surrender.
Terrence,
how are you?
Ari, get your ass
up here!
You embarrassed me
in front of my troops.
Rules are rules.
I apologize.
I appreciate that.
- Now, come up!
- You come down.
Conference room...
neutral territory.
- 1:15.
- Done.
How about you and Sloan
come with us?
- To Paris?
- Yeah.
You guys are getting
pretty serious, right?
I don't know.
You know, maybe.
What if this is it
for both of us?
I think it's a little early
for that for both of us.
Yeah?
Maybe, maybe not.
Anyway, it's never too early
to go to Paris.
That's true.
- Yo!
- We followed them all morning.
Great!
Don't worry.
They didn't suspect a thing.
I'm dropping Vince off
at Mandy's now, guys.
Good!
She just arrived home.
- Where are you?
- Look to your left.
- Was that our car?
- I've gotta go.
It's clear.
That was close.
Thanks.
Think about Paris.
- What's up, baby?
- Hey.
- Where were you?
- I was just shopping with my mom.
Yeah?
- Hey, E!
- Hey!
- How's Sloan?
- She's great.
- Tell her I said hi, okay?
- Yeah, definitely.
Bye.
I mean, she lied
right to his face.
Eric, Mandy dated Chris
for three years.
That's a long history.
Maybe they were
just talking,
and she didn't tell Vince because
she didn't want to hurt his feelings.
- You don't know the whole story.
- I know what I saw.
- What did you see?
- The way they were walking.
What do you mean
the way they were walking?
Just their body language.
Stop looking at me like that.
- I'm telling you.
- Telling me what?
You have some unique skill
I don't know about?
- Maybe.
- Hmm.
What does
my body language say?
That we might not
be making it out to lunch today.
Eric, listen to me.
My best friend in high school,
when I told her
that I thought that her boyfriend
was cheating on her
she never spoke
to me again.
- Was he?
- Mm-hmm.
- Didn't matter.
- Oh.
Still I've got tell him,
though.
- It sucks getting cheated on.
- Yeah, it does.
So, let's agree we'll
never do that to each other
if we ever get serious.
Oh, okay,
Did I totally
just freak you out?
No, of course not.
I want to get serious.
Come here.
Hold on a second.
It's Ari.
This could be important.
Hello?
Let me ask you
something.
- You still seeing Sloan?
- Yeah. Why?
She ever say anything
to you about me?
About you? Why would she
say something about you?
I don't mean it like that.
I mean, work-wise.
No.
E, you're my friend.
You'd tell me if she did.
Ari, I'm at Sloan's. Do you want me
to ask her something?
You're with her now?
Why the fuck didn't you say so?
No, I don't want you
to asking her anything.
I don't want you to say anything about
this. Forget this conversation.
Does she already know
we're having this conversation?
- Ari, what's going on?
- Nothing. It's all good.
I'll call you back.
What's going on?
I think Ari and your father
are having problems.
All right,
let's cut to the chase.
- All right.
- I miss this place.
I miss the excitement.
I miss the action.
I'm coming back
full time.
Muhammad Ali came back
once too often too, Terrence.
Stop, Ari.
This is nothing
for you to worry about.
Good. All right then,
I want an extension.
Well, you have a year left
on your deal.
When it expires,
as always,
- you'll be taken care of.
- That's not good enough.
I want to know that I'm being
taken care of right now.
You know I have a policy
never to extend active contracts,
but I've always been
fair with you.
You were being fair with me
when you said you were leaving.
You coming back now
is not fair to me.
Not now!
Now I want something,
Terrence.
All right.
All right, Ari.
You know,
I've never done this before.
This is what I'm prepared
to offer you.
No e-mails, no faxes,
no phone calls, no nothing.
- Simply silence, Lloyd.
- Ari.
Silence, Lloyd.
It's golden.
- Who's gonna lead this thing?
- I told you, I am.
You guys don't even
need to be here.
- I'm his brother, E.
- Yeah, and I'm his best friend.
- Is that official?
- What?
I always thought that me,
you and Vince were best friends?
I didn't know that you two
were better friends than me and him.
Or that you and him
are better friends than me and you.
Whatever, Turtle.
You want to tell him, tell him.
No, the guy always
kills the messenger,
never kills the best friend
of the messenger.
- Yo!
- What's up, brother?
All right,
what's the emergency?
You see, there's one head
right there.
And there's another one
- I don't see anything.
- Right there.
If you look straight down
you can almost see
that there's two hands
that are almost holding.
This thing's really not designed
for long-range photography.
Anyway, who is it?
Come on, guys.
Who the fuck is it?
It's Mandy and Chris.
We saw them together
this morning.
This morning?
We were together this morning.
Before that.
You were paying for the watches.
Which we didn't get a chance
to thank you for, by the way.
Thanks, Vince!
- Where you going?
- Gonna call her.
Lloyd!
Mm.
This envelope contains
the names of eight agents.
Anyone catches you,
you eat it. Comprende?
Nod if you understand
what I'm saying.
I understand.
You can't
just fucking nod?
Lloyd...
I want you to...
pledge your undying
loyalty to me.
- Ari...
- Listen, Lloyd, do you want to make it
or do you want to fold shirts
at a Chinese laundry?
Now pledge.
- I pledge my undying loyalty to you.
- Okay.
Now, I want you to go
to each of these agents,
discreetly say the words
"tsetse fly."
Say nothing else.
Now, go.
- Ari, are you leaving the agency?
- Shh!
Silence is
fucking golden.
- It's all good.
- How so?
They were just talking.
She didn't want to hurt my feelings.
Come on, guys.
I get it.
They were gonna
get married next week.
Anyway, I'm gonna
go the bathroom.
Are you gonna drive me
to her house afterwards?
Sure.
Denial... stage one.
We ought to go over
to Chris's house and whoop his ass.
Yeah.
Guys, remember, Vince
took Mandy from Chris.
- He should whoop Vince's ass.
- Who's side you on?
I'm just saying,
what if it was nothing?
They rented movies
at Blockbuster.
Maybe they were
returning movies they already had.
- Is that what you think, E?
- No.
- It's not what I think.
- Yeah, me neither.
- Come on, Turtle, let's go.
- Where?
Go get the proof we need.
Come on.
- What are you gonna do?
- Don't you worry about it.
Where are they going?
Uh, another
Saigon meeting.
You know how hard it is
to get a rapper to sign a contract.
Those fuckers
never say goodbye.
Tsetse fly.
Hamburger Hamlet,
right?
Tsetse fly, Davies.
That's all that you're supposed to say.
- Everything else stays the same.
- I'm sorry.
- I forgot what it means.
- Well, you just said it.
- The Hamlet?
- Yes.
Right, the Hamlet.
Nobody who works in this business
- would ever be caught dead there.
- You know what?
You better lock down
some really good clients.
Look, if you have
something to say
why don't you
just say it?
Look, when you guys
told me you thought
Kristen was cheating on me it hurt,
but you were right.
Now you're comparing
Mandy to Kristen?
No! I'm not even
saying she's cheating.
Then what
are you saying?
I'm just saying
it didn't look like it was over to me.
- What do you mean? They were kissing?
- No.
- Were they holding hands?
Then what made it
look like it wasn't over?!
- I don't know. Instinct.
- Whatever.
- You asked me what I was thinking.
- Now you told me
and I don't want to hear
about it again, okay?
Okay.
You think you
got enough cash?
Live and learn.
You throw around enough dough
you can find out
anything you want.
What exactly are we
trying to find out?
We already know
they rented a movie.
Yeah, but what movie?
"Texas Chainsaw Massacre"
might say one thing.
"91/2 Weeks" would say something
very different.
There is no way I can tell you
what movie Mandy Moore rented.
I would get fired.
Are you joking?
There's more where
that came from.
I value my job.
I cannot be bought.
Psst!
- Your Vinnie Chase's brother, right?
- That's right.
Yeah, I saw you
on "Celebrity Justice."
You busted up that guy's car
with a golf club.
That was on "CJ"?
- Yeah.
- Sweet!
You got anything
to tell us?
Break out that money clip again
and I just might.
Just tell me what
this is about, Ari.
I just want to have
a private dinner
with you and Vince
as soon as possible.
To discuss what?
You're freaking me out!
There's no need
to freak out, E.
It's all good.
Believe me.
Just think of it as a
state of the union address
for all my A-listers.
Hold on.
Yeah?
Code red, Ari!
Code red!
- What are you talking about?
- He knows! He knows!
- Who knows what?
- Mr. McQuewick.
I think you're
the first one to arrive.
Oh, fuck!
Lloyd, pack up
all my files.
Pile everything
you see into a box.
Everything! You see a used condom,
an executioner's mask,
and a goddamn
spiked paddle,
don't think, just pack
that bitch! Chop suey!
Ernesto!
Keep it up front
and keep it running!
- Ari, I'm sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
- Sorry, Ari.
- Don't sweat it, Peter.
- It's too bad, Ari.
- It's all right, man.
- Sorry, bro.
- It's okay. It ain't your fault.
You should be
a nicer person.
Maybe then people
wouldn't fuck you.
You talked, Davies?
- Hey, Adam.
- Yeah, Ari?
Just so you know,
your girlfriend
when she was in the mailroom,
she offered to blow me.
True story.
People, we have
a traitor in our midst.
Let this be a lesson
to all of you.
You're making a very big mistake,
Terrence.
That's what Arthur Jensen
said in 1973.
He was the first
conspirator that I ever dealt with.
Try finding
him now, Ari.
He's selling auto insurance
in Reseda.
Okay, people,
most of you
are sitting there
and you're looking
at this good-Iooking old man
and you're wondering,
"Who the fuck is he?"
And you know what?
That's exactly what you should be doing.
You all know who's been running
this company for the past eight years.
And you all know
that when I go,
in no time you will be repping nobodys
like Bill from "The Apprentice."
No one needs to make
a decision right now.
I will be starting
my own agency.
Two very important goals
will apply...
to make everyone
who is in
at the ground floor rich,
and to burn
this motherfucking
place to the ground!
Lloyd, are you
with me?
Lloyd,
what are you doing?
You and me have a special bond.
Come on, let's go.
Ari, swear to me
that you will never again say anything
offensive to me
about my race or sexual orientation.
I can't swear to that,
but I promise I will
always apologize after.
Phone numbers, messages,
anything you remember, write it down.
Get Shauna Roberts,
have her start
drafting a press release
for tomorrow's "Variety" all right?
Ernesto!
Where's my fucking car?
I'll get him.
You kidding me?
My phone's dead!
Company phone.
I think they had it turned off.
Hello?
It's Lloyd looking
for Mr. Gold's car.
Sorry, Lloyd, it's a company car. Mr.
McQuewick said I can't give it to him.
Can't give it to me?!
Ernesto, how many
fucking pesos
did I give you
for Christmas?
Huh, Ernesto?
Every Christmas for the past decade?
Half of Mexico
is eating on my tips
that I have given you.
Bring my motherfucking
car now, por favor!
Sorry, Mr. Gold,
I can't do it.
Oh, and Mr. Gold,
I'm from Guatemala,
and our currency
is the quetzal.
I'll get my car.
Fuck!
Ah!
They rented
"Brian's Song," E.
I heard you.
What do you want me to do?
- The ultimate guy-cry movie.
- Uh-huh.
He cries in front of her,
shows her he's sensitive.
Bang!
He moves right in.
Yeah, his tears
will basically act as a lubricant.
We said our peace.
There's nothing more we can do.
How's that chicken?
Okay, so,
you're mad at me?
No.
I'm not mad at you.
I guess I should have
told you.
- I'm sorry.
- Well, if there's something to tell...
No. Again,
nothing happened.
Chris and I haven't
been together
since we've
been together.
He just...
you know, he begged
to see me today. That's all.
Mm, what did he say?
That he still loved me...
and he wanted to make
sure that me and you
weren't just trying
to recapture first love,
but if I was sure,
then he was happy for me.
Yeah.
Are you sure?
How can I be sure?
It's been, what, two weeks?
Well, I'm sure.
Really?
Huh.
Because...
I'm sorry.
I'm not, Vince.
I'm not sure.
I'm just...
I'm really confused. I can't lie.
Because on one hand
I think about you
and the way that
you make me feel
and how I felt
five years ago.
And then
on the other hand,
I think about him and...
I kind of miss him.
Why don't you
just be honest with me
and tell me which hand
you're leaning towards?
His.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
I'd like to say a few words
about a guy I know,
a friend of mine.
His name is Brian Piccolo.
He has a mental attitude
which makes me proud
to have a friend
who spells out courage
24 hours a day,
every day of his life.
I can't get
Ari on the phone.
- It says his cell's been disconnected.
- Shut up!
- Move.
- You guys have any idea where Vince
- might have his home number?
- No. Shut up!
- Move!
- Call the agency.
There's got to be
a night answering service.
But I say to you,
here and now,
Brian Piccolo is the man
of courage...
Hi, can you put me through
to Ari Gold's voicemail?
Sorry, but I'm afraid
Mr. Gold no longer works here.
Okay, thank you.
I loved Brian Piccolo.
They said he no longer
works there.
Hey, Vince.
Can I get you
to turn off the TV?
Come on, Vince,
it's the best part.
All right, just
to get it over with
so we don't have to talk
about it again.
You guys were right.
It's not over
between them.
And we're done.
- Sorry, buddy.
- Yeah, sorry, Vin.
We're all sorry, bro.
Yeah.
Are you mad at us
for telling you?
No, I love you guys
for telling me.
Anything we can do
for you?
Nah.
Uh, actually,
tell Ari
I'm not gonna
do the movie.
I couldn't work
with her every day.
I'm gonna go to bed.
My life is over!
You will bounce back,
Ari Gold.
I drove to work
in an $80,000 Mercedes.
I'm driving home in a prop car
from "The Fast and the Furious."
I just don't see it.
What the hell
am I gonna say to my wife?
Ari...
I've worked 18 hours
a day to save up the money
to put myself through
Stanford Business School.
While I was there,
I cleaned the cafeteria
during the hours
I wasn't studying
and still graduated
top of my class,
only to take a job
delivering mail
to unappreciative
overpaid little cocksuckers,
then to finally get
the big promotion
that would allow me
to answer your phones
and be both racially
and sexually harassed
for the next nine months.
But I know the endgame,
and you, Ari Gold,
you are it.
So stop your
fucking whining,
and go into your gorgeous
$3 million house
with your beautiful
goddess wife
and figure out how
you're going to make
both of our lives
happen tomorrow!
- That was a good speech, Lloyd.
- Pfft.
If I was 25 and liked cock,
we could be something.
Oi.
We're gonna be okay,
Lloyd.
Oh my God.
This is fate.
Are you out of your
fucking mind, Ari?
Get in the house, now!
Baby.
Baby!
- You're drunk?
- Baby!
What happened
to your hand?
Dance with me, baby.
Nothing nothing.
I haven't stopped thinking about you.
Baby, you're my everything. Baby baby!
Lloyd, what the hell
is wrong with him?
- Baby!
- He is in love is all.
Good night!
Come on.
Baby, this is our song.
You are my life.
I'm not going into that house
until you dance with me.
The music's gone,
Ari.
That's weird,
but I can still feel it.
Come on.
- Ari?
- What? Come on, baby.
Feel it in the house,
okay?
- Ari! Ow!
- My fucking hand, baby!
Oh!
Ari...
Ari, the neighbors.