human beings
need a lot of things to feel alive...
family...
love...
sex.
but we only need one thing...
to actually be alive.
we need a beating heart.
when our heart is threatened...
we respond in one of two ways...
we either run...
or...
we attack.
there's a scientific term for this...
fight...
or flight.
it's instinct.
we can't control it.
or can we?
izzie.
his heart's barely beating.
We need to call a code.
I can't feel a pulse.
Izzie,we need to call a code.
No! I have a plan.
He's crashing.
I need to call the code.
No! If we call a code,
they will rush him to surgery
and replace his lvad,
and then he will stabilize.
He needs to get worse
if he's gonna get this heart.
Izzie,this is crazy.
He has to get this heart.
He will die waiting for another chance.
You know he will.
We have to call a code!
No!
You press that code button,
I will hurt you.
Not a lot,'cause we're friends,
but enough so that things will break,
and you lie on the floor out of my way.
Izzie...
you have a decision to make.
You can stay here
and help me with this,
or you can go.
What's it gonna be,george?
chief,how bad is it?
It looks bad.
Um,I'm here. I can help.
Um,if there's anything surgical,I can help.
Why don't you go run trauma two,
doctor yang?
I get to run trauma two,
all by myself?
Yes,but find me if you need
help and get consults.
I'm on it.
how bad is it?
Uh,G.S.W.
To the right shoulder.
He's lost a lot of blood.
All right,get him to trauma one.
And keep the blinds closed.
Yang is on the floor.
Self-inflicted G.S.W. To the head.
Pulse is thready.
This guy's the shooter?
Yep,emptied his clip then shot himself.
And blew off half his head.
Okay,okay.
push 1 of epi and,
get him on a monito
you're running this?
Damn right I am.
Wait,wait.
I'm--I'm fine.
You need to lay down.
You've lost a lot of blood.
I'm fine. L-let go.
I'm fine.
I have a patient i have to go check on.
No,no,no.
You are the patient.
Lay down.
dr. Bailey,
when did you get here?
Page shepherd.
take over compressions.
You're shot?
Cristina?
-get back to your patient!
-He's shot?
Yang,we got this,okay?
That guy shot you.
Move.
He's a lost cause.
He's circling the drain.
You don't get to kill yourself.
You do not get off that easily.
Push high dose epi.
-Dr. Yang--
-what?!
I want to be able to tell his family
that I did everything I could to
save his pathetic,miserable life.
Give him 3 of epi,now.
We should be hearing
from dr. Burke any minute.
that's what you said half an hour ago.
Well,whether or not we hear from him,
we hit that hour mark,
I'm goin' in to get my heart.
Okay,no.
No exit wound.
Entry to the upper right shoulder.
Could be lodged in the spine.
okay,let's roll him over.
easy.
Okay,watch the arm.
Easy.
Hey,dr. Burke.
The bullet is in dangerous
property here,okay?
We need to check your hand function.
I want you to try and squeeze
my fingers,okay?
They moved my guy upstairs.
-How is he?
-I need you to wait outside.
I'm not gonna wait outside.
Burke?
Can we have a moment?
only a moment.
I don't want to waste any time,okay?
cristina...
no,you don'thave to say anything.
I know you're sorry.
I know you didn't mean to kick
me off the transplant,
and I'm not mad.
I mean,I was,
but I'm not anymore.
So don't worry about it.
Don't even think about it,okay?
I mean,all that matters is that you get better,
and you get through this.
And I'm here for you--
whatever you need,anything.
I need...
you to...
to go...
To check on denny duquette.
Okay.
that was my best supportive girlfriend,
and you kind of ruined it with medicine.
Okay.
Addison!
Thank you for meeting us.
You want to tell me what's so important
i'm keeping it secret from my chief of surgery?
I was chaperoning a prom for my niece.
We had a little bit of a situation.
Camille travis,17,
lost consciousness during sexual intercourse?
Keep it down!
It's okay,aunt adele.
I'm fine.
When your uncle richard finds out
you were cashing in your v-card,
none of us will be fine.
camille?
mrs. Webber?
Oh,my god. Is she okay?
-She has to be okay,right?
-No one ever died having sex,right?
-It was her first time.
You're not gonna tell my parents,right?
Hey,I even used a condom and everything.
george's page said it was an emergency.
You paged meredith?
We need help!
What the hell is going on?
Exacy what I said.
she cut his lvad wires.
What do you mean,
-you cut his lvad wires?
-Are you trying to kill him?
I'm trying to save him.
All I have to do is confirm
that his condition is worse,
and then burke can call U.N.O.S.
And he'll move up on the list,
and he will get his heart.
-About burke--
-she's gone insane,right?
It's not just me?
About burke--
everything will be fine!
Izzie.
When burke gets here,
everything will be fine.
He will know what to do.
About burke--
what?!
He's been shot.
--------------------------
www.ydy.com/bbs
Proudly Presents
--------------------------
Sync: YTET-xjeff0
-==www.ydy.com/bbs==-
Greys.Anatomy.
Season 02 Episode 27
burke's not coming?
Cristina,are you okay?
I'm fine,I'm fine.
Burke's not coming?
Why didn't I take the internship
in san diego?
None of this would be happening
if I was in san diego.
Burke's not coming?
No,izzie,
burke is not coming.
I know you're having problems here,
what,with your possible murder charges
and your unbelievably stupid
idea about stealing a heart,
but burke's kinda busy right now.
denny's gonna die.
Denny's gonna die,
and I killed him.
You shouldn't have done it!
geoeorge.
We have to tell someone.
No,denny won't get the heart,
and izzie will get kicked out of the program.
I'm leaving.
What?
Cristina!
No,burke could die,too.
Complications arise all the time
because of gunshot wounds.
You think about that.
Oh,my god.
Oh,god,you know what?
None of this would've happened
if you were thinking with your head.
-I did what I thought was best!
-Did you think about the rules,
izzie,for one second?
-The rules don't always matter!
-About anyone other than yourself?!
Shut up !
Shut up!
No one is leaving and no one is dying.
thank you.
It was kinda gettin' on my nerves,
all this dying talk.
Denny...
it's okay.
I think,
maybe we should all listen to meredith.
It looks like she might have a plan.
You have a plan?
Just give me a minute.
You girls should go back to the prom.
Are you gonna call camille's parents?
Not until I have to.
You know her mom.
She gets a little hysterical.
brian,disappear.
What?
Disappear! Go. Get--
richard.
Richard.
Adele.
what,are you here to see preston?
Preston?
No.What happened to preston?
Preston was shot.
Preston was shot?
Camille?
What--what happened to camille?
Richard--
why didn't you call ?
She's 17,sweetheart.
She'll be 18 in a few months.
Most girls lose it way before--
Do you think i want to hear that?
You think I want to picture my baby niece...
losing it?
Richard,richard.Take deep breaths.
The bleeding has stopped,
but her pelvic exam does concern me.
I'd like to do an ultrasound.
Three years ago,
camille was diagnosed
with ovarian cancer.
They only removed one ovary to try
and preserve fertility.
But her checkups have been clean since then.
okay.
let's not worry until we have to.
you!
You wait right there.
I want to talk to you.
I said wait.
Stop!
I said stop!
Richard,take deep breaths.
Richard!
that's a stupid plan.
if burke isn't coming,
then we have to confirm denny's
condition ourselves.
We get the blood work,
we do the echo,
and no one even has to know what izzie did.
But none of us have done an echo
on our own before.
Cristina has.
Burke taught her.
I'm not involved.
What if this were burke?
What if you were me?
This is bad.
This is bad and serious
and against a lot of rules.
It's not fun for me.
I don't want to play.
What if you were me?
I wouldn't have fallen in love with a patient.
You fell in love with an attending.
so did mer.What's the point?
The point is we can't help who
we fall in love with.
hand's cold.
My hands are always cold.
Your hand is cold,preston.
I have cold hands.
the bullet could be lodged in the brachial plexus.
That's dangerous.
Yeah,it's very dangerous.
oh,no. Trachea's deviated to the left.
-Absent breath sounds on the right side.
-Give me betadine.
Let's go,let's go,let's go.
14 gage angio.
Let's hurry.
dr. Burke.
Dr. Burke,you gotta stay with me now.
there you go.
That's it.
There you go.You're all right.
Right here,right here.
Your lung collapsed.
You're okay.
You're okay now.
He's been shot?
Dude...
we're gonna have to run these tests ourselves.
U.N.O.S. Gave us an hour.
In a couple of minutes,
our time is up.
M telling you,this chick is hard-core.
She's not gonna wait.
Okay,well,you just have to stall her.
I'm not getting involved with this.
Look,I don't care if that--
that drawling,bedridden whiner ever gets a heart.
Alex...
do this...
for izzie.
I'm not guaranteeing anything.
so...
was it totally romantic?
before the pain and the paramedics and everything?
okay,so...
you know that feeling when you look
into someone's eyes
and you're totally comfortable,
and you aren't self-conscious,
and everything just...
is,like,perfect?
camille,have you had any symptoms?
any abdominal pain,
nausea?
Anything?
no,she's been fine.
You haven't been fine,have you?
o,not for like a month or so.
You've been feeling sick for a month?
wanted to go to prom.
I-I...
I didn't want to be the girl with cancer again.
ou're not.
he's not,right?
I was just trying to remember
the night I lost my virginity.
and I can'T.
I remember who it was with and...
I remember I was 18,but...
can't remember any of the details.
I can remember all of the details.
I kinda wish I couldn'T.
That bad?
No.
just not good.
good came later.
And then really good came.
that little girl in there
is just gettin' started.
She hasn't even seen what good is yet.
Please,addison...
tell me she's going to have a chance
to see what the good stuff is.
I'm so sorry,adele.
How's his heart looking?
His left ventricle's shot.
It is barely pushing blood out.
I'm sorry.
I know that you're worried about burk
-you know,whatever.
-It's fine.
Cristina,can't you just try to understand?
I love him.
You don't even know him.
I do know him.
No,you've never even seen him outside
the four walls of this hospital.
You don't know him.
I know him.
And maybe I don't live with him
or work with him like you do with burke,
but I do know him.
And there'S...
there's possibility here.
And--and given the choice of running or staying--
you should run.
A sane person,
a person who values her career
and everything she's worked for,
a person who values her own heart,
for god's sake,
that person would run.
A sane person...
would marry me.
What?
What did you say?
What did he say?
He said,"marry me"?
He said,"marry me",right?
He did.
Denny,wake up.
Denny.
what's happening?
I'm pumping harder.
I don't know.
he's ftline.
No,no,no,he's not flatline.
There's movement in his heart.
Okay,
let's--let's shock him.
Uh,charge the fibrillator.
Ventilate,george.
I am.
Charging to 200.
you got it?
Clear.
is dr. Burke alive?
Yes.
Shame.
He'd have probably have made a good donor.
Okay,people,
let's get our oans and get outta here.
Hey,that heart is not yours yet.
Seattle grace is still waiting for test results.
I'm not. Ten blade.
You can't do that.
I just did.
Girls.
I called jillian.
And I called tessa.
And then they called simon and
bianca and deborah.
Girls--
it's her prom,dr. Webber.
She can't miss her whole prom.
So...
we,like,brought it toer.
kids...
listen up.
Look,I know you wanted to see camille.
Why don't you come back tomorrow,
during the day,
in smaller groups?
Look,I'm sorry,girls.
I can't have a bunch of teenagers
running in the hallways.
People are sick.
People are dy--
dying?
we know.
How you doin'?
I'm developing numbness in my...
fourth and fifth fingers.
And there's a pseudoaneurysm in the
subclavian artery.
You know the drill.
We'll wait a few days,
maybe the aneurysm won't grow.
Even if it stays this size,
there's too much damage.
We'll just go in there and we'll fix it,
relieve the compression on the nerves.
But the operation could cause damage
to the nerves.
Yes.
And I could...
lose function of the entire arm.
y-yes.
you can do this?
Are you good enough to do this?
I think so.
But you're not sure.
But I'm not sure.
So...
what do I do?
It's not like you to ask those
kind of questions.
It's not like you not to have the answers.
How dare you send those kids away?
Adele,please...
you're emotional,okay?
I just told my sister her baby's
cancer is back.
You're damn right i'm emotional.
If you don't want to bend your
precious rules for camille,fine.
Don't do it for her.
Do it for me.
Do it for your wife who never
asks you for anything,
who says nothing about your long hours,
who looks the other way
while you have an affair with another woman,
who sobered you up when that woman left you,
who stayed with you when everyone--
everyone said I would be better off alone.
I'm not asking you,
I'm telling you.
You're gonna make this up to camille.
You're gonna prioritize the needs of your family
above those of your other patients.
Or...
you're gonna find a new place to sleep.
derek.
Not now,addison.
Derek.
Not now.
there's never a good place
to hide in this hospital.
I'm trying to get perspective.
Everything feels enormous,like it's all...
just--
I-I can't get perspective.
My niece's cancer has come back.
She's 17 years old,
and she's gonna die.
Plus...
25 years ago,
I had a secret affair with...
ellis grey.
And today I find out that my
wife knew the entire time.
There was no...
secret.
And she stayed with me.
I respect him,you know?
Dr. Burke--I...
I respect him.
He's decent. He's honorable.
He's an arrogant ass who just hogs the O.R.
And he thinks he's god,but...
he's decent and he's honorable.
I respect him.
He's one of the foremost cardiothoracic
surgeons in the country,
and I've gotta just...
it's his hand.
I cannot get perspective.
I can't do this.
I can't be responsible for him.
Preston's an honorable and decent man,
but,derek,so are you.
You are honorable and decent.
And you're too honorable and decent to run.
You don't know how much i wish this was bourbon.
Anything I can get for you,dr. Burke?
No.
I'm fine.
No,there--there must be something.
Oh,it would be nice to...
have some ice chips and,
a touch of morphine if I'm allowed...and,
cristina.
Comin' right up.
Where is cristina?
Where are--
where are all of the suck ups?
Excuse me?
My interns--
my ass-kissin',surgery hungry,
competitive suck ups,
where are they?
Why aren't they here fetching you
ice chips and morphine?
Why aren't they here sucking up?
You know something.
I'm a patient.
Preston xavier burke...
what have you done with my suck ups?
what do we do?
What do we do?
I'm starting dopamine and dobutamine drips.
we can use those together,right?
What about milrinone?
I don't know.
You know,none of us know.
Just start the dobutamine and--
what about neseritide?That might help.
I feel like my chest is running away.
heart rate 217.
He's in S.V.T.
No,no,izzie,stop pumping.
Stop.
No,there's no change.
We need that medicine.
What medicine?
I'll know it when I see it.
I-I think--the one that stops the heart.
Here,hold the mask.
No,the whole point is to keep
my heart beating.
No,no,no,it only stops your heart
for six seconds--
meredith,it's adenosine.
his heart is speeding up,guys.
You guys,we have to do something!
He cannot take this for much longer.
What about shocking him?
-I don't--
-found it.
Cristina,come over here.
Okay.
Lift up his arm.
The nurses always lift the arm
when they push adenosine.
It gets to the heart faster.
Okay,denny,you're gonna feel,um--
izzie!
No,it's okay.
It's okay.
It just feels like--
I'm gonna die.
You're not gonna die.I promise.
It's just the meds.
We're heading back to flatline.
Are you sure we used the right drug?
the book said it was the right one.
I used the one I know.
He's not gonna die,right?
Right?
Right ?
You fools better have a good explanation
for this.
Step away from the patient.
I can'T.
I have to pump his heart.
Olivia...
take over for dr. Stevens.
Izzie,you're done here.
I need you to leave the room.
-Izzie--
no,do not touch me!
Olivia,stay...
with dr. Stevens.
Help her if she'll let you.
You three,outside.
Now!
where was rational thought?
Where was cognitive thinking?
Where was first do no harm?
The morals,the ethics--
where was sanity when you three
decided to help that girl?
-We didn't--
no,no.
No speaking.
Nobody speaks.
I do not want to have to testify against
any of you in a court of law.
Not one word.
She cut his lvad wire.
look,I said no speaking.
I didn't say anything!
I said no moving.
Cristina,
burke is asking for you.Go.
I'm assuming you ran labs?
I'm asking a question.
Answer me!
You said no speak--
I know what I said.
Yes.
O'malley,
get me the lab results.
Do not pass go,
do not talk to another living soul.
Get the labs,get back here.
Grey...
come with me.
how are you?
You look good.
Are those your films?
burke.
Shepherd,
doesn't know if he can fix my hand.
But maybe I'll wait it out,
see if this numbness subsides.
Or I could let shepherd operate.
I could lose all hand function.
What if I could never operate again?
Cristina.
Stop saying "yeah."
Okay.
I need...
you said you were here...
for me.
Oh,sorry.
Cristina.
I need you to tell me...
what you think I should do.
I...
I-I told dr. Bailey that I would
be back,okay?
I-I told her that I--
I wouldn't be long,okay?
Cristina.
I'm--I'm--
I'm gonna think about it.
I...
I'm gonna think about it,
okay?
how you feelin',denny?
Really,really good,
like an athlete or a superhero
or some other kind of really healthy person.
You're funny.
You're a funny guy.
izzie,no speaking.
I cut my own lvad wires,you know?
I went rogue,
all my myself.
Shush.
You're weak enough as it is.
Please don't waste energy on lying.
Dr. Bailey.
I did indeed say no speaking.
I don't care.
He's gna get the heart,right?
You're gonna sign the charts
and talk to the transplant coordinator?
Here are the labs.
See?
See,his B.U.N.
And creatinine are increasing.
He clearly has pulmonary edema.
He deserves to move up to 1a status
on the transplant list.
U.N.O.S. Will give him the heart.
You just need to call.
Isobel stevens,
I take my medical advice from doctors.
You are a visitor.
What?
As of now,you are a visitor in this hospital.
You will not be a doctor in this hospital again
until I decide you are.
Olivia,
take over the heart pump.
He gets the heart,though,right?
Sir
i need to ask you a hypothetical question.
Can't we do this another time?
if someone on the staff deliberately
unhooked a transplant candidate
from his lvad in an attempt to worsen
his condition
and get him moved up the donor list,
hypothetically,sir...
I think you need to tell me exactly
what's going on here,doctor.
Believe me,sir,
you want this totay a hypothetical,
because I'm thinking if something
like that did happen,
you'd be duty-bound to report it,
and the hospital would be in danger of losing
its accreditation as a transplant site.
So hypothetically...
hypothetically,
if the patient got worse,
would it be unethical for him to
receive the heart,
even tugh,medically,
his worsened condition  now puts
him at the top of the donor list...
hypothetically?
How bad is he?
In the few hours it would take
a new lvad to be delivered,
he'll be dead.
Our responsibility is to the patient.
If,medically,
he's at the top of the list,
then he should get the heart.
Hypothetically.
Thank you,sir.
But practically,
whoever removed the patient from the lvad,
I expect to be given names,
and there will be severe,
severe consequences.
Yes,sir.
wait. Hold on.
Dr. Hahn.
Can't stop now,karev.
I only have a few hours to get
this heart into my guy.
Dr. Hahn.
U.N.O.S. Gave the heart to seattle grace.
The transplant coordinator already called
and stopped your guy from being prepped.
Oh,come on.
He has kids.
They're 4 and 5.
Do you know how long he's been
waiting for this?
He's a good person.
He deserves a heart.
I'm sorry.
I'll bet you are.
No,I am.
Believe me.
Listen...
we have a chopper waiting on the roof.
And?
You could take up fishing.
I don't fish.
Fishing's a lot more fun than surgery.
I have 80% hand function now.
80% is not enough.
Not for you.
Fishing,huh?
You don't fish.
Shepherd.
You don't have to thank me.
I'm sure you'll return the favor one day.
I was going to say please try not to kill me.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
Look at that thing.
The left ventricle's excessively dilated.
He wouldn't have lasted another
hour with this heart.
No,he wouldn't have.
okay,retract that a little bit rht here.
Okay,I am now removing the aneurysm
from the nerve cluster.
N.A.P.S are dropping.
Arterial pressure's down 50%.
did you cut the nerve root?
I don't see any discontinuity of the nerves.
All right,let's do a,
reflex test on his hand.
Chief.
Okay.
Nothing.
Okay. Try it again.
This doesn't make sense.
I would know if I severed a nerve.
Derek,
is the arm paralyzed?
i'm gonna have to do a wake-up test.
Derek--
there's only one person
who can help me figure out
whether or not I've damaged the relay or not,
and that's burke.
He's been through a lot of trauma today.
I'm trying to prevent the trauma he's gonna feel
if I have to tell him he's paralyzed.
Bailey's treating us like we're children.
We're not children.
We shouldn't have to sit out here
like we're on a time-out or something.
It is a time-out.
What we did is way in need of a time-out.
You realize we could get kicked
out of the program for this?
Not "we."
I did this.
I did this .
And you're probably right.
Maybe I should run.
But I'd rather be running towards
somebody than running away.
yang,
shep's asking for you.
Uh,for burke's surgery?
Yes. Hurry up.
I-I can'T.I'M...
I'm in a time-out.
Time-out's over,
right now.
Yes,sir.
Yang,we need you.
He said,"marry me," right?
He did?
That really happened?
It really happened.
It really did.
Screw this.
I'm checking on denny.
okay.
How are we doing?
He's just at the edge of consciousness.
Very light.
He should be up soon.
Okay.
Yang,you're up.
Oh. What? Sorry.
What do you need me to do?
When he comes to,
he's gonna be disoriented,
and he's probably gonna fight the intubation.
We can't numb the arm
because we need him to move his fingers,
so he's gonna be in a lot of pain.
So we need you to keep him focused,okay?
Okay.
Okay,let's--
let's wake him up.
Burke.
Thank you for calling me about izzie.
I-I didn't do you any favors.
it meant something.
That you called meant something to me.
It didn't mean anything.
Right.
Okay.
Sorry.
Stop saying that you're sorry!
You wanna know something?
I knew.
I knew you didn't feel that way about me...
even during...
when we were in bed,I knew.
I knew,and I still let it happen because,um...
I figured that...
one night with you was better than never.
So...
you just stop saying that you're sorry,
'cause you didn't know any better.
But I did.
And...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,meredith.
Burke,it's cristina.I--
I'm sorry I...
wake up.
Wake up.
burke.
Baby,wake up.
Do it for me.
Open your eyes.
Hi.
Hi .
get ready,get ready.
Hold him down.
Calm him down.
-yang!
-Calm him down.
Get in front of him.
Cristina,get in there.
Cristina,get in his face.
Talk to him. Cristina!
Yang!
Get in there!
Hold him down,hold him down.
-Yang!
-You have to calm him down.
Cristina!
scissors.
beautiful work,dr. Hahn.
The hard part is still to come.
All right,let's start taking him off bypass.
Let's see if this heart will beat on its own.
nothing.
All right.
Come on,denny.
Beat for me.
cristina!
Hold his arm down,chief.
Hold his arm.
Preston.
Preston,look at me.
Look at me.
Right here.
Listen,listen,ca down.
Calm down. Calm down.
Listen...
there was a complication.
We can fix it.
We need you to move your fingers
on your right side.
Can you do that?
You can do this.
Look at me.
On your right hand,okay?
*****
It's just you and me.
I know we can do this.
Okay,
focus.
focus
Now you gotta move your fingers
on your right hand.
Can you do that?
Come on,preston,you can do it.
Move your finger
move your fingers.
Come on.
Come on .
Come on.Come on.Come on.....
no response.
Charge to 20.
Clear.
come on.
Come on,
come on,
--------------------------
www.ydy.com/bbs
Proudly Presents
--------------------------
Sync: YTET-xjeff0
-==www.ydy.com/bbs==-
Greys.Anatomy.
Season 02 Episode 27