Previously on
"grey's anatomy"...
I slept with george.
It was a horrible mistake.
I'm done. We're done.
Pancakes?
he's not my roommate.
This is why I shouldn't
have given up my place.
He would still be our roommate
if meredit would just apologize.
You know,at some point,you are
going to have to talk to me.
your ex did
a real number on you,huh?
-You didn't call me.
-I did. I did.
A few times.
I just hung up every time.
How is she today?
She's great.
She really lights up
when dr. Webber visits.
Denny,your congestive heart failure
is getting worse despite the meds.
We need more time.
www.ydy.com/bbs
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-gagegao
-==www.ydy.com/bbs==-
my college campus
has a magic statue.
It's a long-standing tradition
for students to rub its nose for good luck.
My freshman roommate really
believed in the statue's power
and insisted on visiting it
to rub its nose before every exam.
Are you sure my scrub caps
aren't in the laundry delivery?
I triple checked.
-You're sure?
-Yeah,I'm sure.
Studying might have been
a better idea.
She flunked out
her sophomore year.
but the fact is,we all have
little superstitious things that we do.
all right,everybody
it's a beautiful morning to save lives,
people,okay? Let's have some fun.
If it's not believing
in magic statues,
it's avoiding sidewalk cracks or
always putting
our left shoe on first...
knock on wood...
10 blade.
Step on a crack,
break your mother's back.
paddles.
10 joules.
he's having a reaction.
I need to take him off.
I'm in the middle
of his brain.
We're losing him.
time of death...
call it,grey.
The last thing we want to do
is offend the gods.
Time of death--8:17.
four surgeries,four fatalities,
and the day's barely started.
Could I have a bite of that?
No,you're in my apartment.
You don't get to be in my food.
Dr. Burke gave me
a protein bar this morning.
Burke packs his lunch for him.
Did I mention?
talked to
the morgue guy this morning.
The one with the unibrow?
The one with the,like,teeth thing.
And he said that surgical fatalities
come in threes and sevens.
Says there'll be three more
before midnight.
Well,okay,then,
since dead tooth morgue guy said so.
He's the morgue guy.
He knows things about death.
You dropped this.
He's still ignoring me.
ignore him back.
Derek says I should apologize
until he listens.
"Derek says."
It's good advice.
He's my friend.
That's good friend advice.
Meredith...
what?
Did you sneak out
last night?
Yeah. I,uh...
I couldn't sleep.
-Come on.
-Where?
-E.R.
-All of us?
We've all had deaths.
Let's all go save a life.
Uh,dr. Bailey.
Here you go.
-What's this?
-Hot cocoa.
It's a little ritual
we had in new york.
Four surgeries,four deaths.I figure
we could all use a little good juju.
And cocoa equals juju how?
don't question the cocoa.
Carry on.
Meredith...
thank you for your help
this morning.
Oh,thank you,addison.
Yeah.
You know,thank you.
here you go.
-Juju.
-Yep.
-You jujued meredith.
-I did...
in the spirit of friendship.
What,are we not being friends
with meredith anymore?
No,no,we are.
Meredith and i are friends.
Yeah,and you and i
are married.
So then by proxy,
meredith and I are friends.
That's very big of you.
you don't have to do that.
It's not like I'm gonna be friends with,
let's say,uh...
mark.
Yeah,well,neither am I.
Now finish your juju
before somebody else dies.
There are ten of them-- music notes,
colorful patterns,they were sent out last night.
Sorry to hear about your valve
replacement this morning.
The laundry misplaced
my scrub caps.
You know,there's some
foolish talk goin' around
about fatally clusters
in threes and sevens.
Are you sure they weren't sent
to another hospital?
How many electives
have they canceled today?
This is our third.
And what have the surgeons
been giving as their reasons?
Because I prefer
my own caps.
You're not pushing your surgeries
because you don't have your personal caps.
You understand me?
I didn't push
any surgeries.
No,no,the question is,
when will you find them?
No one changes that board
unless they talk to me.
No one.
Great. No blood,no guts,
no lives to save.
It's dead quiet.
Did you really
just say that?
-Cristina.
-What?
You said the "q" word.
That's like saying
macbeth in the theater.
Please. You think because
someone says it's quiet,
-that it'll mean--
-can someone please help us here?
-She's coughing up blood.
-O'malley,take that.
-denny duquette.
-I got it.
-He's my patient.
-He's both your patients.Answer the call.
two incoming.
okay,uh,yang,first one's yours.
Grey,take number two.
Jesse fannon,32,
unrestrained driver
in a rear end collision.
There was spider webbing
of the front windshield where his head hit.
B.P. Is 120 palp.
Pulse is 75.
what do you want to do,yang?
A primary and secondary survey,
uh,head C.T. And x-ray.
Great,page shepherd
when you get there.
Wait! I'm counting
the siren whoops.
We can't go till
it reaches 33.
He also seems to have
a touch of O.C.D.
Nikki ratlin,30,
erratic B.P. In the field,
complaining of chest
and leg pain.
-What happened?
-I got struck by lightning.
Can anyone spell
"coincidence"?
Grey's Anatomy
Season 02 Episode 22
My horoscope said,
"stay close to home today."
Aries couldn't have been
any clearer.
Okay,I guess it coulda said,
"don't leave the house today unless you
want to get struck by lightning." Ow.
See,ms. Ratlin,you have no
sign of wounds from lightning.
It was a sign.
Clearly,getting struck
by lightning is a sign.
A sign that I shouldn't
have left my house.
Nikki,normally people
struck by lightning.
Have a wound where the bolt
entered and exited the body.
Well... well,I wasn't
"struck" struck.
I--the tree was struck
and it fell on me.
A tree fell on you?
A big,like,branch
or a limb--whatever.
Same difference.
No,actually,medically,
it isn't the same difference.
And it would be helpful if,
from now on...
You told us the whole truth.
You wanna know the truth?
My boyfriend loves that tree.
He's totally gonna freak out.
Oh,chief,there's a,uh,
ms. Warner down in admitting.
She's asking for you.
Who?
Um,olive warner?
50s,uh,blonde hair.
She said she's known you
for about 20 years.
Are you taking about ollie?
RighT. Okay.
Uh,ollie warner--
she presented with,uh,
upper G.I. Bleeding.
And she had a T.I.P.P.S.
Procedure last month for esophageal varices.
I'll take this from here,
o'malley.
I'm happy to help,sir.
No,thank you.
I got this myself.
Ollie.
hi! richard.
It's good to see you.
sinus tachycardia,
low grade fever,
pulse ox 75.
I'm hearing rales
in your lungs.
Yeah,a freight train
rolls through at noon.
How bad is the pain?
I don't know.
A five or six when I breathe.
That means a seven or eight when you're
not trying to impress your doctor.
I heard,uh,
four people died in surgery this morning.
Said they were expecting
three more.
You get that from a nurse?
Never reveal my sources.
Just like to avoid the O.R.
And I'm not liking
that look.
This could be
a pulmonary embolism,denny--
a complication
from the lvad surgery.
We're gonna have to talk
to dr. Burke.
I got hot chocolated.
The she-shepherd
hot chocolated me.
It's her juju.
I don't like people
who say juju.
I say juju.
Juju,juju,juju.
Juju,juju,juju...
I didn't drink it.
You're not obligated to honor
some else's juju.
thought you were
being friends.
I am,with him.
Do I have to be friends
with her,too?
Definitely not
maybe.
I'll,uh,call psych
for you.
That would be good,
thanks.
All right,
that's the worst of it.
Oh,I never should've
gotten out of bed. Oh!
But I really wanted
to surprise my boyfriend
before he left for school.
He had a huge exam today,
and I just,you know,
I wanted to wish him luck.
Dr. Torres,hey.
Hi. Uh,can I give you a hand?
You missed the boat,
george.
You mean on this case or...
or a hot chick gives you her number,
you're supposed to call.
-Yeah.
-right. I was.
-I mean,I am.
-Too late.
Ouch. Don't give up.
I mean,
if you really like her.
Okay...
Okay,the plot thickens.
Nikki,dr. Grey here
is gonna take you upstairs for a C.T.
But before she does,
I have to ask,
you're bruised all up and down
your left side.
You sure a tree branch
did all this?
You think my boyfriend
did this?
He would never hit
a woman,ever.
The bruising doesn't
look like a tree branch hit you.
Fine.
Okay,you guys are gonna think
I'm really weird,
but I was sort of up in the tree
when the lightning hit,
and,well...you climbed a tree
in a thunderstorm?
I really wanted it to be
a surprise,you know,
for my boyfriend,and,
um,I just...I had to see if his psycho dog
was in the yard
because of,like,
the barking and stuff and...
I know.It sounds really weird.
Does it sound really weird?
-Not at all.
-No.
And the thing is,
I mean,he wasn't even there.
The dog?
No,my boyfriend.
He wasn't even home.
I really shouldn't
have gotten out of bed.
Oh,dr. Shepherd.
I've got a 34-year-old male with a blunt
head trauma and severe case of O.C.D.
Oh,really? Did you call
for a psych consult?
-Yes.
-All right,let me know when you get his C.T.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Hey.
Hey,uh,sorry about that,
uh,valve replacement.
Oh,thank you.
The laundry lost my caps.
The guy didn't die because you weren't wearing
one of your caps.
Fine,I know that.
I just prefer...
to operate wearing my own.
It's a comfort thing.
Huh. Well...
I prefer having george
out of our apartment.
So I guess we both have
comfort things.
What are you saying?
Uh,you know,um...
I have one of your caps
in my locker.
Why do you have one of my caps
in your locker?
Oh,that's not the point.
You know,the point is,uh,
is that I think
I'm gonna keep it hostage.
So you kick bambi out,
you get your cap back.
Oh,well,I don't do well
with ultimatums.
Maybe you should think of it
more as a trade.
Dr. Burke...
I've got free time.
Do you have any cases?
Do you need any help?
Actually,I do.
cristina has something of mine,
and I need you to get it back.
just call catherine back.
Yeah.
Gretchen,would you mind
leaving us alone for a minute?
Okay.
Thank you.
She's my new baby.
Six months sober.
She's already
on the ninth step.
You must be proud.
Always.
You're on
the transplant list,ollie?
Couple of years now.
The sclerosis prevents blood
from flowing into your liver,
so it's backing up
into your esophagus,
'causing the ruptures.
It's serious,ol.
Well,of course it is.I mean,you don't
puke blood if it's not serious.
The question is,
can you treat it?
Maybe.Surgically.
We'll have to run
more tests and...
whatever we do,
it's a stopgap.
You need a new liver.
Yet another reason I shoulda
laid off the sauce.
you look scared.
I am scared,ollie.
I haven't seen you
at a meeting in awhile.
I know,I know.
How have you been?
We're talking about you.
Now I'm asking about you.
Ellis grey's daughter
is working at the hospital.
Ellis is in a nursing home
with alzheimer'S.
I try to go see her
every chance I get.
You're having an affair
with the woman
who drove you
to your alcoholic bottom?
Ollie,we're not having an affair.
She's sick.
-You're lying to your wife?
-I'm not lying.
You're lying by omission.
You are having
an emotional affair
and now you're lying
to your sponsor about it.
You haven't been my sponsor
in years.
I still have the right
to bust your ass
if I see you slipping.
I'm not slipping.
Not yet,but you're making
a pretty big mess.
How many years
you have now?
Just passed 17.
I'm proud of you.
And I'm scared,too.
You got me sober,ollie.
You walked me through it.
And I'm gonna walk you
through this.
she still has the...
You're a pervie
little boy,george,
and you're not finding
the cap.
I'll do your dishes
for a month.
-I don't do dishes.
-I'll do your laundry.
I don't do laundry.
Maybe that's why burke likes
having me around so much.
Interesting,interesting.
Are you having sex with him?
No.
Then he likes having me
around more.
Why does it always
have to be a competition?
-What do you want for the cap?
-You outta the apartment.
I'm not leaving till burke
says I have to leave.
Then you're not getting the cap.
Now clean up my crap.
No.
Wow. Is that her spleen?
Looks like a grade iii laceration,
maybe a iv.
What was she doing standing under a tree
in a thunderstorm?
She wasn't standing under it.
She was climbing it.
Why?
Uh...
I'm getting the feeling
she's a little bit of a stalker.
Do we need to call the police?
I don't think so.
I think she's more of a "gentle" stalker
than a "kill you with a knife" stalker.
Right.
Well,let's hope she lives
to gently stalk another day.
Hey,you don't believe in
that seven fatally thing,do you?
I believe this girl needs
her spleen removed immediately.
Go pick up her labs
and get her on the board.
Then we'll break the news.
it's almost over.
You like horses,izzie?
Everybody likes horses.
That's not true.
You know,horses are
a great judge of character.
You don't like horses,
it means they don't like you.
I've got an uncle
that's a rodeo cowboy.
No kiddin'?
This is a big clot,denny.
I can't get it
with a catheter.
I'm sorry.We're gonna have to open
your chest again.
I was counting the clicks--
the turn signal clicks.
I couldn't move
till it hit 333.
The light was green,
but I couldn't move.
I can't blame them
for hitting me.
How long have you been feeling
these compulsions?
A little bit all my life,but it's been
out of control the last three years.
Onset at 30 is typical.
Ruined a marriage.
I can't hold a job.
mr. Fannon,
do you--
is it clean?
-I need to know if it's clean.
-It's very clean.
Any relatives with O.C.D.?
My mother.
Killed herself at 38.
It ruined her life,
now it's ruining mine.
clean,clean clean?
I--we clean it
between each patient.
I think he needs you to say,
"clean,clean,clean."
It's clean,clean,clean.
Thank you.
I know it's annoying.
I can't help it.
Find a penny,pick it up.
All day long,
you'll have good luck.
Find a penny,pick it up.
All day long,
you'll have good luck.
Mr. Fannon,
do you want--
repetitive rhymes,prayers--
it's classic.
He feels he needs to say it
a specific number of times,
probably a multiple of three.
Let's get him in before
he decides to start again.
Is everything all right
with,uh,that?
Find a penny,pick it up.
All day long,
you'll have good luck.
Just don't look at him.
Hey.
Hi.
-Hey--
-oh,hey.
-Hi.
I,uh... have to
-yeah.
-Yeah.
I do,too.
Yeah,I got something,too,
so...
I wish I had good news.
The T.I.P.P.S. Procedure
you had last month failed.
What does that mean?
It means you're lucky
you got sober young.
Ollie,it means I'm gonna
have to put in a portacaval shunt.
It's complicated.
Has only a 50%
survival rate.
What's my other choice?
Okay,then.  Um...
you'll be the one
to do it?
I've performed this surgery
nine times,
had four patients survive.
It's perfect then.
I'll be your five out of ten.
I'm not having surgery today.
You have a ruptured spleen.
And I am sure that the spleen
is very important,
but I am not
having surgery today.
You can operate after midnight,
but not one minute before.
Ms. Ratlin,if I thought
it would be safe,
I'd be more than happy
to wait till after midnight.
However,I have a husband
and a baby at home who won't be happy.
You know who else
won't be happy? You.
Your spleen is bleeding.
Spleen trumps horoscope.
But it was more
than just my horoscope.
I went out to my car this morning--
flat tire.
That's a sign,
but I just changed the tire.
Then there's a wreck
on the freeway.
Do I turn around and go home
like it's telling me to? No.
I detour an hour
out of my way
so that I can get
to kevin's house.
And when I get to kevin's house,
I get struck by lightning.
But you weren't struck
by lightning.
I'll die,okay?
If you operate on me today,
I will die.
'Cause I know I will.
Please,just...
just call my boyfriend
and tell him that I'm having
an operation at midnight,
because he will want
to be here.
Okay.
Please.
Should I call psych?
You can give it a shot.
In the meantime,get her down to I.C.U.
Poor girl's gonna kill herself
tryin' not to die.
Izzie paints a pretty picture
'cause she likes you,you know?
Okay.
I'm just sayin',
she likes you.
Which is gonna be hard
on her.
You mean...
when I die?
Come on...
I'm askin' you,
man-to-man.
With a clot
in your pulmonary artery,
it'll cut off the oxygen
to your lungs and you'll die of hypoxia.
If the hypoxia doesn't kill you,
the strain on your heart will.
And the surgery?
It's not a routine procedure.
You're at serious risk
for bleeding
because of the anticoagulants
already in your system.
What I'm saying
is izzie likes you.
And she's not gonna be
the one to pull away.
XXXXXXXX Wanna know why?
'Cause he couldn't move his car
until he stopped counting.
My girl--ruptured spleen--
won't have surgery
because of her horoscope.
Oh. Well,we should
introduce them.
They'd make a nice,
crazy couple.
Oh,you know what?
I'm sitting with meredith.
Have some self-respect.
Dr. Burke's orders trump any
personal issues I might have.
Is the craziness
rubbing off on him?
He's trying to stalk
burke's lucky cap out of me.
Burke has hat juju?
Apparently.
And you're using it
against him?
Well,
they're forcing me to...
because of
the clarinet playing
and the running
and all the breakfast food.
You guys...
this whole death cluster thing
is just ridiculous,right?
I mean,just 'cause
four died today
doesn't necessarily mean there's
gonna be three more before midnight.
-It doesn't,tinkerbell?
-For reals?
Are you worried about denny?
Yeah. Of course I am.
He's my patient.
I mean,if you're asking me
if I'm "worried about denny," no.
I'm sleeping with alex,so...
it's just...
hey,did burke say anything to you
about denny's surgery?
Did he?
No,it's your case.
Yeah. I know.
I'm just asking,you know,
as your boyfriend,did he--
well,I don't know
why you care.
I mean,you're sleeping
with alex,right?
Yeah.
Right. Whatever.
I'm just saying...
there's no such thing
as a death cluster.
It's just stupid. Right?
I have to go convince
my patient to let us operate.
You're removing
part of my skullcap?
Do you really
have to do that?
It's the only way I can get to
the affected part of the brain.
And the operating room,
it's clean,clean,clean?
Yes,it's clean,
clean,clean.
I'm gonna go get ready.
Can you stop that,please?
No. Sorry.
I wish I could.
She's judging me.
-No,she's not.
-Yes,she is.
I've been living with this
for three years,
and it's always the people
who are most like me who judge me the most.
You're type "a," right?
Straight-a student,
top of your class?
Yes,I was.
Well,so you've managed to turn your
compulsions into something productive.
But we're cut
from the same cloth.
That's why
you can't stand me.
Oh,time to go.
-But I'm not done.
-Uh,yes,you are,sir.
How many do you have to do?
-96.
-Let him finish.
Fine. I'll see you
in the O.R.
hey. Ollie says
you should come in.
She says you need
a meeting.
Not now,not here.
Yeah,except she said to tell you not to
protect your anonymity over your sobriety.
god...
grant me the serenity
to accept the things
that I cannot change,
the courage to change
the things I can
and the wisdom
to know the difference.
-Amen.
Amen.
Hey.
How are you feelin'?
Do me a favor.
My will is inside
my nightstand.
Just make sure it gets
in the right hands,okay?
Why are you talking
about your will?
We have to be realistic,
dr. Stevens.
Dr. Stevens?
We gotta be realistic.
And if you can't,
well,I can.
No,wait. Um,can you
just wait one minute?
Denny,denny,
listen to me,
you're not gonna die.
You can't go into surgery
thinking you're gonna die.
You want me to pee in front
of you? Is that what you want?
-You have it on you.
-Oh,really,you wanna go there?
I wanna go there.
So what are you gonna do,bambi?
You gonna,like,what,take it from me?
Well,burke said to do
whatever I have to do,
and I am gonna do whatever
I have to--
george,it's not there.
It's not there.
-no,you're not gonna get it.
-Maybe it's in here.
You're not gonna get it. No.
I got it. I got it.
Oh,you're getting my breast.
That's my breast,my breast.
My breast.That's my breast,damn it.
hey,dr. Torres.
Dr. O'malley,you're aware
this is the women's restroom?
-Yes,ma'am.
-Good.
Dude,
you called her "ma'am."
She's never gonna sleep
with you now.
Oh,hey.
Have you seen burke?
He's on the phone
with the laundry.
They still can't find
his scrub caps.
That's what I gotta tell him.
Cristina won't give hers back.
Unless I'm ready
to hit a woman,
and even though
it's cristina,
I'm not ready
to cross that line.
Wait. Wait a moment.
Cristina has one of burke's
scrub caps?
She's holding it hostage.
Why do you think I am stalking her?
ow. Ow.
You're touching me.
George says you have
burke's scrub cap.
-So?
-Give it to him.
-No.
-Give it to him,cristina.
-What is with you?
-He needs it to operate.
-No,he doesn'T.
-That isn't your decision to make,
not when he's going in
on denny.
Now are you gonna give it to him or
am I gonna physically take it from you?
Are you threatening me?
I swear to god,cristina,
I like you,I really do,
but I grew up
in a trailer park,
and I am not above kicking
your pampered little beverly hills ass.
And I do mean physically
kicking your ass.
you don't have to follow me.
Thank you.
How long
have you had this?
It's one of my favorites.
You know,
you don't need it.
I keep that cap in my locker
because every morning,
I look at it,
and I'm reminded
of what I'm here for
and what I want to be--
a great surgeon,
a surgeon who is decisive
and who executes
and who doesn't need a piece of clothing
to give him an edge in surgery.
You don't need it.
I know.
You're right.
I know I'm right.
Nicely done,o'malley.
Let's go scrub in.
How am I doin'?
Nikki,is it possible
you're misreading the signs?
I mean,isn't two surgeons
telling you
that you need surgery
a sign
that you need surgery?
Did you call my boyfriend?
I did.
What did he say?
He said he hasn't been
your boyfriend in awhile.
Did you tell him
I got struck by lightning?
-What did you say to him?
-Who?
You know who.
What the hell?
Why does denny think he's dying?
Well,maybe 'cause there's
a good chance he is.
Just so we're clear,
we're over,alex.
This is over.
Oh,you're breaking up
with me over a corpse.
No! No.
I am breaking up with you
because on
your very best day...
that corpse...
is twice the man
you will ever be.
You're not good enough
for me,alex.
for anyone.
You two...
you're not scrubbing in.
Whatever is going on with you,
I don't need it in my O.R.
Fine.
I'll watch from the gallery.
No,no,you won'T.
You will take your energy
as far away from my O.R. As you can get.
Both of you.
Find a penny,pick it up.
All day long,
you'll have good luck.
Find a penny,pick it up.
All day long,
you'll have good luck...
we're gonna give you
your anesthetic now.
I'm sorry,
but we have to start.
Find a penny,pick it up.
All day long...
it's a beautiful afternoon
for saving lives,people.
Let's have some fun.
The incision begins along
the left subcostal margin,
across the right rectus
and extending well into the flank.
Dr. Bailey.
It's nikki ratlin.
I'll be all right,
dr. Bailey. Go.
She's bleeding out.
We need to get her
to the O.R. Now.
I don't want
an operation.
Nikki,
your boyfriend called.
He said he doesn't
want you to die.
Kevin called?
Yes. Now will you
let us operate?
Nikki.
Code blue.
Charge to 200.
Hang more blood.
Clear.
We have the back row
of sutures in place.
Give me some...
clear field.
-Pressure's dropping.
-Hang another unit.
I need the field clear.
Clear.
charge to 300.
Gel foam.
That clip should've done it.
I don't know.
There's something I'm missing.
He's losing pressure,
dr. Burke.
I'm working
as fast as I can.
We're losing him.
I heard they're dying
left and right.
See? I told you
there'd be seven.
Who? Who died?
I don't know.
I bet it was that spleen chick.
You hear she wouldn't
let them operate?
My money's on
the chief's shunt.
I have $20 says
burke's guy went down.
The dude is
a walking time bomb.
bet.
that makes five.
You lost her?
Yeah.
I heard
there's a number six.
Do you know who else?
No.
I'm going
to inform the family.
She made it through.
thank you.
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
You're welcome.
superstition lies in the space
between what we can control
and what we can'T.
so I wasn't one of the seven.
It's past midnight.
There were only six.
You cryin'?
I'm not crying.
You are,too.
Oh,damn it.
I cannot fall
for a patient.
Oh. Okay.
Good luck with that.
Find a penny,pick it up
and all day long,
you'll have good luck.
o'malley...
you are a sad excuse for a man.
Excuse me?
I know you heard me.
You're like a whiny little girl.
Alex...
you know why he's not
speaking to you.
Because he's not over you.
Man,you got laid.
It went badly.
A man would move on.
But you--you mope
around this place like a dog
that likes to get kicked.
You make me sick!
And if it wouldn't get me
thrown outta the program,
I'd smash your pathetic little face
right into that locker.
No one wants to pass up
a chance for good luck.
But does saying it 33 times
really help?
Is anyone really listening?
If you feel that strongly about o'malley,
I'll ask him to leave tonight.
No,don'T.
-I thought you wanted him out.
-I do,but...
not tonight.
Scrub cap.
Oh. Thank you.
And if no one's listening,
why do we bother doing
those strange things at all?
Hi.
I didn't call.
I shoulda called.
I just...
hi...this is
george o'malley calling.
You gave me
your phone number.
I know I shoulda called sooner,
but I'm calling now.
And I just want to know,
maybe you want to go out
with me sometime.
Because...
I...love to watch you
set bones.
And I--oh,I rarely spend
that much time
in a women's restroom.
And...
I really like you.
So...
is that a yes?
We rely on superstitions
because we're smart enough to know
we don't have
all the answers...
-hey.
-Hey.
I'm sorry to hear about
your patient.
Thank you,addison.
And that life works
in mysterious ways.
Here you go,babe.
thank you.
-You ready?
-Yeah.Here you go. Thank you.
Don't dis the juju...
from wherever it comes.
Grey's Anatomy  Season 02 Episode 22
-=THE END=-
www.ydy.com/bbs
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-gagegao