You got the
crescent wrench?
Fucking thing, nobody
ever puts it back-
oh, my god.
Oh, my god!
Tony!
Oh, my god, tony,
are you alright?
Uncle ben.
What happened?
Hey.
What are you
doing here?
We had to
drive out here
'cause some schmuck st
the vcr from the common room.
"Public enemy",
this is a great movie.
For a class.
..just finished.
We're out of here.
40 grand a year to
watch old movies?
Who's "we"?
Just a friend
from class, okay?
Your mom
likes lavender.
I'll be ready
to bolt in a sec.
Mr. Soprano?
Yeah.
Hey, i'm
noah tannenbaum.
How ya doin'?
I appreciate you
letting us screen here.
Those bose direct reflectors
make all the difference.
You a film buff?
People say hawks invented
the genre with "scarface",
but cagney
was modernity.
Muni was not, so i giv
e the nod to william wellman.
Noah, i'm just gonna g
rab the "barenaked ladies" cd,
and then,
let's hit the road.
Last year this course
is being offered.
"Images of
hypercapitalis
t self- advancement
in the era of
the studio system."
So, you guys...
you and meadow...
are you...?
Little early to say.
What's your background,
noel?
Noah.
I'm from los angeles,
west l. A.
What i mean is--
my family'
s in the business.
I mean show business
, i don't know why the
y call it "the business".
Those old
"tarzan" movies?
My dad's an
entertainment lawyer.
What i mean is,
we're italian.
My dad is jewish
and my mother's family
is african- american.
"Tannenbaum",
right.
But on your application
to columbia,
you didn't check
jewish, did you?
No, they can't ask abo
ut religious affiliation.
Oh, right, right,
of course.
What'd you check?
African- american.
So, we do understand
each other here?
You're a ditsoon.
Excuse me?
Uh, charcoal briquette,
a mulignan.
What's your problem?
I think you know
what my problem is.
You see, your little
friend up there.
She didn't do you any favors
bringing you into this house.
I don't know what the
fuck she was thinking.
We'll get to
that later.
See, i got business
associates who are black.
And they don't want my son
with their daughters
and i don't want
their sons with mine.
Fuck you!
See, that's the kind of thing
i'm hoping to avoid.
So, when my little girl
comes down the stairs,
you're gonna say how
nice it was to meet me.
Then you're gonna go
drop her off at school
and you're gonna
say goodbye.
C'mon, if you want to
see the garden state.
We're gonna drop by hunter's,
i want her to meet noah.
Then we'll be back
to pick up my laundry.
Later, dad.
I don't got time f
or these fucking attacks.
You were so good
for months.
If you didn't
instigate things--
i instigate?
He's just
a new friend, tony.
You didn't see the way they
were looking at each other.
You want her to be with
him, just keep it up.
Keep playi
ng the race card,
you're gonna drive her
right into his arms.
Not if i cut off
those fucking arms.
Stop it!
Let me deal with it,
if anybody's gonna
deal with it.
Make things wors
e with your bullshit,
i'm gonna
be really pissed.
I should
call cusamano.
You might need
stitches.
Yeah, if one
of my sisters
ever brought home
a fuckin' butterhead,
you know what my
old man would do?
Hey, ma.
Look who calls.
Actually, i'm standing
here in front of you.
Ah.
Hey.
So, how's it going?
What do you care?
Out of sight,
out of mind.
Brought you some
books on tape.
Since you say you can't
concentrate to read.
I wish the lord
would take me now.
Well, in the meantime...
brought you "the
horse whisperer".
Why, what's wrong,
tell me?
What, are you
gonna freak out
every time i try to do
something nice for you?
Jesus.
What's this?
She's going to
finish baby journals
from long time ago.
My idea.
Oh, yeah,
i remember these.
Carmela gave you one of these
for each of the kids
when they were born.
What the fuck?
Look at this.
Supposed to fill these out,
20 years, fat fuckin' nothing.
Now, look here, i don't
like that kind of talk.
Now, just stop it,
it upsets me.
Carmela's ma returne
d these books to the kids
filled with memories.
You can't write stuff
down from your life
foryour grandkids?
It's none of
anybody's business.
Yeah, you're too busy
feeling sorry for yourself.
She will do it.
It's good for her,
she realize that.
Keep her mind active.
Why do anything if there's
not something in it for her?
Alright, listen up.
I want you to concentrate,
i know it's difficult.
Remember the
airline tickets?
The tickets
were stolen.
Did you say that or
did the feds say that?
What did you tell them
when you were in the lockup?
What?
What did i do?
This is important.
They're trying to buil
d a rico case against me.
What are you gonna say
if they put you on
the witness stand?
'Cause the only reason
they let you go
is to get
your cooperation.
Don't wave
your hanky atme.
What are you gonna say
from now on?
I never stated those tickets
were stolen, capisce?
Now, barbara will testify
i didn't say it,
but you gotta
back her up.
I suppose i should've just
kept my mouth shut...
like a mute.
In the future, any kind of
deal they try to make,
you keep
your mouth shut.
You know, for a ye
ar, i didn't speak to you.
Maybe i should've
kept it that way.
Fuck it,
do what you want.
Did you say something
to noah?
If you're smart, you'll ke
ep walking down those stairs.
You did, what
did you say?
He was all quiet at hunter's,
she thinks he's a snob.
Now he's just
sitting out in the car!
What, you didn't
hear me?
Maybe if i say it
in swahili!
Meadow, can you
come up here please?
What?
I need your help
with this clasp.
That ain't our beer,
where'd you get this?
Well, it's good,
ain't it?
Is my laundry done?
You can sell ours
for the same price.
I can't help it if
i have to buy from them.
They tell me
the same thing
that you do.
Ah, you're yella.
Ah, please, you ai
n't gonna slug me, are ya?
What?
Uh, your mother died.
You're kidding?
I mean...
jesus christ.
Svetlana just called.
She said that...
after dinner, your mother went
upstairs to get ready for bed.
When svetlana came up,
your mother was under
the covers in her nightgown.
Svetlana thought
she was asleep.
Svetlana's waiting
for us over there.
She's dead.
I'm sorry, dad...
that your mom died.
Me too.
Your grandmother
loved you.
She loved
both you two...
very much.
They just removed.
We saw.
She was in no
pain, tony.
What about the cause
of death, did they say?
Massive stroke.
Yeah.
So...
she will not be
finishing journal.
I break promise
to you, tony.
Does not oft
en happen with me,
that these old one
s get away with something.
Journal?
Nothing.
Those "granny remembers"
books you bought her
when the kids
were born.
She never
touched them.
What's your beef?
Asshole robert frost.
How am i supposed to
know what this means?
Like i even care.
"Stopping by woods
on a snowy evening".
Oh, my god, i'm so glad i'
m not in high school anymore.
You read this?
Sure.
What does it mean?
I have to turn in a
close- read by tomorrow.
What does it mean?
"The woods are lovely
dark and deep,
but i have promises
to keep and miles to
go before i sleep."
Okay, look.
Where is he?
He's in a field
on a horse.
He's not o
n the horse.
The horse has bells.
So?
What kind of horse
has bells?
I don't know!
Just give me the fucking
answer so i can write this?
A horse that's
pulling a sleigh.
Oh...
so, this is
a thanksgiving poem...
like,"over the river
and through the woods
to grandmother's
house we go".
No, it's not
a thanksgiving poem.
What's coverin
g the field?
Snow.
Yay!
And what doe
s snow symbolize?
Christmas?
Hello?
Cold...
endless white,
endless nothing...
i don't know!
Death.
I thought
black was death.
"He has miles to g
o before he sleeps."
So, he must be far away
from his house.
The sleep of death.
The big sleep.
He's talking
about his own death,
which is yet to come,
but will come.
That's fucked up.
Gottago.
I thought
black was death.
White too.
I'm coming, i'm coming!
Grandma?
I just can't believe it.
What are you
gonna do?
I'll call janice.
I'll meet you
at cozzerelli's...
around noon.
I already called.
Ma didn't want any
kind of service, tony.
No remembrance at all.
So, we'll pick out
a simple urn or whatever.
I'll see you there.
Proshai livushka.
Which means what?
Goodbye,
little livia.
He's been in this situation
a million times
and has upped
the ante when needed.
Every time.
Let's see what happens
tonight, there he is,
he's pulling thatin.
He's got the...
ton'.
I'm sorry.
We all know...
how much
you loved her.
Thanks.
I could imagine
how you feel.
Yeah, well...
what are you
gonna do?
I'm sorry, t.
What are you
gonna do, you know?
At least she
didn't suffer.
Thank go
that's right. D.
My god.
What next, huh?
How is tony
taking it?
Oh, what the fuck!
Goddamn
fucking bitch!
She was so awful.
What do i tell my kids
when their own aunt
won't even come
to a funeral?
Take it easy
, i'll handle it.
And then he goes,"you gotta
work on columbus day weekend."
Eat your eggs, baby.
Ace garage.
You're not coming to your own
mother's fucking funeral?
May i speak?
You got your
sister sobbing!
May i speak?
Go the fuck ahead!
You may recall, tony,
that i have very good
and valid reasons
why i should not present
myself in the state
of new jersey.
Oh, jesus, that case is
colder than your tit.
It'd do you good to
show up here at this point.
Nothing to hide.
I don't do well
at funerals, tony.
Who does?
You just don't wan
t to get your ass
out of whatever
chair it's in.
I'm gonna hang
the fuck up!
She didn't even want
a funeral, janice,
but can't you come
sit with your family
during this
stressful time?
She was
your mother.
You can just get on a plane
before us working folk.
Oh, listen to this,
woody guthrie over here.
You know, they got special
rates for family death.
Yeah, half of
full fare coach,
which at
this late date
comes to $1, 100.
Fully researched
and everything, huh?
Alright, fuck it,
i'll pay it.
Can i bring
my fiancee?
Fuck that!
One seat,
coach.
And if you don't show up,
let me tell you right now,
don't come
breezing in here
when it comes time
to carve up the estate.
I know you think ma's got
money buried in the house.
What are you telling people
about that other thing?
Richie?
He vanished into the
witness protection program.
It's the truth,
right, janice?
Cozzerelli's
funeral home...
noon tomorrow.
Does harper know
his grandmother died?
Him i'll pay for.
Bring him down
from montreal.
He is your son.
Hal is on the pavers,
tony, he's um...
a street person.
I'm sorry,
i didn't know.
See, you're not the
only one with problems.
Be there tomorrow.
Ain't you got
a drink in the house?
I wish--
there you go with that
wishing stuff again.
I wish you was
a wishing well...
then i could tie a bucket
to you and sink you.
Maybe you found someone
you like better.
Oh, tommy, let me
make you a cup of tea.
Listen, ma, i came ove
r to give you something.
Here, take this.
And when you need
anymore, just say so
, i'm making plenty.
We don't want your money,
i'm taking care of ma.
On two bits a week?
Ma don't go to nightclubs
and she don't drink champagne.
How do you know?
I used to dance
when i was a girl.
Money don't me
an nothing to me.
No, i guess not.
But with no heart and no
brains, that's all you've got.
You'll need it.
Tommy, tommy!
Tommy!
His mother died
last night.
No shit.
Ton', i'm so
sorry to hear.
What are you
gonna do?
I know how you feel.
We lost mom
last year.
You remember?
At least she
didn't suffer.
Ralphie, i need to
talk to you...
albert...
you too.
Vito, have
a sfogliatelle.
Carmela,
she's gone.
C'mon.
Alright, who gave
the order to torch
one of albert's trucks?
One of the trucks.
Be quiet, albert.
Talk to him, he lit up
two of my dumpsters.
What's the matter
with you?
Both of you.
We're in the newspapers
every fucking week
with this shit.
My crew...
is in line for the raritan
township contract, okay?
This guy over there keeps
whispering to albert--
your what?
What did you say?
Whose crew?
You're the boss, you
get to put in anybod
y you want over the crew.
You're a captain, ralphie,
when i say you're a captain.
And i'm gonna turn u
p my hearing aid
so i don't miss it.
Oh, you're gonna
get cute with me?
With my mother
lying dead?
Raritan township,
the recycling manage
r over there, joe...
zachary.
He knows who's in line
for that contract.
But he keeps playing
footsie with albert.
The next minute,
he's threatening to go
to the epa, bust us all.
He said that?
Alright, fix it.
No- more- fires.
Dude, i'm gonn
a ditch spanish.
I'll meet you by
the trophy case.
How could we
possibly get busted?
Don't worry
about it.
The boys' room
behind the stage?
They never check
in there.
Mr. Soprano,
janice, barb, please.
Accept my condolences.
I'll use all my powers,
all my skills.
Don't go crazy,
i mean, you know.
Then we're not envisioning
any visitation hours for mom?
Well, you see, she
didn't want any service
of any kind.
I find that
hard to accept.
Is...
is she still down at
the hospital morgue?
We brought mom
here this morning.
She's downstairs.
There's gonna be a priest
or something, though, right?
Yeah, sure,
a priest, i guess.
What would that be?
You're not hav
ing a funeral mass?
And i'm not
trying to sell here.
Well, she was catholic,
but not religious.
I thought maybe
we'd have a shindig
at the house,
you know...
after, so the grandkids
could, you know.
I don't know.
I do know what
mom's wishes were,
but not to have
a wake or a funeral?
It makes us look like
we're unloving children,
not to mention
cheapskates.
Who gives a shit
what it looks like?
The woman
expressed her wishes.
I wish to honor
my mother.
There's a lot of things
i could say right now
that i'm n
ot gonna say!
What, you think we should
do something now?
When she was young, she used
to picture her funeral.
Alright, fine, you
want to do something?
Let's just do it.
Let's just stop
talking aboutit.
Cozzerelli,
you arrange everything.
The wake, the funeral,
you send me the bill.
I want you to know,
tony, that this all
won't fall on you.
I'll do a painting for
the overleaf of the program
at the service.
Motifs from the mexican
day of the dead.
Oh, one thing i'd like
to suggest very strongly
is at the house,
everyone gathers
and each one can
voice a remembrance
or a feeling
about mom.
No, no, i don't want any of
that california bullshit.
People can drink, they
can eat some gorgonzola,
they want to yak about ma,
that's their business.
No,"i'm sorry",
"my condolences",
nothing.
Actually
, that's good.
It's a relief you'
re not saying nothing,
you want t
o know the truth.
Everybody else,
all bullshit.
Here's the thing.
I'm glad she's dead.
Not just glad,
i wished she'd die.
Wished.
I had this court
case oming up.
She might have testified
against me, so...
when i heard she was dead,
relief flooded into my veins.
How do you feel about
the fact that your own mother
would have testified
against you?
Oh, c'mon, will yo
u listen to yourself?
I mean, is that right,
wishing her dead?
Is that bein
g a good son?
A good son?
Yeah, a good son.
I mean, bad sons...
bad sons, what?
They should
fucking die.
That's a fucking miserab
' disgusting thing to be,
a bad son.
I mean, your
kid up at bard.
He better be
a good son, right?
You know,
you're right.
Why the fuck shoul
d i be a good son
to that fucking
demented, old bat?
The fucking selfish
miserable cunt?
She ruined
my father's life.
Oh, yeah.
But he wasn't
her son.
What did she
do to you?
C'mon, that's a matter o
f public record in here.
We both know.
You don't like to
say it, do you?
Who knows if she eve
n knew what she was doing.
You're letting her off.
My uncle denies
it, you know,
that she took part.
Your uncle loves you.
I never said
he didn't!
Grown children often secretl
wish for an aged parent to die
and it's not necessary
for the parent to be
a witness for
the prosecution.
It's a taboo
thought, but common.
Particularly if the parent
has lost all capacity
for joy at
being alive.
So, we're probab
ly done here, right?
She's dead.
What's happening?
Tony soprano's mother's
wake is tonight.
Want me to
wear a wire?
Why not, you
need batteries?
Let's go right over
here to office depot.
Janice.
I'm downstairs!
Hey.
Mom would want
a closed casket,
don't you agree?
Definitely.
They usually put a
picture on the casket,
what do you think?
Wow, look at that.
She's smiling.
She looks...
normal.
Maybe it was us kids
who turned her into
a freakin' sourpuss.
Maybe it was
one of us.
Oh, get--
get the fuck--
get off!
Alright, alright!
You know, maybe
you're right.
My shrink says tha
t all women are not cu
t out to be mothers.
Is that a slam at me?
No.
Look, if my father
was in the freakin
' "cirque de soleil",
maybe i would've
turned out like har--
hal.
This is fucking weird.
What?
None of my childhood
schoolwork or artwork
or anything, for that matter
is here anymore, nor barb's.
Get the fuck
out of here.
"Anthony soprano.
7th grade,
mr. Martino."
I had him.
"Why "fear strikes
out", by jim piersall
is a good book."
Take a look.
She only saved yours.
What are you
talking about?
Here's barbara's
communion certificate.
Here's h
er baby shoe.
Yeah, that's it.
Nothing of mine.
Everybody agreed
that i had
extraordinary
visualization skills.
Those pencil drawings
i did of grandpa.
They're good.
Ton', sorry.
Tony, i'm sorry.
He's disrespectful.
Thanks for coming.
Fucking motherfucking
pain in the fucking ass!
Could we not, huh?
With the tantrums?
For this shit, i miss th
e jet's first home game!
Are they sayin' when your
making ceremony might happen
now with this delay?
Stop asking
fucking questions!
Even if i knew
, i couldn't tell you.
Hit me, hit me.
Every little
bit helps.
Anything to get
through these events.
Hey.
What a fuckin' blow.
Not you too.
I'm serious.
What are you...
breaking the terms of
your house arrest?
I got a dispensati
on from the marshals.
She's my sister- in- law,
for chrissake.
My dad's very ill too.
Thanks.
Thanks for coming.
Tony,
allow me to expres
s my condolences
and those of
the eighth ward.
Thank you,
assemblyman.
I met your m
om once or twice.
That was...
a proud newarker.
Oh, hey, hey.
My sympathies, tony.
We talked about this
day, did we not?
You know state assemblyman
zellman, right?
From the
eighth ward?
Do i know this guy?
You bet.
Yes, we go way back.
How are yo
u, assemblyman?
Reverend.
Uncle jun',
you alright?
They're droppin'
like fucking flies.
It's all that
charcoal- broiled
meat you people ate.
Nobody told us
till the'80s.
I'm kidding you,
you old fuck.
What's the matter
with you?
Bacala said you
wanted to seeme.
I gotta talk to that
wife of yours first.
Uncle jun', c'mon.
This is a funeral, enough
of her soigne attitude.
What do you want?
I'm hoping that we can
use this sad occasion
to put bitterness and
sore- headed feelings aside.
I'll behave
how tony wants.
I don't want to
add to his stress.
There they are.
Hi, uncle jun'.
How's that surfboard
i gave you?
Ow!
Jun'...
tony's waiting.
Ralphie cifaretto
got word to me.
So, what does
he want?
He wants a bump
up to captain.
The kid's been a
top fucking earner
ever since that rat bastard
went in the program.
You can't deny it.
Ralphie's whipped richie's
crew into shape over there.
And three months
ago by you
the rat bastard was
the second fuckin' comin'.
Why do you
do this to me?
Because i'm the boss o
f this family, you forget.
I forget nothing.
Don't make me say things
to you we'll both regret.
Go ahead, i'm
fucking fed up.
Hey.
I'm on the street.
That's the arrangement.
Stay home, clip your
coupons, be a happy man.
Things are good,
i'll grant you that.
But this economy
is so robust,
you get credit for shi
t you had nothing to do with.
Fucking chinks
and housewives are
betting football.
You better
be finished.
Joe zachary?
Yeah.
Oh, boys,
no fires.
Tony doesn't
want any fires.
I ain't so tough.
Well, zach, what
do you think?
Can't say.
Well, we'll hope
for the best.
Doctor...
this is tom's mother,
brother, and miss doyle.
The lord bless her
and keep her.
The lord make his
face to shine upon her
and be gracious to her.
The lord lift up his
countenance upon her
and give her peace.
Amen.
Did you talk to her?
She's sure you said
something to him.
He won't discuss
it, he clams up.
Beautiful sendoff, t.
Thank you,
thank you.
I want to thank you fo
r all you've done for her.
She was much work,
but in the end,
she defeated me.
Anyway...
we're not gonna be
needing your service
s anymore, obviously.
I'll be moving
into the house.
So, if you could
just get your stuff
out of there
by this weekend,
i think th
at would be good.
I stay there
only during week
when my fiance has
his children with him.
Tony says i can
continue situation
until bill and
me find house.
See, tony should hav
e consulted me first.
I'm gonna be living
at 55 benedek
while we deal
with the estate.
Speaking of which...
my mom had this kind o
f extensive record collection.
Caruso,
robert merrill,
shitload o
f broadway shows.
Many of them w
ere in mint condition.
Do you kno
w where they are?
She gave to me
those records.
What?
She know i like
american show tunes,
so she give to me.
I didn't ask her.
But those are my
mother's records
and i feel ver
y close to them.
I don't want to make
trouble, but miss janice,
i feel i have to
respect her wishes.
Oh, c'mon.
This is just about
you bogarting those
discs for your ass.
Now, they're worth a fortune
to the right collector.
I will not
answer such here.
I want the entire
discography
back at the house
by this weekend.
Mrs. S.
How are you?
Sit down.
How's your mother?
You call her
every day.
Mom passed away.
Really?
When?
About six months ago.
Please giv
e her my regards.
Is she still on
that crazy diet?
I brought
you something.
Umm...
from my restaurant.
I don't know
if you remember...
vesuvio?
Mrs. S.
What's the matter?
After what my son
did to you...
how can i look you
in the face?
What did
he do now?
You don't blame him
for setting the fire?
Artie, what ar
e you doing?
C'mon, we have
people arriving.
Let'sgo.
Thank you
so much.
Thank you.
Look at her.
She's already
becoming a robot
like the rest of us.
I'm so sorry
about your
grandma.
At least she
didn't suffer.
All her innocence
is gone.
...comes to that point
in the service
where the rabbi's
supposed to extol
the virtues of
the deceased.
The rabbi says,
"alas, i did not know
this man, i'm new here.
You all knew him, you say
something good about him."
Dead silence.
Goes on for about a
minute, two minutes.
Finally, a voice
from the back,"his
brother was worse."
I'm walking ou
t with the provolone.
And i think he think
s i smell like that.
This "survivor"
show...
somebody should find winne
r, stick a pistol in the face,
and say,"you not
gonna survive this
unless you give me
25 percent of that
fucking million dollars."
That's not bad.
We could find ou
t where they live.
"See how good
you survive this,
you pezzo di merda."
Everyone, please, may
i have your attention?
At this time, we would
like to ask you all
to join us in
the great room.
Form a circle, sit anywhere,
the floor, whatever.
Get comfortable, so th
at we can all be together
and share a remembranc
e or a feeling about the woman
who has brought us
all here today.
Goddamnit.
Please, everyone
join us.
Paulie gualtieri,
join us please?
Thank you.
What the fuc
k did i say, hmm?
If you'd rather, i
can invite them all
back to her place.
Janice, what are
you doing?
Very good.
We could all take a break
from eating for five minutes,
it won't killus.
Most of you will
probably remember
that this was
her favorite song.
I thought it might
help us get rolling.
Herman? Rabkin?
You two went back,
almost to the pyramids.
I...
i guess what
struck me most was...
she didn't mince words.
Between brain and mouth,
there was no interlocutor.
Anthony jr.
I don't know
what to say.
Ah, c'mon.
Lay off him,
janice, move on.
She was my best friend.
If anybody
died or was
in the hospital,
i could be sure
i'd get a call from
lee letting me know.
Thank you, fanny.
Thank you.
Okay.
What's good
for the goose...
well, most of you will
probably remember that i have
an extraordinary
visual sense.
When i was a child,
my mother didn't let me
rest on those laurels.
She didn't flatter me.
She believed that wild
flowers blossomed best...
among the rocks.
With little water.
She was tough.
But she was right.
And she's the reason
i make videos today.
Tony?
Maybe you'd like
to tell them...
how ma saved all your
childhood schoolwork
and varsity letters
and none of mine
or barbara's?
You just did.
Wrap it up,
janice.
I hear she
didn't suffer.
For that we can
be grateful.
Thank you.
They say there's no two people
on earth exactly the same.
No two faces.
No two sets of
fingerprints.
But do they know
that for sure?
'Cause they would
have to get everybody
together in
one huge space.
And obviously,
that's not possible,
even with computers.
Not only that,
they'd have to get
all the people
who ever lived,
not just the ones now.
So, they got no proof.
They got nothing.
Hey.
So, ton',
she's dead.
What?
I guess our
little secret...
dies with her.
Hey, pick that up!
What am i doing
out here?
Everybody's in there
telling stories of her.
I got a beaut!
Artie.
Artie!
Artie, don't
talk about that!
Mrs. Soprano may
have passed,
but who's to say there
isn't another mrs. Soprano
just like her
or will be?
Maybe not with
the same fears and
paranoia, but...
the same.
What i'm saying is...
thank you, chris.
Thank you.
Umm...
this is such a
crock of shit.
Carmela.
I'm sitting here thinkin
g i should protect my children
from the truth about their
grandmother on the one hand.
On the other, i'm
saying to myself,
what kind of example
am i setting?
Evading and smiling,
passing out cheese puffs...
over a woman that we all k
was terribly dysfunctional!
Who spread no cheer.
At all.
Carmela, be quiet.
This is my house!
I'm leaving.
Let her talk.
Sit down!
I'll speak
if i want!
Goddamnit,
who are you,
minister of
propaganda?
We suffered for
years under the
yoke of that woman.
Years!
She estranged us
from our own daughter.
Ruined i don't know how
many goddamn christmases,
i don't want to
even begin to count.
Hugh.
Don't hand me that!
Bullshit!
You wanted it,
you got it.
Here, here.
From beyond
the grave even.
This is a woman who
didn't want a funeral.
You all, her children,
you ignored her wishes.
Only after she's
dead, by the way.
She didn't
want a funeral.
She didn't want
a remembrance
of any kind.
Why?
She didn't think
anybody would come.
She wouldn't write down her
memories for her grandchildren
because she figured nobody
loved her enough to read them.
She knew there
was a problem.
Um, there's desserts...
in the dining room
if anybody wants some.
Yes, um...
and they're all
from vesuvio.
Our new pastry chef,
bobby vasquez.
Thanks.
Mike's here.
He's come
to see you.
You must like mike
a lot better than me.
No, no, tommy boy,
you're my baby.
You're going to get
well and strong.
All of us
together again.
I'm almost glad
this happened.
Yeah, this is mike.
When?
You were?
Fine.
Ma, they're
bringing tom home.
They are, when?
Right now,
he's on his way.
Oh, it's wonderful.
I'll get his
room ready.
I knew my baby
would come home.
Captions copyright 2001
home box office
a division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.