This i
s so amazing!
Hey!
Oh, my god.
The way you ju
st said hey to me.
You are so nice.
I mean, i knew that
the first day you sawme.
Hug me!
You ha
ve to try it.
I am so not
depressed anymore.
Try what?
Ecstasy!
Where did
you get it?
Your friend!
What the fuck is
he doing at columbia?
God, he's
fucking cute!
Our families are friends
, i've known him forever.
You like that?
I choose you!
Having fun?
Not as muc
h as caitlin.
You see the eyes
she had on me?
The lid, dude.
She's from
okla- fuckin'- homa.
So, jackie, you're
in a frat now?
Rutgers chapter,
since freshman year.
I came up here
to see you.
Got any more x?
For you, the
first hit's free.
Just don't
tell your dad.
I don't
even talk to
him anymore.
Read'em and
suck my dick!
Yes, yes!
Yes, baby!
30 times,
right there,
that's mine.
Ho, he's still
got the dice?
I own these
fuckin' dice.
You're makin
' me a rich man,
ralphie boy.
The boss.
How are ya?
What can i
get ya guys?
Fuckin' faccia
di merda, he don't
come say hello?
What's this, a
new suit, huh?
Hey, t
how are ya? On'
how ya doin'?
What's wrong
with you? The
skip's here.
I'm on a roll here.
You'll be on a slab
you keep it up.
Hey, come here.
Hey, ton'.
I'm sorry,
this fuckin' guy.
Hello, anthony.
You look good.
Want a drink?
Another time,
anthony.
Another time.
Let's whack this cocksucker
and be done with it.
I'm here to
enjoy myself.
I'm so fuckin' hard.
No, jackie, don't.
Meadow.
Meadow, wake up.
I'm so sleepy.
You drank too much
fuckin' tequila.
C'mon, i can't
stop now.
"Another time,
anthony"?
Cocksucker turns
his back on the boss?
That i couldn't
believe.
He's lucky i didn't put
one in his fuckin' head!
On that front, don't
be surprised if paulie
pops the question.
Ralphie's star
is rising.
All those unions.
Paulie can't come near
that kinda cash for us.
Ralphie's a
good earner.
Guy like that...
loose cannon.
You'll be leaving your hou
he'll pull a jack ruby on you.
Why'd i have to punch
this fuckin' asshole?
Frankly...
i was a little
surprised.
You're gonna start
on me now, huh?
He disrespected
"the bing".
So, he's barre
d from the place.
He bashed
that poor
girl's brains in.
I hear you...
i know.
It was a tragedy.
The fact is though,
she was not related to
you by blood or marriage.
She was no
t your goomata.
Ralphie's
a made guy, ton'.
All things considered,
he's got a legitimate beef.
Make him disappear
or make nice.
You only got
two choices.
I would suggest someth
ing in the way of an apology.
Absolutely
fuckin' not!
Do something public that
shows there's no bad blood.
Give him...
give him a piece
of the casino.
We're partnered
with new york on that
and i don't want him
that close to johnny sack.
You could bump him
up to captain.
It's what he's bee
n wanting, you know.
Ralphie a fuckin'
captain...
over my dead body.
Thank you.
You see that
shit before?
The look on tony's
face when i turned
down that drink?
Buy me a drink?
Fuck you.
He knew it
was wrong,
what he did.
He is
the boss,
he could do
what he wants.
Boss or no,
you don't raise
your hands to
another made guy.
Joe mo from mulberry street,
exact same situation.
He smacked that guy
from north bergen around.
Huge problem.
Of course.
Rules are rules,
otherwise, what?
Fuckin' anarchy.
At the very least,
tony owes you an apology.
The money i put
in his pocket for
construction alone,
he should hit his
knees, this prick.
What?
You think i'm afraid
of that fat fuck?
No offense.
I could see
if it was
his daughter,
or a niece of his,
but all this over
some dead whore.
He had to be
fuckin' her.
No.
He knew you were
fuckin' her.
That's why,
that's how he is,
like a dog
with two bones.
I'm supposed to
go over there...
for thanksgiving,
me and ro, tony's.
Really?
Fuck him
and his turkey.
I oughta shove a
drumstick up his ass.
Look who i
caught sneaking
in the fire door.
My parishioners
might not
understand
i'm here to help
feed the hungry.
Reverend.
Happy thanksgiving.
Madonn',
who needs it?
Oh, c'mon, turkey,
sweet potatoes,
pumpkin pie?
You gotta
love all that.
That's because
you never lived through
the "walyo" version.
Major antipast' first.
Then soup,
meatballs
and scharol
then the baked
manigott',
then the bird.
I love manicotti.
Turkeys
are here.
There are some
in here, too.
Thing with turkeys,
they got no sense
of direction.
They're on their
way to food emporium
and now look.
What's this i
hear about ralph
cifaretto?
He refused to
have a drink w
ith you at the club?
So?
He refused the
drink'cause h
e's a despicable fuck
that i bitch- slapp
ed at a moment of
very justified anger.
That sounds like
a problem.
Happy thanksgiving
to you and yours.
Yeah, you too.
Happy thanksgiving,
reverend.
That mine?
Ah, beautiful.
Look at that.
Ah, shit!
What's the matter?
That fuckin' asshole's
supposed to come
to thanksgiving
with rosalie.
No way
he'll show.
I'm gonna give
him the option?
That cocksucker
shouldn't even be ther
e in the first place.
Honey, i know
you don't like to--
i know you don't like
to be pinned down,
but thanksgiving, it would
be very nice to be able to
tell carmela
whether you're coming.
Who's gonna
be there?
Besides us?
I don't know,
carm's parents.
Great.
How about meadow?
So, thanksgiving,
who's all coming
this year?
You know,
the usual.
Nana and grandpa...
chris and ade.
I think janice is bringing
someone from her prayer group.
Um, and aunt ro
and uncle ralph.
Jackie's probably
not coming though, right?
Oh, i don't know, why?
Can't i just
ask anything?
Alright,
take it easy.
I have class, i'll
see you thursday.
Alright, bye.
Hello.
Hey, carm,
it's ro.
God, that is so weird
that you just called.
I just hung up
with meadow
and she was asking if jackie
was coming for thanksgiving.
Oh, really?
Jackie just asked
me about her.
My radar's up.
Oh, you and those
romance novels, rosalie.
Can you imagine
the beautiful children
those two would make,
with those genes?
Remember when meadow
was born, what we said?
Yes, we said a lot
of things, ro.
Do me a favor,
concentrate on that almond
torte of yours, alright?
I'm counting on you.
I'm looking
for the recipe.
Alright, bye.
Here's the turkey.
Oh, my god,
it's huge.
Good thing, i'm
feeding an army
this year.
Not as many
as you think.
I need you to call rosalie
and cancel with them.
Thanksgiving, why?
Just do it,
alright?
Enough of this
jetson's shit
them coming over to
mr. Spacely's house
for dinner.
I was just talking
to her, what
am i gonna say?
Fine, i'll call.
And my excuse won't be
nearly as nice as yours.
Goddamnit, tony.
What, your
stomach still?
Dr. Akavi?
Gloria trillo,
globe mercedes.
Listen, a pre- owned
2001 s- 600 just came in.
You're the first
person i thought of.
Wood trim package,
gps with everything.
Only 7500 miles,
i don't think
it's gonna las
t till saturday.
Tomorrow?
Great.
No, i'm sorry, i can't,
we're doing a sales
meeting at lunch.
Okay, see ya...
bye.
You waiting for
somebody in there?
I got an
appointment.
Did she
double- book us?
I'm usually thursday,
but i had to reschedule
because of the holiday.
This is when
i usually come.
I'm trying to
quit smoking.
Serial killer.
I murdered
seven relationships.
Listen, you're here.
Why don't you take
my appointment?
Oh, no, no,
i couldn't
do that, no.
It would be my good
deed for the day.
Flag on the play.
I'm pretty sure
you said tuesday.
I did?
I'll come back next we
ek at the same time and...
no problemo.
I told her she could
have my appointment.
Actually, it is
a little difficult
getting away
from work.
See?
I...
i could see you
tonight at seven.
Yeah,
yeah, thanks.
Okay.
How hard was that?
Hello?
Ro, it's carm.
This is so terrible to do
on such short notice,
but i just got off
the phone with ma.
What's the matter?
It's my father.
They had some
troubling test results.
Something to do with
his white blood cells.
Oh, my god.
Yeah, i know, uh...
they're gonna have to
do further testing
before they can be
sure of the diagnosis.
Ma just wants to have
a quiet thanksgiving.
She said that they
would have it just
the two of them, but--
they should be
with their family.
I feel so awful giving
you so little notice.
Don't be silly, i
just wish there wa
s something i could do.
Thank you, ro,
that is so sweet.
Of course, i'll let you know
when i know anything more.
Okay, take care,
sweetheart.
Bye.
Alright, bye- bye.
Carm's father,
he's sick.
She had to cancel
thanksgiving.
It's three a. M.
Bam, come
wide awake.
Something specific?
It's a management
problem.
It's a situation
with an underling.
Now, it's partly
my fault.
But he never should've
done what he did.
What was it?
Could you
tell me that?
He caused the...
early retirement...
of somebody else.
The particulars aren't
important, he fucked up.
Ordinarily, i would
just, you know...
put him
out to pasture.
But he's a very valuable
piece of manpower.
Is it complicated by a
personal relationship?
I been reading that...
book you
told me about.
"The art of war",
by sun tzu.
Here's this guy...
a chinese general, wrote
this thing 2400 years ago.
And most of it
still applies today.
Balk the enemy's power.
Force him to
reveal himself.
Uh, i have to ask...
are you in any
sort of danger?
No, can i go on?
Most of the guys that i know,
they read prince machiavelli.
I had carmela go and get
the cliff notes once...
he's okay.
But this book is much
better about strategy.
Listen, i wanted to
ask you about the girl.
That woman that
was here today.
The mercedes
saleslady.
I'm very sorry
about the confusion.
What does somebody like
that need a shrink for?
I can't talk about
another patient.
Just...
it makes you wonder,
that's all.
It's after hours,
it's dark.
You want me to walk
you to your car?
No, thank you.
I have some work i have
to catch up on here.
Anyone for
a turtle?
Hmm?
Aaron, honey.
Hey!
What?
Oh.
Who's winning?
Like you even know
who's playin'.
It so happens
that i do.
Detroit plays
every thanksgiving.
What a shame barry
sanders retired.
He's a real
sweetheart.
A. J. , did you tell
your dad and your grandpa
how i served him
when i waitressed
at kenny roger's?
Colonel sanders.
No, at kenny rogers,
barry sanders.
Yeah, sh
e served him.
Yes!
Hey.
Yeah!
Meadow, you know i lov
e you more than anything
in this world, right?
Dad, what are you
talking about?
I know things haven't been
so good with us lately,
it's just...
if anything were eve
r to happen to you...
everybody, come
on, dinner!
Go ahead.
I'll tell you, thi
s turned out to be
a blessing in disguise.
My two boys...
i was worried about
the gravy, but...
ralph, honey,
you feel alright?
You hardly touched
your manigott'.
I'm fine,
christ, please,
how many times?
Jackie, honey, you don't
have to stay for dessert
if you don't want to.
Jesus chri
st, a little
manners, huh?
What'd she
just say?
It's okay.
Why do
n't you go see
if meadow wants to go
to a movie or something?
Sure, ma.
Good dinner.
I'll tell ya
a nifty trick.
Break off a piece
of ohio kitchen match,
in the screw hole,
give the
threads something
to grab onto.
Yeah?
'Cause i used th
e elmer's and th
e knob still fell out.
Forget about it.
Narcolepsy
is an a. S. D. A.
Certified dissomnia.
It's no picnic.
Almost time for
turkey sandwiches!
I'll put
more coffee on.
Oh, my god, who
could that be?
It's the boston
strangler, jesus, ma.
I'll get it.
Hey.
Hey!
Jackie, hi!
I guess you know
everybody here
except for aaron,
janice's friend.
Hey, aaron.
Have you heard
the good news?
He is risen.
Sit down, we're gonna have
some turkey sandwiches.
Thanks,
i already ate.
Just figured i'd
see if meadow wanted
to do something.
See a movie,
whatever.
Sure, i mean, i was gonna
go over to hunter's.
You wanna go?
Whatever.
I'll be down
in a sec.
A soprano
and an aprile.
So, how's school,
everything good, right?
Yeah, gpa's up
this quarter.
Why don't you just bag
it, and come to dov's?
Hunter's
expecting me.
We can hang out
all weekend.
We wouldn't have to
like do anything.
I have to study.
Don't you have
midterms too?
I don't ev
en go anymore.
What?
Why?
Organic chemistry?
Nucleotides and shit.
You wanna know wha
t i'm interested in?
Men's fashion.
Not the faggy part of
it, but like to be hugo boss.
Did you ever think
of applying to fit?
It's supposed to be
a good school for that.
Come on,
come to dov's.
I wanna be
with you so bad.
I can't, jackie.
What?
You won't go
with me, but you'd
go with that black guy?
It's not that i
don't want to go.
I've been hurt.
Just give me
some time, okay?
...as street corners
are heaps of crumbled
wrath and masonry.
...darling christmas gift--
three shuttles remain, now--
it makes me crazy,
rosalie, all of them.
They're alread
y hiring the caterers.
I mean, we were young
when we got married,
but those two?
Emotionally they are
much younger than we were.
...until then,
here's how you'll
get your thrills.
The mercedes- benz
coups and convertibles.
Earth to tony.
I'm thinking of
getting one of those.
What,
a mercedes?
Go ahead, it's
a cute car.
You hear?
T disinvited ralph
to thanksgiving.
No shit.
Madonn'.
Tony sees
the big picture.
Oh, little paulie.
Hey, ton'.
This prick
treating you okay?
No complaints.
C'mon, little paulie,
everybody,
i'll buy you
an egg cream.
C'mon,
sit down.
So...
how are things going ove
r there with our friend?
The same,
you know.
What's he saying
about me?
To me? Nothing,
he knows better.
He's still breaking
my balls though,
about taking
orders from me.
Plus now, with you and him
and all that other shit there.
It's your job to
make my job easier.
I'm not complaining,
you asked me.
He's a frustrating guy.
I don't know how
things are gonna go...
but i can't promis
e he's gonna go away.
It's not just him.
This freon deal.
We're in the middle
of a major renovation
at the house,
i got two kids
getting ready for
college soon.
Hey, hang in there
, you're doing a good job.
Did you see
those bags?
Fuckin' stress
is killing him.
Yeah.
Maybe he wants
my fuckin' job.
...it's a matter of
honor this thanksgiving
because everyone a
t texas remembers turkey
day two years ago...
sure you don't wanna eat
? i got a little turkey left.
No, than
k you, dear.
Johnny, please,
don't get up.
I'm off to physical
therapy, hon.
Used to be some
hoofer, poor thing.
Takes a terrible
toll on the joints.
You heard what he di
d with thanksgiving?
It's not good,
ralph.
Will you please tell m
e what i did to this guy?
Turn down a drink
? i wasn't thirsty!
Ralph.
Ever since i'm back fr
om miami he's up my ass!
I'm earning with
three hands here,
and it's still not good enough
to satisfy this cocksucker!
And then he
fuckin' hits me?
I'm telling you, john.
He's not leaving me
a lot of options here.
Don't talk crazy!
You wanna commit suicide,
pills are a lot easier.
What do you th
ink carmine wouldsay
if i wanted to
switch families?
Come w
ith you guys.
Carmine doesn't
know who you are.
You could tell him.
Ralph,
listen to me.
As a friend...
i know tony
can be difficult.
His father was the
same, his uncle,
they always need
someone to demonize.
But new york and
the sopranos have
long- standing ties
and that's
not gonna change,
not for you
or anybody else.
You want me
to be frank?
You brought
this on yourself
with that girl.
"A", she was
a whore,
"b", she hit me.
And that wasn't my
kid she was carrying.
It was the
fucking coke,
i should've never
started with that shit.
Fuckin' miami, it'
s all over the place.
Just tell anthony
you're sorry.
I was high
, i admit it,
and i swear to christ
i'm not doing it anymore.
"Tony, i'm sorry."
Fuck that, what good
would it do?
It might
save your life!
He hit me!
He was wrong,
believe me, he knows.
You don't think i know
people are laughing
behind my back?
I'll talk to tony,
i'm sure he'll
make it right.
At this
point, how?
I don't know.
Would you take
capo of your crew?
No, no, i wouldn't
, no fuckin' way.
Ralph cifaretto
came by.
What'd he want,
a fully- fueled jet
and a safe trip to the pope?
He's running scared si
nce you cancelled that dinner.
If your opponent
is of choleric
temper, irritate him.
Yeah, well,
he wants
to apologize.
Oh, really?
Would that p
ut this to rest?
If it's sincere.
It might relieve me of
a very unpleasant decision.
You know, they're about to
break ground on the esplanade.
We're talking about
millions of dollars
here, tony.
It wouldn't hurt either of
to have a point man in there
feels appreciated.
I'm just saying.
It wouldn't hurt
to throw him a bone.
Like what?
Capo?
No fuckin' way.
Never.
You heard
what he did.
That poor girl just
had her 20th birthday.
Capo's what
he mentioned.
I threw cold water
on it right away.
But she was
a whore, tony.
I don't want to talk about
that situation ever again,
with anybody.
You understand me?
It was just
a suggestion,
keep a happy shop.
Correct me
if i'm wrong,
didn't you say you weren't
gonna stick your beak in?
Can't two friends talk?
I talked to him, he's
delighted you wanna see him.
Great, he
said that?
That's great.
That's fuckin'
great news.
What'd i tell you?
Listen, the
other thing,
what's he gonna do
to make that right?
Just talk to him.
He indicated he's very open
to working something out.
Thank you,
thank you.
Anything!
Thank you,
thank you.
Oh, fabian!
The fuck you doing
up before noon?
I'm moving out,
over to dov's.
Beanie boy?
Yeah, his reserve unit
in israel got called up.
God bless
america, huh?
Listen, you find
yourself short on x,
i know a guy.
X?
What?
I'm trying to
do you a favor.
And just so
you know,
that bullshit
your future father- in- law
pulled over thanksgiving,
he knew i had no intention
of going over there.
He's trying
to save face.
So he stoops so
low, he had his wife
lie to your mother.
Whatever you need,
give me a call.
Be good.
The woman is
50 years old.
Sometimes i just want
to scream in her face,
"quit whining, no
wonder he left you!"
Her supervisor looks
at her cross- eyed
and i get a call at
3:00 in the morning.
She wants to talk
about how her father
laughed at her
when she fell off her bicycle
when she was seven.
Does she call yo
ur emergency number?
No, that's not
the point, elliot!
Oh, these fuckin'
interruptions!
I was raped.
You have feelings of y
our own and who is listening?
That's right,
damnit.
I have to sit there
and take care of these
people hour after hour
with all
their problems...
and some of them are very
real and very serious,
and i'm sorry,
i care,
i really do...
but it's hard
sometimes.
I just want to
say,"i hurt!"
Good, sure.
That's why
you're here.
I'm sorry,
elliot.
No need to
be sorry.
You've been
through such trauma.
It takes tremendous
strength of will
and inner resource
to soldier on as you
do at your work.
Thank you,
elliot.
I try,
i really do.
It's just
hard sometimes.
And patient
soprano?
How's all that?
He offered to
escort me to my car.
I almost fell in
his arms crying.
Oh, jesus christ.
Chris.
Paulie.
Ralphie.
You wanted
to see me?
Yeah, tony.
About what?
You know...
to apologize.
Oh.
Sit down?
I was doing
a lot of coke.
I said some things and
i did some things...
that i'm sorry for.
It's not gonna
happen again.
What'd you do?
I was rude
when you offered
me the drink.
And i disrespected
"the bing".
And the girl...
that shouldn't
have happened.
Like i said,
i was doing
a lot of coke.
But i gave
that up, and...
end of story,
and...
i'm sorry,
tony, okay?
Anything else?
Hey.
What's up,
gi?
Hey, gi.
My wife made some
turkey sandwiches
if anybody wants one.
I'm still a
little bloated
from thanksgiving.
Thanksgiving,
1982.
Fucking turkey,
it's like spackle
in my bowels.
Nothing moves.
Want me to run to rite aids
and get you some metamucil?
Nah, i hat
e that shit.
Maybe i'll try
one with lettuce
and cranberry.
Ralph around?
Not yet.
Want me to
give him a call?
Please, let's just
enjoy the quiet, huh?
After decades of planning,
ground was broken today
on the city
of newark,
new jersey's
museum of science
and trucking, and
riverfront esplanade.
Oh, hi, ralphie.
C'mon in, he's
watching tv.
...the project
was held up several times
by political infighting--
nothing, he
gave me nothing.
Two seconds,
look, the fuckin
g esplanade, finally.
We're gonna need our
own bulldozers to
take the money away.
Not a thing, john.
Not a thank
you, not an
apology, nothing!
Calm down,
take it easy.
He let me stand there
like a servant...
scraping,
bowing!
Cocksucker didn't even
invite me to sit down.
It's posturing,
it's part of the game.
Fuck the game,
he's going down.
Are you fucking
stupid coming in here
talking to me like that?
I don't give a
fuck anymore!
I've given my life
to this thing
and this is the
thanks i get?
It's silvio dante
on the phone.
You wanna
talk to him?
Tell him i
'll call him back.
They're my children.
You seriously cannot be--
i'm so sorry!
You shut the door?
Jesus christ, you're
worse than bobby.
Anybody see
you come in?
Yeah.
Fuck'em.
I don't give
a shit anymore.
Brought you some
leftover turkey
and stuffing,
manigott'.
Keep it.
Everything
goes through me.
And these drafts,
i should be down in boca.
Drafts?
It's like the fucking
amazon jungle in here.
What's the
thermostat say?
Don't touch it!
Alright.
Jesus.
You're scaring t
he hell outta me here.
The though
t of losing you.
Grandpa,
did he ever work for
somebody named trillo?
He owned a
lumberyard?
My father was
a master stonemason,
he never cut
fucking wood.
A contractor then?
Built garden
apartments?
There was somebody
named trillo, he had
seven daughters.
I can't remember.
I thought you were
gonna ask my advice
about ralph cifaretto.
Got any thoughts?
What else
do i have left?
A real contremps you have
on your hands here.
A good kid, but you never
should've put gigi in there.
He's strong,
a good earner,
well respected.
Not by that crew.
To them he's a ghibelline
coming over to butt in.
They don't trust him,
they undermine him.
On top of that,
you got ralph now
pissing in their ears.
Any day you'll have a
mutiny on your hands.
So, i take gigi out,
what kind of message
does that send?
That you're indecisive
and unsure of yourself.
Exactly.
Who the fuck would i
replace him with anyway?
All good questions.
Great, what's
the fuckin' answer?
Who says
there is one?
That's what
being a boss is,
you steer the ship
the best way you know.
Sometimes it's smooth,
sometimes you hit the rocks.
In the meantime,
you find your pleasures
where you can.
How much longer,
skip?
I gotta
take a leak!
Holy jesus.
What the fuck
are you lookin'
at? Call 911.
I don't
feel a pulse.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Thank you,
tony.
He was a
good man.
Never said
a bad word
about anybody.
Thank you,
tony.
I'm so sorry.
It's fuckin' awful.
He's a young man.
Heart disease...
the silent killer.
Hey, there are
worse ways togo.
Even still, on
the pisciadood?
Pretty fuckin'
humiliating.
It's how
elvis died.
That guy in
hollywood too.
Don something.
Producer o
f "the simpsons".
So, there'
s a vacancy.
There's a lot
of business to do.
You thought about
who it's gonna be?
Terrible, it's a
terrible thing.
Guy was in here
twice a week.
Brought the kids
in and everything
on sundays.
Artie,
hey, ton'.
I gotta go
rotate my
pork shoulder.
You wanted
to see me?
Sit down.
I'm making
you captain.
You are?
That's great.
Oh, that's
fuckin' great.
Anthony, you're no
t gonna be sorry.
Thank you.
What?
I need to hear
it was merit,
and not just'cause
somebody was constipated
and blew a gasket.
You're gonna be making
a lot more money, ralphie,
so, don't
question.
You wanted captain?
You're captain.
Thank you, tony,
you're right.
I've wanted this
so fuckin' long.
Well...
you know
what they say.
Be careful what you wish
for, you just might get it.
So, um...
we gonna have a drink
together or what?
What's this shit i hear
about tony having a fight
with ralph cifaretto?
Something about
thanksgiving?
I was there.
What,
at tony's?
Wow, on
thanksgiving?
After dinner,
to take meadow out.
Did you
fuck her yet?
Her body is mad ripe.
Yeah, but did
you fuck her yet?
She's creamin'
for me, man.
You didn't
fuck her yet.
I don't know if it's
even a smart thing.
She's tony soprano's
daughter.
I'll be
right back.
See ya.
Jackie, c'mon,
vassar, that band.
C'mon, doubl
e or nothing.
Yeah, rack'em.
You said you were
gonna take me.
Go sit down.
Ha, ha, ha.
Fuckin' brat.
Meadow!
Goddamnit!
Hey, no!
Meadow!
Oh, my god,
fuck, meadow!
Jackie!
Jesus, meadow,
are you alright?
I think so.
Ow! Easy.
What's the matter?
My purse is stuck.
You gu
ys alright?
We're fine.
We're totally fine,
nobody got hurt.
Blew a tire.
But your car...
fuck the car, i'
ll call it in stolen.
Oh, my god, jackie,
i am so sorry!
As long as
you're okay.
I don't know what
i would've done if
you would've got hurt.
You almost died.
I'm so sorry.
I should've
taken you to vassar
like you wanted.
But you loved
that car.
It's alright.
Come on, let's
get you home.
No...
i wanna
go with you.
You sure?
And we could
match up...
well, that
sounds good...
i'll give you
my card.
I'll be here
at 10:00.
Okay? Nice
to meet you.
Nice meeting you.
Hey.
It's you.
I had my eye on...
one of these.
You have good taste.
Mind if i take
it for a test drive?
You have to be accompanied
by a sales rep.
Anybody available?
Dale?
Yeah.
I'm going out.
600.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Mm- hmm.
Hello?
Jennifer it's
gloria trillo.
I'm really sorry, but
i can't make it today.
Everything alright?
Yeah, yeah, fine.
All they had
was wine coolers.
Well...
i'm glad you called.
Do you want to
reschedule?
No, it's okay,
i'll just see you next
week at the regular time.
Okay, i'll see
you next week.
Captions copyright 2001
home box office
a division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.
Captioned by hbo
communications center