CAN YOU HELP ME ?
I'M LOOKING
FOR A WOMAN WHO'S--
EXCUSE ME--
EXCUSE ME.
I'M LOOKING FOR A DANA SCULLY.
WAS A DANA--
SC--
EXCUSE ME.
I'M LOOKING FOR DANA SCULLY.
IS SHE A PATIENT HERE ?
DANA SCULLY ?
IS-IS THERE
AN ADMITTING NURSE HERE ?
LOOK, CAN SOMEBODY
HELP ME HERE ?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO CALM DOWN.
I WILL CALM DOWN
WHEN SOMEBODY GIVES ME
A REASON TO CALM DOWN !
NOW, I'M LOOKING FOR A PATIENT
THAT WAS ADMITTED TO THE E.R.
DANA SCULLY.
YES !
WHERE IS SHE ?
I HEARD YOU THE FIRST TIME.
I HAVE HER IN THE I.C.U.
WHERE IS THAT ?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO TELL ME
WHO YOU ARE FIRST.
WHERE IS SHE ?
AGENT MULDER !
WHERE YOU GOIN' ?
I.C.U.
YOU'RE MOVIN' PRETTY GOOD
FOR A DEAD MAN.
I'M ONLY HALF DEAD.
YOU GOT A LOT TO ANSWER FOR,
AGENT MULDER !
YOU GUYS HOLD HERE.
YES, SIR.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER ?
SHE WENT INTO
HYPOVOLEMIC SHOCK.
SHE'S LOST A LOT OF BLOOD.
DUE TO WHAT ?
SHE'S DYING.
LET'S GO HOME.
THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO.
LET GO OF ME.
GET THE HELL OFF OF ME !
DON'T DO THIS !
DON'T MAKE ME PUT YOU
UNDER ARREST.  DON'T !
[ Blevins ]
I'M SOMEWHAT AT A LOSS HERE
IN GOING FORWARD.
THIS SITUATION
DEVELOPING UNEXPECTEDLY...
DURING A FORMAL INQUIRY
INTO YOUR REPORTED DEATH,
AGENT MULDER.
THE FACT OF YOUR BEING HERE
TODAY VERY MUCH ALIVE,
IT GIVES THE EFFECT OF
RESHAPING THIS INVESTIGATION...
INTO SOMETHING
ALTOGETHER DIFFERENT,
AS WE'RE NOW PUT UPON
TO VERIFY THE IDENTITY...
OF THIS BODY
FOUND IN YOUR APARTMENT...
AND THE CIRCUMSTANCES
WHICH LED TO THIS.
WOULD YOU CARE TO ENLIGHTEN US
ON THESE CIRCUMSTANCES ?
ARE YOU SUGGESTING
THAT I CAN ?
[ Blevins ]  AGENT MULDER,
WE'RE HERE INFORMALLY
TO GIVE YOU THE CHANCE
TO HELP YOURSELF.
HELP MYSELF HOW ?
BY ALLOWING ANY FACTS OR DETAILS
WHICH MIGHT SERVE...
TO LET US GO FORWARD
WITH THIS INQUIRY
IN A MORE INFORMED MANNER.
THAT HELPS YOU.
HOW DOES THAT HELP ME ?
[ Blevins ]  AGENT MULDER,
THIS IS GOING TO QUICKLY
BECOME A MURDER INVESTIGATION.
CRIMINAL CHARGES
ARE GOING TO BE MADE.
[ Skinner ]
WE HAVE ONLY ONE OTHER SUSPECT.
SHE MAY NO LONGER BE ABLE
TO TESTIFY ON HER OWN BEHALF.
AGENT SCULLY LIED TO US.
WHY ?
WHO'S PROTECTING WHOM,
AGENT MULDER ?
[ Blevins ]
YOUR CHOICE IS YOUR OWN,
BUT YOUR FAILURE TO ANSWER...
WILL REFLECT POORLY ON
THE RECORD IN A FORMAL INQUIRY.
ARE WE FINISHED THEN ?
[ Door Opens ]
[ Door Closes ]
WORD OF ADVICE, MY FRIEND.
KEEP PLAYIN' IT THE WAY YOU ARE.
THANKS, BUDDY.
HEY, RIGHT NOW,
YOU NEED A BUDDY.
YOU NEED ALL THE HELP
YOU CAN GET.
YOU SHOULD'VE MENTIONED
THAT AT THE HOSPITAL,
HAULING MY ASS OFF.
I SAVED YOUR ASS,
AGENT MULDER.
I'VE BEEN WITHHOLDING
FORENSIC EVIDENCE ABOUT THE BODY
FOUND ON YOUR APARTMENT FLOOR.
UNTIL YOU SHOWED UP LAST NIGHT,
I WAS THE ONE
KEEPING YOUR SECRET.
I HAD NO CHOICE
BUT TO BRING YOU IN.
SCULLY WILL VERIFY
ALL OF THAT.
THAT'S A GOOD PLACE TO LAY IT,
CONSIDERING HER CONDITION.
YOU WANT ME TO LAY IT
WHERE IT BELONGS, AGENT MULDER ?
PATHOLOGY TURNED UP
TWO GUNSHOT WOUNDS TO
THE DEAD MAN IN YOUR APARTMENT--
ONE FIRED POINT-BLANK
TO THE LEFT TEMPLE
WITH A HANDGUN,
THE SECOND A POSTMORTEM WOUND
TO THE FACE TO REMOVE
THE MAN'S IDENTITY.
NOW, I'D BE HAPPY
TO VERIFY THE BALLISTICS
ON THAT FIRST SHOT.
HOW CAN YOU HELP ME ?
TELL ME WHY
SCULLY LIED FOR YOU.
THE DISEASE SHE HAS
WAS GIVEN TO HER...
BY SOMEBODY CONNECTED
TO THE F.B.I.
TO A MOLE WORKING HERE.
WHO ?
I FAILED TO
FIND THAT OUT, SIR.
YOU DON'T WANT TO FORGET
WHO YOUR FRIENDS ARE,
AGENT MULDER--
TO REMEMBER
WHO YOU CAN TRUST.
[ Man On TV ]  THE CHAIRMAN
SAID, "WHAT ARE THE APPROPRIATE
LIMITS OF HUMAN KNOWLEDGE ?"
I DON'T THINK THERE ARE
ANY APPROPRIATE LIMITS
TO HUMAN KNOWLEDGE.
AS LONG AS SCIENCE
IS DONE OPENLY
AND WITH FREE WILL,
THEN I DON'T THINK
THERE ARE ANY LIMITS.
[ Man #2 ]
SENATOR KENNEDY.
[ Kennedy ]  DR. VERMONT,
YOU'VE STATED THAT...
THE CLONING OF HUMANS
WOULD BE ILL-CONSIDERED...
AND TECHNICALLY DIFFICULT
TO ACCOMPLISH.
CAN YOU EXPAND A LITTLE BIT
ON WHAT YOU SEE...
AS THE BIGGEST TECHNICAL
OBSTACLE TO HUMAN CLONING--
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
I TRUST YOU'VE HEARD.
MULDER IS ALIVE.
AS I SAID, HE'S NOT
TO BE UNDERESTIMATED.
YES, AS YOU SAID.
THOUGH I HEAR HE HAS YOU
TO THANK IN SOME PART
FOR HIS NEW FREEDOM.
USING A STOLEN I.D.,
MULDER WAS ABLE TO GET INSIDE
THE ADVANCED RESEARCH
PROJECTS FACILITY.
AND YOU ALLOWED HIM TO ESCAPE.
YES.
WE'RE TOO VULNERABLE.
OUR MAN IN THE F.B.I.
IS EXPOSED.
WHAT MULDER MAY HAVE SEEN
COULD EXPOSE OUR PLANS.
WHAT MULDER'S SEEN
ONLY SERVES US.
IT SERVES TO ENSURE
OUR PLANS.
MULDER'S IN TROUBLE.
HE NEEDS HELP.
WE CAN GIVE IT TO HIM.
IN EXCHANGE FOR ?
HIS NEW LOYALTY...
TO US.
AS I'VE SAID ALL ALONG,
MULDER'S MUCH MORE VALUABLE
TO US ALIVE.
YOU CAN PROCEED NOW.
MULDER,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE ?
HEARD YOU WERE BEING
MOVED OUT OF I.C.U.,
YOU WERE FEELING BETTER.
MULDER, SOMEBODY'S
GONNA SEE YOU HERE.
IT'S OKAY.
I'M OFFICIALLY AMONG
THE UNDEAD.
WHAT HAPPENED ?
I DIDN'T COME HERE
TO TALK ABOUT THAT.
MULDER, DON'T TRY
AND PROTECT ME.
I NEED TO KNOW.
WELL, THERE'S NOT MUCH
TO TALK ABOUT ANYWAY.
I'M GONNA TESTIFY
TO EVERYTHING I KNOW IN FRONT
OF THE F.B.I. ASSEMBLY.
THE CONSPIRACY,
THE MEN BEHIND IT,
WHAT I BELIEVE IS ITS PURPOSE.
DID YOU FIND OUT WHO
IN THE F.B.I. IS INVOLVED ?
NO.  BUT THAT
DOESN'T MATTER NOW.
YES, IT DOES.
HEY, SCULLY,
HOW ABOUT THOSE YANKEES, HUH ?
MULDER, SKINNER HAS EVIDENCE
AGAINST YOU.
HE KNOWS THAT YOU KILLED
THAT MAN THEY FOUND
IN YOUR APARTMENT.
YEAH.
SKINNER'S WITHHOLDING IT.
MULDER, SKINNER'S DIRTY.
HE'S NOT YOUR FRIEND.
I'M ALMOST CERTAIN THAT
HE'S THE MAN INSIDE ON THIS.
I DON'T BELIEVE THAT.
IF YOU TESTIFY,
HE WILL USE IT TO RUIN YOU.
NO, NOT SKINNER.
HE'S-HE'S BEEN IN A POSITION
TO KNOW EVERYTHING
FROM THE BEGINNING,
EVERYTHING THAT WE'VE DONE
OVER THE PAST FOUR YEARS.
IF I DON'T TESTIFY NOW,
THEY'LL START TO BURY THE TRUTH.
WELL, THEN YOU HAVE TO
LAY IT ON ME.
YOU HAVE TO TELL THEM...
THAT I WAS THE ONE
WHO KILLED THAT MAN.
I CAN'T--
I CAN'T DO THAT.
YES, YOU CAN.
MULDER, IF I CAN SAVE YOU,
LET ME.
LET ME AT LEAST
GIVE SOME MEANING
TO WHAT'S HAPPENED TO ME.
[ Door Opens ]
DANA ?  HI, FOX.
HI, MRS. SCULLY.
- I HOPE I'M NOT INTERRUPTING.
- NO, NO, NO.
I WAS JUST ON MY WAY OUT.
HI.  I'M, UH--
I'M FOX MULDER.
I DON'T THINK WE'VE EVER MET.
I'M BILL SCULLY.
I'M SORRY
ABOUT YOUR SISTER.
MR. MULDER.
YEAH ?
I KNOW SOMETHING ABOUT YOU--
ABOUT WHAT DANA'S
BEEN THROUGH WITH YOU, SO...
LET'S LEAVE THE WORK
AWAY FROM HERE, OKAY ?
LET HER DIE WITH DIGNITY.
PLEASE TELL ME YOU'RE HERE
WITH SEVERE CHEST PAINS.
YOU SHOULD BE GLAD
FOR WHY I'M HERE--
TO PAY YOU SOME RESPECT.
GO TO HELL.
FOR YOUR CLEVERNESS
AND YOUR RESOURCE,
WHAT YOU MANAGED
TO DO FOR SCULLY.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ?
WELL, BREACHING THE SECURITY
AT THE DEFENSE DEPARTMENT
FACILITY,
FINDING THE CURE
FOR HER DISEASE.
WHAT I FOUND WAS USELESS.
ON THE CONTRARY.
IT'S ESSENTIAL
TO HER SURVIVAL.
IF YOU LIKE,
WE COULD STEP OUTSIDE
AND I MIGHT EXPLAIN MYSELF.
I'M HERE TONIGHT AS A FRIEND,
AGENT MULDER.
HE PROMISED ME
IT WOULD BE IN HERE.
[ Frohike ]
I'LL BE DAMNED.
IT NEVER OCCURRED TO ME
WHAT THE DEIONIZED WATER
MIGHT BE FOR.
- WHO KNEW IT WAS A MICROCHIP
WE WERE LOOKIN' FOR.
- THIS IS A CURE FOR CANCER ?
- IT MAY BE FOR SCULLY'S.
- HOW ?
[ Mulder ]
SHORTLY AFTER SHE WAS ABDUCTED,
SHE DISCOVERED A SMALL
METALLIC CHIP IMPLANTED
SUBCUTANEOUSLY IN HER NECK.
IT WAS JUST A SHORT TIME
AFTER SHE HAD IT REMOVED
THAT SHE DEVELOPED CANCER.
- IT'S UNREAL.
- TOO FREAKIN' AMAZING.
WATCH YOUR LANGUAGE, FROHIKE,
AND GRAB ME SOME TWEEZERS.
[ Blevins ]
MR. KRITSCHGAU, THANK YOU
FOR BEING HERE TODAY...
AND FOR COOPERATING
WITH THIS INVESTIGATION.
WE HOPE YOU CAN
PROVIDE INFORMATION...
THAT WILL ALLOW US
TO MAKE FORMAL CHARGES...
FOR THE MURDER OF DEFENSE
EMPLOYEE SCOTT OSTELHOFF.
MR. KRITSCHGAU,
WE HAVE LEARNED THAT
YOU WERE IN CONTACT WITH
AGENTS MULDER AND SCULLY...
JUST PRIOR TO THIS MAN'S DEATH.
- THAT'S CORRECT.
- AND THAT YOU MAY HAVE GIVEN
THEM CLASSIFIED INFORMATION.
WHAT MOTIVATED THIS ?
MY KNOWLEDGE OF GOVERNMENT
INVOLVEMENT IN A CONSPIRACY
AGAINST THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
UH, BEFORE--
BEFORE WE GO INTO
ANY SPECIFICS ON THAT SUBJECT,
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU
A MORE POINTED QUESTION.
DO YOU KNOW WHO KILLED
SCOTT OSTELHOFF ?
NO, I DON'T.
DO YOU KNOW OF ANY CONNECTION
BETWEEN HIS DEATH
AND AGENTS MULDER OR SCULLY ?
NO.
I'M AWARE OF ONE DEATH
IN CONNECTION, THOUGH.
MY SON,
WHO DIED EARLY THIS MORNING.
MR. KRITSCHGAU,
YOU'RE EMPLOYED BY
THE DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE,
IS THAT CORRECT ?
[ Kritschgau ]
TECHNICALLY.
PART OF MY REMUNERATION
HAS COME FROM ANOTHER SOURCE.
A CONGRESSIONAL LOBBYING FIRM--
SOMETHING CALLED ROUSH.
ROUSH ?
ANY IDEA WHAT THAT IS ?
NO, SIR.
THIS IS CRAZY, JUST CRAZY.
WELL, CRAZY IN WHAT SENSE ?
IN THAT IT MIGHT SAVE
YOUR SISTER'S LIFE ?
YOU'RE NOT A DOCTOR.
YOU HAVE NO PLACE EVEN
SUGGESTING THIS SCIENCE FICTION.
IT'S NOT SCIENCE FICTION.
HE'S NEVER HEARD OF IT !
BILL.
[ Sighs ]
- HAVE YOU ?
- NO, I HAVEN'T.
I THINK THERE'S AN OBVIOUS
DIFFERENCE OF OPINION HERE.
[ Scully ]
I THINK...
THAT EVERYBODY HERE HAS
THEIR HEART IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
BUT I NEED IT
TO BE MY DECISION.
DANA--
I KNOW YOU'RE ONLY
LOOKING OUT FOR ME, BILL,
BUT I DON'T THINK
YOU HAVE ALL THE FACTS.
DON'T YOU THINK YOU SHOULD
LISTEN TO YOUR DOCTOR ?
YES.  I AM.
WOULD SHE HAVE TO STOP
HER CONVENTIONAL TREATMENT ?
[ Doctor ]
TO BE HONEST,
AT THIS POINT...
THE ONLY APPROACH I HAVE LEFT
WITH HER PARTICULAR CANCER...
IS QUITE UNCONVENTIONAL.
I'D LIKE TO TRY THIS.
YOU REALLY BELIEVE
THIS CRAP, DON'T YOU ?
YES, I DO.
YOU SEE,
SHE'S YOUR BIG DEFENDER,
BUT I THINK THE TRUTH IS
SHE JUST DOESN'T WANT
TO DISAPPOINT YOU.
IF IT WORKS, I DON'T CARE
WHAT YOU THINK SHE THINKS.
YOU'RE A REAL PIECE OF WORK,
YOU KNOW THAT, MR. MULDER ?
WHY IS THAT ?
BECAUSE I DON'T THINK
THE WAY YOU THINK ?
BECAUSE I WON'T JUST SIT
PASSIVELY BACK AND WATCH
THE FAMILY TRAGEDY UNFOLD ?
YOU'RE THE REASON FOR IT.
AND I'VE ALREADY LOST ONE SISTER
TO THIS QUEST YOU'RE ON.
NOW I'M LOSING ANOTHER.
HAS IT BEEN WORTH IT ?
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I MEAN.
HAVE YOU FOUND
WHAT YOU'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR ?
- NO.
YOU KNOW HOW
THAT MAKES ME FEEL ?
IN A WAY, I THINK I DO.
I LOST SOMEONE
VERY CLOSE TO ME.
I LOST A SISTER.
I LOST MY FATHER.
ALL BECAUSE OF THIS THING
I'M LOOKING FOR.
THIS WHAT ?
LITTLE GREEN ALIENS ?
YEAH.
LITTLE GREEN ALIENS.
YOU'RE ONE SORRY
SON OF A BITCH.
THERE'S NOT A LOT MORE TO SAY.
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
ONE SORRY
SON OF A BITCH SPEAKING.
HOW'S OUR PATIENT ?
YOU DID FIND THE CHIP,
DIDN'T YOU, AGENT MULDER ?
YES.
I CAN IMAGINE
THERE WAS SOME QUESTION
AS TO ITS MEDICAL VALUE.
WELL, THERE STILL IS.
AND SO I HAVE YET
TO EARN YOUR TRUST,
IN SPITE OF MY GESTURE.
[ Chuckles ]
YOU COULD SAY THAT, YEAH.
WELL, I HAVE SOMETHING ELSE
TO OFFER YOU.
I'VE ARRANGED A MEETING
I THINK YOU'LL WANT TO ATTEND,
MR. MULDER.
TABASCO.
IT CURES ANYTHING.
I'LL KEEP THAT IN MIND.
YOU KNOW HIM OR SOMETHIN' ?
I THINK THAT'S MY SISTER.
SAMANTHA ?
I WAS AFRAID
I'D NEVER SEE YOU AGAIN.
HE ALWAYS TOLD ME SOMETHING
HAD HAPPENED TO YOU THAT NIGHT.
WHO ?
WHO TOLD YOU THAT ?
MY FATHER.
I NEVER REALLY KNEW
WHAT HAPPENED.
I COULD NEVER PUT THE MEMORIES
ALL BACK TOGETHER.
BUT AS MUCH
AS I TRIED TO REMEMBER,
I TRIED MORE TO FORGET.
WHY ?
I WAS EIGHT YEARS OLD...
AND FRIGHTENED TO DEATH.
AND THEY TOLD ME
THAT I WAS AN ORPHAN.
BUT YOU CALL THAT MAN
YOUR FATHER.
SOMETIME LATER,
I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG,
MY FOSTER PARENTS TOOK ME
TO A HOTEL ROOM...
AND SAID THAT I WAS
GONNA SEE MY FATHER.
BUT YOU KNEW
WHO YOUR FATHER WAS.
I THOUGHT I KNEW.
BUT HE TOLD ME THAT
IT HAD ALL BEEN A SECRET,
AND THAT HE AND MOM...
HADN'T TOLD ANYONE
TO PROTECT THE FAMILY.
AND YOU BELIEVED THAT ?
HE WAS SO KIND TO ME.
AND HE WAS THE ONLY ONE
I COULD REMEMBER
FROM BEFORE WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU DON'T REMEMBER ANYTHING
ABOUT THAT NIGHT ?
I REMEMBER...
YOU.
I REMEMBER SOMETHING.
MEN, AND--
AND THEN NOTHING.
I CAN HELP YOU.
YOU WERE ABDUCTED, SAMANTHA.
I CAN HELP YOU TO REMEMBER.
I DON'T WANT TO, FOX.
I DON'T.
THEN WHY COME HERE AT ALL ?
MY FATHER TOLD ME
THAT HE'D FOUND YOU.
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME
VERY BADLY--
THAT YOU'D BEEN LOOKING
FOR ME FOR A LONG TIME.
IS THAT TRUE ?
I'M SO SORRY, FOX.
AND I WISH THAT I'D KNOWN
HOW TO FIND YOU.
WHAT YOU'VE BEEN TOLD--
I WANT YOU
TO LISTEN TO ME, OKAY ?
WHAT YOU'VE BEEN TOLD
BY THAT MAN...
MAY NOT BE TRUE.
WHY DO YOU SAY THAT ?
BECAUSE THE MAN
THAT BROUGHT YOU HERE...
HAS KNOWN WHERE I'VE BEEN
FOR A VERY LONG TIME.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY WOULDN'T HE TELL ME ?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I THINK HE'S KEPT
A LOT OF THINGS FROM YOU.
I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
HE'S BEEN A GOOD FATHER TO ME.
HE'S GIVEN ME A LIFE,
AND HE CARED FOR ME
WHEN THERE WAS NO ONE ELSE.
THEN I WANT YOU
TO COME WITH ME--
COME WITH ME TO SEE MOM.
- MOM IS ALIVE ?
- YES.
AND I KNOW SHE'D LIKE
TO SEE YOU VERY, VERY MUCH.
- I CAN'T.
- WHY NOT ?
THIS IS TOO MUCH.
I DIDN'T WANNA
COME HERE AT ALL, FOX.
I WAS AFRAID TO SEE YOU.
I HAVE ANOTHER LIFE NOW.
I HAVE CHILDREN OF MY OWN.
DON'T--  NO.
NO, PLEASE DON'T GO.
I CAN'T STAY HERE NOW.
TELL ME HOW I CAN FIND YOU.
I NEED SOME TIME.
JUST-JUST TELL ME
WHERE I CAN FIND YOU.
PLEASE DON'T, FOX !
WE WILL DO THIS
ON YOUR TIME.  JUST--
THEN PLEASE--
PLEASE LET ME GO.
I PROMISE YOU
I'LL THINK ABOUT IT.
[ Doctor ]
YOU DOING OKAY ?
[ Scully ]  MMM.
EITHER IT'S MY HEAD
OR I'M A LONG WAY
FROM MED SCHOOL,
BUT I CAN'T REMEMBER WHAT
YOU'RE INJECTING ME WITH.
FLURO-DEOXYGLUCOSE.
DEOXYGLUCOSE.
IF YOU'RE MAKING ANY PROGRESS,
I'M HOPING IT MIGHT SHOW UP
FIRST IN A PET SCAN.
YOU'RE NOT HOLDING
YOUR BREATH, ARE YOU ?
I'M GOING AFTER YOUR CANCER
AS AGGRESSIVELY AS
I KNOW HOW, DANA.
IF I CAN JUMP-START
YOUR IMMUNE SYSTEM,
IF I CAN GET YOUR CYTOLYTIC
CELLS TO RECOGNIZE YOUR TUMOR...
AS SOMETHING TO ATTACK,
THEN THERE'S A CHANCE.
HAVE YOU EVER WITNESSED
A MIRACLE, DR. ZUCKERMAN ?
I DON'T KNOW THAT I HAVE.
BUT I HAVE SEEN PEOPLE
MAKE RECOVERIES--
COME BACK FROM SO FAR GONE,
I CAN'T EXPLAIN IT.
ISN'T THAT A MIRACLE ?
MAYBE THEY ARE MIRACLES,
BUT I DON'T DARE
CALL THEM THAT.
THANK YOU.
MY APOLOGIES FOR THE...
RATHER HASTY DEPARTURE
LAST NIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME ?
WANT FROM YOU ?
YOU GIVE ME THESE THINGS,
THE ONLY THINGS
I EVER WANTED,
AND I CAN'T THINK
OF ANY REASON
FOR YOU TO DO SO.
WELL, THAT'S TRUE.
NO ACT IS COMPLETELY SELFLESS.
BUT I'VE COME TODAY NOT TO--
NOT TO ASK BUT TO OFFER.
OFFER YOU THE TRUTH THAT
YOU'VE SO DESPERATELY SOUGHT--
ABOUT THE PROJECT,
ABOUT THE MEN
WHO'VE CONSPIRED TO PROTECT IT.
I KNOW THE TRUTH.
DO YOU ?
I SPOKE TO ONE OF YOUR MEN.
AND YOU KNOW
HE'S NOT A LIAR ?
I'VE SEEN ENOUGH TO KNOW
HE'S NOT A LIAR, YEAH.
YOU'VE SEEN BUT SCANT PIECES
OF THE WHOLE.
WHAT MORE
CAN YOU SHOW ME ?
THIS MAN YOU SPOKE TO,
MICHAEL KRITSCHGAU,
HE'S DECEIVED YOU
WITH BEAUTIFUL LIES.
HE'S TOLD YOU THAT EVERYTHING
YOU'VE EVER BELIEVED...
ABOUT THE EXISTENCE
OF EXTRATERRESTRIAL LIFE
IS UNTRUE.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING ?
AS I SAID,
I'M OFFERING YOU A CHANCE
TO KNOW THE TRUTH.
IN EXCHANGE FOR WHAT ?
QUIT THE F.B.I.
COME WORK FOR ME.
YOU CAN MAKE YOUR PROBLEMS
GO AWAY.
NO DEAL.
AFTER ALL I'VE GIVEN YOU ?
WHAT HAVE--
WHAT HAVE YOU GIVEN ME ?
THE CLAIM OF A CURE FOR SCULLY ?
IS SHE CURED ?
YOU SHOW ME MY SISTER
ONLY TO TAKE HER RIGHT BACK ?
YOU'VE GIVEN ME NOTHING.
I INTEND TO KEEP MY PROMISES.
I JUST NEED SOMETHING FROM YOU.
YOU MURDERED MY FATHER.
YOU KILLED SCULLY'S SISTER.
AND IF SCULLY DIES,
I WILL KILL YOU.
I DON'T CARE
WHOSE FATHER YOU ARE.
I WILL PUT YOU DOWN.
WELL, YOU'RE CERTAINLY CAPABLE,
SO I'VE BEEN TOLD.
I UNDERSTAND YOU HAVE
A HEARING TOMORROW,
WHERE YOU'LL HAVE TO TESTIFY
TO THESE MURDEROUS IMPULSES
OF YOURS.
WHEN YOU RECONSIDER,
THE OFFER STILL STANDS.
[ Mrs. Scully ]
DANA ?
DR. ZUCKERMAN CALLED.
HE, UH--
HE SAID THAT
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME.
WHAT IS IT ?
[ Sobbing ]
I'M SO SORRY.
I FIGHT AND I FIGHT...
AND I FIGHT,
BUT I'VE BEEN SO STUPID.
WHAT ?  WHAT IS IT ?
I'VE COME SO FAR IN MY LIFE
ON SIMPLE FAITH.
AND NOW WHEN I NEED IT THE MOST,
I JUST PUSH IT AWAY.
I MEAN, WHY--
WHY DO I WEAR THIS ?
WHY DO I WEAR THIS, MOM ?
I PUT SOMETHING
THAT I DON'T EVEN KNOW...
OR UNDERSTAND
UNDER THE SKIN OF MY NECK.
I WILL SUBJECT MYSELF
TO THESE CRAZY TREATMENTS,
AND I KEEP TELLING MYSELF
THAT I'M DOING EVERYTHING I CAN,
BUT IT'S A LIE.
YOU HAVE NOT LOST
YOUR FAITH, DANA.
BUT I HAVE... IN A WAY.
WHEN YOU ASKED--
WHEN YOU ASKED FATHER McCUE
TO DINNER...
TO MINISTER TO MY FAITH,
I JUST CLOSED OFF TO HIM.
WHAT'S IMPORTANT NOW...
IS THAT
YOU SAVE YOUR ENERGY.
I'M NOT GETTING BETTER, MOM.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT YET.
THE PET SCAN
SHOWED NO IMPROVEMENT.
I KNOW YOU'RE AFRAID.
I KNOW YOU'RE AFRAID
TO TELL ME,
BUT YOU HAVE TO
TELL SOMEONE.
I'LL MAKE A STATEMENT
RIGHT HERE.
CLONING WILL CONTINUE.
THE HUMAN MIND WILL CONTINUE
TO INQUIRE INTO THIS.
HUMAN CLONING WILL TAKE PLACE,
AND IT'LL TAKE PLACE
IN MY LIFETIME.
I THINK IT'S RIGHT AND PROPER
THAT WE CONTINUE
THIS KIND OF INQUIRY.
I THINK IT HOLDS UNTOLD BENEFITS
FOR HUMAN KIND.
TURN ON YOUR TELEVISION.
ARE YOU WATCHING THE HEARINGS ?
DO YOU SEE WHO'S THERE ?
HE'S GATHERING INFORMATION
FOR WHO ?
OUR COLLEAGUE WAS SUPPOSED TO
HAVE FIXED THE F.B.I. PROBLEM.
YOU WILL FIX IT NOW.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME ?
THEN I WILL FIX IT FOR GOOD.
[ Blevins ]
AGENT MULDER,
WILL YOU PLEASE TAKE A SEAT ?
SOMETHING URGENTLY IMPORTANT
HAS COME TO THE FORE.
AS YOU'RE SET TO TESTIFY
ON YOUR OWN BEHALF LATER TODAY,
I'VE RECEIVED
ALARMING FORENSIC EVIDENCE...
FROM THE MAN'S BODY
FOUND IN YOUR APARTMENT.
I HAVE HERE IN MY HAND
BALLISTIC DATA...
MATCHING YOUR SERVICE WEAPON,
AGENT MULDER.
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT ?
I'M NOT AT LIBERTY TO SAY.
BUT UNLESS YOU CAN OFFER UP
SOMEONE ELSE WHO MIGHT HAVE
FIRED THE KILL SHOT,
EVERYTHING POINTS TO YOU
AS THIS MAN'S MURDERER.
ARE YOU PREPARED
TO GIVE TESTIMONY...
YOU'RE NOT THE MAN
WHO FIRED THE SHOT ?
WHY AM I HERE ?
THE MAN WORKED FOR
THE DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE,
AGENT MULDER.
THE MAN WAS SPYING ON ME.
DO YOU KNOW FOR WHOM ?
AGENT SCULLY...
WAS PREPARED TO NAME
THE MAN AT THE F.B.I...
WHO WAS INVOLVED IN THIS PLOT
AGAINST YOU AND HER.
WE BELIEVE SHE WAS GOING TO NAME
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR SKINNER,
WHOM WE HAVE LEARNED HAS BEEN
WORKING INSIDE THE F.B.I.
WITH A SECRET AGENDA.
I REFUSE TO BELIEVE THAT.
WE'VE ACCUMULATED SUBSTANTIAL
EVIDENCE AGAINST HIM.
CAN YOU SHOW IT TO ME ?
AGENT MULDER,
IF YOU NAME THIS MAN TODAY
IN YOUR TESTIMONY,
WE CAN FILE CHARGES
AGAINST HIM,
CHARGES WHICH MAY VERY WELL
EXONERATE YOU.
NAME SKINNER
AND SAVE MYSELF.
THAT'S WHAT I CALLED YOU HERE
TO RECOMMEND.
AS A FRIEND.
I'LL SEE YOU AT THE HEARING.
GOOD MORNING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE ?
YOU HAVE A HEARING.
YEAH.
I CAME BY LAST NIGHT,
BUT I DIDN'T HAVE THE HEART
TO WAKE YOU.
CAME BY FOR WHAT ?
MULDER, WHAT IS IT ?
I WAS LOST LAST NIGHT.
BUT AS I STOOD HERE,
I THOUGHT I'D FOUND MY WAY.
I'VE BEEN, UH--
I'VE BEEN OFFERED A DEAL,
A DEAL THAT COULD SAVE MY LIFE
IN A WAY.
AND THOUGH I'D REFUSED
THE DEAL EARLIER,
I LEFT HERE LAST NIGHT
WITH MY MIND MADE UP TO TAKE IT.
A DEAL WITH WHO ?
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I'M NOT TAKING THE DEAL.
I'M NOT TAKING ANY DEAL,
NOT AFTER WHAT HAPPENED
THIS MORNING.
WHAT HAPPENED THIS MORNING ?
SECTION CHIEF BLEVINS DIRECTED
ME TO IMPLICATE SKINNER--
TO NAME HIM AS THE MAN INSIDE
IN THE F.B.I...
WHO MAY HAVE DECEIVED US BOTH.
AND IF I NAME HIM,
THEY'LL PROTECT ME.
ARE YOU GOING TO
NAME HIM ?
NO.
THEN THEY'LL PROSECUTE YOU.
YEAH, IF THEY HAVE
EVIDENCE AGAINST ME,
THEY KNOW I KILLED THAT MAN.
EVEN WITH
THE BALLISTICS EVIDENCE,
I CAN STILL BE THE SHOOTER.
SCULLY, I CAN'T LET YOU
TAKE THE BLAME...
BECAUSE OF YOUR BROTHER,
BECAUSE OF YOUR MOTHER,
AND BECAUSE
I COULDN'T LIVE WITH IT.
TO LIVE THE LIE
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE IT,
LIKE THESE MEN WHO DECEIVE US...
WHO GAVE YOU THIS DISEASE.
WE ALL HAVE OUR FAITH,
AND MINE IS IN THE TRUTH.
THEN WHY
DID YOU COME HERE...
IF YOU'D ALREADY
MADE UP YOUR MIND ?
BECAUSE I KNEW YOU'D...
TALK ME OUT OF IT
IF I WAS MAKING A MISTAKE.
[ Door Opens ]
YOU'LL BE IN MY PRAYERS.
HAVE THE FATHER SAY A FEW
"HAIL MULDERS" FOR ME, OKAY ?
IF HE'S A NO-SHOW,
I'M GONNA ASK
FOR A BENCH WARRANT.
[ Door Opens ]
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
[ Blevins ]
AGENT MULDER,
THE ASSEMBLED MEMBERS
OF THIS REVIEW PANEL...
FIRST CONVENED TO ADDRESS
YOUR REPORTED DEATH,
ONLY TO FIND SHORTLY THAT
THIS REPORT HAD BEEN A LIE--
THAT YOU WERE INDEED
VERY MUCH ALIVE...
AND THAT THE BODY FOUND
IN YOUR APARTMENT,
BELIEVED TO BE YOURS,
WAS A MURDER VICTIM
KILLED WITH A WEAPON...
ISSUED BY THE F.B.I.
AND REGISTERED TO YOU.
RESPECTFULLY, SIR,
I'VE COME HERE TODAY
TO SET THE RECORD STRAIGHT...
SO THAT THIS PROCESS
YOU'VE BEGUN CAN BE COMPLETED,
AND THE GUILTY PARTIES
CAN BE NAMED.
RESPECTFULLY, SIR,
I'D LIKE TO ASK
FOR A SHORT BREAK.
I'M... READY TO PROCEED,
PLEASE, SIR.
GO ON, AGENT MULDER.
FOUR YEARS AGO,
WHILE WORKING ON AN ASSIGNMENT
OUTSIDE THE F.B.I. MAINSTREAM,
I WAS PAIRED WITH
SPECIAL AGENT DANA SCULLY,
WHO I BELIEVED WAS SENT
TO SPY ON ME--
TO DEBUNK MY INVESTIGATIONS
INTO THE PARANORMAL.
THAT AGENT SCULLY DID NOT
FOLLOW THESE ORDERS...
IS A TESTAMENT TO HER INTEGRITY
AS AN INVESTIGATOR,
A SCIENTIST
AND A HUMAN BEING.
SHE HAS PAID DEARLY
FOR THIS INTEGRITY.
[ Blevins ]  AGENT MULDER,
AGENT SCULLY LIED
STRAIGHT-FACED TO THIS PANEL
ABOUT YOUR DEATH.
SHE LIED BECAUSE
I ASKED HER TO.
BECAUSE I HAD EVIDENCE
OF A CONSPIRACY--
A CONSPIRACY AGAINST
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
WE'VE ALREADY HEARD TESTIMONY
TO THESE ALLEGATIONS,
AGENT MULDER.
AND A CONSPIRACY INTENDED
TO DESTROY THE LIVES...
OF THOSE WHO WOULD REVEAL
ITS TRUE PURPOSE;
TO CONDUCT EXPERIMENTS
ON UNWITTING VICTIMS...
TO FURTHER A SECRET AGENDA FOR
SOMEONE WITHIN THE GOVERNMENT
OPERATING AT LEVELS...
WITHOUT RESTRAINT
OR RESPONSIBILITY,
WITHOUT MORALS OR CONSCIOUS.
MEN WHO PRETEND TO HONOR
AS THEY DECEIVE.
THE PRICE OF THIS BETRAYAL--
THE LIVES AND REPUTATIONS
OF THOSE DECEIVED.
AGENT SCULLY...
IS LYING IN A HOSPITAL BED
RIGHT NOW DIAGNOSED
WITH TERMINAL CANCER.
THE VICTIM OF THESE SAME TESTS,
CONDUCTED WITHOUT
HER KNOWLEDGE OR CONSENT...
BY THESE SAME MEN WHO,
AS THEY TRY
TO COVER THEIR TRACKS,
WHO SUBORN AND PERSECUTE
THE SAME PEOPLE THEY'VE USED
IN THEIR PLOT,
I WILL NOW CALL BY NAME.
[ Man ]
AGENT MULDER,
DID YOU OR DID YOU NOT
SHOOT THE MAN FOUND DEAD
IN YOUR APARTMENT ?
- I WILL ANSWER THAT QUESTION.
- DID YOU SHOOT
SCOTT OSTELHOFF,
EMPLOYEE OF
THE DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE ?
- I WILL ANSWER THAT QUESTION.
-[ Man ]  ANSWER THE QUESTION
ASKED, AGENT MULDER !
I WILL ANSWER THE QUESTION
AFTER I NAME THE MAN !
[ Blevins ]  AGENT MULDER--
[ Mulder ]
I WILL ANSWER THAT QUESTION...
AFTER I NAME THE MAN WHO IS
RESPONSIBLE FOR AGENT SCULLY.
THE SAME MAN WHO DIRECTED THAT
MY APARTMENT BE SURVEILLED
BY THE D.O.D.
A MAN I WANT TO SEE PROSECUTED
FOR HIS CRIMES,
WHO IS SITTING IN
THIS VERY ROOM AS I SPEAK.
AGENT MULDER, THE SECTION CHIEF
HAS ASKED YOU A QUESTION !
YOU ARE GOING TO ANSWER !
- I CAN'T DO THAT, SIR.
- YOU CAN AND YOU WILL !
I CAN'T DO THAT, SIR,
BECAUSE THE SECTION CHIEF IS
THE MAN I'M ABOUT TO NAME !
[ Indistinct ]
[ Door Opens ]
[ Groans ]
THE SMOKING MAN'S DEAD.
HOW ?
SHOT THROUGH HIS WINDOW.
FORENSICS FOUND IT
AT THE SCENE.
WE'RE ASSUMING
IT'S HIS BLOOD.
ASSUMING ?
WELL, NO BODY WAS FOUND,
THOUGH THERE WAS
TOO MUCH BLOOD LOST
FOR ANYONE TO HAVE SURVIVED.
THIS AFTERNOON
WHEN YOU NAMED BLEVINS,
HOW DID YOU KNOW ?
I DIDN'T.
I JUST GUESSED.
WELL, IT WAS A HELL
OF A GUESS.
BLEVINS HAD BEEN ON PAYROLL
FOR FOUR YEARS...
TO A BIOTECHNOLOGY COMPANY
CALLED ROUSH,
WHICH IS SOMEHOW CONNECTED
TO ALL THIS.
WELL, I'M SURE
WHATEVER CONNECTIONS THERE WERE,
THEY'RE BEING ERASED RIGHT NOW.
THEY'RE CLEANING UP,
TAKING EVERYTHING AWAY.
NOT EVERYTHING.
SCULLY'S CANCER'S
GONE INTO REMISSION.
THAT'S UNBELIEVABLE NEWS.
IT'S THE BEST NEWS
I COULD HAVE EVER HEARD.
WHAT TURNED IT AROUND ?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T THINK WE'LL EVER KNOW.
- CAN I SEE HER ?
- YEAH.  SHE'S IN THERE
WITH HER FAMILY RIGHT NOW.
BUT I'M SURE
SHE'D LOVE TO SEE YOU.
[ Child ]
I MADE THIS !