[ Scully ]
IT BEGINS WHERE IT ENDS--
IN NOTHINGNESS.
A NIGHTMARE BORN
FROM DEEPEST FEARS...
COMING TO ME UNGUARDED,
WHISPERING IMAGES UNLOCKED
FROM TIME AND DISTANCE.
A SOUL UNBOUND, TOUCHED
BY OTHERS BUT NEVER HELD...
ON A COURSE CHARTED
BY SOME UNSEEN HAND.
THE JOURNEY AHEAD
PROMISING NO MORE...
THAN MY PAST REFLECTED
BACK UPON ME...
UNTIL, AT LAST,
I REACH THE END,
FACING A TRUTH
I CAN NO LONGER DENY,
ALONE, AS EVER.
EXCUSE ME.  I'M LOOKING
FOR THE SPECIAL-NEEDS WARD.
SECOND DOOR
IN THE MAIN HALL.
THANKS.
EMILY ?
I'D LIKE YOU
TO MEET A FRIEND OF MINE.
HIS NAME IS MULDER.
REMEMBER I TOLD YOU
ABOUT HIM ?
HI.
SHE'S A LITTLE SHY.
WHAT ARE YOU COLORING ?
A POTATO.
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
MR. POTATO HEAD ?
HE LOOKS LIKE THIS.
DOESN'T HE ?
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK, OKAY ?
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
SOMETHING'S WRONG,
ISN'T IT ?
I FOUND EMILY'S
SURROGATE MOTHER.
I HAD FROHIKE HACK
INTO THE CALIFORNIA SOCIAL
SERVICES ADOPTION DATABASE.
YOU GOT A NAME ?
YEAH.  HER MOTHER OF RECORD
IS ONE ANNA FUGAZZI.
FUGAZZI ?
YEAH, AS IN SLANG TERM
FOR "FAKE."
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY CREATE A FALSE RECORD ?
BECAUSE THERE ARE
NO TRUE RECORDS.
EMILY DIDN'T COME
INTO THIS WORLD THROUGH
ANY SYSTEM THAT KEEPS THEM.
WELL, HOW DID SHE
COME INTO THIS WORLD ?
HAVE YOU ASKED
YOURSELF THAT ?
WELL, SHE WAS BORN TO SOMEONE.
SHE HAD TO BELONG TO SOMEONE.
SOMEONE WHO'S PROVEN THAT
THEY'LL DO ANYTHING
TO PROTECT HER...
OR THEIR INTEREST IN HER.
I CAN PROTECT HER TOO.
AND WHO'S GONNA
PROTECT YOU ?
EMILY'S ADOPTIVE PARENTS
ARE BOTH DEAD BY NO ACCIDENT.
I KNOW.  I--
I'VE CONSIDERED THAT,
BUT I'VE ALSO CONSIDERED...
THAT THERE'S ONLY
ONE RIGHT THING TO DO.
EMILY.
WHY DIDN'T YOU
CALL ME SOONER ?
BECAUSE
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
BUT I NEED YOU NOW TO BE
A WITNESS ON MY BEHALF
IN THIS HEARING.
AND I SHOULD
HAVE DECLINED...
IF I NEVER WANT TO SEE YOU
HURT OR HARMED IN ANY WAY.
THEN WHY ARE YOU HERE ?
BECAUSE I KNOW SOMETHING
THAT I HAVEN'T SAID,
SOMETHING THAT THEY'LL
USE AGAINST YOU...
TO JEOPARDIZE
YOUR CUSTODY OF EMILY.
NO MATTER HOW MUCH YOU
LOVE THIS LITTLE GIRL,
SHE'S A MIRACLE THAT WAS
NEVER MEANT TO BE, SCULLY.
THEY'RE READY FOR YOU.
[ Man ]
AGENT MULDER,
HELP ME OUT HERE.
DOES F.B.I. STAND FOR
FEDERAL BUREAU OF IMAGINATION ?
AM I TO UNDERSTAND
THAT YOUR PARTNER,
ALONG WITH A DOZEN OTHER WOMEN
IN ALLENTOWN, PENNSYLVANIA,
WAS ABDUCTED BY EMPLOYEES
OF OUR FEDERAL GOVERNMENT ?
SHE WAS MISSING FOR FOUR WEEKS.
THAT'S DOCUMENTED IN THE FILE.
AND YOU FOUND EVIDENCE
THAT DURING THIS TIME,
SHE WAS SUBJECTED TO
A SERIES OF EXPERIMENTS...
WHERE, YOU SAY,
THEY EXTRACTED HER OVA ?
YES.  ALL OF THEM.
CAN THAT BE DONE ?
I BELIEVE IT CAN...
AND WAS...
AND THAT EMILY SIM WAS
CONCEIVED AS A RESULT
OF THOSE EXPERIMENTS.
AND THAT
CAN BE DONE AS WELL ?
I DON'T KNOW
HOW ELSE TO EXPLAIN IT.
A MEDICAL EXAM OF MISS SCULLY
WOULD SHOW THAT SHE
HASN'T GIVEN BIRTH.
YOU KNOW,
UNDER NORMAL CIRCUMSTANCES,
THIS PETITION
WOULD BE FAIRLY SIMPLE.
BUT I'M HAVING
A HARD TIME WRAPPING
MY BRAIN AROUND THIS...
MICHAEL CRICHTON BIT.
I INCLUDED THIS
INFORMATION IN ANTICIPATION
OF YOUR REACTION...
AND HOW IT MIGHT LOOK IF YOU
RECEIVED THIS INFORMATION
WITHOUT ANY EXPLANATION.
CAN YOU GIVE ME
AN EXPLANATION...
WHY ANYONE WOULD
KIDNAP MISS SCULLY...
TO CONCEIVE THIS CHILD,
THEN PUT IT UP
FOR ADOPTION ?
NO, BUT THE FACT REMAINS
THAT MISS SCULLY IS
THE MOTHER OF THIS CHILD.
NOT IN ANY
LEGAL DEFINITION.
WELL, IF YOU CAN SHOW ME
A LEGAL PRECEDENT FOR THIS CASE,
I'D LIKE TO SEE IT.
DANA HAS KNOWN
FOR QUITE SOME TIME
THAT SHE CAN'T BEAR CHILDREN.
SHE HASN'T KNOWN WHY.
NOW, HOWEVER THAT HAPPENED,
THE FACT THAT SHE
CAN ADOPT THIS CHILD,
HER OWN FLESH AND BLOOD,
IS SOMETHING I DON'T FEEL
I HAVE THE RIGHT TO QUESTION...
AND I DON'T BELIEVE
ANYBODY HAS THE RIGHT
TO STAND IN THE WAY OF.
TAKES TWO OF US JUST
TO GET MY SISTER-IN-LAW
INTO BED THESE DAYS.
WHEN IS SHE DUE ?
TWO WEEKS AGO.
WHY DIDN'T YOU
TELL ME, MULDER ?
I NEVER EXPECTED THIS.
I THOUGHT
I WAS PROTECTING YOU.
WHY WOULD THEY DO THIS TO ME ?
I ONLY KNOW THAT
GENETIC EXPERIMENTS
WERE BEING DONE,
THAT CHILDREN
WERE BEING CREATED.
CHILDREN BEING CREATED
FOR WHO ?
FOR WHO ?  FOR WHAT ?
I DON'T KNOW.
[ Phone Ringing ]
HELLO.
HELLO ?
IS ANYBODY THERE ?
I NEED A CALL TRACED.
AN INCOMING CALL
TO RESIDENTIAL LINE 550-0380.
MULDER--
DON'T HANG UP.
OKAY, THANKS.
I GOT A TRACE.
COUNTY CHILDREN'S CENTER.
[ Pounding ]
WHAT IS IT ?
WHAT'S THE MATTER ?
HAS ANYONE BEEN HERE
IN THE LAST HALF HOUR ?
NO.  WHAT'S GOING ON ?
SHE'S BURNING UP.
I'LL CALL 911.
SCULLY.
THERE'S SOMETHING
ON HER NECK.
OH, MY GOD.
OKAY, NOW, THAT DOESN'T HURT.
I'M GONNA TURN THIS
LITTLE THING.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TRY BACK LATER.
I JUST SPOKE
TO THE SOCIAL WORKER.
SHE HASN'T BEEN ABLE
TO REACH EMILY'S DOCTOR.
HI.
HOW IS SHE ?
WELL, WE'VE PUT HER
ON A SALINE DRIP
TO REHYDRATE HER.
SHE'S RUNNING A FEVER
OF ABOUT 102.
IT'S GOOD YOU GOT HER HERE
WHEN YOU DID.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT'S CAUSING IT ?
SOME KIND OF INFECTION,
PROBABLY RELATED TO
THE CYST ON HER NECK.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT IS ?
NO.  I'M HAVING IT BIOPSIED.
I'LL GET IT OFF
TO THE LAB RIGHT AWAY.
NOW, ARE YOU TWO
THE PARENTS ?
- I'M HER MOTHER.
- OH, OKAY.
WELL, CAN YOU
GIVE ME ANY HISTORY
THAT MIGHT HELP ?
I KNOW THAT SHE WAS
BEING TREATED FOR ANEMIA.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT TYPE ?
I WAS TOLD...
THAT IT WAS SOME KIND
OF AUTOIMMUNE HEMOLYTIC ANEMIA.
HER TREATMENT
IS EXPERIMENTAL.
WHO'S HER DOCTOR ?
HIS NAME IS CALDERON.
I DON'T KNOW HIM.
EMILY, I'M GONNA ROLL YOU
ONTO YOUR SIDE, SWEETIE.
WAIT !  WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT.  STOP !
STOP !  MOVE
AWAY FROM HER !
- MOVE AWAY FROM HER !
- SIR, I NEED TO GET IN THERE.
[ Mulder ]
GET AWAY FROM HER !
GET AWAY !
DON'T GO IN THERE.
[ Gasping ]
IS SHE STILL SLEEPING ?
THEY HAVE HER
ON A MILD SEDATIVE.
THE E.R. DOCTOR
IS IN AND OUT
OF CONSCIOUSNESS.
HOW DID YOU KNOW ?
IF EMILY IS
SOMEONE'S CREATION,
THEN IT OCCURRED TO ME
THAT SHE MIGHT SHARE
THE SAME BODY CHEMISTRY...
THAT WE'VE SEEN BEFORE.
I HAD THEM PUT THE DOCTOR IN
A COOLING BATH LIKE YOU DID
WHEN I WAS EXPOSED TO THIS.
SO WHAT NOW ?
I MEAN, SHE'S STILL
JUST A LITTLE GIRL.
YOU SAY THAT I CAN'T
PROTECT HER, BUT I CAN'T
LET THIS BE HER LIFE.
JUST A FEW DAYS AGO,
SHE WAS FINE.
SHE WAS ALSO
BEING TREATED.
I NEED SOME ADVICE.
WITH EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENING HERE,
I'M A LITTLE AT SEA.
THIS DR. CALDERON YOU SAY
IS EMILY'S PHYSICIAN ?
HE'S REFUSING TO TRANSFER
HER MEDICAL RECORDS.
HE CAN'T DO THAT.
HE'S ENDANGERING HER LIFE.
HE SAID EMILY
WAS IN HIS CARE,
AND IF YOU'RE RESPONSIBLE
FOR STOPPING THAT, THEN
YOU'RE THE ONE ENDANGERING HER.
IT'S AN ETHICAL VIOLATION.
HE SAYS SHE WAS PART
OF A DOUBLE-BLIND
MEDICAL TRIAL...
AND THAT HE'S SPOKEN
TO YOU ABOUT IT.
HE ALSO SAYS
YOU HAVE NO AUTHORITY
OVER THIS CHILD.
WELL, AUTHORITY OR NOT,
I'M NOT LEAVING HER SIDE.
IT'S BEYOND ME,
I'M AFRAID.
BUT IT'S NOT BEYOND
DR. CALDERON.
I'D LIKE TO SAY
RIGHT UP FRONT THAT I KNOW
EMILY SIM PERSONALLY...
AS YOUR PARTNER PROBABLY
TOLD YOU, AND, UH--
MY GOD, I NEVER MET A SWEETER,
MORE COURAGEOUS LITTLE GIRL.
I'M SO SORRY TO HEAR
ABOUT HER DOWNTURN.
MY HOPE IS THAT
THESE CUSTODY ISSUES
CAN BE RESOLVED...
SO THAT SHE CAN RESUME
HER TREATMENT HERE.
BUT I'M AFRAID
I SIMPLY CAN'T RELEASE
ANY INFORMATION ABOUT HER...
AS IT RELATES TO OUR COMPANY'S
EXPERIMENTAL DRUG TRIALS.
WHAT CAN I SAY
TO CONVINCE YOU ?
IT'S REALLY NOT
ABOUT CONVINCING ME.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT--
WELL, THAT WE SIMPLY CANNOT DO.
IT'S PURELY
A BUSINESS REALITY.
IT HAS TO DO WITH PRANGEN'S
EXPOSURE TO LITIGATION.
AND, OF COURSE, I'LL NEED
TO PROTECT RESEARCH...
WHICH, FRANKLY, REPRESENTS
A SIGNIFICANT DOLLAR INVESTMENT.
SO I'M WASTING YOUR TIME.
THIS IS NOT WORTH THE LIFE
OF A THREE-YEAR-OLD GIRL.
I WOULDN'T FRAME IT LIKE THAT.
THAT'S NOT IT AT ALL.
LOOK, I'M TRULY SORRY,
BUT THERE'S REALLY
NOTHING I CAN DO.
HOWEVER, I DO WISH YOU
THE VERY BEST.
OKAY, THEN.
HOW YOU FEELING NOW ?
A LITTLE MORE HELPFUL ?
CONDESCENDING LIAR !
HELP !
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
WHAT YOUR COMPANY IS
REALLY IN BUSINESS FOR ?
HUH ?
ABDUCTING WOMEN AND STEALING
THEIR UNBORN CHILDREN.
MEDICAL RAPISTS,
THAT'S ALL YOU ARE !
NOW YOU'RE GONNA LET
THAT LITTLE GIRL DIE ?
SHE'S JUST A LAB RAT TO YOU !
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
WHOSE LIFE IS WORTH SAVING--
YOURS OR HERS ?
I WANT EVERYTHING
TO HELP THAT LITTLE GIRL !
[ Door Opens ]
I'LL BE BACK.
[ Alarm Chirps ]
WE'RE READY.
CAN YOU GIVE ME
A MINUTE WITH HER ?
HI.
[ TV Character ]
SOMETHING WAS GOING
AND GOT WORSE.
HEY, LOOFAH SPONGE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE ?
SWEETIE.
IN A MINUTE A NURSE IS GONNA
TAKE YOU TO DO SOME TESTS.
MOMMY SAID
NO MORE TESTS.
WE JUST WANT YOU TO GET BETTER.
THAT'S WHAT THESE TESTS
ARE ABOUT.
[ Whirring ]
[ Whirring Continues ]
HE CAME TO SEE ME.
HE KNOWS I'M INVOLVED.
NOW YOU BROUGHT HIM
TO SEE US.
UH, WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO TELL HIM ?
NOTHING.
[ Alarm Chirps ]
I HOPE YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS.
A NEOPLASTIC MASS,
A TUMOROUS INFECTION.
THE CYST IN THE BACK
OF EMILY'S NECK SEEMS
TO BE THE POINT OF ORIGIN.
AND FROM HER BLOOD TEST
LAST NIGHT AND HER SED READ
THIS MORNING,
IT ALSO SEEMS
TO BE GROWING RAPIDLY.
IS IT CANCER ?
NO.  CANCER GROWS
OUT OF CONTROL.
THESE ARE ANAEROBIC CHANNELS
FOLLOWING THE PATH OF
THE CENTRAL NERVOUS SYSTEM.
THEY HAVE THE EFFECT OF KILLING
THE SURROUNDING TISSUE,
DEPRIVING IT OF THE OXYGEN
IT NEEDS TO SURVIVE.
ITS POINT OF ORIGIN
IS PROXIMAL TO THE BRAIN
AND CENTRAL NERVOUS SYSTEM.
IT COULDN'T BE
IN A WORSE PLACE.
CAN YOU PUT HER
ON ANTIVIRALS ?
I'VE GOT HER ON
A LEVOPHED DRIP TO KEEP
HER BLOOD PRESSURE UP.
SHE'S GETTING STEROIDS
INTRAVENOUSLY TO BRING
DOWN INFLAMMATION.
WE COULD ATTEMPT
RADIATION THERAPY.
NO, YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
HER IMMUNE SYSTEM'S TOO WEAK.
WELL, WHAT CAN YOU DO ?
HAS ANYONE SPOKEN
TO DR. CALDERON ABOUT THIS ?
DR. CALDERON ?
[ Beeping ]
GET DR. VINET IN THERE
AND CALL THE POLICE.
[ Woman ]
DR. VINET TO ISOLATION.
HALT !  DR. CALDERON !
F.B.I. !  STOP THAT MAN !
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
YEAH.
[ Scully ]
MULDER, WHERE ARE YOU ?
I'M FOLLOWING DR. CALDERON.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU'VE BEEN FOLLOWING HIM ?
I JUST SAW HIM.
THERE WAS A SCARE HERE.
WHERE ?
HE WAS HERE.
HE CAME INTO EMILY'S ROOM.
IT APPEARS AS IF HE
INJECTED HER WITH SOMETHING.
IS SHE ALL RIGHT ?
SHE SEEMS TO BE.
BUT WE'RE RUNNING
A TOX SCREEN ANYWAY.
WHATEVER HE INJECTED HER WITH,
I DON'T THINK HE MEANT
TO HARM HER.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ?
- I THINK DR. CALDERON WENT
THERE TO TRY TO TREAT HER.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
WHY WOULD HE ENDANGER HER BEFORE
ONLY TO PROTECT HER NOW ?
AS A BLUFF.  I DON'T THINK
THEY WANT HER DEAD EITHER,
BUT FOR DIFFERENT REASONS.
LOOK, I'M GONNA CATCH UP
WITH YOU, ALL RIGHT ?
DETECTIVE.
HAPPY NEW YEAR.
THANKS FOR COMING DOWN.
I'M POSTING TWO COPS
OUTSIDE HER ROOM.
THAT MAY NOT BE NECESSARY.
WHAT IF THIS GUY CALDERON
IS THINKING ABOUT
COMING BACK ?
THERE SEEMS TO BE
SOME INDICATION THAT
HE CAME HERE TO HELP HER.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU SAID ON THE PHONE...
THAT HE WAS SOMEHOW
CONNECTED TO THE DEATH
OF EMILY'S PARENTS.
BECAUSE EMILY'S MOTHER
WANTED TO STOP THE TESTS,
JUST LIKE I DID.
AND I GUESS
THAT'S WHY HE CAME HERE.
BECAUSE AS MUCH AS THEY
WILL DO ANYTHING TO REMOVE
WHAT GETS IN THEIR WAY,
IT SEEMS THAT THEY NEED EMILY
TO CONTINUE THE TESTS.
[ Knocking ]
HELLO.
ANNA FUGAZZI ?
YES.
YOUR NAME
IS ANNA FUGAZZI ?
YES.
ARE YOU THE NEW DOCTOR ?
NO, I'M NOT.
IS THAT YOUR REAL NAME ?
YES, FOR THE LAST 71 YEARS.
WERE YOU LOOKING FOR ME ?
NOT UNTIL NOW.
[ Scully ]
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
JUST AN HOUR AGO YOU SAID
THAT SHE WAS GETTING BETTER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
HER FEVER'S DOWN.
HER VITAL SIGNS
ARE NEARLY BACK TO NORMAL.
BUT THESE LATEST M.R.I.'s
ARE TELLING ME...
THAT THIS GROWTH
HAS CONTINUED TO SPREAD.
IN HER ARMS, I'M NOW SEEING
WHAT LOOKS LIKE...
A NECROTIZING OF THE TISSUE.
IT'S KILLING HER.
WHATEVER IT IS,
IT MAY HAVE ALREADY BEEN
PRESENT IN SOME AMOUNT.
BASICALLY,
IT'S SHUT DOWN HER BODY...
WHILE IT CONTINUES TO GROW.
WE SHOULD BE THANKFUL
THAT SHE'S NOT IN ANY PAIN.
I PRESENTED
ALL THIS INFORMATION
TO THE COURT.
AND I HAVE TO TELL YOU
THAT THERE IS
GREAT CONCERN...
THAT YOU ARE
MAKING DECISIONS
FOR THIS CHILD.
AND THEY SEEM
TO BE HAVING NO SMALL
EFFECT ON HER HEALTH.
MISS CHAMBLISS,
I AM A MEDICAL DOCTOR,
AND THE DECISIONS THAT I MAKE
ARE REASONABLE AND RIGHT.
BUT I HAVE IT RIGHT
HERE IN THIS REPORT THAT
DR. CALDERON'S TREATMENT...
HAS ACTUALLY RESULTED
IN A TURNAROUND.
NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
THE INJECTION THAT
DR. CALDERON GAVE HER IS
ACTUALLY MAKING HER WORSE.
MISS SCULLY,
I WANT TO SAY
SOMETHING TO YOU,
AND I DON'T WANT YOU
TO TAKE THIS
THE WRONG WAY.
BUT I DON'T THINK THAT YOU
ARE CAPABLE RIGHT NOW...
OF RESPONDING
WITH ANY CLINICAL ABILITY.
DO YOU THINK I DON'T WANT
WHAT'S BEST FOR THIS CHILD ?
DO YOU THINK THAT I'M NOT
TRYING TO SAVE HER LIFE ?
I'M SAYING THAT I'M GETTING
WILDLY DIFFERING REPORTS.
I HAVE A JOB TO DO.
I'M NOT THE ULTIMATE
AUTHORITY HERE, BUT YOU DON'T
HAVE THE AUTHORITY EITHER...
OVER THIS CHILD
OR HER FUTURE.
YOU CAN GET A COURT ORDER,
AND YOU CAN TRY AND ENFORCE IT.
BUT I SUGGEST THAT
IF YOUR JOB IS TO DO
WHAT'S BEST FOR THIS CHILD,
YOU DO EVERYTHING IN YOUR POWER
TO TELL THE AUTHORITIES...
THAT IF THEY TAKE EMILY
OUT OF THIS HOSPITAL,
THEY ARE GOING
TO HASTEN HER ILLNESS,
AND I WILL MAKE IT KNOWN
THAT ALL OF YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO TELL THEM
YOU'RE DOING FOR HER ?
I DON'T KNOW YET,
BUT I WILL.
CHRISTINA SHERMAN...
DELIVERED A HEALTHY BABY GIRL
SEPTEMBER 25, 1994.
GRETCHEN MILLER.
DELIVERED A BABY BOY
MARCH 18, 1996.
EVELYN BURMEISTER.
DELIVERED A BABY BOY...
JUNE 21, 1994.
THAT MAKES EIGHT FOR EIGHT.
ARE YOU IN
ADOPTION SERVICES, MULDER ?
NO, I'M AT THE MATERNITY WARD.
ANY FETCHING YOUNG MOTHERS
IN THERE ?
YOU MIGHT HAVE A SHOT HERE,
FROHIKE.  YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT PHARMACEUTICALS ?
MEDICINAL
OR, UH, RECREATIONAL ?
THERE'S TWO PRESCRIPTIONS
ON THEIR MED CHARTS THAT ALL
THESE WOMEN HAVE IN COMMON.
ABBREVIATED--
PMZ 200 AND DURTAB.
ESTROGEN AND PROGESTERONE.
HORMONES.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
PREGNANT WOMEN HAVE
THOSE HORMONES IN ABUNDANCE.
YOU WOULDN'T GIVE THOSE
TO PREGNANT WOMEN.
YOU WOULD THESE.
ANNA.
THERE'S A DOCTOR THAT COMES
TO VISIT YOU, A DR. CALDERON.
YES.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE HE IS ?
ACTUALLY, I'M LOOKING FOR HIM.
HE'S SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE.
I WAS GOING TO START
MY BEAUTY SLEEP.
YOUR BEAUTY SLEEP.
WHAT IS THAT ?
HE SAID IT'S TAKEN YEARS
OFF MY APPEARANCE.
YOU OKAY IN THERE,
EMILY ?  GOOD.
I'M GONNA BE RIGHT HERE
THE WHOLE TIME, OKAY ?
WE'RE GONNA PUT EXTRA AIR
IN THERE, SO LET ME KNOW
IF YOUR EARS START TO HURT.
[ Hissing ]
YOU OKAY, SWEETIE ?
TURN IT OFF.
- TURN IT OFF NOW !
- I'M DOING IT, MA'AM.
IT'S OKAY, SWEETIE.
SETTLE DOWN.
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU
OUT OF THERE AS FAST
AS WE CAN, OKAY ?
FLINCH AND YOU'RE DEAD.
HANDS WHERE I CAN SEE 'EM.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE ?
JUST GIVE IT TO ME SLOWLY.
UP AGAINST THE WALL.
SPREAD YOUR LEGS.
WHO ARE YOU ?
DETECTIVE KRESGE,
SAN DIEGO P.D.
I'M SPECIAL AGENT MULDER
WITH THE F.B.I.
TAKE THAT GUN OFF ME
AND PUT IT ON THAT MAN.
STOP RIGHT THERE.
RUN.  GET OUT OF HERE.
DON'T USE YOUR GUN.
GET OUT OF HERE !
I SAID STOP RIGHT THERE.
- KRESGE !
- I SAID STOP RIGHT THERE.
DON'T FIRE, KRESGE !
I'M AN F.B.I. AGENT.
I HAVE AN EMERGENCY SITUATION.
I NEED AN AMBULANCE
AND BACKUP.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE I AM.
MULDER.
I GOT HIM INSIDE.
YOU HAVE YOUR WEAPON ?
HE'S IN THERE ON THE FLOOR.
I GOT HIS HANDS CUFFED.
I GOT BACKUP COMING.
THEY NEED A LOCATION THOUGH.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
JUST WATCH THE GUY.
DETECTIVE KRESGE IS GOING TO
RADIO IN THE LOCATION.
SHE'S GONE
INTO A COMA.
I'M OKAY, MULDER.
IT'S WHAT'S MEANT TO BE.
BUT IF YOU
COULD TREAT HER--
I WOULDN'T.
I WOULDN'T DO IT TO HER.
ARE YOU SURE ?
MULDER, WHOEVER
BROUGHT THIS CHILD
INTO THIS WORLD...
DIDN'T INTEND
TO LOVE HER.
I THINK SHE WAS--
SHE WAS BORN
TO SERVE AN AGENDA.
I HAVE A CHANCE
TO STOP THAT.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
THIS CHILD
WAS NOT MEANT TO BE.
I'LL STAY WITH YOU.
I THINK I'D LIKE
TO BE ALONE.
ARE YOU READY ?
I THINK I'LL GET
A RIDE BACK WITH MULDER.
BYE-BYE, MATTHEW.
WE'LL SEE YOU
AT HOME, OKAY ?
WHO ARE THE MEN
WHO WOULD CREATE A LIFE
WHOSE ONLY HOPE IS TO DIE ?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT THAT YOU
FOUND HER...
AND YOU HAD A CHANCE
TO LOVE HER--
MAYBE SHE WAS MEANT
FOR THAT TOO.
SHE FOUND ME.
SO YOU COULD SAVE HER.
HOW'S DETECTIVE KRESGE ?
HE'S DOING BETTER.
HE'S OUT OF THE I.C.U.
AND THE MEN
WHO DID THIS TO HIM ?
THEY ALREADY CLEANED UP
THE NURSING HOME.
ALL THE WOMEN ARE BEING
PLACED IN NEW HOMES.
THERE'S NO EVIDENCE
THAT ANYONE ELSE AT
THE PRANGEN CORPORATION...
KNEW OF CALDERON'S WORK.
THERE IS EVIDENCE
OF WHAT THEY DID.
[ Child ]
I MADE THIS.