[ Muted Voices Murmuring ]
[ Voices Continue ]
- CHECKMATE.
- [ Gunshot ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Whistling ]
[ Alarm Buzzes ]
[ Gunshot ]
GO ON !
TAKE YOUR SHOT, ALEX !
RIGHT THERE !
I WAS... SENT TO BRING YOU BACK.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE GOING PLACES
IN THE BUREAU...
WHEN THE ASSISTANT DIRECTOR
TIDIES UP YOUR OFFICE.
WHAT'S UP ?
I WAS JUST, UH, LOOKING.
FOR ANYTHING SPECIAL ?
I CAME DOWN
TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
I GUESS I WAS NOSING AROUND,
WONDERING ABOUT YOU,
YOUR LONG-TERM PLANS.
MY LONG-TERM PLANS ?
YOU GOT THEM RIGHT THERE
IN YOUR HANDS.
WHAT DO YOU HOPE TO FIND ?
I MEAN, IN THE END ?
WHATEVER I HOPE
TO FIND IS IN HERE.
MAYBE I'LL KNOW IT
WHEN I FIND IT.
IS THAT WHAT
YOU CAME TO ASK ME ?
NO.  THERE'S A CASE.
NOTHING I'D SEND YOU NORMALLY.
A MURDER.  AN ASSASSINATION
OF A RUSSIAN CHESS PLAYER.
THE SHOOTER IS FORMER
NATIONAL SECURITY AGENCY,
ONE OF OURS.
HE'S GOT A LOT
OF PEOPLE UPSET.
THIS KID JEFFREY SPENDER--
SPECIAL AGENT SPENDER--
HE'S BEEN GIVEN THE CASE.
HE'S RUNNING IT.
DID YOU GIVE IT TO HIM ?
NO.
IT CAME AS AN ORDER FROM
SOMEWHERE OUTSIDE THE BUREAU.
HE'S GOT HIS TEAM ASSEMBLED
UPSTAIRS RIGHT NOW.
HE WAS VERY SPECIFIC
THAT YOU BE EXCLUDED.
USING A WEAPON REGISTERED
TO A U.S. INTELLIGENCE AGENCY,
THE SHOOTER FIRED ONE KILL SHOT
AT ANATOLE KLEBANOW...
BEFORE BEING CAPTURED,
WITHOUT INCIDENT, A SHORT
DISTANCE FROM THE SCENE.
NO MOTIVE HAS BEEN ESTABLISHED,
NOR HAS THE SHOOTER OFFERED UP
A STATEMENT OR ACCOMPLICE.
PLEASE CONTINUE.
THE TRAJECTORY
OF THE KILL SHOT SUGGESTS
THE SHOOTER ACTED ALONE,
BUT WE CANNOT YET RULE OUT
AN ACCOMPLICE
OR CONSPIRACY.
A SINGLE BULLET
WAS FIRED FROM A CATWALK
AT A STEEP ANGLE,
STRIKING THE TARGET
JUST RIGHT OF THE SOLAR PLEXUS.
I'M SORRY.
CAN YOU REWIND THE TAPE ?
PLEASE.  I'LL TELL YOU WHERE.
JUST TAKE IT BACK.
LET ME GET THROUGH THIS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS,
WE CAN TALK LATER.
I DON'T HAVE ANY QUESTIONS, NO.
I JUST THINK YOU'RE WRONG.
MULDER, WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
I DON'T THINK
THE RUSSIAN WAS THE TARGET.
I THINK IT WAS HIS OPPONENT.
HIS OPPONENT, AGENT MULDER,
IS A 12-YEAR-OLD BOY.
AND A GOOD CHESS PLAYER.
LET ME SHOW YOU HIS BEST MOVE
IF YOU JUST TAKE IT BACK.
STOP IT THERE.
LOOK WHAT THE KID
DOES RIGHT HERE, RIGHT
BEFORE THE KILL SHOT.  PLAY.
YOU SEE WHAT HE DOES ?
HE JUST PUSHES BACK.
YOU SEE THAT ?
HE JUST COMPLETED A CHECKMATE.
HE'S PUSHING BACK
BECAUSE THE GAME'S OVER.
YOU DESCRIBED A STEEP TRAJECTORY
FOR THE KILL SHOT.
IF THE KID DOESN'T PUSH BACK
AT THAT PRECISE MOMENT,
HE CATCHES THE BULLET
IN THE BACK OF THE NECK,
NOT THE RUSSIAN.
- CAN WE MOVE ON HERE ?
- I THINK AGENT MULDER IS RIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE THE BOY SENSED
THE SHOOTER PRECOGNITIVELY.
IF YOU REWIND THE TAPE,
YOU'LL SEE IT.
THERE'S NO WAY.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
LET'S REWIND THE TAPE
SO WE CAN ALL SEE FOR OURSELVES.
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
YOU LOOK SURPRISED.
IS IT THAT I'M HERE,
OR THAT I'M ALIVE ?
WHEN WE HEARD YOU'D BEEN SHOT,
WE'D ASSUMED THE WORST.
THERE WERE REPORTS YOU LOST
TOO MUCH BLOOD TO HAVE SURVIVED.
OBVIOUSLY YOU
UNDERESTIMATED ME.
MORE OBVIOUSLY,
YOU OVERESTIMATED THE MAN
YOU SENT TO DO THE JOB.
WELL, LET'S SAY
ALL IS FORGIVEN.
NOW YOU HAVE A JOB FOR ME.
THERE'S BEEN AN INCIDENT,
AN UNFORTUNATE MISTAKE.
YES, I'VE SEEN.
I'VE HEARD.  I'VE READ.
THE BOY IS
A PROBLEM TO US.
WHAT WOULD YOU
LIKE ME TO DO ?
SHOOT HIM DEAD ?
SPLATTER HIS BRAINS ?
DEAR GOD !
WHAT'S THE MATTER ?
DOES THIS SORT
OF BUSINESS OFFEND YOU ?
IT'S IN YOUR INTEREST,
AS IN OURS.
YOU THINK YOU KNOW
MY INTEREST ?
CAN WE COUNT ON YOU ?
YES.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN
WITH THE BUREAU, AGENT FOWLEY ?
SINCE '91.
I TOOK AN ASSIGNMENT IN EUROPE
AFTER THE WALL CAME DOWN,
WHEN THE DIRECTOR STEPPED UP
FOREIGN TERRORISM CONCERNS.
AND THEY BROUGHT YOU ON THIS
BECAUSE OF A TERRORISM ANGLE ?
NO, I REQUESTED A REASSIGNMENT.
THERE WERE THINGS AT HOME I
DECIDED I WANTED TO GET BACK TO.
1991 ?  THAT'S ABOUT WHEN
YOU STARTED WORK ON THE X-FILES.
MORE OR LESS, YEAH.
UH, I'D BETTER JUST PUT IT DOWN.
[ Girl On TV ]
NO OFFENSE, MOM,
BUT THAT WAS PRETTY COOL.
[ Woman On TV ]
HOMER, I THINK YOU'D AGREE--
GIBSON ?
HI.  MY NAME IS FOX.
THIS IS DANA AND DIANA.
HOW ARE YOU DOIN' ?
I DON'T MIND IT HERE.
THEY GET ALL
THE GOOD TV SHOWS.
WHERE I LIVE IN THE PHILIPPINES,
ALL WE GET ISBAYWATCH.
WHAT'S WRONG WITHBAYWATCH?
YOU'VE GOT A DIRTY MIND.
YOUR PARENTS ARE GOING
TO PICK YOU UP ON FRIDAY,
GIBSON, TO TAKE YOU BACK HOME.
I DON'T WANT TO
PLAY ANY CHESS.
HOW DO YOU KNOW I WANT TO ?
'CAUSE YOU GOT THAT CHEAP OLD
CHESS COMPUTER IN YOUR HAND.
IT'S NOT SO CHEAP.
DON'T YOU WANT TO SEE
HOW FAST YOU CAN BEAT IT ?
NO.
MAYBE BECAUSE YOU CAN'T.
I'M RIGHT, AREN'T I ?
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
YOU KNEW THE MOMENT
I CAME IN.
THAT'S HOW YOU WIN, ISN'T IT ?
HOW YOU KNOW WHAT YOUR
OPPONENT'S GOING TO DO ?
YOU GET INSIDE HIS HEAD.
YOU READ HIS THOUGHTS.
THAT'S HOW YOU KNEW THAT MAN WAS
GOING TO SHOOT YOU, ISN'T IT ?
I KNOW WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND.
I KNOW YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT
ONE OF THE GIRLS YOU BROUGHT.
OH ?
AND ONE OF THEM IS
THINKING ABOUT YOU.
WHICH ONE ?
HE DOESN'T WANT ME TO SAY.
[ Chuckles ]
THIS KID IS GOING TO NEED
ROUND-THE-CLOCK PROTECTION.
MULDER ?
WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT ?
THE KID'S NO CHESS MASTER.
UNDER CONTROLLED CONDITIONS,
I COULD PROBABLY BEAT HIM.
HE'S RECOGNIZED
INTERNATIONALLY AS A PRODIGY.
HE'S BEATEN GRAND MASTERS.
WITH THE MOST UNFAIR ADVANTAGE.
WHAT HE'S DOING AMOUNTS TO
A KIND OF PARLOR MAGIC TRICK.
HE WAS GOOFING ON YOU.
HE WAS PLAYING ALONG.
WHAT YOU'RE POSITING IS THAT
THIS KID CAN READ MINDS.
WE'VE SEEN A NUMBER
OF THESE CASES BEFORE.
WE HAVE SEEN CASES OF
FAKERS AND LUCKY GUESSERS,
BUT NO ONE THAT HAS EVER
BEEN ABLE TO STAND UP
TO ANY RIGOROUS TESTING...
AND NO ONE WHO HAS
GONE SO FAR AS TO CLAIM
THAT THEY CAN ZERO IN...
ON THE MIND OF ONE PERSON
IN A CROWD OF THOUSANDS.
MAYBE THAT'S WHY
THEY WANT HIM DEAD.
WHO ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT THE MIND READER.
SAY THAT WHAT
YOU'RE SUGGESTING
WERE EVEN POSSIBLE,
WHO WOULD WANT TO KILL A KID
WHOSE ABILITIES WOULD OFFER YOU
THE ULTIMATE ADVANTAGE ?
I MEAN, IN BUSINESS,
IN WAR, IN ANYTHING.
MAYBE SOMEBODY WHOSE BUSINESS
IS IN KEEPING SECRETS.
WELL, LET'S TEST HIM.
I THINK THE KID WILL STAND UP.
LET'S RUN A BRAIN SCAN
AND A PSYCH EVALUATION ON HIM.
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO, DIANA.
SO YOU TWO
KNOW EACH OTHER ?
IT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE ?
I WANT TO TALK
TO THE SHOOTER.
I'VE JUST SPENT THE LAST
SIX HOURS TALKING WITH HIM.
HE'S NOT BEEN WHAT
I WOULD CALL FORTHCOMING.
LET ME SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
I'D PREFER YOU
STAY OUT OF THERE.
IN FACT, I'D PREFER YOU STAY OUT
OF THIS THING ALTOGETHER.
WHEN I FIRST MET YOU,
I FIGURED YOU WERE
JUST AMBITIOUS.
THIS MORNING MY OPINION CHANGED,
AND I THOUGHT YOU WERE ARROGANT.
NOW I'M BEGINNING TO WONDER
WHAT YOU'RE PROTECTING.
I'M TRYING TO RUN THIS THING
RIGHT, NOT LIKE SOME RIDICULOUS
PARANORMAL FREE-FOR-ALL.
YOU'RE INSULTING ME WHEN
YOU SHOULD BE TAKING NOTES.
SOMEHOW YOU GOT
THE BIG ASSIGNMENT,
BUT JUST BECAUSE
YOU'RE WEARING THE SUIT
DOESN'T MEAN IT FITS.
YOU'RE LUCKY YOU'RE
NOT BUSY DEFUSING AN
INTERNATIONAL INCIDENT,
KISSING SOME
SERIOUS RUSSIAN ASS...
AND SENDING A WHOLE LOT
OF AGENTS BARKING DOWN
A WHOLE LOT OF BAD LEADS.
NOW, THE KID
IS THE KEY TO THIS,
AND THE SHOOTER KNOWS WHY.
EXCUSE ME.
WHAT DOES IT TAKE
TO KILL A KID ?
MONEY OR JUST EVIL STUPIDITY ?
I DIDN'T KILL A KID.
NO, THANKS TO THE KID.
YOU WANT TO TALK
ABOUT HEARTLESSNESS ?
YOUR SQUEAKY FRIEND THERE...
HASN'T GIVEN ME ANY FOOD OR
WATER FOR WHAT, LIKE 16 HOURS ?
I WON'T TOLERATE THAT.
SPENDER, YOU GOT TO GET
THIS GUY SOME FOOD.
COME ON.
I'VE GOT NOTHING TO SAY.
I READ YOUR BIO.
YOU'VE BEEN TRAINED,
SPECIAL FORCES.
YOU WERE IN GRENADA, ZAIRE.
YOU WERE INSIDE SADDAM'S PALACE
WITH A HIT SQUAD WHEN THEY
STARTED RAINING BOMBS OVER IT.
YET YOU FAILED
TO KILL HIM AS WELL.
- LIKE I SAID--
- I KNOW.  YOU GOT
NOTHING TO SAY.
THAT'S OKAY.
I'M A PRETTY GOOD GUESSER.
THE KID READS MINDS.
HOW'S THAT ?
WHY DON'T I TELL THEM YOU TOLD
ME THAT, AND THEN LET'S SEE HOW
SAFE AND SNUG YOU FEEL IN HERE ?
WHAT CAN YOU DO FOR ME ?
I DON'T KNOW.  I MIGHT BE
ABLE TO GET YOU IMMUNITY...
OR GET YOU INTO
THE WITNESS PROTECTION PROGRAM.
NEVER HAPPEN.
THINK ABOUT IT.
WHAT'D YOU GET ?
DID YOU GET ANYTHING ?
JUST HIS ATTENTION.
HOW ARE YOU DOING ?
I DIDN'T LIKE THOSE TESTS.
I DIDN'T LIKE
BEING IN THE MACHINE.
LITTLE SCARY, AREN'T THEY ?
- YOU'RE WONDERING, AREN'T YOU ?
- ABOUT WHAT ?  ABOUT YOU ?
ABOUT THAT OTHER GIRL.
SHE'S WONDERING ABOUT YOU TOO.
WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU
A GROUP OF CARDS.
AS WE LOOK AT THEM, WE WANT YOU
TO TELL US WHAT WE'RE THINKING.
NOW, TAKE AS MUCH TIME
AS YOU NEED.
CHAIR.
PIANO.
PIECE OF PIE.
LIGHTBULB.
SMILEY FACE.
STATUE.
CAT.
IT'S AMAZING.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE.
I'VE WITNESSED CLAIRVOYANTS
WHO WERE OVER 90% ACCURATE...
AND SEEN TELEPATHY
BEING DEMONSTRATED,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
I'VE EVER WITNESSED
ANYTHING QUITE LIKE THIS.
WHERE'D YOU SEE THAT ?
AGENT MULDER AND I SPENT SOME
TIME IN PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITALS.
THERE WERE SOME PATIENTS
SERVING CRIMINAL SENTENCES
WE FELT HAD BEEN MISDIAGNOSED.
OMELETTE.
COFFEE AND A CRULLER.
A NONFAT LATTE.
AN ENGLISH MUFFIN.
GRAND SLAM NUMBER TWO
WITH DOUBLE HASH BROWN
AND A SIDE OF CANADIAN BACON.
HE JUST TOLD US ALL
WHAT WE ATE FOR BREAKFAST.
I HAVE TO DISAPPEAR
FOR A BIT.
I WAS HANDED A NOTE.
NOW I'M HANDING IT TO YOU.
[ Buzzer Buzzing ]
[ Man ]
OKAY, HANG ON.  I'M COMING !
SOMEBODY GONNA LET ME IN ?
HEY, YEAH, YEAH.
COMIN', COMIN'.
SORRY.  YOU CAUGHT ME
GETTIN' READY FOR BED.
COME IN.  COME IN.
THANK YOU.
TO WHAT DO WE OWE THE PLEASURE
OF THIS LATE NIGHT HOUR ?
- I NEED YOUR HELP.
-WITH WHAT ?
YOU'VE ALL HEARD OF GIBSON
PRAISE, THE CHESS WUNDERKIND ?
THESE ARE A SERIES OF SCANS
AND NEURO-ELECTRICAL OUTPUTS...
OF HIS BRAIN
AND BRAIN PROCESSES.
THERE SEEMS TO BE SOME SUSPICION
THAT HE'S A FRAUD.
- DORF ON CHESS ?
- APPARENTLY HE WINS BY
READING HIS OPPONENTS' MINDS.
I LOVE THAT.
AND YOU WANT US TO WHAT ?
ANALYZE THE DATA...
WITH AN EYE TO
THE PARAPSYCHOLOGICAL.
OOH, WALK
ON THE WILD SIDE.
FIRST, I WANT YOU GUYS
TO TELL ME WHO DIANA FOWLEY IS.
DIANA FOWLEY ?
JEEZ, WE HAVEN'T HEARD
THAT NAME IN A WHILE.
- THEN YOU KNOW HER ?
- WELL, YEAH.
SHE WAS MULDER'S CHICKADEE
WHEN HE JUST GOT OUT
OF THE ACADEMY.
GOOD-LOOKIN'.
SHE CLAIMS TO HAVE WORKED
CLOSELY WITH HIM FOR A WHILE.
SHE WAS THERE WHEN HE
DISCOVERED THE X-FILES.
SHE HAS SOME KIND OF BACKGROUND
IN PARASCIENCE.
[ Byers ]
SHE GOT A LEGAT APPOINTMENT
A WHILE BACK IN BERLIN.
I ALWAYS WONDERED
WHY THEY SPLIT UP.
WELL--
WHY DON'T YOU BOYS SEE
WHAT YOU CAN FIND ?
I MUST MAKE MY STAND.
YOUR STAND WILL DESTROY YOU.
BETTER TO PERISH FOR
WHAT I BELIEVE IN...
THAN ENDURE FOREVER
AS A TRAITOR TO LIFE.
THEN SO BE IT.
[ Door Opens ]
[ Mulder ]
HOW'S LITTLE CARNAC DOIN' ?
PUT A TV IN FRONT OF HIM,
HE TURNS RIGHT
INTO A NORMAL KID.
BUT HE'S THE REAL DEAL, FOX.
WE TESTED HIM WITH ZENER CARDS,
RANDOM NUMBERS,
A VARIETY OF
E.S.P. TASKING.
HE'S GOT ABILITY TO NOT
JUST FOCUS ON A THOUGHT, BUT
A MULTITUDE OF THOUGHTS AT ONCE.
[ Man On TV ]
AND WOMEN WHO THINK--
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE.
THERE'S SOMETHING
WE'RE MISSING HERE.
THAT WAS A GOOD CATCH
ON THE VIDEOTAPE.
I WAS IMPRESSED.
YOU WOULD HAVE
CAUGHT IT EVENTUALLY.
NO, I'VE BEEN
TOO MANY YEARS...
TRYING TO GET INSIDE THE HEAD
OF TOO MANY ARAB TERRORISTS.
I'M OUT OF PRACTICE WITH
THIS STUFF.  BUT YOU SEEM
AT THE TOP OF YOUR GAME.
IT'S ALL I DO.
IT'S ALL I'VE BEEN DOING
FOR THE LAST FIVE YEARS.
IT'S... BEEN MY LIFE,
SUCH AS IT IS.
SOMETIMES I HEAR ABOUT YOU--
ABOUT THE WORK YOU'RE DOING--
AND I THINK HOW IT MIGHT
HAVE BEEN IF I'D STAYED.
WE'D ALL BE BLOWN UP
BY SOME TERRORIST BOMB,
NO DOUBT, HUH ?
I SENSE YOU COULD HAVE USED
AN ALLY THOUGH--
SOMEONE WHO THINKS LIKE YOU,
WITH SOME BACKGROUND.
YOU MEAN SCULLY ?
SHE'S NOT WHAT I'D CALL
AN OPEN MIND ON THE SUBJECT.
[ Chuckles ]
NO.
SHE'S A SCIENTIST.
SHE MAKES ME WORK
FOR EVERYTHING.
YES, BUT I'M SURE
THERE WERE TIMES...
WHEN TWO LIKE MINDS ON A CASE
WOULD HAVE BEEN ADVANTAGEOUS.
I'VE DONE OKAY WITHOUT YOU.
HEY.
I'M ON YOUR SIDE.
[ Phone Beeps,
Line Ringing ]
MULDER.
MULDER, IT'S ME.
WHERE ARE YOU ?
I'M, UH--
I'M ON MY WAY TO WORK.
I WAS HOPING
I COULD SHOW YOU SOMETHING,
SOMETHING ABOUT THE BOY.
I'M AT THE PSYCH FACILITY
WITH HIM RIGHT NOW.  WHY DON'T
YOU COME BY AND SHOW ME ?
I'D PREFER TO SHOW YOU
AT WORK, IF THAT'S OKAY.
OKAY.  WHAT IS IT ?
I THINK YOU'LL
BE SURPRISED.
VERY SURPRISED.
I'M ON MY WAY.
[ Phone Beeps ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Keys Jingle ]
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Alarm Chirps ]
AGENT SPENDER.
- I NEED TO SPEAK WITH YOU.
- WHO ARE YOU ?
SOMEBODY WHO'S TAKEN
AN INTEREST IN YOU--
IN THIS CASE OF YOURS--
THIS CASE I GAVE YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU ?
C.I.A. ?  N.S.A. ?
YOU'RE A BRAVE BOY.
YOU SAID YOU HAD
INFORMATION.
CONTROL THE BOARD.
KNOW WHICH MEN
TO SACRIFICE AND WHEN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
DON'T BECOME PART OF
SOMEONE ELSE'S CAUSE OR CRUSADE.
PURSUE YOUR OWN SELF-INTEREST.
ALWAYS.
[ Door Opens ]
[ Indistinct ]
AGENT SPENDER ?
AGENT SPENDER !
WHO WERE YOU TALKING TO ?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHO YOU WERE TALKING TO ?
YOU'RE LYING !
WHAT'S YOUR DEAL ?
I WAS TOLD HE WAS DEAD.
OBVIOUSLY, WHOEVER IT IS,
HE'S NOT.
YOU'RE HERE TO
TELL ME A STORY.
[ Clears Throat ]
TELL HIM EXACTLY AS YOU TOLD ME.
I'VE CONDUCTED SOME TESTS
ON GIBSON PRAISE...
AND HAVE COME UP WITH SOME
RATHER UNEXPECTED CONCLUSIONS--
ONES WHICH I MYSELF HAVE
DIFFICULTY RECONCILING
WITH WHAT I KNOW.
- THESE ARE ?
- NEUROLOGICAL TESTS.
MAPPING OF BRAIN FUNCTIONS,
USING A VERY HIGH
RESOLUTION E.E.G.
- WHAT DID YOU FIND OUT ?
-THE TESTS REVEALED...
SOMETHING PECULIAR IN AN AREA
OF THE BRAIN THAT WE ARE ONLY
BEGINNING TO UNDERSTAND--
AN AREA OF THE TEMPORAL LOBE
THAT NEURO-PHYSICISTS ARE
CALLING THE "GOD MODULE."
I HOPE I'M NOT
GOING TO HEAR...
THAT THIS KID IS
THE NEXT CHRIST CHILD.
ALL OF THE BOY'S BRAIN
PROCESSES ARE SHOWING...
EXTRAORDINARY ACTIVITY IN
EXACTLY THIS PART OF THE BRAIN,
WHICH IS NOT JUST
ABNORMAL OR ANOMALOUS,
BUT FROM WHAT I KNOW,
ABSOLUTELY UNHEARD OF.
THERE ARE COROLLARIES--
INDIVIDUALS WHO HAVE
BEEN RESPONSIBLE...
FOR GREAT LEAPS FORWARD
IN UNDERSTANDING IN SCIENCE--
NEWTON, GALILEO,
EINSTEIN, STEPHEN HAWKING.
ALL THESE MEN EXHIBITED
MODES OF THINKING...
THAT ARE SUGGESTIVE OF ACCESS
TO SPECIAL BRAIN CENTERS.
ALL RIGHT, SO THIS KID
IS A HUMAN ODDITY.
WOULD SOMEBODY TELL ME
WHY ANYONE WOULD GO TO SUCH
GREAT LENGTHS TO KILL HIM ?
THIS KID MAY BE THE KEY,
NOT JUST TO ALL HUMAN POTENTIAL,
BUT TO ALL SPIRITUAL UNEXPLAINED
PARANORMAL PHENOMENA--
THE KEY TO EVERYTHING
IN THE X-FILES.
LET ME GET THIS RIGHT.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BELIEVE...
THAT THIS BOY
WAS GOING TO BE KILLED...
BECAUSE OF THE X-FILES ?
- NO, IT'S BIGGER THAN THAT.
- UH-HUH.  EXPLAIN IT TO ME--
- TO US.
- I CAN'T.
BUT THE SHOOTER CAN--
THE ASSASSIN THAT
YOU HAVE LOCKED UP--
IN EXCHANGE FOR IMMUNITY
FROM PROSECUTION.
YOU WANT TO GIVE
A MURDERER A FREE RIDE FOR
THE SECRETS TO THE PYRAMIDS ?
THIS IS CRAZY.  IT'S NUTS !
YOU MISCHARACTERIZED
WHAT I'VE SAID.
THIS WOULD BE QUANTIFIABLE...
SCIENTIFIC PROOF OF EVERYTHING
THAT AGENT MULDER AND I...
HAVE INVESTIGATED
OVER THE PAST FIVE YEARS.
HOW DO YOU QUANTIFY
THE SPIRITUAL ?
IT CAN'T BE DONE.
YOU ASK FOR IMMUNITY
FOR A KILLER ON THAT BASIS,
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL'S
GOING TO GO OFF.
YOU'RE ALLOWED TO INVESTIGATE
THE X-FILES AS AN INDULGENCE.
BUT DRAW THE WRONG KIND
OF ATTENTION, AND THEY'LL
CLOSE YOU DOWN--
PUT AN END TO ALL YOUR WORK--
SOMETHING I HAPPEN TO HAVE
AN INTEREST IN MYSELF.
LET'S EVERYONE STEP OUT
IN THE HALL.
AGENT MULDER, YOU STAY PUT.
[ Door Closes ]
[ Sighs ]
SHE'S RIGHT, YOU KNOW ?
THE RISKS YOU'RE TAKING--
THE LONG-TERM PLANS
YOU AND I TALKED ABOUT--
IF WHAT AGENT SCULLY'S FOUND
IS TRUE, AND I HAVE EVERY REASON
TO BELIEVE THAT IT IS,
THEN THE ANSWERS
I MIGHT HAVE SPENT
A LIFETIME SEARCHING FOR...
MAY FALL TOGETHER
LIKE A MILLION PUZZLE PIECES.
YOU'D RISK THE X-FILES ?
HOW SOON CAN YOU CALL
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL ?
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL'S
HEARD MY REQUEST FOR IMMUNITY.
HEARD IT ?  YOU--
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
YOU SAID THAT YOU COULD GET IT.
SHE NEEDS SOMETHING MORE--
SOMETHING TO CONVINCE HER
THAT YOU'RE NOT
JUST PLAYING GAMES--
SOMETHING THAT
I CAN CORROBORATE.
I NEED ANSWERS FROM YOU.
THE KID IS A MISSING LINK.
TO WHAT ?
HE'S GENETIC PROOF, ISN'T HE ?
GENETIC PROOF OF WHAT ?
THE KID'S NOT SUPERHUMAN.
HE'S JUST MORE HUMAN THAN HUMAN.
HE'S WHAT ?
MOST OF US HAVE GENES
WE DON'T USE.  THEY LIE
THERE DORMANT, TURNED OFF.
SCIENCE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE FOR, WHY THEY'RE THERE
OR WHERE THEY CAME FROM.
RIGHT, AND YOU THINK THIS HAS
SOMETHING TO DO WITH GOD ?
THERE'S A LONG-HELD
BUT UNPOPULAR THEORY...
TIED TO
PREHISTORIC EVIDENCE
OF ALIEN ASTRONAUTS.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GO OUT THERE
AND SAY THE KID'S PART ALIEN ?
YOU THINK THAT'S
WHAT YOU HEARD ?
YOU LED HIM, AGENT MULDER !
NOW YOU'RE LETTING
YOURSELF BE LED !
WE ENTRUSTED YOU.
- YOU FAILED.
- FAILED.  FAILED WHO ?
MULDER HAS GONE
TO THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT.
HE HAS TESTIMONY
ABOUT THE BOY.
THAT'S JUST PART OF THE GAME.
IT'S NOT A GAME,
FOR GOD'S SAKE !
SURE IT IS.
IT'S ALL A GAME.
YOU JUST TAKE THEIR PIECES
ONE BY ONE UNTIL
THE BOARD IS CLEARED.
[ Gasps ]
HEY, MISSY !
HOW ABOUT SOME SANDWICHES ?
[ Both Laughing ]
[ Woman On TV ]
I HOPE YOU'RE ALL HUNGRY.
[ Man On TV ]
GOOD-LOOKIN' BREAKFAST, PEG.
[ Man #2 On TV ]
YEAH, I SEE BACON.  I SEE HAM.
GIBSON ?
THIS IS A GREAT SHOW.
I WISH WE GOT THIS
WHERE I LIVE.
I'D LIKE TO
ASK YOU SOMETHING.
HOW DO YOU DO IT ?
I JUST HEAR YOU THINKING,
LIKE ON A RADIO.
SOMETIMES THERE ARE LOTS
OF RADIOS, AND I WANT TO SHUT
THEM OFF AND WATCH SOME TV.
IS THAT WHY YOU LIKE CHESS,
'CAUSE IT'S JUST ONE THOUGHT
THAT YOU HEAR ?
YEAH, BUT THAT'S NOT
WHY I LIKE IT ALL THE TIME.
WHY ELSE DO YOU LIKE IT ?
BECAUSE THERE'S NO TALKING,
JUST THINKING.
IT'S NOTHING LIKE REAL LIFE
WHERE PEOPLE THINK ONE THING
BUT THEY SAY SOMETHING ELSE.
IS THAT WHAT PEOPLE DO ?
THEY'RE WORRIED ABOUT WHAT
OTHER PEOPLE ARE THINKING...
WHEN THE PEOPLE
THEY'RE WORRYING ABOUT ARE
WORRIED ABOUT THE SAME THING.
MAKES ME LAUGH.
WHY ?
THEY MAKE UP
ALL THIS STUFF TO BELIEVE,
BUT IT'S ALL MADE UP.
SOME PEOPLE TRY
TO BE GOOD PEOPLE, BUT
SOME PEOPLE JUST DON'T CARE.
LIKE YOU.
YOU THINK I DON'T CARE ?
NO, YOU DON'T CARE
WHAT PEOPLE THINK.
EXCEPT FOR HER,
THE OTHER ONE.
[ Knocking ]
I'M HERE TO RELIEVE YOU.
WELL, WE'LL TALK
ABOUT THIS LATER, OKAY ?
THEY WANT TO KILL ME,
YOU KNOW ?
NOBODY'S GONNA DO
ANYTHING TO YOU, GIBSON.
I PROMISE.
I KNOW YOU DO.
I'VE BEEN HANDED
ANOTHER NOTE.
[ Clicks ]
[ Gasps ]
GIBSON !
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
THERE'S A MAN WITH A GUN.
GIBSON, GET DOWN.
GET BACK.  GET BACK.
HE DIDN'T COME HERE TO KILL ME.
HE'S AIMING AT YOU.
WHAT--
AGENT MULDER, SCULLY.
THEY KILLED A U.S. MARSHAL
AND THEN SHOT AGENT FOWLEY.
[ Skinner ]
THEY WORKED ON HER HERE
FOR AN HOUR.
THEY COULDN'T GET A CHOPPER IN,
SO THEY'RE IN RADIO
COMMUNICATION WITH THE HOSPITAL.
SHE'S GOT WEAK VITALS
AND A HOLE IN ONE OF HER LUNGS,
SO THEY'RE NOT OPTIMISTIC.
WHAT ABOUT THE BOY ?
IS HE HERE ?
WHERE'S SPENDER ?
HE'S GONE TO
FEDERAL DETENTION.
WE FOUND THE SHOOTER SHOT DEAD
IN HIS CELL EARLY THIS MORNING.
WE ALSO FOUND THIS.
[ Siren Wailing ]
HELLO, YOUNG MAN.
HELLO.
THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE AFRAID OF.
YOU'RE A LIAR.
JUST LIKE HIM.
YOU'VE NEVER HAD THE STOMACH
FOR OUR BUSINESS.
JUST NOT FOR YOUR PRACTICES.
I'M A NECESSITY,
THE COMPLEMENT
TO YOUR COWARDICE.
YOUR WORK IS DONE NOW.
MY WORK IS JUST BEGINNING.
I GOT A NICE STRAIGHT SHOT.
NO.  HE'S USEFUL, AND YOU
MAY NEED HIM IN THE FUTURE.
SECURE THE AIRPORTS
AND NOTIFY THE PARENTS
THAT THE BOY'S MISSING.
WHO DO YOU WORK FOR ?
TELL ME.
AGENT MULDER !
YOU WORK FOR HIM ?
YOU AND OLD SMOKEY ?
IS THAT WHO PUT THIS TOGETHER ?
YOU'RE GOIN' DOWN FOR THIS !
I'M GONNA SEE YOU PROSECUTED
FOR MURDER !  WATCH ME !
WATCH IT HAPPEN !
YOUR DAYS ARE NUMBERED.
YOU'RE WRONG, AGENT MULDER.
IT'S YOUR DAYS
THAT ARE NUMBERED.
[ Scully ]
WE KNEW THERE WERE RISKS
GOING TO THE ATTORNEY GENERAL.
[ Skinner ]  YOU KNOW
WHAT'S COMING DOWN HERE.
YES, SIR.
THEY'RE SERIOUS ABOUT THIS.
I UNDERSTAND.
I ASSUME YOU'LL MAKE
AGENT MULDER AWARE OF THIS.
YES, I'M HERE WITH HIM NOW.
I'M MAKING A CASE
HIS PERSONAL INVOLVEMENT
CLOUDED HIS JUDGMENT,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL'S
LISTENING.
I'LL COMMUNICATE THAT TO HIM.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE ?
ANY OTHER NEWS ?
YOU SHOULD KNOW
AGENT SPENDER'S GOING
AFTER MULDER FULL BORE.
HE'S BEEN RECITING SOME LINE
ABOUT ALIEN ASTRONAUTS THAT
MAKES YOU BOTH LOOK REALLY BAD.
RIGHT.  WELL, I'LL BE HERE
IF YOU NEED TO REACH ME.
ANY NEWS ON DIANA ?
[ Sighs ]
THEY HAVE HER
ON MAXIMUM PRESSERS,
BUT SHE'S BARELY
MAINTAINING HER PRESSURE.
WHAT DID SKINNER
HAVE TO SAY ?
THERE ARE TALKS GOING ON
RIGHT NOW ABOUT REASSIGNMENT.
FOR WHO ?
BOTH OF US.
THESE TALKS
INCLUDED INSTRUCTIONS...
FROM THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
TO CLOSE DOWN THE X-FILES.
THIS WAS ALL STRATEGIZED,
EVERY MOVE.
I JUST COULDN'T SEE IT.
IT WAS ALL OF A PLAN.
MULDER, WHATEVER
YOU MAY BELIEVE,
THIS TIME THEY MAY HAVE WON.
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
CAN I HELP YOU ?
ACTUALLY, UH, I CAN HELP YOU.
HOW DID YOU GET IN HERE ?
ACCESS, AGENT SPENDER.
IT'S ABOUT ACCESS.
IT'S WHAT I CAN GIVE YOU.
IT'S WHAT CAN MAKE YOU.
IT'S WHY I'M DOING THIS
FOR YOU.
WHO ARE YOU ?
I'M YOUR FATHER.
WHAT ?
[ Alarm Ringing ]
[ Alarm Continues ]
[ Chattering ]
MULDER--
[ Water Dripping ]
[ Child ]
I MADE THIS !