Previously on V....
- Are there others like you?
- They're called 5th Column.
Crush them
before they become a greater threat.
If you're 5th Column, things are
about to get very bad for you.
A human female
is carrying a Visitor baby.
Find them.
You've been looking for me.
I found what you're really looking for.
Joshua said you passed
the empathy test.
- Why?
- Because one day
I'll ask a favor from you.
If my mother's eggs
are allowed to hatch,
those soldiers will destroy
the 5th Column, won't they?
Yes, they will.
You're doing great, Val.
Keep breathing.
You're at 2 centimeters.
This baby's coming.
Can I get you anything?
Yeah, glass of water?
Thirsty.
You have a look.
What's up?
I want to talk to you
about "Live Aboard."
I get that you're not crazy about
that idea, but it's important to me.
I understand your concern about me
moving up there, and so does Anna.
Really?
She even invited us up for dinner.
Just me, you, Lisa and Anna.
What?
Take your food.
I love you.
Jack, it's Erica.
Get everyone to the church.
I have a plan.
Where's Ryan?
- I'm not sure.
- Why'd you call us here?
Tyler's joining
the "Live Aboard" program.
I can't stop him,
but I can stop Anna.
I don't understand.
Ryan told us Anna's V soldier eggs
are about to hatch.
If she has thousands of V soldiers
at her disposal...
- We're dead.
- We are out of time. This is it.
What do you suggest?
We storm the ship and kill the eggs?
That is exactly what I'm suggesting.
My kind of plan.
I like your spunk.
None have ever been there.
We don't know where they are.
No, we don't.
Joshua does.
It's never gonna happen.
We had a plan to take out the eggs,
but since the shuttle was shot down,
Anna's practically
locked down the ship.
There has to be something we can do.
There's two ways into
the incubation chamber.
A guarded corridor and an entrance
in Anna's private quarters.
Not even I can get in there anymore.
I can.
Anna invited Tyler and me
onto her ship for dinner.
- Too dangerous.
- Create a diversion
to get Anna out of her quarters so that
Erica's got time to get to the eggs.
Dinner's at 7:00.
You'll need an explosive
to destroy the eggs.
Now we're talking. What kind?
I have to go.
Contact me when everything's set up.
We need to know you'll be here
if we risk everything on our end.
We will.
Marcus released another wave
of guards through the ship.
They're searching everyone.
Get rid of the comms device.
If they find it on you,
we'll all be exposed.
You haven't returned our calls.
You okay?
I needed my line to be free.
- My baby's being born.
- What?
I've been waiting for Dr. Pearlman
to give me a call if they need my help.
What's going on?
Erica's been invited up to the ship.
She'll destroy Anna's soldier eggs.
Are you serious?
I'm going with you.
You're gonna need my help with this.
No. Ryan, I think you should stay here,
in case Val or the baby need you.
Once you get up there, then what?
Anna's never gonna let you
out of her sight.
Joshua's planning a diversion.
Anna will be pulled away for safety,
and then she'll make a move.
And Marcus? He's her watchdog.
You can't pull this off under his nose.
I can get Marcus off the ship.
I'm on top of the Vs most wanted list.
Makes me excellent bait.
To do this, Erica's gonna
need a layout of the ship.
Every detail you can remember,
everything.
The armada of ships
from our home planet
have arrived ahead of schedule.
They're within striking
range of Earth.
Keep them cloaked and at bay.
We don't want them revealed
until we're ready for the next stage.
Tyler's mother is joining you
tonight for dinner, as planned?
With Agent Evans
as my ally on the ground
and my newborn army,
the humans won't know what hit them.
We got a problem.
- The comms device isn't working.
- What?
We're supposed to confirm
with Joshua we're go.
If we can't reach him,
you're not going up there.
We can try skywriting.
I could go to Chad Decker.
Anna's lapdog?
I prefer the skywriting idea.
Unless someone has a better idea,
I don't see we have another choice.
Chad is the one who went to Anna
with our plans to blow up the shuttle.
Chad is the one who went on air
to convince people
to follow her, to keep her here.
- You think you can trust him?
- I don't.
That's why we'll have him
deliver a message
that he and she won't understand.
We're covered either way.
If he doesn't go to Anna with it, then
he'll deliver the message, we're a go.
And if he takes it right to her?
Then Anna gets her hands
on a message she won't understand.
Ryan, they've got Val.
It all happened so fast.
You've gotta find her.
Anna has my baby.
Tell her Ryan Nichols is here.
You don't have clearance.
Get off me!
Let him aboard.
I want to talk to him.
He's dangerous.
Why don't we destroy him
like any other traitor?
He was able to resist my bliss.
He fell in love with a human
and turned 5th Column.
You don't understand
what we have in him.
An enemy.
Insight into our enemy,
the very thing that fuels humans...
love.
That's exactly
why we have to study him,
up close.
If we can turn him back to us,
we can turn anyone.
Father?
Your call sounded urgent.
What can I do for you?
Yes, I was, given this message
from one of my parishioners.
It needs to be delivered to the mother
ship. I know that you have access.
Delivered to who, exactly?
I don't know.
If you agree to help, you're to leave it
in the medical bay.
So you're saying that there are Visitors
who are part of the 5th Column?
Yes, Chad.
Even her own kind are
turning on Anna now.
And this message...
I'm guessing
it isn't a hallmark card.
I wouldn't know.
I'm just the messenger.
I'm tired of playing games
with you, father.
The 5th Column blew up a shuttle full
of innocent human beings.
All I've seen the 5th Column do
is hurt people.
They're lies, Chad.
The shuttle shoot down was a setup.
Anna wants to paint the 5th Column
as a terrorist group,
gather public support against them,
and thanks to you, she succeeded.
Please, Chad.
What is it?
That favor you owe me?
It's time to repay it.
At 7:00, we're gonna
create a diversion
so your mother's eggs can be
destroyed before they hatch.
What?
Those soldiers are bred
for destruction, Lisa...
To kill humans.
Here, take this.
Joshua, you're asking me
to betray my mother,
to murder my own kind.
Sorry.
I can't.
You know she has a plan for Tyler...
The humans.
It's time for you to decide
which side you're really on.
Get off me!
Where is she?
Val's here.
She's safe for now.
I just wish you would've
come to me sooner.
Valerie's pregnancy
is exceedingly risky.
- It's a miracle.
- So you kidnapped her?
To save her.
If we'd have asked,
would you have let me?
- She could've died down there.
- You're lying.
You don't care about saving her.
All you wanna do is run tests,
like she's a lab rat.
You can fight us
or you can help us
fight to save her life.
It's your choice.
Team Lézards
Cable, John117, MiniBen314
Strex, Némone, tactactac
- Red Sky -
I'm so glad you're here.
- We have to get out of here.
- You don't have to be afraid.
- But you warned me about the Vs.
- We don't have a choice right now.
Because your pregnancy is just
really complicated. It's dangerous.
We need their technology
to deliver the baby.
It's coming, Ryan.
I'm scared.
Val, I'm so sorry for
what I put you through.
I'm sorry I left.
I love you.
I don't want to do this alone,
any of it.
You don't have to.
I'm here now.
Everything is gonna be okay.
Her vitals are dropping.
The baby's crowning. Wait outside.
It's okay.
- Are you sure?
- Yes. Please,
let them save the baby.
I'll be right outside.
You ask me, we need to send you up
to that UFO more often.
Is that the explosive?
The bomb you're gonna use
to scramble the bitch's eggs
is a next gen gel explosive.
Unlike nitrates and peroxide,
it gives off no signature.
Even alien technology
won't pick this puppy up.
What's with the handbag?
Just gonna hide it
in the lining here.
And it's a clutch, not a handbag.
- What's the initiator?
- You got your cell phone?
You slip it in here like so.
You set the timer...
And boom.
Marcus will be off the ship by 1900.
He's second in command.
How you gonna get him off the ship?
I'm gonna grab a gecko
by the peace ambassador center,
have him get a message up to the ship
to set a meeting with Marcus,
and then...
- I'll ambush their ambush.
- That sounds dangerous.
I've walked away from much worse.
Good.
Erica, you...
Be careful.
Like you said,
Anna has an agenda, too.
- Where did you get this?
- From an intermediary.
The same source who gave me
the information about the shuttle.
I've been keeping an eye on him.
I believe I'm close to finding out
who's behind the message.
5th Column?
My instructions were to leave
this envelope in the medical lab.
Does that mean there are Visitors
who are working with the 5th Column?
My people are loyal and of peace.
This message must have been intended
for the "Live Aboard" humans.
It seems we've been infiltrated,
even up here.
Deliver this as instructed.
I don't want to see
anyone else get hurt.
Don't worry, Chad.
As soon as we stop the 5th Column,
nobody else will.
Put the gun down, Mr. Hobbes.
We have a lot to talk about.
I believe you have something for me
as well. Parker's research.
Half of Parker's research.
I kept the other half
in a safe place.
You like to play games, Mr. Hobbes?
You really think I'd show up here
without a insurance policy?
You want the other half?
I want answers.
Why did you frame me?
Because I'd like to hire you.
And what makes you think
I'd ever work for you?
Because you already have been...
For years.
Shall we talk, Mr. Hobbes?
- You ready for dinner?
- Yeah. I'm ready.
Don't embarrass me.
Welcome aboard, Agent Evans.
There are no firearms or
any personal items allowed
in Anna's private quarters.
Your bag.
You don't trust me with my purse?
Mom, they're just trying to be safe.
What if I get a call from work?
You can keep your phone.
I'm sorry, ma'am, It's our policy.
Welcome to the ship.
Thank you for invitings
to your home.
I'm thrilled you could make it.
- Hello, Mrs. Evans.
- Hello, Lisa.
It's lovely to see you.
Please. I'll join you in a moment.
I have a matter I need to attend to.
How can I help you?
I was told to deliver
something here,
from a friend of yours
on the ground.
I don't have any friends
I think you must have
the wrong person.
My mistake.
Must be for someone else.
What if it was a message from Erica?
Why didn't you take it?
Chad Decker's Anna's willing pawn.
He can't be trusted.
We have to warn the others not
to engage with Mr. Decker.
- Anna may be using him.
- There isn't time.
I can send out a message
to everyone.
I'll erase it quickly
so it can't be tracked.
What choice do we have?
Do it.
Why did you use me?
You're a man with a history
of serving your loyalty
to the highest bidder.
We want to continue to
retain your services.
- To do what?
- Infiltrate a terrorist group
known as the 5th Column.
And if I say no?
You won't.
I've got the research
you so desperately want.
I've got the leverage here, chief.
Not you.
We play by my rules,
or I walk out of here,
and you'll never find me.
Well, we may not be able
to find you,
but we found her.
Now...
Let's talk 5th Column, shall we?
Track down everyone
that message was sent to.
Put him with the others
when you find them.
Anna will deal with you.
This was for you.
You set us up.
They'll all be caught.
And?
And they'll be skinned alive!
You're lying.
Anna would never do that.
You've been fooled like
the rest of the humans.
The 5th Column's
trying to save humanity.
She lied to you.
Anna didn't cure your aneurysm.
She gave you one.
I don't believe you.
There's a door
to a restricted corridor
50 feet from Anna's executive suite,
where they take the "Live Aboards."
What you see there
will answer all your questions.
This is your homily
for tonight, is it?
The Visitors as false prophets.
Do you think that's wise,
speaking out against them
after they have done?
I've been quiet about my feelings
about the Vs for too long, father.
They're dangerous.
Dangerous?
People are worshiping them
instead of God,
growing dependent on them.
This is my opportunity
to speak my mind from my pulpit.
It's more than an opportunity.
It's an obligation.
The Visitors are a miracle.
How can you be sure
that Anna isn't sent by our lord?
That the Visitors
aren't his handiwork?
You told me I lost touch
with my parishioners
because I haven't spoken
to them from my heart.
This is what's in my heart.
I want you to speak to them,
but not like that.
I will not allow a message of hate
to be preached fr my pulpit.
Write a different homily.
And if I don't?
This istill my church, Jack.
Speak out against the Visitors,
and you are no longer welcome here.
One more push.
My baby.
I wanna see my baby.
Both the baby and mother are stable.
I'm pleased the baby survived.
The mother, however, did not.
It must be challenging
being a single mother, isn't it?
It can be difficult at times, but...
It's worth every minute.
Head of the task force,
a teenage son...
how do you do it all?
Same as you, I guess.
Lots of worrying.
now I am sure that the Visitors
have overprotective mothers. Right?
We do.
We just show our
feelings differently.
Erica, I want you to know
that you don't have to worry about.
We're gonna take care of Tyler
when he comes to "Live Aboard."
Do you think it's safe
with the 5th Column?
- Mom, come on.
- I'm sorry.
Between the two of us,
I'm sure we'll make certain
he's safe.
But this is a social occasion.
- May I pour you some more?
- I would love that. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It's work. Please excuse me.
- Of course.
- Yes?
- I was just looking for my purse.
- No, you weren't.
I know why you're here.
It's that way.
And you'll need this.
It's a blue energy grenade.
It will freeze the eggs.
Twist the top to activate,
place it in the center of the pool
and get out as fast as you can.
There was supposed to be a diversion.
What happened?
I don't know.
You'll be gone too long.
It will cast suspicion.
Go back inside.
I'll figure something out.
Good luck.
What happened?
We were set up by Chad Decker.
Everyone's been rounded up.
If you can get me out,
- I can still cause a diversion.
- You were right.
I had to choose which side I'm on,
and I did.
I gave Erica
the blue energy grenade.
How do I get you out of here?
I placed a bug in the med lab
security system in case I ever needed
to disable it.
The code is "John May lives".
- What are you going to do?
- Whatever I have to.
Go back to dinner.
I'll wait 15 minutes to cause
the diversion so you're not suspected.
You're very brave.
Thank you...
My queen.
Your ship is beautiful,
but you must get homesick.
I know I would.
It's been difficult, yes.
High commander.
We need to move you
- to a secure location.
- What happened?
5th Column. We're being attacked.
Tell Marcus to return
to the ship immediately.
I can help. I need my gun.
- It's okay. She's an ally.
- Follow me.
Here's to your
children's future, Anna.
Stop.
It's done.
Now how do I get you out of here?
There can be no suspicion
you're 5th Column.
You have to kill me.
I won't. Come on.
I'm dead anyway, Erica.
You have to do this,
for all of us.
We both know that.
Don't.
Come on.
Thank you.
Shooting that terrorist
saved many lives.
To protect the Visitors...
That's my job now, Anna.
Did you get a good
look at the shooter?
The pillars were in the way.
I saw he had a V uniform.
He wasn't a V. He was a human.
- What?
- My security team
reported that a human
infiltrated the ship
and stole a V uniform.
They're still gathering the details.
Anna, I'm sorry.
If there's anything I can do...
Excuse me.
Thank you for
delivering that message.
We're hoping it'll help us
expose more 5th Column.
I would hate to see them
drive you away.
They won't.
And thank you for your loyalty.
You've trusted us with your career
and your health.
Without us,
you'd lose everything.
- Thank you for an enventful evening.
- I hope we can do it again sometime.
You can count on it.
You killed her, didn't you?
You said yourself,
I have use for her.
Why would I kill her?
We did everything we could
to keep her alive.
If you'd come to me earlier,
we could have used our technology
to save her life.
This is what I was trying
to protect your from.
Human emotion.
I'm so sorry you lost her.
But now...
Now you have me.
You made it back in one piece.
Good on ya.
I couldn't have done
it if Marcus was there.
I didn't think you'd come through.
Guess I was wrong.
You wouldn't be the first.
There's a story in the Bible
about a man who loses his way,
only to find it again.
I'm here today to tell you...
That I am that man.
I was lost,
but now...
Now I am found.
I lost the courage
to tell you the truth,
that you need to choose
who you are going to follow...
the Vs...
or God...
because you can't serve two masters.
I know some of you are confused.
But we must stand
for what we believe.
We must reaffirm our devotion to God
and renounce the Vs
as false prophets.
Even a single Judas in our midst
can defeat us.
There is a war upon us.
A war for our souls.
You are not alone.
You will never be alone.
No pain.
No heartache.
No human emotion.
Just peace.
My peace.
With love,
hope
and faith, we can overcome
anything.
Who among you
will join me?
Let "V" no longer
stand for "Visitor."
Let "V" stand for "victory."
I told you not to preach
that message in my church.
I'll speak my heart.
If you don't let me do it here,
I'll do it somewhere else.
This will end badly.
Now there's someone
I'd like you to meet.
Welcome home.
I just found out.
We believe it was Joshua.
As your chief medical officer,
he must have gained access
to your private chambers
and planted a bomb.
We had everything
completely locked down.
He couldn't have done this alone.
Find out who else is responsible,
at whatever cost.
Are they all...
dead?
Only 12 soldiers survived.
Their core temperatures
were severely affected.
We don't know how many will make it.
What is happening to me?
I believe you are experiencing
your first human emotion.
This is terrible, to be sure,
but we must not act rashly.
They must pay.
This is too soon.
If we initiate this sequence now...
Do you know what you've done?
Vengeance.
Welcome back.