In this night and in this hour
I call upon the ancient power
Bring back my sister
Bring back the power of three
Power of the witches, rise
Course unseen across the skies
Come to us who call you near
Come to us and settle here
Blood to blood, I summon thee
Blood to blood, return to me
Piper?
Prue?
Sweetie, it's 4:00
in the morning.
What are you doing?
You're bleeding.
I don't understand
why magic can't fix this.
Why it can't bring Prue back. It's not
like we haven't cheated death before.
I don't understand why this time
is any different.
Because Leo can't heal the dead,
Piper. You know that.
There's other magic,
magic that we've used before:
Scrying, calling a lost witch,
reversing time...
Like, the Book just deserted us,
and deserted Prue.
And I don't understand why.
We lost our sister.
How can we ever understand that?
We have tried every magical way
to bring her back.
But we can't.
She's gone.
I just... I thank God
that I didn't lose you too.
We have to get some rest.
Prue will never forgive us
if we look bad at her funeral.
Social Services, can I help you?
Printing.
South Bay Social Services,
may I help you?
Paige, you find that study yet?
- Paige, did you hear me?
- Yeah, it's in the printer.
- I'm sorry, I have to go.
- What do you mean, go? Go where?
Paige! Hey, Paige!
- Can I get you anything?
- Oh, no, thanks, sweetie.
Look who's back.
Cole.
I was afraid you weren't
gonna make it to the funeral.
Well, l...
I can't make it. Or shouldn't, anyway.
The Source has every demonic
bounty hunter looking for me.
Yeah, so, what else is new?
This is different.
Saving you makes it different.
It makes me a traitor.
He's not gonna stop
until he finds me.
I don't want that happening
at Prue's funeral.
- So we'll protect you.
- You can't protect me.
Why not? We're still witches,
aren't we?
Yeah, but you're not
the Charmed Ones anymore.
He's right.
Without the power of three--
I don't understand. Isn't it harder
to track a demon in a cemetery, Cole?
You have to go.
I need you there.
Hey. How are you holding up?
Okay.
- It's sweet of you to stop by.
- Had to.
Besides, you should know
they're assigning Prue's case
- to another inspector.
- What case?
"What case?" Are you kidding?
Prue and a prominent doctor
were killed here, Leo.
Made a lot of press.
People want answers.
Important people.
So, what's this guy gonna find, that
it was some kind of demonic hit man?
- Give me a break.
- He might.
Look, you don't know him like I do.
He'll keep looking
until he finds something.
- Believe me.
- I'm not worried.
Well, I am. I saw what happened
when they were exposed as witches.
Time may have reversed itself,
but it still cost Prue her life.
Would you people mind?
For God's sake, we're burying
my daughter today. Can't this wait?
Piper?
Honey...
...we have to go.
I don't wanna go.
Why not?
Because if I go,
that'll mean that Prue's
really not coming back.
And I don't think I can handle that.
We can handle it together.
She's been there my whole life.
I've always had a big sister.
And I don't know how to live
without one.
Piper.
Why didn't you save her?
- I tried.
- But you didn't.
Why didn't they let you
save her too?
The Elders?
They couldn't.
They don't have that kind of power.
Then what the hell good are they?
It's okay to be angry.
I'm not angry. I am pissed off.
Don't you understand?
You healed the wrong sister.
You saved me
because I'm your damn wife,
and you should have saved her
because she was the best,
because she...
You should...
Why did they put us through
so much
for it to end this way?
May I be seen?
- Have you found Belthazor?
- No, something else.
Something more important, perhaps.
Nothing is more important.
Not even the Charmed Ones?
- The Charmed Ones are dead.
- Not all of them.
One gone ends the threat.
Of course, if you had foreseen
that a whitelighter
was going to help Belthazor
save his witch, they'd all be gone.
Be grateful I don't turn you
into a snake.
Yes, but then how would you see
into the future without me?
Without the Charmed Ones
to worry about anymore,
I may not need to.
Well, in that case, you better
keep me around
a little while longer.
What do you see?
I see...
...a witch's call on the spirit winds.
...another.
"--that which belongs
to fellowship and love,
that which belongs
to the circle
remains with us.
The wheel turns.
As life is a day,
so our sister has passed
into night.
Nothing is final.
And we who remain behind know
that one day we will once again
share the bread and wine
with our sister."
Oh, blessed spirit,
we bid you farewell,
for you await a new destiny.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
How did you know Prue?
- From work?
- No, just...
Just from around.
You know.
Have we met somewhere?
No, I don't-- I don't think so.
Anyway,
my condolences.
Thank you.
- Phoebe?
- Phoebe.
- Are you all right?
- I saw him.
- The demon that killed Prue.
- Shax?
- What was he doing?
- He was killing that girl.
- What girl?
- The one I was just talking to.
We gotta go find her.
Go, go!
Stop it.
Stop it, stop it, stop it, damn it!
This is Prue's funeral,
for God sakes!
Can we at least bury her in peace?
Is that too much to ask?
Thank you.
- I don't see her anywhere.
- Who?
The girl from my premonition.
Phoebe,
- you need to be more careful.
- I'm sorry.
Are you sure you don't recognize her
from anywhere?
Well, she did look familiar,
like I've seen her somewhere before.
But somehow we have to find her
before night falls,
- or else--
- Honey, what are you doing?
- I'm cleaning.
- You don't clean. You hate cleaning.
I know, but it's better
than falling apart, isn't it?
Maybe you should just try
and focus on the girl.
She was attacked on a rooftop?
Yeah, one with a helipad.
But it wasn't a tall building,
although there were a lot of
taller buildings around it.
Okay, so we just need to figure out
which building it was
- before Shax does.
- And do what exactly?
You can't defeat Shax,
not without the power of three.
Well, you and Prue did.
That's because Prue
was the strongest.
Trying to do it without her
would be suicide.
Yeah, but-- Maybe so, but I got that
premonition for a reason, Piper.
That girl is our innocent,
so we have to try and save her.
Says who? Why do we have to?
- Piper.
- What?
Do you really expect us to keep doing
this stuff after what happened?
To keep risking our lives? Do they?
- Piper, keep your voice down.
- No, Leo, I won't.
I don't wanna do this anymore,
okay? It's-- It's over.
You can tell them we buried
their precious Charmed Ones
when we buried our sister.
No, leave her be.
She needs to be alone.
Look, I don't know
where we go from here.
But I do know
that I can't let that girl die.
Especially not by the same demon
that killed Prue.
The question still remains:
How are you gonna stop Shax
without the power of three
to say the vanquishing spell?
I'm hoping that a demon and a witch
fighting together might be enough.
Interested?
Why not? Beats sitting around here
waiting for the next bounty hunter
to attack.
I appreciate you coming over.
It means so much to the girls.
Dad? Excuse us, Aaron.
- We have to go. Will you be okay?
- Go where?
Trust me, you don't wanna know.
Phoebe, Victor?
Sorry about this, but lnspector Cortez
insisted on meeting today.
I just wanted to extend
my deepest sympathies.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
I'll get the car.
- Where's Piper?
- Upstairs.
- She's not feeling well.
- Understandable.
I lost a sister once myself.
I know how hard it is.
We're gonna find the monster who
did this to your sister, Miss Halliwell.
I promise you this.
Something I said?
No.
Just the word "monster."
Well, that's what he was.
How else do you describe
somebody so vicious?
We gotta stop him
before he strikes again.
I couldn't agree more.
If you'll excuse me, inspector.
I know what a difficult time this is
for you and your sister, Miss Halliwell,
- but we really need to talk.
- But not now.
Of course. Sorry.
I am a witch, damn it.
I've summoned people before,
and I'm going to summon Prue
whether you like it or not.
No more playing games,
no more being the good witch.
I want to talk to my sister.
I need to talk to my sister.
At the very least, you owe me that.
Hear these words, hear my cry
Spirit from the other side
Come to me, I summon thee
Cross now the great divide
- Grams.
- Hello, my darling.
How are you?
How am l? Are you kidding?
Do you guys not get the news
up there?
- I meant, how are you holding up?
- Not very well.
I'm a little lost.
Why didn't you come before
when I called after--?
I couldn't, Piper. I was busy.
You were busy?
I was with Prue.
Of course you were. Right.
Well, that would make sense.
Is she okay?
Your mother and l
are helping her through this.
But how is she?
I'm not allowed to tell you now,
just like you're not allowed
to see her,
at least not for a while anyway.
Why?
Because seeing Prue right now,
speaking to her,
keeps her alive for you,
which keeps you from being able
to move on with your life,
to continue your destiny.
What destiny?
Okay, it's over, it's done.
Prue is gone, and l...
I know, sweetie, I know.
But if there's one thing you've
learned over the last three years
it's that there's always
a reason for everything.
Which means there's a reason
for this too.
Your destiny still awaits.
Blessed be.
Anything?
Unfortunately, since the last attack,
Belthazor has been very elusive.
Leave Belthazor
to the bounty hunters.
What about the other?
Her future's becoming
much more clear.
And it appears...
...short-lived.
Wasn't that good?
That was good, huh?
- You all right?
- Me? Yeah.
Why?
Well, you just seem a little quieter
than usual, that's all.
What makes you think
I'm not like this all the time?
Well, we've been dating
for a month now,
so I think I'd know.
- Hey, can we get a couple longnecks?
- Sure.
Make mine a mineral water, please.
Thanks.
So much for how well
you know me, cowboy.
I don't drink.
I used to have kind of a problem
with certain liquids.
Lots of problems, actually,
but that's all behind me.
- Do you want to go someplace else?
- No. No, no, no. I like it here.
Gosh, I should, I've been coming to P3
for the last year or so, on and off,
I mean, ever since--
Ever since what?
Oh, no, never mind. It's boring.
All right, but if I tell you
all about Paige
and you use it against me,
I will get out my voodoo doll
and make you sorry you're a man.
So my sad story is that I'm adopted,
only it's not so sad,
because I loved my parents.
God rest.
So after they died,
I went searching for my birth mother,
hoping to get some answers.
I went to the police station, found
the church where I was dumped at.
I checked around. I figured she must
have lived near there, you know?
Even thought I might have been...
...related to the Halliwell sisters
for a minute,
but their mom died a long time ago,
so I gave up on that.
Well, did you ever try to meet
the sisters, ask them about it, or...?
Yeah, right. "Hi, I think your mom
abandoned me at birth.
What's for dinner?"
No, I don't think so.
- Here you are.
- Thanks.
You're welcome.
So that... That still doesn't explain
why you keep coming here.
Well, one of the sisters
owns it, so...
I don't know, I guess I just
kind of feel connected somehow.
That's why I went
to the funeral today.
I just kind of felt like I had to.
Okay, I sound certifiably insane now.
Good job, Paige, way to go.
Don't hurt me, okay?
I can't handle any more right now.
Come on.
I have something to show you.
Here.
Thanks.
I think this is the right place,
but maybe we should try
one of the other rooftops
just to make sure.
Or maybe we should follow your
first instincts and stay right here.
Okay, but what if I'm wrong?
That girl will get killed.
You can't save every innocent,
Phoebe. Or stop every demon.
Yeah. Well, I have to stop this one.
I just hope that by me saying
the vanquishing spell,
it wounds him enough
that you can take him out.
I got a better idea. How about
you and me go someplace.
You know, drop off the face of
the earth. Disappear.
Don't tempt me.
Things have changed, Phoebe.
We can't pretend
we can go on like this.
It's only a matter of time
before The Source finds me,
which means every minute
you're with me, you're in danger.
I've lost too much already, Cole.
I'm not losing you too.
Looks like your instincts were right.
- We gotta shimmer over there.
- And tell her what?
That a demon's about to attack?
I think we should stay right here.
Aren't you afraid
that we're gonna get caught?
I like an element of danger.
Oh, look at the stars.
They're so beautiful.
They make me feel free.
All right. Any ideas?
A couple.
I mean about what we do now.
I mean, we can't just keep watching.
It's just not right.
You're right. We shouldn't
just keep watching.
Okay, very good.
Shane!
She orbed.
She orbed. Did you just see that?
Come on.
- What the hell?
- Get out of here. Hurry, go!
Go!
Say the spell, damn it!
Evil wind that blows
That which forms below
No longer may you dwell
Death takes you with this spell
Cole!
- That was too close.
- It's okay, I'm all right.
It's your innocent I'm worried about.
Are you sure she orbed? Are you sure
it wasn't something else?
Leo, she disappeared.
Bright white shiny thingies came,
and then she reappeared.
What else could it be?
- It just doesn't make any sense.
- Why not?
Why would Shax
want to kill a whitelighter?
Maybe he doesn't know
she is one.
Right, The Source sends out
his personal assassin,
but doesn't know who he's after?
Is it possible that she didn't know
she's a whitelighter?
No, why?
Because she acted as if she didn't.
She acted just as surprised
- as we were when she orbed out.
- That doesn't make any sense either.
Okay, why don't you go up and ask
the Elders what does make sense
so we don't go
risking our lives again.
I'll be right back.
Maybe I should go to the other side
and see what I can find out.
- No.
- I'll be careful. Nobody will see me.
Besides, it could be good for me
to go back down,
confuse any bounty hunters
that might be trying to track me.
Don't worry.
I won't disappear on you.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, sure, why not?
We could have another funeral
tomorrow.
I mean, all the dishes are out, and
we pretty much know who to invite.
Piper.
Just tell me one thing.
Are you insane,
or are you just plain stupid?
We buried Prue this morning,
and you go off tonight
and nearly join her.
- What the hell is the matter with you?
- I was trying to save an innocent.
No. You were trying
to get yourself killed,
which is what this family does best,
is get killed.
Isn't it obvious by now
that our only destiny is to die?
And you are making it
way too easy for them, Phoebe.
You are just walking right into it.
I am so sorry.
I cannot handle anything right now,
and I certainly cannot handle
losing another sister.
- Paige.
- Hey.
What happened?
Shane, I feel so bad.
I just got scared and I ran.
- Well, of course.
- Are you all right? What did they say?
It's no big deal,
just a little concussion.
- Oh, no.
- No, I'm gonna be fine.
They wouldn't be releasing me
if I wasn't, right?
I'm just glad you're okay too.
Yeah, well, physically anyway.
Did you talk to the cops yet?
- No, why?
- Why?
They wanna find out who attacked us,
that's why. I told them you saw him.
- You did what?
- Well, you did, didn't you?
Did you?
- Who are you?
- lnspector Cortez, Homicide.
I'd like to ask you
a couple of questions.
Wait, Homicide?
No one was murdered.
Well, based on the m.o., if it's
the same perpetrator I think it was,
that just makes you lucky.
He killed two people
last week, violently.
One of them a young woman
who looked a little bit like you.
Prue.
Prue Halliwell.
Did you know her?
No. No, not really.
Well, in a way you did, right?
What way was that? Were you friends
of hers, a friend of her sisters?
No, not friends.
Then what?
Okay, look. I know
you know something.
I can see it in your eyes.
Just like I know
they know something too.
If you're trying to protect them
in any way, I'll find out.
Well, in that case, they have
nothing to worry about.
You rest up. I'll be back.
Excuse me.
Here, this should help.
It's chamomile.
I had three cups.
Thanks.
Doesn't seem real, does it?
No.
What are we gonna do
with all of her stuff?
And what are we gonna do
with her car?
I don't know.
Sell it, I guess.
- Unless you want it.
- No.
We're gonna get through this,
you know.
We just have to stick together.
- Well?
- Well, they don't know
anything about her,
so she's definitely not a whitelighter.
Then why can she orb, Leo?
They can't explain it.
Wait a minute. How is it possible
that they don't know--?
Sorry I took so long. I had to dodge
a couple of bounty hunters.
- Did you find anything out?
- You have no idea what I found out.
The Source doesn't think
she's a whitelighter at all.
In fact, he thinks she might
be another...
...Charmed One.
That's why he put Shax on it.
He thought he ended
the power of three.
Now he's worried this girl
may somehow reconstitute it.
No, but that's not possible.
Is that possible?
- Piper?
What's going on?
I'm going to ask Grams
what's going on, actually.
Grams?
"Your destiny still awaits," she says.
"There's a reason for everything,"
she says.
So it's time to summon
her transparent butt back here
and find out exactly
what that reason is.
- Okay, Piper, but what makes you--?
- Hear these words
Hear my cry
Spirit from the other side
Come to me, I summon thee
Cross now the great divide
Piper, why are you calling?
Phoebe... What's going on?
Grams, why does The Source think
that the Charmed Ones
can be reconstituted?
I-- I don't know
what you're talking about.
You know what, Grams? You were
a lousy liar when you were alive,
and now as a ghost, you're worse.
If you know something, Grams,
you have to tell us.
We deserve to know.
I can't. I'm sworn to secrecy.
By who?
By me.
Mom?
You can't just walk in here like this.
- Search warrant says I can.
- What the hell are you looking for?
Do you really expect me to believe
you don't know, inspector?
Follow me.
And keep your voice down.
We didn't tell anybody
because we were afraid
that there would be reprisals,
afraid that you girls would be denied
your powers, your birthright.
It happened after your father
and I were divorced,
when Sam and I were together.
Sam?
Her whitelighter.
Apples don't fall far
from the forbidden tree, I see.
Go on.
You were both toddlers.
You just thought Mommy
got a little fat.
You never knew I was pregnant.
- I was the only one who knew.
- And Sam, obviously.
Well, yes, of course.
We wanted to keep the baby...
...of course, but Mother--
Well l-- I knew it would be
disastrous.
You know, before you and Leo,
Piper, it wasn't just forbidden,
it was unthinkable for witches
to be with whitelighters,
I mean, let alone have children
with them.
So that's why we had to--
- Why we decided...
- Yes.
...to give the baby up.
Sam and I took her to a local church
as soon as she was born.
And we asked the nun there
to find a home for her.
And she found one,
a very, very good home.
Yes.
Explains why the Elders
didn't know about her.
All right, hold it.
Wait just one minute.
Are you telling me that that girl,
our innocent, is really...
...our sister?
Your baby sister.
- Their baby half-sister.
- But by my half,
which makes her a sister witch.
Well, actually, not yet anyway.
Not until all three of you
are here together by the book,
just like before.
Charmed...
...again.
And I thought my family
was screwed up.
Well, I'll be damned.
Darryl, do something.
He's a cop, Piper.
And he's got a search warrant.
And believe me, I've found
what I've been searching for.
Don't move. I'll shoot.
- And so will l.
- Cole.
Okay, inspector,
just put the gun down.
There is a very good explanation
for all of this.
Feel free to chime in
anytime, guys.
My whole life, I suspected
evil magic was real.
That there was something more.
I've seen too many horrible things
in the job to suspect otherwise.
Not the least of which are
the two murders that happened here.
- Wait, are you accusing us--?
- I've just begun to accuse you, lady!
All right, fine, you caught us.
Congratulations.
So, what are you going
to do about it? Shoot us?
Easy, Grams. Not all of us
are dead, remember?
All right, look. You can't arrest us.
Especially not them.
- Nobody will ever believe you.
- Maybe not at first.
I'm putting this whole place
under constant surveillance.
I'm taping your every move.
Sooner or later, I'll catch you
doing something supernatural.
And then--
Think you've been through
enough today, huh?
Thank you.
Darryl, go, get out of here. We don't
want you to take the fall for this.
No. It's okay.
No, it's not. This is our problem.
He wants to expose us, not you.
Let us take care of this. Please?
If you need me, you know
where to find me, huh?
Doesn't solve your problem.
He's gonna wake up eventually.
You just bought yourself some time.
Which you're gonna need,
especially if you wanna save your...
Sister?
Well, what are you waiting for?
Just write a spell. Get rid of him.
Get rid of him?
Well, you know what I mean.
Dump him somewhere. Anywhere.
With all the witches in this room,
we ought to be able
to do something with him.
I mean, just start rhyming.
Take him back, take him away
Remove him now, don't let him stay
We call the spirits to help undo
And send him off to...
... Timbuktu
Whoa, it worked.
Timbuktu? You sent him
to Timbuktu?
All right, well, it was the only thing l
could think of that rhymed with "undo."
Don't worry. I'll... I'll find him.
Okay, well, this is way too much
for me to handle. Way too much.
Nobody can blame you
for being angry, sweetie.
Angry? Yeah, I'm angry.
I'm confused.
And you know what?
This-- This is just crazy.
You cannot float in here
after all these years
and go, "Oh, gosh, I forgot.
By the way, you've got a sister."
Especially not today of all days.
I know it's a lot, sweetie,
more than anybody
should have to deal with.
But you're going to have
to deal with it.
The best way you know how.
Losing Prue,
learning about another sister...
...this is your path.
It's your destiny.
Get angry at it, cry about it,
but don't fight it,
or it'll consume you.
Come on, Patty.
The rest is up to them.
I can't sense where she is because
she's technically not a witch yet.
All right, so all we have to go on
is that church that Mom mentioned
- and the nun.
- Let's just get one thing straight:
I am only doing this to save her.
I'm not remotely interested
in reconstituting...
...the Charmed Ones.
I... The door was open.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't be here.
Oh, no, no, no. No, no.
We were just coming to look for you.
- You were?
- Yep.
Come on in. Welcome. I'm Phoebe.
- And this is--
- Piper.
I know. I've been to your club.
It's pretty great.
Thank you. And you are...?
Paige. My name is Paige.
Another P. Imagine that.
It's nice to meet you.
Okay. What was that?
I think that means
you're supposed to be here.
- Run! Get upstairs!
- Leo!
What are we doing?
What is that thing?
We'll explain later.
Okay, just say this spell
out loud with us, okay?
- Spell? What are you guys, witches?
- And so are you, we hope.
Well, we're about to find out.
Evil wind that blows
That which forms below
No longer may you dwell
Death takes you with this spell
It's not enough.
Shax was just the messenger.
- We gotta get The Source.
- The source of what?
Of all evil.
What have you guys
turned me into?
- Paige.
- Wait.
My assassin failed.
The witch is alive.
Yes, I know.
You told me her future
was short-lived.
You told me--
I told you only that it appeared
to be short-lived.
Seeing into the future
is not always exact,
especially when magical forces
are at play.
The power of three is strong.
She'll be almost untouchable
now that she's united
with her new sisters.
Once the bond is formed perhaps.
But it has yet to.
Which means she's vulnerable,
easily swayed.
Forty-eight little hours.
The window of opportunity agreed to
eons ago by both sides
to protect free will.
The great flaw in the grand design.
She hasn't chosen
the other side yet.
Well, she's young, confused.
Doesn't know which way to turn.
You must seduce her
into using her powers for evil.
Then she will become evil.
And that's even better than killing her.
Which, of course, you could still do.
You need to get close to her.
Read her soul, corrupt it,
and she's yours.
And, you.
You need to see the future
more clearly, Oracle...
...for your own future.
What the hell? Who are you?
For now, I am you.
Oh, my God, the most horrible thing
just happened to me.
I can't explain--
It's okay, honey. I'm here now.
It's okay.
I don't understand how you
can keep healing innocents
but you can't figure out a way
to heal yourself.
Well, it's kind of hard to heal myself
when I'm knocked out.
Leo, how's it possible for an angel
to even get knocked out?
I mean, you are, after all,
technically dead.
Three years together,
and now you're asking questions?
Well, I think the more
appropriate question
is how does a whitelighter
get somebody knocked up?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Well, what do you think it means?
If this is about Paige,
I swear the Elders had no idea
that she even existed.
Or that she was your sister.
- Sister witch.
- Half witch, half whitelighter.
Let's not forget that little surprise.
I still can't believe that Mom
kept that a secret from us.
Well, it sounded like she didn't
have much of a choice.
We're her daughters.
She could have found a way
to share that information with us.
That better not be another
long-lost relative.
- Hi, Piper.
- Hi there.
- Where's Cortez?
- Who?
Inspector Cortez,
the one I hit over the head.
The one you said you would
take care of. He's missing.
Police inspectors are not supposed
to be missing. Where is he?
- Well, I kind of sent him to--
- Timbuktu.
It rhymed with "undo."
Timbuktu.
- It's okay. Cole went to get him.
- Cole?
- Cole.
- Wait.
Damn bounty hunters.
They're like gnats.
Where's the inspector?
Don't worry, I found him.
Moved him to a place
he can't tell a soul what he saw.
Literally.
What do you mean?
Where did you put him?
In the basement?
No, I think he means
a little bit further down than that.
Cole, he's a cop.
He's one of the good guys.
He's also the one who can
expose them as witches.
I'd think that you, above anybody,
would want to avoid that at all costs.
Not at that cost.
We have to save him.
Save him? What do you mean,
save him? What--? What's going on?
You know what? We are gonna
take care of this whole mess.
- Wait a sec, hold--
- You don't worry about it.
All right.
Okay, maybe you can talk
to the inspector, reason with him.
And what if he can't?
What if you two get exposed?
What's to say the same thing won't
happen to you that happened to Prue?
Well, it's a risk we'll have to take.
You know what, there's another risk
you guys have to worry about.
On the way back, I heard gargoyles.
Gargoyles? You mean,
like, statues?
That's only in their resting state.
They come alive to ward off evil.
In this case, I think they're trying
to ward off The Source.
I think he's surfaced.
Wait, what?
He's here? Now? Where?
I don't know. Could be anywhere.
Or anyone.
He probably came for Paige.
But she doesn't stand a chance
against him.
She doesn't even know
what her power is yet.
Leo, we don't stand a chance
against him.
Not without Prue.
But you might with Paige.
The new power of three.
Can you sense her?
I don't think so. She's too new.
Well, then we just have to start with
the church Mom was talking about.
- Piper--
- What? Phoebe,
I'm not crazy about it either,
but we can't just do nothing. Not now.
Mom wouldn't want us to.
And neither would Prue.
Oscar, what's the matter,
sweetheart?
It's okay, I'm home.
Maybe he doesn't like me.
Don't be ridiculous.
He's always liked you.
Well, aren't you gonna tell me
what happened last night?
No, it's nothing.
Seemed like something to me.
You were pretty scared.
Let's just say that when I wanted
to find out who I was,
I didn't want to find out
I was a freak.
- Can we just talk about this later?
- Of course.
Hey...
... I never got a chance to thank you
for taking such good care of me.
Oscar.
Listen, I should get to work anyway.
I'm in enough trouble with the boss
as it is.
Well, I know how badly
you want to be there
for that placement hearing.
- How did you know about that?
- Well, you told me, remember?
Little boy, abusive dad.
You said nothing gets under
your skin more than that.
Right, okay.
Make yourself at home.
Stop by for lunch if you feel up to it.
Count on it.
Help me!
You. Stay away from me!
- Stay away!
- We're here to save you.
- You're the one who put me here!
- No, no. Actually, that was just me.
Hoping you'd change your mind
about the girls. Have you?
Killing me is the only way
to keep me from trying to stop you!
We're not gonna kill you, inspector.
But what you don't understand
is that by exposing the girls,
you're not stopping evil,
you're helping it.
Oh, yeah, right.
You do understand
that if we take him back, it's over.
I'll lose Phoebe.
And you'll lose Piper.
- Take my hand.
- No.
Take my hand.
Where else can I take you
that's worse than this?
- So how's Aunt Julie?
- Much better.
- Yeah?
- Thank you, dear, for asking.
Is her hip any better?
Jake and Carol Grisanti
for Mr. Cowan?
Okay. I'll let him know you're here.
I'm sorry. Say that again.
I got distracted.
He'll be with you in a few minutes.
I'm gonna go wash up, all right?
What do you want?
Oh, God.
Hey, before you go,
- can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
Do you guys still go to that church
that Mom and Dad used to go to?
- Yeah, we still go.
- Is there still a nun
called Sister Agnes there?
- lsn't she the one who found you?
- Yeah, right, the one that found me.
- Have you spoken to her?
- No, no, I haven't spoken to her,
but something's come up.
I think I should.
Uncle Dave, I gotta go.
I'll call you back, okay?
- Okay, I love you, Paige.
- Yeah, I love you too.
- Mr. Cowan.
- Hey, look, Paige, I got this, okay?
But you can't let that little boy
go home with that jerk.
Paige, number one, you don't know
for a fact he's abusing the boy.
And number two,
this is none of your business.
You are an assistant,
not a social worker.
That's because you're too cheap
to make me one.
Phoebe, I think I found the...
The church.
Phoebe?
What are you doing in here?
You remember the time I borrowed
this from Prue without asking her?
Which time?
When my boyfriend's cat peed on it.
She got so mad, I thought
she was gonna have a stroke.
But the funny thing was...
...she got mad at you,
because she thought that you
were the one that borrowed it.
And you never told her the truth.
She never knew it was really me.
I miss her so much.
I know.
Me too.
I was wondering
when you were gonna let go.
I was just-- I was trying to-- Thanks.
--stay strong, you know,
keep it together for you.
And then I put all my energy
into trying to save Paige
because I figured only one of us
could break down at a time.
Otherwise we'd both be useless.
I'm scared, Piper.
I am really, really scared.
She always took the lead.
She was...
She was our big sister.
How are we supposed to go on
without her?
How are we supposed to go up
against The Source without her?
I don't know.
But I do know that we can't let
the bastard get Paige either.
So no matter what we think or feel,
she is our sister.
And sisters protect each other.
- What's happening?
- Nothing's been decided.
- We're gonna meet again tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
You can't let him go home
with that kid.
I can and I am.
Look, Paige, you weren't in there.
He was very persuasive.
Persuasive? What about
the police report?
What about the counsellor's
recommendations?
Look, Paige, I know
how you feel about these cases.
But we can't make a decision
based on what you think.
We have to base it on fact.
Right now, we don't have enough yet.
I'm sorry.
You got a problem, lady?
Yeah, I do. I got a problem
with people who hit their kids.
- Come on, Jake, let's just go.
- Wait, wait.
Listen, I can do
whatever the hell I want to...
...and there's nothing
you can do to stop me.
- Where do you think you're going?
- Church.
Can you give me a hand?
I think that he must have slipped.
Excuse me?
- Are you Sister Agnes?
- Yes.
- And who might you be?
- I'm Paige. Paige Matthews.
You might not remember me.
I probably changed a little bit
since you last saw me
on August 2nd, 1 977.
Does that ring any bells?
Oh, dear Lord.
I was just about your age
when they came.
They?
My mother and my father?
They came in a swirl
of bright white lights, just like...
...angels.
White lights? What do you mean?
Well, that's how they appeared,
with you in their arms.
I was stunned.
I didn't know what to think.
They said you were in great danger.
That they had no other choice
but to give you up
to protect you.
- Danger? What kind of danger?
- Well, they didn't say.
But I could tell from their pain
that it must be very real.
They asked me to find you
a good home,
a safe home,
and to keep their secret...
...until you came looking.
But how could they know?
Because you come from them,
my dear.
As wonderful and precious
as your adoptive parents were to you...
...you still come from angels.
They asked me to save this for you
for this day.
It's what they bundled you up in.
Your mother had only one request:
That your name begin with a P.
- Yes, may I help you?
- Hi.
Hey, what's up?
We need to get you out of here.
What did you do to her?
Oh, she just froze her.
She'll be fine.
Yeah, lucky I didn't blow her up.
My powers have been a little off lately.
Piper.
- Is that our blanket?
- No, that's mine.
- Leave me alone.
- All right, jeez.
Paige.
- Stop, or I'll freeze.
- She's a witch, you can't freeze her.
- She doesn't know that.
- Will you please just leave me alone.
Look, we know
what you're going through.
We went through the same thing when
we first found out we were witches too.
Look, you just gotta trust us.
Somebody very, very bad is after you.
Trust you? You just froze a nun.
How do I know
you're not the bad ones?
- Well, if we are, then you are, sister.
- Piper.
What? Fine, then you try.
You have a magical power,
you know.
At least, if you're really
a Charmed One, you do.
And the sooner you learn it, the sooner
you'll be able to protect yourself.
- I have a power?
- According to the prophecy,
the third sister has the power
to move things with her mind.
Like Prue could.
- How does it work?
- You concentrate on an object,
Iike that candle right there.
And then you just wave your arm
at it.
Or you could squint your eyes.
She used to squint her eyes.
Maybe I'm not one of you after all
if I can't even make that candle--
So perhaps the whitelighter
in her makes it work differently?
Half-breed.
She better be here, Oracle.
- I'm running out of time.
- She is. Don't worry.
No!
What is that?
I don't know.
- Paige.
- Shane?
What's the matter?
My God, what happened?
I don't know. Something's after me.
- Paige.
- Come on, let's get out of here.
- Paige, come back!
- What the hell was that?
- Good question.
Look, we didn't have
to bring you back, you know.
We could have just let you rot.
- Cole, I don't think this is helping any.
- Like your way is.
Cortez, where you been?
- Operations.
- This is lnspector Cortez.
I need a surveillance team,
round the clock.
- I'll take one shift.
- What are you doing?
What I said I'd do
before you clipped me from behind.
You're making a big mistake,
inspector.
You have no idea what you're doing.
- You wanna bet?
- Something's wrong.
Piper's calling.
Just so you know,
whatever pain you put Phoebe
through because of what you're doing
will be nothing compared
to the pain I put you through.
You understand?
Cortez, you there?
What's the address?
1 329 Prescott Street.
Phoebe and Piper Halliwell.
They're murder suspects.
- Yeah, all right.
- All right.
Come on. Come on.
- I got four guys who can do it.
- Yeah, thanks.
- Hey, listen, Cortez.
- Let go of me.
You make me sick.
How long have you been
covering up for them, huh?
How many other murders have
you ignored just to protect them?
You're a disgrace to that shield,
my friend.
You think this is the first time
I have risked my career for those girls?
My life, my family?
They're the best people
I've ever met.
They'll do more good
than you'll ever know.
- And it cost them their sister.
- Hey, hey, inspector, ease up.
- You all right?
- I'm good, I'm good.
Yeah.
So The Source was there
at the church?
Well, the gargoyles weren't
exactly whistling "Dixie," Leo.
Plus, something pretty powerful
knocked us on our asses.
But if he was there,
why didn't he try to kill Paige?
Maybe he didn't want to go up
against the Charmed Ones.
No, it doesn't make sense. He knows
that Paige is new to her powers.
If ever there was a time to attack...
Wait a minute.
What if he's not trying
to kill her anymore?
What if he's trying to lure her
to his side?
Translation, please?
- The mythological window.
- There's a window of opportunity,
- an opening.
- Forty-eight hours.
Right, 48 hours where
a nascent witch who hasn't chosen
to use her power for good or evil yet
can be swayed either way.
Wait, so all he has to do
is cast a spell on her?
No, he can't. It has to be her choice,
but he can tempt her, entice her.
If he gets her to use
her powers for evil--
She becomes evil forever.
Who makes up
these cockamamie rules?
Oh, never mind.
Okay, so we have less
than 24 hours to get to Paige
and no idea how to find her.
But I'll bet The Source does.
Here.
Thanks.
I'm so sorry to involve you in all this.
All of what?
Paige...
...what's going on?
I don't know.
I'm so confused.
I don't know what to do.
Hey.
You don't have to know.
You're safe here...
...with me.
I'll take care of you.
Sure you don't want me
to turn Belthazor loose on Cortez,
just for a minute or two?
No. He doesn't have anything
on the girls yet.
Besides, now is no time to be blurring
the line between good and evil.
This is useless.
We're never gonna find Paige
without a little help.
Works every time.
Okay, an enchantment spell.
Wait, how is this
gonna help us find her?
Well, maybe it's not to find Paige.
Maybe it's so we can lD The Source.
See the last line? It's,
"So she can reveal the evil within."
But that'll only help
if we can find him.
Maybe we can.
Or at least, maybe you can.
What does he mean?
Demons can sense
The Source's aura.
It's how he reminds us of his power,
his reach.
Maybe if I focused on it--
Then he'll know you're doing it,
and he'll find you.
Not if I was careful.
It's your only chance
at saving your sister.
Okay, so we need something
to enchant.
Right.
- How about these?
- Oh, Phoebe.
- What? They're perfect.
- All right.
Magic forces, far and wide
Enchant these so those can't hide
Allow this witch to use their ends
So she can reveal the evil within
Okay, better test them.
- Well?
- Nothing. You look the same.
How about me?
What?
What do I look like?
You look like hell.
Enchanting.
Thanks for the magical assist,
Grams.
How do you know
it wasn't somebody else?
You know who you are now, Paige.
This is where your destiny lies.
It lies not with your sister witches.
It's for no one but you.
This is what you've been
searching for your whole life.
This is why you have the power.
You can't stop me.
Use your power
for your own desires,
to seek your own revenge.
Use your power.
Call for his heart.
Call for his life.
Heart.
Jake, what is it?
No!
I don't see Paige anywhere.
Are you sure this is
the right place, Cole?
The Source is here. I can sense it.
Wait, there she is.
- What is she doing?
- I don't know,
but she's got a black aura
around her.
- The Source?
- No, it can't be.
If Phoebe saw my demonic self,
then she'd see his too.
Yeah, well, whatever it is,
it's not good.
Come on.
Jake! Jake, what--?
Paige? Paige, it's me, Phoebe.
And Piper.
He's evil. He's hurting his child.
Someone, hurting--
No, you're being seduced
into doing this.
No! No, Jake!
All right, you know what? Hi.
Leo, take her, go home.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Let's get out of here.
Are you sure you're all right?
Maybe you better lay back down.
I'm not covering for you
anymore, Carol.
You keep your hands off our son.
You two go ahead.
I'm gonna stay behind,
make sure The Source
doesn't follow you.
Don't die too quickly, traitor.
I want your beloved witch
to see your last breath...
...to feel the heartache of loss again.
Oracle, find Paige one last time.
Leo, where's--?
I'm having a hard time convincing her
that she is not evil.
- I see that.
- Lamp.
Bright side? At least she's getting
the hang of her new power.
That was Mom's crystal.
- Okay, somebody--
- Off of me!
Okay, relax. Relax.
All right, now what?
We just better hope there's
some kind of Wiccan exorcism
in the Book of Shadows,
because-- Yeah.
Who are you?
Piper!
That's the-- That's the--
Look, look, look, look, look.
I know who that is.
Your powers are strong.
But will they be enough
without the power of three?
Shane, what's going on?
It's okay, honey. I'm here now.
Stay away from me.
She still has free will.
You can't force her to choose.
Oh, but she's already chosen.
Haven't you?
Come with me.
You'll be safe forever, I promise.
Don't listen to him, he's lying.
They only want you for your power.
You don't have to share it.
It's yours.
You've already seen
what you can do with it.
You did what nobody else could do.
You nearly saved my son
from his father,
from all the pain and suffering
he's put him through.
Please help me.
Don't let him hurt me anymore.
You're my only hope.
No!
Help me!
Phoebe?
Okay, come on, come on.
I guess blood's a little thicker
than evil.
I've broken the Charmed circle before.
I'll do it again.
Besides, it wasn't a complete loss,
thanks to Belthazor.
- What did you do to him?
- Oh, my God.
Inspector, would you get out
of here?!
- Looks like evil wins again, huh?
- Not if I can help it.
- How'd you do that?
- That's what whitelighters do.
We heal good people.
We have to go find Cole.
Cole?
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Heal him.
- You know that it's against the rules.
Leo, screw the rules.
The Elders owe us.
Even if I could, I could only heal
his human half,
and that wouldn't be enough power
to save him.
Aren't I half whitelighter?
I mean, couldn't I use my half
to offset his half?
It's worth a try.
Take my hand.
Hold your other hand
over his wound.
That was good, right?
That was very good.
Let's just hope it wasn't all
for nothing.
Yeah, drive safe.
Thank you.
Thanks, Anna.
- Feels good to be here again.
- Feels good to be anywhere again.
I will drink to that.
- Don't ever scare me like that again.
- Promise.
You okay?
I'm not sure.
Prue?
Yeah.
We barely got through the funeral, and
then everything started to go crazy,
and we haven't had a chance
to mourn yet.
And that's just not right.
I think we'll have
the rest of our lives for that.
I'm still not sure about continuing on
with this destiny thing.
I need some time to think about it.
I hope you're okay with that.
Absolutely.
And I hope you're okay with it too.
They may not be, but I am.
So does this mean
I get free drinks now?
I didn't mean it like that.
It's not that I really drink or...
Okay, I'm just gonna go.
No. Paige, you belong here.
Remember?
Are you sure? I don't wanna intrude.
Come on. Come sit right here.
Okay, so maybe
Leo and I should go...
...pretend like we've got something
better to do.
- Good idea.
- Yeah.
I won't stay long. I just wanted
to come by and thank you.
- For what?
- For what? You mean,
aside from saving my life?
I feel like I should bake you
a cake or something.
Do you cook?
No. No, not really.
So how's Shane?
He's okay, I guess. Except for I'm not
too sure he wants to see me anymore.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- No, I can't say I blame him,
you know. He doesn't know exactly
what happened to him,
but he knows it's something bad,
and he knows it's somehow
connected to me.
Yeah, well, you're not truly one of us
until you've dated a demon,
so welcome to the club.
Can I ask you a question?
Why did you come
to Prue's funeral?
I mean, you never even
met her, right?
No, I never did.
I don't want this to be taken
the wrong way...
...but I just feel like part of me
lost her too.
And I just...
I felt drawn to her, to all you guys.
I guess it was just part of me
trying to find out who I was.
Come on. There's something
we need to show you.
Show me what?
What good magic can do.
Hear these words, hear my cry
Spirit from the other side
Come to me, I summon thee
Cross now the great divide
There's someone here
we thought you should meet.
Paige.
Mom?
Welcome home.