Hey.
Guess what.
You've come to help me
fold the laundry.
No.
What good is being a witch
if I can't just
twitch my nose
and make the laundry fold itself?
Which witch can do that?
Samantha Stephens.
From Bewitched?
Oh, it's only, like, one
of my favourite old television shows.
Sometimes I forget that you've only
been fully human for, like, a month.
And becoming
more human by the day.
What would you say
if I became really human...
...and got a job?
If that's the criteria
for being really human,
then I am in big trouble.
I'm serious.
Paige said that a lawyer
at Legal Aid quit, so she kind of...
...recommended me.
She did?
Of course, if you
don't think I should, then--
No, no.
Actually, I think that's a great idea.
It'll keep you busy
and help you find your identity
while I lose mine.
- Sorry?
- Nothing.
Tell me.
It's just...
...becoming a wife.
I mean, I like Samantha, but I never
actually wanted to become her.
See, Samantha,
she was married
to a human, Darrin.
Darrin completely repressed
Samantha's magic.
Completely denied who she was.
And it wasn't because
he didn't love her. It was just...
That's the way it had to be.
And this was one
of your favourite shows?
Well, not that part.
It's just, growing up,
that was my only role model
for a typical marriage.
So that's all I knew.
And he was able to meet people
and leave the house
and go to work
and build his career.
And she had to stay home.
You know, and cook dinner
and do the laundry.
She went from being Samantha
to being Mrs. Darrin Stephens
overnight.
Well, that won't happen to you.
- Won't it?
- No.
You'll become Mrs. Cole Turner.
Phoebe, come on.
Number one, this is a different time,
different world, obviously.
Number two, we're hardly typical.
I proposed to you
under a hail of demon goo,
and you accepted
while I was bleeding to death.
Remember?
Look, why don't we just...
...do it again, start over.
Grams' ring.
- Where did you get that?
- From Piper.
She gave it to me.
So I could give it to you.
Well, that's not exactly
a good omen.
She was married
with that thing six times.
Well, she must have liked
something about it,
or she would have
stopped at, like, three.
Right?
Miss Phoebe Halliwell,
I come to you,
a man, nothing more,
nothing less, to ask,
will you be my wife?
Yeah.
I will.
Again.
Good.
Tyler, we just wanna talk.
It was an accident. I'm sorry.
- It's all right. Just let us in.
- No, you'll yell at me.
I'll deal with Tyler.
You contact Ludlow.
Who's Ludlow?
He runs the academy
we told you about.
I'm not going to boarding school.
You can't send me away.
Oh, honey, it's for your own good.
I told you, I didn't mean to do it.
I swear I'm not bad. I swear.
Tyler? What's going on?
Is that smoke I smell?
Sun came up again.
Good morning, sunshine.
Let me pour you a cup of coffee.
Notice anything different about me?
Engagement ring.
Notice it, or wear coffee.
- Nice ice.
- Thank you very much.
I can't stop looking at it.
I was like that
when I got my belly ring.
Oh, you're right, a wedding ring
is totally different.
- Phoebe?
- Yeah.
Will you pass me the milk?
It's right next to Leo.
We're not talking to each other.
What? Still?
Wait, I don't understand.
Shouldn't you wait
till after you have kids
to start fighting about them?
Well, what's the matter?
Maybe we can help.
It's about having a magical child
in a non-magical world.
Someone, I won't say who,
has the insane notion of binding
our child's powers.
Why is it insane?
Grams bound your powers
when you were a child.
Yes.
And we spent 20-odd years
ignorant about our destiny.
I look back on those normal days,
and I feel like I was
a complete and total fraud.
I'm not saying hide the truth.
It's just growing up
is hard enough
without the extra burden
of having powers.
Magic is not a burden. It is a gift.
It's a lot for any child to deal with.
Plus ours will be
doubly magical.
Half whitelighter, half witch.
Hey, that's like me.
You might have some trouble.
- Where's Cole? We gotta go to work.
- I'll get him.
And, Paige, thank you so much
for getting him this job.
Especially now, you know,
that we're gonna be married,
and he's gonna have to get used
to bringing home the bacon.
Since when does Phoebe
care about bacon?
I'm sure she meant
all breakfast meats.
Piper, would you please
pass me the milk?
Nope.
Oh, honey, you look gorgeous.
Should I make you some breakfast?
It's the most important
meal of the day.
- I'll grab a coffee on the way.
- Are you sure?
I could whip something up in a jiff.
- In a jiff, really?
- Yeah.
Come on, dude, let's get paid.
Have a great day.
I am so proud of you.
Look at us. We are so Bewitched.
No, no, no. No, we're not.
You feel free to use all the magic
you want while I'm gone.
Okay. Whatever makes you happy.
I wonder what I should
make him for dinner?
So this is your office.
It's got a desk, a chair, a lamp.
What more do you need?
Oxygen.
You know, when I was a DA,
I had an office eight times this size.
Windows, an assistant.
Plus, I could throw energy balls.
Yeah, well, you're human now,
so get used to being humble,
just like all the rest of us.
Cole Turner? Hi, I'm Cynthia Corn,
- director of the Legal Aid office.
- Hi.
Paige has told me such
wonderful things about you.
I wish I had time to get
to know you, but I don't.
- So jumping right in, if we could.
- I have to jump right out.
If anyone needs me,
I'll be down the hall.
Okay, your first case.
Slumlord Alan Yates cut off heat
to his tenants last week.
He's due in at 1 2
for a fact-finding session.
You have two hours to learn
everything you can about this case.
So you better be fast,
and you better be good. Thanks.
Thank you.
I'm only human, you know.
Hi.
Hey.
What's with the kid?
The police brought him in.
Found him sleeping in an alley.
- Is he a runaway?
- Looks like it. His name is Tyler.
I'm having trouble getting
information from him.
Sometimes those little video-game
things help loosen them up.
Billy's got one in the back.
I'll go get it.
Good.
Here you go, Tyler,
thought you might be thirsty.
So have you thought about
giving us a phone number
so we can call your parents,
letting them know you're okay?
Do you want them to know
you're okay?
- Did they hurt you?
- No. They didn't hurt me.
Good, all right.
- But something happened?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
I know it's hard, Tyler,
- but talking is how we fix things.
- I said, I don't want to talk about it!
Fire.
Get the fire extinguisher.
Hey.
Hey, hey, don't go.
You don't have to be afraid.
It's okay. I won't tell anyone
I saw you start the fire.
You saw?
Yeah, but nobody else did.
And I promise I won't tell.
I swear I won't.
I didn't mean to do it.
I know, Tyler, I know.
Please don't make me
go back to the clinic.
I don't ever wanna go back
to my foster parents.
They don't understand me.
I know a place where I can take you
where you'll be safe.
But you gotta trust me, okay?
Come on.
- Sorry, I didn't see you there.
- We're looking for our son.
His name is Tyler,
1 1 years old, blond hair.
- And you are...?
- His foster parents.
Is he here? Is he all right?
- He was.
- Thank God.
We've been checking
everywhere for him.
- We've been worried sick.
- What do you mean?
- Where is he?
- There was a fire,
and in the chaos, he ran off.
Ran off? What do you mean,
you lost him?
Where could he have gone?
We've got to find him.
- I mean, right now.
- I understand this must be difficult.
You don't understand anything. We
need our son, and we need him now.
Would you give me
a moment with my wife?
She's obviously very distraught.
Of course.
You're making a scene.
Can't a mother be upset
about the loss of her son?
You're not reacting
like an overreacting parent.
- You're reacting like a--
- A what?
- A demon.
- We don't have time
to play the concerned parents.
Ludlow wants the boy before nightfall.
- No boy, no bounty.
- These humans can't help.
So, what are we supposed to do?
Wait until Tyler uses his power again?
It's the only way we have
of tracking him.
- What if he doesn't get angry?
- He will.
Just be patient.
How's it going?
Not so good.
He's barely making eye contact.
Not really speaking.
- He's just really afraid.
- Of what?
Himself, his powers.
He's showing the signs of a kid who's
never received sustained affection.
Well, plus being shuffled
in and out of foster homes
doesn't help either.
No, and I get the sense
that he's always
felt like an outsider
and a bit of a freak.
And now he's found out
that, in some ways, he kind of is.
Which is why it could make sense
for us to bind his powers.
Yeah, maybe we could just take off
one of his legs at the same time
because, you know,
they're both part of him.
It is not the same thing, Piper.
Tyler's powers could be a danger
to himself and to others.
You know what?
Don't make our issues his issues.
I think you need to give him
a chance to learn how to control it.
Maybe that's why we met him.
- To teach him, guide him.
- Feed him.
Wow, Phoebe, you went all out.
Oh, well, you know me.
Any excuse to spend
a little extra time in the kitchen.
I do know you,
and that's just not true.
But it is now that I'm gonna be
Sadie, Sadie, married lady.
All right, Sadie, how about
I take the cookies to the kid?
Do you mind if I try talking to him?
No, actually, the sooner
we get through to him, the better
because last time I checked,
kidnapping is still illegal.
I'm gonna go back to work.
You guys call me later.
Eat them while they're hot.
Pheebs, friendly little tip.
Lay off the hair spray.
There's a firestarter in the house.
Hi.
My sister made some cookies.
Do you want some?
I don't blame you.
It could be kind of dicey.
She's not really a great cook.
Why don't you try one so, you know,
her feelings don't get hurt.
Can I have another?
Help yourself.
You know, it's probably
hard to believe,
but something amazing
has happened to you.
You've been given a gift.
A magical gift.
And as strange as it sounds,
you're not alone.
I know exactly
what you're going through.
Yeah, right. You start fires too?
Not exactly.
But I do know what it's like
to possess a power
that you can't control
and to want so desperately to be
normal, but it's just not an option.
And because there aren't
any options, you just
sometimes get so angry
that you wanna--
What was that?
What did you just do?
I proved that I know
what you're going through.
But how did you do that?
Pretty much the same way you do.
I've just learned how to focus
my emotions and control it.
I wish I could control mine.
Then I could be around people.
Is that why you ran away?
Because you were afraid
you were gonna hurt someone?
I was scared.
I set fire to
the living-room couch.
I didn't mean to.
But my foster mom was yelling
at me, that I was "good-for-nothing."
And it made me so mad, I just...
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
In this house, it's okay.
I can also freeze things.
Now, that's cool.
Leo? Could you get some water?
Oh, Leo, I'm so glad you came in.
I have a very important question
to ask you.
What is it?
Do you think that little boy
will be staying for lunch?
I would imagine so.
What's the important question?
That was it.
Really?
Phoebe?
- Are you feeling all right?
- Peachy keen.
I'll get it.
- Hello.
- You gotta keep me
from killing this slumlord.
I got a meeting in, like, ten minutes
with a guy who's the biggest ass.
Hold it. Do not make me
march down there
and wash your mouth out
with soap, mister.
Do you want me to twitch my nose
and turn him into Mr. Nice?
No, I want to use an energy ball
and send him where he belongs.
The jerk cut off the heat, causing
an elderly tenant to get pneumonia.
- Then he tried to evict her.
- Okay, just relax
and try to get through it,
and I will have a martini
- waiting for you when you get home.
- Martini?
Yeah, and a steak. You really need
some more red meat in your diet.
What the hell are you talking about?
Company. I have to go.
I'll get it!
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hi. We're looking for our son, Tyler.
Is he here, by any chance?
You betcha. Come on in.
Can I make you anything?
A sandwich,
- a Spanish omelette, perhaps?
- Wait.
How did you know he was here?
Maternal instinct.
Piper.
I got him.
- Leave them alone.
- Nobody is keeping us
- from collecting our bounty.
- No. Stop.
Shut up, Tyler.
I didn't mean to.
Tyler, you don't have
to explain anything.
We were there,
we saw what happened.
I thought I was gonna
hurt someone,
and then I did.
You did what you had to do.
I did a bad thing.
Tyler, listen to me.
Look at me.
You didn't do a bad thing.
Those were very bad people,
and they were gonna hurt us.
You protected us.
Come on,
I want to show you something.
Come on, it's okay.
A book?
Not just any book.
It's a magical one.
Can I trust you?
Sure. Yeah.
Okay, let's find out
who those people really were.
My foster parents?
They weren't really
your foster parents, Tyler.
- They were...
- Demonic bounty hunters.
"Driven by greed, these heartless
low-level demons will stop
at nothing to collect their bounty."
So if they're bad, does that mean
- I didn't do anything bad?
- That's right.
Is there anything about me in there?
Actually, I think there is.
Here it is. You read.
"The firestarter. An extremely rare
and coveted magical creature."
What does "coveted" mean?
It means "highly desirable, wanted."
I'm wanted?
Very much so.
"Their power is linked
to their emotions.
First manifests itself in adolescence.
They're often trained to be
the bodyguards of The Source."
What's The Source?
A really, really bad guy.
Which means
he's probably resurfacing
if the bounty hunters
are after Tyler.
So Ludlow must be
a bounty hunter too, then.
- Who is Ludlow?
- Some guy who runs
some sort of an academy.
My demon parents
were gonna send me there.
To train, to serve The Source.
So then I am bad.
- Why do you say that?
- Well, if I'm supposed to use
my powers to protect
somebody bad...
No, but that's not how powers work.
They're not good or bad
by themselves.
It's how we use them.
Tyler, why don't you read
a little more while I talk to Piper.
Okay.
See? With a little guidance,
he's already on the road
to acceptance and control.
That's great, but I think
we have another problem.
I figured out how the bounty hunters
found out where Tyler is.
They tracked his powers.
- When he blew up the chair?
- Yeah.
So when he vanquished them...
So there may be
other bounty hunters on the way.
I'm making soup for Cole
He'll eat it in a bowl
I guess that's my new role
Just making soup for Cole
Where's the firestarter?
You nearly scared me half to death.
The boy, now.
I don't like
your tone of voice, mister.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
No messy cleanup.
Since when do you scream
instead of fight?
Actually, I did consider
scratching him.
Okay, that was another
bounty hunter, which means more
are just gonna keep coming
until Ludlow gets Tyler.
Unless we get Ludlow first.
Dishpan hands.
Leo and I can pose as bounty hunters
and say that we have Tyler.
We can gain access to Ludlow
and vanquish him.
Sure. Just as long
as you're home for dinner.
But he's gotta be pretty powerful,
which means we might need
the power of three for us to bring
Ludlow back here, just in case.
And call Paige and tell her
to get her butt back here
- as soon as possible.
- Okey-dokey.
Oh, God, I'll have everything done
for you in one second, okay?
Two secs.
- Paige Matthews.
- Serena? Sam.
Phoebe? Look, I'm in the middle
of about a zillion things.
- Can I just call you back?
- Piper wants you to come home.
And I want you
to bring your appetite.
Yeah, Phoebe, like I said,
I'm in the middle of a zillion things.
Back off. This is assault.
It's better than what you do,
which is close to murder.
- Stay away from me.
- You would not believe
- what Cole is doing.
- Cole? How is my little sweetie?
- Get up, you scum!
- I'll see you in court.
You'll see me every time
you turn around, buddy.
I don't believe this. Let go of him.
- What are you doing?
- I want that heat turned back on
for those tenants today,
do you hear me?
Hands off me.
This is not the way
we do things around here.
Yeah, well, maybe you should.
- Or maybe I should quit!
- You're fired!
He looks so normal.
You sure we should let him
play those games?
Aren't they kind of violent?
Darn it!
Looks like he's learning
to handle his power.
He wouldn't have been
given them if he couldn't.
Is that what you think
about you and your sisters?
I don't know. Maybe.
All I do know is that,
when we finally got
our powers back,
it felt like we were scrambling
to catch up.
And I can't help but think
if we'd had our powers
from day one,
we would have been more prepared.
Things would have
turned out different.
Prue would still be alive?
And The Source would be dead.
And we would be on our way
to having a family,
as opposed to just talking about it.
And life
- would be perfect.
- Not perfect. Just easier.
Obviously, when I recommended you
for the job, I thought
you were a former demon.
You know, do me a favour, Paige,
and don't do me any more favours.
- Good, Paige, you're home.
- Yeah, but not for long.
I have to get back to work
unlike Cole here.
The Legal Aid thing
didn't work out for me.
See, I thought lawyers
were supposed to seek out justice.
Okay, we've got bigger problems.
The Source wants Tyler.
So let's focus
on the most pressing matter at hand.
- Lunch.
- Phoebe.
Darling, what a pleasant surprise.
You feeling okay?
Oh, yeah. Happy as a clam. Why?
What was that?
What was what?
You just flashed. Black and white.
Oh, don't be silly.
Oh, he's not being silly.
We all saw it.
Okay, we don't have time for this.
We gotta get to Ludlow before The
Source does. So, Cole, fix Phoebe.
I don't care how but just do it.
She needs to write a spell.
- Which spell?
- A power-of-three spell, in case
Leo and I have no choice
but to lure Ludlow back here.
Biscuits are ready.
We'll need some proof for Ludlow
that we actually have Tyler.
- We're gonna take his jacket.
- Why can't I come with you?
Because it's too dangerous.
But I can protect myself.
Besides, I helped you out before.
- Didn't l?
- This is different.
Okay, everyone, be ready,
be prepared. No surprises.
Hey!
- What happened?
- He jumped the orb!
Dude, you are so
going back right now.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
We got lost.
The academy is protected by charms,
which means you can't find the place
unless you're looking for it.
Kill them.
- Let's get out of here.
- I'm not going.
You wanna bet?
Hey. I said, no.
Look, just listen to me.
They don't know I'm a firestarter yet.
Once they do,
they'll take us right to Ludlow.
Isn't that what we want?
No. Not at your expense,
and I'm not gonna let you go in there.
And I don't wanna spend the rest
of my life with bad guys chasing me.
He's right. Wherever we take him,
they will eventually find him.
Yeah, but if something
happens to him--
They won't hurt me. Remember?
I'm coveted.
Well, if he tags along,
it might double your chances
of getting Ludlow
and not having to go home.
I'd like to do
something good for once.
All right, but you stay next to me.
And if anything goes wrong,
we're out of there.
Okay.
This better work.
- Hi.
- How'd you--?
We're bounty hunters.
We need to see Ludlow.
- Who's the kid?
- I'm not a kid.
I'm a firestarter.
So are you gonna let us in or not?
- What's the password?
- The password?
It's...
That was it. You're in.
Oh, hi, honey.
What are you doing?
This is no time to be taking a bath.
Piper might be home,
and she's counting on you
- to write a spell.
- Oh, I tried.
And I only got as far
as "hey, demon,"
and then my mind went blank.
Look, I don't know
what's happening to you.
It might be some backfired spell
or curse or something.
But you gotta snap out of it.
There's work to be done.
Yeah. Hey, why aren't you
at the office?
Because I quit my job.
- You what?
- I don't think I'm cut out
- for that whole 9-to-5 life.
- Oh, honey, what will you do?
I don't know.
I'm still searching for who I am.
But we know who you are, which is
a demon-fighting, ass-kicking witch
who never lets her sisters down.
So get out of that bathtub
and show me what you're made of!
Better?
Cole, how's your progress going--?
Oh, God!
Full-frontal Phoebe. Sorry.
- She just-- She just flashed.
- Yeah, I got that.
No, I mean she just flashed
black and white.
Again? She's like an old TV
that's on the blink or something.
Hey, maybe that's the connection.
The TV show Bewitched,
is that in black and white or colour?
Originally black and white.
I'm very chilly.
- Phoebe, sit down.
- Okay.
Why are you asking me
about Bewitched?
Phoebe was worried about
becoming an old-fashioned housewife
Iike Samantha. And that might be
fine for some people,
but for Phoebe,
that could be dangerous.
So I'll take care of her, and you need
to write the power-of-three spell.
No, I've never done that before.
Well, you're gonna have
to learn fast, so go. Hurry.
- And you.
- Yeah.
You're coming with me.
Okay.
So we're gonna try
to take him out, right?
Yes, I will go in first.
What if I can't--?
I mean, I have to get angry
for my power to work, don't l?
- So?
- So, what if I'm just scared instead?
What if it doesn't work?
Just walk through that door.
- Through the door?
- Yes. Through the door.
Relax.
Where is he?
Ludlow.
So...
...you brought
the alleged firestarter.
You've given us quite
the run-around, haven't you, boy?
I said, haven't you, boy?
- Yes.
- Yes, what?
Yes, sir.
No one teaches manners anymore.
About our payment,
see, we don't want any surprises.
Yeah, because we hate surprises.
What are you doing?
Oh, you're afraid
that I'll grab the boy
and stiff you?
If the child is a firestarter,
you'll get your reward.
If he's not...
...you'll all die.
Well, Tyler is a firestarter,
so that won't be an issue.
Prove it.
Go ahead.
Give him everything you got.
What? Not even a flicker?
Okay, he's just a little scared.
Oh, that's ridiculous.
Don't be scared, boy.
You're closing in on the most
important moment of your life.
Prove what you are,
and you'll meet The Source,
the most powerful evil
that exists in the universe.
Yeah, okay, see, that's not helping.
- Do it.
- He's just a kid.
- Do it, boy!
- I mean it, lay off of him!
- lnsolent! How dare you!
- No!
Excellent. Well done.
- What did you do to him?
- Just a precaution
until The Source arrives
to kill him and steal his power.
- But--
- Your bounty's outside.
Leo, hurry. Go get him.
It's a force field.
I can't blast through it.
- I'll go get your sisters.
- Leo.
I know. Hurry.
It's a disaster there.
Ludlow has Tyler.
- It's a disaster down here too.
- Piper needs her sisters immediately.
Oh, I'll be right with you,
as soon as I finish this sleeve.
A child is in danger, Phoebe.
We need you now.
Phoebe? Who's Phoebe?
She can't go with you. She doesn't
even know who she is anymore.
I beg your pardon.
I know exactly who I am.
I am Mrs. Cole Turner.
This is all wrong. Ever since I put
that ring on your finger,
- you've been acting strange.
- You mean I've been acting normal?
Which is strange for you, you know.
I gotta be honest.
If this is what being married to you
is gonna be like,
- you can take that ring off now.
- I will not.
This ring is a symbol of our love.
That's it.
- It's the ring. We gotta get it off.
- Over my dead body.
That won't be necessary.
Grams' ring, please.
- No.
- Listen to this inscription.
"To gain another
is to lose yourself."
- Grams cursed the ring. Why?
- I don't know. Good question.
Look.
Are you feeling better?
I feel a little faint.
Can you hold it together?
We gotta go.
I don't know.
I'm still a little confused.
Well, nothing will remind you
of who you are
better than saving an innocent.
Now go to work.
I can't get in.
You gotta write a spell.
- Are you up to it?
- I think so.
Door unlock
No magic block
- That's it?
- Come here.
Door unlock
No magic block
Honey,
maybe we should go back and check
the Book of Shadows again.
I can't leave Tyler here.
It doesn't look like you
have much of a choice.
No!
Please. Please don't hurt me.
Stand back.
No.
Please.
What was that?
I think you just saw a mother
lift a car off her child.
All the pain...
...is over.
Soon...
...you will serve...
...The Source.
- I'm back.
- I paid you your bounty.
Yeah, that's not what I'm after.
- Power-of-three spell?
- I don't have one.
- What?
I did one.
The brittle winter
Gives way to flowers of spring
Ludlow is vanquished
What the hell was that?
It's a haiku. I couldn't do
the rhyming thing.
- Leo, he's frozen.
- I got him.
His hand is starting to warm up.
He's gonna make it.
Let's get back
to the gate and orb home.
Are you sure you wanna do this?
It's completely up to you.
Yeah, I'm sure.
It's an awful lot to give up.
No, it's not. Not for me.
All right, here you go.
It will bind your powers.
It won't strip them, but it'll bind them.
- Say, "Excuse me."
- Excuse me.
Ludlow's right, nobody
teaches manners anymore.
- Do you think it worked?
- Try it.
Look at something and get mad.
Just think of Ludlow.
I didn't hurt it.
I'm normal.
Whatever that means.
- Where are you going?
- To play video games.
Still wanna have a baby?
I'm just not ready
for an adolescent yet.
Well, Paige said
she found a pretty good family,
not too far from here.
I'm glad because
I want visitation rights.
Plus, you know,
I have to be in touch,
in case he ever wants
his powers back.
You think he will?
I don't know.
He's a surprising kid.
Yeah, like the piggyback orb.
I was so focused on how
I was gonna guide him.
Then he ended up guiding me.
- How?
- Well, you know how I was
upset with Grams
for binding our powers,
Ieaving us unprepared
for our magical future?
- You mentioned it once or twice.
- Well, now, I see
the wisdom in her decision.
She realised, someday, we were
gonna have to battle demons.
But she also realised that
children shouldn't live in fear.
They need to feel safe,
to explore and learn and grow.
I still think magic is a gift.
But Grams gave us
the greatest gift of all.
A normal childhood.
The gift of innocence.
Okay, okay, stop splashing. I'll say it.
Cole Turner
is the greatest lawyer
in all of the world.
The greatest unemployed lawyer
Although Mr. Yates
did respond
to my persuasive argument
and got the tenants' heat back on.
And he's not gonna press charges?
Nope. His lawyer thought the case
would raise more issues than it closed.
I am so proud of you.
Now, that was colourful.
Okay, now, I think I figured out
what Grams did to this ring here.
- Did you, now?
- I think to keep her from
making a seventh mistake,
she put a hex on the ring.
So that if she ever
got engaged again,
the ring would remind her
of what she hated about marriage.
The loss of identity, the subjugation
by a man, the focus on housework.
All those things that I was afraid of.
But Grams was from a different era.
That's not gonna happen to us.
Sitting and knitting
is not the woman you are,
just like sitting and typing
is not the man I am.
No, I can't picture you doing that.
But can you picture us together,
or are you so freaked out by marriage
- that you don't--?
- No.
I wanna marry you.
We just have to work extra hard
to make sure neither one of us
loses our identity.
And as for Grams
and her notion of marriage...
...we can watch that
go down the drain.