Is this the way you treat every driver
with a busted headlight?
No, just the ones without lD.
Now, I've convinced Lopez
not to cite you.
But no more driving
without a license.
- Am I free to go?
- Yeah.
- Finally.
- Finally?
- I mean, thanks.
You think I need this?
You see this assignment board?
It's full of cases, open cases
that I should be working on.
Instead, I'm cleaning up
after your mess.
I don't like it either.
I have to clean up
after the sisters' messes.
I'm trying to fit in as a human,
but I got no lD, no job--
Does anyone say,
"Thank you, Darryl."
--store without getting arrested.
- It just sucks!
- Sucks!
- You good?
- Yeah.
Me too.
Oh, my God, Cole. How's my car?
It's fine.
That was the first and the last time
you borrow my car.
Got it? Good. Let's go.
Being human was supposed
to make my life easier.
- It's getting worse by the minute.
- I know the feeling.
I swear, Phoebe
was closer to marrying me
- when I was still a demon.
- To be honest, Cole,
getting busted by the cops isn't
the best way to win her over.
Oh, Piper, gosh.
I'm sure Cole already feels like
a big enough loser. I know I would.
Oh, thanks a lot.
Oh, God.
It's about to explode.
Come on.
It's stuck.
- I got it.
- Paige!
Careful. Hurry,
before someone sees us.
What happened to you?
Paige!
Cole, why are you being so vague?
I only asked you
where you were going.
And I told you, I'm going to get a life.
See, now, that's the vague part
I'm talking about.
The last time you left like this,
you went and got a gun.
I'm not getting a gun.
Okay, then, please,
tell me what's wrong.
It's just-- I need action.
I kind of thought we were
doing okay in that department.
Not that kind of action, Phoebe.
I went from all-powerful demon
to mere mortal overnight.
You are not mere. Baby,
you are anything but mere.
Next to the Charmed Ones,
I'm a potted plant.
But last night, pulling that woman
out of that car felt so good.
That's because you're a good man.
Well, I won't last as one without
a reason to get up in the morning.
You have me.
I'm a reason.
That's all I have, Phoebe.
And I'm not even sure I have that.
Am I the world's
biggest bitch or what?
Too easy.
Cole vanquished his demon half.
He gave up everything
he has ever known for me.
And I can't muster up
a simple yes to marriage.
You're not the marrying type.
Or so you keep telling yourself.
But you think I am?
I think you're afraid.
Of what?
Cole's humanity.
He was actually a much safer
boyfriend when he was a demon.
Even though he could rip
your throat out with his teeth.
You wanna explain that to me?
Well, on some level
you knew that it couldn't last,
a demon and a witch.
But now that Cole is a human,
the safety net's gone,
and for the first time
in your relationship
the future lies in your hands.
Yeah.
Okay. I don't wanna analyze me
anymore. Let's try somebody else.
- How's Paige feeling this morning?
- No idea.
She flew out the door this morning
like nothing happened.
So we still don't know
why she froze up?
- Nope.
- That is so weird.
I mean, she can handle demons now,
but she can't handle a car wreck?
Yeah, it doesn't make any sense.
If you put your nose any deeper
into that coffee cup,
you're gonna need a snorkel.
What do you know?
Paige told me something
in confidence.
Okay, but it's kind of
a dangerous time for us.
If she freezes up again
at the wrong moment,
are you gonna be sorry
you didn't tell us?
- Paige's parents died in a car wreck.
- Oh, my God.
When did that happen?
About eight years ago
when she was in high school.
She never really dealt with it.
Of course not. How do you deal
with something like that?
And plus she was
a teenager and all alone.
So maybe we could
help her deal with it.
No, I'm not family.
I'm from social services.
I was just calling to see
how she was after the accident.
Thank God.
Okay, I'll just call back
and check in on her.
Thank you.
Hi. Got a minute?
No. I'm busy, guys.
We just wanna talk.
It's kind of important.
Yeah? So is my work. Maybe later.
Paige, it's about
what happened last night.
- Not right now.
- Paige, we're your sisters.
I said, not now!
Paige.
We know about your parents.
We're worried about you and we
want you to know that you're not alone.
And we're here for you.
Fine, but just not here, okay?
I'll just tell my boss I have to leave.
We'll talk at home.
- Got a minute?
- Whatever it is, no.
- You see this assignment board?
- Well, that's why I'm here.
If you've got such a heavy
caseload, let me help you.
- Oh, you wanna help?
- Yeah.
Great. You can help me by following
that little exit sign right there.
That's it. You wanna fight?
Because without the ability to throw
energy balls, I think I can take you.
Look, just relax, all right?
I need to get back in the game.
- What game?
- The good versus evil game.
It's all I know.
Oh, wow.
You wanna be a cop?
I worked for the DA's office.
I know the law.
I'm a former demon.
I know the streets.
- You wanna be a cop?
- I wanna help with your investigations.
- As a cop?
- On my own.
Of course, the DA investigators
are still after me,
but you could close that case,
clear my name, get my identity back.
- And I could--
- No! No, no.
Now you're talking crazy.
No. What's crazy is me sitting around
the manor all day with nothing to do.
All I got in my head,
all I could do with it going
to waste. Now, that is crazy!
Captain.
Mind if I get my office back?
No, sorry.
We'll talk about this later.
Excuse me.
So I wasn't the ideal
high school student, you know.
I skipped classes, partied
all night with my friends.
Pretty much anything
they wanted to do I was up for.
Sounds like somebody else I know.
What I mean to say
is that high school
is a time of searching and figuring out
who you are for everybody.
Yeah, but I was cruel.
Especially to my mom and my dad.
The day they died, I told them
they weren't my real parents.
Which is stupid because
it wasn't even how I felt.
I mean, just because I'm adopted
didn't mean they weren't
my real parents,
because they were.
Well, you were just feeling lost,
and you made a mistake.
I made so many mistakes,
you know, but I got through them.
And I changed, and so have you.
Not in time.
What do you mean?
It was family night.
Just something we did every week.
And my dad
Ieft the fire station early
to pick up my mom and l.
Your dad was a fireman?
Yeah.
And I started bitching
how I was too old for this
and how it was super lame.
And he just lost it.
He was so angry with me.
He didn't--
He didn't see the car that swerved...
...into our lane.
And...
...the next thing I know,
I'm on the pavement.
The car's on fire.
I still don't know why...
...I survived and they didn't.
But you can't blame
yourself for that.
Well...
...I feel guilty every single day.
I know it's hard,
but you gotta try and move forward.
How can I move forward, Piper?
I killed my parents.
What do we do?
How do we help her deal with
something that happened in the past?
Send her back to it.
Okay, wait. So I don't get it.
You wanna summon
the ghost of the past?
From where, the fiction shelf?
Dickens didn't make that stuff up.
He was visited by a malevolent spirit.
Doesn't malevolent mean bad?
Clyde's not the friendliest
ghost that I know,
but he is the only one who helps
the living visit their past.
Clyde? The malevolent
spirit's name is Clyde?
Yeah, he doesn't like it either.
Wait, we're using
bad magic to time travel.
Should I be worried
about any of those
- personal gain issues?
- Not at all.
You're only going back to learn
why your parents died. That's all.
Everyone ready?
Don't we need a summoning spell?
No, Clyde only ignores them.
There's only one way
to get Clyde down here.
Clyde!
Get your butt down here,
you fetid worm
from the bog of eternal stench!
You gotta make him mad.
Your mother was a chunky
substance from a djinn's cesspool!
And she smelled bad too.
Leo!
I was with a client!
1 969, Woodstock.
Hendrix was on-stage!
This better be good.
I need you to take Paige here
back to the day of her greatest pain.
A job?
Why didn't you just say so
in the first place?
Not a job. A favour.
- I don't do charity work.
- You owe me, Clyde.
Or do I need to remind you
of your client that I healed?
The one you returned from
the past on the edge of a cliff?
I believe there were
32 broken bones.
All right, all right. I remember.
Are you sure you wanna do this?
I only open the door to the past.
I don't guarantee no safe trip.
Obviously.
Yeah. I need to do this.
Fine. You guide her.
I won't be able to hear your call.
You guys will be on your own.
We'll be okay.
Just take care of Paige.
Just don't look down.
How's about you two?
Care for a little trip to the past?
See it all a second time.
My rates are steep but fair.
Can you take us back
to meet John Lennon?
- No.
- No, no. Right.
- We'll pass.
- Suit yourself.
If you ever need
my services, just yell.
We need to be here
when Paige gets back.
Yeah.
I'll cook dinner and we can
just hang out for a while.
I hope this plan works.
So do l.
Don't worry, Frankie,
I'll find you a body too.
Rough ride. You okay?
Yeah, I'm all right.
I'm all wrong.
Oh, my God. I saw Scrooged.
I'm supposed
to come back as a ghost,
not a ghost with braces?
You're meant to relive the experience,
not to observe it, Paige.
Yeah, but I just wanted
to come back
and sit on the sidelines
and make sarcastic comments
about my lack of style.
Just take a look around, Paige.
Hey, you're right.
I was cool even then.
Philip Lewiki gave this to me.
My first love.
- Can I call him?
- That's not why we're here.
- What do I do?
- Open the door.
Dad?
Are you ready for school?
You don't wanna miss your ride.
What's with all this?
Is that smoke I smell?
Are you smoking in here?
I don't know how much more
of this your mother and I can take.
- Wait. Wait, where are you going?
- To talk to my dad.
Did you see that look in his eyes?
I can't believe I hurt him.
Rules first. To find
what you came here for,
you need to follow the same path
you took eight years ago.
- What if I don't remember?
- I'll guide you.
You're the only one that can see me.
Just don't forget the goal.
You're here to learn what happened
the night your parents died.
I understand. Thank you, Leo.
Step aside.
Why? What did she do this time?
She was smoking again.
This time in her bedroom.
And when I went in,
she had the nerve to give me
this big hug like I wouldn't get mad.
She told me she quit smoking.
Oh, yeah, right. Just like
the time she quit drinking
and passes out at another
one of those parties.
I had to go pick her up
and bring her home.
School called yesterday. You know,
she's cutting her classes again.
She's not gonna get into college
she keeps this up.
Oh, well haven't you heard?
She's not going to college.
Well, we'll see about that.
I changed my mind, Leo.
I can't go in there.
They think I'm awful.
I was awful.
It's all right.
You can do it.
Just remember why you're here.
Mom.
Oh, my God.
I've missed you so much.
- What's got into you?
- What did I tell you?
You guys, I have
an announcement to make.
Starting now,
I'm turning my life around.
You're not borrowing the car.
- No, I mean it.
- Yeah,
Iike you meant it when you said
you were gonna stop cutting classes?
Mom, you understand me.
- You've gotta believe me.
- Oh, so now I'm Mom?
Last night we weren't even
your real parents.
No, you are!
I was just saying that...
...to hurt you.
- Did you feed the cat?
- Yeah.
You guys, I am not a screwup.
I promise I'll change.
I promise I will go to college and...
Oh, please stop.
- Please, we need to talk.
- Well, you are right about that.
And we are going to talk
about everything tonight at dinner.
Dinner?
The family dinner.
Paige, be careful.
Please, we really need
to talk before we drive.
Oh, Paige, that's your ride.
You have to follow the events
of the day, Paige. No exceptions.
I don't think I've ever
cooked for Paige before.
I hope she likes pork roast.
Just out of curiosity,
do you think that I am
a natural beauty or is this like
- one of those gym bodies?
- Oh, Phoebe, please,
Iike you haven't always
been beautiful.
Oh, that's good, because
I hate lifting heavy objects.
What is with the Blanche DuBois?
Phoebe, hi.
Oh, if you're not the most,
to say the least.
Did I miss something?
Yeah. Me.
I think this sister's night
is a good idea.
I mean, there's still so much
we don't know about Paige...
...yet.
Oh, boy.
Hey! What is the matter
with you two?
That is for Paige.
Sorry, ma'am, we're starving.
In so many ways.
Well, go to lunch.
Good idea.
Let's cut out, Lulu.
All right, enough with the pet names
and the accents in the kitchen
and could you come up
with something better than Lulu?
It sounds like a poodle.
Are you making fun of my girl?
My Frankie is so protective.
Frankie?
- And Lulu?
- Hi, we're ghosts.
And we've been waiting
for about 50 years to finish a job.
So now if you'll excuse us--
I can't believe I remember
the combination.
I used to live out of this locker.
My pager.
You had a pager in high school?
Get with it, Leo, it is the '90s.
Michelle Miglis.
Oh, I can't deal
with her drama right now.
Michelle.
Remember your whole
peppermint schnapps theory?
- No.
- You know,
how you can't tell it
from a breath mint?
You're wrong. I got so busted.
Oh, sorry.
You drank at high school?
What are you,
my guide or my judge?
- Excuse me?
- Nothing.
Whatever. I got grounded
for two weeks.
My mom pulled the whole
estrogen-fest thing.
- I swear to God, she's so damaged.
- She's not damaged.
You're right, she's beyond repair.
No, Michelle,
she's not beyond repair.
She's just trying to set boundaries,
and believe it or not, you need them.
So maybe you should just lay off.
I mean, God, how would you feel
if she died tomorrow?
Jeez, Paige, morbid much?
Wait for me.
Although the Magna Carta
was a document of great importance
to England and
the American colonies,
it originally granted concessions
to few but the baronial families.
The vast majority of England
would remain without an active voice
in government for another 700 years.
The seeds of the Magna Carta
were planted in 1 21 5
- when an assembly of barons...
- You don't want Donny. Trust me.
He winds up bagging groceries
for a living and driving a Camaro.
I love Camaros.
Would you girls please
hold it down back there.
I'm trying to teach.
But nobody's listening.
Yeah, I know.
That's why all you delinquents
are in this class.
The Magna Carta may have
remained legally inconsequential
had it not been resurrected...
This is ridiculous.
I have to get out of here.
I know the feeling.
No. You don't understand.
It's my last day with my parents.
Okay, what are you babbling about?
Excuse me, Mr. Martin?
May I have a bathroom pass, please?
Don't even think about it.
You have to follow the same path.
- What is the problem, Miss Matthews?
- I am tired of wasting my time here.
Well, I'm sorry if I'm boring you.
No, I'm not talking to you,
Mr. Martin.
- Who were you talking to?
- Yeah, really. Who?
- Paige.
- This is stupid. I just--
This is all just a bad memory.
I need to get out of here.
Miss Matthews,
you will sit down and be quiet
and wait for the bell to ring
just like everyone else!
Go, go, go.
Sit down, Miss Matthews!
- No, I won't.
- Paige, don't do this.
Go, go, go.
Going somewhere?
Busted, baby.
Where are we going to, man?
All right. All right.
Did you find anything?
Yeah, there was a Lulu
and Frankie in the database.
Some crazy young couple.
They robbed a series
of jewellery stores in the '50s.
They killed three people
before they were gunned down.
- I knew they were criminals.
- Who?
The ghosts that possessed
Phoebe and Cole.
Will you please not use
the G word around here.
Okay, fine. But we need to find
them before they finish their job.
What job?
They must have some sort
of unfinished business here on Earth,
and they either can't
or won't move on until it's done.
- You know this?
- Well, they didn't take me aside
and share their plan with me,
but it's how most ghosts work, Darryl.
You know, I told you
no creepy talk in the precinct.
Would you just keep down
the creepy talk.
Darryl, I'm sorry,
but what do you want me to say?
My sister was just possessed
by a supernaturally born killer
and my husband is in 1 994, and l
do not mean in the fashion sense.
He time-travelled back
with my other sister.
So the only one left
to help me is you.
Gee, thanks.
Darryl, you know what I mean.
What if they hurt somebody?
What if they kill somebody?
Then Phoebe and Cole
will take the fall.
Look,
the data says that Lulu and Frankie
were gunned down here
outside of a jewellery store.
Maybe that's the job
they were trying to finish.
One security guard.
Armed, right corner.
Got him.
Two female customers.
Can I help you?
We're looking for
a diamond engagement ring.
You came to the right place.
They're all so beautiful,
I don't know which one I like best.
You'd like the biggest one, baby.
Oh, there, that one.
That's the one I want, baby.
Excellent eye for quality.
It's a perfect solitaire.
I don't know.
The cut looks a little...
...off.
Oh, no. I can assure you.
You look like a regular guy.
Could I ask your opinion?
I just wanna know...
...can I borrow your gun?
You stupid?
Move over, baby.
We're back.
I gotta hand it to you, Lulu.
This body's a live wire.
The guy digs action, I can sense it.
This woman loves the feeling
of this diamond on her finger,
although, she'd never cop to it.
Let's split, baby.
Oh, no. Is he okay?
Looks like it was just his leg.
We're too late. They did it.
Hold on just a second.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
- What went down here?
- Weirdest thing, inspector.
They could've cleaned this out.
And all they take is a diamond ring.
That doesn't make any sense.
Looks like your ghosts
still have unfinished business.
Okay, we gotta find them
before they kill somebody.
But, first, is there
a surveillance tape?
Yeah, it's over there.
Oh, no.
Piper.
You froze the crime scene.
You cannot freeze a crime scene.
Well, I did.
Okay, we gotta protect
Phoebe and Cole.
So start wiping fingerprints.
Look. No! No, no.
Look, I am sick and tired of you
and your entire
dysfunctional family unit.
I will not falsify evidence. I'm a cop.
Okay, cop,
do I need to remind you that
you bailed Cole out of jail last night?
So?
So I was wondering what
you were gonna tell your captain
when he sees Cole
on their surveillance tape.
What are you waiting for?
Go get the damn tape.
- I cannot believe I am doing this.
- It's for a good cause.
Check his pockets.
All right, look, that's everything.
Okay.
Back in position.
- You good?
- Yeah.
Thank you, officer.
- lnspector?
- Yeah.
I thought you'd like to know,
a couple fitting the description
just hit a bridal store on 4th.
Stole a dress.
- A what?
- You know, a dress.
A wedding dress.
Go figure.
First, they're all over
each other at the manor,
then they steal a ring
and now a wedding dress?
Frankie and Lulu's
unfinished business isn't criminal.
It's matrimonial.
They wanna get married.
Do you people have any
normal weddings in your family?
Come on.
We don't have a lot of time.
You okay?
No, Leo, I'm nowhere near okay.
My time here is running out.
I haven't done anything.
- You've done enough.
- I haven't done anything.
I came back here to stop feeling guilty,
only now I feel guiltier than ever
because I know what
a damn disappointment I am.
Is that what you believe?
Hello, have you been watching
or eating popcorn?
My mom and my dad
think I'm a total failure.
I'm not.
I can't let them die thinking that.
In fact, I'm not gonna
let them die at all.
You can't change history, Paige,
only learn from it.
I am not letting them
get in that car tonight, Leo.
Yes, you will. And if you
break any more rules--
Screw the rules, Leo.
Oh, is that the teenager
talking or the adult?
The reason we journeyed to the past
was so you can learn from it.
You see where breaking
the rules has gotten you so far?
They're my parents.
I have to do something.
- I'm sorry to barge in like this.
- That incident in class today
was the last straw, Paige.
I'm suspending you from school.
- Just for that?
For cutting classes, starting fights,
smoking on campus,
possession of alcohol.
I swear I don't turn out like this.
Unfortunately, your actions
speak a lot louder than your words.
It looks bad, I know, but it doesn't
turn out this way. I promise.
I get a degree in social work,
I help others,
I even get into Berkeley
thanks to high test scores
and a powerful essay
on the death of my--
Well, let's just say a powerful essay.
Mom and Dad,
you've got to believe me.
How can we do that, Paige?
We've seen your act
too many times.
Please, just look at me
as though you actually saw me.
I'm not who you think I am.
How do you know what we think?
Because I can see it in your eyes.
Disappointment. And, okay, yeah,
I deserve it. I do.
All I can say for myself is that I'm...
...searching. And one day
I will find myself.
- Paige--
- Let me finish.
I'll find myself because of you two.
You've shaped who I am.
I am not a bad daughter.
You did not raise a bad daughter.
I'm good.
I just...
...wish you could see it.
Sweetheart,
of course we can see it.
What?
We know you're good.
We've always known.
But we also know that
you're lost and that scares us.
And there's nothing
in the world that we want more
than to help you find your way home.
We just don't know how.
I think you just did.
I will stand by my word.
You promise?
I promise.
You guys, can we--?
Can we just stay in tonight
and not go to the restaurant?
We still have to talk.
Yeah, we will, just at home.
Okay. Let's go home.
What?
Well, what's it gonna be tonight?
Should we have pizza?
I kind of miss Mom's cooking.
Like you don't have it every night?
You shouldn't do this, Paige.
You can't change the past.
I already did.
Did you say something, honey?
No, nothing.
You don't know what you're doing.
Yes, I do.
Watch out!
No!
Let go of me!
I have to save them!
It's no use. Paige, they're gone.
No. Why did you
bring me back here?
Why?
I thought I could stop the accident.
You couldn't stop the accident
because it was never your fault.
It was my fault.
They would've died anyway.
It was their destiny.
Just like it was your destiny
to be saved by magic.
That's how I got out of the car.
I orbed out.
That's right.
I could always orb?
Magic's always been inside of you.
It saved you because you were meant
to do great things with it,
and you have, and you will.
Don't you see?
This is what you came back here
to find, what caused the accident.
Why you survived it.
You need to forgive yourself.
It doesn't matter.
They'll never know...
...how much I loved them.
They'll never know what
good parents they were.
- How many more chapels we got?
- That was the last big one.
There's one more
in the neighbourhood.
What if they're not there?
Then we expand our search
to the entire city.
Do you take this woman
to be thy wedded wife,
to love, comfort and honour
in sickness or in health,
for sorrow or joy,
so long as you both shall live?
I sure do.
I'm gonna take good care
of her this time.
You okay, Frankie?
Yeah. It's just this guy's
all jumpy inside.
Almost like he wants
to get married as much as I do.
I know what you mean.
This one's, like, quivering inside of me.
What are you waiting for? Continue.
Right.
Do you, Lulu,
take this man to be
thy wedded husband--?
I object to this union!
I didn't call for any objections.
Yeah, well, I still object.
You two are not frozen.
Why are you not frozen?
Well, I know I'm not
the most technically minded,
but I would think it would
have something to do
with the fact that we're ghosts.
- I warned you, witch.
- Freeze!
Put the gun down slowly.
Damn!
Don't worry, baby. We'll try again.
Next time we'll get it right.
Cole.
- Leo!
- I had no choice.
I know.
Get him out of here
and call an ambulance.
- What happened?
- Look, I'm a cop. Come with me.
Oh, please, don't die.
Please, don't die. Leo!
Clyde!
Get your ass down here,
you son of a bitch!
Bring back Leo now.
Cole's been shot.
Step away, Phoebe.
Frankie! Lulu!
Where do you think you're going?
Well, it's an unfortunate slip-up.
I told you, it's a dangerous journey.
You never answered
the chaplain's question.
I never answered your question.
Ask me again.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
I will.
Thank you, guys.
Just no weddings
till we vanquish The Source.
- Apple cider?
- Apple cider, yes.
Paige,
you haven't told us,
and we've been dying to know.
What happened in your past?
Well, I found out I was
not responsible for the accident.
Of course you weren't.
Then what's the matter?
I just--
It makes me sad
that my parents won't see us
or what I've become.
Actually, that's not quite true.
Leo?
Let's just say that I owe Clyde now.
We know who you are, honey.
Who you've become.
We've been with you
every step of the way
and we're so proud of you,
sweetheart.