We're not a threat.
We're salvation.
The world
will have to deal with us.
Previously on the 4400...
this is where
i give you the speech
about how you're
my best field scientist
and tom is my best
lead investigator,
and how together,
you're going to make
a good team.
Let me see
if i've got this straight...
you two met,
fell in love,
and spent eight years together
in some kind
of alternate reality.
Yeah.
What time is the flight?
Uh, noon.
Say goodbye to mom for me.
They arrested a suspect
40 minutes ago.
Claim he's our guy.
[Jarvis]: Roy keith marsden.
Forget about the flight.
Bring kyle home.
They just arrested a suspect
in the collier killing.
It's going to feel
a little weird,
but when we're done,
you'll be able
to see again.
When does it start?
When do i see again?
Just give me one moment, okay?
Kevin's a genius, you know.
You're saying that burkhoff
is the father
of the 4400 technology.
I can think again, too.
You've got
a real fever,
young lady.
I worked at the c.d.c.
For seven years,
and i never saw
anything like it.
I was changing her.
She has these marks on her skin.
Marks? Bruises?
No. Like irritations.
Like someone had her
hooked up to something.
What did i just tell you?
[Jarvis]: You're in charge
until i'm released.
Pool whatever manpower
is still up walking.
Start picking up the pieces.
I'll handle it.
Don't worry about it.
[Tom]:
Okay, seriously,
my back is about
to call it a day.
Just come on...
you're not helping.
Where's this going?
Right there.
Please say
that was the last box.
That's it.
We're officially
living in sin.
Oh, really.
Well, i prefer to call it
"resuming
our eight-year marriage."
Call it whatever you want.
Just don't kiss
in front of me again, okay?
That's disgusting.
Oh, your father thinks
this is so romantic,
but what
he doesn't know
is the reason
i'm moving in
is to take down
his tacky golf stuff.
[Tom]: What?
And replace it
with what?
Oh, oh,
paint splatters?
Maybe a picture
of a triangle
kids!
It's art.
Work out
these decorating issues
amongst yourselves,
but i'm dead serious
about this kissing rule, okay?
It's non-negotiable.
Oh, kyle,
my allergies are
bothering me again.
Could you write me
another prescription
before you go?
Uh, alana...
kyle's only a doctor
in the world you created for me,
remember?
I'm sorry.
I had a brain freeze.
Right.
Trying to decipher
my handwriting?
I was just on the verge
of giving up, actually.
Good.
Bad penmanship
is the best way
for a doctor to keep
his mystique.
There's a page missing
in there.
It goes from page four
to page six.
Sorry.
I'm breaking in a new nurse.
So listen, i think
we finally know
what's wrong
with your daughter.
Maia's suffering
from a type of pneumonia
called pneumocystis jiroveci.
It's "p.j.p."
For short.
I've never heard of it.
It's rare,
but we can treat it...
well, thank god.
But this kind
of pneumonia
could be a symptom
for something more serious.
We've tested her
for every virus...
all negative.
So where is it coming from?
We don't know,
but we're running more tests.
We'll figure it out.
It's not that big
of a deal.
You know, i've just...
i've been working
real hard lately.
I think i got the flu
or something.
Everybody gets that,
right?
Sure. It's just...
shawn...
you can't heal.
For now.
I think you should
get it checked out.
If i can't kick it
in a day or two, i will,
but, uh...
until then,
can you reschedule
all my foundation
appointments?
Tell them that it's temporary.
Make sure they know that.
Lily...
don't tell anyone
i can't heal.
Sure.
Thank you.
Lily...
i mean it. Nobody.
Oh, god.
Ah...
[Speaking german]
[Tom]: How many
are sick?
300... that we know of.
Medical says
more calls keep coming in.
So, what is it?
Well, it's some kind
of immune system disorder,
and it's leaving the 4400
vulnerable
to all kinds of diseases.
His plane landed
at seatac
on schedule.
Chopper should be here
any minute.
What's that?
They told me
he likes green tea.
Is it contagious?
We don't know.
Were they infected
while they were gone?
Maybe they brought this
back with them.
Well, maybe.
We just don't know.
The situation is fluid,
but here's a summary
of what we know so far.
Uh, sir?
They told me
you'd want this.
The numbers just keep
getting bigger.
So we're recovering
from an attack
on this building...
the division commander's
still in the hospital...
what are we
supposed to do?
We take to the field.
Ryland?
Where did he
come from?
We're going to have
every 4400 in this jurisdiction
tested
for this sickness
by day's end.
Dennis, is it good to see you.
Tom.
Diana.
What brings you
to seattle, ryland?
I'm assuming temporary command
of this division.
My orders are to do something
about the spread
of this epidemic.
I'm going to figure out a way
to do just that.
* so long ago, another life *
* i can feel your heart beat *
* it's not a dream
remember us *
* i can see it in your eyes *
* we'll find our place in time *
* our place in time
beyond the sun *
* we'll find our place in time *
* our place in time
to call our own *
You might want
to move that,
unless you want people
calling you "nina."
How's jarvis doing?
They set her collarbone.
Doctors said
she'll be back in two weeks.
My guess?
She makes it in one.
Yeah.
So how's d.c.?
Oh, it's a lot of networking.
Lots of dinner parties.
Patty loves it.
And you?
The pacific northwest
is the flashpoint.
I kind of feel
like i was promoted
out of the game.
A lot of guys here
would trade places with you.
I wouldn't blame them.
A woman releases plague
into the air?
A terrorist attack
on the building?
Some people i work for
think you're
in the middle of a war.
I'm sure
it looks that way on paper.
Don't get defensive.
I'm still preaching the gospel
of highland beach.
I still believe
the 4400 came back here
to change things for the better.
Yeah, and the people
you work for?
Don't worry
about them.
One day, this'll be over,
we'll go out for a beer,
we'll kick back,
we'll trade war stories.
Yeah.
[Ruth]: She was a little cranky
this morning.
I think
she's cutting another tooth.
They're
coming in fast, huh?
She's that age.
Bye, bye, sweetie.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Thank you, ruth.
Lily, what are you doing?
I thought we agreed
nobody was doing
science experiments on our baby.
Just making sure.
Shawn, we need to rearrange
your healing schedule.
There's something going on,
some sort of illness
spreading among the 4400.
I know all about it.
You.
Did you do this?
No, no. It wasn't me.
Then what are you doing here?
I read about this place
in the paper.
I just... i was curious.
Yeah?
Well, go be curious
somewhere else,
because people
still live here, okay?
Do you need some help?
What, are you
a mechanic now?
I can change a tire.
There's probably a jack
in the trunk, right?
Yeah.
I'm sorry i snapped at you.
I just... i'm in a hurry, and...
my boyfriend's little brother
is in the principal's office
again,
and he's... not here...
again.
I guess he's in
a lot of trouble, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, you could say that.
Well, i mean,
it's none of my business.
I can just change the tire
and go.
Please.
Hi there.
Welcome to the center.
Are you here to take the tour?
This is wrong.
It's all wrong.
Excuse me?
This is
the collier museum.
Where are
all the paintings?
Thomas.
Hey, sweetie.
What's going on?
I have a board of directors
meeting,
and they won't let me
go upstairs.
Yeah, yeah.
They called me.
They said you were
a little mixed up.
Alana...
this isn't
the collier museum.
It's...
it's the 4400 center.
What are you
talking about?
I come here
all the time.
Look at me. Look...
alana...
the place
you're thinking of,
it's somewhere else.
No. No!
Why are you
confusing me?
Just calm down!
No!
It's okay.
It's all right.
[Ryland]:
The infection rate is 18%.
One in five of them
are already sick?
One in five today.
Tomorrow...
the national
institute of health
is worried that this illness,
whatever it is,
can mutate
and cross over
into the general
population.
Would it even
have to mutate?
There's
no guarantee
that this is going to
stay exclusive to 4400s
and meanwhile,
we've got two dozen sick ones
right downstairs.
They're not going to
be there long.
Why?
What are we doing with them?
D.c. Wants to put all the 4400
back in quarantine
and keep them there
for the rest
of the crisis.
I know it's a big move, people,
but it's the best one we've got
at the moment.
Can we do that?
According to emergency
quarantine order 74,
we can.
But wait,
you're just talking
about the sick ones here,
right?
No. All of them.
Every 4400
in the country
is subject to this order.
Okay,
but that's only half of them.
This thing's worldwide, right?
England and france
are passing similar legislation.
We expect
other countries to follow.
But why are you forcing them all
to come in?
Because the disease seems to be
showing up at random.
Until we understand
how it's transmitted,
we have to assume
that every 4400
is a potential vector.
How much time
are we giving them?
We'll make
the announcement
in the morning.
They'll have 12 hours
to get to a local
ntac branch,
then they'll be
transferred
to camp dekker
and the quarantine facility.
What if they don't report?
Then it'll be our job
to bring them in.
You're not hearing me...
it's temporary.
Can you be sure?
You already told me
people in washington
think we're
fighting a war.
Washington is
full of opinions.
The town runs on them.
The 4400
aren't just names
in some report...
and they're definitely
not enemy combatants.
You're talking
about my daughter,
tom's nephew...
the woman i love.
I was going to tell you
over that beer.
[Diana]: Now,
what assurances
can you give us
that these people
aren't just being
thrown down some hole
permanently?
You have my assurance,
and that should be
enough.
I was the one who pushed
to let them out
in the first place,
you remember?
We're not trying
to second-guess you, dennis,
but people we love are sick.
I get it,
but getting them all
together in one place
is going to make it
a lot easier
to find out
what the hell this is.
When it's over,
everybody goes home.
We know you'll
fight the good fight, dennis.
I just hope you can win.
Mommy?
You're awake.
How are you, baby?
I'm tired of being sick.
When can i go home?
Why don't you tell me?
I was kind of hoping
you'd had a vision,
about how all this
will be over soon.
They're not coming
anymore.
I'm not seeing things.
My favorite patient
is awake.
More awake than you look.
Mm.
Open wide.
I do my best work
when i eliminate sleep
altogether.
Well, if you need someone
to splash cold water
on your face,
you just let me know.
Thanks.
Do you mind?
I noticed that missing page
made its way back in.
Oh. Yeah.
I told you it'd be back.
What are those two lines
blacked out for?
Well, looks like
we duplicated a test.
They cross it out
so we don't read
the same results twice.
Okay, let's see
how that rash is doing.
[Lily]: I'm fine, brian.
Tell heidi not to worry.
Richard's fine.
Isabelle's fine.
Well, the news
is making it sound
like everybody's sick.
People are terrified,
and if normal people
start getting sick...
"normal people"?
Okay, that
came out wrong,
but you know
what i mean.
And listen, lily,
heidi's not the only one
that's worried about you.
I am, too.
A year and a half ago,
you welcomed me home
with a restraining order.
I know.
I panicked when you got back.
Don't think i haven't lost sleep
over what i did.
I just want you
to know now
that i'm there for you.
You, richard, isabelle.
You need anything...
just call.
"Quarantine."
That's an evocative word
these days.
Conjures up images
of secret prisons and...
what's the euphemism
you're using now?
"Coercion tactics"?
[Tom]: Let me
ask you something...
you have some doctors
on staff here, right?
Yes.
They having any luck
getting to the bottom
of this thing?
Not yet.
Then get off
your soapbox.
You want an image
to hold on to?
Try this one...
4400s dying in droves.
I think what my partner
means to say
is that our
two organizations
need each other.
We should cooperate.
And how exactly
do we do that?
We want you to issue
a public statement.
If the center
counsels the 4400s
to go along
with this order,
things will go
much more smoothly.
And if we don't?
Why are we talking
to you, anyway?
Where's shawn?
Is he all right?
Mr. Farrell
is handling urgent business.
This situation requires
his full attention.
Look, i'll have to
run it by him,
but i don't see a problem
advising any ill 4400s
to seek medical care
from ntac.
Well, that's a start.
What about the ones
who aren't
showing symptoms?
That issue's going to require
a little more thought.
Great.
You have 12 hours.
[Teenage boy]:
What's the point
of painting it over,
anyway?
They're just gonna
do it again.
We don't know that.
Look, sam,
kyle has been nice enough
to come over here
and help us out,
so the least that you can do
is pitch in.
Oh, yes, very good...
picasso.
I'm going to make sandwiches.
Okay, seriously,
what's your story?
Why are you helping us,
kyle whoever-you-are?
My last name's bingham...
and i don't know.
I was just walking by here
yesterday.
Alison looked
like she could use a hand...
yeah, well,
if you were thinking
about hooking up with her,
forget it.
Alison's gonna
marry my brother
as soon as he gets out of jail.
I know. I know.
She told me.
You should listen to her.
Roy didn't kill
this collier guy.
I believe you.
Yeah?
Well, you're the only one.
You and me.
When he does get out,
i don't think
you want him coming home
and seeing "murderer"
written all over his door,
do you?
Richard...
you ready for a promotion?
Me?
A promotion to what?
I'm trying here, man.
I want to lead us all
through this,
but i can't do that right now.
Thank you.
I know i'm a 4400,
but after that,
my qualifications
are a little thin.
They didn't even give me
an ability.
To be honest with you,
i'm not sure how long
lily and i were planning
on staying here.
So it's not a perfect fit,
but you're articulate,
and a war hero,
and you have
the gravitas
of a leader.
I think
it's a good idea.
I haven't given an order
since 1951.
I was in high school
a year and a half ago.
I managed.
So will you.
But it's only temporary, right?
As soon as you get better,
i can go right back
to being camera-shy.
Yeah.
Temporary.
What are you going to do?
What i have to.
Has everyone frightened,
and that's understandable.
But no one's more frightened
than we are.
And that's because,
in spite of all the rumors
that you hear flying around,
only 4400s
are getting sick,
and now the government
wants us to head
into quarantine.
They say cooperation
is essential.
Well, here's
the best we can do...
if you're sick,
the responsible thing
is to report to ntac.
Our best wishes
and prayers
go with you.
But if you're well,
if you're showing no symptoms,
we ask you to consider this...
walking into quarantine
is an easy step,
but walking out...
that might be
considerably more difficult.
Thank you.
Don't they get it?
We're trying
to help these people.
All they hear is
"quarantine," dennis.
You can't blame them
for being scared.
Maybe if we give them
another day,
half a day, even.
Does it look to you
like they haven't
made up their minds?
We tried
being reasonable.
In 10 hours,
we start rounding them up.
Hi.
Hey.
I know who you are.
You're the one
who fixes people.
Yeah. Shawn.
How come you're in here?
Why don't you just
make yourself better?
I wish i could.
They're broken.
Kind of like
the rest of me.
I used to see things.
Stuff that was
gonna happen.
That's gone now too.
It's funny, huh?
When i found out
i was different,
all i wanted to do
was be normal again.
Me too.
But you
get used to it.
Now that it's gone,
i feel like i'm missing an arm.
It'll come back.
Once we get better.
Any idea when that's gonna be?
Not exactly,
but my mom told me
everything's gonna be fine,
and i believe what she says.
That must be a nice feeling.
Don't you have someone
to believe in?
I used to...
but now i guess
i'm just going to have to
believe in you.
You're the one
i attacked
at the hospital.
We didn't think
you'd remember us.
I remember.
I was...
very sick back then.
I'm better now.
Diana, you wanted
to see me?
Kevin burkhoff.
I've been doing
neurological research
on the 4400.
Oh, i've heard of you.
Everybody here has.
Here.
There's some very
interesting data
on the blood work
i've been doing.
Have a look.
See if it helps you figure out
what's going on
with this disease.
Well, thank you.
I'll comb
through this.
Good,
and i can expect
to see your work... when?
I showed you mine.
You show me yours.
That is the way
it works,
isn't it?
Usually,
but the research we do here
is classified.
[Diana]: Max...
max, if ever
there was a time
to bend the rules
a little,
i think
it might be now.
Well, it's not
a wink-and-a-nudge situation.
I give over
classified documents,
i go to jail.
Yeah, and if you don't,
people might die.
Are you implying we're not doing
everything we can?
We've got dozens
of doctors
working
around the clock
to try to solve this thing.
Now, i will look over
everything that you've given me.
If i find anything
that can help you,
i'll give you a call.
That's the best i can do.
I am so sorry...
i'm not interested
in apologies.
I want to see
that information.
Or is ntac not interested
in curing these people?
I know you guys
are kind of cavalier
about putting your own careers
on the line,
but do me a favor...
stop asking me
to join in the fun, okay?
I like what i do here.
They're medical records, marco.
Not national secrets.
Wrong.
They're medical records
and national secrets.
That is why they keep them
in a database
you need six passwords
to get into,
and that's why sport-o
wouldn't give them to you.
Let's just leave max
out of this.
He's under a lot of pressure.
And he wants
to keep his job.
I don't blame him.
You know, i just
opened a 401(k).
Yeah, pretty sure
the government stops
matching donations
once you commit treason.
The government
just turned down
an offer of help
from kevin burkhoff.
Remember him?
Yeah, the future
built a giant tower
to wake him up.
I guess they think he matters.
If anyone in washington
read my report,
they know
he matters, too.
You know, it's weird.
Hundreds of people are sick.
You'd think they'd want
any help they could get.
Well, they're going to
get his help.
Yeah, whether they want it
or not.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
Is isabelle ready
to go for her walk?
Okay, let's go have some fun.
How long has she
been in there?
I don't know.
Five minutes.
I came and got you
as soon as i saw.
What are they
doing to her in there?
Step back.
[Matthew]: Would you
excuse us, please?
How long has this been going on?
Richard, your daughter
has never been
in any kind of danger.
He asked you a question.
Jordan was going to
initiate these tests
as soon as he convinced you
to come back into the fold...
what tests?
What have you been doing to her?
All we're doing
is what you should have done
a long time ago...
trying to figure out who,
or what, isabelle is.
She's our daughter.
That's all you
or anyone else
your daughter
is the rosetta stone
for understanding
what happened to the 4400,
yet you both cling
to the illusion
that she's going to go
to preschool,
first communion, the prom...
she's not communal property.
We're her parents. We decide.
Parents?
You are the stewards
of the future,
and forgive me for saying so,
but you're doing
a piss-poor job of it.
We have given up
everything we have
for that child,
any chance we had
of living a normal life,
to protect her
from people like you.
Look, richard, this is no time
for this conversation.
In two hours,
the government is
coming through the front door.
Yeah, well,
you won't use my daughter
as some kind of weapon
against them.
That was never my intention.
You'll never have the chance.
We're leaving right now.
That's your choice,
but if you do,
if we splinter now,
they will round up the 4400
one by one,
Hey.
Hey, thomas.
They said
you've been asking for me.
Shouldn't you be in bed?
They'll take me back
soon enough.
I wanted to see you.
How do you feel, baby?
They can't get the fever down,
but...
the worst part is my head.
Everything's so mixed up.
This illness,
it affects people's abilities.
Maia can't see things, and...
and shawn, shawn can't heal,
and for you, honey,
i think the boundaries
between this world
and the one you created
are breaking down.
It's so confusing.
I don't know
what's real anymore.
I know it's scary.
You just have to hang on.
They'll get this fixed.
What if they're too late?
What if they can
make my body right,
but not my mind?
I don't want to live like that,
thomas.
You're not
going to have to.
You're going to get better.
You have to believe that, alana.
Thomas...
yeah?
I love you so much.
I wanted us to get married
for real,
in this world.
That's all i wanted to tell you,
before...
before my mind goes...
because...
i don't know
if it will be good again.
So you're sure i can't get you
a beer or something?
No, no,
that's okay.
I don't drink.
Okay.
You know, this isn't
really necessary.
I just did
a couple of chores.
Maybe it's not a big deal
to you,
but i just haven't seen
a friendly face
in a while,
not since... roy went away.
no offense, but, um...
the papers make him sound
like the second coming
of lee harvey oswald.
Yeah.
Well, i wouldn't exactly call it
"fair and balanced coverage."
But he did have
some monstrous gun collection,
right?
Look, i'm not saying
that he was a candidate
for higher office,
and...
he sure as hell
wasn't the world's
greatest boyfriend.
But taking out
two ntac agents
and shooting jordan collier?
Come on.
Yeah.
Eat up.
Sam!
Sam, come on!
We're starting.
I'll be right there.
Hey.
Okay.
Are you marco?
Thanks.
Don't thank me.
Hire me.
I'm gonna need a job.
Where have you been?
Talking to matthew.
Lily...
he's got an idea
on how to handle
this roundup.
I think it might work.
I'm sure
he's full of clever ideas.
We will deal with
what matthew did,
but not now.
The government is about
to declare martial law
we don't have time to squabble.
All i want to hear
is that you're done
with this place for good.
It's not that simple.
We can't just go off
and hide in the woods somewhere.
It's not going to work
this time.
The center betrayed us.
They betrayed our daughter.
And they learned
about her,
more than we did
in almost a year.
Lily, stop.
Did you know
isabelle has connections
between the right and left
hemispheres of her brain
that have never been
seen before?
Even if that's true, richard...
it's not that they studied her.
It's how they did it.
Do you trust
the government?
Because
if we go into quarantine,
isabelle will end up
right here,
or with them,
and if they find out
what she can do...
we'll lose her forever.
[Ryland]: That's it.
That's the deadline.
Where do we start?
I want everybody
to holster their pistols.
My goal is to do this quietly,
peacefully,
and without incident.
What if they want
an incident?
Then we'll give them one.
Is everybody ready?
Affirmative, sir.
We're in position.
Let's go.
Moving in now.
Copy that.
They're on the move.
They're
spreading out
and letting us
through.
Welcome to the center.
Did you come for the tour?
You know damn well
why we're here.
Out hunting, i'd guess.
Well, i'm afraid
you've come to the wrong place.
You are welcome to look around,
????????
?????
I have no idea
where they went.
You had 1204400s
taking shelter at your center.
That sounds about right.
I don't have an exact figure.
You just came
downstairs,
and they were gone?
Until 7:00 this evening,
they were free citizens.
I had no reason
to track
their movements,
and since i've broken no laws,
unless you want to talk about
lifting this quarantine order,
we have nothing left to discuss.
We'll talk again.
I suspect your job
is going to get rather ugly
from here on out,
kicking in doors
and such.
If i worked at ntac,
i might spend a little less time
trying to find missing 4400s,
and a little more
trying to cure the ones i had.
So tell me,
have we got a list
yeah.
All the sick ones we know of
are in.
As for the rest,
we had about 75% compliance.
Nationwide,
there's about 5204400s
unaccounted for.
Well, that's not a few holdouts.
That's an insurgency.
So this is it, huh?
Us against them.
You know, it feels
kind of like the war
jordan collier always predicted.
Predicted or provoked?
We declared martial law on them.
We had no option.
I'm going to pursue
a policy of non-aggression
as long as i can,
but if it comes down
to a choice
between the safety
of the american people
and the welfare
of the 4400,
tom...
that's no choice at all.
[Richard]: Collier left behind
37 safe houses
throughout the country.
We liquidated the center's
emergency slush fund
should last for awhile.
Any 4400
who contacts the center
for help
will be given
an email address.
If we're satisfied
they're legitimate,
they'll be told
where to go.
Our goal is to get
every 4400 who wants shelter
to safety.
And then what?
Matthew will try
to continue
to end this peacefully,
but if we have to
protect our own...
we'll be ready.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Lily...
you make a good speech,
but this isn't korea,
and those
aren't soldiers,
and your daughter
could get caught
in the crossfire.
You don't think
i'm worried about her?
And you too?
Lily, i'm not looking
for a fight,
but right now,
we don't have another option.
Hey. Sam said he liked comics...
you son of a bitch!
You lied to me.
What?
Wait a minute.
It wasn't like that.
Oh, really,
"kyle bingham"?
Your last name
is baldwin,
and your dad works
for ntac.
So, what are you?
His little spy? Huh?
Did you think you were going to
sleep with me?
I was going to tell you
all about roy?
You go and you tell your daddy
that he didn't kill anybody.
I know that.
I was just trying to help you.
Why?
You come off like you're
this really great guy,
and all you were trying to do
was use me.
You're a lying prick.
Okay.
This thing that's
killing them,
it's not a disease.
It's a side-effect.
Dr. Burkhoff,
just calm down.
What are you
talking about?
A side-effect of what?
I don't know exactly,
but i do know this...
there's a synthetic substance
present in the blood
of every 4400,
all the ones i tested,
every medical report
you gave me,
sick ones, well ones,
doesn't matter.
They all have it.
They even gave it a name.
They call it
"promicin inhibitor."
Promicin?
What's promicin?
I have no idea,
and i don't know why anyone
would want to inhibit it,
either.
But whatever it is,
it's gathering
in their lymph nodes,
compromising
their immune systems...
it's what's making them sick.
But ntac's been
studying the 4400
ever since
they got back.
They should have
known about this.
They do know.
It's all in here. They know.
So why haven't they
told anyone?
That's a very good question.
When you find out,
why don't you tell me?
[Car idling]
Are you sure
you want to do this?
Just get me and isabelle
someplace safe.
"P.i. Dosage"...
it's on memos,
in every 4400 medical report.
It's on the fifth page
of every report.
That's what hudson
had crossed out
when i went to see maia.
"P.i."
"Promicin inhibitor."
Alana was getting it too,
and shawn.
Everyone was getting it.
Every time
they came to ntac medical.
Every checkup.
We did it to them, tom.
We made them sick.