PREVIOUSLY ON THE 4400--
WE'RE NOT SURE WHAT'S JUST HAPPENED.
THE LIGHT IS GONE,AND THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE
HAVE JUST SUDDENLY APPEARED.
-WE'RE LETTING THEM GO.
-WE'RE LETTING THEM GO?
YOU DON'T HAVE A LEGAL RIGHTTO HOLD THEM.
YOU'RE PREGNANT?
I WASN'T PREGNANT WHEN I WAS ABDUCTED,
BUT I WAS WHEN I GOT BACK.
WHAT'S ALL THIS?
WHAT'S IT LOOK LIKE?
THAT BABY COULD BE THE KEY TO THE FUTURE,
AND IT HAS TO BE PROTECTED,AND I CAN DO THAT.
GO AHEAD. RUN!
THAT BABY BELONGS WITH ME.
THIS IS  YOUR NEW HOUSE?
IT'S YOURS TOO.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FORWARD TO THIS MOMENT FOR TOO LONG.
DIANA SKOURIS,
YOUR ADOPTION OF MAIA RUTLEDGE
IS HEREBY COMPLETE,LEGAL,AND BINDING.
HER VISIONS STOPPEDABOUT FOUR MONTHS AGO.
WE'RE NOT SURE WHY.
MRS. USHER NEXT DOOR IS GETTING A KITTEN.
MOMMY'S BOSSES WILL BE PUNISHED FOR BETRAYING US.
IT WASN'T ME!
THAT CREATURE MADE ME    PULL THE TRIGGER!
GETTING DRESSED FROM THE TOP DOWN NOW?
THAT THE WAY THEY DO IT ON THE MARINERS?
MARINERS?
GARY'S GOT HIS EYES  ON THE SOX.
NO,YOU MEAN THE SOX GOT THEIR EYES ON HIM.
HOW'S IT FEEL,ALL THOSE SCOUTS IN THE STANDS?
YOU BEND OVER TO TIE A SHOELACE,THEY MAKE A NOTE.
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE RESPECT,HUH?
YOU'RE IN THE PRESENCE OF THE NEW JACKIE ROBINSON.
FIRST 4400 TO MAKE THE BIG LEAGUES.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE SCOUTS,MAN.
I'LL FLOAT YOU SOME RIGHT DOWN THE MIDDLE.
YOU JUST GET INTO YOUR RHYTHM,
FORGET THEY'RE EVEN OUT THERE,ALL RIGHT?
CAN'T BLAME HIM.
SIX SCOUTS.
I'D BE AFRAIDI WAS GOING TO CHOKE.
I'M NOT GONNA CHOKE.
BARNES CAN'T SERVE THEM  ANY BETTER THAN THAT.
JUST... JUST    GIVE ME A SECOND.
HE'S THROWING HIM A BEACH BALL.
HE'S SCARED,MAN.
WHAT WAS WRONG WITH THAT?
WHAT A LOSER.
FOLLOW THROUGH.FOLLOW THROUGH.
THIS TIME TRY TAKING THE BAT OFF YOUR SHOULDER.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY KISSING MY ASS?
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM,GARY?
NAVARRO!GET YOUR HEAD IN THE GAME. FOCUS.
I WANT TO SEE SOME CONTACT.
THE MAJORS?
KID DOESN'T LOOK LIKE HE'S
READY FOR ROOKIE BALL.
JUST SHUT UP!
WILL ALL OF YOU  JUST SHUT
THE HELL UP AND LET ME CONCENTRATE?
WHOA,GARY--
TAKE IT DOWN A NOTCH.
YEAH,YOU'RE A FLAKE,AREN'T YOU?
GO AHEAD. TAKE A SWING AT ME.
I'LL PLANT YOU WHERE YOU STAND.
I AM NOT GOING TO HIT YOU!
WHO SAID ANYTHING   ABOUT HITTING,MAN?
THAT'S IT,NAVARRO.    YOU'RE DONE FOR THE DAY.
I WANT TO SEE YOU IN MY OFFICE AFTER PRACTICE.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH ME.
THERE IS NOTHING WRONG WITH ME.
-KEEP WALKING,MISTER.
-THERE IS NOTHING WRONG WITH ME!
KEEP WALKING,MISTER. NOW.
GARY,MAN,TAKE IT EASY.
DON'T TOUCH ME!
THIS KID ISN'T READY,MAN.
THIS WAS A BIG WASTE OF TIME.
READY FOR THE BIGS,MY ASS.
WHAT WAS WRONG WITH THAT?
YOU SHUT UP.
SHUT UP!
YOU SHUT UP!
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH ME!
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG    WITH ME!
WELL,IT BEATS THAT DITCH IN THE WOODS.
NOT BY MUCH.
IT'S JUST   A DAY OR TWO.
LET ISABELLE  GET RESTED UP,
THEN WE'LL PUSH ON    THE REST OF THE WAY.
WE GOT ENOUGH TO MAKE IT TO WHITE BIRD?
NEW CAR...
TRIP TO THE EMERGENCY ROOM...
IT'S GOING    TO BE CLOSE.
ALL THIS RUNNING AND HIDING,
SOMETIMES I FORGET WE HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING WRONG.
THREE DEAD MEN IN THE WOODS MIGHT DISAGREE.
DO YOU WANT TO SHOWER FIRST,OR SHOULD I?
YOU GO AHEAD.
GIVE ISABELLE HER BOTTLE,OKAY?
THAT WAS YOU,WASN'T IT?
WHO STOPPED THOSE MEN    IN THE WOODS?
DADDY SURE WOULD LIKE TO KNOW.
BUT YOU'RE NOT GOING TO TELL ME,ARE YOU?
WHAT'S FUNNY?
MARMADUKE.
CAN WE GET A DOG?
OH,SMOOTH,HOW YOU SLID THAT IN THERE.
NO.
SKOURIS.
APRIL.
NO,NO,NO,NO.
I'M GLAD TO HEAR FROM YOU.    YOU'RE MY SISTER.
IT'S JUST... IT'S BEEN A WHILE,THAT'S ALL.
NO,WE'RE HERE,JUST HAVING BREAKFAST.
HANG ON A SEC.
MRS. LENNOX MUST'VE FORGOTTEN HER KEY.
I'LL GET IT.
NO,NO. NO,I'LL GET IT.  YOU JUST KEEP EATING.
I JUST HAVE TO LET MAIA'S TEACHER IN.
COMING!
ONE MORE SEC.
SURPRISED?
APRIL--
HOW'S IT GOING,SIBLING?
GOOD.
YOU LOOK GOOD.
YEAH,YOU TOO.
THANKS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
THE PACIFIC NORTHWEST    BODY ART EXPO.
I HAVE A BOOTH.
DON'T TELL ME YOU HAVEN'T    GOTTEN YOUR TICKETS YET.
UH,NO.
HELLO.
OH,MY GOD.
YOU MUST BE MAIA.
APRIL SKOURIS,BLACK SHEEP OF THE FAMILY.
DI,YOU ARE SO LUCKY.
LOOK AT THIS FABULOUS KID YOU GOT.
AND NO LABOR,NO STRETCH MARKS,NO DIAPERS...
NO CRAPPY HUSBAND.
OH,WAIT,THAT WAS ME.
HOW COME I NEVER MET YOU BEFORE?
-IT'S COMPLICATED. -WE'VE BEEN BUSY.
OKAY,WE'LL STICK WITH "BUSY."
WHATEVER.
I'M HERE NOW.
SO WHERE ARE YOU STAYING  WHILE YOU'RE IN TOWN?
THIS COUCH LOOKS COMFORTABLE.
IT'S NOT AN EXECUTION,SHAWN.
LAST TIME I WAS ON STAGE
WAS MY FOURTH-GRADE  SPELLING BEE.
THESE PEOPLE  ARE INTERESTED IN US.
THEY WANT TO HEAR  WHAT WE HAVE TO SAY.
YOU'LL THINK OF SOMETHING.
HELLO.
MY NAME IS SHAWN FARRELL,
AND I AM ONE OF THE 4400.
UH,A FEW MONTHS AGO,
I NEVER THOUGHT ANYONE WOULD EVER CLAP WHEN I SAID THAT.
BUT WE DIDN'T KNOW THEN WHAT WE KNOW NOW--
THE FUTURE OF MANKIND IS IN JEOPARDY,
AND RIGHT HERE,WITH YOUR HELP,
IS WHERE WE START TO SET THINGS STRAIGHT.
IF YOU JOIN US HERE--
MR. COLLIER,MR. DRAVITT'S HERE FOR YOU.
THANK YOU.
...THE BEST VERSION  OF YOURSELVES.
IAN.
THANKS FOR FITTING ME IN.
INTERESTING PLACE YOU GOT HERE.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE ABDUCTED    BY ALIENS,AM I?
NO,IAN.  THEY WEREN'T ALIENS.
THEY WERE FROM THE--FUTURE
I KNOW.SO YOU'VE TOLD ME,AD NAUSEUM.
LOOK,IT'S ALL THE SAME SIDESHOW TO ME.
SO,HERE I AM.
HERE YOU ARE.
WHAT SAY    WE GET DOWN TO BUSINESS?
IAN DRAVITT.
FOUNDER AND CEO    OF EXECUTIVE PROJECTIONS,
A MULTINATIONAL CORPORATION   BASED IN ZIMBABWE.
YOUR COMPANY WANTS TO DO
BUSINESS IN A THIRD WORLD COUNTRY,
THEY'LL SHOW YOU  THE LAY OF THE LAND.
IT'S ALL PERFECTLY LEGITIMATE--
YEAH,ON THE SURFACE,
BUT DRAVITT'S REAL MONEY COMES
FROM MERCENARY ACTIVITY  AND ARMS DEALING.
SOLD GRENADE LAUNCHERS   TO THE I.R.A.,
WHITE PHOSPHORUS LANDMINES TO
THE SHINING PATH GUERRILLAS IN PERU...
SO WHAT'S HE SELLING   TO COLLIER?
GOOD QUESTION,
BUT OUR OBSERVATION TEAMS CAN'T EVEN
TELL YOU WHAT TIME COLLIER TAKES LUNCH.
BEYOND THE LOBBY,THAT PLACE IS A MYSTERY.
I MEAN,WE'VE SENT OUR AGENTS
IN DISGUISED AS AIR CONDITIONING GUYS,
FIBER OPTICS REPAIRMEN--
YEAH,WE GET A BUG IN,
IT'S YANKED BEFORE THE DAY IS OVER.
PROBABLY SWEEPING THE PLACE    EVERY FEW HOURS.
AS FAR AS COLLIER'S POW-WOWS WITH DRAVITT...
ALL WE CAN DO    IS GUESS.
YOU THINK    HE'S STOCKPILING WEAPONS?
OH,ARMS,ANTHRAX--
NOTHING WOULD SURPRISE ME.
I MEAN,COLLIER'S ALL BUT SAID
HE'S AT WAR WITH THE U.S. GOVERNMENT.
COULD BE LAYING DOWN
A DEFENSE PERIMETER AROUND THE CENTER.
THAT WAY,IF WE EVER HAVE TO GO IN THERE,HE'LL BE READY.
THINK WACO.
JONESTOWN.
JARVIS.
I'LL SEND THEM DOWN.
MR. NAVARRO?
I'M AGENT SKOURIS.   THIS IS AGENT--
PLEASE... PLEASE,DON'T TALK.
IT'S TOO NOISY.
YOUR VOICES AND YOUR THOUGHTS,THEY JUST ALL BLEED TOGETHER.
THE E.R. REPORT SAID YOU WERE GOING ON ABOUT--
NO VOICES.
JUST CONCENTRATE   ON WHAT YOU WANT TO ASK ME,
AND I'LL HEAR YOU.
A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO.
IT WAS DURING A GAME.
I COULD HEAR EVERYONE'S THOUGHTS.
AT FIRST,IT WAS JUST THE PITCHER,WHICH WAS PRETTY GOOD,ACTUALLY...
BECAUSE I KNEW EVERYTHING  HE WAS GOING TO THROW BEFORE HE THREW IT.
WENT FIVE FOR FIVE.
TWO HOMERS,TWO SINGLES,AND A DOUBLE.
THAT IS EXACTLY WHAT--
YEAH,IT WAS GREAT   WHEN IT STARTED,
BUT I CAN'T CONTROL IT.
FIRST,IT WAS    EVERYONE ON THE TEAM,
AND THEN EVERYONE IN THE STANDS,
AND THEN,I DON'T KNOW,IT WAS JUST...
JUST EVERYONE.
IT'S LIKE  THIS OCEAN OF NOISE CRASHING AROUND IN MY HEAD.
I WANT SOMEONE   TO MAKE IT GO AWAY.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
I WAS THIS CLOSE...
TO MAKING IT TO THE MAJORS  WHEN I GOT SNATCHED.
THIS TIME,I'M GONNA MAKE IT.
I HAVE TO MAKE IT.
WHAT,SO NAVARRO IS REALLY SOME KIND OF MIND READER?
I BELIEVE "TELEPATH" IS THE WORD YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
WELL,CALL IT SOMETHING ELSE
IF THE WORD MAKES YOU UNCOMFORTABLE,
BUT THE GUY DEFINITELY KNEW WHAT WE WERE THINKING.
INTERESTING GIFT.
I COULD THINK OF A FEW PRACTICAL APPLICATIONS FOR IT.
DR. OSTMAN GAVE HIM SOME HALOPERIDOL.
IT CALMED HIM DOWN,QUIETED THE NOISE SOME.
SO HE CAN FUNCTION AS LONG AS HE'S ON  ANTIPSYCHOTIC MEDS?
WE DON'T HAVE TO FIT HIM  FOR ANY STRAITJACKET,
BUT HE'S NOT GOING TO BE HITTING ANY KNUCKLEBALLS EITHER,
WHICH IS ALL HE WANTS TO DO.
YEAH,I'LL PUT  NTAC MEDICAL ON IT.
IF THEY CAN HELP HIM,THEY WILL.
GREAT.
KYLE BALDWIN.
SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER?
THERE IT IS.
BALDWIN...
NOPE.
YOU'RE NOT ELIGIBLE TO REGISTER.
SURE I AM. I GOT IN LAST SEMESTER.
I JUST TOOK DEFERRED ADMISSION.
EXCEPT YOUR TUITION    HASN'T BEEN PAID.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
MY DAD SENT A CHECK.
NOPE.
BALDWIN.
GLAD I CAUGHT YOU.
I'VE GOT NAVARRO'S   TRANSFER FORMS RIGHT HERE.
YOU SIGN THEM,HE'S ON HIS WAY TO NTAC MEDICAL.
YEAH,I WILL,BUT NOT JUST YET.
WHY NOT?
WELL,WE WANT TO KNOW WHAT COLLIER AND IAN DRAVITT ARE UP TO.
A 4400 WHO CAN READ MINDS JUST WALKED THROUGH THE FRONT DOOR.
YOU WANT TO USE NAVARRO  AS A MOLE?
IS THAT EVEN LEGAL?
MM-HMM. D.C. CLEARED IT.
WELL,HOW ABOUT ETHICAL?
GUY'S ASKING US FOR HELP.
HELL,HE'S EVEN BEGGING US.
AND WE'LL HELP HIM.
BUT HE'S GOT TO HELP US FIRST.
WHAT IF HE SAYS NO?
THEN YOU'LL GET HIM   TO SAY YES.
EXCUSE ME.
CAN WE GET ONE MORE BLANKET?
THE ONE WE HAVE    IS KIND OF THIN.
YEAH,WELL,THEY'RE ALL KIND OF THIN,
BUT IF YOU WANT    TO BRING IT DOWN,I'LL SWITCH YOU.
OH,I THINK WE MIGHT NEED BOTH.
YOU MIGHT THINK YOU NEED THEM,
BUT YOU AREN'T   GOING TO GET THEM.
SEE,THERE'S ONLY SO MANY ROOMS  AND SO MANY BLANKETS.
AND YOU HAVE YOUR ALLOTMENT.
MY BABY IS COLD.
CAN I PLEASE  HAVE ONE MORE BLANKET SO SHE DOESN'T GET SICK?
I'LL GIVE YOU FIVE DOLLARS.
I'M A SUCKER FOR A PRETTY FACE.
HE WASN'T VERY NICE TO US,WAS HE?
HERE.
THANK YOU
WHAT OF THAY CATCH ME?
WE'LL BE MONITORING YOU
EVERY STEP OF THE WAY
WE PLANT A TINY TRANSMITTER/RECEIVER
BEHIND YOUR EAR UNDER THE SKIN
TAKES 10 MINUTES,NO SCAR
IF THINGS GO SOUTH
WE'LL BE IN THERE LIKE THE CAVALRY
WHEN I WAS A KID,MY,UH
MY FAVORITE SHOW WAS
>
30 YEARS,JUST GONE IN A SNAP
MY LITTLE BROTHER IS RETIRING
FROM THE TACOMA POLICE FORCE
AT THE END OF THE YEAR
HE'S 53
THE GUYS I PLAYED BALL WITH?
THE ONES THAT MADE IT TO THE MAJORS ARE...
SIGNING AUTOGRAPHS AT CARD SHOWS NOW
THE GAME IS ALL I HAVE
YEAH,I GET THAT
WHAT,DID YOU PLAY BALL?
SENIOR YEAR IN COLLEGE
I BLEW MY KNEE OUT
TRYING TO SLIDE UNDER A TAG
WHAT POSITION?
THIRD BASE
ANOTHER INFIELDER,HUH?
YOU MISS IT?
ALL THE TIME
BUT WHAT WE DO HERE,GARY
WHAT WE'RE ASKING YOU TO DO FOR US...
IT'S NOT THE WORLD SERIES
BUT IT'S PRETTY DAMN IMPORTANT
I DO THIS FOR YOU GUYS...
YOU'RE GONNA FIX ME,RIGHT?
YOU HAVE MY WORD
OKAY
SORRY ABOUT DINNER
NEW CASE
WELL,I'M GLAD YOU DIDN'T WAIT FOR ME
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE SORRY ABOUT?
DINNER?
ASK ME HOW MY FIRST DAY OF COLLEGE WAS
HOW WAS YOUR FIRST DAY OF COLLEGE?
I DIDN'T HAVE ONE
NOBODY PAID MY TUITION
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
OF COURSE I DID
THAT'S RIDICULOUS
I TRIED CALLING YOU A BUNCH OF TIMES
YOU DIDN'T ANSWER YOUR PHONE
I WAS IN MEETINGS ALL DAY
I KNOW I WROTE THAT CHECK
THAT'S GREAT,DAD
I'M SORRY,KYLE
I MUST HAVE FORGOT
WE'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT THIS FOR MONTHS
HOW COULD YOU FORGET?
HERE. BRING IT IN TOMORROW
I'LL SEND A NOTE
OR I'LL TALK TO THE REGISTRAR MYSELF
WHATEVER YOU WANT
HERE
KYLE! DON'T WALK AWAY FROM ME
JUST... LOOK
I ADMIT IT
I'M NOT DENYING IT,I SCREWED UP
BUT WORK'S BEEN A LITTLE CRAZY--
OH,THE JOB?
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THAT ONE
FINALLY FEELS LIKE OLD TIMES AROUND HERE
WHAT'S THIS?
LILY?
WHAT IS IT?
DID YOU SPEND ALL THE CASH
BUYING THIS STUFF?
THEN WHAT? TALK TO ME
THE CASH REGISTER  AT THE FRONT DESK...
WAS OPEN...
AND WE NEEDED FOOD
AND ISABELLE NEEDED DIAPERS
YOU STOLE MONEY?
IT'S NOT LIKE I PLANNED IT
I MEAN,I HAD TO BEG FOR A BLANKET
AND THE DRAWER WAS OPEN,SO...
HE LEFT YOU STANDING THERE
WITH THE CASH REGISTER OPEN?
NO,NO,HE CLOSED IT
AT LEAST I THOUGHT HE DID
I DON'T KNOW--
IT WASN'T OPEN,AND THEN--
AND THEN IT WAS OPEN
THAT STILL DOESN'T MAKE IT RIGHT
THAT'S NOT HOW I LIVE MY LIFE
HAVE YOU LOOKED AROUND?
'CAUSE THIS ISN'T HOW I PLANNED
TO LIVE MY LIFE EITHER
LOOK,I KNOW IT WAS WRONG
I DON'T NEED YOU
TO TELL ME IT WAS WRONG
STOP SHAKING YOUR HEAD
JUST EAT SOMETHING,OKAY?
IT'S SILLY FOR ALL THIS FOOD
TO GO TO WASTE
GO AHEAD
I'M NOT HUNGRY
HOW MUCH FUN WAS THAT?
I LIKED IT. THANK YOU
SO WHERE HAVE YOU TWO BEEN?
YOUR NOTE JUST SAID "OUT."
LOTS OF PLACES
THE PIER,PIKE STREET
AND EVEN THE FERRY
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE TO--
YOU DIDN'T!
I TOLD YOU SHE'D FREAK!
RELAX,THEY'RE RUB-ONS
AS IN "FAKE."
BUT THEY'RE PRETTY,AREN'T THEY?
OH,YEAH,THEY'RE VERY PRETTY
NOW WHY DON'T YOU GO
GET STARTED ON YOUR HOMEWORK?
I'M IN TROUBLE
DO YOU AT LEAST LIKE THE SHIRT?
AND BY THE WAY--
YOU LIVE IN SEATTLE
AND YOUR KID'S NEVER
HEARD OF KURT COBAIN?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU,DI?
THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE HERE TO TEACH HER
ALL ABOUT TATTOOS
AND SUICIDAL ROCK STARS
AND BY THE WAY
WHO GAVE YOU PERMISSION
TO TAKE HER OUT OF SCHOOL?
I'M HER AUNT
I DIDN'T KNOW I NEEDED PERMISSION
WELL,IF YOU'RE GOING
TO SEND HER TEACHER HOME FOR THE DAY
YOU DO
SITTING AT YOUR KITCHEN TABLE
ALL DAY LONG?
YEAH,THAT'S A BIG LOSS
WHAT ARE YOU KEEPING
THIS KID LOCKED AWAY FOR?
IF I WANTED YOUR OPINION
ON HOW I'M RAISING MY DAUGHTER
I'D ASK
MOMMY?
WHAT'S WRONG,SWEETHEART?
I THINK I HAVE TO THROW UP
WHAT DID YOU GIVE HER TO EAT?
ANYTHING SHE WANTED
OH. GOOD GOING,AUNT APRIL
OKAY,GUYS,I'M GOING IN
COLLIER'S GOING TO WANT TO MEET YOU
YOU'RE ONE OF THE 4400
ANYTHING YOU CAN LEARN ABOUT HIM IS GREAT
BUT OUR MAIN TARGET IS IAN DRAVITT
SEE WHAT YOU CAN FIND OUT ABOUT HIM
AND WHY HE'S THERE
YOU HAVE A TWO-WEEK SUPPLY OF HALOPERIDOL
IT SHOULD KEEP YOUR MIND CLEAR
BUT HOPEFULLY YOU'LL BE DONE
IN A COUPLE OF DAYS
EXCUSE ME
CUTE. NICE SHOES
STEER HIM OVER TO THE BROCHURES
WELCOME TO THE CENTER
MY NAME'S DEVON
I'M GARY NAVARRO
I'M KIND OF INTERESTED IN
FINDING OUT WHAT YOU GUYS DO HERE
WELL,I'D BE HAPPY TO SHOW YOU AROUND
HAVE YOU READ MR.COLLIER'S BOOK?
I DIDN'T HAVE TO
I LIVED IT
I'M ONE OF THE 4400
OH. WELL,WELCOME HOME
GARY NAVARRO
JORDAN COLLIER
IT'S A REAL PLEASURE TO MEET YOU
WELL,THAT'S A NICE FIRM GRIP
I'D EXPECT NOTHING LESS OF
A PROMISING SECOND BASEMAN
HOW DID YOU KNOW I PLAYED BALL?
WELL,IT'S MY BUSINESS
TO KNOW EVERYTHING ABOUT THE 4400
SO,UH...HAS ANYTHING SHOWN UP YET?
AN ABILITY,OR...
NO,NOT ME
I,UH,HAVE A HARD ENOUGH TIME
HITTING A SPLIT-FINGER FASTBALL
IT'S KIND OF DISAPPOINTING,ISN'T IT?
ALL THOSE YEARS LOST?
NO ABILITIES
PASS HIM OFF TO DEVON
GET BAC TO DRAVITT
JORDAN,WE NEED TO TALK
ABSOLUTELY,SHAWN
FIRST,I'D LIKE YOU
TO MEET A FELLOW RETURNEE
GARY NAVARRO.HAWN FARRELL
- HI
- HOW'RE YOU DOING?
SHAWN HERE'S A LITTLE LUCKIER
THAN YOU AND I
HE CAME BACK WITH
QUITE A REMARKABLE ABILITY
YEAH,I'M BLESSED,ALL RIGHT
SEE THE HALO AROUND MY HEAD?
I REALLY NEED TO TALK TO YOU
GIVE US A SECOND
I'VE BEEN DOING SOME POKING AROUND
ON THE INTERNET.
I FOUND OUT SOME STUFF
THAT YOU NEED TO KNOW
BECAUSE,LET ME TELL YOu
I REALLY HOPE THAT
YOU DON'T KNOW ALREADY
IF IT CAN BE FOUND ON A SEARCH ENGINE
BELIEVE ME,I KNOW IT
YOU'RE OKAY WITH THIS DRAVITT GUY?
EYES ON THE PRIZE,REMEMBER?
DOING BUSINESS WITH OUR FRIEND
DOES NOT MAKE US OUR FRIEND
DRAVITT'S NOT MY FRIEND
HE'S A DANGEROUS PRICK
I'LL MEET YOU OUTSIDE IN 10 MINUTES
AS SOON AS I GET GARY SQUARED AWAY HERE
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT
HERE YOU GO
HELLO?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHOA. WHERE WAS I?
FAR AWAY,I THINK
FIRST DAY MELTDOWN?
JUST LOST AND LATE
AND BEGGING MY WAY INTO CLASSES
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO TAKE
NOT SUCH A GOOD DAY,THEN
"INTRODUCTORY SURVEY
OF 19TH-CENTURY NOVELLAS."
KILL ME NOW
MAYBE IT'LL ENLIGHTEN YOU IN WAYS
YOU NEVER COULD HAVE IMAGINED
NOT LIKELY
IT WAS THE ONLY THING OPEN THIS PERIOD
WELL,THIS IS OLIN HALL
TAKE THE STAIRS INSIDE TO YOUR LEFT
THANKS
MAYBE I'LL SEE YOU AROUND
YOU NEVER KNOW
HELLO,EVERYBODY
I'M WENDY PAULSON
WELCOME TO
INTRO TO 19TH-CENTURY NOVELLAS
IS EVERYONE IN THE RIGHT PLACE?
I WILL SPEAK TO YOU AFTER CLASS
I CAN'T HEAR ANYTHING
I'M GOING TO TRY TO GET CLOSER
GARY,WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
COLLIER AND THAT KID
YOUR NEPHEW
I THINK THEY'RE ARGUING
ABOUT THAT GUY DRAVITT
WHERE ARE YOU?
GARY,GO INSIDE
GETTING A GOOD EYEFUL?
I'M JUST--
SHOULD WE PULL HIM OUT?
NO,NO,NO,NO,NO
NOT YET. NOT YET
MAYBE HE CAN TALK HIS WAY OUT OF IT
NOW WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
LET HIM GO
YOU SHOULD BE CAREFUL
WHO YOU LET IN YOUR MANOR,MY SON
WE DETAINED HIM
AS A PROFESSIONAL COURTESY
JORDAN,THESE GUYS ARE THUGS
NO NEED FOR NAME-CALLING
WE MERELY HAPPENED UPON THIS GENTLEMAN
IN THE PROCESS OF SPYING
ON THE TWO OF YOU
I HAD A COUPLE OF QUESTIONS FOR YOU
THAT'S ALL
I MEAN,I SAW YOU GUYS WERE
HAVING AN ARGUMENT OR SOMETHING
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO,INTERRUPT?
WANT TO KNOW WHAT WE WERE TALKING ABOUT?
BECAUSE IT'S NO BIG SECRET
I'LL TELL YOU EXACTLY
WHAT WE WERE TALKING--
SHAWN,ENOUGH
YOU'RE GOING TO FIND
I'M TIED UP A LOT OF THE TIME
GARY,IF YOU HAVE QUESTIONS
ANY OF MY STAFF...
WILL BE HAPPY TO HELP
YEAH,SORRY
NEXT TIME I'LL KNOW BETTER
ALL RIGHT
GO ON BACK INSIDE
CAREFUL WHERE HE WANDERS
NO ONE'S GETTING
BETWEEN ME AND $30 MILLION
RICHARD?
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
THE POLICE
OH,MY GOD
I'M SO SORRY
I'LL TELL THEM I TOOK THE MONEY
YOU DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT
POLICE,OPEN UP
GIVE US A MINUTE!
OPEN UP. NOW!
THEY'RE NOT AFTER US
WE'RE OKAY
GUYS? YOU THERE?
GO AHEAD,GARY
YEAH,SORRY I'VE BEEN SO OUT OF TOUCH
THEY HAD ME IN THESE CLASSES ALL MORNING
I HAVEN'T EVEN SEEN COLLIER ALL DAY
OR THAT OTHER GUY
WELL,THAT'S OKAY
YOU JUST GO WHERE THEY TELL YOU
YEAH,BUT I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WANTED TO KNOW MORE
ABOUT THAT MONEY  THAT COLLIER'S SHELLING OUT?
WHERE ARE MY MEDS?
GARY,WHAT'S WRONG?
MY MEDS,THEY'RE GONE.I DON'T--
UH,EXCUSE ME?
I,UH,I HAD A PRESCRIPTION
SOME TRANQUILIZERS IN MY ROOM
AND NOW THEY'RE GONE
YOU DON'T NEED THOSE
YOU'VE BEEN CONDITIONED
TO THINK YOU NEED THEM
TAKING ANYTHING THAT SUPPRESSES
YOUR NATURAL OPENNESS
IS COUNTERINTUITIVE TO OUR PROGRAM
MAYBE YOU SHOULD SIT THROUGH
THE NUTRITION AND PURIFICATION LECTURE AGAIN
DID YOU HEAR THAT,BALDWIN?
THEY TOOK THE HALOPERIDOL!
YES,GARY,I HEARD IT
YOU WANT TO ABORT?
YOU WANT TO WALK OUT OF THERE?
EVERYTHING IS JUST-- JUST--
GETTING LOUDER IN MY HEAD ALREADY
IT'S ALREADY GETTING WORSE
VOICES ARE STARTING
TO BLEED THROUGH THE WALLS
JUST CALM DOWN,GARY.
WE'LL COME AND GET YOU IF WE NEED TO.
IT'S YOUR CALL.
GARY,TALK TO ME.
OKAY. UM...
Y-Y-YOU GUYS  ARE GOING TO HOLD UP
YOUR END OF THIS DEAL,RIGHT?
YES. OF COURSE.
OKAY,OKAY.
I'LL,UH,I'LL HOLD UP MY END,
AND I'LL HANG IN    AS LONG AS I CAN.
GOOD. WE'LL HANG IN WITH YOU.
NOW,LISTEN,GARY,
SOMEONE'S GOING TO BE ON THIS CHANNEL 24/7,REMEMBER?
YEAH RIGHT
RIGHT
I,UH,
I READLAST NIGHT.
JUST LIKE YOUR SYLLABUS SAID.
THAT'S A GOOD START.
WELL,NOT JUST THE FIRST 20 PAGES.
I GOT REALLY INTO IT
I READ THE WHOLE THING.
19TH-CENTURY NOVELLAS NOT QUITE
THE HELL ON EARTH  YOU EXPECTED?
IT DEFINITELY WASN'T BORING.
I'VE GOT A LOT OF QUESTIONS,THOUGH.
OKAY,WELL,
I HAVE OFFICE HOURS WEDNESDAYS,ONE TO FOUR.
OKAY,YEAH,I'LL TRY TO STOP BY.
OR WE COULD RUN BY
THE COOP  AND GRAB SOME COFFEE?
LIKE,RIGHT NOW?
I LIKE TALKING  ABOUT JOSEPH CONRAD.
IT'S WHY I PICKED THIS   FOR A LIVING.
WHERE DID YOU LEARN  TO DO ALL THIS?
MOM NEVER TAUGHT US  TO COOK.
I DON'T KNOW
I JUST LEARNED HOW.
HAD TO BE BETTER THAN YOU AT SOMETHING.
AUNT APRIL,DO YOU HAVE ANY KIDS?
NOPE.
NO KIDS.
ARE YOU MARRIED?
I USED TO BE.
ASK YOUR MOM WHAT
SHE THOUGHT OF MY EX-HUSBAND.
DON'T START.
YOU DIDN'T LIKE HIM?
NEITHER DID APRIL,APPARENTLY.
SHE ONLY STAYED  WITH TREVOR FOR WHAT,SEVEN MONTHS?
YOU WERE HOSTILE FROM DAY ONE.
YOU NEVER GAVE HIM   A CHANCE.
I DIDN'T REALLY THINK HE DESERVED    MUCH OF A CHANCE.
HE WAS... KIND OF A MORON.
HE WAS 22.
SHOW ME ONE GUY    WHO ISN'T A MORON AT 22.
HE KNEW   YOU HATED HIM,
AND THAT DIDN'T MAKE IT   ANY EASIER
FOR US TO STAY TOGETHER.
COME ON.
YOU CAN'T KEEP BLAMING THAT ON ME.
I MEAN,JUST GROW UP.
OKAY,THIS WAS A MISTAKE.
I THOUGHT IT WAS A GOOD  IDEA TO COME HERE,
BUT OBVIOUSLY I WAS WRONG.
I'LL GO PACK.
THERE'S A LITTLE HOTEL   UP THE STREET.
NO!
IT'S OKAY,HONEY.    WE'LL STILL SEE--
BUT THE POWER'S GOING TO GO OUT THERE TONIGHT,
AND YOU WON'T HAVE ANY LIGHTS.
WHAT IS SHE   TALKING ABOUT?
CAN I PLEASE BE EXCUSED?
MR. NAVARRO,IS SOMETHING WRONG?
THIS IS NO GOOD. I NEED MY HALOPERIDOL.
WHERE'S COLLIER?
MR. COLLIER'S IN A MEETING.
MR. NAVARRO?
MR. NAVARRO...
[DIANA]: GARY,WHAT'S WRONG?
[GARY]: I JUST GOT  TO TALKTO COLLIER.
THAT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA,GARY.
MR. NAVARRO--
HE'S IN A MEETING!
MAKE IT STOP.
PLEASE,MAKE IT STOP.
I NEED MY MEDICATION.
WHATEVER'S EATING YOU,OLD SON,WE'LL MAKE IT STOP.
COUNT ON THAT.
A 4400 WHO CAN READ MINDS?
SO YOU DO HAVE AN ABILITY.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE LIED TO ME,GARY.
YOU MEAN TO TELL ME
THAT THIS GUY KNOWS   WHAT I'M THINKING?
BECAUSE I DO NOT LIKE ANYONE INSIDE MY HEAD BUT ME.
JORDAN,THIS GUY'S ONE OF US.
WE CAN'T JUST STAND HERE AND LET HIM GET KILLED.
NOBODY'S KILLING ANYONE.
FIRST WE DETERMINE WHAT OUR MAN HERE KNOWS
AND THEN WE DISCUSS HIS FATE.
BECAUSE THERE ARE THINGS I KNOW   THAT COULD GET YOU KILLED!
THAT COULD GET   ALL OF YOU KILLED.
CALL JARVIS.    TELL HER WE'RE GOING IN.
LOOK,IAN--
SHUT UP!
SHUT UP NOW!
HI. I'M EVAN.   WELCOME TO THE 4400 CENTER.
SECOND LEVEL'S NOT OPEN  TO VISITORS.
WE'RE NOT VISITORS.
HEY,LOOK,BUDDY,I'VE GOT A BADGE TOO,
AND THIS IS PRIVATE PROPERTY.
WHAT THE HELL'S    HE DOING TO HIM?
LET HIM GO,
OR SO HELP ME,
I'LL SPLATTER YOUR BRAINS
ALL OVER   YOUR HIGHLY POLISHED FLOOR.
NOW,THAT IS ENOUGH.
DROP THAT WEAPON! NOW!
HOW THE HELL  DID YOU GET IN HERE?
YOU DON'T SOUND SO HAPPY   TO SEE US.
WELL,NOW.    WHAT IN THE HELL IS THIS?
NTAC AGENTS.
I DON'T APPRECIATE THE GOVERNMENT INTERFERING IN MY BUSINESS.
YOU SHOULD BE MORE CAREFUL WHO YOU DO BUSINESS WITH.
THEY'RE NOT BUYING WEAPONS.
THEY'RE PLANNING A COUP OVERSEAS,SOME TINY COUNTRY.
YOU SENT A SPY IN HERE,UNCLE TOMMY?
GOOD JOB.
YOU ALMOST GOT US ALL KILLED.
YOU TOO,MR. DRAVITT.
WELL,IT'LL BE INTERESTING TO SEE
IF YOUR FRIEND'S IMPRESSIONS WILL STAND UP IN COURT.
I GUESS I'M THE ONE SHOULD BE MORE CAREFUL
WHO I DO BUSINESS WITH.
SHAWN,YOU CAN COME WITH US  IF YOU WANT.
GREAT.
I'LL TELL YOUR MOTHER YOU SAID HELLO.
GARY,YOU SHOULD HAVE    COME TO ME FIRST.
I'D HAVE TREATED YOU BETTER THAN THEY EVER WILL.
WE'RE AT WAR HERE.
DON'T PICK THE LOSING SIDE.
LOOK AT THE CUTE LITTLE BABY.
I THINK SOMEBODY WANTS TO TRY YOUR TOY,WALT.
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
HI.
PUT HER BACK IN THE CAR?
WHY?
NOW,PLEASE.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
THAT LITTLE BOY WAS BEING SWEET WITH HER.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT    ANYBODY GETTING HURT.
HURT?    WHO'S GOING TO GET HURT?
WHAT IF SHE DOESN'T WANT TO GIVE THE TOY BACK?
WHAT'S GOING  TO HAPPEN THEN?
DON'T LOOK AT ME
LIKE YOU DON'T KNOW  WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
THOSE THREE MEN  IN THE WOODS...
THEY WANTED US DEAD.
YOU SAW WHAT HAPPENED TO THEM.   THAT WAS ISABELLE.
WE BOTH KNOW IT,
AND THERE'S NO USE    IN PRETENDING OTHERWISE.
WHATEVER ISABELLE DOES,SHE DOES IT OUT OF LOVE FOR US.
SHE'S OUR DAUGHTER,RICHARD.
I KNOW SHE IS.
I LOVE HER RIGHT BACK,BUT SHE'S SOMETHING ELSE TOO,
AND I WISH TO GOD  I KNEW WHAT THAT WAS.
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
I'M FINE.
SO,WHAT?
SO COLLIER PLANNED TO SPEND   $30 MILLION
FUNDING MERCENARY ACTIVITY  IN SAO TOME?
THEY'VE HAD THREE COUPS SINCE    THEIR INDEPENDENCE IN '75.
MY GUESS?
COLLIER WAS TRYING  TO BUY NUMBER FOUR.
DID GARY HAPPEN TO HEAR
WHY COLLIER'S SO INTERESTED  IN AN ISLAND
OFF THE WEST COAST OF AFRICA?
WITHOUT HIS MEDICATION,
WE'RE LUCKY TO HAVE GOT  THAT MUCH OUT OF HIM.
YEAH,BUT WE DO KNOW
THAT COLLIER THINKS HE'S HEADED TOWARDS A CONFLICT WITH SOMEONE
NTAC,THE ENTIRE GOVERNMENT,I DON'T KNOW.
HE INSTALLS    A FRIENDLY GOVERNMENT IN SAO TOME.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN A PLACE TO GO  WHEN THINGS HEAT UP.
WHAT,LIKE A HOMELAND  FOR THE 4400?
TOO BAD YOU CAN'T PROSECUTE A MAN FOR DELUSIONS OF GRANDEUR.
THEY'RE NOT DELUSIONS
IF YOU CAN MAKE  THEM COME TRUE.
WE'RE ALWAYS  ONE STEP BEHIND COLLIER
BECAUSE WE KEEP SEEING HIM    AS SOME KIND OF CULT NUT.
WHAT WE SHOULD BE  ASKING OURSELVES IS,
BEFORE COLLIER WAS ABDUCTED,
DID HE EVER SET HIS MIND  TO SOMETHING
AND... NOT GET IT DONE?
THEY DIDN'T MAKE HIM ANY DUMBER IN THAT BALL OF LIGHT.
WELL,ANYWAY,WE WANTED TO KNOW WHAT COLLIER WAS THINKING.
GARY FOUND OUT   FOR US.
TIME TO TURN HIM OVER  TO NTAC MEDICAL,RIGHT?
SOON.
"SOON"?
THE NSA IS CC'D
ANY TIME WE REGISTER A NEW 4400 ABILITY.
THEY HAVE BEEN LEANING ON D.C.
TO BORROW GARY FOR AN OP  THEY'VE GOT PLANNED.
NO-- NO MORE CLOAK-AND-DAGGER STUFF.
HE'LL SIT IN ON A FEW CONFERENCES.
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS WITH DIPLOMATS.
THEY DON'T ALWAYS SAY WHAT THEY THINK.
THAT WASN'T THE AGREEMENT    I MADE WITH HIM.
BUT TERMS HAVE CHANGED.
GARY'S TOO VALUABLE.
I GAVE HIM MY WORD.
YOU'RE TURNING ME INTO A LIAR.
YOU'VE BEEN IN THE GAME    ALMOST 20 YEARS.
MY GUESS IS,
YOU'VE COMMITTED ALL THE SEVEN DEADLY SINS,
JUST LIKE THE REST OF US.
I SHOULD HAVE LET HIM   STAY WITH COLLIER.
HE MIGHT HAVE USED HIM,BUT HE WOULD'VE HELPED HIM TOO.
DON'T YOU EVER USE ME AGAIN.
ALL I WANTED WAS TO PLAY BALL.
YOU GUYS PROMISED TO HELP,
BUT YOU CAN'T DO THAT,CAN YOU?
WE'RE WORRIED ABOUT THE 4400.
IT SEEMS MORE AND MORE LIKE THEY SHOULD BE WORRIED ABOUT US.
YOU KNOW THAT BAR,MEL'S?
CORNER OF LANCASTER  AND THIRD?
YOU FEEL LIKE JOINING ME?
WE DON'T GO TO BARS.
WELL,I'M GOING TONIGHT,WITH YOU OR WITHOUT YOU.