Previously on the 4400...
I'm blacking out.
If you're losing chunks of time,
you should talk to your dad about it.
What's he going to do?
Turn me over to NTAC medical?
Let me see if I've got this straight.
You two met, fell in love, and spent eight years
together in some kind of alternative reality?
Liv, you were pretty far
gone last night.
When I O.D., it's not going
to be any big loss, right?
Maybe I can save you.
Whatever it is,
there's a way out of it.
That's easy to say.
You don't know what "it" is.
You told me everything
that happened that night, right?
Yeah.
If you need some time
to clear your head
and get away from everything
so you can figure stuff out,
I can make that happen.
Dad,
I had to leave. I'm sorry.
Look, I'm not interested in excuses.
I don't care how you do it,
who you have to lean on,
you just get him out of
lock-up and over to L.A.X.
I want him on
the next plane out.
Skouris, where's Baldwin?
He's not in yet, why?
What's going on?
L.A.P.D. is holding some piece of street garbage
who wants to see daylight again.
Says he can make the dealer
who sold the Collier murder weapon.
Who's handling
the L.A. interview?
Nobody. I'm having him shipped
up here for questioning.
This one feels good.
My partner's going to
like hearing that.
You can fill me in when
I get to the office.
Look, I know we're not ready
to pop any champagne yet, but
this witness has intel we kept out of the media,
specific details about the Collier murder weapon.
Sounds like we finally
caught a break.
Look, Diana, I really have to go.
Are you okay?
You sound a little distracted.
It's personal business.
Not your worry.
Well, any idea
what time you'll be in?
I can't really say just yet.
Look, I'll get in touch with you
as soon as I can, okay?
Okay, no problem.
Bye.
How long has this been going on?
Calm down.
No. I asked you a question.
How long?
Look, Kyle told me, like, a month ago.
Look, you remember that night?
Wha...
What night?
The night that he almost got arrested
for smashing that store window.
You mean when he got drunk?
He never said he was drunk.
You said he was drunk.
Kyle said he blacked out.
It happened a bunch of times
after that. One minute,
he'd be one place, the next thing
he knew, he was someplace else.
He never mentioned it to me.
He never said anything.
Well, he tried once,
but you wouldn't listen.
Look, you could have
come to me, Danny,
told me what was going on.
He's your cousin, your friend.
Which is why I promised him not to.
The last thing Kyle wanted was to
be thrown back into quarantine.
Danny, Kyle never came
home last night.
If you know where he is,
please, tell me.
He went to stay with Shawn
over at the 4400 center.
Great.
Uncle Tommy...
There's something else
you ought to know.
Kyle thinks he did something
during one of his blackouts.
He wouldn't tell us what it was,
but he really seemed
freaked out about it.
This is the committee
latest recommendation
37-year-old pipe fitter from Detroit.
He was diagnosed with Hodgkin's
disease four months ago.
When do we fly him in?
Two days from now.
Shawn.
Where is he?
Who? Kyle? He's not here.
Don't play games with me, Shawn.
Can you excuse us, Lucy?
Thank you.
Danny said Kyle came here.
Yeah, well, Danny needs to check his text
messages, because Kyle never showed.
You're not listening to me, Shawn.
I want my son.
You're not hearing me.
He's not here. Where do you think
I have him stashed, in the basement?
I wouldn't put it past you.
Oh, my g...
uncle Tommy!
Just because Kyle is having a rough time
does not make it my fault!
Been known to happen, Shawn.
He's not here!
he's not here.
Kyle?
Thomas.
I picked this up
in a village outside Barcelona,
and they said it was very special.
What's wrong?
Kyle never told me any of this.
At least I'm not the only one
out of the loop.
I thought the doctors said he was
fine when he left quarantine.
They did...
But he spent three years with a separate
consciousness living inside of him.
I don't think the doctors
knew what to do with that.
Have you called the police?
I can't get them involved,
not until I know what Kyle did.
What about Linda?
Well, she says she hasn't heard from him.
Promises to call if she does.
I'm sorry about all of this.
I'm just glad I'm back.
Where are you going?
Well, I'm not going
to find him sitting here.
I'll come with you.
No. Look... I'd rather you
stay here by the phone.
This way, if he calls...
You'll be here.
Okay.
I'll stay in touch.
And this guy is some
big-deal media consultant?
Oh, he's more than that.
Keith Petrick has prepped prime
ministers, members of parliament.
I'd say an interview with Sky News
merits a few hours' homework.
So he's going to tell me what? Just new and
different ways to say "we're not a cult?"
No,
he's going to teach you
to stay on message.
The British press loves
to play "gotcha".
Keith.
Matthew Ross. Thank you for coming.
This is Shawn Farrell.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Shawn.
Just one minute. Sorry.
Uncle Tommy came to see me.
Yeah. That's what I figured.
He came here, too.
What'd you tell him?
Well, the truth.
Kyle ditched us. He never showed.
Listen,
you know, he might still show up.
- You know?
- Yeah.
I'd give you the big tour, but...
Yeah. No. Things are crazy. I get it.
Wait, just wait, just wait.
Liv. Liv. Hey.
This is Danny, my brother.
- Hi.
- Hey.
This is Liv.
She's one of our first keys.
Actually, I'm second key now.
Really?
I'm impressed. Star pupil.
Hey, do you think
you could give him a tour?
You know, Shawn, you don't have to...
I want you to see the place.
Just hold on. Is that cool?
Sure. Yeah.
It's cool.
You two kids have fun.
I've got to... I have to
go back to work, so...
That's my brother,
off to heal the world.
Somebody has to.
You ready?
Yeah. I'm all yours.
I know who sold the rifle
that killed Collier.
That's a start.
Do we have a name?
Victor Rios.
R-I-O-S.
He lives at 43207
Sumac Drive.
S-U-M-A-C...
I've got it. Thank you.
I'm at Victor's place last month.
He gets all cranked up and starts
waving this cannon around
like he's the second coming
of Tony Montana.
He wants to swap it
for some of my product.
I told him I wasn't interested.
Can you describe
the weapon, Mr. Kovec?
I watched him put
that sucker together.
.50 caliber.
Never saw bullets so big.
And it had this humongous
scope on it,
like a huge neon sign
saying "can't miss".
What makes you so sure this was
the weapon that killed Collier?
Because...
... next time I saw Rios, he was bragging on
how much he scored for that piece.
This was, like...
Two days before Collier
got taken out.
I figure that's not a coincidence.
What do you think?
I ask you to give him a quick tour,
and two hours later...
She's a good guide.
Really sells this place.
Danny was expecting
shaved heads and robes.
Yeah. I didn't see
a single tambourine.
Are you disappointed?
Ah, you don't hear
me complaining.
So, hey, listen, big boss man,
you let your workers off
the farm at night?
So I invited Liv to a party,
but she's too shy to ask if it's okay.
Think of her like a missionary...
... a lot of potential recruits
out there at the Northmount campus.
Could be cool. I haven't left
the center in a while.
I don't think it's a good idea.
I'm sorry, man. You're going to have
to find yourself a different date.
Who are you, her warden?
Danny.
Listen, you guys can hang out here
as much as you want, no problem.
But a kegger,
that's an different story.
The wise and powerful
Shawn has spoken.
I hear and obey, your majesty.
I'm serious.
Since when did Shawn have
such a problem with keggers?
Since he developed
a messiah complex.
So what time's this party?
All right.
I woke up in the middle of the night and there
was Kyle, out here, crouching in the hallway.
With no idea how he got there.
That's right.
And I sent him away.
You were, uh..
you were scared.
It's understandable.
Not as scared as he was.
I told him he needed to get help, that
he should talk to you about these blackouts.
I wish he had.
We'd have worked it out.
Well, he wanted to.
Then what stopped him?
Look, Mr. Baldwin, your relationship
with your son is none of my business...
Agreed, but if you have
something to say, say it.
I'm sure Kyle loves you...
But I don't think he really trusts you.
What?
He told you that?
Pretty much.
Eggs, butter, walnuts,
cocoa powder.
Who said making
brownies was difficult?
Don't forget to preheat
the oven at 350 degrees.
Uh-oh.
Now things are getting
really complicated.
Relax.
I'm just kidding.
Yeah?
Now?
No. That shouldn't be a problem.
I just need to get a sitter first.
If there's a problem,
I'll call you back.
I'm sorry, sweetie, I've got to go
to work. I'll call Mrs. Skalka, see...
No, wait. Don't go.
Well, I have to. We can make
brownies another time.
That man...
You don't want to catch him.
What man?
The man you're chasing after.
Someone's going to get hurt.
Who?
Is it someone I work with?
I don't know.
Just don't go.
Are you worried about me?
Don't go.
Do you think I should get to
my car and head for the border?
Or ask to be assigned
to another case.
Hmm. Hand the risk
off to another agent?
It's not an option.
Have you told Tom?
No, not yet. He's been off
the case for a while.
Might be better for his health
if he stays that way.
She said someone was going to
get hurt, but she didn't say who.
I don't know.
Maia's visions
aren't usually so vague.
This time, she's had a vision
involving her mother.
Maybe she doesn't want
to see it too clearly.
You're not making me
feel any better.
Okay.
How about this?
Hmm?
Any better?
Sure.
You recognize that man,
Mrs. Rios?
He was a customer
of your husband's.
Husband?
He got me my green card
and more trouble than I need.
Why don't you ask Victor?
If you can find him.
Yeah, well, that's the problem, Mrs. Rios.
Your husband has left the country.
Now, we know he's in Puerto Rico.
You see? You know more than me.
He didn't tell you he was leaving?
I haven't seen him in two weeks.
Look, I need to get back to work.
A month ago, your husband
sold this man a weapon.
Your husband is implicated
in a murder, Mrs. Rios.
This is not a very good
thing for you.
Particularly if you value
your green card.
Why don't you just take
another look at the sketch?
I remember the beanie.
Not a regular customer.
He only stopped by once.
He was the one
who bought the big rifle.
And the handgun.
What handgun?
Uh, you know.
What do you call it? A 9 mm.
Anything else?
He was young... in his twenties.
Very quiet.
He only stayed a few minutes,
then left in a taxi.
How do you know that?
I called it for him.
Oh, we're going to
need that number.
We were in the middle
of a bio-lab practical,
Kyle stood up, said he'd be
right back, and that was it...
Bye-bye.
Didn't see him again
till the next day.
About what time did he leave?
Had to be 7:00, 8:00, tops.
He's wrong, as usual.
It was closer to 6:00.
Don't you remember?
We broke up right after Kyle ditched.
Yeah, look.
Anybody remember the date?
End of last month, wasn't it?
It was the 25th.
You sure?
Yeah. I remember when I got back to
the dorm, it was all over the news.
Jordan Collier's murder.
Baldwin.
You going to grace us
with a visit tomorrow?
Yeah, I'm hoping, but right now
it's looking doubtful.
Doubtful doesn't cut it.
We're closing in on this guy. Look,
we've got real leads, and I need you in here.
What kind of leads?
You want to know?
You get your ass into work.
Thomas, it could be anyone.
Look closer.
Tell me there isn't a resemblance.
This is insane. Why would Kyle
want to shoot Jordan Collier?
If it happened during one of the blackouts,
he wouldn't need a reason.
Not if the future wanted
their number one prophet dead.
So you think they were
controlling him again?
Yeah, directing his actions,
moving him around like a puppet.
Anything's possible.
Well, in that case,
he wasn't responsible.
The "body snatcher" defense? Alana,
I'm not sure the jury's going to buy it.
What the hell do
they want from Kyle?
They took four years of his life.
Isn't that enough?
They warned us
about this, remember?
They said you'd be
facing a crisis.
What, and that makes it all right?
They warned me?
I don't remember them telling me
they'd turn my son into a murderer.
There must be a reason.
Don't defend them, Alana.
Just don't! They used me...
All of us... Kyle, Shawn.
I'm fed up.
I love him too.
I know. I know you do,
Alana. Just...
I've got to find him
before NTAC does.
I've got to find him.
Stop it.
Serious business.
Your answers are going to determine
how far you would go in the center.
If that security guard comes by,
we'll both get kicked out.
Is that far enough?
Okay... question number one...
Did you have fun tonight?
Aren't you glad
we didn't listen to Shawn?
That's two questions.
- Shh.
- Oh!
You're supposed to think about your
answers, not say them out loud.
- Right.
- Rules are rules.
Okay.
What, are we done?
Question number two...
Are you ready for
the night to be over?
If your answer to question
number two is "no",
remove your goggles
and take your medicine.
Percocet.
Where'd you get these?
At the party. Your buddy had
them in the medicine cabinet.
So you stole them?
What's going on in here?
This area's closed.
Thanks so much, Mrs. Skalka.
I couldn't sleep.
Was that because of me?
Well, I'm home now, sweetie.
No worries.
You know this case
that I'm working on,
Can you tell me anything else
about what you saw?
Anything at all?
Because if you're keeping
something from me...
I told you everything.
Don't you believe me?
Of course I do.
Are you going to work tomorrow?
Well, honey, it's my job.
Can I go to sleep now?
Sure.
Here.
Linda.
Have you heard from Kyle?
No. I would've called you if I had.
I was hoping you'd heard something.
Linda, you two talk all the time.
Yeah, I don't remember any law
against it in the divorce settlement.
Listen, Linda, if you have
any idea where he is...
What, you think I'm holding
something back?
You're the one with all the secrets.
Look, you're his mother. It makes
sense you'd try to protect him.
In any way I could.
But I thought that's why he was
living with you, wasn't it?
Protecting him was
supposed to be your specialty.
You want to blame me? Fine.
Go ahead, but I've got to find Kyle now.
What if he doesn't want
you to find him?
I think he may be in trouble.
Serious trouble.
Tom, what is it?
What did he do?
At least give me a hint.
You don't want to know.
It's like I said...
You're the one
with all the secrets.
Hello?
Kyle, I just spoke to your father.
You didn't tell him where I was.
You came to me because you didn't want to
go back to NTAC. That's what you said.
Mom, I can't talk to you
about this, I told you.
Well, that's not the whole story, is it?
Mom, please.
Kyle, tell me what's going on.
Could you excuse me
for a moment?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Just don't tell me
"I told you so".
Okay, I won't, but I did.
Don't go blaming Danny for any of this.
It was all me, okay?
The night just got away from me.
I had some beers, and I...
You shouldn't be having beers, Liv.
You shouldn't be having anything.
A month ago, you were an addict.
We can quit the lecture.
I've already packed my bags.
You know, you want to quit,
I can't stop you.
But if you want to stay...
and you can promise me that nothing like this
is ever going to happen again, then please,
enjoy life as a first key.
I'm a second key.
Not anymore.
Mr. Farrell? Are you going
to be much longer?
No.
Come in.
So I've...
I've got a bunch o
new songs I've written.
Maybe I can play them
for you sometime.
Yeah. We'll see.
It's not like I know him better
than you, but we do talk.
And he told you where his
secret hiding place was?
No, but you looked
in all the obvious places,
and Kyle likes his privacy.
Maybe you do know him
better than I do.
No...
I didn't want to believe it, I kept...
I kept hoping I was wrong
about this.
Thomas, this is not Kyle's doing.
You've got to hold on to that.
okay...
Wait, don't turn around.
Alana,
take this, hide it in the house.
What are you going to do?
Go back to work.
All right, I want
this area secured.
Garrity, I want a warrant to have these
lockers opened and searched, ASAP.
Well...
Look who came out of retirement.
Good timing, Baldwin.
Your partner can bring you up to speed.
That is, assuming
you intend to stick around.
- I'm here.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, we do know that two days
before the assassination,
our man arrived at this station
with a bag full of firearms.
Well, he could've gone
anywhere from here.
Yes, so we're canvassing
all the metro routes,
we're talking to the baggage handlers,
ticket agents, bus drivers...
That sounds right.
Meantime, we just had
a shoeshine guy
I.D. the sketch. He claims he helped
our man make change to buy a locker.
Does he recall which locker?
He thinks it's in that
group there.
But all the people who use
these lockers in a month...
The odds are, like, 1 in, what, 10,000
we'll turn up anything useful.
Yeah, so why are
we even bothering?
You never know.
All we need is one print.
Yeah. We can only hope.
I guess.
You okay?
Maia had another vision.
Now, she says if
we catch this guy,
someone's going to get hurt.
Did she say who?
Welcome back.
Is Tom here?
Uh, no, he isn't.
You must be Alana.
I'm Linda.
I know.
That my interview?
I don't want to see it.
I know I sucked.
I wouldn't go
so far as "sucked".
But you could do
with more eye contact,
better enunciation.
But they didn't drag any unnecessary
dirt out of you, and that's something.
I was all distracted. Liv was here right
before, and we got into this thing...
Because you told that junkie
not to go out with your brother.
Ex-junkie.
I'm just trying to protect
her, that's all.
I'm sure that was part of it.
What do you think, I'm jealous of Danny?
You do realize that a relationship
with this girl is out of the question.
Matthew,
advise me all you want
about the center...
But that's where it stops.
You don't understand, Shawn.
You are the center.
Everything about you,
everything you do.
You cannot afford to have
an inappropriate relationship.
Jordan Collier was all about
inappropriate relationships.
I mean, every girl in this place
was fair game to him.
All the more reason
not to repeat his mistakes.
So what girl is worthy
of the great Shawn Farrell?
I will let you know
when you meet her.
On to more important things...
I wish I had time
to wipe that locker clean.
Kyle's prints could be all over it.
We've got to find him,
get him out of town.
Out of the country.
You didn't get anything else out of Linda?
Something she wouldn't tell me?
No, she's as scared as we are.
I felt guilty lying to her.
The less people who know
the truth, the better.
Still, I know how hopeless she feels.
Her son is missing. She needs answers,
and all she has to go on
is a three-line goodbye note.
Did you tell her about the note?
No.
She brought it up herself.
I never mentioned it to her.
Kyle...
Dad.
No, Kyle, wait!
Wait!
Goddammit!
- Stop it!
- Let go of me!
Enough!
Enough, Kyle.
Then I have been up on that roof, watching
Collier through the scope, the way the
trigger felt
when I pulled it,
and how his body
twisted before it hit the ground...
I mean, I remember all of it,
but it just feels like
somebody else's memories.
They are.
You weren't in control
of your actions, Kyle.
You did not kill Jordan Collier.
I haven't had another blackout since.
You think it's over?
Let's hope so.
How long do you think
I'll be put away for?
Kyle, I am not going to let them put you
in prison for something you did not do.
- Do you hear me?
- Yeah.
I just only wish
you would have
told me about these blackouts
when they first started.
You tried.
I didn't listen.
You know...
It's not a new thing, dad.
I... I know I haven't always
been there for you, Kyle, but I...
... I thought we had
a pretty good relationship.
We do. It's just,
you know, growing up with a dad who works for
the FBI, NTAC... it can be pretty intense, you know?
You mean I can be
pretty intense.
You can be scary at times.
If you don't believe me, ask mom.
I don't have to.
I believe you.
I'm sorry, dad.
Me too.
Hey, baby.
- Kyle.
- Hi.
I packed a few things for you.
Anything else you need, we'll get in Brussels.
What time is the flight?
Noon.
All right, we'd better check in at
the airport. We'll be safer there.
Okay, I emailed my friend,
and they'll meet us when we land.
They promised
to take good care of Kyle.
Say goodbye to mom for me, okay?
- Sure.
- Yeah
I promise to break
the news to her gently.
- I'll come and visit you as soon as I can, Kyle.
- That'd be good.
Okay.
- I love you.
All right.
- Thanks, dad.
- Yeah.
Alana...
Keep a close eye on him, okay?
I will, Thomas.
I will.
So far, we've found two ounces of hash,
some bootleg DVDs,
and three dop kits that belong to people
who shower in the terminal bathrooms.
I'm hoping we find a picture of Collier with a big fat "X"
marked through it, all covered in usable prints.
Yeah.
Is everything okay at home?
Because if you need to take care
of business, now is a good time.
I can hang with forensics
in case something turns up.
Thanks. I'll, uh...
I'll stick around here.
Skouris.
When did that happen?
No. We'll be right there.
That was Jarvis.
She just got a call from Metro West.
They arrested a suspect 40 minutes ago,
claim he's our guy.
Roy Keith Marsden.
25, unemployed.
Made threats against Collier
after his uncle joined the 4400 center.
Oh, and get this...
He owned a .50-caliber JHLP-6.
Alana?
Forget about the flight.
Bring Kyle home.
They just arrested a suspect
in the Collier killing.
You know, if you're here to give me
grief about Liv, you can forget it.
What happened was
your screw-up, not mine.
You know,
you could've pulled me aside,
told me she had this drug problem.
I would've backed off.
So
if you're expecting me to apologize
and kiss your robe, you're wasting your time.
I didn't come here for that.
Look, I just don't want
this to become a big thing.
Ok, when we were kids
we used to fight like crazy.
Yeah. All the time.
Yeah, and then the next day, we'd blow it off.
Everything would go back to normal.
Yeah.
Simple as that.
Nothing wrong with simple.
Are you, uh, planning on standing there,
or are you going to help me out here?
With the car?
I don't wash cars anymore.
I've got people that do that for me.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah, well, I don't, so...
grab a sponge.
Oh, see, now...
I should've known
I was going to get wet.
Yeah, attaboy.
Get your hands dirty.
It's been a while, huh?
Come on.
Hey, sweetie.
Hi.
Look, I know you've
already had dinner,
but what do you say we take
another crack at those brownies?
Okay.
Great.
So how was your day?
Pretty good.
Good.
Aren't you going
to ask me about mine?
We caught that man, the one that
we were looking for, and guess what.
Nobody was hurt.
So there's nothing to worry about.
It's all over.
Not yet.