When you get sick,it starts
out  with a single bacterium...
One lone,nasty intruder
Pretty soon,the intruder duplicates
becomes two.
Then those two become four
and those four become eight.
Then...
before your body knows it...
it's under attack.
You can't put that in there.
They told us to grab a cubby.
Yeah,I know.It's just... we
keep it empty for a reason.
Can you just take your stuff out?
There are some empty ones
over there you can use.
I don't think so.
I said take it out.
Great.I got the crazy one next to me.
You want to fight?'Cause I will.
I will fight you you're pretty tiny.
- Come on.Come on.
- I could take you down in just a couple of seconds.
Come on.Stop.
It's an invasion.
The question for a doctor is,once the invaders
have landed,once they've taken over  your body...
they took george's cubby.
how the hell  do you get rid of them?
www.arcadya.net par AGT
Traduction: Bebbop, Clochette,
Luoleilina, Dark_Chii
Relecture: Luoleilina, Clochette
Namelimitsuck, Thirteen
Locus ( je suis pas sur), confortable
locus fedding on our surgeries
There should be at least a couple of days where they act
like guests before they put their feet up on the coffee table.
And what's with the orange scrubs?
- What,ours aren't good enough for 'em?
- We ran out.
They're on back order.Randall from the supply
company says there'll be here in a week.
That's what you learn
when you lie here all day.
Why bother ordering new ones?
We could just give these to our replacements.we're
not gonna be replaced by anybody.
- If I have to become a coroner...
- No one is becoming a coroner.
Cristina,tell him.
Tell him what?They're here.It's over.
We are not some stupid hosts.
They can't invade us.
They can't attach themselves to our faces
and then while we're eating spaghetti,
explode out of our chests
and skitter across the floor.
This is our ship.
This is ourship.
excuse me. Are you are you
quoting a sigourney weaver movie?
- Shut up.
- That's what happens when you live here.
You watch a lot of tv.
We own this hospital.
We were born in this hospital.
And we will hold this hospital
with our last gasping breath.
I really don't want to be a coroner.
I don't like dead people.
Go out there and go get surgeries
before they take them.Go!
And I want a full report
by the end of the day.
And what is wrong with you?
I-I don't know what i'm fighting for.
Surgeries,cristina.Surgeries.
There will be a cardio
god here again one day.
And when there is,you don't
want to be out of practice.
Now go.
is this overflow from mercy west?
Their--their E.R. Closed for good
last night.Everyone's coming over here.
Another one of the
perks from the merger.
-Our new attending.
- First day back?
- You picked a good one.
It's nice and quiet. Not a lot going on.
Thank you.
Where do you want us?
At this point,anywhere is good.
At mercy west,we do zones.
When it's super busy,we just
give everyone a zone, space.
The nurses put a person in that space,you know
it's your pient.Helps you get to 'em quicker.
This is the E.R.Not a school
yard.We're not playing four square.
- I like it.
- What?
It's a good idea.Let's
try it.What's your name?
- Jackson avery.
- dr. Avery,dr. Hunt.
It's all yours.Zone away.
let's go.
- Chif
- what do you need ?
I know you still have cuts
to make at the resident level,
and I just want you to keep in mind
that izzie stevens is not 100% back yet.
I mean,she's recovering.
Look, she just...
she needs this.
I have a hospital to run,karev.
I have two hospitals to run.
That wasn't cool.
- What?
- In the locker room.
My friend should've left
that cubby empty.I'm sorry.
- Well,she's obviously not,so--
it's the first day of school.
Everyone's on edge.I'll probably kill
someone before the day is through.
I'm charles,by the way.Charles percy.
it might be kinda hard for
you not to talk to me all day.
It can be done.
I almost didn't talk to my family for
a car ride across the whole country--
10 days,15 states,not a peep.
Just read books,pretended
I was a hostage.
Izzie stevens.
Nice to meet you, Izzie stevens.
Do you happen to know the
key code to the research library?
I was here last night,and it was closed.
It took me two years to get that code.
I need every advantage I can get.
Did the gentleman from the
waiting room ever find you?
What?
It's the gentleman who could
possibly be your father.
What?
daddy.
Calliope.
What... what are you doing here?
I came to see you.
Why?
Calliope,we used to talk.Every
sunday,we used to talk.
I'd wait for your call,and you'd tell me
everything,all about your crazy adventures.
even when you were in trouble,you'd
still call,and we worked it out.
We'd always work it out,mija. Hmm?
daddy.
- I'm sorry. I' m... I'm sorry things got so...
- Sure.
But the fact that you came...
daddy,is that father kevin?
Hello,calliope.
Wh--are you t--
two here to...
you think you can pray away the gay.
We can just sit and talk.
Oh,no.You can't pray away the gay.
Calliope iphegenia torres!
You can't pray away the gay!
The man flew 3,000 miles to make
me straight... with a priest.
I'm lucky they didn't
march into the E.R.
- Swinging incense,all--all hepped up for an exorcism.-
- Are you done yet?
no!
He came here to disinfect you from
my life.You n't find that abhorrent?
- I do,but
- There is no "but,"
What,you're gonna you're gonna
tell me you get where he's coming from?
Maybe you should try and talk to him.
I have nothing to say.
If he wants to throw away our relationship
after 30 years,then that's his decision.
He hasn't done anything here.
You're the one who changed the game.
You didn't expect a little understanding
when you came out to your parents?
I never had boyfriends... ever.
I had a poster on my wall of cindy
crawford,and I wasn't just looking at her mole.
It wasn't news to my mom when I
brought somebody home named joanne.
But you,you dated men your whole
life.You loved men.You even married one.
you want to talk about 30
years of a relationship?
You know,he's been
consistent for 30 years.
And all of a sudden,you're
a whole new girl.
Cut him some slack.
Sit down and have a conversation.
Give him room to be a little shocked.
I hate you.
'Cause I'm right and I'm awesome.
thanks for being my tour guide
through all this first-day madness.
- We both got assigned zone five,so...
- I know it's not like you had any choice.
Still,you're a peach
to pretend otherwise.
- Being the new kid is...
- A little scary,I know.
Of course,you were here when that psycho-intern cabal
was marching around chopping out each other's organs.
now that must have been scary.
I'm dr. Kepner. Oh handcuff !
I'm not an ax murderer.
I just broke in to someone's house.
Dude came after me with a golf
club,beat the crap out of me.
Look,you don't need the
cop.I can barely move.
- Roll him.
- Oh,we'll keep the cop.
he's got multiple contusions
and ecchymosis over his back.
He's gonna need lumbar
and thoracic films.
Down.
And by the way,it was one organ--an
appendix.It wasn't a psycho cabal.
Good to know.
hey,sarah.
dr. Stevens.  I have to go.The doctors are here.
My sister and her daughters want you
all to promise them it's a good kidney.
it's a good kidney.
There,all right?bye.
Uh,sarah fremont,age
27.End-stage renal disease.
On dialysis for three
years,waiting for a kidney.
She's down to her last access site.
That's the polite way of saying they've
run out of places to stick the needles.
Ms.Fremont has a subclavian
catheter for access.
Why is this not ideal?
It's difficult to obtain sufficient blood
flow through... You guys raise hands.
Frank Nusbaum,42,multiple,mostly
superficial stab wounds.
Vital signs stable.
His buddy's got a lacerated palm.
- Got it.Thanks,ray.
- I'm not his buddy!
He touched my little girl,my baby!
She's not a baby.
She's 19 years old.
There ain't a scrap
of baby left there,don.
On three.One,two,three.
We got a bleeder here.
Draw me up some lidocaine
and,uh,get me a lac tray with 3-0 silk.
- Need any help?
- Sir,this is gonna pinch.
He came at me with a carving knife.
- He tried to cut off my--
- Come on.I was gesturing!
You ran into the knife.
- You're an idiot and a pervert.
- Tie.
She used to babysit your brats.
I can't believe I ever
let her in your house!
I love her,don.
I love her,and she loves me.
I'm gonna kill him.
Easy,all right?
Let him die.Just let him die.
It's what he deserves.
Can you shut him up?
- Are you sure there's nothing I can do ?
- there.
You know what?That's how we
do it on our side of town.
Nice try.This is my
zone.He's my patient.
Yet I'm the one actually helping him.
How long have you been
having stomach pains?
A few days now.
They keep getting worse.
- My dad a fell a couple of months ago,had a stable hip fracture
- Excuse me.
- This is my patient.
- Not anymore.
Fine.Good luck doing
an h&p without a chart.
I'll just add this to the chart later.
If you can find it.
This is the nurses' lounge.
It is literally always  someone's birthday,so
if you're nice to the nurses,you will get cake.
The lab.
How's the I.L.-2 going,dr. S.,Good?
Good.
I.L.-2,huh?
- Are you feeling
- Stable for now.
And you don't want anyone to know because they'll be
blown away by the fact that you're already back at work
and they'll only be able to think of you as some
sort of awesome super woman,which clearly,you are.
You know what?
The fake flattery?
It's kinda gross.
You want tknow something
deeply personal about me?
You see that girl?Her name's reed.
I have the biggest crush in the world on
her,and she doesn't even know I'm alive.
She calls me charlie.
Nobody named charlie ever got the
girl, charlie brown,charlie manson.
I'm not trying to minimize your cancer
or anything,but this really sucks for me.
You like her?
I love her.
43-81.
What's that?
The code to the research library.
"While performance has been evaluated,the
largest considerations have been budgetary.
" This is the speech we want you to use when you're
firing staff-- these exact words.Don't deviate.
I'm not using your speech to fire
people,and I don't need an H.R.Chaperone.
Thank you for your time.
Chief,are you familiar
with Megan Nowlan?
Mm,yes,yeah.
Uh,e was an intern.
She was married to steve mostow.
I fired her.I know how to fire people.
I don't like it,but I know
how to do it,and I do it well.
You used an e-mail to fire her,and now she's
suing the hospital for wrongful termination,
claims she was fired
because she was prnant.
This is the speech.
Don't deviate.
T&l spine films showed
a burst fracture at t-12.
And here you can see evidence of instability
because the veebral height loss is greater than 50%,
which implies both A.L.L.
And P.L.L.Are disrupted.
What's that mean?
I got a broken back?
I'll still be able to walk,right?
You will still be able to
walk,burgle,have a full life.Ideas?
Decompression via corpectomy and reconstruction
with strut graft and anterior instrumentation.
I might be out of my league here.
She has a photographic memory.
We're all out of that league.
And here I was thinking you could do
transpedicle screws with a posterior approach.
Seemed like a good
idea,but,you know,maybe not.
Let's go with the pedicle screws.
Get him into pre-op,and let me
know when his test results come back.
I'm on it.
Frank.Oh,my god.
Honey,are you okay?
I'll be fine,sweetheart.
Get off of her,you perv!
Daddy.
I will kill you,you son of a bitch!
Security! stop!
nice work. Thanks.
I got it from here.
Tackle like that,you
had to play football.
I played a little in college.
- Safety?
- And wide receiver,yeah.
Offense and defense.Impressive.
Can you bring that guy over later?
I want to thank him.
He saved my life.
No,I saved your life.
I'm still saving it.
- You paged?
- Yes.I ran a C.T. On your guy with the tummy ache.
Turns out he has an adrenal mass.
Thought you might want to see the scans.
I was waiting until I got the
lab results to order a C.T.
You stole my lab results?
And look,now I get a
surgery for all my trouble.
excuse me,dr. Karev,my dad
and I have some more questions.
He's still pretty upset.
Yeah,I'll be there in a minute.Thanks.
I'll take those.
You gonna fight back at some
point or just let her bury you?
She's not burying me.
She's new.She's just
finding her footing.
She found her footing
on the back of your neck.
What do you care?
I don't know.
I like you.
No,I like that. stop. That's good.
Find her open window.
Everyone has one--
a we spot,undefended.
An open window or a key hidden
in a fake rock,that's how I do it.
Yeah,well,you're a criminal,and I'm not.
It's not a crime to do to
her what she's doing to you.
Which is what,exactly?
Making you look like an idiot.
- Have you talked to any of them?
- Who?
The mercy westers.
- Yeah.
- And?
And... I love you.
No,not that.
I need to know what's
going on out there.
I need to knowhow cristina's doing.
She was cardio deprived and depressed.
Are you and cristina in
a dark and twisty place?
Are you having the dark and twisties?
We are.
Both of you are dark and twisty?
I told you,we are.
Excuse me dr. Hunt, you paged me?
Your patient was having neurologic
symptoms and you didn't notice,karev?
Lucky for you dr. Adamson did
and correctly diagnosed carotid stenosis.
Book an O.R. For the afternoon.
What about the surgeryfor
his adrenal tumor?
Your dad has a 90% blockage
in his right carotid artery.
We need to operate on that first.
Now I know that's a lot to digest,but dr.
Adamson here will keep you informed,all right?
With all due respect,dr.
Hunt,mr.Goldman is my patient.
- I found the tumor
- And when I operate on the tumor,you can scrub in on that.
In the meantime,I want you to help
dr. Adamson  the patient for the C.E.A.
- Sir...
- Whatever she needs,karev.
Neurologic symptoms?
You didn't put that in the chart.
Oh,I didn't?
all right,fine. I get it.
I sprang this on you.It
was a lot to take in.And...
you feel like you don't have
much experience with gay people,
even though uncle berto hasn't been
single for 60 years for no reason.
- Calliope
- It's still an adjustment.
That said... you
should've adjusted by now.
I mean,you're supposed
to love me no matter what.
That's... what a parent does.
I love you with all my heart.
But with all that's going on with
you now,it'S... look,m scared for you.
It's an abomination.
It's an eternity in hell.
Let's not start with words like "hell.
" Oh,that's why you flew 3,000
miles,to tell mewas going to hell?
I thought you came here to apologize.
I can't apologize,calliope.
I don't understand what
happened or where I went wrong.
Where you went wrong?
Okay,leviticus.
"Thought shalt not lie with a
man as one lies with a female.
" Oh,don't do that,daddy.
- Don't quote the bible at me.
- "It is an abomination.
" "The outcry of sodom
and gomorrah is great,
and their sin is exceedingly grave.
- Carlos,this is not what we
- Jesus"
a new commandment that I give
unto you that you love one another.
- Romans,"but we know that the law
- Jesus--"
he who is without sin among
you,let him cast the first stone.
" So you admit it's a sin?
"Blessed are the merciful for
they shall obtain mercy"--jesus.
"Blessed are the pure in heart,for
they shall see god"--jesus.
"Blessed are those who have been persecuted "for
righteousness sake for theirs is the kingdom of heaven.
" Jesus is my savior,daddy,not you.
And jesus would be ashamed
of you for judging me!
he would be ashamed of you
for turning your back on me.
He would be ashamed.
with this kind of injury,there is a chance that
you could end up with severe weakness in your legs.
That's okay.
I carry the stuff out
with my arms,not my legs.
This is serious,billy.
You're gonna fix me up fine.
Listen... I've got a present for you.
You stole her notebook?
Keep it down.You want
my cop all over this?
Don't you get it?
This is her open window.
I don't--I don't
want her open window.
"You're not just a good doctor.
You're a great doctor.
" "You are the future of medicine.
"  "only you can keep you down.
" And my favorite is,uh... "no
one can tell it's plastic surgery.
" Oh,my god.
I think it's the nose,but it could
be the boobs.What do you think?
Give it back to
her,and stop reading it.
"Future of medicine" alert.
You haven't seen my
notebook anywhere,have you?
Small,red, I was
holding it all morning.
I'm not sure.
So much for that
photographic memory.
Good luck finding it.
this blows.
getting your ass kicked?
Shut up.I hear yours got a
standing ovation in the E.R.
Yours is the one who saved the whole
E.R.From the maniac with the hammer?
He didn't save anyone.
He did some stupid ninja
leap and then tripped a guy.
I used actual medicine to
stop a person from dying.
Well,mine has a notebook,a
notebook that she takes notes in,
notes of a very personal
nature,and I stole it.
- You what?
- Give it.
No, I am not
sinking to their level.
They are vindictive and they are aggressive
and--and they are not  team players.
and if we are not careful,that spirit
is going to infect our hospital.
We have to fight it.
Which is why you stole her notebook?
and read it?
She's not a very nice person.
Score.
You rock.
- Oh no.That's not for you.
- Who's it for then?
Charles.
Your mercy wester?!
They're handing us our asses on a
plate,and you're serving 'em coffee?
Charles is actually kind of awesome.
And if you all could get past your
sad,little egos,you would realize,
you can't write off  all of the mercy west
residents just 'cause you feel threatened.
- we don't feel threatened.
- No.
We feel pretty threatened.
they're not here.
Hallelujah.
They're not eating.
They're working.
- Oh,my god.They don't eat lunch.
- Oh,god!
What's going on?
Pulsatile mass over the stab
wound.What are we looking at,dr. Avery?
Can't be sure without an angio,but
I think it's a pseudoaneurysm.
I think you're
right.Keep pressure on it.
Let's gehim up to angio,and if
it's positive,you're scrubbing in.
- Thank you,sir.
- But that's my patient.
He was here,and you weren'T.
- dr. Hunt!
- What?
Cristina,what?
What?You know what?That doesn't matter
that that's my patient or my surgery?
You're prioritizing based on some sort of random
code,some stupid rule you have not to favor me?
This--this is
one surgery.
forget it.
the woman does whatever I ask.
I want something...  she gets it for me.
The research library?
Anytime you want to go in,it's
closed,just say the word.
She gave me the code to the place.
- You're kidding.
- She can't do enough for me.
it's like I have my own surgical bitch.
didn't go well,huh?
well,at least now I can
move on with my life.
Stop entertaining any thoughts of actually
getting back together with my family.
whatever.I don't need a father.
I don'T... not one who won't accept me.
I know.
well,his vital signs are fine.
B.P. Looks good.
I hurt.
- The neck... blood...
- what?
In head... ple... 12.
- What's happening here?
- I'm not sure.
We're gonna have
to,uh,hold off on the O.R.
pathetic.
Look,he just said a
bunch of weird crap,okay?
He has expressive aphasia,which means broca's
area,which is the left side of the brain.
You said it was the right
side that was blocked.
5% of people have broca's on the right.
You want to take that chance?
What if it's a brain met from the tumor?
Oh,right.Because you diagnosed
a tumor,now it's a met.
I've seen this before.Have you?
Stop. Your behavior has been disgusting.
I mean,all you've done all day is take
pleasure in how the other one got it wrong,
how they screwed it up.
This is my father...  my father.
And... and you are
supposed to be healers.
That's what you're job's
supposed to be,to heal people.
We're gonna run some more tests,ma'am.
We're... very sorry.
thank you.
- dr. Stevens,can i talk to you for a minute?
- Go away.
Picked up the labs for you.If you
want,I can take care of the dialysis.
I've got this.
I don't need a surgical bitch. Thanks.
Izzie,it wasn't personal.
That stuff,it just...
comes with the job.
I'd expect you to do
the same thing to me.
Outside of work,you can be friends.
But inside,it's a whole different story.
At least it wasat mercy west.
That isn't how it is here.
Here,we don't just
think about ourselves.
We support one another.We
have each other's backs.
We throw ourselves in front of buses
to save the lives of complete strangers.
You will never measure up
to the people we've lost.
Let's do a 140-base sodium,37-base biocarb and a
zero-k bath with an ultrafiltration of 3.5 liters.
"That,I suppose,makes
everything quite all right."
"Oh, this?"
Cristina.
Cristina, talk to me.
- No.
- cristina.
- He wouldn'T...
- What happened?
here.
talk to me.Tell me what happened.
Nothing.
Nothing is happening to me.
You know,I don't I
don't know what I'm doing.
I'm,like,chasing after
surgeries I don't care about.
Do you know how long it's been
since I've hela heart iny hand...
since I felt that... that joy,that rush?
you know... I miss burke.
I-I m--I miss
him all day.
I miss--you know,I-I-- it's--it's
not the relationship or--or the sex.
I miss...
every day when he was
here,I held hearts.
And I got picked,not because of some favoritism,but
because it was just,like,it was right.
And I learned.I learned.
and I felt seen.
And now you know what?I don't know what.
I spent this entire day fighting...
and I-I don't want to do it anymore.
Come over here.
Where are we at with billy sheehan?
He's ready.I helped put him
under.He's prepped and positioned.
I thought we said I was handling that.
Yeah,we did.I just wanted to make absolutely
sure everything was ready for dr. Shepherd.
Well,your first day here,and
already you're making my life easier.
Yeah,dr. Kepner--no,she's
not just a good doctor.
She's--she's
a great doctor.
In fact,if you ask me,she's
the future of medicine.
Only you can keep yourself down,right?
By the way,I can tell.
d-dr. Shepherd,I just need a moment.
Look at this.
Acute on chronic subdural hematoma.
That's not mets.
No,it's a brain bleed.
Which would explain the
aphasia and the numbness.
It would explain everything.
I'll tell neuro.
Oh,no.Nice try.I'll tell neuro.
I'm the one that said
it was a brain issue.
The only reason why you knew that was because I got
e ball rolling by diagnosing the carotid stenosis.
Can't you give it a rest?Didn't you
hear what goldman's daughter said?
Sorry.
I'll stop if you stop.
I've stopped.You can have it.
Talk to arizona robbins--
she's head of neuro.
She's not really head of neuro,is she?
what the hell happened?!
Push another 2 of ativan now.
Get me new chemistries and an E.K.G.
Get the crash cart in here now.
Start ventilating her.
Torsades?You gave her torsades?
What the hell did you do to her?
I didn't do anything.You were
the one who was with her last.
- Page bailey.
- I already did.
clear.Clear!
I don't know you well
enough to talk about her.
We're not gonna do that.
Most people think that I was named
for the state,but it's not true.
I was named for a
battleship--the "U.S.S. Arizona."
My grandfather was serving on the arizona
when the japanese bombed pearl harbor,
and he saved... 19
men before he drowned.
Pretty much everything my father did his
whole life was about honoring that sacrifice.
I was raised to be a good man in
a storm,raised to love my country,
love my family and
protect the things I love.
When my father... colonel daniel robbins
of the united states marine corps,
heard that I was a lesbian,he
said he only had one question.
I was prepared for "how fast can
you get the hell out of my house?
" But instead... it was... "
are you still who I raised you to be?
" My father believes in country
the way that you believe in god.
And my father is not a man who bends,but
he bent for me because I'm his daughter.
I'm a good man in a storm.
I love your daughter,and I
protect the things I love.
Not that I need to.She doesn't need it.
She's strong and
caring... and honorable.
and she's who you raised her to be.
She's alive,barely.
Is she still gonna get the kidney?
I'm asking the questions
right now,stevens.
dr. Percy here tells me that you
were in charge of sarah's dialysis.
- Is that true?
- Yes.
He also says that you
were pretty upset with him.
I don't see what that
has to do with anything.
It has to do with the fact that your
mental state may have clouded your judgment,
may have made you a
less competent doctor,
may have led you to read the labs
wrong or not read them at all.
Otherwise,why would you tell the
tech to give sarah a zero-k bath
when her potassium this morning was 3.4?
You sucked all the
potassium out of that woman.
You stopped her heart.
She's alive,but she's
not getting her kidney.
After three years of waiting,somebody
else  will be getting her kidney.
And if we don't find her another one in
the next three days,she's going to be dead,
and you will have killed her.
The surgery went
pretty well.
We had good bone alignment.
And I'll be back to my old self?
I'll be able to get around?
Get around?Yes.
To where you were?
No,probably not.
Probably about 70%,which is
good considering your injuries.
I guess that means I only
steal 70% as much stuff.
you see this?
I noticed this afternoon there were splotches
all over the page,and... they're tears.
She was crying when
she wrote this stuff.
She's scared.
And these stupid little
sayings,they make her feel better.
This is her comfort.
We stole her comfort from her.
You and me,we're-- we're taking things
from people,and we're leaving them at 70%.
you promised.
You promised my nieces I
was getting this kidney.
I'm sorry.I am... so,so sorry.
But I am going to make this right.
I'm going to get you another kidney.
it's my sister.
What do I tell her?
I'm sorry.
it must be hard,being the
new people,being the invaders.
But that's no excuse for you being A...
I don't like you.
but what I did...
that was over the line.
Oh,I'm sorry.I thought
you wanted to see me.
This is Missy Grant
from human resources.
You're kidding me.
You're firing me?
- Stevens
- You can't do that.
You can't fire me
for-- for having cancer.
I'm pretty sure that that's
five kinds of illegal.
This is not about the cancer.
It's about the kidney patient?
I made a mistake.I...
but doctors make mistakes
in this hospital every day.
- Yes,but when there's
- You let me come back after I cut an l-vad wire.
That was a different era.
Times have changed.
dr. Shepherd and dr. Hunt... had concerns
about your stamina and emotional stability.
- And dr. Karev has questions about
- Alex?
Alex said something to you?
dr. Webber.
In the wake of the merger with mercy
west,the needs of the hospital have changed.
While performance is evaluated... the
largest considerations are budgetary.
There was simply no room on the staff.
please don't do this to me.
please don't take this away from me.
I don't have anything left.
please.
What do you do  when
the infection hits you...
calliope?
When it takes over?
I can't do this anymore.You'll,you
know,see me in hell.
Listen to me,please.
I have to catch you.
What?
Your whole life,you... you've always been on a
bridge,calliope,ever since you were a little girl.
And you don't just walk on it either.
No,you climb on the railing and
you're-- you're ready to leap.
And when you do,when that happens...
I have to be there,I have to catch you.
You don't have to catch me,dad.
Yes,I do.
It's my job.
if this works out between you
and arizona... is there a chance
that maybe you'd,uh...
give your mother a wedding?
I think if arizona wanted
to spend the rest of her life with me?
Yeah,I'll put on a big white
dress and dance down the aisle.
How-- how
about grandkids?
Yes,I would imagine...
When the time came...
there would be kids.
Does she make you happy?
Yes,dad.
she makes me very happy.
I love you.You know that?
she's not a vegetarian,is she?
Because I-I don't know
how much more I can take.
She's not a vegetarian.
I feel very old.
Do you do  what you're supposed
to  and take your medicine?
Or do you learn to
live  with the thing ?
and hope someday  it goes away?
tell me everything.
Did you beat them?
Did you kick their asses?
Come on.I want a full
report.Everything that happened.
Izzie left me.
She wrote a note and she left me.
I don't--I don't-- I don't
know if she's coming back.
Wh-what do you mean,she
left?Where did she go?
- Go hug him.
- What?
Go hug him.
Synchronisation: xCathx
Or do you just give up
entirely  and let it kill you?