It's intense, what
happens in the o.R.
When lives are on the line...
And you're poking at brains
like they're silly putty.
You form a bond
With the surgeons
right next to you...
An unbreakable, indescribable bond.
It's intimate, being
tied together like that...
You up? No.
Yes. Whether you like it or not,
Whether you like them or
not, you become family.
The wicked witch is dead.
Metaphorically dead or dead dead?
Who are we talking about?
Hahn. Hahn.
Her name is off the surgical board.
Her surgeries have been canceled.
I don't know how or why,
but I do know hahn is gone.
That's too bad. She
was really talented.
You're not talking to me.
Hi.
Is, uh, grey home?
Yes.
Death?
Come on. Where are you, death?
Death?! Aah!
Die! Oh, my
god! It's been--
Forever. Oh.
Oh, wow. You look like...
Death! Death!
Is the guy in the
pajamas your boyfriend?
'cause if so, then hot. Right?
Uh, hey. Uh... Who are you?
I'm sadie. Who are you?
I'm--i'm--i'm
cristina.
Wow.
Apparently they went backpacking
Around europe together
or something... Mm.
Before med school.
You know that woman all but
kicked me out of the bed?
That's terrible.
And death? Meredith's name
is not death. It's mer.
I really feel for you.
You know, she's never
even mentioned this woman.
I mean, how good of
a friend can she be?
Good enough to kick
us both out of bed
Welcome to my world.
This woman is the reason
I went to med school
in the first place.
I figured if a slacker like death...
Mer. Mer. Could handle slicing
people open, then I could, too.
Meredith's not a slacker. Ooh,
I could tell you some stories.
But you won't. So, sadie,
you postponed your residency
To work in a morgue?
Yeah, you know, a lot
of the fun cutting,
None of the rules, but I got bored.
Started craving blood
that was flowing.
And now you're here. I
can't believe you're here.
Yay.
Iz, you coming?
Yeah. I just need a minute.
Look, I get it. Hahn's case
brought up the denny thing.
But hahn's not even here anymore.
It's stuff from the past.
Stuff from the past, iz.
You don't understand.
I might...
If you'd talk to me.
Fine.
See you inside.
I'm walking.
Morning.
Walking straight
ahead, all by myself.
You know, you look
good. Tired, but good.
Did I mention I find the
short hair kind of sassy?
Now I'm turning this
corner, again, all alone.
Ouch.
Um...
These are s--uh,
scratches from my kitten.
He's a crazy scratchy scratcher.
You're a cat person?
I meant hairbrush.
It--it--i have a crazy
scratchy hairbrush.
Solo surgeries are
at stake here, three.
I can't have you acting weird
Or wounded.
I'm--i am on top
of my game. Really.
I'm sending you to plastics,
far, far away. Just go.
Hey, what do you know about
a heart guy named dixon?
Dixon? Uh, no, not a guy.
I've heard of virginia dixon.
She's got an incredible
record. Really low mortal--
Wait. Is she coming
here? Yeah. Today.
Piggyback heart
transplant. I'm on the case.
What? What? W-why
am I not on the case?
So she's your pre-cristina cristina?
You gonna tell me why
she calls you death?
Oh, no. The adventures of dea and die
Are better left untold. Hey,
Pedia's julienning her
skinny little chickearms
And still no word on
what made "h" hitch a ride
With her flying monkeys.
Later. Translate that for me.
Lexie may be a secret cutter,
And there's still no
word on why hahn quit.
Is that true, about lexie? I
don't know. How would I know?
If it's true, what are you
gonna do about it? Nothing.
Meredith, you can't do
nothing. She's your sister. And?
And you're family.
I'm not understanding.
Lexie is your family.
Forget it.
Hello, dr. Hunt.
Dr. Yang.
Thank you.
Hey, what do we got?
Uh, crush injuries.
Couple minutes out.
Hey, w-what do you know about hahn?
Um, she's gone.
Yeah, but why? I don't know.
You two are friends. I don't
want to talk about it, okay?
I want blood and guts
and mangled bones.
I want a guy so badly smashed
up, it takes all day to fix him.
I want to rock a surgery. I don't
want to talk about hahn. Okay, okay.
Unidentified man with
prolonged extrication time.
They had to fish him out
of a working garbage truck.
Multiple crush injuries,
open fractures, g.C.S. 3,
And we couldn't unhook him
in the field. Unhook him?
His femur's broken in half,
and it's puncturing his torso.
He's impaled.
Impaled on himself?
Human pretzel.
That'll do.
Wow.
Check his popliteal pulse.
I'm getting nothing. That's
because his knee is over here.
You think he was
sleeping in that dumpster
And they started crushing
the trash? That's a bad day.
Here I am.What did I miss?
It's your first day.Why don't
you just stand back and shut up?
Breath sounds are clear and equal
both sides.Unbelievable
So no punctured lung.We need a
portable x-ray and an ultrasound
Someone paged us?I did
you did? that's a first.
So is this. I've seen a lot
of trauma-Guys cut in half
amputations, eviscerations.But I
have never seen anything like this
I wondered if you could help.
You hire when you're
number 1, not number 12.
But I need you to be
my ambassador today.
Show dr. Dixon what
seattle grace is all about.
I've thrown a lot
of money, a big title
And a lot of research dollars at her.
But... But what?
Um... She's a little different.
She's a little off.
So we're wooing today, bailey.
I can woo with the best of 'em.
So, what, dixon is
a nut job? Excuse me?
I'm just saying, I've
already had my quota of crazy
For the year. Hey, I've had my
off days. You want to judge me?
You never even met the woman, karev.
Now you heard the chief. Our job
is to impress dr. Dixon today,
So be impressive. I've got
the chart for dr. Dixon.
I'm ready to work. I'm excited.
Don't be. She's off. Karev.
You okay?
Yeah.
All right. Heads-up. Here she comes.
Oh, dr. Dixon. H-hi.
Welcome to, uh, seattle grace.
We're very happy to h-have you here.
I'm--i'm dr. Bailey. I-i
brought my own lab coat.
I'm here to perform a
heart transplant today.
I do hearts.
A procedure invented by
christiaan barnard in 1967.
I do hearts.
Uh, i--i'm dr. Richard
webber. We spoke on the phone.
Karev, would you get dr.
Dixon the latest labs?
Stevens, let's prep
the patient, please.
Okay, then. She's a little off.
His femur's in pieces,
I mean, except for the part
that's stuck in his torso.
There's no way I'm saving that leg.
It looks like the impaled piece
is lodged under his clavicle
C-spine looks clear. Without a c.T.,
It's hard to be sure. And
why can't we get a c.T. Scan
The way he's impaled, it's
hard to get a clear reading.
You know, there is such a
thing as a stupid question.
Stand over there. Guys, guys, we
have a very limited window here, okay?
With vitals like these,
in a few more hours--
His body won't be able to
withstand surgery at all
Good thing he's unconscious.
Well, we can't do anything
Till we dislodge the femur from his
Clavicle. Okay, then
let's unimpale him
Yang, grey, new kid, hold
his shoulders. Brace him hard.
I'll hold his c-spine.
I got his torso.
I need to guide the
posterior hip dislocation.
The second that leg is out,
be ready to assert pressure
To stop the bleeding. Got it?
Better thaworking on corpses, huh?
On the count of three. One...
Two...
Three.
Okay, push directly on
the clavicle while I pull.
Femur's really wedged in there. Okay,
almost there. Almost there. Steady.
Just a little bit further.
S-sloan, I need you to, um,
Rotate his knee to my right.
Push 10 of morphine now!
Oh, gee. Okay, all right.
Up, up, up, up. Just get in
there and hold the pressure.
Okay, get his femur stabilized
and down by his side.
Hurry! Hold pressure.
Get in there. Come on. Aah!
Corpses don't do that.
I need you to calm down,
sir. What are you doing to me?
Sir, can you tell us your name? Get
out of my face! Get your hands off!
You're hurting me! Do as he
says. Hands off, everybody.
But--
hands off.
Thank you.
What's your name?
Timothy miller.
Mr. Miller, w-we need
to get you into surgery.
I'm gonna be able to walk,
right? I gotta be able to walk.
Right now, we're just
trying to keep you alive.
Our cardiac wing is extensive
And well-equipped
with all of-
The first successful heart transplant
Was performed on september 7, 1896,
By dr. Ludwig rehn,
frankfurt, germany.
Okay.
Uh, excuse me. I don't
mean to interrupt. Uh--
Please inter--
I mean, just, uh,
Please update dr.
Dixon on the patient.
Uh, dr. Stevens is prepping
Your transplant patient for surgery.
They scheduled a-a-a
transplant six years ago,
But the heart was too
small, so they doubled up
And added a donor heart to
help his own heart function.
They did a piggyback--
heterotopic transplant.
Piggyback is the colloquial
name for the procedure.
Don't do that.
How about we... Take
you to meet the patient?
They tell my heart belonged
to a girl that was hit by a car
While she was hitchhiking.
And now when I'm driving, I
see hitchhikers all the time,
Always up ahead, just up ahead,
But when I get up
ahead, they're gone.
You're not buying
any of this, are you?
I should never have gotten the heart.
I-i don't understand
how the heart--
Navajos--we don't
even touch the dead
We don't touch their
bodies or belongings
Because the spirit clings there.
So to have part of a dead
body sewed into my chest is...
My friends who follow the old ways,
They begged me not to do
it. I should've listened.
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
You think you're haunted
by your transplanted heart,
But you're here for a new transplant.
No! That's what I'm
trying to tell you
I don't want it. I
don't want the new one.
I just want you to take the old one
out. Wait. That's just plain stupid.
Take the heart, man. Take
the heart if they offer it.
Did he just say he doesn't want
the donor heart? Yes, ma'am.
Clay bedonie, are you aware
that without a new heart,
You'll live a short life
attached to a machine
Before dying a sudden
and agonizing death?
See, that--that's
what I'm talking about.
Five parallel pulley
stitches per cut, then switch.
You sure I'm numb?
Toughen up.
When one of our residents gets
picked for the solo surgery,
One of us gets to scrub
in, so we have a goal here.
Focus on the goal. Solo
surgeries. Totally worth it.
Solo... Surgeries. Totally worth it.
Hello, hello. I need
someone to run these labs
And pull these x-rays, please.
Will do.
Hey, this looks like a
cool place to hang out.
What are you guys doing?
This is for interns.
It's--it's our hangout.
Go find your own.
Sorry.
Solo surgeries.
Totally worth it.
I don't want to live if I can't walk.
We'll do our best to save
the leg-- I'm homeless.
Walking is how I survive.
It's how i... Get from
one day to the next.
Marion street's safe
from 2:00 to 6:00 a.M.
And then I go over
the half-mast bridge,
And I hang there till 6:30
until the traffic hits.
And then I go over to belltown
and hang out on the waterfront.
And then the waterfront,
If it's trouble, then I
go back up to 4th street.
I'm homeless. I-i can't not walk.
I-i--what am I gonna
do? What am I gonna do?
Your injuries are critical.
If we n't get you to surgery--
Will your surgery make me walk?
Huh?
Then I don't want it!
Okay. All right.
You heard the man. The surgery's off.
I appreciate you trying
to advise me to do
What you think is best.
These are facts, not
opinions. What'm saying is--
He's trying to say he would
rather live a shorter life
That's unhaunted than
a longer one that is.
I'm not saying I agree. I'm just...
I'm just gonna stand over here.
That's a good idea.
The heart that you take out
of me, what happens to it?
It goes from the o.R. To
pathology to medical waste.
I need that heart back for ritual.
We have laws. There are rules.
Rules are rules.
Maybe there's a
compromise to be made here.
Uh, we could, I don't know,
Uh, give him back the old
heart to do the ritual,
Then give him a chance to live
By still putting
the new heart in. No.
No. It doesn't work that way.
I will still be haunted,
just by a new ghost.
There are rules. We have
laws, and there are--
Rules are rules and laws are laws.
No.
So that's it?
No surgery? You're
just gonna walk away?
I'm respecting the patient's wishes.
The patient's unstable
with an open wound.
Which we are packing.
This guy is circling the drain.
You cannot just walk away.
Don't tell me how to run
things in my e.R. Your e.R.?
We save lives here.
We don't just patch up
patients and leave them to die.
If you can't handle that,
Go back  the desert and leave us here
To do our jobs.
Dr. Torres, please tell me
you can figure out some way
Well, the right femur's toast.
So is the hip and half the pelvis,
But if I put some pins here
and maybe a plate here...
I mean, there are some
viable bone fragments.
We're not starting from nothing.
What do you think? I think it's wild.
All right, she wasn't talking to you.
It's her first day.
Could you not be so-
No, she's an intern. She
needs to learn her place.
I think it's a lot of hardware.
What the guy needs
is a whole new leg.
Well, maybe I can do that.
Yeah, I mean, it's kind of a puzzle.
I just need to figure out
What equipment I need
and--and how to pull it off.
Like lincoln logs. Uh, it's a
little more high-tech than that.
It's exactly like lincoln logs.
Okay, I need you guys to grab
Every piece of titanium we've
got in the hospital. Okay.
Um, I need the hospital
rules to specify the fact
That we must respect all religious
And spiritual beliefs
of our patients.
The rules?
Yeah, I'm asking
you to declare a rule
Of our department.
That we respect the
beliefs of our patients?
Yes. Isn't that just common courtesy?
Yes. Then why am I declaring it?
Um... Dr. Dixon doesn't
do common courtesy,
But she understands rules.
So if it's a rule, we're golden.
If not, we have a pissed-off patient
An apoplectic surgeon,
and none of those things
Makes for a successful procedure
On a faulty heart,
Not to mention the failure to woo.
You want me to announce it as a rule.
I'm here's a witness, you can
maybe raise your right hand,
Put your left one
On the "physicians' desk reference."
It's a rule.
Thank you.
Dr. Dixon, I'm cristina
yang. I'm a resident here,
And I've been focused on cardio
since I began my internship.
I'm certainly looking forward
to anything that you might--
Were the other ones
taken off my case?
Oh, uh, what other ones?
The black one, the male one,
the one with yellow hair.
Not that I'm aware of.
Then why are you talking to me?
What happened to hahn?
Wh-whatever made hahn
leave, it can be fixed.
U-unless she a was fired.
She wasn't fired, was she?
She's not coming back.
You don't know that.
She kinda does.
How?
Because she doesn't...
Look, it's just too...
We had a fight.
Oh, please. Meredith
and I fight all the time.
We still work together.
It's not like hahn was your
girlfriend or something.
Oh, my god.
She was your girlfriend?
Look, we hadn't...
Figured it all out.
Wait, so are you a lesbian now?
I don't know. Maybe
you were a once-bian.
Or a twice-bian.
Whatever. It's over.
Are you okay?
She's fine. Leave her alone.
I hit the titanium mother lode.
Hi.
Hey.
Oh, come on. Really?
Hey, lexie.
How are you?
Is, uh, everything going okay?
Why, did somebody say something,
Like I was doing something?
No, I'm just, uh, you
know, as, uh, I'm asking
As a person who's
sort of related to you
If there's anything
bothering you-- so
This is completely not
as a boss or a residen
Or a superior keeping
an eye on what I do
As a student in this program? No,
no, I'm just a compassionate person,
And I'm just wondering if you're
Channeling your tragic pain
into, uh, self-mutilation.
Are you a secret cutter? No.
Little grey, torres is, uh,
trying to set a world record
For most titanium rods
used in one patient. You in?
Little grey?
Little grey. Big grey.
That's how I tell you two apart.
Yeah, I'm in. I'll just be a minute.
Can't you people let
a guy die in peace?
Your, uh, vitals are slipping.
I'm not gonna lie to
you. That's not good.
I been through worse.
Yeah, I imagine you have.
Oh, don't get like that.
Don't look at me like
I'm some tragic hero
With a secret past.
You have a story.
We all have a story.
I took a turn in my life.
And I couldn't connect.
I lost...
I couldn't connect.
My life, it took a turn and...
And I just couldn't turn it back.
Guys, we need to shut
down for a few days.
People are starting
to get suspicious.
I was accused of
being a secret cutter.
So wear long sleeves.
Oh, I didn't realize we were
inviting more people here.
Are you kidding? A
secret intern society?
I'm all over that.
We, I still think we
need to take fewer risks.
Fewer risks?
Come on. You got a guard at the door.
You're using more local
anesthetic for three sutures
Than you would upstairs
for a chest tube.
Look, I get that you're doing
all this to learn new skills,
But you're only gonna learn
so much by being careful.
Uh, actually, I would disagree.
I think the only safe way to...
Who wants to stitch me up?
Oh, right here.
You gonna tell me
about death and die?
Nope. But I did talk to lexie for you
And now I need you to do
something for me. What's that?
I need you to tell mark
to keep his little sloan
Out of little grey.
Is he hitting on you?
No, not my little grey.
Lexie's little grey.
I don't know what's
going on with her,
But the last thing she needs
Is sloan going all man-whore on her.
So you need to tell
him to step away from
Little grey. All right.
I'll see what I can do
Little grey, derek. Little grey.
Did she, uh...
She say good-bye to you?
Nope.
Are you okay?
Do I look okay?
You look great.
Then I'm okay.
So...
There's a 9-day ritual
To--to undo
a haunting?
It starts with a 9-day ritual.
Okay.
Are you really gonna
waste nine days on this?
Dr. Stevens. Yes.
Why are you sonterested
in my haunting?
Can...
Can ghosts do things?
I mean, can they make
things happen in your life?
I--i've had two cases
with two patients in a row
That have really reminded
me of my dead fianc?-
Heart transplants
and l-vads and--
Could he be doing that? Could
he be bringing them to me?
Izzie, come on.
Is he here right now, your ghost?
I... I hate to ask, but...
Oh, you don't want
me in your surgery.
It's not that I think there's
something wrong with you.
It's just... I don't
need any extra ghosts
In my operating room.
Mr. Miller.
What does a guy have to do
To get a little peace
and quiet around here?
The fatigue you're feeling
is from the blood loss.
The queasiness,
the dizziness--
It's because you're
slowly bleeding to death.
What, are you trying
to scare him? No.
I'm trying to ascertain whether
he's suicidal or just defeated.
Mr. Miller, you
survived in the streets,
So I know you're a fighter.
That doesn't make me a fighter.
It makes me lucky.
How long you been out
there, 10 years, 20?
You're not in jail, you're not dead.
That's not luck. You're smart.
You gotta be smart to take
care of yourself on your own.
I guess.
This...
What you're doing
right now, mr. Miller,
Refusing surgery,
It's not smart.
There's a rehab center
not too far from here.
Medire takes care of
it. You could stay there.
Food, bed, long as you need.
Just let us operate.
Let us operate, and
we'll figure the rest out.
Wow. That's the fastest
I've ever seen anyone
Dissect through adhesions.
Uh, dr. Dixon, there
is a rule, uh, regarding
Giving medical waste to the patient.
Dr. Dixon?
What?
Uh, I was just saying
there is a rule,
An official, very,
very specific rule,
That in the event a
patient asks for their organ
Or body part back for any reason
Related to or involving
their cultural beliefs,
We must respect that
patient's wishes,
And return that organ to the patient.
That is the rule I
forgot to tell you about.
If I went down to
pathology right now,
Would they know about the rule?
Oh, the chief would know.
Uh, it's his rule. He declared it.
A rule's a rule.
Dr. Karev...
Make sure that...
We follow the chief's rule
And return the heart to the
patient after the surgery.
I'm going back to work now.
Clamp.
What the hell is that gooey thing
They're taking out of him?
Oh. The silent treatment.
Okay, if you're gonna be that way.
I'll just, uh...
I'll just stand here
and--and be quiet.
Okay, but that... That is disgusting.
I thought you were gonna be quiet.
You know, you're acting like
you don't want me to be here.
You know what I've wished for
every day since you've died?
I've wished that I
could see you again.
I'd have given anything
just to see you...
One more time.
Looking at you and knowing
that I can't touch you,
It's hurting me.
Izzie, you can touch me.
You're not real.
You can't be real.
So that means that I'm sick
Or something is wrong with
me, and I can't hope for that.
I...
I can't hope.
You're not real.
Izzie, I am as real as you
Or that gooey, disgusting
thing down there.
Touch me.
Izzie... Touch me.
I'll prove it to you.
No!
Why are you here?
Why?
I am here for you, izzie stevens.
Clamp.
Okay, that's it.
The donor heart is separated.
We have the cannulas
ready for bypass.
Next step is the l-vad.
Y--what--what
is that?
That's not right. That
can't be happening.
His heart's beating.
How is his heart beating on its own?
It... Can't be happening.
It shouldn't be happening.
That heart is beating.
It shouldn't be beating.
It sh-shouldn't be beating.
I've never seen a
reconstruction like this.
Well, I've never done one like this.
Here's hoping it works.
All right. I'm ready for the rod.
How are you guys doing up there?
A lot of hemorrhaging,
bleeding through the packing.
Try the fibrin sealant. Good
call. Thank you, dr. Shepherd.
How you doin' on that lac, little
grey? Good. Moving on to the next lac.
You finished already? Let me see.
Wow. Pulley stitches.
Nicely done.
Thank you, dr. Sloan.
So my heart...
It started beating by itself.
If it continues to
function like this,
You won't need an l-vad or
any other kind of machinery.
It's wonderful news.
It's very atypical.
Not for me. I'm finally free.
I'm not haunted anymore.
Your heart had six years to rest,
Which is... Probably enough
time for it to repair itself,
Which is why it
started beating again.
I've never seen this before.
I've read about it, but
I've never seen it before.
You have your beliefs. I have mine.
I don't have beliefs. I have science.
Science is a belief,
A belief in only what
you can see and touch.
I believe in more.
Just thought I'd stop in to
see how everything's going.
Well, I'm still several hours away,
But I may actually
pull this off--
Rebuilding a man's
skeleton from scratch.
And we just found out
that, uh, dr. Grey here
Can out-pulley stitch shepherd.
Oh, I wouldn't go so
far as to say that.
Excellent job, dr. Grey.
And excellent job of
teaching, dr. Yang.
Sir? Taking the time
to teach yo interns,
And they are retaining
that knowledge.
I haven't made my decision
yet on the solo surgery,
But you keep teaching like
that, and you're my one to watch.
Thank you, sir.
He's crashing. V-fib. Start c.P.R.
Push 1 of epi and charge
the paddles to 360.
right away
Clear.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
So what do you do now
with the haunted piece?
Do you bury it or...
Burn it. Actually, my tribe's
medicine man will burn it.
I'm not allowed to
even touch the smoke.
So does the not-touching thing,
Does that apply to
just the flesh or--
No, we don't touch their belongings.
We can cleanse jewelry, medals,
but fabric, bedding, clothes,
Books that were owned by the dead,
We burn all of it.
The spirit can cling to any of it.
Oh, no.
Your ghost...
You still don't have
anything of his, do you?
Time of
death--1922.
I built his bones.
You tried.
We all tried.
No, I didn't try. I did it.
I did my part. I built his bones.
I built his bones from scratch,
And you...
All of you, you were
supposed to keep him alive.
That is all you people had to do.
You just had to...
Keep his body breathing.
You just had to keep him safe
and--and breathing and living
Until I made his bones.
I made... I made his bones...
Until... Until I made his bones.
I made his bones.
I made his bones. Why
don't you guys go ahead,
And I'll help dr. Torres clean up?
Go call the morgue. We've got it. Go.
Everyone, clear out.
Uh, excellent job today, dr. Dixon.
Excellent... Rule following.
I only have one real area
of interest--the human heart.
I love it. I like its regularity.
I know everything there
is to know about it.
I like its predictability.
It has rules.
Every chamber has a function,
every function has a movement.
I like the color. It's comforting.
Are you familiar with
asperger's syndrome,
Dr. Bailey?
Uh, of course.
A significant impairment
during social situations...
I'm not good at cues like
sarcasm or condescension,
But I do know when
I'm being manipulated,
And I know when I'm
being made fun of.
I don't think I like
this hospital very much.
this hospital at all.
Ah, that lexie grey
Sure knows how to wrap
herself around a suture.
Mark, meredith has some concerns.
Well, that's not news.
About lexie.
Apparently lexie is... Fragile,
And getting involved with a superior
Might make her more fragile, so...
I was talking about her sutures.
Keep little sloan out of
little grey is my point. What?
Little sloan does
not enter little grey.
Are we clear?
Did you just say--
Okay, that's just
creepy and inaccurate.
Big sloan.
You heading home?
I love you.
I will always love you.
You own a piece of me.
So even though you'll be gone,
You will never be
forgotten, not by me.
I'm sorry we never got our chance.
I'm sorry we never...
Got to get married or have children
Or grow old together.
I wanted that so much.
I wanted to be your
wife morehan anything.
Why are you telling me this?
I'm trying to let you go
So that your soul can be at peace.
But I have peace, izzie.
I'm here for you.
Good-bye, denny.
I love you.
But good-bye.
I can explain.
I did not teach you the
parallel pulley stitch.
I can barely do that stitch myself.
Whatever you guys are
doing, shut it down.
Do not practice on
yourselves. That is insane.
Shut it down.
Iz?
I see you.
I've seen you all day.
I-i see you struggling.
And I know you don't want my help,
But let me help you.
Whatever it is, I can help.
So let me.
Will you burn this for me?
I hate how hard it is.
It's just, like, you
get attached to someone,
And then they work
their way into your life,
And then you wake
up one day-- suddenly
All you can think
about is their little..
Another round?
Oh, I'll get it.
Tell me the stories.
What stories?
The ones you won't let sadie tell me.
They're ancient history.
Humiliating and ridiculous.
Ridiculous is a grown man
telling another grown man
To stay out of a
woman's little--
You did it?
I did, those exact words.
I did it because...
It was nice to see you
sticking up for your sister.
I did it for you.
So now you owe me...
A story.
Okay, fine.
But you can never tell anyone, ever.
I'm--i'm sorry we
lost him, the patient.
I'm--i'm
sorry.
I don't need you to be sorry.
Okay. I don't need you to be sorry.
Okay. I
don't need--
All--all right. All
ri-- I don't need you.
The ties that bind us
Are sometimes impossible to explain.
They connect us
Even after it seems like
the ties should be broken.
Some bonds defy distance...
And time... And logic...
Oh, god. I...
I said good-bye. I b--
I burned the sweater.
Yeah, thanks for that, by the way.
I love that sweater.
You made me that sweater.
Oh, my god. Oh,
my god. Izzie--
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh,
my god. Stop freaking out.
You're not real. You're
not real. Hey, I told you...
You're not real. You are
not real. I'm here for you.
You are not real. You are not real.
You are not real.
Izzie, look at me.
Touch me.
You see?
I told you I was real.
Oh, god. Hey.
Because some ties are simply...
Meant to be.
www.tvsubtitles.net