Number one rule of surgery
is limit exposure.
Good.
Keep your hands clean,
your incisions small
and your wounds covered.
I've removed the tumor
and placed the catheters.
Now I'm going to flood
the abdomen with heated chemo.
It allows a greater
concentration of drug
to be delivered directly
to the affected area.
And the heat helps target
the cancer cells
while leaving the normal cells
virtually unaffected.
Start perfusion.
We'll place him in Trendelenburg.
Then reverse Trendelenburg
as we agitate the abdomen
to make sure that the chemo
really washes everywhere.
She saw me.
Now I can go.
- She's just getting started.
- I have a headache. I need coffee.
I have a cure for a headache
that doesn't involve coffee.
I'm leaving.
There's a seat right there.
Thanks.
I've never seen
a hot chemo lavage before.
- It's fascinating.
- I thought you were leaving.
The Chief asked me
to finish out my contract, which
has a few more weeks.
Number two rule of surgery...
Is when rule number one
stops working...
Try something else...
- What I said, I didn't mean.
You mean offering to trade Owen
like a horse or a baseball card
or a stale peanut butter sandwich
from your lunch box.
- It was thoughtless...
- Fine.
Fine.
Let's just forget about it.
Because sometimes
you can't limit exposure.
Sometimes the injury is so bad
that you have to cut
and cut big.
- If you report him...
- He's an alcoholic!
If you report him,
it'll be the end of his career.
You don't give people any room.
- Flaws are unacceptable to McDreamy.
- Don't "McDreamy" me.
McDreamy is being McAss.
He is an alcoholic.
How long has he been drinking?
- Since the holidays?
- You want to take notes?
So you can show it to the board so
they can offer you his job on the spot?
You want his job.
You know it and I know it.
I'm the head of neurosurgery.
I've a responsibility to this hospital.
- Admit you want to be Chief.
- I'm done having this argument.
I'm going to the board.
I'm reporting Richard.
Post-it.
- You can't call post-it.
- I am calling post-it
because I told my secret about
my friend to my husband...
Not the head of neurosurgery,
my husband...
Which I have to be able to do.
So the laws of post-it clearly prevail.
- This is wrong.
- Post-it.
- The Chief...
Fine. I won't tell.
Fine.
Damn it.
You just make me want to...
Izzie's coming home.
I have to tell Alex.
I won't go to the board.
I won't say a word.
Just think about what I said.
Okay.
Izzie's... Coming...
- Izzie's coming?
- Home.
Crap.
Izzie leaves, and Mark gets a kid,
and you two decide that
the best way to deal
is to get drunk
and mash your genitals together?
No freakin' way you get to judge us
or give relationship advice.
Besides, you were a total
dirty mistress, like two weeks ago.
Are we calling me a dirty mistress?
That was two years ago,
and his wife didn't have cancer.
Because I've only been with, like,
six guys in my whole life.
Alex and I... We've done it before.
That was recycling.
It was, like,
good for the environment.
Izzie's gone, I was horny,
she was there.
Crap. I am a dirty mistress.
God. You're gonna tell Derek,
and then Derek's gonna tell Mark
- that I'm a whore.
- I am not going to tell Derek,
and neither are you,
you're not gonna say anything.
We are keeping our mouths shut.
Izzie is coming home.
No one needs to know.
Know what?
S06E12: I like you so much better
when you're naked
There were no sterile
supplies in the OR last night.
Surgery came to a complete stop
for a full hour.
Central supply and maintenance
are understaffed,
and the autoclaves have been
breaking down. Now anything else?
- I want to help.
- I don't need your help.
The sterilizers are up
and running, so...
Not the hospital.
You.
You stopped operating.
You're not teaching anybody
but Meredith.
I'm wondering if...
If you need some help.
No shame in asking.
You know that.
You can help...
By doing your own job
and letting me do mine.
Anything else?
I'm done.
So I went to the trailer.
I don't live in the trailer anymore.
So...
Meredith called me and told me
you might be moving on.
Just wait.
I realize now
that I was wrong to blame you
for getting fired.
- I'm sorry. It wasn't your fault.
- I don't want to have some big talk.
I gotta go to work.
I have a pet-scan later, so maybe
I'll see you at the hospital?
Is everything okay?
I found some residencies
with open spots and applied.
They all just want to
make sure I'm stable.
One of them is close.
It's in Tacoma, so...
We'd be okay.
I could commute from here and...
I know that you don't want
to have some big talk, but
Seriously I have
to get to the hospital.
The place really sucks these days. You'd
be happy you don't work there anymore.
- Sorry.
- Don't be.
I am happy. I'm gonna work in Tacoma,
and it's gonna be awesome.
You're gonna be jealous.
- You're operating?
- I am.
- A whipple. That's big.
- I say, go big...
Or go home.
Excuse me, sir?
- You're taking dr. Bailey's whipple?
- Is that a problem?
Not at all.
I'm the resident on the case.
I'm thrilled to be assisting you.
I will be assisting you, right?
You can open.
That way, dr. Grey will be fresh
when she dissects the neck
of the pancreas from the portal vein.
- That's the hardest part.
- That's a fifth-year procedure.
It's what we've been practicing.
And I'm telling you, you're ready.
But if you don't think
you're ready...
I'm ready. I'm ready.
- What's going on?
- Hunt's got an MVC in here.
- Use a hand?
- What?
Can I help?
You know what you can do first?
You can make that stop.
Dude! Stop singing!
I'm trying to get you people
to understand
the seriousness of the problem.
I've lost my upper register completely.
Dr. Karev, this is Mr. Mafrici,
your consult.
I just need some antibiotics.
I open in "Tosca" in a week,
and he gave me bronchitis.
- I did not give this to you.
- Take a deep breath.
He teaches piano to children.
I can hear them hacking away
during their lessons, and then he comes
in the house and touches things.
Stop talking.
He's got decreased breath sounds.
He's gonna need an x-ray.
- Can you take him up?
- Page an intern. I don't have time.
Hunt took him up,
said thanks for your help.
You got time now?
- You're hot.
- You're hot, too.
No, you're... "hot" hot.
Okay. Thanks.
You have a fever.
- What is that?
- What?
- Oh, my God.
Pox. Pox.
You have chickenpox.
Turns out she loves Owen
and thought she came here to be all,
"Teddy and Owen," but there's me,
and now she's all pain
and threatening to leave,
- so I told her she could have him.
- What?
She's an amazing teacher, and
I'm happy again,
I'm in the OR and I'm feeling
like myself and...
And, of course, I didn't mean it.
I love Owen.
I love him. But that means that
I don't get to have her, so...
Maybe I meant it?
Here's the thing...
You can't talk like this.
It's, like, I get you...
But other people don't,
so you can't talk like this.
It's crazy. It's, like, if you tell
someone their baby is ugly.
They know it, you know it, everybody
knows it, but you don't talk about it.
But you're saying surgery, right?
Gun to your head, you would
choose surgery over Derek?
I am saying don't talk about this.
And don't talk about it to Owen.
That's the world-class specialist
you wanted me to see?
Little Grey has had
the chickenpox vaccine.
I snooped through your personnel file.
I on the other hand, have not
nor did I ever have them as a child.
- You're a pediatrician. How have...
- I am a pediatric surgeon.
I don't do little diseases
on little people.
I do big surgeries on little people.
This is ridiculous.
I'm going home.
You're not going anywhere.
You're highly contagious right now.
You leave this room, and you're gonna
touch doorknobs and elevator buttons,
and then you'll be
the outbreak monkey.
- I'm going to kill you.
- I love you.
Stop scratching, cause you're just gonna
make it worse, then you're gonna scar.
I gotta get my hands
on a body again, Mer.
I think I'm gonna get an offer
from Oregon, but I can't take it.
It's too far. I can't do that
to Alex. I gotta get this Tacoma thing.
You know what would help? A call from
Derek Shepherd, head of neurosurgery.
Talk to him.
- Talk to me about what?
- She's up a for a job in Tacoma,
and she wants you to call.
- It isn't even ranked in the top 20.
- But it close,
- and she can repair things with Alex.
- Fine. Have her give me the number.
I read the board.
The Chief is doing a whipple,
and you're scrubbing in.
- You can stop worrying. He's fine.
- He hasn't operated in months,
and his first surgery back
is a 7-hour procedure
with a 20% complication rate.
First you were worried
that he wasn't operating.
- Now you're pissed that he is.
- I don't trust him anymore.
Post-it.
He's fine. He's fine.
I thought it was infection.
Like pneumonia?
- That's one of the possibilities.
- What are the others?
The fluid could also indicate...
Karev made the diagnosis.
Let him talk.
Heart failure and cancer
could also cause
- this much fluid to occur.
- Cancer?
Would you have to remove my lung?
- He said cancer is only a possibility.
- I sing.
It's my entire life.
... Besides me.
What you meant to say was that
singing was your entire life
besides me.
You heard the Chief
is operating today?
Took my whipple
and is having Meredith Grey
do the pancreatic dissection...
A procedure that I performed
for the first time just last year.
The Chief's judgment...
Is not clear and rational.
There's nothing I can do.
You're the only one who can.
I performed
intraperitoneal hyperthermic
chemo this morning,
and I kept looking up into the gallery
to see if the Chief was there.
That was a big deal for me.
Anyway, he wasn't there.
And I don't know
why I thought he would show,
because the truth is...
He's gone.
And he's been gone a long time.
Arizona thought some work might take
your mind off your itching.
Scratching will take
my mind off of itching.
Take off my gauze paws.
She said that you'd say that,
and that I should say no.
So how about we start with the tibial
plateau fracture, room 22-40?
I'm an attending.
You're a resident.
As your superior, I'm ordering
you to take them off.
She said that you would say that, too.
Technically, I'm on her service today,
so she's my boss, not you.
We have the lisfranc fracture,
room 22-11.
Please let me scratch,
- just for five minutes,
- No. It'll scar.
I don't care. Scars are hot.
Scars are badass.
Scars are poetic.
I'm begging you, little Grey.
- Please don't call me little Grey.
- I'm in pain...
"down to the core of my being" pain,
"I'm going crazy" pain,
"scary, will this ever go away" pain.
Do you get that? Do you know what I...
Do you know what I mean when I say that?
Because this pain is
"need to scratch an itch
I can't scratch,"
"the pain of a thousand itches,"
and it's making me crazy.
Not "funny" crazy.
This is "bad" crazy, okay?
It's "dark" crazy.
It's "make a suit out of someone else's
skin" crazy. Pain, little Grey. Pain.
I had sex with Alex.
I had sex with Alex, which I regret,
Completely, because I am in love
with Mark. I didn't think.
But I'm scare that I can't handle
the daughter and the baby
- the "Mark's gonna be a grandpa" thing.
- Why are you telling me this?
I am in pain, too,
is what I am saying.
I get your pain.
Don't you see that?
I do feel your pain
because I am in pain, too.
I have pox between my butt cheeks.
Your "pain" does not begin
to compare to mine.
Get out.
Just out!
Out! Out! Out! Out! Out!
- What are you talking about?
- She's on this thing...
If you had to choose between
the thing you love...
Surgery... and the person you love
which would you choose?
You would choose Izzie? Cause you two
are gonna get back together.
Why do you have to choose?
Doesn't matter you just do.
Which one? Surgery or love?
- I want both.
- That's what I said.
- You can't have both.
- Why the hell not?
- Why the hell is he here?
I said he could be in here
- cause he's in the whipple, too.
- Whatever. Once again,
- you can't have both you've to choose.
- Choose what?
My petscan got pushed back an hour,
so thought I'd...
Join you for lunch.
Okay. That.
You have to give up that...
Learning the procedure,
tuning out the world until you get it,
like, you know,
doing the procedure is
the only thing that matters,
like if you don't get to do it,
you'll die.
- That's what you have to give up.
- For what?
- Love.
- Why?
- That's what I said.
- That's not the point.
You know you couldn't do it.
You know you'd choose the procedure.
Fine! If I had to choose, gun to
my head, I would choose surgery.
Thank you.
Is that so hard to say? I don't know,
why is it so bad to say that out loud?
Because it's crazy.
How? It's crazy.
Surgery... it's just a job.
It's just a job. It's the thing
you come home from,
not the thing you come home to.
And if you lose your job,
you get another one,
cause there's always another one. But
If you lose your love...
If you think
you're losing your love...
Then suddenly, nothing else matters.
This is what you guys
talk about during lunch?
I'm with them.
Love comes and goes.
Surgery doesn't.
Results are back.
You choose love.
Just did a perfect dissection
without lacerating the portal vein.
You gonna do that little
fist pump in surgery, too?
The tests showed a malignancy
on your left lung.
It's called pleural mesothelioma.
And it's a cancer that surrounds
the lining of your lung.
- So what, you... You cut out his lung?
- Best-case scenario,
we won't have to remove any lung
tissue except for the tumor.
- Did you hear that? That's good.
- I'm not deaf.
What's the worst-case scenario?
We get in there, and the damage is too
extensive, and we have to remove more.
- My whole lung?
- That's the worst-case scenario.
But, yes, it is a possibility.
But it's also possible they
won't have to remove any.
- So let's stay positive.
- Will you please shut up?
I can't take
your cheerful little voice
shoving positive thinking down my throat
when my life is basically over.
People do recover
from things like this.
- And then they go on to...
- What?
- Go on to what?
- Live.
I won't have a lung.
I'm a singer.
So you see my problem?
You can direct.
You can teach.
Like you?
I'd rather die than spend
two hours every day
listening to mediocre
music majors doing their scales.
I know that this is
a lot to take in,
and if you need time to talk
or get a second opinion...
I want my lung.
Dr. Altman...
I'm big...
Too big.
I don't fit in airplane seats,
and as Jeff is telling me, my feelings
don't always fit the situation.
If my food is overcooked
in a restaurant,
I get enraged.
I want to kill the waiter.
But I don't.
I politely ask him
to take my meal back
and bring it to me
the way I asked for it.
I spend my days
making myself smaller,
more acceptable.
And that's okay,
because at night when I go on stage,
I get to experience the world
the way I feel it...
With indescribable rage
and unbearable sadness
and huge passion.
At night, on stage,
I get to kill the waiter
and dance on his grave.
And if I can't do that...
If I all I have left
is a life
of making myself smaller...
Then I don't want to live.
I don't.
And believe me, honey,
you don't nt me to live.
Are you stealing sterile supplies?
I need sterile instruments.
I'm not gonna get caught
with my pants down cause
- this hospital can't get...
- I get it.
I want to do something...
Something I...
Think is...
I have a responsibility.
But I just...
So what's stopping you?
The other half
of the twisted sisters.
Is that what you call Meredith
and Cristina... The twisted sisters?
That fits.
So this...
This thing...
I could come out of it looking,...
Pretty bad...
Like I did it for the wrong reasons,
like I did it...
For myself.
In my experience,
nobody goes into a battle
cause they want to win
a purple heart.
You do the right thing,
and sometimes that gets you a medal,
and sometimes it gets you killed.
How do you know
it's the right thing?
When it's the best thing
for the most people,
the thing that...
Keeps the most people alive.
How you doing?
A little claustrophobic.
Focus on your breathing.
That always helps.
Alex, I have to know.
When Mer called, she said
you were moving on. Have you...
Moved on?
I slept with someone.
Damn it.
We'll get through it.
- Are you still there?
- I'm right here.
Can you hold my hand or something
so I know you haven't left?
I can't reach your hand.
I can hold your foot.
Foot is good.
Look, Derek, I'm busy.
I have a surgery in less than an hour.
You want me to drink that?
But I believe you will.
I'm gonna go,
and you're gonna drink it.
You're gonna try not to,
but in the end...
You'll drink it.
I also believe that this won't be
the first drink you drank today.
This tumor is huge.
I've never seen pleura this thick.
It's like a watermelon rind.
Damn it. I'm gonna have to get rid
of the lung, the diaphragm
and the pericardium with this tumor.
That's what I need to do.
That's what's advisable
for optimal survival.
But that's not what we're gonna do.
We are going to remove the visible tumor
and we are going
to treat the lung with
with intrapleural
hyperthermic chemotherapy.
Karev, find out what Bailey used
in the procedure this morning,
and gather everything that I need. Yang,
you're gonna help me remove this tumor.
This morning, Bailey said the hot chemo
lavage was only indicated
in abdominal surgery.
Sugarman at the Brigham has been
researching its applications
as it applies the pleural mesothelioma.
And he's a singer...
And he needs his lung.
You look like hell.
Chickenpox.
Stay back.
I'm contagious.
I had 'em when I was 6.
How was L.A.?
Addison nicked
one of the uterine arteries.
But she was able to fix it.
Sloan's okay,
and the baby's gonna be okay, too.
Good.
I slept with Addison.
I gotta tell Lexie?
It's Lexie. She's so good.
- How do you lie to a girl like that?
- Lie.
- Really?
- Really.
I hurt.
Here.
I got you covered, kid.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna help you.
That's amazing.
- No scar.
- Keep going.
Thank you. Thank you,
thank you, thank you,
You saved the lung,
the whole lung?
Now what?
Now the work really begins.
This is gonna be a long recovery,
but he should be fine.
Does it make me awful to say
that I'm just slightly disappointed?
I guess I was
sitting out here thinking,
now he's gonna be
like the rest of us, who
teach and direct
and do all the things
he finds so demeaning.
You know what's demeaning?
Loving a man, taking care of him,
doing his shopping,
making his meals,
making sure
his humidifiers are clean,
cause God forbid
his humidifiers aren't clean.
What's demeaning...
Is loving a man
who thinks so little of you.
He's got an army of nurses, so if
you want to walk out of here, you can.
We'll take care of him.
You could go.
I love him.
You should hear him sing.
Nobody sings that well.
He does.
See that stitch there? You just made
the dude diabetic for life.
Shut up. I'm trying to concentrate
until the Chief gets here.
Dr. Webber apologizes.
He got caught up in some sort
of administrative something.
So let's dig in.
Patient ready?
We are all prepped and ready.
Just waiting on you.
- Dr. Grey, care to open?
- Actually, I was gonna open.
Okay, sure.
Dr. Webber was going to let me do
the pancreatic neck dissection,
- so I've prepped.
- I don't believe you're ready for that.
I'll be doing it.
You're welcome to observe.
Go ahead.
10-blade.
I'm sorry you didn't get
a chance to do the procedure.
- Something came up. It happens.
- I'm not surprised about Richard.
You're not a dumb person, but,
you're acting like one.
I am not going to turn him in.
Tacoma passed on Izzie.
I did my best. Just too much history,
too many red flags.
If I went to the board,
they'd make me Chief.
The first thing I'd do
is hire Stevens back.
It's your choice.
It's up to you.
That should be me.
Don't be jealous.
They're just friends... Best friends.
I had the chickenpox,
and I told her I hadn't because...
I find her miraculous...
Breathtakingly stunning.
Just...
I can't stop looking at her.
And I was afraid, with the ooze
and the fevers and the
scratching...
I wanted to stay
in the sexy part of things. So,
So I lied to my girlfriend,
and now...
He makes scratching look sexy.
He makes everything look sexy.
So you get it.
You didn't have to do that,
but you did.
- You get it.
- What are you talking about?
I choose surgery over a guy.
I'm not gonna apologize
for it, especially to you.
You didn't have to save his lung.
The right thing would've been
to remove it. But the patient was clear
that he didn't want to live
without his gift,
and you get that.
I choose my gift.
I want to be great,
and I want to learn from you.
I choose my gift.
- How'd your surgery go?
- Great.
See? And you were all worried.
You're a rock star. Speaking of which,
Do you know if Derek
has talked to Tacoma yet?
No, I don't.
Good. Cause I just got my scans back,
and they're really good.
And so it would be great
if he could mention
that I am officially not dying
of cancer when he talks to them.
I'm gonna get this job, Mer.
I'm gonna get this job
and I'm gonna get Alex back
and I'm gonna be myself again.
I can feel it.
I'm gonna go get Derek and show him
my scans before he calls Tacoma.
I'll go tell him... Derek.
And you go tell Alex.
Okay.
Okay, fine.
You can go to the board.
Just...
Sorry. Car crash came in.
I got here as soon as I could.
That's okay.
It gave me time to get drunk.
So what's the occasion?
I thought Beth was an idiot.
If we're being honest here...
I didn't know that we are.
Maybe not an idiot,
but just not good enough for you.
So how long you been here?
I'm sure that it
wasn't easy for her...
But do you know
what she said to me once?
She said that once you guys
were married, she was done.
She was done teaching and she was
just gonna start making babies.
And I remember thinking to myself,
Does Owen know
you have, like, zero ambition?
And then there's Cristina,
who is exactly the opposite.
It would actually be funny
if it wasn't so just...
Not funny.
I get it.
She... She is beautiful
and talented and kind of amazing.
She's right. I get her.
I'm calling you a cab.
Can I get a cab?
- Come on. Let's get you home.
- But she was willing to trade you...
For me.
If I stayed,
she said I could have you.
How was your surgery?
It was good.
It was fine.
It was...
Here. Want to see?
I'm so...
I'm so glad.
- It's like it never happened.
- Yeah, but it did.
It all happened, Iz.
You got cancer, and we got married,
You died and you lived again...
And you...
You left, then you came back.
And we got through it.
I got through it.
And I'm on the other side.
I love you so much,
and I...
Till I met you,
I used to think
I just wasn't a good guy.
Growing up with my family,
That's what they told me.
But now...
After all of it,
I know that I'm a good man.
And I thank you for that,
because I know now that I'm good enough
not to deserve this...
Not to have to feel like this...
Not to love you so much
that I almost hate you.
I deserve someone who will stay.
I'm happy you're okay.
And I'm happy about your job.
And I want you to go...
And be happy and not come back.
I'm sorry about the surgery.
- I got caught up with paperwork...
- You don't have to apologize.
You don't have to apologize
for anything.
In surgery...
the healing process begins
with a cut...
An incision...
the tearing of flesh.
Where have you been?
You just disappeared.
I left you, like, ten messages.
Are you drunk?
Wait. What? What? What?
You make me sad.
You think that surgery
is gonna make you feel.
You think that a successful career
is gonna make you happy.
You think you know things.
You know things,
and nothing else matters,
no one else matters.
People do matter. I matter.
We...
We matter.
So you don't get to toss me aside.
I won't let you.
We have to damage
the healthy flesh...
in order to expose the unhealthy.
It feels cruel...
- ... How did, Sloan's surgery go?
- I slept with Addison.
Thank go
Cause I slept with Alex.
Oh, I was feeling so...
You know how I was feeling...
Which is why this is great.
You know, we're...
We're even.
We kind of canceled each other out.
You slept with Karev?
While I was dealing with
my sick daughter?
While I was hurting?
You weren't hurting.
You were sleeping with Addison.
You broke up with me,
left me...
And just...
I can't even look at you right now.
Do you know what it took
for me to make this happen?
Please tell Derek I'm really sorry.
This isn't about Derek.
It's about me. It's about us.
You don't just walk away
from people.
- You don't just throw people away.
- I can't, Meredith. Okay? I can't
be here. Please.
Please try to understand.
I have to start over.
I need to start over, okay?
Please don't go.
This is your home.
No, it's not,
not anymore. It's just a place
I worked, and I can do that anywhere.
But it works.
You risk exposure...
What are you doing? You'll...
You'll get the chickenpox.
So... I get the chickenpox.
For the sake of healing.
And when it's over...
once the incision has been closed...
you wait.
Did you see him before he left?
I didn't think it'd make it easier.
For him or for you?
It's the best thing for him.
You knew that.
It was the only thing.
Let's not pretend
you did this for him.
It's just you and me here, Derek.
You did this for you.
In the choice
between surgery and love,
you chose surgery.
- You chose ambition today.
- So did you.
You knew he wasn't ready to
go back into the OR
But you wanted to do
that surgery so badly,
you were willing to overlook it.
We're the same.
You wait...
And you hope
that your patient will heal...
That you haven't in fact...
Just made everything worse.
Mc Dreamy Team
www.forom.com