Previously on Grey's Anatomy...
- He's gone.
- It's over...
So over.
Dr. Burke handed in
his letter of resignation
- two weeks ago.
- I was named chief resident.
I would've made
an excellent chief resident.
- We're breaking up.
- A breakup kiss.
A breakup kiss.
I'm lexie. Lexie grey.
I'm your sister.
Why are you avoiding me?
I'm all alone in a forest,
all alone in the forest, George.
Where are you?
I love you, too.
In the hospital,
we see addiction every day.
I feel this, uh, this...
this exhalaration.
It's like I finally figured it out.
You know what it's like?
It's like I was sleeping,
and it's like I woke up.
And it's just...
It's just amazing.
It's shocking how many
kinds of addiction exist.
This is the best breakup ever.
I don't know why we didn't
break up a long time ago.
- What are you doing?
- Sleeping.
- No. No sleepovers.
- Yes, please. It's 3:00 in the morning.
We agreed. No sleepovers.
Broken up people don't sleep over.
Sex only. It's the only part
of the relationship that works.
I know. Why screw it up
with everything else?
Dinner, conversations.
You're mocking my severe
emotional limitations.
I could live without conversation.
I could live without meal or sleepovers.
We shouldn't have sleepovers
because you snore.
But mockery? Mockery, that's the XXX.
Okay, sex and mockery it is.
It would be too easy
if it was just drugs
and booze and cigarettes.
She said she loved me,
and you know,
my dad, he c--
Oh, god, he loved her.
And you know,
when he died then...
I shouldn't have gotten married.
I think the hardest part of kicking
a habit is wanting to kick it.
I mean, we get addicted
for a reason, right?
I thought it was right,
but it wasn't.
- It's not.
Often, too often...
things that start out
as just a normal part of your life
at some point cross the line
to obsessive...
compulsive...
- ...out of control.
- I...
I gotta tell her.
I have to tell her
the marriage is over.
It's the right thing to do.
Did you see how I walked
out of here all determined?
It made me proud.
It's the high we're chasing,
the high that makes
everything else...
fade away.
He loves me, too.
- What do you think of the board?
- Good. It looks good.
- Did a good job.
- I didn't do it.
I'm delegating.
I am being a delegator.
I'm doing it all different,
making time for my wife.
Yeah? She talking to you yet?
She will when she sees
I'm a delegator.
- I should move that surgery up there.
- Junkie.
Right. It's good.
That's fine.
Okay. I'm delegating.
Being a delegator.
- What's wrong with the chief?
- He's a junkie.
Him? You're the one
who looks all strung out.
- I'm just tired.
- Let me guess.
You are back together, and you've been
up all night doing the horizontal salsa.
Mambo. Horizontal mambo.
Meredith and I, we're justriends.
Sexy friends?
You're the worst, most juvenile
human being I've ever met.
You know the first step to recovery
is admitting you have a problem?
How many nurses have
you slept with this week?
That's not a problem, man.
That's an adventure.
- it is beautiful.
- I know. It's a belgian flip round pro.
- What do you want?
- What do you got?
Next time I get a projectile vomiter,
I could lose your pager number.
You can do better than that.
Surgeries, baby. Preferably cardio.
Are these all wedding gifts?
Yes. She's giving them away.
I have dibs on the mixmaster.
I'm not giving you the mixmaster.
The tradition is
you're supposed to return them.
Well, burke registered
for this crap.
Now I'm the one stuck dealing with it.
So i'm using it
for professional gain.
- You're ready to part with this?
- She's not. I want it.
I am if I can help on the rhomboid
flap in your next mohs defect repair.
Come to daddy.
- You steal this stuff?
- Make her give me something.
- Give her something.
- Give me the mixmaster.
Face it.
You have nothing I want.
Would you look at the residents.
Big, snazzy residents,
standing around
playing with housewares.
Turn a blind eye and
the soup tureen's yours.
Four!
Take this mix!
Hey! Take the mixmaster
and all this crap and
put it in my locker.
Carnage in the pit.
My day's improving.
Follow.
We're not gonna round?
Carnage trumps rounds, three.
Write that down.
Carnage always trumps rounds.
Hey. I know.
I never made it home last night.
But I got swamped with paperwork
and fell asleep in an on call room.
I need to talk to you
when you have time.
I have no time. I'm out of time.
This chief resident
thing is kicking my ass.
Later, then. Tonight, when we're alone?
Is it serious?
what do we got?
A gas main blew in
an apartment building.
Five injured, some badly.
Excellent.
Horrible. It's horribl sad.
Marla kristler,34-year-old female,
abdomen blown out, skull fracture,
third-degree burns over
at least 40% of her body.
Okay, I got this. Open O. R. Two.
Page Dr. Shepherd.
Torres, triage the rest.
Yes, sir. Yang, you're with the chief.
- Go.
- Oh, thank you.
Uh, one, four, come with me.
what about us?
Uh... go help bailey in the clinic.
my wife--she came in in
another ambulance. Is she here?
- Where-- where'd they take her? -Yeah, yeah.
She'll be going straight to surgery.
- Sir, are you injured?
- No. My son!
18 months old,contusions,possible head
injury. B.P. And pulse are elevated.
karev!
- I'm supposed to be on plastics.
- I'll take it.
I called karev. You're
with the kristlers.
Wh-what about me?
oh, you up late last night?
You look a little tired.
Perhaps you should sit this one out.
I'm fine.
Not up late. Went to bed early.
- hello, mister...
- roche. Archie roche.
Age 60, second-and third-degree burns over chest and upper
abdomen, facial contusions and possible shoulder fracture.
One minute I'm reading the sports section, the next I'm flat on my back
looking up at a hole in the ceiling right into dave and marla's apartment.
These burns should be debrided
while he gets worked up.
All righT. We'll do a trauma
series and shoulder films.
- Stevens.
- Got it.
where's your pain?
Just promise me you'll take
care of marla and the baby, okay?
Are they your family, sir?
They might as well be.
how close to the explosion was he?
Oh, we were, uh, we were in the living
room, his mom was in the kitchen.
The gas line blew?
I-I think it was the stove.
All right, we're gonna run
some tests on your baby.
Kav, I'm going into surgery
with the chief. Keep me posted.
Marla and david are friends.
I was just leaving when the--
when the kitchen blew up.
The blast knocked me into a wall.
Have you seen this?
Grim.
You guys look grim.
Uh,clark,we need to get a C.T.
Internal bleeding?
I was on my way to work.
um, hey, I need a resident
to help me out in the clinic
to oversee the new interns
while I'm workinon this patient.
No, I'm sorry. I can't help.
You can't help?
The clinic is voluntary, bailey.
I'm not gonna force any residents to go in
there with this much going on in the pit,
but you can have as many
interns as you need, okay?
And tell Dr. Kent he's gotta
find himself another O.R.
The chief's taking his.
I want the waffle maker.
Haven't we already covered this?
Yeah, but now I got something you want.
Oh, yeah? What?
Hello.
I'm jane burke.
Dr. Burke's mother. How nice to see you.
Uh, I'm looking for Dr. Cristina yang.
Yang, yang? Let me see.
Dr. Yang...
I'll page her, but I
think she's in surgery.
I'll wait.
- Waffle maker?
- Fine.
- What's the 9-1-1?
- Mama is here.
I'm working with callie.
Callie. Gotta find george.
- Your mother?What?
Mama. Mama is here.
Seen george, mer? He's your intern.
Oh, burke's mother.
Yeah, make the synapses fi a
little more quickly, meredith.
You know, I was just with a patient.
I'd be very happy to go back there.
No, no, no. You have to help me.
I'll help for the mixmaster
and george's current location.
- Dr. Yang, you scrubbing in?
- Yes, sir. Absolutely.
Just get rid of her, okay? Politely.
- What?
- George!
come on, B. It's okay.
Brian, stop crying, baby. I
can't--I can't think, baby.
I'm--why won't
he stop crying?
Hey there, brian.
whoa, you're a big boy.
Do you work out, huh?
You take care... take care of yourselF.
Dr. Karev.
C.T. Results.
Should I page shepherd?
No, he's in surgery. Let me take a look.
- What do you see?
- Uh, there's nothing acute.
Acute? Nothing?
Yeah, I'm gonna--I need to
run a couple more tests, okay?
schedule an M.R.I.
- Why?
- Because I said so, nancy drew.
Just do it.
Rooms one and seven are private and should be used for private
conversations with patients, not for closed-door socializing.
All carts are setup the same.
Memorize where everything is.
Will we be able to do
procedures on our own?
No. You are interns.
All procedures will be discussed
and overseen by an upper level.
All charts will be signed
out by an upper level.
And all patients will be looked
at by someone other than you!
And what if--ooh!
I'm sorry.
Uh, I, uh, sorry.
What if we can't find anyone?
Mrs. Burke.
What a surprise to see you here.
Are you visiting someone?
You're the maid of honor.
Miss grey.
That's me.
When you stood up in front of preston's
friends and loved ones and you said,"
it's over. It's over. It's so over,
were you trying to smash the hopes of the
best man, or were you just trying to be funny?
I--
because making light of that
situation would be inappropriate.
And to use that moment to send
a message to your boyfriend...
well, that'S... selfish.
So were you being inappropriate,
or were you being selfish?
I, uh... am, uh...
I ologize for that, mrs. Mama, ma'am.
I'm just gonna go. Okay.
- Miss grey?
- Yes, ma'am.
When you report back to cristina, would you
tell her, please, that i am waiting for her
and that I will
continue to wait for her?
Yes, ma'am.
Sorry.
Any news on marla?
My neighboR.
I promise, as soon as I hear
something, I'll, uh, give you an update.
Crap.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
I'm really sorry.
3-part proximal humerus fracture.
He's gonna need a percutaneous
reduction and internal fixation.
That boy of
theirs--brian-- gorgeous.
Sometimes they're
not-- kids.
Sometimes they're ugly.
You ve any kids, doctor?
Not that I know of.
Not married either, are you?
I'm afraid I haven't found
anybody who will put up with me.
Well, get on the stick.
Don't do like I did.
Don't be a bachelor your whole life.
You can only play the field for so long.
Then suddenly one day, your
whole life passes you by,
and those parts aren't
working like they used to.
They have medicine for that now.
They don't have medicine for
that "all alone" part, now do they?
No, I suppose not.
You got some pretty ones right here.
Oh, I'm off the market, Mr. RochE.
I--I'm very
happily married.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry.
You can't tell her.
Wh--
we decided.
I'm supposed to tell her.
I have to tell her tonight.
No, I know. You can'T.
You just--you
can't, okay?
I'm working with her. She's my boss.
Damn it!
Maybe it'll just work
itself out if we wait.
You'll grow apart.
- Izzie- - she's been
working long hours.
Maybe she's avoiding you.
Maybe she's having an affair.
- Izzie- -
don't tell her.
How long would you suggest I
wait until I tell her about us?
I don't know.
At least until she's
not in such a bad mood.
A week? A month?
I'm sorry.
But--well, then, you
know, we can't, uh...
I know.
Then you better walk away.
I better walk away.
Yeah, I really better walk away.
So george has clark in line for his C.T.
- Grey.
- Yes.
Okay, I need you to
work in the clinic, grey.
- Well--
- no, no.
Before you open your mouth and tell me all the
reasons why you can't, just--just let me say this--
i need this, because I have
idiots-- you understand me, grey?
Idiot interns are down there in my clinic, a
clinic dripping with my blood, sweat and tears,
grey, and I am not convinced-- not at all convinced--
that they will not burn it down with their ineptitude.
Look, no, I'm not telling,'cause I-I understand
I do not have the authority to tell.
So I'm asking... nicely.
Okay, I'm just saying, if I ever did anything
for you, like, I don't know, save your life...
if you ever felt you owed me a debt of
thanks, now is when I'd like to collect.
Please.
Oh, no.
Hey, are you working down hertoday?
- Uh, I don't, um, know.
- Great.
Well, we have no idea what we're doing.
Plus, I was really hoping we'd
get a chance to speak. So...
yay.
Yay.
I can't believe this.
This is surreal.
- You claustrophobic?
- No, I'm not claustrophobic.
It's just, I was on my
way to work, you know?
I was on my way to work and i stopped at a friend's
house, and the next thing you know, I'm in a cat scan machine.
It's like...
how did this happen?
Dr. Karev.
lab work?
it's crazy, isn't it?
Stay here. Stay in this
room and do not leave.
Do not leave that man
alone with that child.
***
Dr. Yang, was that Dr. Burke's mother
I saw in the waiting room earlier?
Mrs. Burke is here?
I don't think-- I
wouldn't know, sir.
Okay. How are we doing
up there, shepherd?
Good. She looks good from my end.
That's the best part about
the job, don't you think?
Giving good people second chances.
Believe me, I know. I get it.
But, you know, it's life. It happens.
You know, you're going down one path, and
all of a sudden, then you realize, like,
oh, no, no, no, this is
the-- this the wrong path.
This is...
no, this isn't the path for me.
And--and it's-- and it's good because you
learn and you realize that you can handle it.
And you can.
You can handle this. You...
Clark.
Clark!
Clar--code blue. We need
a crash cart in here.
Chief.
The 1 year old-- brian kristler?
He's strung out on meth.
- What?
- Yeah, it was a meth lab that blew up.
This woman and her husband
are running a meth lab.
Oh.
clear.
***The joys of surgeondom.
Saving the lives for those
who deserve it the most.
Tell Dr. Torres to follow
exposure protocol for children.
Tell her I am counting on
her to take care of this.
Got it
sure you don't want page somebody to
take over so you can go handle that?
I'm trying to get back
with my wife, derek.
In order to get back with my
wife, I have to learn how to--
delegate.
Dr. Torres can handle this.
- They were shooting him up with-
- no, they weren't shooting him up.
When you cook meth, the fumes, they
coat the walls, the floors.
The baby walks around, crawls around, puts its
hands in its mouth, it gets in his bloodstream.
God. Okay, um, call the police and
social services. I'll spread the word.
Wait, what about the dad? He's
still in therewith the kid.
You call the police and social services.
You let them take care of the
dad. You take care of the baby.
Sloan.
We got a situation.
You're doing a fine job.
You were acting awfully odd
before, had me a little nervous, but--
Mr. Roche, I'm gonna ask you a question.
I don't want you to be offended by it, but
the answer could affect your surgery.
Fine. Fire away.
Are you a crystal meth
user? You're kidding, right?
He's, like,60.
No judgment, sir. All I
need's a yes or no answer.
Crystal what? It's a drug, sir.
Um, it's addictive and very dangerous.
Well, unless you put it in
my blood pressure medicine, I
- I never touched the stuff.
What's going on?
The kristlers had a meth
lab in their apartment.
It's what caused the explosion.
Marla and dave had a drug
lab in their apartment?
No. Impossible.
Absolutely not.
I've known those two
for five--five years.
We go on picnics, to ball games.
I babysit for them.
I babysit for drug dealers?
o'malley! what happened?
- He coded.
- He coded?
Coded, out of nowhere.
Heart stopped. Coded.
- Probably a drug addict.
- What?
That's what I came here to tell you.
That fire that he was in, it
was a meth lab explosion.
He could have
cardiomyopathy from meth usE.
That would explain it.
Oh... it's a miracle I got him back.
Wait, you ran the code
yourself? Where's grey?
She's covering in the clinic.
What the hell is she doing in the clinic?
I thought I told you to take interns.
I didn't want interns.
Sorry about that.
Some things, o'malley, some things
just don't need to be told.
How about here? Does it hurt here?
Weird.
It feels weird?
No. That lady is staring
at me... or my fat.
Oh, don't worry. She's staring at me.
I'll be right back, okay?
well?
How'd surgery go on the mom?
Yeah, she'll live. Whatever.
Oh, I tried. I trieD.
Mama is not budging, and
she is very scary.
Yeah, obviously.
What does she want?
Did burke send her?
I don't know. I mean, you have to go.
You have to go deal with mama.
Just go get it over with and then when
you're done, come back and tell me all about it
because I could really
use a pick-me-up.
Okay, mama showdown is
not for your enjoyment.
Besides, my patient is stable and until
I'm paged, I'm gonna stay right here.
- she keeps staring at us.
- I know.
Make her stop.
- You make her stop.
- You're her sister.
I'm an only child. You're her resident.
if you have time to stare, you have time
to get me coffee, so move, move, move.
Two, stay.
Now see?
If you could just do that with mama...
mrS. Burke!
I don't think I know you.
I'm george o'malley.
I'm a friend of burke'S.
I was burke's guy.
Hi, george o'malley-- burke's
friend, burke's guy. Please sit.
I guess I have a minute.
You know one time he let me live on his
sofa when I had no place else to stay?
How is he? Is he... okay?
He's preston.
He's a gentleman.
And so... he doesn't
lik to talk about it.
And I just really don't
know what to say to him.
Maybe, uh... I don't know.
Maybe you can tell him
that he dodged a bullet.
I mean, marriage is...
once you're in, you're in.
Burke is smart, you know?
He didn't make a mistake.
'Cause it's a mistake that, you
know, it's hard to take back.
Which, even if you want
to take it back, you can't.
So you can tell him that.
Once you're in, you're in.
Make sure you have that engraved on
your wedding ring when you get married.
Oh, I'm already married.
You're already married?
George o'malley-- burke's friend, burke's
guy-- staying in a marriage out of obligation?
That's no way to live.
That's no way to love.
But I think you know that.
I do.
Sometimes I do.
Oh, your timing could not have been
more perfect. Where are we going?
What do you mean, where are we going?
You paged me, right?
- I did.
- Good. So on call room?
You know, I was thinking maybe
we could, uh, go to the cafeteria.
Thought you might be hungry.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Derek, we agreed--
"s" and "m" only.
- "S" and "m"?
- Sex and mockery.
Right,"s" and "M.
- So you're eating lunch?
- I am.
- Want to come?
- No.
Meet me in the lobby at 8:00.
- And eat your dinner first.
- Yeah, great. Perfect.
that's a really big needle, man. Do
you have to use such a big needle?
His I.V. Came out,and
he needs to be hydrated.
- Okay, okay. Look, I'm--
shh. -it's all right
Look, I'm just--I'm freaking
out a little bit here.
I mean, do you think you could
get me an update on my wife?
Your wife has a crater in her abdomen,
so even if she does survive surgery,
it's gonna be a
long, hard, painful recovery.
she's gonna be okay, right?
I mean, she's gotta be okay.
Wh--brian, please, sweetheart, look
at me. Brian, okay, stop crying.
Brian, please. Brian, stop crying!
He can't stop crying!
okay?
He can't stop crying because
his nervous system is shot.
He can't stop crying because his brain and his
heart and his renal system are all compromised.
He can't stop crying because he's in
withdrawal from crystal meth, you son of a bitch.
no, no. That's impossible.
He wasn't in the room
when we were making it.
It was all over your apartment, okay?
I tested him'ause i
smelled it on his skin.
I love my son.
Okay, we--we were
broke. I lost my job.
And I'm a good dad,
and I love my family.
Well, now you can love
your family from jail.
I'm sorry.
Dr. Torres.
- Yeah, chief.
- Yeah, chief"?
Is it that you don't know what's going on in
my hospital, Dr. Torres, or that you don't care?
Um, I'm sorry. I guess I don't know.
I delegated the meth
lab situation to you.
And now one of youresidents has
been attacked and a baby is missing.
I don't understand.
I told karev to take--
I don't want to hear
any of your excuses.
Finish up here.
You better hope that baby shows up.
I think you're a good chief resident.
what?
I know--I know that you've
been having a hard time with it,
and--and this thing with the
baby... clearly it's not an easy job,
and I think you're
doing a good job at it.
I can take it from here.
- What?
- Get out of my O.R.,Stevens.
Now!
So the happy little family makes meth.
There's no such thing as a happy family.
What's with her?
Well, mama burke is here,
and we don't know why.
My guess is that she's
here to kill cristina.
She's hovering again.
If you're done with the charts, go
fold something, like, you know, sheets.
What are you lookin'at?
Don't look at her.
Your sister. She's hot.
I'm an only child.
don't talk to me about lexie.
Oh, the police want to talk to me.
You know,
all I want to know is why she's herE.
Is that too much to ask?
he's not returning
my phone calls anymore.
He's doing his best.
Do you think... do you think
she really loved him-- cristina?
I-I think she loved him
the best that she knew how.
And that would not have
been enough for you either?
No.
It wouldn't have been
enough for me either.
So you would've ended it, too?
Well... burke and I
are-- are built differently.
He's stronger than I am.
He was strong enough to...
and, um, we're not built the same.
honorable men are all built the same.
And you think I'm an honorable man?
Do you know when to walk away?
Do you know when not
to take less than you deserve?
If you do, then you're an honorable man.
When you got injured in the fire, the shock to your body combined with the drugs and the damage--
your heart seized up,
and you went into cardiac arrest.
You're also bleeding internally,
so you need to stay for observation,
which means that you are probably
about to go into withdrawal.
But you can't leave because it is still
quite possible that you'll need surgery.
You got any good news, Dr. O'malley?
I wish I could say yes.
Come on.
Where are you?
Damn it!
How's the surgery on the old guy?
Fine.
Callie?
Damn it. I can't talk right now.
I have to find a baby.
Are you okay?
A baby was lost... on my watch.
I am chief resident.
I am responsible.
And the chief,
he gave this to me, and I blew it.
And--and now a baby's missing.
So no, I'm not okay.
No.
No, you are not okay.
Plus, I think...
I think my husband's having an affair.
well, if that's true, he's an idiot.
and if that's true,
you need to talk to him.
You know, as an alternative
to destroying your career.
Um, Dr. Grey...
I was wondering, do you know
where the thermometers are?'Cause--
do you really not know where
the thermometers are, lexie?
Or are you just looking
for an excuse to talk to me?
I-- simple question, lexie.
Are you an idiot or a stalker?
Okay.
that was a mean thing to say.
I'm aware of that because I'm
generally not a me but I'm a person
who just doesn't want to know you.
And you are a person who's
making that very difficult.
So please, just stop making
it so difficult for me to not know you.
Okay?
brian, oh, my god.
Please, wake up, baby. Please.
Mr. Kristler.
He won't wake up.
He was shaking, and then
he just--he just-- he won't wake up.
Let me take him, Mr. Kristler.
No, I love my baby.
I don't want to leave my baby.
It sounds like he had a seizure.
- Okay, please let me-
- I don't want to go to jail.
You don't want him to die, so
if you love him, please let me take him.
I'm sorry! Let me take him.
Baby, please.
**a stroke.
You can yell, you know?
Not my job anymore.
I'm just saying, you can if you want.
I-I deserve it.
Oh, you do deserve it.
You do deserve, Dr. Karev, to be chastised for your stunningly poor decision making.
You--you've certainly earned a-a reprimand for your unbelievably destructive tactical error.
You got in the face of a drug dealer?
You got in the face of a drug
dealer before the police had arri--
you got in the face of a known felon while his 1-year-old child was still in the room?
Are you stupid?
Are you without intelligence?
Because I know you were
taught better than that.
I taught you better than that,
Dr. Karev.
Gettin'in the face of a drug dealer.
Fool.
Thank you.
Oh, no. Thank you.
I am nice person.
Okay, I-I am.
And... i don't know what
it is that I did to you,
but, you know, we have the same dad.
So I was just thinking
that a simple conversation--
we don't have the same dad, lexie.
You and I, we do not have the same dad.
My dad disappeared when I was
5 years old, and I never saw him again.
Does that sound like
the daddy you grew up with?
I cked a man out of my
bed in the middle of the night--
the world's most perfect man,
who loves me, and I can't let him.
And it doesn't take
a shrink to figure out why.
Because our dad chose you.
So I'm sure you are
a very nice girl, lexie.
But I hope you can understand, you're not a girl I ever wanted to have to know.
I never even tried drugs until I was 30.
Stupid.
I'm so stupid.
I went to a party, and there was all
this-- this meth floating around and...
I just figured, what the heck?
Once won't kill you.
And then-- and then it's more than once, then it's all you can think about, and then--
then you're outside your dealer's
house at 7:00 in the morning.
This isn't me.
It--it isn'T. I'm not this guy.
I'm--I'm not this guy.
I'm not this guy.
clark?
hello.
It took you long enough.
Yes.
I came for preston's key.
I'd like to pick up some of his things and the necklace I ge you for the weddinG.
Of--of course.
just, uh, leave it under
the mat when you're ne.
And I wanted to say I'm sorry.
I... I've come to know you, I think.
And what you love even more
than preston is being a surgeon.
You are planning to continue with cardiothoracic surgy like my son, am I correct?
Yes.
So I'm sorry you lost the man you love.
But more than that,
I'm sorry you lost your teacher.
With him by your side...
you could've become
a brilliant heart surgeon.
I see.
You're a strong woman, cristina.
I respect that.
I wish I could've been
born at another time.
I might be more like you.
So I shall leave the key under the mat.
Uh, can you take the gifts?
There are all these wedding gifts,
and I can'T...
can you--can you please take them away?
Of course I can.
He's never coming back, is he?
Not even to say good-bye.
Remember... you're a strong woman.
His heart couldn't take it.
There was just too much damage.
He couldn't take it.
I'm not this guy.
I won't be this guy who...
I'm going to tell her.
oh, chief.
I, uh-- I've got paperwork, Dr. Torres.
Kidnapd babies make
for a lot of paperwork.
I was planning on maybe
going to see my wife tonight.
But instead, I get to do this.
I could help.
I mean, I-I could-- I could help.
No, you've helped enough for one day.
What... h-how did I get...
you were cooking crystal
meth and the substances exploded.
Where's--where's my--
your husband and your son,
u sustained only minor injuries.
Althought seems, um, your son had been
passively ingesting methamphetamine.
He suffered a stroke earlier today
and went into surgery this afternoon.
I believe the surgery went smoothly.
Your husband was taken by the police, and I'm sure they'll be wanting to speak to you as well.
oh, okay.
Okay, you know what?
Just try--try to breathe.
Slowly.
Breathe.
I'm sure it must feel...
as though everything is coming apart.
But you can get through this.
Just... breathe.
breathe.
The thing about addiction
is it never ends well.
Because eventually whatever
it is that was getting us high...
stops feeling good and starts to hurt.
wa to grab a drink?
I have a problem.
What's up?
No, I'm just...
I'm admitting I...
I have a problem.
What's gonna happen
to them and the baby?
Um... his grandmother is coming fohim.
I think she's gonna take custody.
they were it.
They were my family.
Can you imagine?
After 60 years on this planet...
my family's a couple
of drug dealers and their kid.
You know, just because
people do horrible things,
it doesn't always mean
they're horrible people.
Still, they say you don't kick
the habit till you hit rock bottom.
But how do you know when you're there?
So I take it you still want to talk?
Yeah, I do.
no.
- No, I-
- no, you don'T.
George, please. Just...
please, please don't say anything.
Please. I am asking you as your wife.
I am asking you not to say anything.
I am asking you to just not.
Not tonight.
I am your wife.
Do this for me?
Okay.
Dr. Grey.
I'm heading over to joe'S.
You want to grab a drink?
Oh, no, thanks.
I'm, uh, meeting someone.
Yeah.
Derek asked me to track you down.
He's, uh, stuck with a patient.
Not gonna be able to meet you.
Sends his apologies.
Oh, okay.
So... Joe's?
I think I'm going home.
Meredith.
Because no matter how
badly a thing is hurting us...
sometimes letting
it go hurts even worse.