Previously on Grey's Anatomy...
- I slept with Izzie.
- George told me.
Everything.
You named me Ava,
and I was more me
as Ava, than I'll ever be as Rebecca.
Dr. Hahn, I was pleasantly surprised
to hear you were joining us today.
You remind me of myself
when I was an intern.
Focused, intense...
- Cold.
- My mother is dead isn't she?
- Yes.
- Let's do this once.
I'm fine, she's cremated,
I picked out a beautiful urn,
she's hanging out
in the back of my closet.
Any more questions about my dead mother,
or can we get back to work?
Pick me. Choose me.
Love me.
You're the love of my life.
I can't leave you.
But you're constantly
leaving me.
Imagine my disappointment
when I wake up
after five years and discover
that you're no more than ordinary.
There's a reason surgeons
learn to wield scalpels.
We like to pretend
we're hard, cold scientists.
we're fearless.
Pick me. Choose me.
Love me.
But the truth is, we become
surgeons because
somewhere, deep down,
we think we can cut away
that which haunts us...
What are you guys doing up?
Couldn't sleep.
Weakness,
frailty...
Death.
What is that?
My mother.
Happy freakin' Halloween.
You're moving out
of Burke's place?
Yes, sir.
My wife has filed for divorce.
I'm very sorry, sir.
At any rate,
I need a place to live.
And Burke's place...
I was there once.
I suppose actually
it's your place now?
No, It's still Burke's place.
Now it's yours.
What are we looking at?
Meredith put her mom in a baggie
and brought her to work.
I had to get her out of my closet.
She was haunting me.
And now she's haunting us all.
- I'm putting her to rest.
- She is cleansing.
In tribal culture, when one
wants to cleanse the past,
One cuts off all of one's hair
and buries it in the earth.
You might try that, too.
Okay, listen up.
Today is a holiday, which means
the pit will be overrun.
You've got the usual
drunken stupidity...
And then you've got
Seattle's annual chain saw
pumpkin carving contest.
- I love this city.
- Stay on your toes,
- stay on top of your interns.
- So we should round bedore
- heading to the pit or...
- Direct your questions to Dr. Bailey.
Oh, we're directing
our questions to Dr. Bailey?
Oh, not you. Just Stevens.
Why is Stevens directing
her questions to Dr. Bailey?
Because she's been sleeping
with my husband.
All righty, then.
Have a good day.
This is even more disturbing
than your bagful of mommy.
His medication was due
half an hour ago.
The man is living in the hospital
while he waits on a heart.
Erin, honey.
I'm thinking it's kinda hard
for anyone to take you seriously
in your mouse costume.
See, I work with 5 year olds, dad.
My costume is appropriate.
Hers is not.
Look, I'm... I'm just saying,
if you have time for Halloween costumes,
you probably have time to provide
my father with basic care.
Hi, I'm Dr. O'Malley.
We'll take care of your father
right away.
Thank you.
You should always make sure they have
their meds before you do anything else.
Thanks.
I like your costume.
Oh, well, Dr. Yang said that we c...
Dr. Yang is screwing with you.
Oh, I knew it.
Are you the doctor?
- Oh, I am.
- Good.
That's... That's good.
Is your leg hurting you?
It's not the leg.
It's the foot.
And it's not hurting so much
as it's not mine.
Something happened.
I can't explain it.
But this foot does
not belong to me.
It... It feels like
it's a corpse foot.
Did you lose feeling in the foot?
Is it numb?
No, it's... It's not numb.
It's just...
It's not mine.
Please, I'm...
I'm not crazy. I work at a bank.
I'm not crazy.
Please. I need a surgeon.
I need you to get me a surgeon
who will remove it.
A surgeon who will
remove your foot?
A surgeon who will amputate
your seemingly healthy foot?
- What is that?
- It's charts.
- It's my mom.
- What?
I had her in the cubby,
she was freaking people out.
I was just gonna go put her in the car.
You think that's disrespectful,
to leave her in the car?
It's a little...
It's not that strange.
I'm trying to figure out
how to put her to rest.
I can't shove her in the back
of my closet anymore.
I have to deal with her. And...
This is me...
trying to evolve.
I'm trying here.
So...
Cubby or car?
You're asking me if I think
you should put your mom's ashes
in your cubby or your car?
And you don't think that's very strange?
Are those really
your mom's ashes?
It's strange, right?
It's strange.
Are you lost?
No, my mom works
in the cafeteria.
She said I could come up here
and look for Dr. Sloan.
Do you know him?
Um, can you take care of him?
Yeah.
Can you take care of her?
Good morning.
Don't do that.
Don't smile at me.
Don't smile at her.
Don't smile at me, either.
We're on to you.
We've compared notes.
Compared notes? Really?
Compared notes,
compared pickup lines,
- compared techniques.
- Techniques?
Identical.
- Identical?
- We formed a club.
Nurses unite against Mark Sloan.
Are there any club activities?
Man. You would not believe
what just happened to me.
- There's a kid looking for you.
- What?
Daddy?
What?
- Nicely done.
- Thanks.
- I'll be getting you back for that.
- Looking forward to it.
You're not my father.
But I am hoping
you'll build me some ears.
Dr. Karev, request for you.
Curtain three.
Dr. Karev, I'm feeling
a little under the weather.
And rather than risk
spreading germs to the patients,
I thought I'd head home for the day.
Do you want to be a surgeon
or do you want to go to bed?
It's one or the other.
Surgeons stand up through
10-, 12-, 15-hour surgeries
without food, without bathroom breaks,
without complaints.
Surgeons do not go home because
we have a tickle in our throat.
It's not a tickle
in my throat as much...
- Make yourself busy, Norman.
- Right.
All the moms in my town,
they all dress up for Halloween.
So I was thinking what would I...
want to be if I had to dress up
or what I...
And the only thing
I could come up with,
the only thing that I wanted to be...
...was Ava.
You found him.
You two know each other?
You know his parents?
His mom works in the cafeteria.
- What's all this?
- Letters from the kids in my class.
Letters to me.
He has the internal structure
to hear,
he just doesn't have a canal
or external structure.
So I thought if I came in
with my letters,
Dr. Sloan might feel sorry for me
and do the surgery for free.
Uh, look, I'd like to help,
I would if I could,
but pro bono surgery...
You should probably know,
on my way here this morning,
three different people
thought I was in a costume.
My head looks like
a permanent Halloween costume.
Just thought
you should know that.
You're good.
Pro bono surgery is not just
about me giving you my time.
A surgery like this
requires O.R. time,
an anesthesiologist,
a general surgeon
to remove the cartilage from your ribs,
at least two surgical nurses.
Couldn't you ask them for help?
I could, but I don't have
any social capital.
The nurses hate me.
They've formed a club
that's all about hating me.
And the other doctors
don't owe me any favors 'cause
I've never done any for them.
I'm sorry.
I wish I could help.
I would if I could.
I have social capital.
Or I don't. Nobody knows me,
but they knew my mother.
So maybe I can make this happen.
Fine, make it happen.
You manage that,
I'm all yours.
These people
who knew your mother,
do they know you brought her
to work in a baggie?
Oh, you...
You didn't come for me. You...
You chickened out.
When I... When I was leaving,
when I was...
When I asked you to give me
a reason to stay,
you chickened out, which I get.
I get that. It was a lot.
It was scary, and I know
I can be kinda intense,
but I thought... I thought...
I thought
after the chickening out part,
I thought...
You would come for me.
I came back for you,
which basically...
makes me a beggar.
I'm a beggar for Halloween.
Now you're mocking me.
I'm not mocking you.
We need...
to talk.
We will.
Body dysmorphic disorder?
You can prescribe him
some antianxiety meds
to try to lessen
the urgency he's feeling.
The man is requesting
an amputation,
and the best you can come up with
is antianxiety meds?
Dr. Bailey.
Chain saw contest time?
Yep.
Mr. Miller.
I have to get to the E.R.
But I'm gonna write you
a prescription
for some medication
I think may help you.
Medication? I need...
I need a surgeon.
A surgeon can take off the foot.
Get me a surgeon!
I am a surgeon,
and I can tell you right now
that you won't persuade me
or any other surgeon
to do what you're asking.
Please try this medication.
I have an earless boy.
- I'm sorry?
- Sloan has agreed
to build him ears pro bono
if you will donate the O.R.
And all the equipment...
I'm sorry, Grey.
My pro bono slate is full.
There are protocols
to be followed,
- all sorts of red tape...
- Trick or treat.
Get it?
He's trick-or-treating...
For ears.
- Grey...
- You know, my mother,
she was big
on pro bono surgeries.
O.R. 2 is free at 6:00 p.m.
Thank you.
If you two need to talk,
I could wait over there.
Why? It's not like we have
any secrets anymore.
Callie told everyone.
Everyone.
Yeah, it's gonna be a long day.
Erin Shanley, 34,
massive head trauma when a brick
came through her windshield.
- G.C.S. of 3 in the field.
- A brick came through her windshield?
Kids were screwing around
on a bridge, halloween crap.
- I'm looking at brain matter here.
- I checked. She's a donor.
- Oh, my god.
- What?
Her father's on three.
He's waiting for a new heart.
It was awesome.
It was the sickest pumpkin head
you ever saw.
And then the next thing you know,
it's like, blood gushing,
and it totally stained
my pumpkin head.
- You don't say?
- Made it even sicker, though.
- I brought it in... The digit.
- Oh, you have the finger?
Yeah, but it's, like,
lodged in the chain saw.
Wait.
It was right here.
- Who took my saw?
- What? Sir, the cut isn't clean enough
- to consider re...
- Yo, who took my saw?
Oh, no.
- What is that noise?
- I have no idea.
Dude! Sick!
Interior nerve is shot.
There's nothing salvageable here.
Completely mangled.
I can't believe he held that saw
to his leg long enough...
- Was he high?
- No, I just gave him
some morphine for the pain, but
the tox screen was clean before that.
Unbelievable.
All right, I'll finish the job.
Yang, go ahead and prep him
for complete amputation.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Hey, you okay?
Severed limbs don't sit well with me.
Just a little queasy is all.
But I'm fine.
I'll help Dr. Yang.
Gotta love Halloween...
When all the crazies
come out to play.
I kind of get it. I mean, I get
that you can wake up one day,
and your life doesn't
feel le your own.
I heard...
About your marriage.
And if there's anything you need
me to do to cheer you up,
I'm around,
day or night...
Night in particular.
I was married.
I said "Till death do us part," okay?
In a church.
I mean, it was the church of Elvis,
but still it was a church.
I just...
I can't believe this is my life.
I don't understand.
How did this happen?
How could this happen?
Injuries like these
happen very quickly.
She probably
didn't feel any pain at all.
Mr. Shanley.
According to Erin's driver's license...
She was an organ donor.
And as next of kin,
if you agree to take her off
of life support,
you could direct the heart
to yourself.
She is young, she was healthy.
She would be a perfect match
for you, sir.
Could you just please go away?
- Mr. Shanley, if you would just...
- Please, go away.
Please.
Dr. O'Malley will bring you
to see your daughter
if you like.
Oh, so sorry.
Excuse me. You okay?
No apology necessary.
I'm Sydney, by the way.
Dr. Sydney Heron. General surgery.
Big fan of your work. Yeah.
We were seated together
once at an M&M.
Anyway, now seems
as good a time as any
to make it official...
Our introduction.
Ah, Derek Shepherd.
- Pleasure.
- It's very, very nice to meet you.
Nice meeting you, too.
You think she's pretty?
Yeah. I like cheerful people.
I can be cheerful.
I think the ashes thing
makes that kinda unlikely.
Dr. Bailey,
we're gonna help rebuild
a little boy's ears today, pro bono.
And I thought maybe
you could donate some time.
Thanks to the fine,
upstanding citizen
who cut off his foot on my watch,
I've got a mountain of paperwork.
On top of that, I promised
to try and get out here in time
to see my son
in his Halloween costume.
Is Tuck even old enough
to know what Halloween is?
He's not, but his father is,
and that's who I promised.
Trick or treat.
For ears?
He's trick-or-treating for ears?
Could you also persuade some of
the surgical nurses to help out?
They seem to really like you.
- Trick or treat.
- Stop that.
All right, I'm in.
She's warm.
It doesn't make sense.
I'm sorry.
She's breathing
with the help of machines.
Erin, the persn that you knew,
isn't there anymore.
Would you bring the paperwork?
You can have her...
Have her...
Her organs.
That's what she wanted.
And her heart?
Give it to someone else.
We could scatter her off the roof.
She was afraid of heights.
They're ashes, Meredith.
The ashes aren't acrophobic.
I need to put my mother to rest.
I need to not become her.
I need to not die emotionally
crippled and alone.
And I need to not...
attend the wedding
of Derek Shepherd and Sydney Heron.
I need to put my mother to rest.
Sydney Heron?
Just ask.
So you two are together?
Like "together" together,
in love together?
Sexy love, not sibling love?
Yes. Yeah.
We're together.
And...
you two have been...
I mean, without any of us knowing...
Doing this the whole time?
Just once.
I said she could ask questions.
And now we're waiting to...
Be together...
- Out of respect.
- For Callie's feelings.
She's not judging.
Right.
I have an earless boy
waiting for me.
But...
I'm happy for you guys.
- Do you have to go?
- No.
Norman can get by for
a few more minutes without me.
How are you?
I mean...
How have you been?
I'm in love with my daughter.
She's perfect. She's...
She sucks on her fingers.
It's her new thing.
And she makes, like this...
perfect little cartoon suckling sound.
And your husband?
My husband's in love
with my daughter, too.
You look tired.
I haven't been sleeping much.
I haven't been sleeping much either.
The baby wakes up all the time.
Not as much now
that I figured out that...
if wrap her in whatever shirt
I'm wearing...
She smells you.
And she sleeps.
What are we doing?
What are we gonna do?
Dr. Hahn.
Thank you for coming
at such short notice.
Not a problem.
Are we harvesting the heart for UNOS,
or is the recipient here?
I'm hoping the recipient is here,
but he hasn't agreed yet.
I've never had much trouble
talking a heart patient
into taking a heart.
It's his daughter's heart.
Okay.
Get him to OR 2 and page torres.
- OK. Where are you going?
- His daughter...
- What's Hahn doing here?
- She's been declared brain dead...
Heart transplant.
Don't think about it.
It's my patient.
Dr. Hahn, I understand
you're doing a heart transplant today,
and I thought I'd volunteer to scrub in.
Isobel Stevens.
She's my patient, the donor.
So if you need any information,
I have it, all of it.
She's... She's my patient.
You've got some eager
junior residents around here.
Lucky me.
Take your pick.
Well, Yang, I appreciate the offer,
but I date men.
So I don't think
you'll be able to impress me
the way you've impressed
your mentors in the past.
- What?
- You sleep with them, right?
Preston Burke, Colin Marlowe...
That's your thing.
It's my...
It's... I'm sorry. What does
that have to do with anything?
My theory is if you had
the chops in the OR,
you wouldn't need to try
to impress in the bedroom.
- Stevens, is it?
- It is.
Let's go, Stevens.
I bust my ass here,
and Burke skips town
with my cardio reputation.
So now instead of
a heart transplant,
I get to participate in the amputation
of a crazy man's foot.
- I'm not...
- Crazy.
Cutting off your foot is crazy.
Walking through your life
like you have no power,
like you have no say...
No say in your own destiny...
Like you have no control
over your own body,
walking through life
likethatis what's crazy.
I still think it's cutting off your foot
with a chain saw that's crazy.
Mr. Shanley, I'm Dr. Hahn.
The transplant team is in place
if you're ready to say good-bye.
You must not have children.
- I'm sorry?
- If you had children
you'd never say it. You'd never say
"If you're ready to say good-bye."
Mr. Shanley, I'm very sorry,
but I want to suggest
one last time...
No, I am not taking her heart.
I can't have my daughter's heart
beating in my chest.
It would haunt me
every day of my life. No!
All right.
I'm very sorry for your loss.
Page me when he's ready.
Mr. Shanley...
I don't have kids,
so I don't know
what it's like to lose a child,
but I do know what it's like
to lose a parent.
Your daughter loved you.
I saw her this morning.
She was fighting for you.
She was fighting for your life.
You're her dad.
She didn't want to leave you.
I know that.
I also know that she would
want you to have her heart.
I would've given my dad
my heart if I could.
If I could've saved him...
I would've given him my heart.
All right.
- It's not my fault Hahn chose me.
- Whatever.
I can't believe that you are judging me.
That after what Hahn said to you,
that you are judging me.
- It's not the same thing.
- It is the same thing.
It's exactly the same thing.
I'm sorry that I hurt Callie.
I didn't mean to hurt her.
You slept with her husband.
I slept with my boyfriend.
It's not the same thing.
Meredith slept
with another woman's husband.
The two of you are like
this closed circle.
You can commit whatever crime you want,
in your little circle, it's all fine.
I know that you didn't
sleep with Burke to get ahead.
And if Hahn had asked me,
I would've defended you.
I'm not even asking you to defend me.
I'm asking you to just...
cut me an inch of slack.
And believe me when I say
that I am sorry I hurt Callie.
We are not a closed circle.
You are.
Dr. Shepherd.
Here's a question...
Were there actual shepherds
in your lineage?
- Sorry. What?
- You know, shepherds.
The ones who watch over sheep.
I mean the geneology.
My name for example,
not actually after the bird...
You know, I'm sorry.
Would you excuse me?
- Of course.
- Okay, thank you.
Yeah, you did this.
- Payback's a bitch.
- What the hell did you tell her?
I put the word out that you
were lookin'.
- That I'm looking?
- Lookin'.
It sounds way dirtier without the "g."
You wonder why they formed a club?
- You heard about that?
- Yeah.
Okay, so we have
one plastic surgeon,
a general surgeon,
an anesthesiologist,
one, two, three scrub nurses
and an OR.
Let's call your mom, kid.
You're gonna get some ears.
He cut off his foot.
Yeah.
He cut off his perfectly good foot.
Well, people do
some very strange things.
I had the world' shortest marriage.
I was left in a church
while I was literally wearing
a wedding dress.
George cheated on me
right in front of me,
and I missed it.
Burke sent his mother to say
good-bye to me.
I'm gonna be a divorcée.
Now Erica Hahn thinks I'm a fraud.
I'm...
I'm not feeling very...
- Crap.
- What?
My intern, something happened.
I don't know what.
We need to talk.
Well, we will.
I'll come back. Okay?
Okay.
Don't chicken out.
You know, I'm impressed.
I didn't think you'd pull this off.
I'm actually
pretty surprised myself,
considering it was
my first time trick-or-treating.
Your first time?
Yeah. My mom never made it
home in time to take me,
never got it together
to make me a costume.
Plus she said it was rude
to knock on people's doors
and beg for food.
What?
Just...
The apple fell pretty far
from the tree, huh?
- Dr. Karev, you want to slow down?
- I just heard.
- Did he have a stroke?
- He did.
3 inches to the left,
he'd never talk again.
- It's gonna be okay, right?
- No way to know
till we get the clot out
and he wakes up.
- But he's gonna be okay...
- Karev, stop talking.
Is your marriage really over?
Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
- Thanks.
Did Meredith really bring
her mom's ashes to work?
Look at that.
Not a bad day's work.
Paddles.
Let's see what we've got.
There it is.
Come on. Norman...
Come on, man...
come on, come on.
What happened?
I just saw a heart transplant.
I just helped build
a little boy some ears.
That's cool.
Yeah.
I dug up my mom's cat.
What?
My mom didn't leave
any instructions
'cause it was so...
Unexpected.
So...
We had to figure out on our own
what she would have wanted.
And... my mom loved that cat.
So... I dug her up...
The cat...
From her little grave
in our backyard.
And I snuck into the cemetery
in the middle of the night
and reburied her
right beside my mom.
And it was...
creepy and morbid,
carrying around a dead,
decaying cat in the cemetery
in the middle of the night, but...
It made my mom really happy.
At least...
I like to think it did.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Look, Tucker, I said I'm sorry.
No.
I didn't...
No, I...
Tucker...
Perfect.
Hi.
We just put a man's daughter's heart
in his chest.
His daughter's heart?
Well, that just makes you
want to throw up, now doesn't it?
You all right?
You're Dr. Bailey.
You hear everything.
And if you haven't heard everything,
I'm sure you've heard.
About your marriage?
Yeah, I probably would've.
I'm sorry...
If I...
disappointed you.
I'm not your mother, O'Malley.
I have to apologize
to her now, too.
Look, you're not a bad guy.
I don't mean to let you off the hook
entirely, because what you did
was unkind,
and hurtful and wrong.
But you're not a bad guy.
I'm just saying, it...
It takes two.
To reach the point
you reached in your marriage,
it takes two.
I mean... I mean, I'm here
late at night, Halloween,
helping an earless boy get ears,
and my husband wants to act
like that ain't an important thing.
He wants to act like...
It isn't a good thing
that I did today.
Now that isn't just on me.
That's him wanting things
to be the way he wants.
to be purely black-and-white.
I mean, I missed my son's...
first Halloween,
and my heart is aching
inside of my chest,
but, you know,
that doesn't mean anything.
It doesn't count because
in a black-and-white world,
I simply didn't make it home,
and that makes me the bad guy.
Always.
I'm always the bad guy.
You hear what I'm saying?
Sorry you missed
your son's first Halloween.
Look, what I'm saying to you is...
Okay, I was there.
All right? I was there...
the day your father died.
I was there
when you came back from Vegas,
married after a week and...
All I'm saying is...
It's not black-and-white...
And you're not a bad guy.
I did not sleep my way to the top.
I'm attracted to a talent
that resembles my own,
not that it's any of your business.
Your comments were
unprofessional and inappropriate.
You know what? You're...
inappropriate
and unprofessional.
This is gonna be so much fun.
Dr. Yang,
did you hear?
Dr. Hahn has agreed
to become our new head
of cardiothoracic surgery.
Lookin' forward to it, Dr. Yang.
You can't have my apartment.
I'm...
sorry I didn't listen when you said
you weren't feeling well.
Sorry, I didn't answer your page.
Do you know why I chose surgery?
I'm a little south of 60
and blood makes me squeamish.
I wanted to go into psych
because I like to talk.
I've noticed that.
But I had this voice in my head
telling me to choose surgery.
It was as if...
my Mary Beth
was whispering in my ear.
And so I listened.
And do you know
what I think now?
I think I was about to have
a massive stroke...
and my Mary Beth wanted me
to be surrounded by...
world-class surgeons
when it happened.
So what are you gonna do now?
Well, I'm gonna go into psych.
Because you people, you surgeons,
You're just
a bunch of little children
running around with your scalpels
and your severed feet and your...
inappropriate sex
in inappropriate places.
You all need a good shrink.
Dr. Grey?
I had a goldfish,
and when he died,
we flushed him down the toilet,
back to the sea.
Okay.
Back to the sea
is better than your cubby.
You okay?
I don't know if I can handle
one more night in that hotel.
What's the matter with you?
I have to start dating.
It isn't just surgeons.
The truth is, I don't know anyone
who isn't haunted by something...
Or someone.
And whether we try to slice
the pain away with a scalpel
or shove it in the back of a closet,
our efforts usually fail.
We made it through this day.
Yeah, we did.
So the only way
we can clear out the cobwebs
is to turn a new page...
So it's the kitchen,
bedroom, bathroom.
There's the sofa.
You can sleep here.
Great. So...
- Do you mind if I clean up a little?
- Yes.
I mind a lot.
Or put an old story to rest...
Grey.
Chief.
What are you doing, Grey?
This is a sterile environment.
It's my mother.
And I think this is
where she'd want to be.
Should we say a prayer?
She didn't believe in anything.
Finally,
finally to rest.
Ashes to ashes.
Dust to dust.
Transcript: www.swsub.com
Sync: Kasius & Benj!
© www.seriessub.com