Previously on "grey's anatomy"... I passed?
You're not an intern anymore. George doesn't know I exist.
Do you want to go on a date with me? What if I'm not into it?
I'm not letting you do this to me, Alex. I know I'm being an ass.
I think I found a way to save lives. I could find patients
For a clinical trial.
The tumor's shrinking. The virus is working.
You keep a diary? It's not mine.
Whose is it? Your mother's.
I am a rock.
I am an island.
That's the mantra
Of pretty much every surgeon I've ever met.
We like to think we're independent,
Loners, mavericks...
That all we need to do our jobs is an o.R., a scalpel
And a willing body.
Is Yang on call tonight?
Uh, yeah. Why do you think it's so clean in here?
But the truth is,
Not even the best of us can do it alone.
Surgery, like life, is a team sport.
Can I just say,
The whole "taking it slow" thing?
Best idea ever.
It really takes the pressure off.
Mm. Yeah.
We can just, you know, Hang out without all the--
The expectations.
Why rush things? Exactly.
And eventually,
You've got to get off the bench and decide...
What team are you batting for?
You know, one of the joys of cohabitation
Is having breakfast together.
Well, I can't today because Bailey paged us in early.
Well, I guess you don't have time
To look at our work in a major medical journal.
They published our clinical trial? Mm-hmm.
It's on the cover.
"a new method in treating inoperable malignant gliomas--
The Shepherd method." what do you think?
It's a picture, a big picture of you. You're making a face.
I'm not making a face. I love that picture.
I have to go.
"the Shepherd method." it's about time this hospital
Got some good publicity for a change.
Oh, I heard you found a donor.
Yes, sir. The last piece of the puzzle
Finally fell into place. This is the day, dr. Bailey,
The day that seattle grace comes back swinging.
Shepherd on the front page of a national journal,
Bragging rights to a flashy surgery--
I don't see Mercy West taking on a project of this magnitude,
Do you? I'd rather wait to celebrate till we pull this thing off.
Yeah, that's a good call. We don't want to jinx it.
Eat that, Mercy West.
God, I've been looking everywhere for you.
Well, I had an early morning palatoplasty.
You see this? "the Shepherd method"?
Yeah, yeah, very impressive. Listen, last night, Erica--
You think they airbrushed his picture?
I mean, the man does not have one damn
Pore. Could you focus? I need you right now
All right, well, I'm a little exhausted,
But if you want to hop on and do all the work...
No, I need to talk.
Last night,
Erica and i... We...
We did it. Sort of.
Congratulations.
No. No, no.
It was not good at all.
I choked.
I couldn't go down there.
I-i tried, but it just felt so weird and clinical,
Like gynie rotation.
I left this morning before she got up.
I couldn't even face her.
What if--what if me and Erica are--
What if--what if we were a mistake?
Where are you going? I can't talk about this.
Oh, come on. You love talking about this stuff.
Girl on girl. It's hot. Two girls getting nasty and loving it? That's hot.
One girl talking about how much it sucked?
Depressing and wrong.
Just wrong.
The chief wants us to give George one of our interns?
Except for Grey. She already lost O'malley.
Just dump your dead weight. Oh, please. They're all dead weight.
That's why I need all four of them, not three.
George is filling out paperwork,
Getting his real live doctor wings,
So I thought now would be a good time to
Decorate his locker. Give me that coffee
Okay. I don't even want the credit,
But the clinical trial was my idea.
And I had to beg him to do it,
More than once. It's okay you want the credit
I would want the credit. When you screw the attendings, you get screwed.
They have all the power. Interns. You could screw interns.
I mean date. Residents could date interns,
'cause we're nonthreatening.
I read this study once that said that interns hardly ever file
Sexual harassment claims because we feel so weak and powerless
In the hospital environment, so that's good.
Interns-- the other white meat.
Where are we going? You'll see when we get there.
Dr. Bailey, I'm actually on dr. Sloan's service today.
Everyone's off their services. You're all with me. Where are we going?
You'll see when we get there. Hey,
Did you see your locker? I put a smelly candle in it
So now your scrubs are gonna smell like cinnamon bun. Gosh, thanks.
Dr. Bailey, dr. Sloan is doing a transpalatal advancement.
I've never seen one. Hahn said I could scrub in on her aortic bypass.
And I really need to get to the clinic. I've staffed it
With nurses and p.A.S, but I'm the only doctor on call,
And I've got administrative work to-- today is not about you.
It is not about whose services you wish to be on.
It's not about your career. This is about me.
This is a project I've been working on for a long time,
And it's very important to me,
Therefore it will be very important to you.
And the only way we can pull this thing off
Is iwe work together as a team,
So today, you are not 15 individual doctors,
You are one team of surgeons representing this hospital.
Is everybody clear othat?
Um, why would they need
So many doctors for one surgery? I don't know.
Because it's not just one surgery.
It's 12 surgeries-- 6 kidney transplants
In six o.R.S, all at the same time.
Paired matching kidney donation.
A 6-way swap-- 6 people donate kidneys
To total strangers,
Six people get kidneys from total strangers.
12 people walk away happy.
Paired matching kidney donation. Otherwise known as--
Dude, a domino surgery.
Stan Mercer, 46,
Chronic renal failure secondary to high blood pressure.
His wife here wanted to donate a kidney to him,
But she wasn't a match.
So she will be donating her kidney
To ms. Chen over there, who is a match,
While mr. Mercer will be getting a kidney
From this young man today. Nice to meet you.
P.J., please.
Uh, Kurt Walling, 58,
Chronic renal failure secondary to diabetes.
His son p.J. Wasn't a match, so mr. Walling will be getting
Ms. Herman's kidney today.
Thanks for the kidney, ms. Herman. Oh, call me Lindsay.
We're gonna be pretty close by the end of the day.
And so on and so forth. Why do you still look stupid
Well, maybe if we had a cheat sheet.
Ms.Herman gives her kidney to mr. Walling
Mr. Walling's son gives his kidney to mr. Mercer.
Mr. Mercer's wife gives her kidney to ms. Chen.
Ms. Chen's sister gives her kidney to mr. Patel.
Mr. Patel's wife gives her kidney to ms. Loring,
Who came in with her cousin, ms. Gomez, who's giving
Her kidney to mr. Cross, the professional
Flautist. For those of you without a photographic memory
It's up on a board in the conference room. And why do we have to do
All x transplants at one time? So no one backs out at the last minute.
Why would anybody back out? It's such an incredible thing
To be a part of. Well, passing the organ's kinda creepy. I'd back out.
Yeah, yeah, that's why this whole surgery
Is a giant house of cards. If we lose one donor,
We lose them all. So you will not only provide
Excellent medical care, but you will keep
Your patients happy.
We need to make sure this whole thing doesn't fall apart
Before the surgery. Any questions? Um,
I heard when the did a domino at boston gen
The residents all got to keep one of the dead kidneys
In a jar aa souvenir. I want a kidney in a jar.
Me, too, can I have a kidney? Well, if they get kidneys, I get a kidney.
Quantities are limited. I asked first.
Can we? No one is taking home a kidney in a jar
Diseased kidneys
Are not tchotchkes for your coffee table.
Now go. Go.
Hey, you okay?
Uh, Bailey snagged
All the surgical residents and interns,
So I'm stuck with the psych interns.
Not the sharpest. Okay, you're busy. I'll be brief.
I was thinking, if you weren't on call tonight,
That, uh, maybe we could, uh, go to my place,
Order in dinner, rent a movie.
Tonight? You want to get together again tonight?
Well, I had a lot of fun last night. Fun.
Anyway, just let me know.
Okay, as you may know, one of you is going
To O'malley today. Oh, me! I-i'll go if you need a volunteer.
I decide who gets to go after I decide
Which one of you sucks the most.
And you better not suck on purpose, because I will know.
Honey, would you like your book or some music,
Something to help you relax? I don't know. Maybe some water.
How about some ice chips instead?
Your ankles are looking a little thick.
My wife loves tracking my fluid retention.
And, Megan, will you please come over here
And tape the needles so we n start dialis?
Sounds just like a real doctor.
Uh, it says here that you don't have a loved one
In the domino, ms. Herman. No.
So you're just donating a kidney to a complete stranger
For nothing in return? It's really no big deal.
I have two kidneys, and they say you can live with one, so...
Are you kidding? That's amazing, what you're doing.
U.N.O.S. Is always short on organs.
If everyone in the world did this-- yeah,
It'd be all peace and love and unicorns
She gets it, Grey.
I'm so sick of all the "yay, you."
I totally understand.
Oh. The chief has got me doing press all day
With journalists.
My face is starting to hurt from smiling.
Uh-huh. I already pushed that. It comes faster when I push it.
Oh, must be that Shepherd method. Funny.
I think I'll take the stairs.
Meredith, are you bothered by this? Why would I be bothered?
You can't call it the Shepherd-grey method
Because then people would ink you had help.
So do I really have to give my kidney to that old guy?
Mr. Mercer couldn't be more than 50. My son's 22.
To him, everyone over 40 is on the brink of death.
Turned 23 in august. Oh, that's right.
Maybe we could have a little belated party
Here in the hospital, get you an ice cream cake.
You used to love those. Yeah, when I was 7.
Look, I'm not here for a reunion.
I just want to get this over with
And get out of here, okay? So you are on dialysis four times a week now?
They might as well chain me to the machine at this point.
My kidneys are shot. I'm living on borrowed time.
So I'm pretty lucky to have a son who would do this for me.
You're lucky you're loaded.
So when do I get the 10,000 bucks,
Before or after the surgery?
It's a Christmas gift.
Well, it's october.
I see you two hovering.
Hypothetically, say a patient
Was... Paying his son for a kidney,
What exactly would happen?
Paying money for a kidney?
Hypothetically.
Well, as someone who stole an organ herself
Not that long ago,
You should know, what would happen
Is your patient would be out of the exchange.
Which means that this person,
Since her husband's no longer getting a kidney,
Would drop out.
Then they would drop out, then they would drop out,
Then the whole thing would fall apart.
That's what would happen. So if you both are suggesting
That that's what's going on here,
You'd better be damn sure about it.
It's just a gift.
Uh, an early stocking stuffer.
Most girls your age, they're busy shopping.
You're in the hospital giving a kidney to a stranger.
Oh, I'm not such a saint.
Your kidney may not be going directly to my husband,
But you're one of the people saving his life today.
To me, your mother teresa. Honey, would you mind running
And getting a wet washcloth for me?
I'm just-- oh, yeah, of course. Excuse me
Thank you.
You know, my mother invented the Grey method all by herself.
You know, maybe you should stop reading her diary.
It's gonna make you feel inadequate.
She's dead and in the past and still outpacing me.
Okay, see, see that intern over there? Is he clean?
Huh? What? Well, I was just thinking, what Lexopedia said,
And, you know, she may be on to
Something. You're gonna sleep with an intern
It'd just be scratching the itch.
It's been a long time.
I can't do this. All these people telling me
How wonderful and selfless and giving I am--
I-i can take it anymore, especially not
From her. All right, just keep your voice down
Did you see her face, thanking me for saving your life?
Stan, this is crazy.
You promised you would tell her. Please!
Ah. Mr. Mercer, is everything okay?
No, I don't feel so good, actually. Tell her!
If the past three years have meant anything to you,
You have to tell her!
Stan?
I'm not an idiot. I know there have been other women.
All these years, I told myself it was just sex. It's just...
My god, Stan. She's giving a kidney for you.
That--that's not sex. It's family.
All right, his, uh, cardiac enzymes and e.K.G. Look good.
He had an acute anxiety attack. I can clear him for surgery.
I do everything for you.
I've given up my entire life to get you to dialysis,
Drive you to the doctors-- I didn't ask you to do any of that.
I can drive a car. I can pour my own juice.
I got sick, not elderly.
Well, don't worry.
I won't do one more thing for you,
And that includes giving a kidney.
Get on the phone with u.N.O.S.
Tell them we need a kidney
That matches mrs. Mercer's antibodies.
U.N.O.S. Is a long shot.
It's only shot we have. Go, now.
She's barely a second-year resident. I made the virus. She assisted.
When Michael jordan scores, no one cares about the assist.
I don't know. Scottie pippen... You know what I mean.
These women, they overthink everything.
Somebody's cranky today. What is that?
"experimental treatments for cleft palates."
Huh. You're working on your own clinical trial, aren't you?
I'm--i'm jt-- I'm doing a little research.
Mm-hmm. See, the very sight of me
Reminds you that you've not made
One worthwhile contribution to medical history,
Doesn't it?
Get out. You should read my article.
It will enrich your life,
Make you a better man. I'm saving it for the bathroom
It started as an office thing,
You know, light, fun.
And then one day you wake up,
And...  This older guy is all you can think about.
You'd do anything for him,
Even give a kidney.
Why?
I could save his life, too.
I mean, she may be married to him,
But... I'm saving his life today, too.
So then he'll finally have to choose.
Her or me?
Apparently, Erica loved it, the non-sex sex.
I think she might want more. Happens to me all the time with women.
I barely remember it, their minds are blown. That's your sage advice?
I'm a world-class surgeon,
Double boarded in plastics and e.N.T.
I have more meaningful and worthwhile things to do
Than dispense sex advice. Yeah, like what?
Nice. Oh, come on. No, Mark, I need your help.
Excuse me.
What is going on?
Trying to decide which of our interns
To give to georg in front of us.
They're deciding in front of us, like livestock at a state fair.
I think I'll keep Lexopedia. She remembers many things.
Mm-hmm. And she bathes,
Which is much more than I can say for...
Stinky two over there.
You smell. Well, Graciella charts like crap.
But she can put in a line. Claire, on the other Hand,
Nearly castrated a guy with a catheter. Mm.
We can hear you. I might dump Pierce.
Ooh, how does he suck? I just hate saying the name Pierce.
Mm. We should revolt.
They'd respect us more if we didn't participate
In our own humiliation. Yeah.
You revolt first, and I'll follow.
Hey, have you heard from u.N.O.S. Yet?
They're still searching for a match
But so far, nothing.
I hope they come through. My guy really needs a kidney
Yeah, they all need kidneys, Izzie.
If Derek needed a kidney, I wouldn't give him one
He'd take the credit.
He'd say he magically grew it himself.
My guy's been sick for 15 years.
Can you imagine having your life on hold like that?
Plus, he's got such a crappy kid.
Hey! Did I say you could put that down?
No, so pick it up.
Weak. No stamina. Yeah, but he takes orders.
True. True.
Is my husband getting a kidney or not? Wait, what about my sister?
If she's not getting a kidney today,
Am not giving mine to some stranger.
I will do my best to make sure everyone gets a kidney today.
I'll update you as soon as I have information. Please.
Sir, i--i've got this under control.
I have Grey talking with u.N.O.S. I have--
We are being featured on the national news.
All eyes are on seattle grace.
Fix this.
Yes, sir.
I have been poked and prodded like a lab rat,
What, all for nothing?
We got to spend time with each other.
That's not nothing.
Oh, oh, now you want to spend time together?
Well, you're about 20 years too late.
So, yeah, nothing.
P.J... Do I still get the $10,000 if the surgery doesn't happen?
'cause if not, I'm outta here. I have a life to get back to.
Please. I need you.
If you could... Just be patient a little bit longer...
I was gonna punch that kid.
I mean, what kind of a selfish idiot--
His father is sick, he's really sick,
And all he cares about is his stupid money.
All right, the guy must have done something really ba
To make the kid so angry. Maybe he just cares about his son,
But the moron is too emotionally stunted to let him.
Okay, uh, I'm--i'm--
I'm trying to be, uh... I am,
But this right here?
This--this-- this is exactly your problem.
You get all wrapped up and involved and you just--
You start--you start caring about these people.
Your patient in there, he's the moron.
His son's never gonna give him what he wants,
And he's just gonna be disappointed.
And the sooner he gets that, the sooner you get it...
No, go on, please.
Be a selfish ass.
'cause at least then I know what to expect.
'cause this being a decent guy one second
And a total jerk the next, it's getting really old, Alex.
So who's it gonna be? Pick one.
O'malley. 'sup, bud? It's doctor.
Hey. Missed you at lunch today.
It was an all-new level of hell.
Oh, no, I was busy doing my own charts.
The interns don't respect me. I would respect you if I was your intern.
George, they don't respect you
Because they're not scared of you.
Just decimate one every few days.
It's not rocket science. Two.
Who's getting, uh, ms. Herman's kidney?
Uh, I can-- I can go check.
Three? Mr. Walling.
That's right. No. I totally forgot.
You forgot.
Like you forgot to do your notes before rounds?
Or like you forgot to pull the drain on my post-op s.B.O.?
Or like you forgot to sign all your dictation,
So all your charts-- uh, my charts--are delinquent?
You forgot...
Because the only thing you can retain
In that pea-sized brain of yours is what time lunch is.
Grey here is gonna become a surgeon
While you dig ditches by the side of the road.
It's brutal, but it's effective.
I am not gonna do this with you.
Do what? Have this silent fight.
I'm gonna write the editors
And have them print a correction--
The Shepherd-grey method. I don't want you to give me credit
Because you're mad that I'm mad.
I want you to give me credit
Because you think I worked hard for it and I deserve it.
You don't deserve it. You're a baby.
You have the potential to be a good surgeon,
Maybe a great one.
But you haven't even scratched the surface
On what you need to learn. It was my idea.
And I hate that picture.
U.N.O.S. Doesn't have a match.
Okay.
Uh, we can, um...
We've been stalling. We haven't released anyone.
I can talk to ms. Mercer--
You can't do anything that could be seen as coercion.
U.N.O.S. Is very clear. But, sir--
The last thing we need
Is to lose our status as a transplant center.
Let the patients go home.
It's over.
I've got a cabg in an hour. Want to get some coffee?
I'm not cut out for this.
Coffee?
No, this, the--the touching and the... Sex with a girl.
I just--i-i can't do it. I thought I could but...
But you did do it. I don't understand.
It wasn't good for you.
I can't believe it.
I got so close.
You're gonna be pretty high on the transplant list.
Something else will come up.
It's not the kidney I'm upset about.
Oh. Your son.
We hadn'spoken in over a year.
It took me months to find him.
This was my chance to get him back.
Right.
I know p.J. Can be selfish...
Rude...
But it hasn't been easy for him.
His mom died.
I worked late most nights.
I made a lot of mistakes.
You can't blame yourself.
Some people are just broken.
I guess you just try not to care too much.
Then you can't be disappointed.
These are, uh, your discharge papers.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why I'm...
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Now all you have to do is sign there at the bottom,
And you're free to go.
You must think I'm a terrible person...
Refusing to give my kidney.
We're not thinking anything, ma'am.
He's taken everything.
My love, my pride, my dignity--
It's all gone.
But the one thing that he doesn't have is the kidney.
And the thought of giving him that last part of me...
You must think I'm a terrible person.
I'm not allowed to think anything.
There are rules that prevent me
From having an opinion here--
Good rules, rules in place for a reason--
Because giving an organ
That god put in your body to someone else
Isn't something that you can be coerced into doing.
It is... A big thing.
It is an extraordinary thing.
It's a gift that must be freely given.
And if you were to give it, and I'm not asking you to,
But if you were to give it,
It's not just for your husband.
It's for five other people,
People that you don't know from adam.
Our six donors are all anesthetized and ready to go.
They'll be done first, followed by the recipients.
Each pair will be color-coded so as not to confuse them.
This surgery is a hornet's nest, people,
So work quickly but carefully.
Use each other. Operate as a team.
Let's go make medical history.
We're lucky as hell that woman changed her mind.
Yes, we are. Yes, we are.
Huh. Now that's what I call a nice-looking kidney.
Put that on ice
And start flushing in the preservation solution.
You want to do the honors, dr. Yang?
Good.
That's quite a geyser of urine, sir.
That means we did our job right.
You never get tired of seeing that.
We're ready for you, Grey.
Walking with the kidney.
5-second rule! 5-second rule!
I'm gonna need more ice, uh, and another tie.
I'll get it.
No, you don't touc anything else.
Someone dropped a damn kidney?
I know you don't want to talk about it anymore.
I know you're over it. Oh, for the love of god.
Just hear me out.
I like to be good at things, okay?
I do not fail.
I do not quit.
I like to be good at things, and I want to be good at this.
So... I need you.
I need you to show me.
Show you?
Just because you didn't publish a big clinical trial
Doesn't mean you're not a genius.
Fine. Take off your pants.
Really? Oh, my god. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I'll show you the Sloan method.
Won't ever be in a medical journal,
But it should.
Shouldn't it be pinking up by now?
It's just getting venous blood.
Let's check the back side again.
I don't know.
I think I see... A little pink, maybe.
Ah, come on, come on.
All right.
Come on.
Come on, pink up.
Pink up, pink up, pink up, pink up.
Come on.
Yes. Yeah, it looks good.
We have a live kidney.
Oh, come on. I am offering two interns.
Two interns for the price of one--come on.
I'll trade you Laura for both of 'em.
Leo drains pus and likes it. I dropped an internal organ...
On the floor.
It happens.
Okay, okay. Uh, how about this?
Four goes to George. I get James.
Karev, you get two. Izzie, give Leo.
What are you people doing?
We were just, uh, just deciding which of our interns
To give to George. Mm-hmm.
Oh, you think I got to choose my interns,
And I picked you people
'cause you're all such a surgical dream team?
You--you're lazy. You're whiny.
Butterfingers overhere is downright depressing,
And you, Yang, you-- you're just annoying.
Choosing their own interns...
What are--what...
Give me those damn cards.
O'malley...
You have interns.
What is it?
Okay, open his fluids.
Karev, push a gram of mag. Do a c.B.C. And electrolytes.
Stevens, uh, order a color flow doppler
And do a full neuro workup. You think there's a bleed?
There's no way of knowing till we evaluate everything. Where is... P.J.?
Where's my son?
Stan had better be dead right now.
He's doing fine.
He hasn't called my room.
Just lay back.
He hasn't asked for me.
It's been three years.
I gave a kidney for him,
And he still hasn't made a choice.
He hasn't asked about you
Or called.
I think he's made a choice.
But I gave a kidney for him.
I gave a kidney.
Oh, my god.
Hey, man, the nurse was supposed to bring my dinner
Like an hour ago. Your dad just had a seizure.
Okay. So what does that mean?
It means something's wrong. It means he could be dying,
And he doesn't know you give a crap.
Honestly, he doesn't know, and maybe you don't,
But if you do, he's dying, and you're gonna be too late. Alex, stop.
He's asking for you, and you're gonna be too late,
And you're gonna live with it for the rest of your life!
You really want to live with that, huh? Do you? Alex! Alex.
So tomorrow we'll meet, uh, one hour before pre-rounds.
Dude, that's, like, 4:00 a.M.
Dr. Stevens
Never made us come in before pre-rounds.
Yeah, O'malley, you gotta chill.
They probably should say dr. O'malley.
So those are your interns? Did you even ask for me?
What?
I helped you study.
I helped decorate your stupid locker.
I-nd you didn't--
You don't-- you don't even see it.
You don't see anything.
I am such an idiot.
And you are a jerk.
You didn't even think to ask for me?
Screw you, dr. O'malley.
Ms. Loring and mr. Mercer, they're all stable.
But mr. Walling, he has delayed graft function
And god knows what else. Ah, the press is gonna be all over this tomorrow.
And I'll need you Available for interviews and some photo-ops.
Make sure you wear your nice scrubs. Did you hear me, sir?
Mr. Walling--he has a serious complication.
His electrolytes are off, his crit's down. But you saved five other lives.
That's a pretty good scorecard. Not perfect, but good.
I told you. I don't want to see Stan.
I'm not taking you to see Stan.
Oh, this is her.
This is the woman who gave me her kidney.
Nice to meet you. Thanks so much.
How's she doing?
I'm keeping a close eye on her,
But so far, she's completely stable.
Come with me.
This man is very ill,
Maybe dying.
He's got a perfect, healthy donor kidney
That wasn't dropped on the floor.
There's only so much we can help...
And so much we can hurt.
Forgive yourself.
Visiting hours are over.
It's okay.
Dad...
Your urine output is up to 25 cc's per hour.
That should make you happy.
My wife would've been happy.
Who's gonna care about my urine output now?
Well, things are gonna be a little different.
Ah, dr. Bailey.
I heard your big surgery went well today.
Congratulations.
Same to you.
Must feel good to see your name in print like that.
It would feel better if Meredith wasn't so--
You know, she's acting silly about the credit.
She's getting emotional. That girl worked her ass off for you,
And you got all the credit. I would've gotten all the blame had we failed.
But you didn't fail.
It's simple. I'm an attending. She's a second-year resident.
Who you're now living with. That's not simple. It's messy.
If it were me, I'd start with "thank you."
You'd be surprised how far that one goes,
Especially with us silly, emotional women.
So Derek said that I was a baby. What?
And that I had a lot to learn. Whatever.
I mean, not whatever. He's right. I did drop a kidney.
And don't say it happens, because it doesn't.
But I do hate it when he's right. No, okay, he is not right.
Stop caring so much about what he thinks.
It makes you seem desperate.
Okay, to the one trolling for interns.
Yeah, I changed my mind.
Interns are weak. I don't want weak.
You know, Burke was a man.
He was a man.
Joe.
I think, uh, we need another round.
Hey, Joe. How you doing?
Excuse me. Here you go.
Wh--ho-- is this for me? Yes.
Hey, honey. I brought you Roses. Let me back in the house.
Oh, no. Mm. Yes.
Holy crap. What the hell is that thing?
Oh, that is a kidney in a jar. That's not fair.
How did you get that? Well,
Being an incredibly important, fancy neurosurgeo
Has its perks.
Thank you.
I couldn't have done it without you,
Not one surgery, not one patient.
I couldn't have done any of it without you. Thanks.
Yeah, could you guys go ahead and get this thing
The hell out of here before people start to freak out? Okay.
Okay. Um, are you gonna be okay? Yeah, yeah, go ahead.
All right. Good night. Good night.
Good night, Joe.
The thing about choosing teams in real life,
It's nothing like it used to be in gym class.
Being first pick can be terrifying.
Take off your pants.
Excuse me?
Take off... Your pants.
We're trying this again.
And being chosen last...
Isn't the worst thing in the world.
What?
I care about you.
I care about you, and I'm not gonna go crazy,
And I'm not gonna try to kill myself,
And I'm not gonna stop caring about you,
No matter how hard you push me away.
Shut up and get out of my room.
No.
I care about you.
And I know you care about me, too.
It is not too late for us.
Get out of my room.
Admit it. Admit that you care about me, too.
I know you do, and I care about you.
I care about you.
I care about you. I care about you.
I--
So we watch from the sidelines,
Clinging to our isolation...
It glows.
Yeah.
When my mother was a resident, she wasn't dropping kidneys.
You're reading your mom's diary?
I'm not half the surgeon my mother was.
Because we know as soon as we let go of the bench...
What, are you leaving already?
There are no real men left in the world, Joe.
See you.
Hey, shot and a beer. Uh, whiskey.
You know what? Better make it just the beer.
I start work tomorrow.
Someone comes along
And changes the game completely.