Previously on Caprica...
A group known as Soldiers of the One
is responsible for the bombing.
We don't really know
the people closest to us.
My daughter died
in the bombing of train number 23,
but I think she may have caused it.
My daughter was a terrorist!
I'm just trying
to find out who I am.
I'm Zoe
and the avatar and the robot.
Like some kind of what-you-call-it,
three-parter.
Trinity.
That's what you are.
I've been given a mission
that will change my life.
I have someone for you to find.
Keon Gatwick.
I need to know I can count on you
to get me to Gemenon.
I made a promise to Zoe
before she died.
- I need to get something to Gemenon.
- I'll see what I can do.
Everything I've built
is on the line.
People are so angry,
they are throwing away
their Graystone computers.
Sarno's making public opinion,
and everyone is watching.
Have Briyah book me on Sarno.
Blood for blood.
It the Tauron way.
Daniel Graystone
lost his daughter, right?
I lost my daughter and my wife.
Balance it out.
- What's going on?
- Bomb in a holocafe three hours ago.
- Place was closed and empty.
- So not out to kill.
Threat?
Or warning or nuisance
or personal beef with the owner.
Or STO.
What? You don't come back
after ten years just to blow up a train.
They want us scared.
Small bomb, middle of the night.
My money's on copycats.
If you got no STO worries,
maybe you don't want to hear
what I picked up at the courthouse.
Don't be coy. I hate that.
What you got?
Intercolonial court on Libra
handed that down an hour ago...
Last matter of the day,
Themis standard time.
A search warrant for a private school?
How'd you get this?
When Amanda Graystone held up
that pendant at the memorial service,
she handed us grounds
to search Zoe's property,
which includes her locker at school
and any other locker
she might have used.
- You're gonna make a thing of it?
- I might.
Keep it tasteful.
Good morning.
Am I too sweaty for you?
Is that your phone?
Get off me.
Get off me right now.
What's going on?
I'm so sorry.
It's my fault entirely.
Global Defense Department!
Listen carefully, everybody!
I need you to step away
from the lockers right now!
Everyone, now!
Step away!
Clear the hallway.
Let's go. Ladies.
That's it. Move. Move out.
Come on, folks.
That's it.
Toss everything.
Toss them all.
We need to talk.
I'll walk away.
You follow in a few.
Next one.
This is clear.
This is a script.
It's a list of talking points.
"I loved my daughter very much...
But I knew she was troubled.
"There were disturbing signs well before
I developed the Holoband."
All it needs are stage directions.
Should I point to my heart?
We're not telling you how to say it.
- Use your own phrasing.
- I don't want to say she was troubled.
- It's important.
- Why?
If she had a preexisting problem,
it takes the onus off the Holoband.
Then I'll find a different way
of saying it.
She's not happy I'm going on Sarno.
Exactly how not happy?
Not happy enough
to make another announcement?
- If she contradicts you...
- She'll be fine.
You should probably play it
a little guilty.
You missed the signs. You'll always
blame yourself because of that.
People want contrition.
Just make it clear it's not guilt
for making a dangerous product.
- What happened to Zoe...
- Nothing to do with the Holoband.
That's just true.
That was great.
Do that.
I'm a star.
Can you say it all
from the beginning again?
Why isn't it done?
Because, so-fis-tace,
they're both in the house,
and there's two other people.
How big a bloodbath do you want?
Right, no.
Gods, no bloodbath.
You still want to do this, right?
Of course.
Then have patience, Yoseef.
-= Lords Of Kobol: Before The Fall =-
pour La Fabrique
Gravedancing (1.00)
http://www.sous-titres.eu/
I know it's all been
very, very upsetting,
I'm gonna make sure
it doesn't happen again.
Now, everybody just go home.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Go on.
- Are they gone?
- They went ahead to the studio.
I need to get dressed.
Do you know
where the coat to this is?
I have no idea.
That's gonna strobe, anyway.
You're right.
I can't believe you're going out there
to dance on her grave like this.
I'm just saying the exact same thing
that you said.
- I didn't say she was crazy.
- She blew up a train.
Maybe. You know,
I don't even know what she did.
- Maybe she was running away.
- I want to do this?
I don't, but I have to,
because you opened up
this dialogue with greater Caprica.
I didn't mean to go on television.
You are deliberately going
on television.
There were cameras
all over that park.
- I was just talking to the crowd.
- We just have to go with it, all right?
Does this tie work?
It's great.
Look, can't you just go out there
and say that this is a very sad time
for our family
and that we need time to process...
But that just doesn't play.
The car should be here by now.
Doesn't play?
Did you actually hear
what you just said?
I don't have time
for this right now.
I'm about to go
on international television.
We are not company spokespeople.
- We're parents!
- Parents?
Actually, no, we're not.
Can I help you?
Oh, hell.
Hello, beautiful.
How are you doing?
Me? I'm doing great.
Thanks for asking.
They leave you down here all alone?
Let's take a closer look.
You know, that is the finest work
that I've ever done, designing that.
You need a name.
I want to go through it again.
Let's run it.
One more time.
- I still see the bruises.
- I'm doing my best.
She was complicated.
Long before I invented the Holoband...
"Troubled" is better.
"Complicated" is meaningless.
I shouldn't have to say it
in one word.
Zoe was...
Zoe's troubles
started a long time ago.
- How's that? "Zoe's troubles"?
- It's not the same.
"I loved Zoe."
What?
It's a good place for you to start.
"I loved Zoe,
"and I wish I'd seen the signs,
but it wasn't the Holoband."
She was troubled.
- Give me a cigarette, Cyrus.
- You can't smoke while I'm working.
I am so sorry.
I did not mean to offend you.
But the idea of going on live TV,
quite frankly, makes me want to vomit.
Is there anything I can do
to help change your mind?
I'll give you 1,000 cubits
if you let me have a cigarette.
Done.
Thank you.
Where were you?
You weren't at school.
They called.
I was with uncle Sam.
It's not a problem, is it?
I guess not.
We won't tell your father.
On Tauron, when you're 13,
you're a man.
You make your own decisions.
Thank you, Tsattie.
He barely sees you.
He shouldn't be angry when he does.
What do you want to be?
I don't know yet.
I haven't really thought about it.
Not when you grow up.
What do you want to be now?
There was this job for kids,
where you work inside the locker rooms
with the pyramid players.
Be that.
It's just that...
Dad knows the owner,
Mr. Graystone.
I'm not sure if they're still friends.
I'm not sure if he still likes him.
You think you only get things
from friends?
You get the best things
from enemies...
Because they're scared of you.
Sam can look into it, okay?
Your uncle knows
how to make things happen.
You're the one who sent me to do this.
You're gonna have to live with it.
Just get it done.
Keep your pants on.
I'm going in now.
- Wait a minute.
- What?
Wait.
GDD.
What?
Global agents.
My guys, inside.
Just give me a second.
Everybody in?
Press, you got to stay outside!
- You can't do this here.
- Warrant.
- My husband does defense...
- The girl's room is downstairs.
Everybody wears gloves.
This warrant applies to the residence.
We're not going near your husband's lab.
If you're gonna do this to her,
I want to see this.
Doctor, please. Stay calm for a second.
We're not gonna do anything to her.
We're trying to find out
who turned her into a bomber.
Please, not her cello.
She's...
At least please tell them
to be careful with it.
Careful with the cello.
You really have to do this?
Really?
What do you think
you're gonna find here?
I really don't know...
Maybe who she met with...
who brainwashed her into believing
in a moral dictator called God...
Maybe the name of some other kid
who blew up a Caprican business
in the middle of the night.
Do you honestly think
that information's here?
Really?
In the jewelry box.
That wasn't...
I put that there.
That wasn't here.
There are loose ends, Doctor,
and I'm sorry if we have to take
your daughter's life apart
in order to put other terrorists
behind bars,
but if we have to, then so be it.
What is this to you?
Did you lose someone on that train?
I lost everyone on that train.
And...
I'll see you later.
What are you doing here?
Last time I saw you,
I had you pinned to the ground.
You said you'd help me
get to Gemenon.
Well, I was wrong.
I can't.
You shouldn't have scampered off
during the locker search.
- It made you look guilty.
- You should go.
I'm the only one here today,
and I have to have this bucket case
fixed by the end
of the afternoon, so...
- What are you doing?
- My mom does repairs, for a living.
What if someone sees us
together?
Who's seeing?
Nothing in Zoe Graystone's room.
The parents cleaned out the room.
Look at the school.
Nothing there
either minor drug stuff.
You guaranteed me
detonators and infinity symbols.
Sir, it is too clean.
Somebody got to those kids.
Please,
give me the power to access
communications to the students e-sheets,
phones.
Gee, scout leader Duram,
this slope's getting
kind of slippery.
Ben Stark and Zoe Graystone,
I guarantee you
they are not the only students
the STO turned at that school.
Now, we find out who it was
who warned those kids,
we find out who it was
who's running the operation.
You're wrong about this,
I own your or-khayss.
Tauron slang,
that's very street of you, sir.
Fine.
I'm wrong,
I'll serve them to you on a plate.
There.
That's a nice-looking chest.
I think it looks great.
So let's...
check you out, shall we?
See that we didn't glitch
any connections.
Running diagnostic test.
Look at you.
I'm gonna make you dance.
All right?
Here, try this.
Diagnostic test complete.
Last of the e-sheets for today.
Now, if we had
an up-to-date computer...
Check around 6:00 AM.
It's most likely a group-send
to the entire student body.
I've never seen you like this.
We had Ben Stark, and we let him go.
I'm sorry.
I'm not putting this all on you.
We all got complacent.
We're all responsible.
Really?
So are we all responsible
for the bad wheat crop on Aerilon?
Why are you doing it?
You're still here,
you're working as hard as I am.
It seems that Gemenese scum are luring
good Caprican kids into a killer cult.
Anyone doing that
needs to be destroyed.
I got something for Willie.
They're like jacks,
since you threw out his fancy games.
What are these, bones?
Tauron children play jacks
with the finger bones
of the Tauron children
who lose at jacks.
That was a joke.
They're bones from chicken feet.
The interview
you thought you'd never see.
Daniel Graystone coming up at 10:00
on Backtalk with Baxter...
That's the man you don't like.
Well?
It's gonna be taken care of.
Good!
The dead don't really die
until their death is avenged.
My daughter and your daughter
are caught between life and death.
He's gonna pay.
Good.
Believe me.
Hey, guys.
Welcome to Backtalk.
Thank you so much for coming out.
We have got a pretty amazing show.
I don't need to tell you why...
So let's get through this monologue
that I wrote two minutes ago.
Not that things
are perfect here on Caprica.
Some of you know that, many residents
are not too happy with the government.
- They're saying 30 seconds. Let's go.
- They think they are soft on terrorism.
So in order to protest...
I see you guys laughing over there.
Here we go.
- They're about to introduce you.
- I just... I need a second!
My gosh, they broke our back.
They sent us peppermint sticks.
And finally,
some of you may have heard,
yesterday security
was called in here,
but there's nothing
to worry about now.
It turns out
it was a huge misunderstanding.
I was only bombing figuratively.
Figuratively.
Fire half of the writing staff.
On that grim note,
let's bring out our first guest.
Needs no introduction.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome Daniel Graystone.
There he is.
The Global Defense came to the house.
They ransacked the place.
They're doing this wrong.
- There are things he has to say.
- Can we just talk about this later?
It's too late. He's on.
Thank you for coming on.
I think I may have mentioned you
a couple of times this week.
You did.
My solstice wish
was for free publicity.
Probably should have been
a little more specific.
I feel so much better
about my monologue right now.
All right, that's...
I'm sorry, listen,
This is what's going on.
- Is this water?
- That, indeed, is water.
Was there something else
in your rider that you needed?
I'm fine with water.
Can we get something stronger
for Mr. Graystone?
- We're good?
- I'm fine. Thank you.
Your wife has stated
that your daughter,
Zoe Graystone,
was involved with terrorists
and may have been...
- ... responsible for the bombing...
- We don't know anything for sure, but
it does seem she'd fallen in with
this group, the Soldiers of the One.
She was...
She was troubled...
But this started a long time
before I invented the Holoband.
- Let me tell you what I see.
- Troubled?
I see a lot of young people
growing up
in a virtual world right now.
I've actually heard
your theory about this.
- I've heard it before, and if I may...
- No theories. Let's talk facts.
Facts... your daughter...
your troubled daughter...
growing up with Holobands
and learning
that there are no consequences,
absolutely.
But...
- He was right. It's not a good word.
- It's not a good word. You know that.
But you see the thing is,
she didn't even like the Holoband.
- She didn't like it? Hated it?
- Not at all. Yes.
Maybe because it was making her
want to blow things up?
You know, and the whole...
Oh, wait.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome
Dr. Amanda Graystone.
People watching at home,
let's hit "record,"
and we'll be right back
after these messages.
This is going to be very exciting,
so stick around.
We are back.
Dr. Graystone,
this is a shock and a surprise.
It's a surprise for me too,
but I couldn't stand there.
I just had to.
You're both getting this wrong.
I'm getting this wrong.
I just flashed back to my first
and third marriages there.
I mean, Okay, I'm sorry.
I don't know why I made a joke.
Dr. Graystone,
what is your take on this?
You're out here
saying that Zoe was crazy.
Zoe wasn't crazy.
She wasn't.
Zoe was... Zoe was angry.
She was defiant.
She was rude.
She was frustrating.
- Okay.
- Well,
show me
a 15-year-old girl who isn't.
She slammed her door.
She played loud music.
She said that
we embarrassed her in public.
... she played loud music
and blew up a commuter train.
When was I supposed
to call the cops?
I don't know. Maybe when
she started worshipping
the big destruct'-o God
in the sky maybe.
We didn't know.
There weren't any signs.
You said she was troubled.
Damned...
She was angry.
It's a better word. My wife's right.
Angry, but I'd also like to add
morally blank,
because the virtual world
is a poor teacher
and doesn't teach you boundaries.
You know who would completely
agree with that is Zoe,
and that's exactly
how the STO got to her.
The... okay, I'm sorry,
you have to slow down
and back up and keep in mind
half of this audience is stoned.
She saw things
in the virtual world...
Ritual sacrifices,
games like New Cap City,
and she felt the absence
of moral guidelines,
just like you do,
like a lot of folks do.
And into that absence steps the STO,
offering this marvelous
ultimate moral arbiter.
It's quite appealing,
for a teenage girl, especially.
You're assuming all of this.
- I talked to her.
- You did?
When?
After she died, I created
a virtual version of her, an avatar.
You cre... I'm sorry.
You...
You made an electronic ghost
of your dead daughter.
I just wanted to hear
the sound of her voice again.
I sympathize.
This is very disturbing.
It is disturbing,
but show me a parent
who would not do anything possible
to try and understand their child.
- Okay, well...
- It was disturbing.
I know that.
But I was trying to make sense...
You got a bracelet?
There's a plastic bracelet
for backstage visitors.
I used the tools,
the gifts that I have to do that,
and I know she wasn't real, but...
but I could use that ID Badge.
I used the tools,
the gifts that I have to...
But it did offer some small insight
into her motivations.
If this whole thing
was a reaction to the V-world,
we're just right back
at square one, aren't we?
Isn't technology the problem?
Isn't the V-world the problem?
- Maybe.
- That's not the problem.
- I'm sorry. Maybe?
- Maybe.
I'm starting
to like you, Mr. Graystone.
We thought we could control
the content in V-world,
especially for kids,
but we've failed, clearly.
I think the temptation
to hack the code is too great.
All right,
then what is your solution?
I don't know.
- Well, think out loud.
- I don't know.
For there to be any...
any beneficial change,
you'd have to take away
the profit motive,
like when they legalized drugs,
for instance.
Okay, well, that's a good point,
but you're also talking about something
that took decades of pretty
violent arguing back and forth...
Why not?
Why couldn't we...
try it?
But this is a huge leap
you're talking about.
Graystone industries
will no longer charge
for licensing of any legal spaces
and any profit
we make off the bands will go to
some charity or...
A foundation that we can create.
For young people to find
the right experiences and values.
Okay, this is...
You're saying this now,
and I support it.
I think this is very admirable.
Are you gonna say this Monday
to your stockholders and your directors?
Great PR.
No, that's great PR.
- Yes, I can promise this.
- That's 60% of our net.
My company will make no more profit
on the Holobands
or V-world licensing.
Hold me to it, Caprica.
Okay, well, speaking for Caprica,
and you know that I like to,
we will.
Thank you, Doctors Graystone,
this was a fascinating
discussion that I was
completely unprepared for.
Thank you very much,
and I think we need to credit Amanda
with the most amazing save
since Bracken Oka...
- She's on there?
- Beat Jenkins at the horn?
She's not supposed to be.
Let's pick an analogy
where the Bucs won, okay?
Okay, I don't let my...
I could kill her
with my own hands...
Sleep well every night.
Couldn't you?
I see a lot of panicked faces behind me.
This might take a while.
- Don't say that.
- You should go home.
- All right, well, I got a taxi, so...
- I can get you a car.
I can get another one.
I'll see you at home.
- Love you.
- Thanks again.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
I'm Baxter's driver.
If you like, I could take you home.
Yeah, perfect.
Thank you.
What's your name?
I'm Sam.
- Nice to meet you. I'm Amanda.
- Nice to meet you.
You saved my life with this one.
So,
did you have something
in your locker?
- Did you get a warning?
- I can't tell you.
I can't.
I just can't.
I get why you're being cautious.
That's smart.
But I have to do this.
I have to go to Gemenon
and take Zoe's package with me.
I have to.
If there's any way
you can help me...
I can maybe set up a meeting
with Barnabas.
That's all I can do.
He's the one who can decide
if you get the STO's help.
Thank you.
Are those homemade?
- I'm sorry, what?
- Your tattoos... Are they homemade?
I'm sorry. I don't mean to pry,
but I'm a plastic surgeon.
I'm really interested
in that sort of thing.
They're cultural...
Tauron.
Oh, yes, of course.
They have meanings, right?
A lot of people here on Caprica
think they mean that you're a gangster,
but they don't.
- Of course not.
- Well, I mean, it might, but...
It doesn't have to.
You know, you get ink
because you're a parent,
or you got a fancy pedigree,
or there's some sort of ritual,
maybe made a mistake.
I could give you a fancy pedigree.
I could...
add a few accomplishments,
take away a few mistakes.
Yeah, well,
that wouldn't be real, I'm afraid.
Very little is real these days.
This isn't the way home.
Come on, Sam.
Don't.
Larry, hi. Listen,
I need to get a hold of Sam.
And it's an emergency, and it's...
He won't answer his phone.
Please.
Have him call me soon
as you hear from him, okay?
Thanks.
Turn on your frakkin' phone!
Excuse me, this isn't the way home.
There was an accident
on the thruway.
I'm just gonna cut
through Little Tauron.
Don't worry.
It's good people here...
Not very nosy...
Which is a good thing, right?
What with all those people
angry about all those deaths.
I lost my sister-in-law
and my niece on that train.
My Gods, I'm so sorry.
Well, you can't turn back time.
Nothing I could do
to change that now.
I guess all we can try and do
is understand.
Or look for some kind of balance.
Maybe try to even things out.
My sister-in-law's name was Shannon.
My niece was named Tamara.
She was gonna make us all proud.
Larry hates it
when I come home bloody.
Did you do it?
I...
can't hear you over the water.
Is it done?
Yeah, it's done.
Why you think I'm washing up, huh?
She was getting a little...
Apo-play-ktay in the car.
Didn't want a fight
in a closed space,
so I ordered her out of the car,
said we were having engine trouble,
she should go
inside this restaurant.
Connie's place, remember?
We used to go there in high school.
I know Connie's place.
I sent her inside, right?
Jacks. Nice.
And she notices right away
that there's no one inside,
'cause I called ahead just in case,
so I'm standing in the front
with the knives, the sfa-gi-dess.
- Yeah.
- Frak.
She tries to get out back
to the alley, but it's locked.
You killed her in the kitchen?
Well, that stuff
they spray at crime scenes,
can't tell the difference between
animal blood and human blood.
You really did it.
I'm messin' with you
to teach you a lesson
about yanking me around like this.
Wait.
What?
Are you...
Was that sarcastic?
What do you think?
I can't tell, Sam!
Stop frakkin' around!
Did you kill her?
I don't turn off my phone, Yoseef,
and I got other people
who call me, you know?
So, yeah...
I got your, like, 60 text messages.
I didn't kill her.
Scared her a bit.
Bet she's getting
a lot of that right now.
- You're frakkin' with me.
- I'm frakkin' with you,
I knew
you couldn't go through with it.
Frakkin' Caprican in a Tauron body.
- No, I talked to her.
- You did?
When?
Again?
Weren't you watching this earlier?
After she died, I...
I created a virtual version of her,
an avatar.
Yeah, well, I like it.
Seems like every time this family's
on TV, I get so much out of it.
I just wanted to hear
the sound of her voice again.
Feeling better?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I guess people are just...
really scared and angry right now.
I don't blame them.
I think from now on,
we both need to be
a little more careful.
So you made an avatar of Zoe.
It was nothing.
You know how it works.
It's just a picture of her,
nothing more.
I know how an avatar works,
and so do you.
Why did you do it?
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't know it got that bad.
I mean...
- You could have talked to me.
- I know. I just...
I miss her...
You know?
Yeah, I know.
I just miss her.
I miss her too.
I really...
I really do.
Want to watch TV?
Graystones are on Sarno tonight.
- I heard they were really good.
- I am so sick of them.
They're everywhere.
- Awful.
- Rich.
- Disgusting.
- Ridiculous people.