Previously on Caprica.
I thought I knew my friends.
but I guess I was wrong.
For the One True God
knows all and directs us all.
- So say we all.
I'm sorry, Zoe.
It's God's will.
Did I really even know my daughter?
You think that Zoe
knew one of the terrorists?
Dr. Graystone, we think that Zoe
might have been one of the terrorists.
D. Graystone says
he can bring my daughter back.
Can I trust him?
The device I need is called
a meta-cognitive processor.
There's only one company
that has this device, and it's not mine.
I need something stolen
from the Vergis Corporation on Tauron.
- Daddy.
- It's okay, baby.
- I'm right here.
- My heart isn't beating.
- I miss you.
- Daddy, my heart isn't beating!
My baby!
She couldn't feel her heart beat!
My daughter died
in the MagLev bombing,
but she continues to exist
in the virtual world.
Hi, daddy.
You're an avatar,
a virtual representation of Zoe.
I don't feel like a copy, daddy.
What are you doing to her?
Stop it, Dr. Graystone!
- What did you do to her?
- I captured her avatar.
She's in here now.
Daddy.
Daddy?
IRRECOVERABLE ERROR
- Who is this?
- It's me.
And I think
I'm gonna need your help.
Come here!
- Who is it, who are we gonna meet?
- You'll see.
See this infinity symbol?
It's the symbol
of the soldiers of the One.
We're the ones who are gonna bring
the word of the One True God
to the people.
Ben, there's someone here
I'd like you to meet.
She's perfect.
She'll do it.
It's all gonna change.
You're a gift...
And everyone will know it soon.
Powering down.
What are you talking about? It's been
working great in the demos for defense.
- Beyond expectations.
- And this chassis works great.
But take it out,
put it in another body, it's a moron.
Is that true?
Yes, it's true.
Put this chip in any other body,
it doesn't innovate,
doesn't anticipate.
All the bodies are identical,
but the MCP only works in this one.
Can't be.
The bodies are functionally isomorphic.
It can't know which one it's in.
Is this it?
Is this the one?
Wait, is this the same one
I was working on? Is this the prototype?
Right.
We don't know why it's happening.
In fact, when we put copies of the MCP
in other bodies,
we expected them to bond too.
But, no, they're all morons.
There's something unique
about the bonding of this chip and body
and if we don't figure out
how to replicate it,
this whole contract is in danger.
So the military liaison,
- he's all over me...
- I get the problem.
I'm gonna miss the jump.
Tell you what.
Have this thing sent to my home lab.
- I'll take a look at it this weekend.
- Take care of it.
Hey, Serge?
Yes, Amanda.
I know we have
some old home movie tiles of Zoe.
- Will you help me find them?
- Right away.
Did you get my invitation?
Right, Saturday.
Lunch at your house.
I haven't been
to a teacher's house before.
We do eat.
Can I expect you?
Good.
What's going on?
It's been two days.
Two?
My god, I'm losing track.
I've been having these dreams,
my life and the original Zoe's life
all mixed up.
Listen, Sister Clarice invited me
to her house for lunch tomorrow.
She can help us.
The only control that I have right now
is that no one knows I'm in here.
Promise me you won't tell.
I promise.
They're taking me to the lab
in Zoe's house.
Once I'm there
I might be able to do something.
I'm gonna try to get
Zoe's original program...
Frak!
Great piece of engineering.
I know.
She gives me the chills.
She?
Dude, stop feminizing it.
It's weird.
It's unnatural.
There's nothing wrong
with feminizing it.
Nothing wrong
except it's not a person.
It's useful.
Just a tool.
Lords Of Kobols :
Before The Fall.
.: La Fabrique :.
The STO espouses
a monotheistic religious philosophy,
advocating the worship
of a single all-knowing,
all-powerful God.
One month after the MagLev bombing,
GDD agents
continue to interrogate...
Graystone stock hammered today
at its 52-week low on rumors of loan...
For this exciting pyramid showdown,
the tip is just moments away.
We send it down now
to Abasi Lowe and Steve Bahara
at Atlas Arena in Caprica City.
Let's hear it
for all-star mid-corner,
number seven, J.G. Moon!
Abasi Lowe and Steve Bahara
coming to you from Atlas Arena
for the long-anticipated match
between the Caprica Buccaneers
and the Olympia Stallions.
We've been waiting for this pairing
since last year's controversial victory.
Daniel Graystone, owner of the Bucs,
and his wife, Dr. Amanda Graystone,
waving from their box,
acknowledging the crowd.
Their daughter, of course,
one of the victims of the MagLev bombing
that happened in the city
exactly one month ago tomorrow.
So say we all.
Caprica.
Thought you could stay.
Hang out.
Make fun of the cheerleaders.
That's always a good time.
But I'm not quite there yet.
Daniel, listen,
I know you're at the game.
I wanted to ask you something
about, you know,
what you showed me.
Will you call me,
let me know you're getting this?
My gods!
Wilson elementary.
This is Willie Adama's...
Adams' father.
Could you find him,
tell him to wait?
I accidentally went
to his sister's school.
Philo, aren't you done
with that thing already?
Just move your right elbow up
by about...
45 degrees.
Now rotate your hands 90 degrees.
We could have disassembled it
and loaded it twice by now.
- Now move your right arm...
- It's equipment, Philo.
To the right. It's a work of art.
It deserves some dignity.
So if you move your forearm about
three dorans to the right.
- Great, now just lean it back and...
- Come on!
- Be gentle with it, please.
- Quick and easy.
- Would you be careful with that?
- She likes it rough,
she told me.
We gotta get it to the lab,
not screw around with voice commands.
- Hey, kid.
- Hey, dad.
I'm sorry.
- Glad you got a ride.
- It all worked out.
Tammy's school?
Did you go again?
I was held up in court.
We thought we lost you.
There's an invitation.
Really?
To a memorial event?
The victims families?
I don't need this.
The Graystone give some money.
Should be eoo-pa-tree-dace.
Frack the Graystones.
Global Defense Departement.
Requesting access.
You know what?
Just let them in.
Agent Duram.
Dr. Graystone.
You can't search here. My husband
does Defense work on the premises.
I am aware.
I'm just here to ask a question
if that's okay, Doctor.
About Ben Stark.
We're looking
at any other known associates.
I don't know a Ben stark.
I've never heard that name.
- Was he the real bomber?
- Really?
Ben Stark?
He was your daughter's boyfriend.
Take a look at the picture.
My daughter didn't have one.
She wasn't old enough.
She died before...
Good night.
Get this thing inside, already.
Call it a day.
Can't believe he's getting us
to come to the lab.
He like never, never...
Frack!
What did you do?
Where you going?
Frack!
Pull the chip.
Pull the M.C.P.
- Just relax.
- Pull it.
- I'm not going to hurt you.
- Hurry up!
All right?
I'm sorry.
It's all right?
- We're good?
- We're good.
If you just wouldn't think
about what it is, you'd like it.
Not that I don't like, I'm full.
- Sure.
- It's true.
You haven't eaten all day.
Eat some of it.
- I'm full. I can't eat.
- Later we'll go out for burgers.
- I might not be full.
- All right.
- I won't make another Tauron meal.
- I'm sorry. It's just that...
I understand.
Help me clear the table.
You can do that at least.
Come on.
Would you bring
the other plates in, please?
Daddy.
I wonder why
it would freak out like that.
Didn't have any sensory reafference
under the cover.
Thrashed around
and replaced the input.
Went nuts just like
a little kid would.
- That's totally cool.
- It is, actually.
This robot,
she's doing all kinds of things
I never thought I would see her do.
Even the way it moves,
it's like you can see it think.
Look at that.
It's all out of wack.
- Must have done it in the van.
- We'll run a diagnostic.
I got it.
Still going to run it.
Hold still.
- What did you do?
- Frack.
Hospital. Come on, let go.
Get my fingertip.
- Where did it go?
- I don't know. Over there somewhere.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Found it.
All right.
You're okay.
Been wandering around
looking for your house.
- Thought I would remember it.
- It's not very memorable.
You okay?
Hard day at school.
Listen.
Can I talk to you about Zoe?
I'm just trying to figure her out.
Lacy, get in here.
What was she running away from?
Was it from us?
From me?
I don't really know.
She just said that...
there would be a new family
waiting for us on Gemenon.
A new family?
Sorry.
It's the last thing I heard her say.
So the problem with the M.C.P.
is that it's only going
to work in one body.
I think the M.C.P. is diffusing
some of the control
to the peripheral subunits
of this particular model.
So we've made exactly one soldier?
But it's a really good one.
I'm glad you like it
but our contract
is for 100,000 robots, Philo.
I couldn't find the address
and I forgot to bring, like, anything.
Don't be silly.
Come on in.
Just about to sit down.
Come on.
Let's meet everyone.
Sorry, it's crazy around here
at lunchtime.
Sorry.
I've been in a water fight all day.
That's... sure.
You must be Lacy.
I'm Nestor.
You're right.
She is pretty.
About time someone in this family
brought home someone interesting.
- Nice to meet you.
- Come on.
Is he, like, your son?
This is my husband.
He's young enough to be my son.
But don't worry, I'm not married
with everyone. Some are my friends.
These are my wives Marbeth,
And Helena and Desiree Willow.
We use her surname.
And my husbands,
there's Nestor and Tanner
and Olaf and Rashawn.
And I don't know
where the others are.
I've known a few kids
from group marriages.
- It's cool.
- Kids, turn that TV off.
Soup's on.
Let's go.
Come on.
This way you can sit next to me,
I'll look after you.
We've got hobo stew.
This one's spicy.
This one's vegetarian,
and that one is squirrel.
He's joking.
It's just regular.
- Regular sounds good.
- Regular it is.
Who needs bread?
- Want some bread?
- Nestor, can you join us?
What the heck's the matter with you?
He gave you lots of squirrel.
It's good.
It's tasty.
Little Tauron's pretty cool.
- I actually like.
- Me too.
Used to hang out here with your dad.
All the Tauron kids came here.
I'd be hopelessly trying
to flirt with some guy.
Meanwhile, your dad would get
a date with a sister.
He was lee-pa-ross.
You know that word?
- Not really.
- It means, smooth.
How'bout that? We got you
some Tauron school after all.
Hold up.
Are you sure you can do that here?
Shopkeeper's all right with it.
He's read all about me.
From where?
Here.
- Your tattoos?
- Tells a whole story.
Here, hold on to this.
Son of a bitch. I gotta take this.
Wait here, all right?
Can it wait?
I got my brother's kid with me.
I'll be there.
- Let's go.
- Was it the Gautrau?
- Don't you use that name, all right?
- Why?
I got some stuff to break.
Is this different than
your usual saturday lunch?
But it's nice.
My mom's kind of... formal.
And here, everyone's
so comfortable with everyone.
I heard...
How you lost your friends.
You must miss them so much.
Zoe Graystone
was Lacy's best friend.
A real tragedy for all of us.
She was very special.
I mean, she was brilliant.
At computer stuff, right?
That's my major.
Did you know that
there are bits of software
that you use every day
that were written decades ago?
Is that true?
That's amazing.
You write a great program,
and, you know, it can outlive you.
It's like a work of art.
Maybe Zoe was an artist.
Maybe her work will live on.
We're back from the break, and we're
gonna take a look around the league.
Really quickly.
Starting off with the team
that's had a surprisingly poor
showing early in the season
that been the Caprica City...
Working hard, I see?
I'm letting the old subconscious
find the answers.
Off.
Oh, Gods.
Think I saw this guy
in a movie once.
He was trampling Oranu.
What a monster.
Horrible.
So listen.
Tomorrow's the memorial.
I was thinking maybe we should go.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I just... I can't.
I got a picky robot.
I've got too much to do.
I know this is important,
so you should go.
But I just can't.
Sorry.
All right.
- Come on, Caesar.
- Sweetie...
Mr. Joseph Adama is at the main gate
requesting entry.
Denied.
- Thank you.
- It was a pleasure. See you soon.
This isn't a spectator sport.
You can help.
What was that?
What's going on
with Nestor and that girl?
Are you and Nestor trying to...
Nestor, did I ask you to seduce
Lacy Rand?
What? No.
Look, I understand how hard
it's been for you to...
To lose your student...
- The bombing's got us all on edge.
- You can't blame us for wondering...
Given your track record.
My track record?
If a student suffers a loss,
I help them.
The girl's lost her only friends.
I've done nothing wrong.
And if you'd wipe the slate clean,
you'd see that.
- We do, of course...
- We know how hard you work.
Look, I can't...
Do you mind if I beg off
the rest of the clean up?
I'm going for a walk.
It's sudden death.
Graystone steps up
to the line and...
Graystone eyes the shot.
Sees the angle.
What do you say, Serge?
We've been over this.
- The crowd goes frakking wild, sir.
- Thank you.
They're tearing up the seats.
It's bedlam.
Thank you.
They demand another hour
of game time, sir.
Let's fix this thing.
The same body.
Same body this whole time.
So why is this one different?
I put her in there...
Now she's gone.
But where...
Where?
She's not in the mainframe.
Where did you go?
So if she's not in there...
Why can't we copy you?
Nice car.
Looks like score, but...
But it's got 350 under the hood,
a triple-mounted clutch.
Most knuckleheads
will tell it's a bad thing.
But if you know anything about cars,
you'll realize that
what you really want is a triple C
with an undermount wedge.
That way you got control and power.
And it's all about control
and power.
All right, let's go.
Come on, let's go.
Walk, walk.
- You smashed a window.
- Don't worry about it.
Don't you understand?
You just broke a window!
- Relax.
- Crap, there's cops.
- All right, stick around.
Stick around.
Don't run.
You do, you're guilty of two things.
The thing and the running away.
- Just follow me, all right.
- Sam Adama.
Officer Mendez.
- You know what to do.
- I certainly do.
Let him cuff you.
Relax, it's okay.
So what are you doing,
running a criminal school?
You wanna join?
Better pay, top benefits.
- I think I'm good.
- Well, you think about it.
Transport for two.
Don't panic, all right?
I take care of this
with the phone call.
- I take care of the whole thing.
- How, with some kind of bribe?
Frak, say it louder, kid.
You just pay the fine, all right?
It drives them crazy.
They don't tell about paying
after one day.
You gotta know this.
- You listening?
- I'm listening.
Give in on the little things,
They miss the big things.
Now, you remember that.
That's good advice.
Do not point that camera at me.
- Can we switch?
- All right.
And this is it.
Our lives are about
to change forever.
You believe what you're saying?
I do.
I believe how beautiful I am, too.
Stop.
Why do you want
to go to the memorial?
Why?
I don't even know that I do.
Because I don't want
to think about her.
I know it sounds awful,
but it's true.
I don't want to think.
I just feel awful
- angry and numb.
- Angry at who?
Everybody and everything.
Myself and the world.
Her and the robot.
The robot didn't do anything.
No, it didn't.
I'm just going a little crazy.
Really?
What's that like?
Like you don't know.
I sure love you.
And if you still want to go
to the memorial, I'll go with you.
Because you're ready to think?
Because I promised Serge
some time alone with the UA-87.
I think he's got a little...
crush.
It's not pretty.
It's not a pretty thing.
I still can't believe
they just let us go.
I told you it was good advice,
didn't I?
- You want to hear more?
- Sure.
Someone tries to make you feel guilty,
you figure out why they're feel guilty
and you talk about that.
Also don't smoke.
You know why?
Because it's bad for you, maybe?
Life is bad for you.
You don't smoke because they can get
genetic data off a cigarette butt now.
Listen, don't tell your dad
I told you that.
Come on.
You got to get them in the thing
or they don't take them.
It's Zoe. I'm at the house.
I need you. It's important.
My God.
Something you want to tell me?
Thought you might be sick because
you didn't show up for class today.
Tauron school is boring.
It's about us.
Finding out who you are.
It's about being Tauron.
Being part of a family.
It's hard being part
of a family, dad,
when there is no family.
But you can punish me if you want.
- Very nice.
- I haven't seen you here before.
It's been a while.
You've come to the right place
to fall off the wagon.
I need privacy, a smoker
and two grams of purple.
Right.
I couldn't believe
when you said you were here.
Is it really?
It's me.
Lacy, it's me.
It's okay. You can take a good look.
This is you.
Your arms and your face.
Your voice comes out of here?
And you see here?
Your arms.
You got to tell me.
Do I look a male to you?
Frack.
But you're here walking
in the real world.
Just like Zoe said you would.
First time I've seen you
in the real world ever.
But I'm trapped.
I get manhandled and ordered around.
They loaded me like cargo.
One guy touched me,
and I hurt him, Lacy.
God.
I don't know how to help you.
What are you going to do?
I've already started some of it.
I went into the computer
and checked.
Zoe's original programme was destroyed
when he put me in here
so at least he won't be putting
any more of me,
more robots.
God.
It's confusing.
I'm Zoe, and an avatar and a robot.
Like some kind of...
What you call it? Three-parter.
Trinity.
That's what you are.
Three faces of one thing.
Sort of.
My mom called me a monster.
To be fair.
I think I could live
with this much better.
So we had to take the train
instead of walking.
- Do you want to say something?
- Gods, no.
What to say?
I see some parents
from the school over there.
- We should go and say hello.
- Sweetheart, don't talk to people.
You'll be everyone's shoulder to cry on.
I'll never be able to get you out.
Please.
Or you could say nothing
all day long?
Is that better?
He would have thanked me
if I woke him up.
But I didn't do it.
I told mom you were getting too old
to take the Lev.
I don't know how something like this
could have happened.
I love you, mom.
Natalie Stark.
Ben's mom.
Zoe's boyfriend.
There were people everywhere
asking for help.
But I didn't know
what to do for them.
I was in the back car.
You don't return phone calls.
It's okay, Sean.
Go get a drink.
Sorry about the calls.
It's been crazy at work.
You sent your bodyguard away.
You're either very confident
I'm not gonna hurt you
or afraid I'm going to talk
about a certain theft.
I've gone through his room,
and there were things Zoe left.
Costume jewelry, school papers.
I thought you'd want them.
He loved her very much.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
A group known as soldiers of the one
has claimed responsibility
for the bombing.
Now, as I'm sure you all know,
the STO espouses
a monotheistic religious philosophy.
Dr. Graystone, we think that Zoe
might have been one of the terrorists.
A purse-snatcher, yes...
but a mom?
I don't understand how something
like this could have happened.
Well...
- I need to see her again.
- You wanna talk, we can talk.
- Call my office, we'll set up a time.
- I need to see Tamara.
The Tamara that you made.
She's gone.
It was a beta test.
I went back in
to iron out some of the kinks,
and Zoe's avatar was gone.
So because Zoe's gone,
you know Tamara's gone?
It makes sense that they would
disappear at the same time.
What?
She didn't disappear
when I took that band off?
From her point of view,
you disappeared, not her.
So she might be
all alone in there...
not knowing where I went?
- Maybe stuck between dead or alive.
- Every one of you...
Not knowing what she is
or why her heart doesn't beat!
That's come up here today
has talked about...
how much you miss
the people that you lost.
I do miss Zoe.
I miss her with every breath.
But...
I don't really know
what it is that I'm missing.
My daughter had a whole life
and a boyfriend
that I knew nothing about.
Beliefs that I don't...
I don't understand at all.
Grandma,
have you seen my pyramid game?
No, dear.
Looking back, I think that she...
Only showed me
what she wanted me to see.
I just didn't know her!
You've all talked about...
how guilty you feel.
It's our job.
We create life, and then...
one day we have to face...
who they are...
what they become and what they do.
My daughter, Zoe Graystone,
died in the bombing
of Maglev train number 23.
But I think she may have caused it.
This was hers.
I found this.
My daughter was part
of the Soldiers of the One.
Get over here.
Bring the car.
My daughter was a terrorist.
I'm sorry!
My daughter was part
of the Soldiers of the One.
She was a terrorist.
Get back!
Drive.
Murderer!