I'm Wayne Malloy.
My family and I are travelers.
Our kind has been living
in this country for 150 years.
We're not listed in the phonebook,
we don't have social security numbers.
We live off the grid.
Some call us gypsies,
others call us thieves,
most though,
don't even know we exist.
I've got three kids :
a boy, a girl,
and, uh...
My wife Dahlia is just out of jail,
on parole.
We took her home
to the traveler camp.
The family gave her a warm welcome.
I, on the other hand,
got a different type of welcome.
I am the new boss.
He is the old boss.
Get over it.
Sometimes, it takes a beating to
make you realize it's time to move on.
So where are we gonna go ?
Life's a river, kid.
You gotta go where it takes you.
So, with a loan from the family bank,
I packed up the RV and went out
in search of something better.
It wasn't that long
before the family tried to stop us.
You're in the wrong lane, asshole !
Mick, look out !
Shit ! Stop !
Oh, my God, no !
Unfortunately, they stopped
someone else instead, and then they ran.
Knowing that
we couldn't go back to our old home,
we decided to visit their new home,
Edenfalls, as the Riches.
Welcome to Panco.
Doug Rich.
Meet your new team.
Panco team,
meet your new legal chief.
Aubrey's a five-star paralegal,
who wants to be a lawyer, too.
She's the hardest worker I've got.
- Would you like to take a stab at this?
- I am not a lawyer, Mr. Rich.
The Rosemere Academy,
fifteen-hundred a month,
eighteen a year.
Our school is currently full,
Mrs. Rich.
They're ain't nobody gonna tell me
I don't care about my kids.
- They're not gonna let us in.
- Yeah, they will.
We can't leave her.
Her bird is missing.
Ms. Fedley is an adult.
I'm sure she can manage.
Just give me the bird.
- Yell "over here".
- Over here !
I want to repay you.
There's nothing
you could do, Jane.
Um, Cherien...
I got the kids into Rosemere.
You know those little pills
you gave me yesterday ?
I was just wondering
if just you have like a few more.
Did you tell her where we are ?
Yeah, Di. I gave her the address
'cause I'm that dumb.
So how do I find you?
I'll pick you up.
8:00 tonight.
Hey. Look what I got.
Pink wine.
Kids okay ?
Sam's asleep.
Didi's screwin' around on the guitar.
Cal must be out with
a neighborhood kid, according to Didi.
Cal's hangin' out with buffers ?
That's what she says.
Shit.
How do you know you're pregnant ?
I just know.
We've been gone a week.
What do you mean, you just know ?
It happened before that.
Why didn't you tell me ?
God, you're acting
like you don't believe me.
I believe you, Tammy. I'm just...
No, you seem like you don't.
I'm tryin' to make sense of it.
Why else would I come
all the way out here ?
What if Dale comes after me ?
He won't.
They're never gonna know
where we are, okay ?
Come here.
- You want to get out of here ?
- No, wait a minute.
Tell me again
about the swimming pool.
It's a swimming pool.
It's heated, it's got a slide.
A slide, huh ?
Why do you keep lookin' outside ?
Who followed you ?
Is Dale outside ?
You set me up.
Shit.
Why didn't you get
that thing on a bun ?
How many times
I got to tell you, Ma?
White bread is worse
for you than heroin.
911.
What is your emergency?
He's been gone a long time.
Maybe he's taking a dump.
The car's still there.
He ain't gonna go
no place without that car.
Somethin' is up.
Shit.
Evenin', officer.
You from around here, son ?
No, sir.
Just passing through.
Yeah, we got us a report of some
unsavory activity goin' on around here.
Well, what kind of unsavory activity ?
Prostitution.
She's my ma.
I've seen stranger.
I ain't no whore.
Son of a bitch.
Hey, you watch your mouth,
dickhead.
Spread 'em.
Well, now, what do we have here ?
What name you goin' by today, son ?
Luther ray ?
Bodie ? Bud ?
There he goes, Dale.
Now, we ain't gonna be
able to follow him.
Shut up, Ma.
Or you like Armando ?
Does that work for you ?
- It works for me.
- That's a pretty good one.
Thanks.
Maybe them buffers
got the right idea.
They should do have
some strange pets though.
No shit.
Oh, baby, look.
Look at that.
What happened?
Oh, there are mosquitoes.
Scratched myself raw.
I haven't noticed them
so much lately.
- Oh, come back, baby.
- No, I'm tired.
- It's so nice out here.
- No, it's real hot.
Come and talk to me.
I'm gonna take a shower.
~SeriesSub.com~
present
Transcript:
swsub.com
Synchro:
Jarick
Golgi
Synchro:
Hutch
Season 1 - Episode 04
Been There, Done That
Mum?
Trixie ?
Someone stole her.
Who would want her ?
I didn't know
this place was zoned for llamas.
Alpacas.
If you got more than an acre,
you can keep anything you want.
Jim chose Alpacas.
They're the Cadillac
of camelids, Doug.
Jim used to be an engineer.
So, now you're...
An Alpaca engineer.
Raising alpacas has allowed me
to walk away from a corporate career
and all the stress and bullcrap
that went along with it.
- I love it.
- So you breed them for their m-e-a-t ?
Oh, god, no.
This is an investment
you can hug, Doug.
It's all about breeding stock.
Alpacas are hot.
Everyone wants one.
In three years, our Alpaca portfolio
has quadrupled in value.
On paper.
In reality, old "hercules"
hasn't impregnated a single bitch.
And to think you paid
$20,000 for him.
Give him time.
Us own fellows don't
respond to all the pressure.
Exactly what I was saying.
We haven't had sex in five years.
Really ?
Well...
Nice mug.
Thank you.
I made it myself.
Is that an eggplant ?
Okay, here we go,
one picture,
just for the school day.
- Dad, stop.
- Just for the files.
Look up, look up, look up...
That's gotta do.
Cal, will I ever get you
to look up ?
And thank you for the finger.
This is a momentous day.
Monumentally lame.
You will never regret an education.
I mean, only the educated are free.
This isn't exactly free, Dad.
So the deal is,
I have to make a lunch
for each of you every day.
- And a snack.
- Or we could just buy lunch.
No. No, I can do this.
Little baggy.
Little Sammy.
You want a snack too, huh ?
- Bye, Mam.
- Bye, baby.
Bye, baby.
Don't call me "baby".
Make it a great day.
- Could you be more annoying?
- I'm not annoying.
I'm taking a photograph...
a video.
Bad enough
that he's going to school.
It's amazing that
I can work this thing.
You got that right.
Gotta go.
So what are you gonna do today ?
Be a buffer wife. Isn't that
what I'm supposed to do here ?
We're gonna be late for school.
You just don't want me to screw
things up for you, do you Wayne.
Dad, we're gonna be late.
Bye. Have a great day.
Make a lot of money.
Who is this ?
You called me.
What do you want?
Tell Doug I know where he is.
No, there is no Doug, okay ?
There is no Doug.
You got the wrong number.
You gotta stop calling here, okay ?
You understand ? Just stop calling here.
There's no Doug !
- Hi.
- Hi, Nina.
- Can I come in?
- Well, sure, honey.
You cookin' ?
Chicken tortilla soup.
I'm making it for the party tomorrow.
Y'all are comin', aren't you ?
Well, good, 'cause we burns
throw a hell of a party.
How do you cook every day ?
I mean, do you like it ?
Well, we have to eat, don't we ?
- So what's wrong, hon ?
- Nothing.
It doesn't look like
nothing from here.
Well, Nina...
Do you know those little pills
we like to share?
Do you think...
people like us,
who like little pills like that, ...
have a little problem ?
You mean like a drug problem ?
Maybe.
Oh, honey.
It's not a drug problem.
Those are prescription pills.
Cause sometimes...
I feel like I really need
something to get by.
Of course, you do. We all do.
Everybody needs something
to get by every now and then.
Alcee Stringer,
down the street,
all she does is eat broccoli
and exercise all day.
And Boyd Harrelson,
he's addicted to animal porn.
We have to watch
our Alpacas at night.
And Gunner Mowbrey's wife
left him for their best friend's
17-year-old son.
Oh, man, that's terrible.
In her defense,
he was a mature seventeen.
Anyway, what's a little pill or two?
I mean, life's hard, Dahlia.
We all just do the best we can.
Amen.
I always say, as long as nobody's toes
get stepped on, who gives a damn ?
And Jim don't care?
Jim wouldn't notice
if I had a sex change operation.
He's too busy
with those shitty alpacas.
White widow, great shit.
Neighborhood kid sells it.
I love you, Nina.
I love you, too.
- Who is it ?
- Hi,
we're the welcoming committee
from temple beth el.
Uh, y'all got the wrong house.
I don't know anyone named beth.
May we come in ?
I'm real busy right now.
Oh, we'll make it quick, hon.
Cherien, I'm Helen Weiner.
We spoke on the phone.
I handled your membership.
My membership ?
For the temple.
We got your check.
Oh, right.
The temple.
We just wanted to fill you in,
give you a chance to join
a chavurah with the temple.
There are a lot of
goyim around this area.
This is a great way
to meet other jewish families.
Jewish families ?
Well, it's not temple.
But there are about
of 800 of us here.
We're jewish.
- Yes, we know.
- We're jewish, yeah.
That's an interesting
necklace, cherien.
It looks like a cross.
Well, actually... You...
You're looking at it sideways.
It's a "x."
You know, it's like one of them
"x marks the jew" necklaces
from wal-mart.
Wal-mart ?
Okay. Thank you for stopping by.
Okay, I gotta clean my house.
Okay. Bye-bye.
We are jewish now.
Jesus.
Good morning, tuesdays.
- Kimmie.
- Good morning, mr. Rich.
Love that color on you.
Aubrey, how's it going ?
Mr. Panetta just nixed
my summer vacation.
Apparently, I haven't
served my full two years.
I just bought the tickets.
Four days, five nights, costa rica.
- Right. He can do this ?
- Why don't you ask him ?
He's in your office.
- What's he doing in my office ?
- I have no idea.
- Bright and early.
- Yep. Catching the worm.
Afraid not.
That worm's long gone.
I'm always in at six.
So, Doug, got a little matter
I need you to handle.
Little pr thing, no big deal.
Right up your alley.
Panco sucks !
Where's the other lawyer ?
The other gentleman
no longer works here for a reason.
I would like to say to you
that Panco hears and
understands your grievances,
and we are working
to get a quick resolution
to your concerns.
If you could now please disperse
and go home, I think we could all get-
This is just another bunch
of Panetta's bullshit.
- Where is Panetta anyway ?
- Mr. Panetta-
We've already told you how to
resolve this. Buy back our homes.
That's the only resolution
that works for us.
- Buy back your homes ?
- Why would we buy back your homes ?
Because you knowingly
built halcyon trails on the site of a
former military
practice bombing range.
There's unexploded ordnance
all over the place.
- Ordnance ?
- Bombs, rockets, charges, mines.
Don't forget my dog.
Carol's dog went missing.
And all they found was a leash
and an awfully suspicious
crater out by her doghouse.
- Sir, what is your name ?
- Martin Chambers,
president of homeowners
against Panco. Ask Panetta !
- He knows my name really well.
- Mr. Chambers,
we're not interested in people,
or pets blowing up.
I mean, I mean, we are completely
against anyone blowing up.
I mean, even a little bit.
But you know, sometimes...
sometimes in your life...
Shit just happens,
you know ?
You know it does.
I mean, you're just going along,
living your own life,
living in your house,
just money your own business,
suddenly, kapow !
Your whole life explodes.
Just like in, uh--
well, but then,
what are you gonna do ?
You gonna give up ?
You gonna just call it a day ?
No. No, that's not
what we do.
No, we rally.
We-- we turn it all around.
Because we're americans.
We take those grenades and
we turn them in into lemonade,
because that's what
distinguishes us from sand crabs.
We keep going.
And I ask this of you because
I ask nothing less of myself.
Thank you.
Thank you for your time.
- Hey, how'd it go ?
- Swell.
How long have you been
dealing with these people anyway ?
They're all a bunch
of nutcases. I'll back'em down.
Thanks for coverin'.
I can't stand that Chambers asshole.
I just got off the phone
with Jolinda's Attorney.
Your ex-wife.
Apparently, she plans
to start garnishing your wages,
unless you make good
on the payments.
How long you been
holdin'out on her ?
Oh, I get it, Doug. Believe me,
I get it. Got an ex-wife of my own.
Couple of'em, actually.
Nothin' I'd like more than
to stiff' em on alimony
and child support. But
I don't like trouble, and I don't want
anyone snoopin' around my business,
so take care of that,
won't you ?
Oh, the attorney didn't have
your address, but...
it's only a matter
of time before he gets it.
My ex-wife.
They always find you.
What do you think,
that Fitzgerald was trying
to say about society ?
I don't know.
I don't relate.
Well, that aside,
do you think that
Fitzgerald was trying to present
a positive portrait of the Rich ?
Okay, well, clearly,
fitzgerald was
preoccupied with money and
social status in all of his novels.
So the question, people, is,
do you think that the buchans
ever really accept gatsby ?
- Delilah, have you read this book ?
- It's didi.
And, yes. But, no, I don't think
that they ever accepted him
'cause he wasn't born
like them. Rich.
You know, he had all that money, and
he threw all those parties and stuff,
but when it really
comes down to it,
people just wanna
stick to their own kind.
But gatsby had money.
Why wasn't he happy ?
Well, all the money in the world
couldn't buy him what he really want.
the girl.
You know,
money isn't everything.
I guess
he just never really
figured that out.
Good. Didi,
that's very good.
Aubrey. Aubrey...
I want you to do
a little research for me.
I'm already working on
the Halcyon trail thing for you.
Forget about that for the moment.
This is important.
I want you to find out
everything you can,
about this woman's
- divorce
- Jolinda Rich ? Who's she ?
Doug's ex-wife.
My ex-wife.
When I'm nervous, I refer
to mysel in the third person.
So I'm looking for
Douglas Rich versus Jolinda Rich ?
Yes. No.
Howard Douglas Rich
versus Jolinda Rich. Yes.
So am I looking for anything specific ?
I mean,
this was your divorce, right ?
Yes, but it was traumatic,
so I've just blanked
everything out.
Whatever.
Oh, and, Aubrey, Aubrey.
Also,
find out everything you can
about this pensacola divorce attorney.
- Randall prutt the third ?
- Yeah, everything you can.
Give me one good reason why
I shouldn't report you to the cops
for stealing my wheels.
I don't know what you're talkin' about.
Is that a good reason ?
I saw you return
the car last night.
Look, wait.
Oh, you think you're hot shit,
don't you ?
So, hot shit...
Can you break
into anything else ?
What'd you have in mind ?
An ex-wife ?
- He has an ex-wife ?
- No, it's not-
- Oh, god, it's over. We are screwed.
- No, no. You're panicking.
I'm being realistic.
We have gotta get out of here now.
- Look, baby-
- Don't touch me.
I told you this would happen.
I told you this would happen !
That woman on the phone,
she knows where we are.
- No, she doesn't.
- Yes, she does. She called today.
You told me not
to answer the phone.
What's she gonna do
when she shows up,
and she finds you impersonating
her ex-husband,
and us living in this house,
stealing all of his stuff ?
Calm down.
I am not going back to prison.
- No, you are not going back to prison.
- That's right,
'cause if anyone's going back to prison
this time, it is gonna be you.
And that way, you get to feel what
it's like to be scared and alone.
Is that why you started using ?
Those tracks on your arms,
they're not mosquito bites, are they ?
Don't you think we got bigger things
to think about right now ?
Like how come,
once again, I listened to you
and this has all turned to shit.
I wanna know if you're getting high.
I want the truth.
You want the truth ?
The truth is I'm pretty sure
I can't trust you anymore.
That is the truth.
That is the goddamn truth.
- Aubrey,
- Yeah ?
tell Hugh I'll be unavailable today
'cause I'll be in the field.
Where are you going ?
- You know the field ?
- Yeah.
Well, I'll be in it.
Okay, you can reach me
on the cell phone.
- Where are you going ?
- Don't even start. You need me.
- How much you got there ?
- Seventeen grand.
Cash advance on some
of Doug's plastic.
What about the lawyer guy ?
Aubrey's done some research.
Seems he isn't exactly big potatoes.
Works out of an office in pensacola.
Works solo.
Member of the local turf club,
got suspended once for
some kind of financial impropriety.
- Gambler.
- I think.
- Still, I could be wrong.
- I know.
Okay. I'm struggling here.
Why do you wanna break into the school ?
Believe me.
There's nothing here worth anything.
See, that's where
you're wrong, man.
The school computers
are the key to our futures.
You get us inside that building,
my buddy lane here
will take care of the rest.
- Got an alarm system ?
- Yeah.
Video surveillance,
motion sensors ?
- Hell, no.
- Oh, shit.
- This is gonna be a piece of cake.
- How do you know all of this ?
Prison.
I'm not using.
Personally, I don't get these guys
with money who think
they can just walk away
from their responsibilities.
But it makes us
a good living, don't it, jeff ?
Well, it certainly helps pay
for some of those trips to tahiti.
Sorry, I'm late, darling.
Sorry.
- How do you do ?
- Randall Prutt,
may I present
Julia Gardner-Jones.
- It's nice to meet you, ma'am.
- Nice to meet you.
So sorry about all of this.
You buy a Maserati
and what you don't know
is how long it spends
in the garage getting tuned up.
I mean, what is it,
a bloody cello ?
Anyway, down to business.
Now, the good news is,
is that our client
has agreed to give
Jolinda the sum total
of his liquid assets,
which is here.
And how much would that be ?
$17,000.
- 17,000 ?
- Yeah.
The bastard owes 75.
Holy shit.
I mean, this is a down
payment, of course.
17,000. The rest will be paid
in six months or so.
Probably less time.
Last time I checked, your client
had half a million dollars in assets.
Then it disappeared
along with Doug,
and the trail went cold.
So where's he hiding
the extra 483 grand ?
Stocks ? Real estate ?
Are you implyin' that our client
has some sort of secret investment ?
And how is he payin' you ?
Or are you flyin' to
Tahiti on your charm ?
We are not at liberty to discuss this.
It's a total violation-
to hell with
attorney-client privilege.
I'm guessin' that our Doug
has sucked his money away
in some golden goose,
and you're gettin' the benefit
of one or two eggs.
That's the first time I've heard royal
rhapsody referred to as a golden goose.
Darling ?
Royal rhapsody, huh ?
Is that a racehorse ?
Oh, my golly gosh.
We have to go.
We have to catch
a flight to Monte-Carlo.
I know a thing or two
about horses racin', you know, and-
Oh, well, horses are fine for
a couple of thousand here or there.
Very sorry about this situation.
Look, just call me on the mobile.
We don't take off till 3 :00.
So sorry.
Thanks awfully.
We just moved in.
It's very nice.
We- we haven't really
had a chance to unpack or
really do anything at all.
It's cool.
Shit. It's almost 3:00.
What do we do now?
I mean, he doesn't have to dig very
deep to find out we're full of shit.
Damn.
I thought I could smell his greed.
Maybe your instincts are
off like last time.
The credit card scam was a bad idea.
I never liked it, I told you,
and you didn't listen,
because you're too busy
being turned on by the risk.
- It was no big deal.
- No, not until they busted me.
I trusted you.
I trusted your instincts.
I don't know what I can do about that.
I cannot do anything about that.
- I can't give you the two years back.
- I'm not talkin' about two years.
Screw them.
I'm talkin' about right now
and how you do not trust me at all.
Because you keep getting
high and lying about it.
My god. Jesus!
You wanna go there?!
Do you?!
I started using speed in prison,
and it turns out,
I really, really liked it.
- I knew it was bad--
- it wasn't that bad.
Prison wasn't that bad.
What was bad was
the way I felt about you.
Do you have any idea
what it is like to hate the personn,
you love the most in the world.
And all you can do to escape
feeling that way
is getting amped.
This is part of who I am now,
no matter where we live,
no matter who I'm pretending to be.
I have not
shot crystal meth
since I left prison.
It's him.
Hey, it's me.
We're in the bloody plane.
All right, we'll be there
in five minutes.
That's an f.
- "a" minor.
Weird.
Alpacas.
I'll be damned.
- I can only imagine what--
- Can the shit, julia.
There are no secrets
in the age of Google.
Royal rhapsody is an Alpaca,
sold for $600,000 at auction in 2003.
Now his whole line is ready to breed.
What's your point, Randy?
What if I had a way
to satisfy your fee
and my client's judgment
in cash,
not even a little money left ever
for you guys to put in your pockets?
You're heroes, I'm a hero,
y'all spend a few extra weeks
on the beach in Monte Carlo.
We're listening.
I can tell you guys aren't stupid,
so I'm assuming
Doug's planning to pay
you with a very
special Alpaca.
Hercules is worth more to us
than a few weeks on the beach.
He's the last herdshire
of his generation
that Doug is willing to part with.
And he's not for sale.
Everything's for sale.
Everything's for sale
You see,
my wife,
is an animal lover,
and her birthday is
comin' up next month,
and I think she'd just love
little ol' Hercules.
I'll give you
80 gs.
You've got to be joking.
I mean, his stud fee alone is 5,000.
Per squirt.
And if the filly's feeling frisky
and he gets off twice
- it's double.
- Ninety, then.
He's not for sale.
I'd rather sell julia.
Come on, folks.
We all know this is the best way.
This way, we all get off fat.
And you know very well
that if I come after your client,
you may not be able to hold on
to that Alpaca anyway.
You must be aware that
this is all highly unethical.
I don't get win if you made
this kind of proposal.
you could be...
- Disbarred.
You mean, we could
all be disbarred,
which is why
I'm not worried about it.
I know that you'll perform
to the letter.
One hundred
and twenty grand,
and that's it.
And only because
I love my wife.
You don't have to give her all of it.
What do we do when Prutt figures out
that Hercules is shooting blanks?
What's he gonna do, call the cops?
Be careful.
God damn it, Wayne.
I wish I could offer you
more than money.
You can.
I can?
I want an apology
from him
in his own words
That could be a little hard
to get right now.
I won't accept this money
without an apology.
He owes it to me.
Well...
I'll see if I can get him
on the phone.
What are you doing?
I'm sitting here with Jolinda.
Yes, she's got the money.
But she woud like to talk to you.
Are you crazy?
I actually think
this could help, Doug.
I have no idea what
you're talking about
'cause there's no way
she's gonna believe I'm Doug.
He feels horrible.
What?
And he's deeply, deeply sorry.
Bullshit.
She's not buying it, Doug.
Well, the woman is pissed off,
and I do not blame her
being married to that bastard.
Ask me, I'm glad he's dead.
Okay, Doug, I hear you.
He says he has deep regrets.
And,
That he was having
a big ol' mid-life cris,
and...
He had a horrible mid-life cris.
He gained 80 pounds
and lost all his hair.
He's gained a lot of weight,
and he's gone bald.
I don't give a shit about his hair.
Tell him our house was foreclosed on
and my electricity was shut off.
His children spent a month
in a homeless shelter.
How does he feel about that?
What an asshole.
Did you get that?
Tell her he missed his kids more
than he could bear.
He says
he missed his kids.
He sure didn't act like it.
Tell her,
they're the only thing
give his life meaning.
And most of the time...
He not even really sure
who he is anymore.
Tell her anything.
He says he's sorry,
he hurt you.
that you're the last person
he wanted to hurt.
He's crying.
Crying?
Like a baby.
I'm sorry Doug, what was that,
I didn't get that.
I didn't say anything.
I think Doug would wish
he could be different.
I wish he would
have done it different.
And I think
he would ask for forgiveness.
I think may be
we all need to be asking
for little forgiveness
right about now, baby.
I know.
I hate you.
But it's much than I hate you.
I love our kids even more.
And I'm grateful for that.
You're right.
About the credit card thing.
He wasn't thinking of anyone.
Anything else.
It's turn on by the risk.
Sorry.
I'm very, very sorry.
I'm sorry too.
Come on up.
Hey, help me to close the windows.
Shit.
How are we getting
in there now?
Break the glass.
No, no, children not to worry.
This...
called "bumping".
Come on ???.
That was too...
How freakin' cool is this?
Would you look, The Riches are here.
Let me get you a Pomegranate Martini.
There are wonderful.
I had three already.
So Jim, how's enginering.
Hey neighbors.
You got here before we all take exctasy
and dive naked into the pool.
Seriously?
It's happened.
Well, excuse me boys,
I'm gonna go powder my nose.
Come on.
I want you to meet some people.
I've got something for you.
What's this?
A consolation price.
Sold out that dead Alpaca of yours.
25,000$
Been there, done that.
Come on, let's get a drink.
I'm surprise you show your face
at the party after
playing hookie all day, body.
Yeah, you got me, Hugh.
You're fired, Doug.
I'm just kidding.
See.
Come on I need another drink.
Okay my man, you now have
an A minus in calculus.
Nice.
I wanna know something.
What's so great about Princeton.
It's Ivy League man,  in about
a million miles away from my dad.
Let's get Avy Vincent
a D in litterature,
she'll totally shit herself.
- For sure.
- No. Don't do that.
It'll just call the attention
on yourselves if you get caught.
You two should go
on a business, though.
What do you mean?
It seems that lot of kids
have been looking for good grades.
Don't you think?
You're a lot smarter
than you look my friend.
Thank you.
Come baby.
You come?
By the way,
we're Jewish.
~SeriesSub.com~