Last season on The Riches...
Now, who buys a house on the internet?
- A rich man.
- What about his job?
Someone's gonna come looking for him.
You gonna tell me no one's coming
throught them doors tomorrow?
I don't know who's coming.
Okay, I'm confused.
I don't get it. What's the angle here?
- How are we bleeding them?
- We're not bleeding anyone!
- Oh, we're not?
- Then what are we doing here, dad?
The American Dream.
What?
We're gonna steal it.
Hi, I'm Doug.
Doug Rich! Meet your new team.
Panco team, meet your new legal chief.
Come and meet our new neighbors.
I'm Jim. This is my wife, Nina.
Andrea said we should
introduce ourselves.
How do you do?
I'm Mrs. Doug Rich.
Haven't you read Calder v. Bull?
Have you read Hester v. Strapeling?
Ratson v. Catson?
You are the best goddamn lawyer
I ever met.
Dad, we have to do something.
Dale came here for us.
Dale seems to have been here
for a while now.
He could have blown our cover
at any point, he didn't. Why?
He's Dale. He's working an angle.
I don't know.
We have a lot to talk about, my friend.
Doug is a republican.
His best friend is Pete.
Pete's a mortgage broker from Dallas.
He's e-mailed twice about a golf trip.
Is Doug here?
Doug who?
Guess you're probably surprised
to see me here, Wayne.
You and I both know
you're not Doug Rich.
Though everyone here...
seems to think you are.
Who are you?
And where the hell
is my best friend, Doug Rich?
I don't like Wild Berry.
Yeah, you do.
You like it. Okay.
Got about an hour.
It's Hugh.
We don't have time.
Can we talk?
It's 4:00 in the morning.
She locked the doors on me.
We got to go!
We had this fight. I said some stuff.
I called her names.
Pete is not dead!
He is asleep! We do not have all day!
The saddest person she ever met.
She didn't mean that.
- She was upset.
- We are heading out!
I'm sitting here telling you I need you.
I'm on my way.
Oh, dear lord.
What happened to you?
I won't ask.
I won't tell.
I know.
I just wish...
I could come with you.
I just wish I had the guts.
Everything okay up there?
Please, help me!
You're...
That guy in the truck.
I'm a handyman.
Where are we gonna go? Mexico?
- I vote Canada.
- It's too far, Di.
What do you say, baby?
Wherever we go,
we got to go right now.
Mexico it is.
Sorry, Didi,
I could do with a margarita.
So, this,
Doug and Cherien,
the Riches?
You've known them for years?
They're real?
Or they were.
And these people,
wherever they are,
they took over their lives.
Information like that
you could hold over somebody's head.
You could use that to get some green.
You mean blackmail them?
Are you out of your mind?
I don't want money!
I want my friends!
We got to go to the police,
have those two arrested.
I have to find out what
they've done with my friends.
Oh, my God! What am I doing here?
What's wrong with me?
- They're getting away as we speak.
- No, they're not going anywhere.
Distributor cap's gone.
Shit!
Great, what the hell are we gonna do?
- That's got to be Dale.
- The guy's probably awake by now.
No. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay 'cause,...
your dad has a plan.
Are you coming?
Yeah, Pete,
I'm coming.
Let's go for a little stroll.
You don't have a plan.
Well, not at the moment.
We got to get out of here.
How much money we got?
- 7 grand.
- 7 grand?
Your dad fakes it as a lawyer
for three months
and all we got is 7 grand?
Calm down. There's nowhere to run to.
We got to get out of here.
If Pete wakes up, calls the cops,
we're gonna get busted
for killing the Riches.
This is what we'll do.
I'll go back to the house.
I'll get the Mercedes,
and pick everyone up.
- The house could be crawling with cops.
- I'll take that risk.
Dale could be waiting for you anywhere.
- Well, I'll take that risk.
- Sam's gone.
Wait, wait, wait!
- Baby, what the hell?
- I have a plan.
Okay, what's your plan, sweetheart?
- Where did you get this?
- In the woods where you buried it.
I want to give it to Pete.
You're gonna bribe Pete?
You had this all along
without telling us?
- I was saving it for a rainy day.
- Oh, my God.
When your dad had
to break into Hugh's office
so that Dale wouldn't kill him,
- that wasn't rainy enough for you?
- Not as rainy as this.
You're gonna bribe Pete?
No, you can't, sweetheart.
You can't bribe men like Pete.
- Not with this.
- Why not with this?
Money makes the world go around.
Every man has his price.
Okay, good try.
Go wait for us in the RV.
All right.
Get in the car.
What's wrong? Get in the car.
I want you to grab the kids,
get the hell out of here.
I will meet you in Galveston.
Wayne, get in the goddamn car.
I'm not going, baby.
Got the 40 grand
and the 7 grand we saved up.
I'm gonna talk to him.
Like Sammy said,
money makes the world go around.
He's a little boy. You're a grown man.
There's things you want,
and there's things that are.
- You got to know the difference.
- I have to try.
You can't bribe Pete.
Don't you get it? He's honest.
Then I will buy you a little time
and get you closer to Mexico.
Get in the goddamn car.
If anyone's going to prison,
this time it's me.
Where are you, Pete?
Pete, you okay?
Jesus!
I scared you.
- Rough night, huh?
- Go shit yourself!
"Pete, you okay?"
Where is he?
I love this part.
I spilled a little bit on your bed.
Really nice bed.
It's very soft, pillowy.
Where are you, Pete?
What did you do with Pete?
The mailbox of the subscriber
you are trying to reach...
Pete who?
I'm just pulling your leg.
You're talking about your buddy, right?
Your buddy Pete.
Where are you, Pete?
You're really
gonna want to see this one.
Yes, Sirree.
Is that...
you...
Doug?
Is that you...
and your lovely wife?
What do you want?
What do I want?
I want to sit down
and formulate a little plan.
Blow it out your ass.
So what did you do? Did you kill them?
Move into their house,
start living their lives?
Is that what you did?
You stole their names?
- I didn't kill anyone.
- Where's Doug and Cherien Rich?
Where the hell
are Doug and Cherien Rich?
I got all the cards.
I'm holding all the cards,
and you're holding none.
What do you want to do?
Where is he?
Screw you.
It's just a little blood. Calm down.
Right now. Where is he?
- Put that thing away.
- Where is he?
Pete's alive.
He's just a little hurt, but he's fine.
Bullshit.
He was gonna go to the cops.
I had to stop him.
I did you a favor.
I did you a favor!
Wait. I did you a goddamn favor, Wayne!
Where are you go... I did you a favor!
- What are you doing?
- None of your damn business.
Do you think I'm stupid?
Do you think I'm a moron?
You ain't gonna find him.
He is safe and sound, tucked away.
The mailbox of the subscriber
you are trying to reach is full.
Transcript
swsub.com
Subtitles
Grischka
Jarick
THE LAST TEMPTATION OF WAYNE
Hey, man.
Man, wake up.
Come on, wake up!
You killed him.
I just... I hit him, and then...
But he fought back.
You murdered him!
- I did you a favor.
- You murdered him!
You were in a shit storm,
and I swept up all the shit.
Back up.
You owe me
a big goddamn favor, Doug Rich!
- Just back up.
- What are you doing?
Getting the hell away from you!
I'll call the cops.
- I'll call the cops on you.
- I don't care!
They'll think that you did it
'cause people saw you with Pete.
Call them, then! Go on, call them!
I will tell them...
that you killed the Riches.
Go ahead and do it, goddamn it!
Shit.
Jesus.
Help me get him in the house.
Come on.
All right, mama. Mind your head.
Get your foot in. Here's your blanket.
What are you doing?
- It's my stuff.
- Take that back.
Come on, I actually bought this shit.
You should have robbed it,
we're only taking necessities.
If you ask me,
you never should have let him go back.
- I'm not asking you.
- Yeah, mom, it's bad luck.
Don't say that!
It's bad luck. We work
when we're together. You know that.
We're not together, okay?
Your dad is a stubborn ass.
- We have to wait for him.
- We have to go back.
Don't you think I tried?
Okay, look, I know you're scared.
This is what we do.
We can do this, all right?
We split, we come back together,
we go on the road...
This is how we live our lives.
Have you forgotten?
Go on. Go close up the RV. Let's go.
- You can't take all those books.
- How many can I take?
None of them.
I mean, we're fully loaded up.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
We don't need
these damn buffer clothes anyhow.
Don't tell your brother or sister.
Easy there, Speedy.
You got to keep your eyes on the road.
Eyes on the road, mom.
Watch it!
Shit. Sorry.
What the hell is that?
Mom, what is that?
Oh, shit. Nina?
I changed my mind.
As it happens, I do have 'em.
Have what?
The guts.
Nina, sweetheart,
you can't come with us.
My life's in shambles, Dahlia.
My future's bleak.
My marriage is bust.
I mean, look at me.
Do I look like a woman
with something to lose?
I guess not.
We can't.
Get in the back.
Come on.
Get in, gypsy Rose Lee.
Sorry, grandma.
Come on, Sammy.
You don't need all that space
for your little butt.
What's wrong with Justin?
Don't move. Hugh?
Keep this against your head, okay?
Justin's blessing.
Who are you?
I'm Doug Rich.
- Your friend.
- Then why did you try to kill me?
I didn't know you were there!
Bullshit.
I was just back...
I was coming to see you!
That's really bullshit.
You never even asked where I was.
Jesus! Who the hell is that?
Hey, there, Mr. Panetta.
Doug, what the hell's going on?
Hugh, this is Dale.
He is a local handyman.
He's just helping me around the house.
At 4:00 in the morning.
We had a spillage.
Okay, just stay here.
We have been acquainted,
Mr. Panetta, at your wedding.
That's a sweet ride
you have out there, the Denali.
Vortec, 6.2-liter.
I'm gonna have one of those one day.
If I work hard.
That's what I tell myself.
Whatever floats your boat.
- Help you out.
- Easy. Easy.
- What?
- Your hands.
Kind of dirty.
So, I don't like it.
Germs.
Little germs never hurt nobody.
No, I said don't... Geez!
Tell him not to touch me!
Get away!
Get away from me!
- Morning, officer.
- Is this your vehicle, sir?
It is. I am so sorry.
You realize that it's illegally parked
up here on your lawn.
I know.
I need the bathroom so bad, I just...
I'm sorry to bother you
at this time of night,
but we just can't have this.
I understand.
This is no bother at all, officer...
I'm the new co-head
of Edenfalls security.
It is very good to meet you,
officer Delroy. I am Doug Rich.
- So you'll re-park the vehicle?
- Absolutely.
I will. The key's inside. I'll just...
- When?
- It'll be done.
I will do it right away.
Car sounds awful.
Mom, it's getting worse.
- You got to pull over.
- We can't stop.
Cops may have an apb out on us.
The car is bleeding antifreeze, ma.
Would you just stay with me, please?
We're gonna pull to the next town,
dump this piece of shit,
and Cal's gonna steal us a new car
'cause that's what we do.
Mom, I really don't want
to go to Mexico.
You're gonna have to go,
because it's either that or prison.
Adios, amoeba.
Let's freaking cucaracha.
So, Doug is not a lawyer.
- He isn't even Doug.
- His name's Wayne.
Wayne Malloy.
- And you're Dahlia Malloy?
- That's right.
And the kids?
Kids are Malloys, too.
Then who are the Riches?
I don't know.
You mean you never met them?
We just stole their credit cards.
We're not their best friends.
So you're con artists.
That's right.
Some kind of identity thieves.
We're drifters, Nina.
We are grifters and drifters
and nomads.
We are the scourge
of the goddamned earth.
We are travelers!
Right?
Don't make Mama sing!
Come on.
Busted flat in Baton Rouge
Waiting on a train
Feeling about as faded as my jeans
Bobby flagged a diesel down
Before the rain drove it
all the way to New Orleans
Would you sing with me?
We're living large. We're on the road.
Come on, goddamn it. Sing.
Freedom's just another word
for nothing left to lose
Nothing, I said nothing, hon,
if it ain't free
And feeling good was easy enough when
Bobby sang the blues
- Feeling good was good enough for me...
- Shit.
And there she goes.
Nice. That's good, mom.
Oh, shit.
I should have stopped earlier.
Bobby McGee.
What the hell's going on?
Just be calm.
Keep that ice bag against your head.
Don't you tell me what to do.
You keep your dirty hands away from me.
Shut up, Hugh!
- Don't tell me to shut up! I say...
- You shut up.
- Car keys.
- What?
Give me your car keys right now.
Hold on. I...
Shit.
You lost your car keys?
Oh, no. Shit.
Shit. It's...
No, it's...
You looking for this?
Fell out of your coat
while you was unconscious.
Thought I'd keep it for safekeeping.
Thanks.
Tussey custom-molded grip.
Matter of fact it is.
Fact it is.
Sweet.
Okay, car keys now.
Quickly!
So, Dale...
Know your tussey, huh?
Yeah, I know my guns.
I can't find the keys.
I'll move it first thing in the morning.
Is that your vehicle, too?
yes, that is.
- You got a busted tail light there.
- Yes. Fender bender.
With the Denali?
You can't drive around like that.
- I know.
- You want some help with it?
I'll be fine.
They probably got
some replacement bulbs in the trunk.
I believe they do.
But I'll be fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- It'll only take a second.
- I like to do those things myself.
It shows you're the man about the house.
What's that?
What was that?
Well, that sound.
Was that an owl?
- Sounds like a cellphone.
- Oh, that's my cellphone.
In the trunk?
Aren't you gonna answer it?
Well, it's 5:00 in the morning.
It could be important.
Not at 5:00 in the morning.
My kids, they did this.
That's where they hid it.
- Okay, it's none of my business.
- I've been looking for it all day.
The kids, they just...
My eldest...
I just can't do, he just does this.
It's none of my business, sir.
You have a good evening.
Thank you very much.
That was a gunshot.
That sounded like a loud cough.
- I have to investigate this.
- I don't even have a gun, actually.
I know who it is.
- It's my friend, and he has...
- I have to do my job.
Step away from the path, sir.
I can't do that 'cause I pay your wages,
and I know my rights here.
- Step away from the path now!
- I will not do that.
- Step away from the path, sir!
- I can not do that.
I tried to tell you, Dale.
That's this kind of hair like triggers.
Sure does!
Who the hell are you?
I have reason to believe
there was a gunshot.
Nope, there no gunshot.
Sir, I heard a gunshot.
Are you the owner of the...
- Who the hell are you?
- Hugh, calm down.
This is officer Moody.
Officer Delroy Moody.
Security. He's not even a cop.
Sir, I'm gonna ask you again.
Where is the gun?
Shut up.
Don't give it to him, Dale.
- I think your friend is a little drunk.
- He's trespassing!
You tell him,
"go home."
Shut up.
Sir, let's just try
to be responsible here.
He's got no power.
He's a rent-a-cop.
He is bullshit!
Now, be a man
and tell him to go home!
Sir, please.
You heard the man.
Go home.
Jesus, Dale!
- I didn't say pull the gun on him.
- Dale...
Give the officer the gun, please.
I said "go home."
I can't go home.
I am on duty.
This is my job.
If I see alcohol
and there is a gun involved,
I'm required by law
to confiscate the gun.
Come get it.
No, I said come and get it,
bullshit man.
Put the gun down, Dale.
You make me.
Just how do you want this to end?
Do you want to take him out, too?
Do you want to go to prison...
or...
do you want to be my partner?
Just how much blood
do you want on your hands?
50-50.
Blunt, huh?
I don't like the smell of this town.
All right, blunt's what we got.
We're gonna get a car,
and we're gonna get out of here.
Mom, I'm starving.
I could use a shower!
Honey, you got a bug in your hair, okay?
Come on, girl.
A normal breakfast
is all we're asking for.
I'd just like to point out
that if you hadn't have got rid
of the toolbox,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
I had to take it out for Sammy's books.
You should have spoke up.
Grandma looks tired. I think
we need to get her something to eat.
God, when did you kids become so soft?
Mama, y'all want some pancakes?
Mama, talk to me.
Is she dead?
Cal, put her over there on that bench.
Be careful.
Okay. Here we go.
You're all right.
Mind her head.
Oh, ma, please don't die.
Is she breathing?
I can hear her heart.
You hear her heart?
Yeah. It's just faint.
We got to take her to the hospital.
Hospital.
Mr. Rich, I have to report this
to the police. A law was broken.
Officer Delroy, please call me Doug.
I just want to say one thing.
You know who that man is over there?
Like I said, I'm new here.
He is Hugh Panetta.
I mean, he made all this.
Doug, with all due respect,
God made all this.
No, no, no, no, all this.
This. The Edenfalls.
His company carved out and created
this community of Edenfalls.
I mean, you got him
to thank for your job.
Well, I suppose, technically,
I did trespass on your property.
That's a legal situation
you got yourself in there.
I know. I'm a lawyer.
But I still have to turn in this gun.
Well, then you turn the gun in.
You keep it in the bag. It's safe there.
Well, Doug, for your information,
I am not bullshit.
It is my job to keep this place safe.
I know.
And I'm gonna do it.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Screw him.
I got another one.
- We got to get you back home.
- I can't go home!
My heart's broken, Doug.
I lost my wife.
- What did you do?
- Tried to give her this ring.
And I was all excited about it, too.
I wrapped it up.
I stuck it under her pillow.
- She didn't like it?
- She liked it.
- What's your problem then?
- She didn't love it.
- That's what the problem is.
- How do you know she didn't love it?
The eyes. I could tell.
Something in the eyes.
You know, when a girl's lying to you,
she's trying to be polite.
I said, "Baby, you don't love it.
"Why are you lying to me?"
And she's all...
"Dreams are complicated, Hugh."
Perhaps she was telling the truth
about the ring.
I know what lying is.
So I asked her, politely,
not to lie to me
and to be happy!
I mean, she jiggy danced
in Vegas for a living.
Now she's living in a house on a hill.
I'm making her dreams come true.
Least she could do is be happy about it.
So she cried a little,
said she was happy.
And I guess I sort of took the ring
and just stuck it on her finger.
The ring didn't fit. It's too small.
I drew some blood.
She called me a monster,
saddest man she ever met.
So, I pulled it off
and threw it in the toilet.
- I think it broke.
- The toilet?
The finger.
Anyway...
She's in pretty bad pain.
I tried to call 911.
She kicks me out on the street.
How'd you get the ring back?
- What?
- From the toilet.
What's she mean?
"Dreams are complicated," Doug?
God. I don't know. Maybe she meant,
now she's got the house on the hill,
she doesn't want it.
- Then why'd she marry me, then?
- Maybe she married you for who you are.
Who I am is
a guy with a house on the hill!
You busted her finger!
You want to apologize,
get down on your hands and knees.
You crawl and you ask for forgiveness.
Then you get some time off
and you take a vacation.
No. No, I can't.
You can't crawl on your hands and knees?
No. I can't take a vacation right now.
Hugh, just take a vacation, okay?
Can't. I can't. Come here.
Take a look at this.
Bayou Hills, Doug.
We can't pass it up.
There will always be another deal.
There's not gonna be another Bayou Hills
as long as we live.
That's why I came over here
to talk to you tonight.
You came over here
to talk to me about your wife.
Her too.
Here. Look at this.
Christ.
Uh... right.
Sweet. Excellent.
Sweet?
It's the deal of a lifetime, Doug.
The state took our bid.
We're all-in.
We're not calling. We're not raising.
We're all-in!
Five days to raise the money.
This goes through,
Panco makes $150 million.
I make a third of that,
and you cash in on a baker's dozen...
$13 million, Doug.
$13 million?
Your mother's heartbeat is very faint.
- What's wrong with her?
- Calm down.
She has arrhythmia.
Now, that's either from heart disease
or she's dehydrated
and drunk.
Has she been drinking?
No! Of course not!
You're sure?
Not that I know of.
Cause she reeks of alcohol.
No go?
Can I see your i.d., please?
Yeah. Hold on.
Well, there we are.
Can you hear me, sweetheart?
- Mrs., uh...
- Morgenstern.
Could you try to sit up for me?
It's Dr. Morgenstern.
Is she a doctor?
I want a large cadillac.
Everyone does, dear.
Does she have dementia?
We think.
- You think?
- We're sure.
How was she diagnosed?
- Alzheimer's.
- Dementia.
There was a big debate going on
among the doctors who treated her.
So many...
things in here.
There we go. Yeah.
- Thank you, Miss Prestwich.
- Of course.
Never know who's spending
your money these days.
Don't I know it.
How old is your mother, Mrs. Prestwich?
She's 78.
78...
Let me see.
Your daughter...
- says she's 91.
- Well, that's incorrect.
All right, then.
I'm gonna need to admit your mother
to blunt presbyterian.
She's just drunk!
You don't know much
about your mother's health.
You gave her alcohol.
You barely know how old she is.
Now, if anything,
that's elder abuse.
You saying I abuse my mother?
- Do you know how old your mother is?
- I beg your pardon?
Do you know how old your wife is?
Do you know about their health affairs?
When was the last time
your wife had a pap smear?
Well, as...
I don't want to know.
That's not the point. I love her.
How dare you accuse me of elder abuse!
I'm outraged!
You just calm down.
Your mother is coming with me,
and she's coming to blunt presbyterian.
You just wait here a moment,
and I'll be right back.
Son of a bitch.
White coat.
Say I don't love my ma.
I'm a good daughter.
Have you used that card recently?
You know, I don't know.
Maybe not recently.
That must be the problem then.
I bet they froze it for security.
Please, I really just want
to get my grandmother treated.
That's why you should give
those Visa folks a call.
The card's dead.
Oh, shit. Shit!
If they froze Prestwich,
they froze them all?
- I guess. Probably.
- Hey, you got any cards?
Uh, I left them.
I left all my credit cards and cash.
- You ran away without a penny?
- Yeah.
Why?
I thought it would be more fun.
You know, kind of live off the earth.
You got to get cash.
Okay. All right. Pay with that.
Find out exactly what medications
they need for her.
Screw blunt presbyterian.
She just got to get rehydrated.
Y'all want to live off the earth,
now's your chance.
I can't believe grandma was drunk.
She wouldn't even let me have a sip.
- She drank that whole thing of whiskey.
- I know.
That's, like, amazing.
- What's going on here?
- Football night.
Oh, that figures.
- Everything all right here, folks?
- Great. Thank you.
You ordered too much.
- We'll just take some of it with us.
- We don't have the cash, Di Di.
We just had to pay for mama.
We're going on the road.
We got to pay for gas and drugs.
Whatever you haven't started,
you send it back.
I need my steak and eggs.
- I'm gonna get up.
- Don't you...
Don't you... I'm warning you!
- I'm going to the bathroom.
- Such a little bastard.
Can I eat my steak and eggs?
That's nice. That's real nice.
You robbing old ladies now, hmm?
Feel good?
Do you feel good?
That was a shitty thing to do.
Let that be your "comeupponce."
I think the word is comeuppance.
What are you, the word police?
You shut your pie hole.
Wrap that steak in a napkin.
Go steal me a car.
- Don't you look at me like that.
- Can I come?
No, sweetheart.
Starsky don't need no Hutch.
You all right there, ma'am?
Are you sure?
I thought I had $40.
Oh, sweetheart. I know how that is.
Here you go.
Don't you mind that.
Jesus!
You scared me to death.
I just want to see how it's done.
Which way, Doug?
Which way to the light?
Just through these doors.
I can't talk.
I'm with him now.
This goddamn town
is giving me the creeps.
Let's get ma and get out of here.
Partner.
We said 50-50.
I love you.
I love you. Where are you?
I'm at the house.
Where's Pete?
We are in this together.
Did you really think
that spiking my scotch would lick me?
Pete's fine. Everything's all right.
Everything's all right.
Well, everything's all right.
Where do you think you're going?
Oh, Jesus.
This is my van.
The gang's all here.
Get out of the car.
I am talking about a certain dead body
festering in the trunk.
I know what you're talking about,
and I am dealing with it.
So why don't you get out
of the goddamn car now?
This ain't your car.
And that ain't your house.
And I don't know Doug Rich,
but I'm assuming he, too, is
in a festering condition, am I right?
You rat me out,
I rat you out,
vice versa and so on.
Mutually insured destruction.
We're in this together...
Two peas in a pod.
Mutually "assured" destruction,
you asshole.
That's right. "Mutually assured."
Mutually insured to the bitter end.
What's the plan?