Mick, look out!
I'm sorry.
You want to pretend
to be the dead guy ?
You want to wear his suits,
you want me to be his dead wife ?
- I know everything.
- You don't know shit.
I know Wayne Malloy
stole the family bank.
I know that you are up
to your eyeballs in shit
if you don't get
that money back.
I know none of this
is helping your position here.
My being here means
you're a dead man, Wayne Malloy.
I think Dale would be
mighty interested in your address.
What do you want,
Ginny Dannegan ?
Well, look who it is.
Hi, everybody.
- Who is that ?
- This would be Ken.
Di's fiance.
What ?
Why does he have
to stay with us ?
Cause, you know,
the fiance always stays
with the in-laws in
the run-up to the wedding.
- It's tradition.
- I'm not gonna marry him.
Well, it's tradition.
That's all I'm saying.
Holy shit.
I'd do anything for you, Delilah.
What kind of monster
steals the family bank ?
- He won't do it again, on my honor.
- It's over.
Why don't you just
tell me where you are ?
You and the kids
can wait outside.
Is that what you think of me, Daddy ?
Can't trust me to run the family ?
It's a real big burden,
being responsible for a whole family.
Don't feel bad at your daddy
for not picking you.
All I ever wanted to do
was make you proud, Daddy.
And I will carry you
in my heart...
till the day that I die.
It's 4:30 in the morning.
What do you want ?
Is that you ?
Dale, what is it ?
He's dead.
My daddy is dead.
What happened ?
He wanted to die.
He crawled out to the woods...
to die.
The funeral is this weekend.
You gotta be there for the family.
I can't.
You have to be there for him.
You gotta sing for him.
Just bring back the money, D.
I'll take care of things from here.
I don't have it.
Who are you, D ?
Are you one of us,
or you one of them ?
Shit.
Have you reached China yet ?
We've lost the money.
You're not gonna find it.
He's dead.
He loved us and
we left him like he was nothing.
How do you know ?
Dale told me.
He said Earl crawled off
in the woods to die.
He crawled ?
Look, would you stop digging ?
Dale said if we just
pay back the money...
Since when do you
believe a word Dale says ?
Damn this.
Look, I'm just gonna
go alone, Wayne.
I'm gonna find the money,
I'm gonna take it back,
and make things right again.
You cannot make
things right again.
So you don't want to go
pay your respects to Earl ?
This is a chance, Wayne,
to make amends.
They don't want
our goddamn amends.
How can you be so cold ?
- He loved you !
- And I loved him.
It's over.
Oh, my God, I cannot talk
to you anymore.
Maybe Dale lied,
maybe Earl's not dead.
He would never lie
about something like that.
- You're so sure ?
- I choose to believe him.
I choose to have faith
in the people I love.
You love Dale ?
Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
Who do you want me
to love, Wayne ?
You want me
to love our neighbors ?
Your boss ?
All the lovely people who come
into my life now call me Cherien.
You want me to love them ?
~ SeriesSub.com~
present
Transcript:
swsub.com
Synchro:
Jarick
Hutch
Season 1 - Episode 07
Virgin Territory
We never use
any of this shit anyway.
If you don't use it,
then we don't need it.
- What is she doing ?
- You gonna hock all that ?
Mom, stop.
You can't hock the coffeemaker.
Someone help me, please.
You want all
this shit now, don't you ?
You see,
that's what happens.
You start to believe
that you actually need it.
Baby, calm down.
You know what ?
I'm not asking for a single thing
from any one of you.
I'm going by myself.
I think she wants
to go to the funeral.
You know how close
she was to Earl and Susan.
They were like her parents.
We can't let her go alone.
Who knows what
they're gonna do to her there.
If she goes,
we all go together.
- You can't go.
- Why not ?
Shit.
Yeah, Cal's right.
Your mother and I'll go alone.
You can't go, either.
Dale wants to kill you.
Dale wants $40,000.
Well, that's a lot
of silverware, Dad.
Yeah, well, I'll get it.
You're gonna get
40 grand in cash ?
Count me in for three.
- Brent still owes me.
- Who's Brent ?
Cal and Brent are
in business together.
Yeah, I'll give him a call.
I'll have the cash here tonight.
- What time is it ?
- Oh, who knows ?
Mom stopped all the clocks.
Dahlia, put the bag down.
You're not going anywhere.
All right.
If you go...
we're all going with you.
Hey, which one's your office ?
I'm not telling you.
I want to know
where my dad works.
That one.
No shit. For real ?
Don't steal anything.
Come on.
What do you mean,
"don't steal anything" ?
What the hell is that ?
Barbecue at Hugh's.
Goddamn small bills.
Isn't this what got us
in trouble in the first place ?
Get outta here.
Cal, are you around ?
Come on, dude,
where are you ?
Who are you ?
- Um, I was...
- You want something ?
Did you get a good look ?
You want to see
me naked ?
Come in.
Come on.
Sit down.
Now, let me
tell you something.
Women...
are smarter than you,
and you gotta respect them.
So when you were
over there in the door
peekin' in on me,
you're taking
advantage of my pain
for your own pleasure,
and that's wrong.
I'm sorry.
Okay, I didn't mean
to just stare at you.
What are you looking for ?
Love.
- Love ?
- Yeah.
Well, then, you gotta ask
yourself a question.
"Who can I count on ?"
"How can I trust ?"
Cause if you can't answer that...
Then you're gonna be all alone.
- I thought...
- Bobby!
It's Brent.
Lord, I appreciate
your sexual energy and all,
but, you know,
you're 17,
your Cal's friend.
I'm never, ever gonna
have sex with you.
You understand that ?
Oh, honey.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
You're cute as a button.
If I was gonna do a 17-year-old,
you'd definitely have a shot.
But...
it's not meant to be.
Go on. Get out.
Get out.
Go on.
Ken, you know,
we're going back for the funeral.
You know we're going
back for the funeral.
Have you seen
this alligator guy ?
He's cool.
I gotta talk to you.
You know when there's
a traveller funeral, there's often
a traveller wedding.
Now, your sister Jenny,
she may use this opportunity
to make you marry Di.
Really ?
That's great.
No, not great.
It's bad.
You've got to
tell your sister "no".
Why ?
She's too young.
She's pretty, sure,
but she's too young.
She's naive,
she's gangly,
she doesn't know what's what.
You...
You're a man of the world.
You've been around.
You've seen it, you've seen
a horse, you know.
You've played the field,
you've been in fields.
It's just, you gotta be strong here.
You gotta protect her.
Well, I sure want to.
I know you do, so when
your sister Jenny says,
"what about the marriage ?",
you're gonna say...
- Yes.
- No.
No. It's a "no" sound.
- Nnnno.
- No.
That's the one.
You're gonna say,
"I want to wait".
I want to wait ?
"I want to wait",
much more positive.
- I want to wait.
No, that's more of
a "I want to wait ?"
"I want to wait",
you just go down.
I want to wait.
- I want to wait.
- Yeah.
You're the man.
Let's go, baby.
Come on.
Shit !
Honey, if we want to get there,
we gotta get moving.
Don't worry, guys.
Things get rough, I'll protect you.
That brings us comfort, Ken.
Don't laugh, honey.
We need his protection.
Ken, try not to talk about
living with us, okay?
Right.
Sure thing, mr. Rich.
Let's go.
How long are we gonna stay?
We get in, we get out.
Thank you for coming.
Nice to see you, too, Mick.
Darlin'.
Sorry.
Hello there, honey.
I'm so glad you're here.
I'm so glad you're here, sweetie.
And you, too, honey.
I'm so glad you're here for me.
I'm really sorry.
- I gotta do this.
- Dad...
Stick with didi. Don't waste
your breath. I'm comin' with you.
Love what you've done with the place.
Look at you, you son of a bitch.
You dress like the goddamn
president of the United States.
- How much that cost you?
- You think I bought it?
Such are the limits of your imagination.
Whatever.
Tell me where you're livin'.
Do you want this or not?
How much you got?
I want an oath of protection.
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna
tell you something
right off the bat here,
mr. President,
whatever you got,
we want more.
Haven't you heard?
Everyone wants more.
You get the other half when we leave.
Okay, I'll give you the oath.
We love you.
It's good to have you back,
Wayne Malloy.
Thanks for this, Wayne.
I love you.
I gotta talk to susan.
Dahlia, we agreed.
Let it go.
- Don't even think about it, Cal.
- I'm not an idiot.
Congratulations, didi.
On what?
Aren't you and Ken gettin'
married tonight?
- Who told you that?
- Jenny, I think.
Shit.
She must've gotten to Ken.
Got a really bad feeling about all
this wedding stuff, dad.
We gotta get the hell outta here.
Gave you 20 grand?
Without missin' a beat.
And that night she saw him,
Cal was drivin' a Mercedes, huh?
Yellow, shin', brand-new.
Who the hell does he think he is?
The king of Siam.
He betrayed us,
- every one of us.
- We're oughta make him eat shit.
Slainte mhath.
I heard you two were havin'
a rough couple of months.
I'm real sorry.
Couple of years.
- We manage.
- I'm tired of managin'.
I would love to help you guys out.
- You deserve a piece of the good life.
- You're damn right.
Well,
I got some money now.
There's a lot of insurance out on daddy.
I'd love to pass some your way.
Twenty-five gs sound like
a nice round number?
Now, I'm not sayin' get rid of Wayne,
but if he disappeared,
que sera-sera.
What exactly are you sayin' here, Dale?
Hey, Ken. We gotta go.
Can't. I'm losin'.
It's solitaire, Ken.
That's why it hurts so much.
Sam will play solitaire
with you in the rv.
Promise?
We're havin' a weddin', Wayne.
Somethin' died, somethin's born.
Somethin' ends, somethin' begins.
Dad.
Okay, Ken, we're leaving.
Now is the time to say your peace.
Tell her what you really think.
Di's counting on you.
We want you to be a man here.
I've been thinkin', mr. Rich.
You're your own man, Ken.
We're all counting on you
to do the right thing here.
I'm tryin' to do the right thing.
Well, now is the time
to say the n-o word.
No. A little bit more ballsy there.
"no."
No... no, I mean no.
I'm sorry, mr....
but I want to.
I want to marry her.
I've always wanted to.
I mean, ever since before my fever.
Now, I don't rember much,
but I remember her.
- Maybe you've...
- No, it's okay, Delilah,
'cause I want to,
and I'm gonna marry her.
Well,
the weddin's happenin',
and it happens tonight,
or I walk into that camp,
and I start runnin' my mouth.
You'll have about a hundred rvs
parked outside Edenfalls by sundown.
I thought he'd live forever.
You shouldn't have left.
You shouldn't have taken that money.
That's when all the trouble came.
Susan, I'm sorry for what happened.
I am, I'm sorry.
I hugged you in public.
What more do you want?
I just...
I missed you so much.
I just... I wanted to talk
to you like we used to.
Well, it's too late for all that.
Why did earl kill himself?
You go ask Dale about that.
Why would I ask Dale?
'Cause
maybe I don't want to talk
to you anymore.
How you feelin', mama?
I need a nap.
Well, go take one.
My daddy
wanted us to get married
almost as much as I did.
Almost as much as you did.
Do you rember that picnic
when you followed me
around all day long?
I was 14 years old.
- That first kiss...
- You stole it.
What's wrong with that?
I love Wayne.
What do you see in him?
I see myself.
He asked you to betray who you are.
- Tell me about earl.
- What about him?
How'd he get down in the woods?
He crawled there, I told you.
He crawled there on
- his hands and knees?
- I reckon.
- And what about the cuts?
- What cuts?
On his hands.
Cuts on his hands and his face.
That must have been painful.
What's with all the questions, D?
I just want to know what happened.
Well, I wasn't there, now, was I?
Were you?
What?
You think I carried him there...
And just left him there to die?
How did he get all them cuts then?
Tryin' to crawl home.
You really want to know how he died?
If he cried or...
Or whimpered?
Is that what you want to hear?
You left him there, D.
You left him there to suffer and die...
Just as much as anybody else.
Dahlia, we got a problem.
What happened?
- You're shaking.
- I'm cold.
Baby, we've gotta leave.
We gotta grab our little girl,
and we gotta run.
Dale killed earl.
- How do you know?
- How?
He pretty much told me.
God! Where the hell is dad?
I don't... look, just play along, okay?
Dad will come up with something.
He always does.
It doesn't really feel that way, Cal.
Don't touch me.
You bitch! God!
Just who do you think you are?
That's what I want to know.
'cause I rember when
you was 14 years old,
and you were just
a scrawny little runt.
Do you promise yourself
to Delilah Malloy,
in body and in spirit,
in heart and in mind,
forever and ever and always?
I just wanted to talk.
Do you want a drink?
Are you sure?
You bet.
And you, my child,
do you promise yourself to
kenneth dannegan,
in body and in spirit,
in heart and in mind?
Mick, I see where you're heading,
but is there any chance
you could kill me later?
They're trying to marry off
my little girl, and I just got to...
Don't you move.
- I can handle it.
- He's got a gun!
Damn it, Dahlia.
Forever and ever, and always?
Now you tell me why killed your daddy,
you brutal son of a bitch.
No.
I can't, I...
What the hell is wrong with you people?
Jesus!
You're bonded together forever.
Well, no, not really.
We'll handle it from here, father.
Go on.
What are you doin', D?
Shut up!
Pack enough clothes for
a good long time. Go on.
You're just pushin' me out.
Why do you hate me so much?
I loved him.
I goddamn worshipped him.
He was even choosing that idiot,
Ginny dannegan, over me.
I mean, how much is a man
supposed to take, right?
Zip it up.
You zip it up!
Now,
you are gonna write a letter,
you're gonna tell everyone what you did,
and you're gonna explain
to them why it is you're leaving.
I'm don't want to leave.
- I got nowhere to go.
- That's too bad.
Now get a goddamn
piece of paper... now!
Just keep walkin'.
Don't talk to him.
Where you live, Wayne?
I want to know.
I'm happy to tell you whatever you want.
I want to know what you're doin'.
- I want to know what it's like.
- I said,
don't talk to him!
Aluminum siding, outside of Baton Rouge.
- Aluminum sidin'?
- It's heaven on earth.
How dumb do you think we are?
Dumb enough to leave
the scene of an accident.
You let me in, you little slut!
God, just leave me alone!
You little whore.
You ungrateful brat.
Do you have any idea what
I could do to your family?
Why don't you just do it
already then, Ginny,
because I can't take it anymore.
You want me to tell everybody
where you've been livin',
huh? All about that big,
beautiful house,
and them beautiful cars?
And how about that boy?
You know, the one that's got
his hands in your pants.
Go away.
You're not thinkin', Di.
What about the cops?
You want me to tell 'em
where your mama's livin'?
About how she's breakin' her parole,
huh?
What happened?
Mick killed them.
My whole family saw it all.
We haven't told anyone...
yet.
Now, you listen to me.
Ken's gonna come up here
in about two minutes,
and you're gonna open that door,
and then you two are gonna
consummate that weddin'.
Ken's dream is gonna come true.
After that, I don't give
a shit what you do.
You just want me to screw him?
Fine. Why don't you just send him
in here right now?
I'll screw him.
I'll screw him right here.
Get a pen.
Go on.
Sit down.
Now, you write, "dear ma."
You're gonna kill me, aren't you?
Write it!
I guess we're supposed to...
consummate now.
I... I'm a virgin.
Can you show me what to do?
So why don't you put
that gun down, mick,
and we can just sit down,
and we can talk about this.
And, you know, the thing is,
I think you want in on it.
I think you want in on
my aluminum siding deal.
- I've made more money than jesus.
- Shut him up!
I can't stand to listen to
any more of his lies!
He doesn't give a shit about us!
I want that money, mick.
- Give me that.
- Let go of the...
You shot me, you asshole.
Oh, god.
This feels like a dream.
Will you kiss me?
I don't want to, Ken.
Don't you love me?
You think
maybe someday you'll love me?
I barely know what love is.
But I'm pretty sure
I'm never gonna love you.
Why are you marrying me then?
Your sister's threatening me.
She says that if I don't marry you,
she's gonna send my mom back to prison.
- No, she won't.
- Yes, she will.
Listen to me.
I'll never let my sister blackmail you.
You understand?
If you don't want to marry me,
if you want to live in Edenfalls,
away from here...
I'll protect you.
I promise.
My pen ain't got no ink.
Well, get another one.
He tortured me.
- He hated me.
- Shut up.
I did it for you, I did it for you.
You know, I swear,
I swear I need you.
Get down on your knees.
I love you, Dahlia.
And I would've done it 10 times over
just to see you again.
I'm not done.
I am through with this place.
My mama's always on my back.
My pen ain't got no ink.
This place is so small.
Why won't you listen?
I don't know what you're talkin' about.
I'm talkin' about the truth, susan.
You shouldn't have taken
the money, Dahlia.
What do you...
what money?
I'm talkin' about your son
bein' a murder.
My son
did nothin' wrong.
And if you'd been here,
nothin' ever would've happened.
You're blaming me
for what your son did
to your husband
You get outta here!
She won't hear it.
Let's go, baby.
You can't make things right here.
Come on.
You hurt didi in any way,
hurt her family...
I ain't your brother no more.
I'll choke you while you sleep.
Honey, get your sister's dress.
Some day, huh?
Can I ask you somethin'?
Can you make someone love you?
What did you say about me?
Nothin'.
No, I didn't mean to...
Where do they live?
~ SeriesSub.com ~