Previously on the Riches...
Do you really think dad has a plan?
He stole the money, ma lost the money,
and now we're here
in a dead guy's house.
Doug Rich was a litigator.
You have to be the worst
lawyer in the world.
I am. And you, you're fired.
The new guy doesn't know anything!
You want to be a partner?
- That's what I went to law school for.
- Okay, man, in the meantime,
- you need to invite me to a dinner.
- A dinner?
I check out your house,your friends,
your family, see if you're
partnership material.
This is Chunky K.
She was my cellie in prison.
Man, this whole maid
thing is weirding me out.
If I don't work for you,
I gotta work for somebody.
I want you to think of three adjectives
that describe Doug and Cherien,
and if I like your adjectives, I知
gonna make Doug here a partner.
If I don't, he's out on the street.
- Jesus Christ!
- Shut that goddamn door!
You want to make me a partner
- right now, right here?
- Why the hell not?
Maybe later. I wanted to be a partner.
Something about it makes
me sick to my stomach.
Oh, we're turning into buffers, baby.
- You want some?
- No.
If you decide you do want some,
I値l just leave it right there for you.
- Don't.
- So stop me then.
Why didn't you come to bed last night?
What's the matter with you?
I saw the little baggy your
friend K passed you last night,
- the one with the white powder in it.
- She left it here.
I just can't take the
lying. That's what I can't take.
I'm not lying, Wayne. I
told you, I知 off that shit.
Really? 'cause after you went to
sleep, I went around the house,
and I found about 15 bottles of
tranquilizer hidden all over the place.
You must be the most tranquil
person on the goddamn planet.
Has it ever crossed your mind I
might need it to get off the meth?
Well, why didn't you tell me?
Because maybe I did not
think you would understand.
I bet Hugh understands.
- You do it with him, too?
- Oh, my God. Jesus.
Isn't it enough that I知 not
takin' the shit anymore, huh?
What do you want from me?
Mom, dad, I need someone
to sign my permission slip!
Science museum, huh?
Don't you need to get to work?
I don't know. Probably.
- Dad, are you gonna quit your job?
- I don't know.
- Is that why you were sleeping on
the floor in my room last
night, because you're gonna quit?
I think that's between him and mom.
No, no it's not about
mom. I was just thinking,
life is too short to work for assholes.
Remember that.
Calm down. There's a million
buffer jobs out there.
Is that you're looking
for a cashier interview.
Sammy, there is no way that anybody
need involves with that minimum wage.
Okay? Just forget that.
Would you relax? I'm Doug Rich.
I'm a high-profile lawyer, okay?
I've settled two major cases.
Hell, I知 a member of
Edenfalls Country Club,
and your mom's still
got the job at Panco.
Dahlia, you're gonna be late!
Coming!
Hey, I was gonna flush it!
I was gonna flush it! I was! I swear!
I was gonna flush it!
How big a supply is
this? A month? A week?
No, you gotta believe
me, I was gonna flush it!
If you are gonna do this
shit, I知 gonna do it too?
No, I値l go and flush it, Wayne...
Now I believe you.
God!
~ SeriesSub.com ~
present
Transcript:
swsub.com
Synchro:
Ricana &
[Yossarian, sheva85] from
Synchro:
::ItalianSubAddicted::
www.italiansubs.net
Season 01 Episode 10
This Is Your Brain on Drugs
Are you crazy?
I mean, are you tryin' to kill yourself?
I don't know. Are you?
Of all the assaholic things you have
ever done, this is the most assaholic.
Are you aware of how
much of this shit you did?
I am so sorry. I forgot to
read the crank head痴 handbook.
Oh, yeah, it burns!
That's right! That shit is lethal,
Wayne! You better get to work
'cause I think I quit.
Jesus Christ.
If you let the kids see you like this,
I知 gonna rip your nuts off.
I can't tell if I'm
enjoying your reaction
because it's actually gratifying
or 'cause the meth is kickin' in.
Mortgage, four grand a month.
Uh, Rosemere Academy...
is $500 a month.
Edenfalls Country Club
is $1,000 a month.
Temple membership, water,
electric, telephone...
Sam, will you stop, okay?
He's not gonna quit.
He might.
Somethin' went down with
him and mom at that party.
why are we gettin' a bill from
Mountain View Nursing Home
for $4,700 a month?
Must be where Cherien's mother is.
I mean, he was never gonna make it in
the corporate world anyway. God knows
- mom's not gonna hang on to a job.
- So what are we gonna do?
What we always do, move somewhere else.
And what? Go back to stealin' wallets
and rippin' off car stereos?
Maybe you can wear a mustache this time.
You see, that sounds really fun to me.
Okay, does Mom make
$14,723.51 per month?
'cause that's what we're gonna need.
That's after taxes, buddy.
You gotta add 35 percent.
Okay, do not go upstairs.
Your Dad has food poisoning.
Mom, do you make $19,876.74...
Do not go upstairs, okay?
Where's Doug? Hey, Doug.
Hey, it's me. Oh. Are you there?
I know you're there. I just want to
make sure you're still alive, huh?
No... Oh, he had bad clams.
Would you call me, you asshole?
- So Doug's not comin' in?
- Who the hell cares?
Hugh does. He called from Reno.
The REIT is gonna be here
at 9:00 for the closing, and he needs
Doug to answer any questions.
- The REIT?
- The Real Estate Investment Trust?
They're buying that office tower.
Hugh left the papers on his desk.
Okay, um, well, I'll handle that. Now,
Kimmie, you know how to
work the Google thing, huh?
Can you find out what a
person's supposed to do
if another person does a
whole shitload of meth?
Is it the one where you pack
their head in ice? Huh?
I'm... I'm givin' an anti-drug
talk at my kids' school.
My monthly expenses are...
$19,000!
- Hi, this is the Riches, we're not here
- Nineteen...
- at the moment, so leave a message.
- thousand... dollars!
- I've got to get a job.
- Wayne?
Wayne? Wayne. Pick up the goddamn phone.
Wayne, it's me. Pick up the phone.
No, I understand you got a
hiring freeze, Craig.
It's not just the hiring freeze, Doug.
We specialize in tax law.
We can't use a securities litigator.
"extreme euphoria, anxiety,
aggressiveness, hostility,
paranoia, mania,
excessive talkativeness."
it doesn't say what to do, but...
check out the symptoms of a overdose.
heart damage, kidney failure,
hallucinations,
stroke, heart attack."
that ought to scare the kids, huh?
You better go in there.
They're gonna have questions.
Okay. Call Doug.
You read him that list of symptoms
'cause he's gonna have to do
the drug talk for the kids.
Doug? Doug, Cherien wanted me to
read you these symptoms:
"aggressiveness, hostility, paranoia,
excessive talkativeness,
- rapid breathing."
- shit.
"extreme sex drive,
sweating, heart palpitations."
These here... All right,
so I'm gonna, uh,
notarize this stuff.
Uh, Panetta said we should talk
to head of legal
- before we sign.
- Well, the head of legal
kicked it upstairs... to me.
$19,000. I mean, how
the hell did I get here?
I hear ya, and that's before you're
blowing 45 grand a year on college.
Forty-five grand. I mean,
how the hell did you pay it?
- Took out a 2nd and a 3rd mortgage.
- God damn it.
Look, Doug, I wish we had an
opening here, but the truth is,
- even if we did have one...
- Look, I know,
I'm not a defense litigator, but...
I hate to sound harsh, but
we need someone younger.
- Shouldn't we read them first?
- Sure.
Whatever blows your hair back.
- Don't need anyone right now.
- Not now. No.
God!
"We'd like to thank you for giving us
the opportunity to meet with us..."
Hayden-Javitz!
"We're so sorry you haven't accepted
this position. Should you ever rec..."
Hayden-Javitz?
And just to put your kid through 1 year
of college costs $45,000,
and I didn't even go to college.
Of course, I went to college.
I went to...
Georgetown university to
do my college degree,
and then I went to har...
Princeton university,
and I studied law. Again,
I have done a lot of
extracurricular activities.  was...
I was in an eating club,
where we ate a lot of food.
That's the thing you do there.
And I was Prince Dauntless
in "once upon a time on a mattress".
I was a very
excellent leading man.
Dear God, you may ask,
why put that on my resume?
I ask why I put it on my resume,
but it's on the resume to
show you who I am.
- If I could just talk to mr. Javitz...
- Fine!
I'll call the managing partner,
and I'll ask if he'll see you, okay?
Just please have a seat. I will.
I have a mr. Rich out here in the lobby
with a file of wrinkled-up papers,
saying he wants to meet you.
Wayne, where the hell are you?
do you have any idea how much
your mothers' nursing home costs?
My mother's been dead for 32 years.
Mr. Rich, our managing partner said
he'd be delighted to see you.
I have Doug Rich for you.
Stewart.
- Holy shit!
- I know. What are the odds?
Last time I saw you, you were all blurry
'cause one of Panco's
security goons was macin' me.
No hard feelings, man.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
you got my job, I got yours.
What goes around comes around.
That is... Well, that is really big
that is really really big,y'know?
- I fired you, man.
- Nah.
That was Hugh's thing.
Survival of the fittest.
Well, talk about darwinian.
You know how much it costs
to send your kids to college?
It never ends, huh?
Friggin' gerbil wheel.
A sickness.
We americans never
feel like we have enough.
- Why do you think that is, Doug?
- I don't know.
You think it has to do with
our goddamn puritan work ethic,
- Workin' and workin' and workin'?
- Absolutely.
You know, it all goes
back to that psychotic
dickhead myles standish.
You know he...
You know he was only 4'11"?
I mean, you know, a major puritan,
and 400 years later,
we're still dealing with his
short guy complex.
We gotta stop the madness, huh? We gotta
- say, "I have enough."
- I have enough, yeah.
You know what isn't enough,
though, Doug?
Your new job here...
As a janitor.
Yeah, a janitor.
You lousy prick.
Nobody fires my ass.
Now get the hell out of my office.
You little shit!
- Security!
- Hey, get off me!
Hey, he is a total fraud!
Look at the pictures in his office!
They're not even his kids!
That's my resume.
I am...
unclear on item 15
sub a.
Excuse me.
- Where are you?
- Do you know how much we pay for hbo?
Okay, Wayne,
do not give me this shit about hbo.
- Where the hell are you?
- I'm here.
- I've had a wake-up call, Dahlia.
- Where are you?
We don't need any of this shit.
It is time to say, "enough."
Wayne, will you just tell me,
are you having chest pains?
And where'd you put all the goddamn
pills? Did you throw 'em all out?
Did you throw out the ones
underneath the garden gnome?
'Cause if you didn't, would you
please take five of 'em?
Fine, but we gotta cut out hbo.
We've gotta stop drinking those lattes.
We've gotta stop using
the cell phones and the internet
and the cable, and we gotta reus
e paper towels, 'cause you know what?
Nobody wants Doug Rich.
He's an old, sleazy, washed-up nothing.
But that's okay 'cause
we don't need any of this shit.
The pilgrims didn't
even have paper towels.
What'd you have, squanto sitting
on the edge of plymouth rock,
watching hbo, for God sakes,
or paying a nursing home
$4,700 a month?
Jesus christ!
Shit!
$2,300 for a single room?
What are you, the ritz-carlton?
- You pay a premium for privacy.
- She doesn't like privacy.
She likes lots of people.
I mean, she... She's lonely.
Mom is very, very
lonely.
You know,
the search for individual freedom,
which, and I'm quoting mom here,
has led to
a culture of alienation and anomy,
which ironically leads
us to spend more and more money,
trying to fill the howling, aching,
empty...
Are you... Are you answering e-mails?
I'm multitasking, mr.
Rich. What do you want?
I wanna know what the
hell this medical charges
of 1thousand and 500h and 82
We had to put dr. Morgenstern on oxygen.
I'm paying for her doctor's
medical bills as well?
your mother in law is doctor
is doctor Morgenster
and she needs oxygen
So you're charging
her to breathe now.
Well, that's illegal.
She doesn't want to live like that.
I mean, hooked up to an oxygen tank,
what kind of life is that?
Tell her it'd be okay if she lets go,
you know? Tell her to let go.
Tell her to go towards the light.
They love that. Tell her... Hello?
I just need
a little clearing up on article 41.
Okay, you know what? I don't give
a good goddamn about article 41, buddy.
I have to say,
I think we've been really
good sports about the
lack of clarity in these documents.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Sorry.
I have a relative with
some addiction problems.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Shit.
Let's look at article 41.
You know, uh, ahem... I, uh...
I hope this doesn't cross the line, but
you've seemed quite
upset all morning, and
I just want to say
my son's had some addiction issues.
He's been in and out of rehab.
Well, I just mean that I...
I know how it can rip your guts out.
Can you not read the sign?
It says, "no solicitors."
I can read.
I just thought you might like to know
that your
roof is looking a little tired.
Please don't make me call security.
I also do house paintin' and haulin'.
I've already billed my services
to some of your neighbors,
your backdoor neighbor in 1405?
- Doug Rich?
- No, no, that's not his name.
A fella with a beard, three kids,
- big ol' mercedes benz in the driveway.
- Yeah, that's Doug Rich.
That's his name?
Are you sure about that?
Well, I think I would remember his name.
That prick screwed
me out of $10 million.
$10 million?
Doug Rich screwed
you out of $10 million?
You were robbed. That is...
That is a gross overcharge
for aluminum siding.
Do I look like someone
who uses aluminum sidin'?
He's a lawyer.
That shit-suckin' bastard.
Would you care for a fresh latte, Dale?
We do not euthanize our patients, sir.
Read our mission statement.
I am just trying to understand,
what is this charge
for $279.50 for "miscellaneous"?
Miscellaneous is the cappuccino cart.
She bought a cappuccino cart?
We have a cappuccino cart.
It's one of our perks.
Dear God, you must be peeling
the old bat off the ceiling.
I mean,why can't she just rip
some bark off a tree and chew it?
That's probably what squanto used to do.
It didn't cost him a dime.
Bark is a natural stimulant.
You want your
mother-in-law to chew bark?
Okay. You tell her.
Front desk, visitor for dr. Morgenstern.
No, no, no, not now.
I don't want to scare her.
Look, she's elderly and
obviously overcaffeinated,
you know? This is just a recipe
for cardiac arrest.
She doesn't want to see me.
She hates lawyers.
I mean, mom has had
it with the litigious society.
Chances are she won't
even rember you, mr. Rich.
We had to move her to ward c.
Dr. Morgenstern, hon?
Your son-in-law is here.
mother?
Hi, it's Doug.
I've had some work done.
Mom?
Sometimes you have to speak up a little.
Hi, mom, it's Doug.
You remember?
Who?
I'm Doug Rich.
I think... I think you're...
You're marvin o'keefe, sir.
I'm Doug Rich.
What is this,spartacus? I'm Doug Rich.
Do not antagonize mr. O'keefe.
You lousy sack of shit!
I'm Doug Rich!
Maybe you are Doug Rich.
Is that why I'm not getting any jobs?
You're causing me to be unemployed.
You're causing the supply of Doug Rich
to greatly exceed
the demand for Doug Rich.
That's it.
Why is there no air in here?
Come on, ma, we're getting out of here.
she's not covered without
a day release form.
We're going.
Thank you, Doug.
This is great.
This is a great idea.
We're just gonna get some air.
God!
You all right there, ma?
Isn't this fun, ma?
I'll put that. Here we go.
Gotta get some air.
I bet you like this air.
This is real air, ma.
Gotcha. I gotcha.
I gotcha.
Okay, this is fun, huh?
Down.
Now, ma, watch your head there.
Back you go.
Not so far back.
You have to go here.
It's like a ride.
Here we go. Okay.
- I made some calls.
- What?
Yeah, yeah, excellent plan.
- Where's Cherien?
- Cherien?
Look, what kind of
doctor are you, anyway?
Tell me all about that.
- Where is Cherien?
- No, no, no.
We'll go to the park, what about that?
Do you want to go to the park?
We could feed the ducks.
Where is Cherien?
All right! I'll take you to Cherien!
But...
She's changed.
She's changed an awful lot.
More than me.
And now,
he's livin' with some skank
in little rock
with maroon hair...
And "Satan" tattooed on her neck.
Hey, hold that thought.
- ...any of the stuff, just lattes.
- Where the hell have you been?
I've got a surprise for you in the car.
What happened to your suit?
There was a minor altercation,
but it's good.
Really cleared things up.
Everything is totally clear now.
It is a bad sign. It is a very bad sign.
No, it's great sign.
Because everything finally makes sense.
Everything is not supposed
to make sense.
If it makes sense and
everything's beautiful.
Everything is beautiful.
You see, now you're tweakin', all right?
This is very dangerous, Wayne.
All this is just symptoms, okay?
These are symptoms.
Euphoria,aggression,
heart palpitations, extreme sex drive,
all these things you're
feeling right now.
Pretty soon, you're gonna crash,
you're gonna get suicidally depressed,
then maybe
you're gonna feel like
there's bugs crawling
all over your skin.
I'm so glad you're back.
I was all worried.
I once ate bad herring,
and I had the trots for a week.
God, that means so much.
Some many people don't give
a sheet about Doug Rich.
Okay, that's enough.
Okay, that's enough. That's enough.
Sorry.
I'm experiencing extreme sex drive.
Go in your office now!
Okay. Now, what are you doing?
Are you trying to blow
this whole thing to hell?
How do you like it, watching someone you
love self-destruct?
This is your brain on drugs.
I feel so close to you now.
Now there's no more bullshit, no lying.
Could you just put
your pants back on, please?
I can't. This is extreme sex drive.
- I love you.
- Wayne, this is the meth talking.
You know what's happening right now?
You're getting a big release of
dopamine in your prefrontal cortex.
- That makes two of us.
- Get off me.
Get a grip on yourself!
I am not using.
Yeah? I'm supposed to believe that?
My God. Why?
Do I look like you right now?
Is that what you think?
You think I'm all runnin' around
with the crazy eyes,
humpin' the secretary,
rantin' about squanto?
No, I'm trying to keep
a goddamn job together!
I'm trying to keep this together, Wayne!
- Do I seem like I'm using?
- Why would I think that?
- Did Hugh give you pills?
- No, Wayne. No, he did not.
Yeah, but he knew! You told him!
Everybody knew, Wayne.
It was goddamn obvious.
I never lied, okay. Are you gettin' me?
You were the only
person who did not know
because you were too
busy lying to yourself
because, Wayne, that is what you do!
You stuff everything down, Wayne.
You try and make everything look pretty.
I think that's why you dragged us
here to Edenfalls, so we could live
in this glittery,
and pretend to be happy.
You want me to be happy, huh?
Then let me do drugs.
I thought we were in this together.
Did you drive here?
Your mother's in the car.
No, don't go out there. No.
I liberated her from the nursing home.
Look, she's completely senile.
You gotta go down
and say you're Cherien.
She won't go until she
knows that Cherien is...
Shush!
Be quiet.
Stay here.
Do not move.
I'm gonna go deal with the old lady.
He had an allergic reaction.
To his pants?
Just don't let him leave the office.
You could go buff...
Buff or ecru.
Or you could even go oatmeal.
And you can do the whole thing for 500?
Seein' as you're a preferred customer.
So, Doug Rich is
a lawyer for a real estate company, huh?
Shoes!
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
And his
real estate company
screwed you out of $10 million?
That's right, because of a
legal action I filed against them.
Why'd you file a legal action?
Because they caused me
irreparable harm and loss of limb.
Loss of limb?
No, not my foot.
I broke that on the stair.
It is still clearly attached to
my body. You know what?
I don't care to discuss it.
Please use the stain remover sparingly.
It was your arm, wasn't it?
I believe I just said that
I didn't care to discuss it.
And now you're ruinin' my shag.
You know what?
My paint's fine. I do not need
new paint. You are free to go.
And if you don't get those stains
off my carpet, I will sue your ass.
Jesus christ.
Hi, ma. Hi.
Hi.
Oh, my goodness, look at you.
Don't you look fine?
Now,
you might not even recognize me.
It's been a long time since
we've seen each other.
I've had an extreme makeover, okay?
I gonna take you back to
the nursing home, honey.
here we go.
All right.
Oh, boy.
Well,
I have had a personal setback today.
Thanks for that.
Doug's gone crazy.
I think he might have fried his brain.
Your hand is warm.
Nice and warm.
Kind of nice havin' a mama,
even a bullshit one like you.
I'm just kind of freaked out, you know?
I'm scared he might jump off
a building when he crashes, or
try and drink himself to
death because, you know,
that's what you do when
you try and numb the crash.
Oh, my God, this is so wrong.
I don't know what I'm doin'.
I'm not supposed to be
the strong one. I'm not.
You're not Cherien.
I'm sorry, Doug, but since you're here,
the reit has some questions
about the documents.
- What?
- They're kind of waiting.
Fine.
Well, of course, I'm Cherien.
You know?
Don't you recognize your own daughter?
You really are senile, ma.
You're not Cherien,
I'll have a grande mochaccino.
I got to get you back to
the nursing home, honey.
I have to pee.
Okay, well, you can pee
at the nursing home, huh?
I have to pee.
I have to pee!
Okay, okay, okay. Don't pee now.
I'll take you to my house.
You can pee there, okay? Okay?
You're not Cherien.
Cherien's a bitch.
Oh. There's,
There's no provision
in these contracts
for our offer to be
contingent on inspection.
You....
You are the head of legal, right?
Am I?
Is that who I am?
I'm not sure what's real anymore.
I don't think the bugs are.
You know,
we run and we run and we run
we think we're getting closer
to what we want, but,
really,we're just trying
to pay the 19,000
$19,876.74 a month.
I feel you.
Try being divorced, double everything.
Try being divorced twice.
Is that who we are?
Is that what's gonna be on my tombstone?
"here lies a guy who came up with"
"19,876.74 a month"?
I grew up in a jesuit orphanage.
Is this what the brothers
educated me for?
I don't even remember what
I was supposed to want...
If I don't have Dahlia.
Okay, hold on 'cause
we are almost there.
Just in here. Hi! We're home!
She's senile.
You're not Cherien.
She's mostly senile.
It's Cherien's mom.
But I thought she was in a nursing home.
Yeah, your dad set her free.
Hey, grandma.
Yeah.
Grandma's gonna go pee-pee,
and then we're gonna go back to
the nice nursing home real fast.
See, I thought both our
grandmas were dead.
There you go.
It's a miracle.
- Wayne?
- Cherien, it's Kimmie.
Doug walked out of the office.
I couldn't stop him,
- and he was wearing his pants.
- Oh, jesus christ.
Oh, Wayne, please don't
do anything stupid, honey.
Wayne! Aw, shit.
Dad didn't come home, did he?
- I thought dad was at work, mom.
- Told you he was gonna quit.
Okay, now you listen to me.
You do not do anything stupid, okay?
Don't get in any fights, please,
and do not drive anywhere.
Mom, I think grandma
fell in the bathroom!
Bless me father for I have sinned.
It has been...
Twenty
Twenty Two...
Twenty Two Years...
Since my last confession,
and I have done a shitload of meth.
Uh, my name is Doug.
my name is Wayne.
Wayne Malloy.
Okay, let's get you in your wheelchair.
Careful there.
Let's get you back to the nursing
home, sweetheart, okay?
You're not Cherien.
No, I'm know, sweetheart.
I made some calls.
Okay. Who'd you call?
Did you call the nursing home?
They're not gonna believe you,
sweetheart. I mean,
you know, you're a senile old lady.
- Who'd you call?
- She didn't call the cops, did she?
You're not Cherien.
Her doing meth,
it's because I failed her.
That's why I came here.
I thought if I could build her a castle,
a whole new life here in Edenfalls,
then... Then I'd make it up to her.
What a crock of shit.
If want to rip off my skin.
I want to drink so much,
I can't even rember who I am.
I want to die.
I want more meth.
God, you must think I'm such an asshole.
No, of course not.
You're in a lot of pain.
It's the human condition.
We're all flawed, Wayne.
I mean.
Th-thanks.
I understand how you feel.
I'm having something of
an existential crisis myself.
You're an existentialist priest?
I'm quitting the priesthood.
Next week is my last week.
I don't believe in God anymore.
Whoa, what bad timing.
Stains are all scrubbed out now, ma'am,
so I'll just be on my way.
Okay, thank you.
Look, I'm sorry if I bit
your head off earlier.
Oh, it's a sensitive topic,
ma'am. I can see that.
So Doug Rich, he really screwed
you over on that paint job, huh?
He can suck shit in hell for all I care.
That's Everett.
He's my husband.
So you must really hate him, huh?
- Your husband?
- Doug Rich.
Yeah. Do you?
He screwed you out of $10 million.
You must hate his guts.
You probably want to kill him.
No, I wouldn't dream of killin' him.
That would be awful.
I did once think of running him over
when he was mowing his lawn,
but I was very angry that day, and
I would never really do that, of course.
Yeah. The thing about killin'
is, uh...
My daddy passed recently,
and I realized that
once a person is dead...
Things are always up in the air.
It's like time stands still
since the day they died.
Plus, they come to you
when you're asleep.
My arm does that.
When I dream of it, it's still attached.
Can I touch it?
I'm sorry.
I just... I'm kind of mechanical,
and I ain't never seen
no mechanical arm before.
You wouldn't be disgusted?
That's some solid craftsmanship.
They didn't scrimp on them joints.
I hope you weren't
shocked by what I said
about, you know, killin' Doug.
I didn't mean it.
I just have very strong
feelings, that's all I meant.
Yeah, I know how it is.
I've felt like that sometimes.
Would you like to stay for supper?
- Keep thinking about squanto.
- Yeah.
What an asshole.
Upwardly mobile son of a bitch,
spoke fluent english,
- played everybody.
- Mm-hmm.
You know, I kind of
always wanted a grandma.
No. No, don't do that.
We're taking her back tomorrow.
I know that.
I'm just saying, she's just...
kind of easy to talk to.
She even held my hand
there for a second.
So, you guys... You
talked to her about us?
- That's great, Didi.
- Calm down, Cal.
She doesn't even
understand anything, okay?
I'll have a grande mochaccino.
- Mom, grandma wants
another mochaccino. - Ma!
Geez, I just fixed you one.
Wayne? Where the hell are you?
I can't drive.
Father jeff took the bus.
I want to die.
It's gonna go away after a while.
Is this how you felt?
I'm so sorry.
I was so ashamed, Wayne...
But I couldn't tell you.
I wanted to make
you this beautiful life.
But it's not real.
Come on, let's go.
- You don't want your shoes?
- No.
- You know, my buttons
are falling off. - What?
- My buttons are fall... - Okay, okay.
Let me see, let me see, let me see.
You scared the shit out of me today.
All I could picture was you lying dead
in some hospital
somewhere from an overdose.
Hey, are we big enough for this life?
Are we big enough for this crazy
world we found ourself in?
'Cause I don't know.
I've messed up your whole life.
Yeah, you have.
But, baby...
all I ever wanted was
a messed-up life with you.
Without you...
I can't do my buttons.
- Should we go home?
- You're so pathetic. Come on.
~ SeriesSub.com ~