Previously on The Riches...
Do you really think dad has a plan?
He stole the money,
ma lost the money,
and now we're here
in a dead guy's house.
What kind of monster steals
the family bank?
We're gonna get caught, Di.
How'd y'all get in the front gate?
We live here.
Hi, Doug Rich.
Welcome to Panco, Doug.
I hope your time here is fruitful.
Dahlia, what are you doing here?
Hugh offered me a job.
I'm gonna take him up on it.
How do you do?
I'm mrs. Doug Rich.
Just bring back the money, Di.
Dale wants $40,000.
That's a lot of silverware, dad.
Goddamn small bills.
Isn't this what got us
in trouble in the first place?
How long are we gonna stay?
We get in, we get out.
I want an oath of protection.
The car's right outside.
Come on. Let's go.
Dad, these people have been
staring at us.
No, honey. It's just your imagination.
Hey, take your coat.
Why can't we just park
the rv at our house?
They won't let it through
the gate, buddy. It's too ugly.
It's our home.
Not anymore.
This is a bad idea.
What do you mean?
Rvs there, there, there, over there.
We're gonna blend right in.
They're gonna break in
the minute we leave.
Maybe they're nice.
Or maybe they're just like us.
- We got history. We got culture.
- Good morning.
Community.
You mean, we used to, right?
No, sweetheart.
We got it whether
we're with travelers or not.
I said hey.
What are you, deaf?
No, I'm not deaf, but
I sometimes get a buzzing in my ears.
Does that count?
What she's trying to say
is there's a fee.
Oh, Jesus Christ, I knew it.
You know what?
You ain't got no right
chargin' me no fee, buddy boy.
True. We have no right,
but it's 200 bucks.
That'll cover the first week.
We'll keep an eye on it for you guys.
Don't you pay 'em, Wayne.
Completely reasonable.
Oh, my God.
Thanks. You have nothin'
to worry about.
Come on. We got to get back to work.
Screw work.
We've been gone two days.
Yeah, let's not mention
the other little thing.
What, you mean the money we stole?
Jesus, sam, he just said not
to mention it.
Stay calm, baby.
Well, what's wrong, Kimmie?
Hugh's gone crazy.
He's crazy.
He thinks someone robbed him,
stole $40,000 from his safe.
He's not letting anyone leave
until he finds who it was.
Your name?
What's your real name, Tony?
It's Tony.
It is.
Shit.
Where the hell have you been?
~SeriesSub~
present
Transcript:
swsub.com
Synchro:
Hutch
Golgi
Season 01 - Episode 08
X Spots the Mark
Been gone two days,
same as the money.
What money?
The 40 grand in my safe.
Ring a bell?
You saying you suspect us?
I suspect everybody who works for me,
everybody who had access to Panco
on the day of the crime.
Hugh, as your counsel,
I must warn you
that forcing your employees
to undertake a lie detector test
is completely illegal.
Potential liability is enormous.
It's scientifically useless.
Am I right?
Where the hell have you been
for the last two days?
Food poisoning.
Bullshit.
No, it's true. He had a bad shrimp.
You're the head of legal, Doug.
You don't disappear
'cause you ate a bad shrimp.
Now, you're gonna tell me
where you were,
and you're gonna tell me the truth.
I'm gonna get it out of you
one way or another.
Reynaldo, you can go.
- Whatever the hell your name is.
- He's not done.
He's done.
You, too, Cherien.
No, I'm stayin'.
Get the hell out.
Okay, Doug, you're on the hot seat.
I was in florida,
in Boca Raton,
working on a new investor for you.
An investor.
A big one,
one to help you with
your current cash flow situation.
So who took the money?
I don't frigging know.
Why didn't you just tell me
you had an investor, Doug?
Because I was trying to keep it quiet
because it was supposed to be
your end-of-the-quarter surprise.
Who is he?
Well, that was part of the surprise.
It is a very delicate
personal relationship,
and the deal is not quite closed yet.
Excuse me.
Well, you better close that deal, Doug.
You better close it.
How much you got him on the line for?
What's he in for?
A hundred grand?
Two? Three hundred?
Four?
500,000?
I had no choice.
You signed us up for $500,000?
What was I supposed to do?
I hate those machines.
They creep me out.
What, you think
it's gonna steal your soul?
People pass polygraphs
all the goddamn time.
Who? What people?
In the movies.
He would've had me at "Doug Rich."
My God. Where are we gonna
find half a million dollars?
I said I will find an investor.
I will just have to find that investor.
What? To invest in this shithole?
Honey,
we are con men,
remember?
We do fake investors.
We don't do real investors.
Where are you gonna find a boca man?
All right team.
Listen up.
We're thinkin' of doing
a big store with Panco as the front.
So we need to find a mark
that's rich, greedy, and stupid enough
to wanna drop a load
without thinking twice.
What about Jim and Nina?
Don't they have
a lot of money from alpacas?
Cupcake, I love Nina.
Guys, I got one.
Averil Utrell, age 79.
She's a recent widow.
Her husband was some Rich oil guy,
and it turns out
she's giving all her money
to animal shelters
and music stuff.
No, we don't do little old ladies.
Di, did you burn your moral compass?
Look, why don't we just try
pullin' a rag on
an apple down
by the train station?
That's a good idea but we don't know
shit about the store market, do we?
Next?
Come on, family.
Lots of easy marks around.
Yeah, except they can't know us,
they can't be too smart,
and they gotta be greedy as shit.
You're makin' it difficult.
Rudy Blue.
Perfect.
- The baseball player?
- Yeah. He loaded.
Ain't he still in jail?
Not anymore.
Okay, Rudy Blue is quite possibly
the coolest guy in the world.
Speak up, Cal. I can't hear you.
He's the most badass
baseball player of all time.
He had sex with a hooker girl
during of the seventh inning stretch
a world series game.
When baseball was baseball.
And he got busted havin' sex
with a 17-year-old girl.
Okay, he says they were just friends.
Her dad found them naked in a hot tub.
Okay, he's got a shitload
of cash, right?
First day out of the big house,
he bought a Ferrari 612 scaglietti.
250 gs.
That's a man with somethin' to prove.
And money to lose.
He invested in shrimp boats,
bana farms,
and Rudy's chili and fries.
A guaranteed loser.
Hi, I'm rudy, and,
I'm a sexaholic.
Hi, Rudy.
Okay, and we have newcomers.
Please introduce yourself.
First names only.
Hi. I'm Mel,
and I'm a... sexaholic.
Hi, Mel.
Thank you, Mel.
And,
would you like to introduce yourself?
Hi. My name's Cherien.
And I...
I'm just so goddamn horny.
Hi, y'all.
Hi, Cherien.
All right, settle down now.
Settle down.
So there I was in the cockpit,
workin' my magic.
Wait a minute,
you gave a handjob to a pilot
while he was on duty?
It's not like no one else
was flying the plane
'cause, you know,
the co-pilot was there, too.
Luckily, I'm ambidextrous.
I guess that makes you a member
of the mile-high club.
Look who's talking,
mr. "I like 'em young."
Come on.
Don't remind me of that fact.
Come on, Rudy.
You don't have to be ashamed.
Everybody still loves you.
They don't.
Not after that girl, they don't.
That little slut?
Whole world knows she set you up.
My ex-wife has everyone convinced
that I'm just a dumbass, horny loser.
A horny loser?
You're a baseball legend.
You are.
Yeah, I guess. I...
Who do you think built
Rudy's chili and fries?
That was my idea,
my hard work, my business savvy,
and that damn judge,
he just gave her everything.
Well, it's your name on the sign.
- He gave her that, too.
- They did?
My own name.
She took everything.
Well, you still got your health...
And your money, right?
Yeah, I still got that.
But my family,
my teammates, my self-respect...
&I respect you.
- Shit.
- What? Is there a problem?
It's my ex,
makin' my life miserable.
Do you have kids?
Just Sammy,
who that bastard is trying to take away.
Posey did the same thing to me.
You got to fight him, Cherien.
Fight him.
Yeah. Everybody's saying, you know,
he's so smart, and
he's making money hand over fist.
He fights me on every penny.
I mean, he's doing a huge deal right now
that I happen to know is going to make
him even richer than he already is,
and he still wants to cut my alimony.
What does this guy do anyway?
Real estate developer.
We got married real young.
No, he couldn't deal with my problem.
I mean, can I help it if my needs
are more than he can handle?
Because I...
Controlling my lust...
Is a daily...
Hourly struggle.
I mean, temptation is everywhere.
I'm sorry.
I'm just finding this whole
abstinence thing
very, very challenging.
Cherien, I... I understand.
Me, too.
Guess I better call a cab.
Got to go pick up the kid
from the dickhead.
Well, I can give you a ride.
Really?
I mean, you think it's safe
for us 'cause
I don't want to do nothin'
to trip us up.
We're both in the program, Cherien.
I just want to be your friend.
There's still so much to discuss.
Sammy falls asleep real easy.
I love kids.
Let's go.
Sam, mama's home!
I'm here to pick you up!
Hello to you, too.
Who's your friend?
None of your damn business.
Hey, mom,
I missed you.
Sam... antha,
hi.
So this is my little girl.
And you better go get
your stuff, honey, cause
nice mr. Blue's gonna give us
a ride home.
Hey, I know you.
You're Rudy Blue.
You used to play for the Cubs.
And the A's and Royals and Rangers...
And the Mariners and the Angels
and the Braves.
My God. I am a huge fan.
Sammy and I, we order Rudy's chili
and fries probably three times a week.
Great, great. Thanks.
Rudy Blue in my own house
with my ex-wife.
Don't you listen to him, Rudy.
He's just tryin' to kiss your ass.
Where's my video?
You better find it because
I'm gonna burn this place down.
Instead of subjecting our guest
to your insanity,
perhaps we should deal with
our problems in private.
- Will you wait for me?
- Sure.
I'll just be a little bitty minute.
So sorry about this.
Help yourself to a drink.
Drinks in the kitchen.
Mi casa su casa.
Great. Thanks.
You lost our Hawaii video?
What do you care?
I'm naked in it!
What do you think?
You afraid I'm gonna put it
on the internet?
Who would want to see you naked?
Screw you!
You'd do it just to piss me off!
Fine. Take it.
You have it?
I don't want it anyway.
Just stop blogging about my sex drive.
Jesus Christ.
Are you really a baseball player?
Yeah. Well, I used to be.
My daddy is gonna buy a baseball team.
He is, huh?
Well, you know, baseball teams cost
an awful lot of money.
I know.
Once his new deal closes,
he's gonna be richer than God.
It's a secret, though.
I can't even tell mom.
Hey, free country.
I can write whatever i want.
Enough Cherien.
One more stunt like that,
I'll sue your ass.
I am so sorry, Rudy, but
Doug and I still have a few things
to fight about like cats and dogs.
It may take a while.
Can I call you in the morning?
Thank you so much.
So what do you guys think?
Is he a gut guy or a research guy?
Gut guy.
You, guys, if he does even
a little bit of research on Doug Rich...
- He's gonna...
- He's gonna find Doug Rich,
a respectable lawyer, working
for a respectable real estate firm.
I don't understand why
we can't just call the guy.
No, baby, you never,
ever call the mark.
He's gotta call us.
We can't call him.
Gotta set the bait.
See, if he takes it,
then calls, he's the right guy,
and if he doesn't...
Then he's the wrong guy.
Never was the right guy.
And I think he's gonna call.
I think Rudy's the man.
You know...
Eat that.
Listen, he's just out of jail.
The man's got a lot to prove to people
that he's still worth something.
Yeah, and as much as
he wants into mom's pants,
I think he wants in on this gig
a little bit more.
I don't know, dad. It's a long shot.
We need children of little faith.
- Could be.
- No way.
Come on.
I can do lunch.
No. Yeah, I know it.
I will meet you there.
I'll meet you there for lunch.
All right, I stand corrected.
My boobies are gettin' credit
for this one, I'm telling you.
You're pretty sly, Rudy,
snagging one of my business cards.
Well, I just thought we had
a few things in common.
Seems you know baseball, you know...
I don't know how to tell you this,
slugger, but she is
a nut case.
Well, she seemed pretty sweet to me.
If she wants you to do something,
you do it,
then she'll turn around,
she'll bite your head off,
you know?
The sex...
Sex was dangerous.
Really?
Different positions.
She loved to try out
many different positions, and she's...
She's doubled-jointed,
and I'm not,
So it was a challenge.
I shouldn't be talking about this.
But aside from the sex,
you know, everything else
was a catastrophe.
I mean, she lies like a rug,
she spends like sailor.
God, I know exactly what you mean.
My ex-wife, she takes so
much money from me.
I can't even live off
the interest anymore.
Must have been making the wrong
investments, my friend.
Is that why you asked me to lunch?
Well, you know, I heard
you had something going.
You're into real estate, right?
I love the land, Rudy.
So what exactly is this deal?
Did she tell you about Edenfalls too?
It wasn't Cherien. It was...
You don't need to cover for her.
She does this.
She thinks I'm gonna make a killing,
and she wants in on it.
And, sure, it's a good investment,
but it's closed.
Sorry.
How closed?
It's a tricky investment, Rudy.
You know, I can't open it
to inexperienced investors.
I've analyzed
a profitable opportunity.
We got to move fast.
I used to assess knuckle balls
in less than a second.
That fast enough for you?
Less than a second?
Come on.
The spotted crawfish.
The what?
It's an endangered species that lives
on a piece of prime real estate
about 60 miles north of here.
215 acres,
beautiful, lush, green land
just begging for concrete.
Sad sack who owns it
is stuck with it for the last 30 years.
Point being?
Point being that in last 30 years,
the little spotters have gone crazy,
screwing all over the place.
Fish and wildlife no longer
need to protect them.
So now, the land could be developed.
They're lifting the restrictions
on monday.
How do you know that?
Got someone on the inside.
How inside?
Under secretary of the interior inside.
So mr. S. Sack, who owns the land,
is now quite a happy man.
I bet he is. He's gonna be in
some serious cash on monday.
What?
He doesn't know about monday,
and on saturday, he's gonna sell
his land to me and my investors.
You make me one of those investors,
and I swear to God,
you can call it Rudy Blue
estates if you want to.
Cal, you're on the inside.
Di, you're on the inside.
Sammy, you're on the inside, too.
- Dad, who's on the outside?
- Does anybody else think
that the inside-outside problem is
just about the smallest one we have?
I hate doing this nympho routine.
- Don't laugh.
- I'm sorry.
It's just, I'm feelin' him up,
I'm all over him. It don't feel good,
and he's just about to put the moves
on me, and I can't really blame him.
Did you hear any of that? Okay, good.
Well, rub his back, and
remind him you're in the program.
I really need to figure something out
here. So we're gonna get some guy
to sell a bunch of fake land to you and
rudy and a bunch of other guys, right?
- Investors.
- Investors, yes. So the question is,
who are the investors? Who's the guy?
Who is anyone involved in this plan?
Who are the shills, dad?
This is a big operation.
We don't know any shills here.
The only people we know here
are the pool guy and Nina.
We got a pool guy?
What about the people
from the trailer park?
They would need the money.
- They're completely unskilled.
- They took 200 bucks off your dad.
They live in a trailer park, you guys.
They have to act like millionaires.
- We act like millionaires.
- I will check them out,
but we gotta make it on saturday
'cause the office's empty.
It's not. Hugh works there on saturdays.
- We gotta get him out of there somehow.
- This is insane, dad.
- Why?
- Because we can't do this.
I mean, half a million dollars?
We don't even know what that means.
Look, the biggest thing
that we've ever done
is sell bogus condos out of
that strip mall on myrtle beach.
That was just a couple grand
for finders fees.
- We live in this house.
- I know, mom, but
people like us,
we don't make that kind of money.
People make money like this
- all the time.
- But we don't know what we're doing.
I mean,
we're totally in over our heads here.
You know that.
So what?
We didn't know what we were doing
when we first came here.
Your dad needs our help, okay?
So we're gonna help him.
If he don't get this money, he's gonna
lose his job, and if he loses his job,
you're gonna lose this
sweet life you like so much.
So either we go or we stay,
but if we stay,
you gotta roll with it.
What the hell is that smell?
Oh, the rug cleaners were here.
They were spot testing.
They're gonna clean
the whole office tomorrow.
- Tomorrow's saturday, I gotta work.
- Well, you have to work at home.
No, I'm gonna work here,
Cherien, like I always do.
Sure they can just work around you.
I don't think the chemicals'll be
too bad. What do they got goin' here?
"mono-tetrachloride,
sodium ozone phosphate, nitric
gastro-hydraulic-mercury."
Ah, should be fine.
I'll let them know you'll be here.
Acting?
- What kind of acting?
- Are there gonna be cameras?
- I don't want cameras.
- Shut up, gerard.
There will be no cameras, gerard.
For the sum of $1,000 apiece,
you'll be acting in a theatrical event.
You will be acting in a traing seminar.
- Like for emergencies?
- Like for emergencies.
Like for investments,
like for an emergency investment.
no questions asked.
No taxes,
no withholding,
no questions asked.
- Is that last part clear?
- Fine, but what's in it for us?
Money, gerard. Christ.
Look, how do we know
you'll come through?
Air force one.
Keep it as collateral.
But no test drives, okay? It's on fumes.
Hang on.
Excuse me, gentlemen, lady.
What is it?
Holy crap!
Oh, my gosh. Are you okay?
My throat's closing up.
Should never have hired
those shithead rug cleaners.
What are you lookin' at?
How are the investors?
A little scary, actually,
one of them particularly.
But mr. Blue called. Your friend,
he's worried about a losing streak,
so you better go round there and rub
his thighs and turn them into a fire.
Rudy, thank you so much for meeting me,
'cause I was shoppin', and
I almost pulled the store clerk into
the dressing room and made him...
You know... God!
Man, I really feel like
I can talk to you, you know?
And I feel like
I can talk you, too, Cherien.
Great, 'cause I need your help.
I haven't had sex in 14 hours.
It makes me kind of jittery, you know.
- Anyway, how are you?
- I'm good. Good.
I had lunch with Doug.
My Doug?
We're gonna do
a little business deal together.
No, no. I do not know how
I feel about my boyfriend and
- my ex-husband doing deals together.
- Wait, I'm not your boyfriend, Cherien,
you know.
I mean, well, I would be.
I'm tempted. I'm really tempted.
Yeah, yeah, you're right. You're right.
I keep forgetting. I forget we're
in program. We're program.
We don't... We don't think
about each other that way no more.
Right.
We've grown.
- It's a door we choose not to open.
- Right.
So, I figured it would be okay
to invest a little money with Doug.
Sure.
And... And... And here's the thing.
The thing is, I'd really like you to
come to the meeting with me.
What meeting?
This little investor thing.
Truth is, uh...
My ex-wife made
all the big money decisions.
I tell people that she didn't, but
she really did.
She was very good at it, and...
Well, let's just say since the divorce,
I haven't exactly been hitting
them out of the park, you know?
I even tried not changing
my socks for a while, but
anyway, I was thinking if
I had another smart,
really pretty woman
sittin' next to me...
Y'all don't need me.
A man of your accomplishments,
your achievements,
everything you've done on the field
and off,
you don't need anyone.
But I gotta say, there's nothin'
that turns me on more
than an accomplished, money-makin' man.
Now, that's the truth.
So, rudy...
I would be so, so
honored...
To be with you.
Yes, rudy. Yes, I will go
to your meeting with you.
Pack this stuff up, everything in boxes.
Move this thing out here.
Okay, I want this table to the right,
this table around to the left.
- Whose left? His left?
- No, gerard, his left.
Just that way.
This one comes round here,
this one forms a line like this.
Gonna create an amphitheater here.
This is opera.
Look, don't question me.
I am the director,
- and you guys are the actors, okay?
- Okay, honey,
you got a little vein poppin'
in your neck. You need to breathe.
Look, our test client is gonna be here
in an hour. You're just gonna sit quiet
- and playing millionaires.
- She's playing a millionaire?
- Shut the hell up, gerard.
- Okay, would you be quiet, please?
My stylist is gonna come,
you'll get nice clothes,
and you're gonna look like millionaires.
- She probably once blew a millionaire.
I love where we're going here,
but it's not helping.
this is what you're gonna do.
You're gonna be
mr. Balsam, heir to the balsam fortune.
Got it? Who are you?
- Nope.
- Mr. Balsam.
Fred, you're gonna be mr. Marsho,
all right?
- Of the marsho hedge fund.
- Marsho.
What's a hedge fund?
You know, when you keep
something in a hedge?
Well, imagine a fund in a hedge.
Imelda, I want you
to be signora Boiva, right?
Ceo of Argentina transmobile.
- How's your spanish?
- Oh, it's perfecto. Gracias, papito.
That's easy for you to say.
Uh, Cal, what you gonna be?
Dieter platter, german internet genius.
Yeah, a very quiet genius. Okay.
Olin. Where's Olin?
Olin, snap out of it!
You don't have to yell.
Olin, this is important.
You're a key player here.
You're mr. Abbott,
and you are the seller.
Aw, jesus, Wayne,
he is drunk off his ass.
- Olin, this is 9:00 in the morning.
- Just give me some coffee.I'll be fine.
No, he won't be. He's on a bender
- He's gonna wreck our whole show.
- What the hell do you care?
I care because I'm a professional.
A professional gas station attendant.
I'm a musician, you two-bit whore!
Mr. Blue just called. He's on his way.
He'll be here at 10:00.
Okay, everybody,
remember what I'm saying.
Do this, work things out,
help me here, okay?
Everybody help me.
Put those in there. And, sweetheart,
please don't steal anything.
- It won't fit down your tube top.
- All right.
Olin, snap out of it!
You do not have to yell.
- Take those off, try these.
- You are lookin' good, olin.
- I think I need more concealer shit.
- He's good, isn't he?
Oh, yeah, he's the best.
Okay, imelda, honey,
you got to come out.
- He's gonna be here any minute.
- No,
- they're gonna laugh at me.
- No one will laugh at you.
Okay, the thing to rember,
at the right time,
do not forget to
take out your cell phones.
Ferrari, 2 o'clock.
- He's here!
- All right, places, come on, people
- Imelda, come out!
- All right, keep your hair on.
You say anything,
I'll rip your friggin' head off.
Imelda, tattoo.
Rudy, good to see you.
So you want in on this after all?
Yeah, well, I'm thinkin' yeah,
yeah, probably. I, uh...
Abbott's here. He is so glad
to be unloading this land.
You sure you want to do this?
Because i will happily put in
another 500 grand for your share.
Hello, rudy. Sorry I'm late.
What are you doing here?
This is invitation only.
I was invited.
Right, rudy?
Hey, you are bringing a date
to a limited partnership offering?
He's not my date. He is my sponsor.
Mr. Abbott is getting very impatient.
He says he has a 2:00 charity function.
Thank you, Di... Helen.
This way.
You know, I'd really like it if
she could be here, if you don't mind.
I promised I'd look after her. You know,
she's horny as a toad, that one.
Well, it's your funeral. You've got a...
So, mr. Abbott,
I think you'll find the price of three
million dollars is more than fair,
and I strongly suspect that
you will find it very difficult
to get that price from any other buyer,
especially considering
that your land has endangered species
zoning restrictions,
and that no development
is possible upon your land.
I know the development is one
of the things you were hoping for.
That development was one of your hopes.
- Mr. Abbott!
- Yes, yes, I had hoped
to develop...
- Alas.
- Alas, yes.
So, therefore...
As environmentally,
socially conscious, aware people,
we believe that your land
would be perfect
for a bird sanctuary,
named after yourself,
the abbott aviary habitat.
And not only that,
we will build a visitors center
for this bird sanctuary,
which will be called the abbot
aviary habitat visitors center.
Whoever can say that
quickly will win an award.
This is the idea, this is the scope
of what we wanna do
with your beautiful land,
We will buy your land for twice
what you paid for it in 1974.
So, mr. Abbott, what do you say?
Well,
I... yes, I might as well sell.
Excellent.
Now, if you could just
sign the contract.
You look so rich.
There you go. It's all yours.
Thank you, mr. Abbott.
You just follow helen here.
This way, mr. Abbott.
- Hey, can I just ask one thing?
- I'm afraid we have notime to question.
- Thank you, and...
- Aren't you rudy blue?
Yep, that's me.
Shit the bed, I thought so.
I thought that you...
You know, I got to tell you,
you are my favorite player of all time.
- Thank you.
- Enough of that, mr. Abbott.
But, my God, man,
and I say this from my heart,
you have got to lay off
that underage pussy.
Baby.
Hey, look, can't I just stay and watch?
Look, you just sold three millions
dollars with the land, buddy.
You don't stand around
and watch after that.
I know, but if I can get
his autograph, I can sell it on ebay.
This will cover the autograph.
And so, ladies and gentlemen,
say goodbye to the abbott
aviary habitat visitors center,
and say hello to Edenfalls II.
Edenfalls II...
144 luxury homes
in a garden setting
with a gated community around you.
Gated, of course,
to keep out the riffraff.
A safe, secure community,
a safe, secure investment.
And you're sure the protection
is gonna be lifted on monday.
I'm sure as sure.
I happen to have some photos
of mr. Undersecretary
underneath his secretary,
and so we are assured of his assurance.
I'm in.
Sounds good.
Very good. Now, if you
could just turn to the red folder,
the limited partnership
agreement and sign that,
that would be wonderful.
Baby?
- Is there a problem?
- No. Rudy? There's no problem.
There's no problem, is there?
It's extortion. It's illegal.
- It's only a little illegal.
- Yeah, but it's illegal.
I just got out of jail.
I... I can't do stuff like this.
If we've done that,
then if you could please
and transfer the money
into the Panco account.
Please make the transaction.
Yes, please, wire the money.
No, I don't understand why
this is so difficult for you.
Thank you. 6-6-5-9-6-5.
Please sign. Please.
Banco rio dinero?
Transfer 500,000 to Panco, inc.
Yes, 1-1-3-5-6.
Gracias.
"rudy blue."
Thank you so much.
Nobody move.
Robert Chin, FBI.
You are all under arrest for conspiracy
to commit real estate fraud.
Who is this? What's going on?
- You didn't tell me there'd be cops.
- Everyone calm down.
Agent chin, We can work something out.
Yeah. I've got it all on tape
You are all looking at 30 to life.
What did you get me into?
I'll be deported!
- I'll go to jail!
- Sit down! Back! Get back!
You wont take me to jail!
Jesus, he's dead.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Holy crap.
- You killed an fbi agent.
- I didn't mean to. I... I panicked.
- Forget it. We're out of here.
- No, no, no. God! Help me.
You can help us.
Come back. Just help us here.
Rudy, you'll help us.
No. This is gonna go viral.
No one has to know you were ever here.
- He got all on tape.
- We'll destroy the tape.
- We'll destroy the body.
- Are you insane?
We won't destroy the body.
No, no, destroy it.
No, baby, don't go, please. I need you.
- What if one of them tells?
- No they can't,
- they're accessories to murder
- Accessories to... Holy mother of shit!
- Listen, I want my money back.
- You can't get the money back.
It's in Panco already. But it's a very
good investment. 32% over two years.
I'm a silent partner, you understand?
For all you know, I'm still in prison.
- Oh, jesus, I could go back to prison.
- Rudy, I love you.
Oh, stay away from me, both of you!
Rudy, rudy. Call me.
- It's not as bad as it seems.
- Get away!
You died so well.
Very good, bob.
That is the end of
the emergency training program,
and I think we really learned
something here today.
- That was so great.
- Very good.
How was it? I thought maybe
I came in a little early, and
I think I could have been stronger
on that second line.
It was very good. It was... It was real.
It was very precise.
You were in the moment.
Your intentions were good.
That's the main thing.
- Something for yourself.
- These seminars are so great.
I don't get a lot of opportunities
to practice my craft.
- So you all can come next week?
- Uh, that would be?
Cats. I play Bustopher Jones,
community playhouse on lake street
this saturday night.
- All right, great.
- Oh, hey, bob.
Next week with the pool,
a little less chlorine.
Sure thing, mrs. Rich.
Hey, thanks.
Oh my God!
Holy shit.
We just made half a million dollars.
Panco just made half a million dollars.
We didn't make a thing. That's great.
Good for Panco. We were really good.
- I was really good.
- No, I was better.
- But I was good.
- I did a lot of stuff.
Next time we should keep the money.
You think?
Well,
I wouldn't have to pretend
to be a lawyer.
You wouldn't have to pretend to do
whatever it is he wants you to do.
Well...
You got a job.
I got a job.
The kids are in school.
We live here now.
We do?
Yeah.
So what do we do now?
- I thought you knew.
- No.
Do you know?
Rudy blue, rudy blue is your guy.
It did take two days,
but, ultimately, I persuaded him
that real estate is a solid investment.
You got rudy blue
to invest $500,000 in Panco.
Yes, but he wants to remain anonymous.
No publicity.
He's actually a very shy man.
I think he's becoming a recluse.
How'd you talk him into it, Doug?
I just persuaded him
that trust is an important thing.
That he should trust me.
You could sell the hair off a dog,
couldn't you?
You know, maybe I...
Maybe I should make you a partner.
What the hell?!
There's another one!
- Looks like a blood stain.
- Oh, my gosh.
Those rug cleaners. I don't know
what they used, but it did not work.
You should see over by my desk.
Hellacious mess.
You were right, Hugh. I never
should have hired them shitheads.
All right then, back to work.
~ SeriesSub.com ~