It's been six months,
three weeks, 14 hours...
18 minutes since I last
saw Tina's cute little...
What are you doing?
Got to go.
You can't hold it for 20 minutes?
I'm not going to tell Marci
I got to hit the head first.
Aw, come on, Tom.
I promise not to shake
it more than once.
I'd have returned the money.
A buck eighty-five.
It's the principle, not the amount.
I didn't notice at the drive-thru.
I dropped the change in
the ashtray and we left.
You didn't notice because
you were too busy leering
at the blonde working the window.
I wasn't leering.
Drooling a little, maybe.
The point is, I didn't
notice her mistake
until after we parked and I took
the change out of the ashtray.
The point is, you did notice,
which makes not returning
the money a conscious act.
Well, I'd burn more than a buck
eighty-five in gas driving back there.
It's going to come back to haunt you.
What is?
Karma. What goes around,
comes around like a boomerang.
And when yours comes back around
you better duck really low.
Mm, well, you don't have to
duck if you don't believe.
Believe what?
Kind of a private conversation, McGee.
With all the bad karma you've
built up with women alone,
I am surprised that something
hasn't just fallen off.
Missing something, DiNozzo?
Yes. Gibbs.
Agent Gibbs, this is dispatch.
Have a DOA in Norfolk.
We've got a body at Norfolk.
Get Ducky.
I thought he was flying to London.
Plane doesn't leave for a few hours.
Do you believe in karma, boss?
I've had three wives, DiNozzo.
Should have driven back.
Driven back where?
Who found the body, Commander?
Those two seamen off
the George Washington.
She docked yesterday, after a
six-month deployment in the Gulf.
They were driving off
station for two weeks leave.
Stopped to use the head.
That what they call
bleachers in Norfolk?
The one over there was locked.
Yeah, well, I guess I'd go
out behind the bleachers, too.
After discovering the
body, they flagged down
Petty Officer Cluxton, who
was passing by on patrol.
You do all this, Petty Officer?
Yes, ma'am.
After ascertaining the Lieutenant
was deceased I searched for I.D.
You touched the body?
I was wearing gloves, sir.
Go on.
Finding no I.D., I radioed in
the report, retraced my steps,
marked my footprints for
exclusionary purposes,
and taped off a 20-yard perimeter.
How often did your patrol take
you past this area last night?
Every hour on the 30, sir.
From?
20-hundred hours when
I came on duty, sir.
Saw nothing unusual
until Seamen Jennings
and Wilkens flagged me down at 0132.
- DiNozzo, get their statements.
- On it, boss.
I took their statements, sir.
You mind if we take them, too?
No, sir. Of course not.
You did a good job, Petty Officer.
Thank you, ma'am.
Petty Officer Cluxton.
Agent McGee.
Hey, how... how...
how have you been?
I've been good.
You?
Sorry, Kate.
Yeah, good.
Uh, um... yeah, I've been assigned
to NCIS headquarters at the Navy Yard.
So I heard.
It was kind of a surprise transfer.
Uh, you know, one minute
I'm in Norfolk, the next...
You're back at Norfolk maybe
even permanently, McGee.
Yeah, uh...
sorry, sorry, boss.
The Petty Officer and I, we...
vetted civilian job applicants back...
I'm going to start
measuring and sketching now.
Yeah, McGee, you do that.
That will be all for now, Petty Officer.
Yes, sir.
If you need me, Special Agent
Gibbs, I'll be in my office.
Okay.
You could have told her, Gibbs.
Told who what?
Petty Officer Cluxton.
She did a good job.
Did she now?
She wore gloves, marked her footprints,
cordoned of the crime scene...
Searched the body for I.D.
How do you do that without
disturbing the body, Agent Todd?
She could have... should
have waited for the M.E.
That would have been doing a good job.
Keep shooting.
Dr. Gutterman will be
filling in in my absence.
I should warn you, the old boy
does love to hear himself talk.
I'll do my best to handle, Doctor.
Yes, I suspect the good doctor
will be a tad grumpy as well.
Why is that?
He lost the coin toss.
What coin toss, Ducky?
The one that, in two hours,
will send me to London,
to the assembly of the
Collegium Mortum Scrutinium.
Of course.
The Society of Medical Examiners.
Very good, Kate.
Four years of Latin
has finally paid off.
Do you know who founded the society?
Not a clue.
Leonardo Da Vinci himself.
Wow, indeed.
Yes, we can trace the
roots of our society,
dedicated to the history
of forensic sciences,
to one formed by Leonardo in the same
year that he began the Mona Lisa.
In fact, that transcendent
painting is the symbol...
Duck, you want to meet with your
society in London, or give us a lecture?
Ooh, quite right.
I do have a plane catch.
Thank you, Jethro.
De nada.
Now, what story do you
have to tell us, my dear?
You know, Ducky, someday,
one of them will talk back.
The language of silence may
be hard to hear, Caitlin,
but, unlike the living, when
the dead speak, they do not lie.
Small abrasions and visible
bruising of the neck.
Strangled?
Most likely.
Dr. Gutterman can confirm that
when he examines the soft tissues.
Bruises on the thighs.
She could have been raped.
Gutterman can confirm that, too.
Liver probe.
Ready.
Usually, you ask, Jethro.
Master-Of-Arms already
searched the body, Duck.
I'm double-checking.
I do wish they'd wait until I arrive.
Hey, boss, got statements from
Seamen Jennings and Wilkens.
Can I cut them loose? They've
been at sea a long time.
Know where to find them?
Motel at Virginia Beach.
Girlfriends are waiting.
Yeah. Let 'em go.
Haven't been with their women in...
six months, three weeks, 18 hours.
The longest I went
was 11 days, six hours.
I can't believe you
actually know these things.
It's a gift.
Liver temp: 81.6.
Ambient temperature: 73.1.
Time of death?
Uh, somewhere between 2300 and 0100.
Well, my children, I
have a plane to catch.
How long are you in London for, Ducky?
Only three days.
Actually, I won't be in London.
I'll be in the city of London.
There's a difference?
There's a little known
fact that the city of London
isn't actually London at all.
How can it not be London?
No, I.D.
We've got a Lieutenant Jane Doe.
The moment Special Agent Gibbs is done
processing the scene, we
get her back to the morgue.
Of course, Doctor.
Ducky, if it's not London, what is it?
Shouldn't you be on a
plane by now, Doctor?
One of the modern marvels
of air travel, Mr. Palmer
miss one flight, there are numerous
others from which to choose.
You started without me.
I believe, as you are my
assistant, as opposed to the
other way around, it is my
prerogative to start without you.
Abby here.
You're on the air.
Abby, it's Ducky.
Oh, Ducky on the AirFone. How cool.
I'm in Autopsy.
Then you're going to be
way late for afternoon tea.
I'm sending Mr. Palmer up
with the victim's fingerprints,
semen and blood, for DNA analysis.
Ooh. Raped and murdered.
Be sure to sign the
evidence exchange forms.
I will check.
Okay.
As soon as I'm finished
with this explosive
swab analysis I will get all over it.
No, you will get all over it now.
Why are you still here?
I- I'm not.
You're back, aren't you?
You bastard.
That good for you?
Trust me, Mr. Goodwrench, I'm smiling.
I'm not.
Hey, Gibbs.
Hey, boss.
Special Agent Goodwrench?
McGee is rewiring my hot box.
That's a nickname for a bundle
of receptors in the firewall
that regulates the flow of
energy throughout the system.
See, when stimulated
correctly it sends out
waves and waves of rhythmic pulses.
Waves that, uh...
that hyper-crank the transfer
speed of digitized infor...
Abby.
McGee is helping me speed up the search
for Lieutenant Jane Doe's
fingerprints in the AFIS database.
I got to I.D. her fast,
to keep their hound at bay.
I'm more Jack Russell Terrier.
No, not you, Gibbs. Ducky.
He's barking at my heels
like a dog with the mange.
He's still here?
He's in autopsy.
And he's so grouchy he'll
give you a run for your money.
If I said that to Gibbs,
I would be seeing stars.
Well, that's the advantage of being me.
Now get back down there.
Dr. Mallard?
Jimmy Palmer.
Oh... how stupid is that?
I know that you know
I'm not Dr. Mallard.
I just...
because he... uh...
He's not here, sir.
He catch a flight to England?
No, he said he was going to Norfolk.
I think drove.
Why?
Why'd he drive?
Go to Norfolk.
Oh. Uh...
he didn't say.
He just finished the autopsy,
told me to put her to bed
and then he said he
was going to Norfolk.
Anything unusual in the autopsy?
I don't know, sir.
Dr. Mallard wouldn't
even let me assist him.
He did everything by himself.
He ever do that before?
No, sir.
He took quite a while, too.
He wanted to check everything over and
I thought he only made
me do that 'cause I'm...
...inexperienced.
Sheesh!
seen that look before.
You went to the men's
room 45 minutes ago.
You clocked me?
What could take you so long?
Don't answer that.
Actually, Kate, I was...
I don't want to hear it!
...returning the buck
eighty-five to the drive-thru.
You returned the money?
See, the whole hands over
the ears thing doesn't work.
I used to do that when I was a kid
I could hear everything my parents said.
They had some interesting words.
I can't believe you gave it back.
Well, she was off duty.
You didn't give it back.
The pimply-faced mall
rat at the drive-thru
would've just pocketed it.
You brought the teacher coffee?
Thinking ahead, Kate.
Thinking ahead.
After you tell Gibbs
we've got nothing, a cup
of his favorite brew
will tame the beast.
After I tell Gibbs?
Tell me what?
Hey, boss.
I got you a little...
Hot, hot, hot, hot...
Aah...!
What are the odds of that
happening twice in one day?
The same as me firing the two
of you if I don't get a report.
The victim's picture
is on the Navy Intranet
to department heads of every
in-station vessel and base unit.
Nothing yet.
PSA?
No missing females.
Officers or enlisted.
PSA is Personnel Support Activity.
I've been here a year, Tony.
I know the acronyms.
Ah, a year.
Seems like only yesterday you were
mixing up NAV-SOCs
with NAV-SUPs.
Our little girl's growing
up fast, isn't she, boss?
What was that for?
Not growing up.
What else you got?
Nothing.
Hey, guys.
But it looks like Abby does.
Who is our victim?
We do not know.
Then what are you doing here?
We're... we're...
we're through, boss.
We ran the entire AFIS data
bank, we didn't get a match.
How can AFIS not find a match?
She's a Navy lieutenant.
No, she isn't, Jethro.
Lieutenant Jane Doe is a misnomer.
The poor woman was never in the navy.
Match this sperm against the
sample I removed from our victim.
Please.
You've been holding out on me, Doctor.
Yes, Agent Gibbs...
I have.
Tell my family what happened to me.
Please.
Dr. Mallard.
That's not the first trident you've seen
carved in the neck of a victim, is it?
No.
I shouldn't have held out
on you, but I wasn't sure
it was the same until I did the autopsy.
You weren't sure when
you saw the trident
on her neck at the crime scene?
Unlike you, Agent
Gibbs, I prefer to rely
on forensic evidence and not my gut.
We're a team, Doctor.
Team members don't hold out.
Yes, you'right.
It was... unprofessional.
I'm still hoping that
Abby doesn't get a match
and all this is just
some macabre coincidence.
Forgive me, Jethro.
Tell me about that other case.
Well, it was ten years ago...
A Navy corpsman, out jogging,
fod a body in a culvert
beside an athletic field at Norfolk
a Navy lieutenant who'd
been raped and strangled.
She had a trident carved
on the side of her neck.
We ran her prints through
AFIS and got nothing.
She wasn't in the Navy.
Our profiler believed that the
murderer had dressed his victim
as a Navy lieutenant to
fulfill some revenge fantasy.
'94 was the first year women
were deployed on combat ships.
Special Agentes Iassumed that the killer
had served under a female officer.
Dawes?
I don't know him retire?
Uh-uh. He passed on,
oh... seven years ago.
He investigated every Navy
unit with a trident insignia.
Especially those wiemale officers.
He didn't come up with a single suspect.
The trident symbol may have
nothing to do with the Navy.
That's the conclusion we came to. But...
this note was found at
the scene of the crime,
three days after the
body was discovered.
Was it missed on the initial search?
No.
It was found where the body had been.
But he didn't come back.
Not until now.
I've got one question for you, Ducky.
Why is this case so personal?
Did you know that Leonardo Da
Vinci never gave the Mona Lisa
to the patron who commissioned it?
Nope.
Instead... he carried
the painting with him
for the rest of his life.
She's been with me
for ten years, Jethro.
She was the only Jane
Doe I never identified.
The only one whose
family has no closure.
The only one who never went home.
Autopsy.
Ducky?
Do I sound like Ducky?
No. Actually, these days he
sounds more like you, Gibbs.
I'm not in the mood, Abbs.
Well, maybe this will rise your spirits.
The semen sample from
Jane Doe's murderer
matches the sample of the Ducky case.
This is good news, right?
Abbs, that semen is from
a ten-year-old cold case.
He's back, isn't he?
Not again Jethro.
We can't let him escape again.
I saw this trident carved into the neck
of the victim at the crime
scene and told no one.
Not even Gibbs.
All I can do is apologize and assure you
that such an inexcusable
lapse of forensic protocol
will never happen again.
Right.
Ten years ago, another Jane Doe
was found raped and strangled
in a culvert beside an
athletic field at Norfolk.
She, too, was a civilian, dressed
in the uniform of a naval lieutenant.
She had a high blood-alcohol level
and a trident carved
into the side of her neck.
Abby has confirmed that
sperm from both victims
came from the same man, so we are
pursuing a serial rapist and murderer.
This note was found three days after
the crime scene had been processed.
A challenge to investigators.
You think, Kate?
I've asked Commander Reynolds to place
our crime scene under
discreet surveillance.
Since '94 was the first year
we deployed women on warships,
this wacko may be an enlisted
man acting out a revenge fantasy.
They investigate units with
tridents on their patches?
Gee, I don't think they
thought about that, Tony.
Yeah.
They investigated every ship and
shore division with female officers.
Nada.
Abbs, you need to go to the head?
No. I have a question.
Isn't ten years a long
time between murders?
Absolutely.
This doesn't fit a
serial killer's profile.
Ducky, could pull the headshots
up for me again, please?
Now if he goes through the
trouble of dressing two civilians
like a lieutenant he hates, why
is one blonde the other brunette?
One Anglo, one Hispanic?
They're both cute for being dead.
He's a wacko!
Maybe just being female and
intoxicated was good enough.
Unless Abby blew the sperm match...
No way.
...the same man killed both of them.
Which means he didn't rape and
murder for ten years because...
He was in prison!
Hey...
- Okay, homework assignments: McGee
- Boss.
Search JAG records for sailors
incarcerated after October of '94.
And recently released.
On it.
Kate, suspect interviews
from ten years ago.
If any of these men still
live in Norfolk, question them.
Okay.
DiNozzo, flash this Jane
Doe at every bar, club
and strip joint within a
mile of the Norfolk Gate.
Given the victim's blood-alcohol level,
maybe he picked her up at one of them.
No problema.
Abby, forensics may have
missed something in '94.
Go over it again.
Yes, Professor.
Come on, people.
Let's go! Let's go!
Hey, wait.
Come here.
You'll need Ducky's help.
No, I won't.
Abbs...
Yes, I will.
Hey, uh, Duckman...
Yeah.
The cross polars in my polarizing
light microscope won't center.
You may have a problem.
However, I think I have the solution.
How's NCIS doing?
Well, according to my friends,
I'm having some bad karma.
Not that I really believe in
that stuff, but... you know.
You really should, you know.
That right?
Yeah.
See, I used to reject
all things spiritual,
mystical and existential
But once I began to embrace them,
my whole life started to blossom.
She been in recently?
No. What'd she do?
Got herself raped and killed.
Such a sweet countenance.
"Sweet countenance..."
Yeah, that radiant look on her face.
She doesn't look
radiant- she's dead.
In that picture?
Yeah, she's dead.
She's dead?
She's dead.
Why do you think her eyes are closed?
I thought she was meditating.
Okay, thanks.
Guess he doesn't
believe in that, either.
Well, have Petty Officer
Cluxton deliver it ASAP.
No. The evening pouch
will not do, Commander!
He didn't wait three days.
Hello.
Abbs, Norfolk got a note from our wacko.
Ooh, did you catch him?
He made the drop before
surveillance was in place.
You'll have it in a couple of hours.
Listen. Compare the ink,
the paper, the handwriting.
Did you get DNA?
You get DNA off the first note?
Yep. DNA testing was in
the caveman aera in '94.
I'm good.
I'm really good.
Gas pain?
What?
No!
Well, then stop grinning
and tell me what you got.
When he found the first
Jane Doe while jogging,
Petty Officer Goetz was in port
on a carrier, the Teddy Roosevelt.
Really? Agent Dawes
interrogated him a number
of times on the Big Stick and here.
Big Stick?
Teddy Roosevelt.
"Talk softly, carry a...
Carry a big stick. Cute.
Goetz stayed in the Navy, is a chief
and arrived in Norfolk
on the same carrier
as the seamen who found our Jane Doe.
Uh, the "Honest Abe."
"Shall Not Perish."
What?
The Lincoln's not the "Honest Abe."
It's "Shall Not Perish."
What kind of a nickname
is "Shall Not Perish"?
Ask Chief Goetz when you
pull him in for questioning.
Okay.
The Emancipator.
That, that would be a good
name for the Abraham Lincoln.
Since he, uh, he signed the
Emancipation Proclamation.
Uh, the... Sorry.
This have to do with the body
I found ten years ago, sir?
Yeah.
Isn't there a statute of
limitations on questioning a suspect?
Didn't say you were a suspect.
Why se would I be here, sir?
Another body was found two nights ago.
Same MO.
She have a trident... here?
He said he'd be back.
Now, how did you know that?
Agent Dawes never told you.
No, sir.
But he had me write out "I'll be
back" with my right and left hand.
Not too hard to figure out why.
You arrived two days ago
on the Abraham Lincoln?
Yes, sir.
First nit back, where'd you go?
You think I raped and murdered her?
Never said she was raped.
You said the same MO.
Where'd you spend your
first night ashore?
Clubbing?
I didn't leave the station.
Six months at sea,
your first night in port
you spend it aboard ship?
No, sir.
I said I didn't leave the station.
I stayed with a friend.
stationed here at Norfolk?
Yes, sir.
Hey.
Hey! Whoa. Whoa!
Where's the five-alarm?
I think I have a suspect.
Machinist Mate Harlan Wilson.
He was there in October '94.
Discharged that December.
Arrested two months later in Toronto
for sexually assaulting a
female Canadian naval officer.
Got 15 years.
Paroled two months ago and
is now living in Norfolk.
I didn't know there were
women in the Canadian Navy.
I gotta tell Gibbs.
Whoa, probie, first, you report
to your immediate superior.
I just did.
"Blah-blah-blah-blah, female
Canadian naval officer."
That's not reporting.
Yeah, that would be all you heard.
Again, start with the name.
Can't do that, sir.
Your friend married?
No, sir.
An officer?
Yes, sir.
So, you see how I
can't give you the name.
Chief,
I'm not interested in ruining careers.
I need to know where you
spent the night of the murder.
Can we speak off the record, sir?
Just you and me?
Kate...
stop the tape.
Stop the tape.
Yes, ma'am.
No sound?
Gibbs is having a private
interrogation: no sound, no video.
McGee needs to talk to him.
I'm not going to interrupt him.
Kate...
No.
Okay. Fill her in, McGee.
Tell her about Harlan Wilson.
Meet me in the garage in five.
I'm waiting, Chief.
How do I know they stopped taping?
Because I told them to.
The name.
Lieutenant Commander...
William McDougal.
Hey, Starsky, check
the sweet '70's ride.
Nice.
All right, you be the Avon Lady.
I'll cover the rear.
Yah.
What's the peekie, probie?
Doesn't look like anyone's home.
I'd love to get a look
inside while he's away.
I told you we should
get search authorization.
No time.
Besides it's a Catch-22.
It is?
Yeah. We go inside and get something
we shouldn't, we're screwed.
We don't go inside
and don't get something
we could've, we're more screwed.
I'm not following.
That's because I'm a
highly seasoned senior
field agent and you're a pathetic...
Probie. Yeah.
You're a fast study, McGee.
15 seconds personal best.
Harlan's no Martha Stewart.
Well, he's gonna be home soon.
How can you tell?
Hungry Man in the oven.
Buck
eighty-freakin'- five.
Pickup's pulling up!
Yeah?
NCIS.
Harlan Wilson?
Tom Wilson-
his big brother.
Your kid brother around, Tom?
No.
He listed this address
on his parole release.
He was here.
You know where he is now?
Yeah.
Well, we need to talk to him.
Well, that's gonna be hard to do.
He's been dead for six weeks.
Chief Goetz's alibi checks out.
Where was he?
With a friend.
You're taking the word of a friend?
No,
a saliva swab to compare his DNA
with sperm taken from the victim's.
Any other questions?
Good. My turn.
Where's McGee?
He took Harlan's hairbrush to Abby
to compare his DNA to the sperm.
Probie won't give up on the obvious.
Harlan Wilson was dead when the
second murder occurred,
wasn't he, DiNozzo?
Very dead, boss.
Big mother heart attack.
Fax of the death certificate.
How many bars and clubs did you canvass?
Uh, 24, 25.
Which was it?
24 or 25?!
You in a bad mood, Boss?
No!
Didn't think so.
Covered every one within
a mile of the Norfolk
main gate like you said.
What about the other gates?
You didn't ask me to look at...
I'm gonna... I'm on that.
Kate, you go with him.
You want me to go bar-hoppg with Tony?!
You've never been in a bar, have you?
Not the kind sailors hang at.
Agent Gibbs?
You can catch him at the rear elevator.
Agent Gibbs.
You have the note, Petty Officer?
I do, sir.
Knowing how important the note
is forensically, I jumped a ride
with a CH-53 that was
headed to Quantico, caught
the Amtrak to D.C., then hailed a cab.
Well, that's creative
thinking, Petty Officer Cluxton.
Thank you, sir.
Are you taking the note to the lab now?
I'm...
pretty interested in forensics, sir.
Tell me you're not serious
about the last place.
Completely serious, Kate.
I mean, strip clubs
are good for more than
just fraternity bashes
and bachelor parties.
You honestly think bar
mitzvahs are appropriate.
Oh, trust me.
Nothing says "welcome to manhood"
as perfectly as a skillful lap dance.
Speaking of...
Hello.
We don't open until 6:00.
And you're working here
instead of catching rays
at the beach in a thong.
I know it's cold out, probably too cold.
You do wear a thong, don't you?
Tony...
Sorry.
It's my humor.
Not for everyone.
NCIS.
Naval Criminal Investigative Service...
Yeah, I know what it means.
What do you want?
Tony...
Well...
Tony.
What?!
This is the girl playing
the drums, isn't it?
Yeah, she hasn't been
here the last three nights.
What happened to her?
Can you tell us her name?
Janice Santos.
She isn't sleeping, is she?
Not sleeping.
Oh, my God.
We need an address.
What happened to her?
She was raped and murdered.
Some man raped and murdered her?
Yeah. It wasn't me.
I'm trying to catch the bastard.
Sorry.
It's just a shock.
Any ideas who could've done this?
No. God, no.
Do you have the address?
Yeah, of course.
I'll get it for you.
She took that hard.
Yeah. She sure did.
The writing looks the same
to me, Special Agent McGee.
It's pretty similar,
Petty Officer Cluxton.
There are slight discrepancies,
within the range that
a person's handwriting
would change in ten years...
Special Agent McGee.
What's this?
Oh, that's a polarizing
light microscope.
Let me show you how to use it.
You touch that, McGee,
you'll be singing soprano.
Yeah, Abby's under a lot of pressure.
What are you doing to the note?
Are you writing a book?
No, I'm just...
interested, ma'am.
Looking for prints.
The fumes are from heated super glue.
In its gaseous form,
its bonding capabilities
enable us to obtain fingerprints.
Nothing.
Well...
I'd better get back to Norfolk.
Thanks for letting me observe, ma'am.
Anytime. Well...
not anytime... sometime.
Maybe.
Good seeing you again,
Special Agent McGee.
Likewise, Petty Officer Cluxton.
So, are you two that formal when
you're exchanging bodily fluids?
Stay outside, sir.
Did Janice Santos always
keep the place so empty?
I don't know.
No clothes.
No personal effects.
This place has been cleaned.
We better call Gibbs.
At least I can tell Duck you've
I.D.'d Jane Doe Number Two.
If her apartment's
that clean, this Janice
Santos probably knew her killer.
Wh you're finished with the crime scene,
bring everything back here.
I'll see you at Abby's in the morning.
DNA processing can take several days,
but knowing the hyper-urgency
of the case, I processed
all of the sperm
samples in just 37 hours.
Gonna be another 37
before we get some results?
Okay, um...
DNA off the first
note matched the sperm.
The killer wrote it.
The second note?
No prints. No DNA.
What about the handwriting?
It could be a match.
I sent a copy to an expert I met at
a forensics conference
at the Greenbriar.
It is such a sweet place.
They have golf, tennis, falconry...
Falconry!
I hunted with a falcon
in Scotland in my youth.
It's so cool. Yeah.
It's almost a lost art, I'm afraid.
Like forensics reporting?
Okay... moving on to saliva,
always a crowd pleaser.
There is no way Chief Goetz's DNA
comes close to matching the sperm.
I guess you were right, boss.
You guess?
I know.
Abby, why do you call us all
in here when you have nothing?
But I do!
I matched the DNA off the hair
from the brush McGee gave me.
Hello, Mr. Wilson?
The DNA matches the sperm
found in both victims.
That's impossible.
Wilson had been dead weeks
when Janice Santos was raped.
DNA does not lie.
Hey.
Hey, he died before
she did, boss, I swear.
Boss, what if...
what if Wilson's semen was inserted in
Janice Santos after she was murdered?
Ew!
How'd the murderer get the semen?
Same way I did.
Looking at the time code, this
is the day before the murder.
What is it, McGee?
She's the one.
Well, how can you tell?
She's not even near the refrigerator.
His gut.
No, no, no, it's not just my gut, boss.
When I was back at Norfolk, Cynthia...
Petty Officer Cluxton
and I, we were friendly.
Really!
Abby...
She liked me, but not that way.
What way would that be, probie?
I didn't ask, Tony, and she didn't tell.
Cluxton's gay?
Boss, we I.D.'d Janice
Santos in a lesbian bar.
There's more.
Petty Officer Cluxton
used her mother's name.
Her father was an NCIS
Agent before he died.
Special Agent Dawes.
Boss, I didn't think about this until...
I think that's her.
That's okay.
Run the tape.
Janice Santos was your lover.
You met her at Flip Side...
a lesbian bar.
Which is why the
bartenderdidn't respond to me.
You accusing me of being gay, sir?
No. No, I'm accusing you of murder.
Murder?
I didn't murder anyone, sir.
She jilt you, Petty Officer?
I have no idea what
you're talking about, sir.
It doesn't matter.
We have you on tape removing
semen from a Jane Doe case
your father worked ten years ago.
Can you identify on that tape what I'm
removing in the evidence locker, sir?
I can't.
You copied the killer's M.O.
from your father's case file.
I'm not sure where my
father's case files are, sir.
You strangled Janice Santos,
put her in a Navy uniform.
carved a trident in
her neck, inserted semen
from the first murder in her vagina.
Not true.
None of it, sir.
Even left a note like the one
found at the first crime scene.
I didn't leave that note, I found it.
So, who killed Janice Santos?
Obviously, whoever murdered
the Jane Doe ten years ago, sir.
No, not whoever.
His name is Harlan Wilson.
A former machinist's
mate stationed at Norfolk.
You caught him, sir.
No.
No, but we matched his DNA to
semen found in both victims.
Why are you accusing me?
Harlan Wilson died five weeks
before you killed Janice.
Damn...
damn...
damn!
It's time for our relationship
to change, my dear.
It's time for you to go home,
but it's not the home
you knew in this life.
But I think you'll find peace here.
And the way things
turned out, so will I.