You have entered the circle.
You have felt the flames.
You have suffered the seven trials.
You have reached the
moment of your final test.
Are you prepared?
- Yes, sir.
- Then let's do it.
Go!
Last one to the house
drinks the keg dregs!
I love Hell Week.
Did you see their faces?
Strike Force Command, this is
Red Leader. Alpha Team is in play.
Roger that, Red Leader, I have visual. You've got hostiles
on both the north and east quadrants of the building.
Hostile on the left flank. All teams prepare
for entry. Our target is located on the...
Say again, Strike Force
Command. Did not copy your last.
Uh, wait one, Red Leader.
Copy that. Red Unit, hold your positions
Hi, Probie!
Uh, David, I have to call you back.
Copy that, McGee
I told you he was a boxers guy.
Damn, McGee, I thought for sure
you were a tighty-whitey man.
Come on, let's get dressed. You
don't want to keep Gibbs waiting.
You said 0900. It's only 7:30!
We thought we'd observe you
in your natural environment.
Kind of like watching
National Geographic.
We watch as the McGee moves slowly from
the watering hole trailed by hyenas.
Is this the History Channel Room?
Ah... this is where you
do your writing thing, huh?
Look at this.
"The Continuing
Adventures of L.J. Tibbs."
That's personal!
Hmm...
I wonder who "L.J. Tibbs" could be?
Check it out. He eats dinosaur cereal.
Okay, wod you both please just wait
by the door? By the door, please?
Got any Macy Gray in here?
Wait, Tony, don't touch those. Those
are collectibles. They're very valuable.
Oh, my gosh. Sorry.
I just thought they
were musty old records.
It's bad enough having to work on Sundays,
without you guys ransacking my appartment.
Yes, it was very inconsiderate of that
Marine sergeant to die on a weekend.
I'm getting my weapon.
Don't touch anything else!
Hey!
George Clooney could not
get laid in this place.
Your place needs a lot of help, McGee.
At least you're not building
a boat in your basement.
Come on.
Tim?
Strike Force Command, this is
Red Leader. McGee, are you there?
This is Strike Force
Command. Do you copy?
Based on the rigor resolving itself, I'd say
our Sergeant's been dead for at least 36 hours.
I'm more concerned with
how it happened, Duck.
Well, apart from the obvious,
he took a tumble down the hill.
Neck's probably broken.
Yeah, but then, we never do put
too much emphasis on the obvious.
Do we, Sergeant?
Ow!
It's remarkable how these college
hangouts all smell the same.
Stale beer, tobacco...
...vomit.
It's from the kid that found him.
Any idea why the young
man is half-naked?
It must be a college thing.
Hey...
... where you been?
Stopped for coffee.
Got... you are welcome.
Marine Sergeant Joseph Aaron Turner. Found
dead at 0200 by a drunk college student.
Sounds like Hell Week.
Hell Week?
Yeah, fraternal rite of passage.
Worst week of my life.
Followed by the best four years.
Yeah? You were running around
in your skivvies, DiNozzo?
Technically.
But back then, they made
us wear them on our heads.
I think it was a...
... sort of a character-building thing
Certainly explains a lot.
- Uh-huh. Hey,
McGee... -Yeah.
- Find out what Turner was doing on campus.
- On it.
Excuse me, Special Agent Gibbs?
I wonder if we could let Mr. Pippin
go home and dress more appropriately?
Sure. After one of my agents
interviews him. DiNozzo.
Um, you know, I think that's
really more up Kate's alley.
Well, maybe, but you two
have so much in common.
Go.
This area popular with students?
For all sorts of extracurricular
activities. Bonfires, fraternity pranks...
Hazing?
We've had our share of incidents.
Broken bones, alcohol poisoning.
And this isn't the first
accidental death we've seen.
Who said anything about an accident?
You think this is a homicide?
Until I find out it wasn't.
Boss, I had Turner's SRB pulled. He's an NROTC student
attached to the Waverly University campus. Lives in the dorms.
Get an address?
Uh, just getting on that.
I'm going to radio his unit.
I thought college students
were supposed to be poor.
Most of my midshipmen would not have survived without
at least 200 channels and a DSL hook-up, Agent Gibbs.
How long have you been Turner's Marine
Officer Instructor, Captain Lemay?
Since he enrolled last year.
You expect to lose men in
combat, not on the college campus.
- What the hell happened to my Marine?
- Working on it, Captain.
What can I do to help?
You can start by telling us about him.
He was one of my best midshipmen.
Came to us straight from the fleet after
two combat tours in Iraq and Afghanistan.
How is he taking to college life?
There's a fair amount of culture shock,
but like any good Marine, he adapted.
- Any personal problems or issues?
- We had a few incidents with student activists on campus.
Protesting the war?
Protesting anything military.
Our unit was vandalized, rallies outside our offices.
When word got out that Turner was a vet, he took some heat.
What kind of heat?
Name-calling, mostly.
Turner handled it like most Marines.
Not well.
He lost five Marines
in his squad in Iraq.
He handled it as best
he could, Agent Gibbs.
He was a damn fine Marine.
- And intelligent, too.
- Boss...
This is graduate-level mathematics.
- Theoretical calculus.
- He was on the advanced track in math and physics.
He was a real asset to the Corps.
You're blowing in my ear, Mr. Palmer.
Oh, sorry, Doctor.
Something piqued your interest?
It seems this break is too
clean to be the result of a fall.
Correct. If he landed on his
neck, this would be jagged here.
But this? This is too precise.
- You notice anything else?
- Uh, he took a beating.
Yes, bruises round the eyes, knuckles grazed...
but what captured my attention most were these.
This coloration suggests they were recent-
inflicted on our poor Marine just before his death.
Do we know what caused
them? We do not... yet.
This reminds me of an English earl
who was abducted and asphyxiated.
- Every bone in his body was broken.
- What happened to him?
Well, it was on a moonlit night...
We know what killed him yet?
Sergeant Turner was involved in a nasty
fight that resulted in a broken neck.
- He was murdered.
- Yeah.
What about these welts?
Well, certainly painful,
but they didn't do any internal damage. Mostly
surface. You thinking what I'm thinking, Doc?
I'm afraid so, Jethro.
Call me when you find out.
Find out what, Doctor?
Sergeant Turner...
...may have been
tortured before his death.
- Whoa!
- Yeah.
So that's what happened
to the English earl.
What English earl?
You said Turr was smart, McGee, when, in
fact, you should've said he was brilliant.
These equations rock.
It's Homology.
Mm, close. Cohomology
I think it's Homology.
No it's cohomology. I did my independent study in
advanced string theory; so I think I would know.
- I see you're playing the MIT card again.
- No, I just happened to go to school there.
And you just happen to
talk about it... a lot.
Oh, so glad to see you two
don't need adult supervision.
McGee was annoying me again.
Don't.
- What do we have from the crime scene?
- Oh, um...
I got Turner's toxicology report back.
His blood alcohol level
was.07- not drunk.
Not sober, either. What else?
- There were foreign blood samples found on
his face and his knuckles... Yeah, and?
And a Chinese menu of chemicals found on his skin. Mixed dried paint,
turpentine, bleach-it's like he was partying in a janitor's closet.
What about Turner's laptop?
Well, I completely underestimated
the depth of his mathematics ability.
I thought that he was concentrating on numerical analysis,
but it turns out he was also working on fiber bundles.
I mean, the work's a little rough...
- Anything connected to his death, McGee?
- Not yet.
Um, I didn't go to MIT, but
I think I found something.
Turner had a private container. It's like a vault
inside the hard drive where he can hide files
... very sophisticated.
- Can you open it?
They don't call me "Five Fingers Sciuto"
for nothing. Actually, nobody calls me that.
- My nickname was actually Vamperstein, but I never
really liked the sound of it. Ah, Abby...
Right. Too much caffeine. Sorry
It'll take just a second...
And...
we... are...
... in.
It's an encrypted e-mail.
He received it on Friday.
Same day he was killed.
One, two, three!
That's it!
Maybe I should give you a break, you
know... because you're college girls.
What do you think, Simmons?
No, Gunnery Sergeant?
Damn straight!
To me, you're midshipmen!
Barely! Understood?
Yes, Gunnery Sergeant!
You pull a stunt like that again with me, and
you can both kiss your scholarships goodbye!
Go!
A way!
Gunnery Sergeant Leeka
Special Agents Gibbs
and Todd- NCIS.
Sorry you had to hear all that.
What'd they do?
Notice the hair, ma'am?
Oh... Not regulation?
No.
Purple and orange?
Oh.
Sometimes I feel like I'm
a kindergarten teacher.
Oh, yeah... I'm familiar
with the sentiment.
So, Captain Lemay said you wanted
to talk to me about Sergeant Turner.
- What kind of midshipman was he, Gunny?
- He put most of those kids to shame, sir.
Would've made one hell
of a Marine officer.
Your captain said that he had
problems with war protesters?
Eh, you could say that, ma'am.
One of them spit on his uniform.
Turner cleaned his clock.
Well, do you think this protester
was the type to look for revenge?
You saying Turner was murdered?
- We are.
- I want to know why.
- Simmons!
- Sir!
- Get me Midshipman Blake!
Double-time! -Yes, Gunny!
Blake's a Petty Officer.
He was tight with Turner; he's also the one that pulled
him off the protester before the campus cops arrived.
Who else was Turner tight with? Blake'll know.
They're the only two enlisted men in the unit.
Excuse me, Gunnery Sergeant.
- What, Simmons?!
- Midshipman Blake didn't report to formation this morning.
Blake's never been UA-
not since I started here.
You telling me Petty
Officer Blake is missing?
No, I'm telling you
that he is, Agent Gibbs.
No one's seen Blake since Friday night.
Oh, hi, ladies. Oh, God, I miss college.
Find the room yet, probie?
- Right here.
- Yeah. Blake's not there.
You never told me you had a brother.
Any idea when he's coming back?
I haven't seen him for a couple days.
You guys are definitely not campus cops.
- I make you for FBI.
- Wrong. NCIS.
- That stands for...
- Yeah, I know what it stands for.
You're here 'cause of Turner, right?
Did you know him?
I was in his NROTC unit.
- Oh, wow! These are the new docking stations for the...
- Yeah, yeah. He just got that.
For the new Axxum X-5 handheld
computer. It's sweet, right?
Sweet!
Shouldn't you guys be wearing rubber gloves? You're
completely compromising the integrity of the crime scene.
It's not a crime scene.
It's a dorm room.
- You totally think Finnegan had something to do with Turner's death.
Why else would you be here? You got us, Sherlock.
Maybe they were partners in some kind of illicit
business- like, they dealt drugs on campus.
- Well now, did they?
- No. I was being hypothetical.
Do you guys have a warrant?
'Cause if you don't, nothing you find here will be admissible
in court. Unless, of course, you have probable cause.
That is exactly what we have.
- I don't know. Just because he wasn't home?
- Little girl, what's your name?
- Simon Frankel.
- Okay. Listen, Urkel,..
...we're here on official business, so why don't you go back to your dorm
room and play Dungeon Master, and let professionals do their work, okay?
I'm just trying to help.
You want to be a big help?
Yeah. Definitely.
Okay. Put your hands in the air.
Nothing to be worried
about. Spread your legs.
Okay, stick out your tongue.
You're the gargoyle
that guards this door.
- That was nice.
- But they don't pay us to be nice, McGee.
Hey!
Put on some gloves.
There is definitely
something wrong with this guy.
What?
Listens to folk music.
There's something else wrong
with this guy too, Tony.
A bloody rag.
Nice work, McGee.
That's a lot of blood loss.
Injured?
Or dead?
Message on the left
was on Turner's laptop.
Message on the right
was found on Blake's.
He received it on Saturday, boss.
- Who sent them?
- McGee's working on it.
What else do we know?
- No one on campus has heard from Blake since...
- Friday.
And Abby says that the blood on the
rag and bed matches Blake's type.
Two enlisted men:
One missing, one dead...
...what do they have in common?
The resentment of the Coalition
Alliance Team for Peace, Gibbs.
Cat-Pee. Not a very attractive acronym.
Their leader's a Waverly
senior, Hunter Huxley.
He's been arrested five times for disturbing
the peace. He's majoring in political science...
Minoring in antigovernment subversion and sticking it to
The Man. I dated a girl like that in college once, boss.
Wasn't bad till she stopped
shaving her armpits and her...
She owns a car dealership now, in
case you were looking for a good deal.
Huxley's been leading the antiwar protests on campus, and last month,
at a peace demonstration in front of the NROTC building, we know...
...that he started spitting on midshipmen.
- And Sergeant Turner dropped him.
After that, Huxley made Turner his
personal target. Harassed him regularly.
- You think he could've taken it to the next level?
- I think you and Kate are gonna go find out.
Hey, turn that frown upside down,
sweetie. We're going back to college.
Tony, your problem is you've never left.
This is what I'm talking about. It's
like I'm having flashbacks or something.
I'm surprised you even remember college.
You spent most of it throwing up in a urinal.
Well, I'm pretty sure you spent your Saturday nights
alone, in your PJs, watching Julia Roberts videos.
Oh, you don't know
what I did in college.
Mm, but I do know what you
did on your Spring Break.
I knew it! You still have that
wet T-shirt photo, don't you?
- I don't.
- You swear?
Well, I don't have it on me.
- A-Chi! Way
to go! -Yeah.
God, you're pathetic.
Gotta move on, DiNozzo. They're over.
- What's over? - Your glory years.
They've passed you by. It's time to retire the beer bong.
- Ouch, Kate. Ouch.
- Oh...
There's our budding anarchist....
...is the puppet of corporate America!
This is an immoral act! No... more... war!
No more war!
Learn the truth about this war!
Your government doesn't trust you, don't trust your
government! Hey, man, help us defeat Big Brother?
We kind of work for him.
- Agents Todd and DiNozzo, NCIS.
- I got a permit to be here.
I'm sure you do. That's not the
reason we're here, Mr. Huxley.
Sergeant Joseph Turner.
If he's pressing charges on me,
then I'm pressing charges on him.
That fascist nearly broke my jaw.
I'd hold off on the charges.
He's dead.
What?!
His body was found on
campus Saturday night.
- You hadn't heard about that?
- I've, uh, I been out of town. I just got back today.
That's convenient.
Hold on a second. You think I did it?
- Well, you two didn't exactly get along.
- Well, yeah, because tried to beat the crap out of me.
After you spit on him.
You do realize I'm a
peace activist, right?
Anti-violence.
Maybe you knew his friend, too?
Petty Officer Finnegan Blake?
He was a midshipman.
Been missing since Friday.
I get it! So this is
how it happens, huh?
They send their Gestapo goons
to try and quiet the movement.
You planning on arresting me?
- It's crossed our minds.
- Do it.
I'm not afraid of you, I'm
not afraid of your tactics.
You should really meet
our boss. He'd like you.
And you should really meet
my lawyers. They'd love you.
The student organizations
alone are mind-blowing.
- Did you know that there are seven online mystery
writer workshops on campus? No, I didn't.
But I'm sure you're going to tell me
what that has to do with our dead Marine.
I thought that whoever was involved in
Turner's death might have a campus Web account,
...so I hacked into the servers, looking for
any mention of Turner or Blake. -Okay. Any hits?
No- the servers have
been pretty quiet.
What is that?
Someone's IM'ing Sergeant Turner.
- It's an "Instant Message," Gibbs.
- It's like an e-mail, but live.
Just put it up on the plasma.
"Hello, NCIS."
He's not on Turner's buddy list.
He's probably using an alias.
Can you trace it, McGee?
If we can keep him online
- Abby, talk to him.
- Okay.
Hello, Creepy Voice.
"You're looking in the wrong places."
He's diverting his connection
through half a dozen servers.
We've got the Baltimore Public Library
by way of a public server in Buffalo...
That's it- get
him. Get him, McGee.
Where should we be looking?
Deeper.
Oh, come on. How's that gonna help us?
I've back-traced him to the
Waverly University campus.
Where on campus?
Almost there.
Look beyond the surface.
Oh, that's a really sucky clue.
When you say "beyond the surface",
are you being literal or metaphorical?
I'm just trying to clarify.
"They're everywhere."
Okay, I've got it down to one city block.
Right off of campus. Just one more second...
Goodbye.
Got him, boss!
Yeah.
You are sure about this, right?
I was able to triangulate the connection to the
campus servers, and then reran the back-trace...
Just answer the question, McGee.
Yes. I'm sure, boss.
Let's do this. Kate, cover the back.
No, no! Stop!
Federal agents! Don't move!
I am going to kill McGee.
We got it covered, Kate!
So, is Gibbs still mad at me?
About what, Probie?
Dead Marine on campus?
The missing Petty Officer?
Computer hacker who might be
part of a radical peace movement?
None of these things are your fault...
... really.
But sending Gibbs on a panty raid?
He's going to kill you.
Hey!
I want answers.
Where is Abby?
She's on a run to the
evidence garage, boss.
Anything on the hacker?
Um, he was on a wireless connection.
The house you hit was set up for WiFi.
He was probably sitting
somewhere outside on the street.
But I'm working on
tracing him right now.
You tell Abby I want her.
Oh, Gibbs, I never knew!
Ducky asked me to help him figure
out where the welts came from.
I think I'm gonna start with the ball peen hammer.
I don't know why. I just like the way it sounds...
...ball peen, ball peen,
ball peen, ball, peen, ball...
What else?
Um, probably go with the stun
gun, and then the Garden Weasel.
And someone is in a really bad mood.
Spending the night in a room full of
crying women tends to do that to me.
Well, this will cheer you up.
I got the analysis back from
the blood found on Turner's body.
It belongs to your
missing petty officer.
Blake? You're kidding.
I also ran the bloody
rag from Blake's house.
Most of it is his,
and some of it is not.
Sergeant Turner's?
Bingo.
Was his name-o. Blake and
Turner were in a fight.
And one turns up dead and
the other hits the road.
Or they were killed together
at the same location, Kate.
It's the hacker. He's sending
us another instant message.
"NCIS, if you want the truth,..."
"...be at Unity Quad,
ten-hundred hours today."
- He's somewhere on campus right now.
- Tony, Kate, you're with me.
And you get me an exact
location this time.
- You sure you can do it?
- Positive. I think.
Excuse me.
How can we be sure Creepy
Voice is even here, McGee?
Because, Tony, the campus WiFi
system is broken down into nodes,
...and our hacker's signal
is coming from Node Five
Yeah? What does that mean?
Hi.
It means he's somewhere in the quad right now. So
look for somebody with a laptop or a wireless device.
Not real helpful, Probie.
Less chatter.
Keep your eyes open. Find him... or her.
Boss, your 1:00.
Red hat, sunglasses,
looking real suspicious.
That's what I'm talking about.
Don't you get enough of that at home?
My Internet connection's down.
Yeah.
It's 10:45.
The hacker's playing with us again.
No, Kate, I'm telling you he's
here. Look for something abnormal.
You're gonna have to
be more specific, McGee.
Look out! Move!
Out of the way! Hey, watch it!
Move it!
I'd say that's abnormal.
We've got two suspects,
one in a black ski mask.
Moving to intercept.
They're coming out of the tunnel.
Okay.
Hey, get out of the way!
Move it! Get out of the way!
Clear the way! Get out of my way!
You're dead!
He's got a gun!
NCIS! Federal agents! Drop the weapon!
Put down your weapon!
- Drop the weapon!
- Hold your fire!
What's going on?
Shut up, dumbass.
That hurt?
Yeah.
That hurt, right there?
"Kyle Zolin". He's a midshipman.
Yeah. Gibbs.
Gibbs, Gibbs, I figured it out.
- I know what caused the welts on Turner's body.
- We know.
A paintball gun.
I really, really hate
it when he does that.
Whoops.
You retreads think you
deserve to be officers?!
Do you?!
Playing illegal games on campus?!
- You're lucky I don't rip your heads off and stomp on them!
- Agent Gibbs'll take it from here, Gunny.
Yes, sir.
I expect you gentlemen to
answer his questions truthfully.
Sit down.
Where's Finnegan Blake?
We don't know, sir.
How many midshipmen in this
little paintball club of yours?
Uh... yeah, that's right.
You turn them in, they'll probably
be kicked out of school just like you.
It's admirable;
...protecting your friends.
Turner... does not need protection.
He's lying dead on a
slab with a broken neck.
- I think Blake is the one who put him there.
- No.
No, not possible, sir.
- They were best friends.
- Yeah?
Then why were they beating the
crap out of each other Friday night?
You were there!
Yes, sir, but it's not what you think.
They tossed a couple
punches, we broke it up.
An hour later, they were drinking
beer and laughing about it.
Does that look like a couple
of punches to you, Midshipmen?
His neck is snapped in half.
He, uh... he didn't look
like that when he left.
What was the fight about?
Turner never lost a paintball game,
...so Blake decided to change
the rules. By killing him.
No, sir.
We play one on one, but Friday morning we
all got Turner's target photo in our e-mail.
And we ambushed him.
It was supposed to be funny.
I want the names of
everyone in your club.
You do that, and we can
talk about your futures.
And if we don't?
Son, you trust me.
You will not do well in prison.
They call themselves "The Red Cell."
They all claim the last time they saw Blake
was on Friday night, right after the fight.
We think they were protecting him.
Who else knew about the group?
According to them, no one.
Only the Red Cell members.
First rule of Fight Club: Never talk about
Fight Club. God, that's a great movie.
Brad Pitt, Edward Norton.
It's, like, the greatest guy movie...
...ever. I'm going to rent that for you.
They're either lying, or one of them
is the hacker that led us to the group.
Find them.
Boss?
Find my hacker yet?
Uh, no, but...?
Poor Probie.
- You think he needs a group hug?
- Oh.
I found Blake.
I've been monitoring the campus WiFi nodes, waiting for the
hacker to come back online, and that's when I thought of it.
When we searched Blake's room, he had the docking
station for an Axim X5 handheld computer,..
...but the unit itself
was not in his room.
And they're, like, 2,000 bucks. He probably took
it with him when he pulled his disappearing act.
Why does this matter?
Because it has wireless built in. It
automatically connects to the nearest network.
He's online right now.
Where?
Waverly University, Node Three. And according to the network
logs, he's been hiding out there since Saturday morning.
Not bad, McGee.
Let's roll.
See? I told you he likes you.
You sure about this, Tim?
I'm sure.
He's here, or at least his computer is.
Well, I hope for your
sake that you're right.
I'm right, okay?
Wait.
He's in the building
right behind this one.
Got some bad news for you, Probie.
I don't understand. He should be here.
- Maybe he disappeared with the building.
- I'm telling you, it's here.
The signal's getting stronger.
It's here!
Where?
It's right below me.
He must have buried it.
We're being screwed with again.
It's the hacker, McGee.
I found something!
It's a body.
It's laying face down. This
is where the head should be.
He's wearing a hood.
This is now a crime scene.
It's Blake.
He's not lying face down.
Petty Officer Blake was killed
early Saturday morning...
...just hours after
Sergeant Turner's death.
Now we're dealing with a killer who's not
only extremely powerful, but methodical.
Each of these young men
had their necks broken...
...in a violent and identical fashion.
I think by someone
using their bare hands.
Well, how's that?
Ah.
Well, it's a very specific technique.
- May I demonstrate, Mr. Palmer?
- Of course, Doctor.
Yes, well, one hand is
placed firmly on the jaw here.
- And the other hand...
- I'll do it, Duck.
Thank you, Jethro.
This ought to be good.
No, on you.
You think that's really necessary?
Yeah, it'll be fun. You
can either lie on the floor,
or I'll drop you on the floor.
We used this to silence enemy sentries.
One hand on the jaw, the other
behind the head of the individual.
66 pounds of torque and...!
Your eyes are in the back
of your head, DiNozzo.
Any questions?
No, I think I got it, boss.
You missed your calling, boss.
Could've been a chiropractor.
We're looking for someone
who knows how to kill.
Yes, but what troubles me is our
midshipmen, in order to receive such a...
...killing blow, would have to have
been face-to-face with their assailant.
Which means either
they were ambushed or...
They knew him.
Hey. Another midshipman?
They teach combat
courses at an NROTC unit.
Maybe. You found my hacker yet?
McGee's upstairs working on it.
I didn't ask McGee.
I asked my senior field agent.
I want that damn hacker.
Did you hear that, Palmer?
- Yeah, he sounded pretty upset.
- No,...
...he called me his senior
field agent. Finally!
This guy's good, Abby.
He's too good.
Yeah, but we... are better!
I thought you went to MIT.
Abby, I don't think
I can track this guy.
Don't let Gibbs hear you
talking like that, Probie.
Caff-Pow, baby.
You guys are just in time
for McGee's crisis of faith.
He's starting to realize that there may be
someone on the planet that's smarter than him.
Oh, I'm looking at one right now.
Well, Kate, in all fairness...
...I am the senior field agent, but I think it's an
experience thing... -I was talking about Abby, dodo head.
Thank you, Kate.
Okay, the only chance we have of finding this y is if he
contacts us again. I can embed a virus in the IM software.
- Use it to tag his computer and hope that it leads...
- Viruses, tracking software?
You guys are going
about this the wrong way.
What is the first rule
of Fight Club, Probie?
Okay, Tony, you can barely turn
your computer on. So, no offense...
You do not talk... about Fight Club!
And what is the second
rule of Fight Club?
Abbs?
Do not talk about Fight Club! Sir!
Exactly.
And Creepy Voice is the
guy who led us to Red Cell.
- So he's either a member or he knows a member.
- And they're all midshipmen.
Of course, if the guy's giving McGeek a run
for his money, he's got to be pretty smart.
McGee, what was your GPA in college?
3.9.
I failed a fencing
class in sophomore year.
So I'm sure you already checked the NROTC records,
to make sure there's no computer genius in the unit.
- I hate to say it, but that was actually smart, Tony.
- What was, Kate?
- Tony might have figured out how to find the hacker.
- It's his job.
You think I keep him
around for his personality?
There are 22 midshipmen in the unit with computer
science majors. Only one of them has a 4.0.
Look familiar?
You want to bring him in with me?
Considering he embarrassed me, almost got me
fired and ruined my weekend? What do you think?
"Hello, NCIS."
You might be smart,
but my geek carries a gun.
Hello, you twisted piece of...
Howdy, Urkel.
Ow! Man, you're hurting me! Ow!
You hear something, Tony?
No.
Me, neither.
No need to worry. Federal
agents. Have a nice day.
Hey.
So what do they call it?
The box? Coffin? Sweat shop?
We just call it interrogation.
What's the deal? You lean on me first, then
bring your partner in, get me blabbering?
Are you the good cop
or the bad cop? Sit.
Okay.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
This is a major waste of time.
You clearly didn't do this.
Reverse psychology.
But my boss, he needs to close the case.
Brass wants answers.
And there is this...
other agent-
Kate...
Severe-looking thing.
No sense of humor.
She built a profile on you.
What kind of interrogation
technique is that?
The DiNozzo method.
Not pretty,...
...but it's effective.
Turns out... you're the geeks' geek.
The last one to be picked for the team.
That's not true.
This isn't me, Urkel.
Okay? I think you're great.
Sure, you broke a few federal laws, interfering
with an ongoing murder investigation.
I was trying to help you.
Right.
It's the way you did
it that's suspicious.
Look at me, hmm?
The last thing I need is to
be pegged as a rat in the unit.
Those guys would have killed me.
Maybe you were looking for payback? They
wouldn't let you into their little club?
That's crazy.
You know what's crazy?
Me almost putting a bullet in a kid's
head 'cause he's playing paint ball.
That's a little crazy.
I didn't...
I didn't want anyone to get hurt.
I was... just trying to help.
Turner was a friend.
So you thought sending cryptic e-mails
was going to help us find his killer?
I think I know who killed him.
Who?
Petty Officer Blake.
Yeah, why'd he do it?
There's this girl in the
unit- Ashley Simmons.
She used to date Blake,
but they broke up.
She started dating Turner?
I'm not sure. I know he liked her.
He liked her?
Not a real strong
motive for murder, Urkel.
Last week I saw all three of them together in the quad. Ashley
was crying. Turner and Blake started arguing with each other.
About what?
I couldn't hear, but
I saw Blake push him.
So they fought?
No, Turner just left with Ashley.
When I asked him about it later, he said it was
personal, something between the three of them.
Well, that's a real interesting
theory, Matlock. One problem.
What?
Blake's dead.
He was murdered a few
hours after Turner.
B- By who?
Someone who wanted to frame him
for the murder of his best friend.
Find Midshipman Ashley Simmons. Now.
Why is your hair still purple, Simmons?
It takes a few days to wash out, Gunny.
I hope the time you've spent
field-daying is starting to sink in.
I own you until the day you graduate.
Yes, Gunny. It won't happen again.
You want to give people orders someday?
You need to learn how to follow them.
Sounds like pretty good advice, Gunny.
Good evening, sir.
Any luck finding Blake?
That's why we're here.
We can talk about this in my office.
- You missed a spot over there, Simmons.
- Actually, we're here for her, Gunny.
Simmons? For what?
- We found Blake.
- Where?
He's dead.
- We think she knows why.
- I don't, I don't know anything about it.
Then you won't mind
answering a few questions.
Take her out to the
sedan. I'll be right out.
But I don't know anything!
Tell me everything you
know about her, Gunny.
Simmons?
Kind of a screw-up,
...but not a bad kid.
You think she's involved in this?
I don't understand.
Blake didn't kill Turner?
Nope, they were both murdered.
Not pretty. Almost
twisted his head clean off.
Oh, my God,
he did it.
I'm getting too old for this crap.
ROTC was supposed to be an easy tour.
You want a cup?
Uh, no. No, thanks, I'll pass.
Mm. Good call.
So just how was Blake murdered?
I went to them for help last week.
He wouldn't leave me alone.
Wow,
two identical neck-breaks?
Yeah, we think the killer
has military training.
He was forcing me to sleep with him.
Blake and Turner were going to
go talk to him, make him stop.
And he killed them.
Who, Midshipman?
I'll have everyone in this
unit standing by tomorrow.
You can question them
all at the same time.
Thanks, Gunny. Appreciate it.
Just one thing.
What, sir?
I said that
...Blake had been found
dead. You said "murdered."
You gonna answer that?
No.
No, I'm pretty sure I know
what it is they want to tell me,
Put your hands up.
Not bad, Agent Gibbs.
I'd give up now. It's
only going to get worse.
I think he knows.
You think?
You should have stayed
out of this, old man.
Okay, stand back.
Cuff him.
Sure thing, boss.
Somehow I don't remember
college being quite like this.
Reminds me of this time at Ohio
State, we had this frat guy...
The next person who
mentions a spring break...
...or a frat party,
or college...
is fired,
are we clear?
- Yes.
That's good.