Anything?
You keep asking if there's anything.
Pardon me for appearing desperate,
but before the pilot was ripped
from the cockpit,
he did say that no one's gonna find us
unless we get that transceiver working.
So... is there anything?
- No.
- Okay.
What were you doing
in the bathroom?
Thought you could tell.
l was getting sick.
Puking. My one tangible
contribution to the trek.
No, l'm glad you came, Charlie.
- Every trek needs a coward.
- You're not a coward.
[tapping]
- Are you all right, sir?
- l'm good, thanks.
- Can l get you a water or...?
- l'm fine. Thank you.
Please?
All right.
[tapping continues]
- Excuse me.
- [woman] Guess he really had to go.
[flight attendant] Sir? Excuse me!
Sir, excuse me.
[woman] Excuse me.
[rumbling]
[bell rings]
Ladies and gentleman, the captain has
turned on the ''fasten seatbelts'' sign.
Please return to your seats
and fasten your seatbelts.
[man knocking] Sir?
Are you all right?
Just a minute.
[knocking]
l'm gonna have to ask
that you open the door.
[knocking]
[man] Open the door now, sir.
Sir?
- [crashing]
- [grunting]
[people yelling]
[grunting, gasping]
[people chattering]
Hey. We're going through
some clothes. Sorting them.
l see you found your bag.
- Come on, you wanna give us a hand?
- Not really.
You're wasting your time.
They're coming.
[Claire] ls that your boyfriend?
My brother. Boone.
God's friggin' gift to humanity.
[sighs]
l used to have a stomach.
- Do you know what it is?
- Not yet.
l haven't felt the baby move
since yesterday.
[Michael] Excuse me.
Hey, uh, have you, uh...?
Have you seen my boy?
[speaking Korean]
Sorry.
[Michael] Walt! Walt!
Vincent!
Come here, boy.
[Michael] Hey!
What did l tell you
after what's happened?
- l thought Vincent would be around.
- Stay on the beach.
l thought this would be okay.
Don't do that. You listen to me,
l mean what l say. You understand?
- What is this?
- l just found 'em.
Come here.
- Hey, guys, come on.
- [grunting]
Hey.
Hey! Break it up!
- Break it up! Get off!
- Hey, come on, break it...
- You son of a bitch.
- That's it. lt's over.
- Come on.
- That's it!
- l'm sick of this redneck!
- Want some more?
Tell everyone what you told me!
Tell them l made the plane crash.
- The shoe fits!
- [Jack] What is going on?
[speaking foreign language]
- What's going on?
- My kid found these in the jungle.
This guy was in the back row
of business class the whole flight.
Never got up.
Hands folded underneath the blanket.
And for some reason,
just pointing this out,
- the guy next to him didn't make it.
- Thank you for observing.
Don't think l saw them pull you
out of line before we boarded?
- Come on! Bring it!
- Stop!
We found the transceiver,
but it's not working.
Can anybody help?
Yes, l might be able to.
Oh, great! Perfect.
Let's trust this guy.
Hey, we're all in this together.
- Treat each other with respect...
- Shut up, lardo.
Hey!
Give it a break.
Whatever you say, doc,
you're the hero.
You guys found the cockpit?
Any survivors?
No.
[Sayid] Dual-band. Military spec.
Chances are the battery is good,
but the radio is dead.
- Can you fix it?
- l need some time.
Doctor, that man with the shrapnel,
l think you should take a look at him.
Chain-smoking jackass.
- Some people have problems.
- Some people have problems. Us. Him.
You're okay. l like you.
You're okay too.
Hurley. Oh, just...
Sayid.
- How do you know how to do that?
- l was a communications officer.
- Oh, yeah? You ever see battle?
- l fought in the Gulf War.
No way. l got a buddy
who fought over there.
He was in the 1 04th Airborne.
What were you, Air Force? Army?
The Republican Guard.
[woman speaking Korean]
ls it working?
lt seems to be, except
we're not picking up a signal.
Why? Aren't we
trying to send one?
Yes, but what you want
to see here is little bars.
The bars show
it's getting reception.
- We need the bars?
- We could broadcast blind,
hope that someone, maybe a ship
somewhere picks up our distress call.
But that would be a waste of the
battery, which might not last for long.
- There is one thing we could try.
- What?
- Get the signal from high ground.
- How high?
How is he?
Can you do anything?
- l can pull out the shrapnel.
- But you said if you took it out...
That was yesterday. l was hoping
he'd be at a hospital by now.
lf l leave him like this
he'll be dead within a day.
lf l open him up...
lf l can control the bleeding,
and if he doesn't go into sepsis,
and if l can find some antibiotics,
he might be all right.
l'm going on a hike.
- Sorry?
- Sayid fixed the transceiver,
- but we can't use it, not from here.
- Wait.
You said we had to send a signal.
- You saw what that thing did.
- Yeah, l did.
What makes you think we're any safer
here than we are in the jungle?
- Wait for me. l don't know how long...
- Sayid said the battery won't last.
All right.
lf you see or hear anything...
Anything...
Run.
[speaking Korean]
- What's up?
- [speaking Korean]
- What, that?
What, eat that?
[speaking Korean]
Dude, dude, l'm starving.
But l am nowhere near that hungry.
No. No. No, thank you.
No way. No.
[chuckling]
[Michael] The comic's in Spanish. You...
- ...read Spanish?
- No. l found it.
Tell you what, we get home...
...l'll get you another dog.
[Jack] Hey!
- l need your help.
- Okay.
Help me go through the luggage. l need
any prescription medications you find,
especially drugs that end in ''mycin''
and ''cillin.'' Those are antibiotics.
What's this for?
[sniffing]
What are you doing?
l think l was mean to him.
What?
[sobbing] He's that guy from the gate.
He wouldn't let us have our seats
in first class. He saved our lives.
Shannon, we're trying to clear
the wreckage. You should help out.
You're just being worthless over here.
- Being what?
- What do you want me to say?
- You're sitting staring at bodies.
- l've just been through a trauma.
We all have. The difference
is you've given yourself a pedicure.
You know what?
- lt is easy to make fun of me...
- l wish l didn't waste my time.
l wish l didn't have a reason!
lt is easy.
Screw you. You do not have
the slightest idea what l am thinking.
- No, you don't!
- Okay, Shannon, what are you thinking?
l'm going with them.
On the hike.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yup. l'm going.
- No you're not, Shannon. Shannon!
- l'd like to come with you.
- She's not going.
- The hell l'm not!
- This is what she does.
- You don't know!
Makes bad decisions
to upset her family, me.
Shut up and stop trying to be charming.
l'm coming with you.
- l don't know if that's a good idea.
- What are you, two years older than me?
- You're going, aren't you?
- Yeah. Are you?
- Yup.
- Yeah, l'm definitely going.
Look, everybody can come.
But we're leaving now.
You couldn't tell from that,
but she's really nice.
[Kate] You decided to join us.
l'm a complex guy, sweetheart.
[Michael] What are you looking for?
Some sort of blade.
How's your son?
Walt?
Yeah, l think he'll be all right.
- How old is he?
- Nine. Ten.
Ten.
Walt's more worried
about his dog than anything.
The dog was on the plane, so...
- Kids, you know.
- ls it a lab?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- l saw him yesterday. ln the jungle.
- What? Where?
Over there...
...a couple hundred yards in or so.
He looked good.
What is it, like checkers?
Not really.
lt's a better game than checkers.
Do you play checkers with your pop?
No.
l live in Australia with my mom.
You have no accent.
Yeah, l know, we move a lot.
She got sick.
She died a couple of weeks ago.
- You're having a bad month.
- l guess.
Backgammon is the
oldest game in the world.
Archaeologists found sets
when they excavated the ruins
of ancient Mesopotamia.
Five thousand years old.
That's older than Jesus Christ.
Did they have dice and stuff?
But theirs weren't made of plastic.
Their dice were made of bones.
Cool.
Two players. Two sides.
One is light. One is dark.
Walt...
...do you wanna know a secret?
[speaking Korean]
No, thank you.
No, that's fine. [giggles]
[speaking Korean]
No.
Okay. Thanks.
[speaking Korean]
- Mmm.
- [speaking Korean]
[gasping]
Oh, God.
l just felt it!
l just... Come here, feel this!
Feel this. Please.
Do you feel that?
That, right there.
That's a kick!
There, right there's a foot!
Oh, my God, wait,
he's moving around.
He. He.
l guess l think you're a he.
[Sawyer] Okay. Wide open space.
Check the radio, see if we're good.
- We're not gonna have reception.
- Just try it.
- l don't want to waste batteries.
- l'm not asking to keep it on.
- We're blocked by the mountain.
- Check the damn radio!
We might not have any juice left
when we get to...
[grunt]
[rustling]
Oh, my God.
- What the hell's that?
- Something's coming.
[snarling]
Coming towards us.
- Come on, let's move.
- l shouldn't have come on this hike!
[Shannon screaming]
- Go, go!
- Sawyer!
- Let him go!
- [Shannon continues screaming]
[gunshots]
[roaring]
[groaning]
[Shannon] That's...
That's a big bear.
You think that's what killed the pilot?
No. No, that's a tiny,
teeny version compared to that.
- [breathing heavily]
- Guys, this isn't just a bear.
lt's a polar bear.
You sure he's out?
He's out. [sighs]
How do you know he won't wake up
when you yank that thing out?
l don't.
Hey, guy, you awake?
Yo! There's a rescue plane!
We're saved! Yay!
Yeah, he's out.
So, what do you want me...?
lt's unlikely
he'll regain consciousness,
but the pain might bring him around.
lf it does, hold him down.
Uh... l'm not so good
around blood, man.
Then don't look.
Yeah. But...
l'm not so good around blood.
Just do the best you can, okay?
- Don't look.
- [breathing nervously] Okay.
[mumbling]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[both straining]
Dude.
- Hand me those strips.
- Dude.
- l need to get this bleeding stopped.
- l don't think l can.
- What? What's going on?
- Just hand me the strips.
Give it to me.
Don't even think about it.
Don't even think it. Hurley, hey!
Damn it.
- That can't be a polar bear.
- lt's a polar bear.
[Shannon] Wait a minute.
- Polar bears don't live in the jungle.
- Spot-on.
- Polar bears don't live this far south.
- This one does.
Did. lt did.
Where did that come from?
Probably Bear Village.
How the hell do l know?
Not the bear, the gun.
- l got it off one of the bodies.
- One of the bodies?
- One of the bodies.
- People don't carry guns on planes.
They do if they're a U.S. marshal.
There was one on the plane.
How do you know that?
l saw a guy lying there with
an ankle holster, so l took the gun,
thought it might come in handy.
Guess what, l just shot a bear.
- So why do you think he's a marshal?
- Because he had a clip-on badge!
- l took that too. Thought it was cool.
- [Sayid] l know who you are.
- You're the prisoner.
- l'm the what?
You found a gun on a U.S. marshal?
You knew where it was because he
was bringing you back to the States.
The handcuffs were on you.
That's how you knew.
- Piss off!
- That's who you are.
Be as suspicious of me
as l am of you.
- You are the prisoner.
- Fine, l'm the criminal.
You're the terrorist.
We'll all play a part!
Who do you wanna be?
- Does anybody know how to use a gun?
- l think you just pull the trigger.
- Don't use the gun.
- l want to take it apart.
There's a button on the grip.
Push that, it will eject the magazine.
There's still a round in the chamber.
Hold the grip,
pull the top part of the gun.
- l know your type.
- l'm not so sure.
Yeah, l've been with girls like you.
Not girls exactly like me.
[woman] Can l get you a refill?
- l'm fine with this, thank you.
- [bell dings]
You, sir, can l get you anything?
Cocktail, soda?
Just coffee, sweetheart. Black.
Coffee, sure.
You look worried.
l'd be worried too, l was you.
But you gotta stay positive, kiddo.
There's always that off-chance
that they'll believe your story.
l know l sure do.
- l don't care what you believe.
- Oh, l know that's true.
That has always been true.
You sure you don't
want some more juice?
Yeah, l'm sure.
[bell rings]
[rumbling]
[woman on PA] Ladies and gentleman,
the captain has switched on
the ''fasten seatbelts'' sign.
Please return to your seats
and fasten your seatbelts.
l have one favor to ask.
Really? This oughta be good.
- [rumbling]
- [pounding]
- [grunts]
- [gasping]
[alarm beeping]
[gasps]
[creaking]
[squealing]
- [crashing]
- [shrieking]
[Sayid] We should keep moving.
[gasping]
No.
[groaning]
Where is she?
Who?
Oh, now's a good time to check
the radio. Not before, but now.
- We're up higher.
- Yes, we are.
[static]
[whirring]
Bar.
Hey, we've got a bar!
- Mayday, Mayday!
- [feedback]
- What is that?
- Feedback.
- From what? What would do that?
- l don't know.
l'll tell you what. This guy not fixing
the radio. The thing doesn't even work.
No. No, no, no, no, it's not broken.
We can't transmit because
something else is already transmitting.
- From where?
- What?
[Sayid] Close, the signal's strong.
Somewhere close?
On the island? That's great!
- Maybe it's other survivors.
- From our plane? How...?
- What kind of transmission?
- Satphone, radio signal.
- Can we listen?
- Let me get the frequency. Hold on.
- There's no transmission.
- Shut up!
- The rescue party, it has to be.
- [woman on radio speaking French]
French. The French are coming! l've
never been so happy to hear the French.
l never took French.
What is she saying?
- Does anyone speak French?
- She does.
No, l don't. What?
What? You spent a year in Paris!
Drinking! Not studying!
[man on radio] Iteration 7-2-9-4-5-3-1.
- Okay, what's that?
- Oh, no, no, no.
- [Shannon] What?
- Batteries are dying.
- How much time do we have?
- Not much.
- l've heard you speak French. Listen.
- l can't!
Do you speak French,
because that would be nice.
- [man] Iteration 1-7-2...
- That voice is weird. What is that?
Come on, come on.
- [woman speaking French]
- lt's... lt's repeating.
- She's right.
- What?
lt's a loop. ''lteration.''
lt's repeating the same message.
- lt's a counter.
- [man] Iteration...
- The next number will end 5-3-3.
- [man] ...9-4-5-3-3.
Does anyone know
what he's talking about?
lt's a running count of the number
of times the message has repeated.
lt's roughly 30 seconds long, so...
How long...?
- Don't forget to carry the one.
- [man] ...5-3-4.
- She's saying... ''Please.''
- [woman speaking French]
She's saying, ''Please, help me.
Please, come get me.''
Or she's not!
You don't even speak French!
- [Kate] Let her!
- [Boone] Shut up!
Guys, the battery.
The battery.
[man] ...7-2-9-4-5-3-5.
- [woman speaking French]
- ''l'm alone now.
l'm... on the island alone.
- [continues speaking French]
- Please, someone come.
The others, they're...
They're dead.
lt killed them.
lt killed them all.''
[static, whirring]
- That was good.
- [Sayid] Sixteen years.
[Boone] What?
Sixteen years... and five months.
That's the count.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- The iterations.
lt's a distress call.
A plea for help. A Mayday.
lf the counter's right...
...it's been playing over and over...
...for 1 6 years.
Someone else was stranded here?
Maybe they came for them.
lf someone came,
why is it still playing?
Guys...
...where are we?