[narrator] Previously on Lost:
Right now, this is our priority.
Oh!
How did you come to be
on this island, Danielle?
The ship slammed into rocks,
ran aground.
[speaking Korean]
Hold on a second, dude.
You want what now?
- You wanna make snowballs?
- Hold the bamboo tighter.
l think.
- [Jack] Hey.
- [Michael] Hey.
- How's it coming?
- lt's coming.
Long as nobody sabotages
this one as well, huh?
l got people standing guard 24l7.
Nobody gets near this,
with or without intent to burn.
l was thinking, uh,
the chances of a passing ship
spotting this raft out there
is pretty slim.
We could use something
to send a distress call
to any ship that might be close.
Like an SOS.
OK. l'll ask Sayid, but even if he
could make something like that,
he's not gonna have anything
to power it with.
Didn't Sayid say that crazy
French chick had batteries?
- Absolutely not.
- l'm not asking you to go.
- l'll do it.
- No, you won't.
- We're trying...
- Do you think she would
give up something she needs
to a stranger?
All l'm asking is for you
to tell me how to find her. That's it.
l was brought unconscious
to her camp.
l was disoriented.
l don't know how to find her.
Don't know, dude?
Or don't want to?
[Jack] Sayid, look. You've got
her maps and her papers.
You thought they were
pointing to something.
- l was wrong.
- Maybe they're pointing to her.
Look! l don't know what
these papers mean!
They could be the ravings
of her disturbed mind.
Song lyrics, mixed with equations!
lf this map is pointing to her,
then you should know
she resides here in this area.
She gave it a name.
''Territoire Fonce. ''
Shannon translated it.
lt means ''Dark Territory.'' That sound
like a place you'd like to visit?
- So you won't help?
- l didn't say that.
l'll build the distress beacon.
l suggest you find another power source.
- Something in the cockpit.
- [Jack] We're not going to the cockpit.
~ Swing your partner, dosey do
- Step high!
- [woman] What are you doing in there?
- ...when you cut the....
- l'm just checking something out.
l hope you're not watching those
G-string mujeres again.
Look, Ma, we talked about this.
lf you want me living here,
you gotta respect my privacy.
And no, l'm not.
Look at you.
lt's Saturday night.
A grown-up man
sitting at home watching TV.
You should go out.
Try to find yourself a nice woman.
l'll get right on that.
Try eating better.
You're gaining weight again.
...with the Mega Number 42.
And that makes tonight's
Mega Lotto Jackpot Drawing
four, eight, 1 5, 16 and 23,
with the Mega Number 42.
Whoever has
those numbers has won
or will share
in a near record jackpot.
[man] That's right, Mary Jo,
because this is the
sixteenth week without a winner.
[crashing]
Hi.
You awake?
l was just wondering that myself.
That French lady wrote this stuff?
lt's the middle of the night.
What do you want?
Nothing. Couldn't sleep.
And l got curious.
You and Shannon,
you guys have been trying
to figure out some of this stuff,
and l was wondering what...
...you guys figured out
about this stuff?
- What stuff?
- l don't know.
Well, take these numbers
she wrote down a bunch of times.
Got any idea what it means?
l thought at one time they might be
coordinates of some kind.
Coordinates, yeah.
But when you first found her,
the French chick,
you said you saw a wire
or something on the beach.
You followed it,
and it led you to her.
No. lt led me into a trap she set.
But her place is
probably close, right?
- Why are you interested in Rousseau?
- l'm not.
Just making conversation, dude.
Sorry if it's a bad time.
Good night.
- [camera shutters clicking]
- [chattering]
Yeah, you.
How did you come up
with the winning numbers?
Oh, uh, they just,
uh, sorta came to me.
- Why don't you introduce your family?
- Oh, yeah, okay. Um...
This bashful beauty is my mom, Carmen.
Come here, Ma.
And this is my brother, Diego,
and his wife, Lisa.
- Whoo! We're rich!
- Nice, dude.
lgnore him. He's an idiot. And, uh...
Oh! You gotta meet this guy.
This is the greatest guy l know.
My grandpa, Tito.
He's worked three jobs for...
- How long's it been, Abuelito?
- 52 years.
Fifty-two years!
He's 70 years old, and the closest thing
that he's had to a vacation
is when they put a pacemaker
in him four years ago.
The first thing l'll do with the money
is to give him the rest he's earned.
That's what it's all about for me,
to be able to do things
for the people l care about.
'Cause l really put my family
through a lot recently,
and, um, well, this way
l can make it up to them.
You know, maybe even
buy my mom a new house.
And, uh...
Maybe after, uh, my grandpa
comes back from his cruise,
we can get to do some of the things
that we always wanted to do.
Grandpa?
- Hey.
- l'm not doing anything.
What?
- What?
- Just saying good morning.
Oh. Right.
Morning.
- Sorry.
- You going somewhere?
Me? No.
Well, yeah...
...just thought
l might take a walk.
Uh, maybe scope out
some, uh, new fishing area.
- l'll come with.
- That's okay.
l could use a bit of the wide open.
Dude, l could really use
some alone time right now.
Sure.
l'm a big guy.
l get dehydrated easy.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Claire, you got a second?
- Uh, sure.
- l was wondering if you're free
to help me with a little project.
- Me?
- Yeah.
l'm building something and l could
use an extra pair of hands.
l'm nine months pregnant.
l can barely waddle to the beach.
Could you hold a saw?
- Um, yeah.
- Can you move your hand back and forth?
- Possibly.
- You're perfect.
Come on.
Okay.
So, what exactly are we building?
Where is it?
- Where's what?
- The map. lt won't help you find her.
- l don't have it.
- What's worse
is you won't do your own dirty work.
You get Hurley to do it.
Wait a minute. Hurley?
He was in my tent last night.
Quizzing me about Rousseau.
About numbers she wrote,
how l came to find her.
You don't know anything
about this, do you?
- Charlie, have you seen Hurley?
- Um...
Couple of hours ago.
He was setting out for a walk.
Acting like a loon, l might add.
My God. He's going after her.
- When are you gonna be back?
- lf we catch him, before nightfall.
Why?
Are you worried about me?
So what if l am?
[Jack] Sayid!
You ready?
l'll be fine.
[rap music plays]
Hugo, turn that noise down.
- Oh, sorry.
- [turns volume down]
[mother sighs]
Where are you taking me?
You know l don't like surprises.
You're gonna like this one, Ma.
l mean, after everything
you've been through...
...like Grandpa...
[speaking Spanish]
Then at the funeral, Father Aguilar
getting struck by lightning.
Man, that was a freak storm.
And Diego moving back home
- after Lisa left him for that waitress.
- Don't mention that whore.
l'm just saying, you deserve
something good to happen.
You know,
ever since l won
the lottery, it's like...
...we've had nothing but bad luck.
Like, l don't know,
the money's cursed or something.
Ow!
That's blasphemy.
You know we are Catholic.
- We don't believe in curses.
- Jeez, Ma, l'm just talking.
Okay, we're almost there.
Here, put this on.
- Why do l have to wear this?
- Give me your hand. Careful.
- You be careful.
- Stepping down.
l can't see anything.
Okay, now,
take off your blindfold,
and get a look at
your new dream house.
My ankle. Ahhh!
l said take off your blindfold.
Why did you make me
put that thing on?
Hugo, do l smell smoke?
Aw, crap!
Hang on. l gotta call 91 1 .
You tell them l broke my ankle.
[sirens blaring]
Drop the phone.
Move away from the vehicle.
- No, no! lt's the house.
- Do it! Now!
Turn around.
[Hurley] No such thing as curses, Ma?
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you.
Yo! French chick!
[man] l would think you'd be happy.
Every one of your stocks is up.
Your interests in orange futures
skyrocketed
after those tropical storms hit Florida.
And you are now the
majority shareholder
for a box company in Tustin.
- A box company?
- Mm-hmm. They make boxes.
Lucrative business.
Everybody needs boxes.
Which reminds me,
your sneaker factory in Canada...
- l own a sneaker factory in Canada?
- Well, not anymore.
- lt was destroyed in a fire last month.
- Of course it was.
You might have read about it.
Eight-something people died.
But the good news is,
we over-insured it.
lt's gonna yield you a windfall.
And when we add in the generous
settlement from the LAPD
for your false arrest,
you've almost doubled your net worth
in a few short months.
l still can't imagine how the police
mistook you for a drug dealer.
- Bad luck.
- Hugo.
You are not the first
lottery winner to believe
the money's brought nothing
but trouble. lt's in your head.
You don't believe in jinxes?
You know, curses?
l'm an accountant.
l believe in numbers.
- Where'd you get 'em, anyway?
- What?
The numbers. What did you use?
Somebody's birthday?
- Phone number?
- lt's nothing. lt's just something...
What?
That's it.
lt's not the money,
it's the numbers.
The numbers are cursed.
Dude, don't look at me like that.
l'm not crazy.
- This is really...
- Listen to yourself.
''The numbers are cursed.''
You know there is no such thing as...
[man screams]
You wanna hit that a little harder?
l'm sorry. ls my building a raft
to get us rescued bothering you?
- At the moment, yeah.
- Why aren't you helping?
l am helping, short-round.
Keeping watch for arsonists.
Walt's got a point.
You could pitch in,
as you've already bought your ticket.
[speaking Korean]
Did you tie this like l told you?
lf you'd tied it like l told you,
the thing would still be together.
What's the matter with you?
What is your problem?
He's never going to
speak to me again.
He just needs time.
l humiliated him.
When the raft sails,
do you think he's going
to leave with them?
l don't know.
[flies buzzing]
[clicking]
Don't move!
- Hey, what are you guys...?
- Do not move.
You're on a pressure trigger.
lf you take your weight off it,
it will release that.
Oh, man.
We need to replace
his weight on the trigger.
- How we gonna do that?
- Don't move.
Hey, everybody just calm down.
- Can l drop the wire?
- Maybe l'll find a rock.
- l'm dropping the wire.
- No!
- l can make it.
- Hurley, don't move.
l can get out of the way.
l'm spry.
- Stay put.
- No, wait!
[Jack] Hurley, don't even...
Hurley, what the bloody hell's
wrong with you?
Nothing.
What are you doing out here?
l came to get a battery.
Seriously, what's going on?
Nada.
You guys coming?
You all want to go? Fine.
But perhaps l should take the lead.
Excellent notion.
Lenny. His name is Lenny.
- Or Leonard.
- But you don't know his last name.
Look, l just need to talk to him
for five minutes.
lf you can't tell me
the person's name,
- l can't look it up.
- How many Leonards are here?
Can't you just type in ''Leonard''?
The guy's been here forever.
He knows me.
Our records are private,
And any visitors...
Dude, do not
do that right now!
Leave the bulb
for another time, man.
Five minutes.
All l need is five minutes.
Hugo?
- Oh, hey, doc.
- lt's good to see you!
What are you doing back here?
Uh...
[doctor] l don't remember you
and Leonard being that close, Hugo.
[Hurley] Yeah. Well, we hung.
[doctor] l'll leave you gentlemen to it.
- Good luck, Hugo.
- [Leonard grunting]
Hey, Lenny.
Remember me?
Hugo.
Hurley.
Well, l was...
...just, you know,
in the neighborhood and, um...
[grunting]
Look, Lenny, l gotta know,
what do the numbers mean?
[repeating]
4-8-1 5-1 6-23-42.
Come on, Lenny,
give me something.
Anything.
Where'd you get the numbers?
ls that why you're here?
lt's 'cause of the numbers?
Did they do something to you?
'Cause l think
they did something to me.
l think they turned me into a jinx.
Bad news to everyone around me.
And when l tell people
l think l'm the cause,
they look at me like l'm nuts.
They don't believe me.
But, l know.
Ever since l won the lottery
with those numbers...
You used those numbers
to play the lottery?
Uh...
- Yeah.
- You shouldn't have done that.
- You've opened the box.
- l what?
- You shouldn't have used those!
- Why?
lt doesn't stop!
You gotta get away from those numbers.
- You gotta get far away.
- [man] All right. Slow down.
Don't you understand?
You gotta get away from them
or it won't stop.
- [man] Calm down.
- Wait. l need answers.
- Step away.
- The numbers!
- Where'd you get 'em?
- Sam Toomey. He heard them.
He heard them in Kalgoorlie.
- What's Kalgoorlie?
- lt's a town.
- A town where?
- ln Australia.
Oh, God.
lt stops here.
lt goes into the ground.
This poses somewhat of a problem.
[Charlie] Guys,
you should come see this.
Whoa.
- You never mentioned a bridge.
- l never saw this before.
- [Jack] No way she built this.
- [Sayid] No, but her team could have.
[Charlie] Or Ethan's team.
- What are you doing?
- Relax, l'm just gonna check it out.
- You guys stay here.
- Get back here!
Dudes, chill.
[creaking]
[gasping]
- Charlie...
- Hey!
Hey! lf he can do it...
[creaking]
- [snaps]
- Charlie!
Charlie!
Dude, you okay?
l'm okay. Whoo!
You two stay right there.
We'll find a way around,
and we'll meet you there.
Nah! Screw that!
You guys stay!
There's a path right here.
Will you shut up and listen to Jack.
He said stay put.
You're acting like a bloody lunatic.
[knocking]
lf this weren't the middle of nowhere,
l'd say you were lost.
- Hi. ls this Sam Toomey's house?
- lt is. l'm his wife.
Well, is he around?
'Cause l'd kinda like to talk to him.
l'd like that too,
but Sam's been dead for four years.
Your husband worked
with a guy l know, Leonard Simms.
That's right.
They served together in the U.S. Navy.
How is Leonard?
Still in the service?
Uh, he's, um... retired.
Anyway, he told me about Sam...
...hearing something.
- You're talking about the numbers.
- Yes.
The numbers. Exactly.
Do you know anything about them?
Sam and Leonard were stationed
at a listening post
monitoring long-wave transmissions
out of the Pacific.
Boring job. Sam hated it.
Nothing to do but listen to static,
night after night.
Until one night,
about 1 6 years ago,
there's something in the static.
A voice comes through,
a voice repeating those numbers
over and over again.
Couple of days later,
we're at the fair in Kalgoorlie,
and some wally there's got this jar,
must have been big as a pony.
lt's filled to the rim with beans.
Fella's offering 50 grand to anyone
able to guess how many beans
were in that jar within ten.
- Sam used the numbers.
- Yep.
The answer was exact to the bean.
Man had been running
the same scam for 40 years,
nobody had ever come close.
So we won the money.
On the way home, a pickup truck
blows a tire on the highway,
hits us head-on.
Lost my leg that night.
- What about Sam?
- Barely a scratch.
Most people would consider
themselves lucky,
but not him.
He was never the same after that.
He started keeping a record.
Anything terrible that happened
to anyone around us,
he believed it was all
because he used those numbers.
He moved us out here in the middle
of nowhere, hoping it would stop.
Did it?
Did he ever find a way
to make it stop?
Yep.
He put a shotgun in his mouth
and pulled the trigger.
What is it you're
looking for, Mr. Reyes?
l used them.
The numbers.
To win the lottery.
And now l think
l'm under the same curse.
Curse? There's no curse.
- You just told me...
- You think l'd still have my leg
if Sam hadn't have picked
the right number of beans?
Floods wouldn't have happened?
Homes wouldn't have burned?
People wouldn't have died?
Well... yeah.
You make your own luck,
Mr. Reyes.
Don't blame it
on the damn numbers.
You're looking for an excuse
that doesn't exist.
lt's a trap, right?
For catching animals?
Pass me that cup, please.
- Ugh! What's this gunk?
- Glue.
Where'd you find glue?
l made it out of
rendered animal fat.
You made glue?
Wow.
You should have one of those shows
where you fix up houses for people.
[chuckles] l don't think so.
Thanks for this.
Giving me something to do.
l'm tired of trying to remember
what happened to me out there.
How's that coming...
...your memory?
Bits and pieces.
Here and there.
Nothing that makes any real sense.
Well, maybe l can help.
l'm good at putting
bits and pieces together.
What?
This is familiar. This area.
We're close.
How do you know?
l thought she lived underground.
- [click]
- Jack!
What the hell was that?
Hell of a security system.
Somebody trips a wire,
and the whole place blows up.
- There's nothing here.
- The batteries?
Nothing.
l don't get it.
She knew.
She knew that one day
l'd come back and bring others.
So she abandoned this place,
booby-trapped it
and moved on.
Moved on where?
[Hurley] Jack! Sayid!
[Charlie] Do we know
where we're going?
[Hurley] The blast sounded
like it came this way.
- l think.
- You don't know.
Dude, what do you want from me?
What do l want? To know what
we're doing in the middle of nowhere.
And don't tell me
it's because of some batteries.
One minute you're
''good-time Hurley.''
The next you're Colonel Kurtz.
lt just doesn't make any sense.
lt's not you.
Dude, you don't know me.
All this time, you've told me
nothing about yourself.
- We all got personal stuff.
- Don't change the subject.
We're lost out here.
Jack and Sayid could be hurt,
all because you're acting
like some bloody nutter.
l am not crazy!
- l've got my reasons for every...
- l think l have a right to know.
Okay.
- All right, you wanna know?
- Yeah.
About a year ago...
[gunshot ricochets]
ls someone shooting at us?
Oh!
- You must be the French chick.
- Who are you?
Hurley. l, uh...
Sayid, that guy you tortured...
You were on the plane.
Look, l came here to find... Easy.
l'm just getting your notes.
Please, tell me
why you wrote this.
What do these numbers mean?
Please.
l don't know.
What?
You don't know?
Okay, that thing in the woods...
...maybe it's a monster,
maybe it's a pissed-off giraffe.
l don't know.
The fact that no one
is even looking for us,
yeah, that's weird.
But l just go along with it.
'Cause l'm along for the ride.
Good old fun-time Hurley!
Well, guess what?
Now l want some freaking answers!
Our ship picked up a transmission,
a voice, repeating those numbers.
We changed course to investigate.
After we shipwrecked,
my team continued to search
for the transmission source.
lt was weeks before
we found the radio tower.
There's a radio tower on this island?
Yes, up by the black rock.
Some of us continued to search
for the meaning of those numbers
while we waited for rescue.
But then the sickness came.
When my team was gone,
l went back, up to the tower
and changed the transmission.
- That distress signal we heard.
- Yes.
But the numbers...
Did you ever find out
anything about them?
Do you know where
they got their power?
Power?
They bring bad stuff
to everyone around you.
They're cursed,
you know that, right?
The numbers are cursed.
The numbers are
what brought me here.
As it appears,
they've brought you.
Since that time,
l've lost everything,
everyone l cared about.
So, yes...
...l suppose you're right.
They are cursed.
[whispering] Thank you.
Thank you.
You have no idea
how long l've been waiting
for somebody
to agree with me.
Thank you!
Oh, God, thank you.
We need to find
Hurley and Charlie,
get out of this jungle.
l hate that we're
going home empty-handed.
Hey!
Someone shot at us!
Hurley and me.
- We were looking for you when...
- Rousseau.
- Where's Hurley?
- l don't know.
He was right behind me,
then he just...
He just wasn't.
- l'll go and find him.
- No.
- We'll all go.
- Go where?
What the hell happened to you?
Need a battery?
She says ''Hey.''
- [Locke] You think of a name yet?
- [Claire] Huh?
For the baby.
Haven't really thought about it.
l was gonna give it away.
You know, for adoption.
- Must've been a difficult decision.
- Yeah.
Well, doesn't matter now.
lt's my birthday today.
Why haven't you told anyone?
l'm pregnant, single
and on an island
in the middle of nowhere.
Doesn't really matter
that it's my birthday, does it?
l guess not.
Your birthdays will be close,
you and your baby.
- That's good luck.
- Yeah? You think?
Yeah, l do.
You believe in that? Luck?
l believe in a lot of things.
That should do it.
Okay. l give up.
What is it?
lt's a cradle.
Happy birthday, Claire.
Thank you.
l know food's scarce,
but your shirt?
When you find a laundromat,
let me know.
Back in the jungle,
before we became target practice,
you were gonna tell me
what inspired this little quest.
l think the plane crash
might have been my fault.
- Don't be daft. How could you...?
- Before we came here,
a lot of bad stuff used to happen
whenever l was around.
- What do you mean, like bad luck?
- Yeah, that's...
...that'd be kind of
a mellow way of describing it.
Hurley, bad things happen.
Planes crash. People die.
You ought to let me finish.
You think you're
the only person with baggage?
You know what l was doing
when the plane went down?
l was snorting heroin. ln the toilet.
l was such a junkie,
l couldn't even take a plane ride
without having a fix.
l suppose that was
your fault as well?
So how about it?
What?
l just told you
the biggest secret in my life.
Thought you'd wanna reciprocate.
Okay.
Back home,
l'm worth 1 56 million dollars.
Fine. Don't tell me.
- Dude.
- l bare my soul,
and all l get is bloody jokes.