The trick to onions...
cut them in half lengthwise,
but leave the roots on.
Then make your vertical slices.
Need a dozen.
Think you can handle this?
A dozen is 12, right?
Next, we add mustard greens...
spicy, and they pack a nice punch.
Plus, they're really good for you.
Improve mental function,
protect against
rheumatoid arthritis.
Even inhibit
certain types of cancer.
Are you going to chop those onions
or give them a thai massage?
Well, i guess a happy ending
is out of the question.
I don't recall adding
making snide remarks
to your list of duties.
Just taking initiative.
Secret ingredient:
porcini mushrooms.
You want to reconstitute
them in a bowl of water.
You also want to hire an assistant
who can stay focused for
longer than 30 seconds.
- Why don't I hear you chopping?
- Just give me a second.
- You're kidding me, right?
- So sorry.
Are you OK?
You want to sit down?
My lips are blue. Cyanosis.
Pain in my back and chest.
Spontaneous pneumothorax.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm a doctor.
- You are?
- And I need a doctor.
House - Season 05 Episode 14
"The Greater Good"
Synchro: ShalimarFox, mpm, IceFreak
www.house-fr.com
You drool.
Shut up.
I know gas is expensive,
but i could've given you a ride.
- Elevator's broken.
- It was fine
when I came up from admitting.
Dana miller, the cancer researcher.
- Spontaneous pneumothorax.
- Awfully thin file.
- She just got admitted.
- Lots of things can cause pneumothorax.
Why don't we let eight or ten
other doctors rule out the boring stuff?
We wanna take this case.
She's maybe 5 or 10 years away
from curing retinoblastoma.
Which would make this
case attractive to anyone
who has some vested interest
in people curing the incurable.
She hasn't suffered from COPD.
She doesn't smoke.
She hasn't been scuba diving.
O2 sats are low even
after chest tube insertion.
Pneumothorax could be
secondary to a bunch of things.
Cystic fibrosis, lung cancer.
Or, to be slightly more optimistic,
late-onset asthma triggered
by an unknown allergen.
- We have a case?
- Did you just get to work?
Am I in trouble?
- Did you take the elevators up?
- Yes.
So, steroids for asthma?
Yeah.
Do a CT looking for
hyperinflation to confirm.
I thought my hospital was high-tech.
I'd have to wait all day for a CT.
- Dr. House gets a few perks.
- He has his own scanner?
No, just very loose interpretations
of hospital procedure.
- I appreciate the extra effort, but...
- Our gift to society.
We want to get you back to
work as soon as possible.
Well, i'm not working.
At least not as a doctor.
I quit.
I left eight months ago.
You mean, like, a sabbatical?
I had a uterine myoma. Benign.
But it ruptured
and I needed emergency surgery.
I was lying there
on the table thinking,
"I can't die now.
I haven't been happy yet."
Couldn't you just buy an overpriced
german sports car, or have an affair?
My sports car is doing
what I want when I want.
Now I'm learning how to run a kitchen
from one of the best chefs in New York.
You're washing pots
and smashing garlic?
Smashing garlic makes me happy.
Before that it was eight years
studying, 12 years in that lab.
It was always what I was supposed to do,
and never what I wanted to do.
Come here. Look at this.
Come here.
Adorable. Elevators keep crashing.
- Is mercury in retrograde or what?
- Elevators can be capricious.
Sometimes it just seems
like they're out to get you.
She keeps playing with the blanket.
Why would she do that?
Why do you think the elevators
would be out to get me?
I don't know.
Maybe they wanted to take time off
to spend with their little dumbwaiter.
But they the had to leave it
at home with an elevator sitter
because you drove the
replacement elevator to quitting
because you're incapable of
listening to anybody but me.
That's just a theory.
You're wrong.
I don't even listen to you.
Either do your job or go home.
Leave me out of it.
I am gonna do my job.
It doesn't mean I have to do it happily.
Doesn't mean I have to
do it without resentment.
It definitely doesn't mean
I have to do it without seeking
vengeance on the person
making me be here.
Congratulations.
You've officially dragged
me down to your level.
Okay.
Hey, blue.
It's not asthma.
Lung volume is normal.
She did have a uterine myoma
removed eight months ago.
Central line IV could have made a hole
near the lung that slowly expanded.
No pleural thickening.
- I can't believe she quit.
- People have the right to be happy.
I saw a four-year-old
with retinoblastoma
on my oncology rotation.
The cancer had eaten through
her eye and into her brain.
Horrible diseases exist.
It doesn't mean people
should give up
recreational anything.
Why not? Big picture...
I don't care if Jonas Salk's life
is a miserable shell.
I just want him to cure polio.
You can't live your life
"big picture."
You've gotta look out for yourself
and people you care about.
Why are you a doctor?
Why aren't you sitting by a pool in fiji
knocking back mai tais?
People act in their
own self-interests.
You're all here because
you're happy to be here.
- At least `cause it's your best option.
- I'm here `cause I want to help people.
No, you're here because
it makes you feel good to help people.
Taub and Foreman are here because
they've got no other viable choices.
And Thirteen is desperate to make
her life matter before it's over.
- So... you're happy to be here?
- Does it show?
Are those... increased
interstitial markings?
- Could be pulmonary fibrosis.
- Do a biopsy.
"You've got to look out for
the people you care about."
That wouldn't have anything to do
with you screwing your clinical trial
by slipping Thirteen
the real drug, would it?
You said that would be stupid.
Does she know?
Because Jonas Salk
would not approve.
There's nothing to know.
Got it?
- Good?
- Yep.
- You okay?
- Just a headache.
- I took some ibuprofen, but...
- Where's the pain: front or back?
Front.
Why are there never any interesting
pictures on these cards?
- They should make a dirty version.
- Sharp pain, or more of a throbbing...
Relax, it's not a side effect.
People get headaches.
True, but I can get you an MRI.
If I'm on the drug, it's been weeks.
It's not like something's
going to suddenly crop up now.
First card.
Train, duck...
You can't remember?
Piano.
We need a biopsy to confirm...
You need an open-lung biopsy
to confirm pulmonary fibrosis.
That's invasive surgery.
I'd be out of commission for weeks.
No offense, but you're not working.
What does it matter
if you spend time in bed?
Doesn't mean
I don't have places to go.
I've got my book group, piano
lessons, cooking classes.
They make me happy.
A warm apple fritter makes me happy.
It doesn't fulfill me as a person.
- And working here does?
- If it didn't, I'd have found a way
- to go back to tucking tummies.
- Well, good for you.
If your job fulfills you and
makes you happy, that's rare.
I didn't say I was happy.
I loved being a plastic surgeon.
The money, the lifestyle.
And in a lot of ways
this job stinks.
I'm making five bucks, I'm
always annoyed...
- But...
- You can look yourself in the mirror
and think
"I did something worth while today."
Exactly.
That's important.
And i do miss that.
But...
it just wasn't enough anymore.
That doesn't feel right.
Sit up.
Oh, that's weird.
What is it? Ascites?
Your belly's full of blood.
First her lung deflates,
like me after a cold shower.
Now her liver starts to
bleed, like me after...
You okay?
Great.
Just practicing my
clown college audition.
Someone set a trip wire.
- We were with the patient whole time.
- We were in the grc.
Lung, liver, go.
Shouldn't you be obsessing
over who did this to you?
Nope... anybody bother
mriing our patient's liver for tumors?
No tumors, no
cysts, no clear etiology.
If you're not obsessing,
you must have already
figured it out.
Yes.
So I'm obsessing about
why you're not obsessing
about why our patient's
liver suddenly sprang a leak.
There's a tiny spot on the caudate lobe.
Could be a granuloma.
Erodes into the hepatic artery,
causes the bleed.
- What caused the granuloma?
- Blastomycosis.
Could have been
asymptomatic for months.
It hits her lungs,
we give her steroids.
It blossoms and attacks her liver.
Get a piece of her lung,
stick it under a black light.
If it glows, sick children who need
her souffles can breathe easier.
Again?
- You have a problem.
- I told you, i didn't...
then you really have a problem.
They way she turned her
head to look at the MRI...
I think she's losing
her peripheral vision.
Because she turned her head?
I'm happy for you.
A love so deep you're ready
to chuck your medical license
to give her powerful, unproven drugs
with dangerous side effects.
I don't want to make any assumptions
about your feelings for me, but
I do have a birthday coming up.
I hear cuddy's seal training
finally came in handy.
Should I be investing
in a flak jacket?
You're safe.
No carpet bombing?
No burning of dresden
to teach her a lesson?
Since you're incapable
of taking the high road,
I assume there's some deeper,
more long-term strategy in effect.
Cuddy's not playing games.
She's not looking for leverage.
She wants pure,
unadulterated vengeance.
And your counter-move
is to let her have it?
The only time to strike back
is when i want something.
All I want now is to get
things back to normal.
Which i can't get by escalating.
The only way to win
this war is to lose it.
Let her punch herself out.
Yeah, that makes sense too.
"Too"?
I was thinking you actually feel guilty
about taking her away from her baby.
Your explanation's good too.
It's completely inconsistent
with your character, but...
Thank you, rationalization man.
You have saved the village.
You wanna eat?
You forgot your file.
Dana miller?
The cancer researcher?
Not anymore.
Dr. Miller, I doubt
if you'll remember me...
James Wilson, right? Chicago.
The adenocarcinoma conference.
Impressive.
- You want some cortisone for that itch?
- Liver failure.
Itching is one of
the lovely side effects.
Why did you quit?
The worst thing is
is now every time I get sick,
I have to listen
to a dozen people judge me.
Do you want me to congratulate you?
I've got four kids in ped-onc
right now who are gonna die.
Three of them within a year,
the other in a few days, probably.
Breakthroughs will happen.
With or without me,
someone will find the answer.
Maybe.
I... I...
I'm in the trenches.
I'm... I'm doing triage
as best I can.
You had the chance to end the war.
How is someone like me
supposed to keep fighting
when someone like you just...
Walked away?
When I left my job,
a lot of people were furious
with me.
It was easier to be angry than
to admit they weren't happy.
That they were stuck in a rut somewhere
in their lives, unable to move forward.
What's your rut?
Okay, you're freaking me out.
Do you think we should have kids?
- We've had this conversation.
- Ten years ago.
Things change.
On our third date I told you
that I didn't want to have kids,
and you said that
you were okay with that.
I said it because
I wanted to sleep with you.
And then I fell in love with you.
And I realized that I really
could be okay with it.
It wasn't like I had this
burning desire to have children.
God, have you been
resenting me all this time?
- Is that why...
- No.
Of course not.
I'm just...
I'm just... revisiting.
This isn't
a whim for me.
It's not a decision
that I made lightly.
Don't you ever wonder
what it would be like?
All the time.
Just not enough to make me
want to do it.
I like our life.
Are you okay?
Could you turn the tv back on?
Look straight ahead.
Why didn't we
do this test this morning?
You see that?
Damn.
I'm losing my peripheral vision?
I am on the drug.
Does this mean you have
to tell them and take me off it?
No, and yes.
As far as they're concerned,
you're on the placebo.
I found out last week.
The trial was getting
positive results...
So I switched you.
So my headaches...
I'll stop taking the drug,
and everything should be fine.
Specimen's negative
for blastomycosis.
That's it?
I'll go give House the test results.
You can tell the patient.
We've been dating for two weeks.
You just broke trial protocol
and risked your entire career
to give me a drug we're
not even sure will help me.
I don't think I'm ready for that.
Dr. Miller?
I'm sorry.
The test was negative.
So I'm gonna take you off...
- What happened to your head?
- I don't know. I was sleeping.
It's so itchy.
You were scratching it
in your sleep.
You scratched
right through your skull.
This is brain matter.
Need some help in here!
I did a free flap closure to avoid
any scarring. She was lucky...
The scratching didn't cause
any brain damage.
But the first thing she saidwas:
"It still itches".
Itch receptors are only
in the top two layers of skin.
Which means she's not actually itchy,
she just thinks she is.
- So the problem's in her brain?
- Thank god we have you to interpret.
Sorry, I have a headache.
Could be psychogenic. She made big,
sudden change in her life.
Could be the result
of a mental imbalance.
She wants to do what she wants to do.
What's crazy about that?
Why do you have to quit to do it?
If I want to do something, I do it.
If you can figure out a balance,
there's no burnout.
Thanks, Deepak. The itching
started yesterday, not 8 months ago.
Meningitis, encephalitis...
Those are diffuse processes.
This is localized.
Could be plaques.
MS would explain, possibly the lungs.
So would a brain tumor.
Well, how'bout we stop guessing
and mri her head instead?
- You want to talk about your headaches?
- Not particularly.
You went off the drug,
but the headaches are worse.
- You need an mri.
- The patient needs an mri.
If she had gangrene,
would you be amputating my leg?
Those pills have codeine.
You're taking twice
the indicated amount.
I've only been off the drug
for 24 hours,
so I think the bigger issue here
is that I've been off you for 24 hours.
You have worsening headaches,
loss of peripheral vision,
and a long history of pretending
bad things aren't happening.
You really think this is just
about my hurt feelings?
- I don't remember demoting you.
- I brought you something.
The latest issue of Parent magazine.
Really interesting column.
Apparently, working moms
are actually more engaged
and attentive than stay-at-home moms.
Something about personal fulfillment.
That's just a rationalization
by working moms
to justify not being with their kids.
Which is fine, if that's what they want.
It's not what I want.
And this is Nurses quarterly.
- The point is...
- You're only here to get back at me
by dumping dirty mop water
on my carpet.
Just get it over with
so I can get back to work.
I'm sorry.
I figured...
I don't know, one of us needed
to go out on a limb.
I thought I could help you.
It's hard to have a conversation
when I'm trying not to move.
Oh, God.
Patient's mri was negative.
- No tumors, no lesions.
- Where's your cane?
Where are your coworkers?
- I paged them.
- It could still be psychogenic.
Technically, it can't still be that,
because it never could be that.
She scratched through her skull
while she was sleeping.
Unless she was having
a dream about fleas...
Oh, hey! Funny you should drop by.
We were just talking
about this patient of ours.
Tell him the part about where
two of her doctors don't show up...
Where are you going?
Polyneuropathy. If it's not in
the brain, it's in the nerves.
It explains itching, lungs, liver.
Shock the affected area,
reboot the nerve... She'll be fine.
How bad is she?
She's got a tumor
in her optic chiasm.
- You don't need your coat to treat it.
- I'm going to the drug company.
To tell them that you
compromised their trial,
your ethics, and the patient's health?
That's a great idea.
They have records
on hundreds of patients.
I can ask them for access, find out
if other patients developed tumors
- and how they were treated.
- This drug inhibits cell death.
It could take a wild guess
at how I treat that.
Stop taking it?
She tried that yesterday.
Oh, my God, it's been a whole day,
and her brain tumor hasn't melted away?
If you get on that elevator,
and it's only 'cause you're worried
about getting to sleep...
I want to be able to tell this happened
to other people, and they're fine now.
So tell her.
- I'm not gonna lie to her.
- A little late for that.
You need to wait.
Because if it doesn't go away,
she's gonna need you
to still have a medical license.
So I spoke with House.
- He thinks we should just...
- My leg is bleeding.
- What happened?
- I was going for the phone,
and I fell over the table.
I can't see.
What do you mean?
I can't see anything.
- You gonna tip Housekeeping?
- Get it from Cuddy.
Don't tell me...
She burned your apartment to the ground.
The warmth would have been nice.
No heat, no power.
Apparently Mrs. House
called the utilities
and told them we were moving.
You have 17 messages.
And your non-involvement strategy
doesn't seem to be working.
Hang up, he's here.
- We've been paging you all night.
- By all means, let's discuss
the failed attempts to contact me,
not the reason behind them.
Patient  has experienced spinal shocks
before the machine was turned on.
Lhermitte's sign.
Shocks without shock,
an itch that won't stop.
She needs Dr. Seuss.
Lhermitte's sign could mean
Bechet's, B-12 deficiency.
No sores, no anemia.
- Where's Foreman?
- No idea.
Could be another
demyelinating disease.
Why are you asking
about Foreman and not 13?
Because both questions are bound
to have the same answer.
Ebony and ivory
are joined near the hip.
Forget the brain.
Look lower.
The spinal tumor wouldn't
explain the liver or the lungs.
But an aggressive
spinal hemangioma could.
Go find it.
You didn't answer the door.
Probably because I didn't
want to talk to anyone.
You can leave your stolen key
on your way out.
I was looking for Foreman.
I figured...
You can't see.
- Where is he?
- On his way to the drug company.
Tell him to come back.
I'll dial.
- If they can help.
- You think that drug company
has a magic tumor wand
that no one else knows about?
You need radiation,
not ritual sacrifice.
He asked for my advice
before he switched you
off the placebo.
I told him to do it if he loved you.
He only thinks he loves me.
It's the same thing.
Yes, he's an idiot.
You didn't ask him.
You're pissed off that he did.
So let him torch his career
to pay for his sins.
Unless you actually
feel something for the idiot.
In which case, you might
want to tell him to turn around.
You're hurting him.
Good, after all the stunts
he's pulled on me.
You're physically hurting him.
That's the point.
What's the point?
What do you think
you're going to accomplish?
House shouldn't be allowed
to make people miserable
- without paying for it.
- You're not!
- You're telling me how I feel?
- You're here because you like this.
You like working with him.
If only I'd known I was having fun,
I wouldn't have canceled
the bouncy House.
Fire him, and go be home
with your new baby.
I like what he does
for this hospital.
What he does is who he is.
And the same goes for you.
Slow down.
Unless you want to radiate
her heart instead of her brain.
Then your problems
would actually all go away.
Thanks.
I'm not beating myself up
enough already over this.
Entering the left common carotid.
You broke the rules.
Girlfriend went blind.
You gotta be ready for losing
to be one of the possibilities.
You're at the carotid bifurcation.
I knew that giving her the drug
would be bad for me if I got caught.
I never thought it'd be bad for her.
Nobody else was having
adverse reactions.
You did it because you love her.
Ironically, you never
took her into consideration.
Can't wait to see what
you get her for your anniversary.
Catheter's adjacent
to the optic chiasm.
We're in position.
Nukey, nukey.
What's going on with everyone today?
It involves House, Foreman,
and Thirteen,
which means it's either dumb, dangerous,
or tragic, or a combination.
I'm embracing my ignorance.
House was right
about the hemangioma.
Looks fixable.
What's that?
Hemangiomas travel solo.
This thing has brought a friend.
Masses in her lungs and spine.
One in her pericardium.
They're everywhere.
Classic for mesothelioma.
It metastasized outward
to the spine and muscles.
Ah, the irony of it.
Maybe she wouldn't be sick
at all if some other lazy
cancer researcher
hadn't gone home early.
Where are foreman and thirteen?
Shouldn't you be saying,
"those weren't there when
we scanned her two days ago"?
Mesothelioma shouldn't
grow this fast.
Good rephrasing.
Have wilson do a biopsy to confirm.
No.
Something weird is going on.
It involves our colleagues...
We should know.
You want us to treat the patient,
tell us what's going on.
Actually, all he needs us to
do is tell wilson to do something.
So...
You always blab
to watch people react.
So not blabbing means you don't want
us to react, which can't be good.
Is thirteen's headache
not just a headache?
If I check with admitting,
am I gonna find her name?
A little pinch.
I'm sorry about the other day.
I unloaded on you.
- And...
- You're not sorry.
You feel bad because
mesothelioma means I'm dying.
You're a good person.
I appreciate the sentiment.
I'm not apologizing
because you're dying.
I'm apologizing
because you were right.
I am stuck.
My girlfriend died.
She was the only person
I've loved for a long time, and...
I'm still living in her apartment.
I'm surrounded by her things.
I have left it all
exactly where it was.
I don't know how to get unstuck.
The only wrong thing is...
To do nothing.
All right.
That's not supposed to happen.
Have you thought about going to the
drug company, see if they can help?
- I thought about it.
- We need to give it more time.
It's been half a day.
This thing keeps growing,
there's other stuff in your brain
you might need later on.
If I were any other patient, you'd both
be in the lounge, eating donuts.
You're not any other patient.
Right.
Any other patient,
you don't feel guilty.
But you don't get to torch
your career to pay for your sins.
House told her to say that,
didn't he?
Does that make it any less true?
- You think he's right?
- Who cares?
You're a hypocrite.
You don't ask her if she wants
to be on the drug,
but when there's a chance
you could help her get better,
suddenly you're letting
her call the shots?
That's not being noble.
That's saving your own ass.
I'd feel worse if
he destroyed his career.
Mesothelioma doesn't bleed.
So what causes masses that do bleed?
Avm's secondary to schistosomiasis.
She'd be crawling with worms.
We'd have noticed it.
Gorham's disease and
kasabach-merritt can both cause
super-aggressive vascular tumors.
Patient's heart just stopped.
So what causes that?
Cardiac tamponade.
She's bleeding into her pericardium,
smothering her heart.
Syringe.
B. p.'s going back up.
It's working.
No, it's not... look.
We're transfusing platelets, ffp,
everything to try to keep her stable.
But we can barely keep
up with the blood loss.
At this rate, she could
be dead by the end of the day.
We need to resect the vascular
tumors, stop the bleeding.
Too late... No surgeon's
gonna touch her now.
Should we give up?
Just let her bleed out?
Don't be silly.
You know what that would do
to our malpractice insurance rates?
We go on the offensive.
Cut off the invading
army's supply line.
You're talking about embolization?
Cut off the arteries that feed blood
to the tumors, they wither and die.
Start with the ones in her lungs.
If they get any bigger, she's
gonna have a hard time breathing.
So she'll have a hard
time telling us she's dead.
You can't kill the tumors
without also killing healthy tissue.
If we wipe out 3/4 of her lungs...
Let's hope that running marathons
wasn't on her happy list.
I found this.
In the, uh, coat closet.
Where I hid it.
Thought I'd never see you again.
Little, little greg.
Yeah, you heard me right!
Well, you are who you are.
It's annoying, but...
It's not your fault.
It isn't about you.
I...
I'm sorry.
Because you were doing this job
perfectly until the baby came along.
What?
I'm apologizing.
Can't you just accept my...
I accept.
We gonna have to do
this dance again in 28 days?
- What the hell is wrong with you?
- Yesterday, you hate me.
Today, you're practically
weeping on my shoulder.
I can only assume that what I'm hearing
is your aunt flow telling me...
When I was being a jerk,
you suddenly act human.
But when I act human,
you turn back into a jerk.
Guess our cycles
aren't matched up yet.
This is your way of saying
you accept my apology, isn't it?
Nope, this is my way of saying
you were doing a crappy job before;
you will a slightly
crappier job now.
Everything keeps going.
Nature of life.
Nature of parenthood.
Or this whole thing is just an act.
And you've gone back to
the part you think you need to play.
You should go talk to wilson.
Rationalization man
needs a faithful sidekick.
Now, rational man
needs to go save a life.
If you're looking
for returnable bottles,
kutner's already cleaned it out.
Damn!
Oh, well.
That means the only thing
i'm gonna get out of this...
Is a diagnosis.
So the nurses gave her
pads instead of tampons.
Is that diagnostically relevant?
Fact that the nurses
had to give her anything is.
Means she's bleeding
from her uterus.
Women do that.
It's perfectly natural.
Not scary at all.
She menstruating
and she's bleeding everywhere.
There's about a 3 or 4
in 28 chance it's a coincidence.
Which leaves a much bigger chance that
the diagnosis is ectopic endometriosis.
She had a myoma eight months ago.
Surgeons cut through
her uterine wall.
Every cut of the scalpel
could have sent endometrial cells
spilling out into her bloodstream.
Some of them took up
residence in her lungs
some in her liver,
some in her spine.
And like all horny little cells,
they went forth and multiplied till
they reached a critical mass.
In the days leading up
to her next period,
when her uterus is supposed
to swell, everything swelled.
And when her uterus was supposed
to bleed, everything bled.
Yes, ladies,
I am blaming her period.
Granted, it's the worst period ever.
Although,
frankly, not by all that much.
Cut out the masses, she'll be fine.
Can't do surgery until her
cycle's over and she stops bleeding.
Let's hope
she can hold out till then.
In the meantime, get her a pint of
cookie dough ice cream
and a dvd of beaches.
I'm sorry.
I can see you.
How you feeling?
Relative to the last few days,
awesome.
You almost died.
For the second time in eight months.
I know.
How do you feel about
your life choices this time?
I didn't lie there
thinking "what if?"
I always worry, on my deathbed
I'll think,
"i didn't do anything
really important."
You're gonna spend one day
of your life on your death bed.
The other 25,000 are the
ones we should be worrying about.
Go to bed happy tonight.
Dr. Schmidt.
It's eric foreman.
Actually, the trial
isn't going too well.
You told them, didn't you?
Well, you really had no choice...
On account of being an idiot.
They gonna pull the drug?
I broke protocol.
Her results are no longer
admissible to the trial.
They don't have to do anything.
Anyone else gets a tumor,
they'll put a warning on the label.
Gonna keep your license?
They'll come after me if I attempt
to participate in any more trials.
That's very decent of them.
Well, good for me.
I'll see you tomorrow.
And the next day.
That wasn't your locker, was it?
It's a lock-er room.
How else are they gonna learn?
Do you think you can't
be happy without a kid?
I don't know.
I know I can't be happy without you.
You snore.
Shut up.
www.house-fr.com