And now, coming to the line,
last year's "Rookie of the year",
Casey Alfonso!
And in lane two,
nine times national champion,
Tony Cooper!
Tony's got his light on in lane two.
- And now Casey's approaching the line.
- How do you feel?
Great.
- I feel like throwing up my guts.
- You always feel like throwing up.
Come on dad,
let's get this digger on the line.
You're sure you don't wanna
go to law school?
- I hate lawyers!
- Yeah, so do I. Go get them baby!
Okay, looks like we're ready to go.
Let's hear it folks!
And it's Casey Alfonso
by Less than half a car length!
What a spectacular finish
for the young phenom.
Casey Alfonso with an amazing finish.
- What'd you do at the end there?
- Yeah, heh...
At about 250 feet,
the car got out of shape a bit.
But about halfway down...
I just got into the zone or something.
I pedaled it back into the groove.
It was the coolest ride of my life!
How does it feel to beat nine-time
national champion
Tony Cooper?
I'm sorry.
Can you repeat that?
How does it feel,
to beat nine-time national champion
Tony Cooper?
Casey!
Casey! Casey!
Out of the way!
Out of the way. Casey!
Casey! Get the ambulance!
Brian, get the ambulance!
Casey...
Transcript: swsub. com
Sync: BlueDoc, ¤AkaZab¤
Season 4 - Episode 6
"Whatever It Takes"
- 68-year-old male, non-smoker.
- 68's a good run.
That'll leave something
in the lockbox for the rest of us.
- Next!
- That's your breakfast?
Technically, it's Wilson's Lunch.
20-month-old baby,
Persistent rash, fever.
- Too much crying.
- Female college student?
Too much drama.
You don't care about the crying
or the drama.
Cause you won't see the patient.
And you'd treat methuselah
if his snot had an interesting color.
It means you've already decided
which case you wanna take next.
- Tell me about speed racer.
- Female,
seizure with visual
and auditory processing deficiency.
- I did a consult and...
- What kind of race car?
Dragster.
Continue.
You're gonna take a case based
on the car she drives?
Nothing says "thanks for saving my life"
like a test drive in a car,
that accelerates faster
than the space shuttle.
Can't save her life,
cause she's not dying.
Her lab shows signs of dehydration.
That means the problem's just likely...
Heatstroke.
Kinda hard to get heat-struck
in 4 1/2 seconds.
Not when you're wearing
a three-layer fireproof suit.
Excuse me.
Dr. House?
No, lazy ass called in sick again.
We can give him a message.
May we talk in private?
So... Either it's Heatstroke,
in which case we take the afternoon off,
or it's one of the diagnoses
that you guys are gonna have for me
in two minutes.
- You're in charge.
- I know.
- Cop?
- He's not packing.
Your dad's either a cop or
a security guard.
Or she carries a weapon.
You're with the CIA?
One of our employees just returned
from an assignment sick.
We believe he may be the victim
of an assassination attempt.
Sure.
You wanna close the door?
Door?
I assume you're gonna drop trou
at some point during the dance.
- I don't see why I should share.
- This isn't a joke.
If you're willing to help us,
we need to leave now.
If I have to walk somewhere,
there better be at least
five girls involved.
And they better be working
their way through college.
Okay, what do you got?
Hereditary brain disorder,
transient ischemia,
or paraneoplastic syndrome.
None of those go away with IV fluids.
It's heatstroke.
- Or cushing's or calcium deficiency.
- Who's your friend?
We use the term "life partner."
Get a fresh history,
neurological exam,
and an MRI of her head.
15 minutes for the lap dance.
A half hour to scrub
the guilt off my soul.
See you in 45.
- Dr. House... We need to hurry.
- Yeah, we need to hurry.
Little advice, I mean, obviously
the village people played
out the whole cop thing.
But, come on, CIA?
Do you seriously
expect anyone to believe that?
It helps when you have props.
Keep your eye on my pen.
Very good.
Any nausea or vomiting
before the seizure?
No.
My Dad had some,
but he's always like that before a race.
It could have been food poisoning.
Two eat breakfast to gether?
- No.
- Any history of sciatica or
spinal injury?
No.
Abnormal deep tendon reflex.
Really?
Let me see.
It's there.
I didn't say it wasn't there.
I said it was abnormal.
We're gonna give you
an MRI to be sure, but
I'm guessing your symptoms were caused
- by just dehydration and the heat.
- You're guessing?
Look,
I make a living
driving 300 miles an hour,
which makes the ability
to stay conscious kind of important.
I'm sure it's just heatstroke.
But we're gonna do an MRI
to be extra careful.
You said you left your cell
in your office.
I lied.
I wasn't going to take it,
just tell you to turn it off
for takeoff.
I know.
Just wanted to see if you could tell
that I was lying.
Useful information.
- Yeah?
- Where are you?
I'm on a top-secret mission for the CIA.
Right.
There was nothing on your racecar
driver's CT,
and the history and physical
were normal.
Her deep tendon reflexes seemed
a bit weak to me.
Areflexia could mean miller fisher.
Yes, are flexia could
Mean miller fisher,
but since the reflex was weak,
not absent,
it doesn't mean anything.
I'm releasing her.
You can go back to your poker game.
Poker's illegal.
CIA would never allow illegal activity.
Have you considered Miller Fisher?
Why? What happened?
She just had another seizure.
And now she's getting
a vertical nystagmus.
We think it's Miller Fisher,
an inflammatory process.
In rare cases,
it can cause respiratory failure, but...
Wait, she could stop breathing?
You said there was nothing wrong.
You said you were sure.
You just had another seizure.
Clearly, there's something wrong.
So why should I trust you
to figure out what it is?
Where's Dr. House?
I'm at this hospital.
It's gonna be all right.
We just need to start
the plasmapheresis.
No!
It's not going to be all right,
because you obviously don't have a clue.
What you're doing.
I'm not letting you touch me.
- Honey, come on.
- I wanna see House!
Where is he?
Looks a lot better on 24.
I take that back.
Dr. Samira Terzi.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Dr. House.
We really appreciate the consult
on such short notice.
There's nothing that gives me more
pleasure than helping out a colleague.
This is Dr. Sidney Curtis
from the Mayo Clinic.
He's also agreed to help
with the diagnosis.
- Dr. House.
- Curtis on Immunology Sidney Curtis?
- You've read it?
- Nope!
But it is keeping my piano level.
So...
Where is the poor, sick fella?
- What do we do?
- I don't know yet.
- She needs treatment.
- This is a test, right?
You're reporting back to him
everything we do.
Yeah.
And I asked the patient
to be uncooperative.
- Personally, I think she overplayed it.
- She's being uncooperative.
Because you made us all
look like idiots.
We're only gonna look like idiots
If we can't figure out how to get her
to agree to the treatment.
What would House do right now?
Pop a pill, insult us,
and trick the patient.
We can do that last part.
She's never met House before, has she?
- Who's got a cane?
- House isn't here.
We're not gonna act like him.
What do you want?
I...
I'm gonna do what doctors
aren't supposed to do.
Admit I made a mistake.
I shouldn't have been so quick
to dismiss your symptoms.
But you need to let us start
the plasmapheresis.
What do you want?
Case?
Honey, do you know where you are?
She's burning up.
- Start the treatment.
- We can't.
You've got my permission.
She's obviously confused.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Miller Fsher doesn't cause dlirium
and fever.
I don't know what this is.
I'm afraid there are going to be ome
limitations on his medical history.
Just let me know what you need,
and I should be able to provide it.
FYI, my mal practice insurance
doesn't cover alien autopsies.
That's fine.
X-files are the next wing over.
Where was the patient
when he first felt ill?
Sorry, that's classified. But assume
there aren't too many places
in the world John hasn't been.
And, yes, John's a cover name.
What makes you think
it was an attempt on his life?
Sorry, can't tell you that either.
What can you tell us?
Yeah, did Oswald really have sex
with Marilyn Monroe?
Good lord.
Very professional.
Five days ago, he was 185 pounds.
Perfect health.
Cool.
Fever and delirium rule out...
He's not gonna hire you
just because you call him the most.
Especially since it's obvious
he doesn't wanna be called.
Symptoms rule out miller fisher.
MS fits better.
Progression's too fast.
More likely meningitis.
Areflexia doesn't fit as well with.
Does with amyloidosis.
That's even slower than MS.
It's lupus.
I'm with the little man on this one.
It's attacking the body and the brain.
Classic autoimmune.
Flirt all you want,
but I should warn you.
Shiksas are for practice.
Lupus this aggressive
wouldn't spare her kidneys.
It's primarily neurological.
- Let's start her on.
- Why no plaques on her MRI?
MRI was inconclusive.
- So I don't know.
- So now you're sure that it's MS.
Just like you were sure
it was miller fisher.
An hour after you were sure
it was heatstroke.
The symptoms fit.
- Start her on interferon.
- We're not gonna score any points
with House if we solve
this just by running your errands.
- I get that you want to be right.
- You don't?
I'm just trying to save a patient,
not score points with my boss.
Would it hurt the patient
if you let us run some tests?
You've got three hours.
We've run six complete tox screens,
tested for every heavy metal, poison,
and biological agent we can think of.
It says here he ate a lot of chestnuts.
Hold on a second.
If the squirrel liberation
army's involved,
I'm outta here.
Those little rodents are.
Horse chestnuts are poisonous.
If someone switched them.
Horse chestnuts may look like chestnuts,
but they taste like a horse's
lower-than-chestnuts.
Which makes the theory
that he accidentally ate a couple
of hundred slightly less persuasive.
And seeing as how he was prowling
the back alleys of... Tehran?
It wasn't tehran. It was...
Oops, you almost got me.
Unless we know
the local environmental factors,
- poisonous flora...
- You know I can't tell you that.
Well, then, why are we here?
You might as well just Google "poison."
All they would tell me is...
He spent the last 11 months in Bolivia.
Who you gonna kill in Bolivia?
- My old housekeeper?
- We don't kill people.
I'm sorry.
Who are you gonna marginalize?
If it is my housekeeper,
she has it coming.
Cleaning the windows
means cleaning both sides.
Am I right, or am I right?
What does it matter what he was doing?
- The guy's dying.
- Not anymore.
I know what's poisoning him, and who.
John.
It's just pancreatitis.
He's not an alcoholic.
And unless his pancreas
is in his fingers.
Spies can't get fungal infections?
And the burns on his skin?
Spies can't get sunburns?
Bolivia doesn't have sun?
So, either we go
with his theory
of the non-drinking drunk,
Or he was poisoned by some group
with the resources
to make it completely untraceable.
Some customized isotope.
Let's treat for radiation poisoning.
The iodine's to protect your thyroid.
Antibiotics are to handle infections.
Should start working
in a couple of hours.
We should celebrate,
with a beer,
or eight.
I don't drink.
Me thinks he doth protest too much.
He's deathly ill.
Why would he lie about drinking?
Guilt over killing a man.
Make anyone hit the sauce.
- We don't kill people.
- Right.
You just lie to your friends and family,
establish false identities, trick people
into betraying their country.
He'd never cover up his drinking.
He's too honest.
Something I've always wanted to know.
That poison lipstick that ginger
used to kiss Gilligan...
Why didn't that kill her?
Okay, drum roll.
LP is negative for meningitis.
Sorry, Cole.
Fat pad biopsy is...
Wait for it...
Negative for amyloidosis.
And thirteen goes down.
Could we hurry this up? My son has.
Can I have a kid too?
I'm working too hard.
I could hook you up.
I had two minutes and some anti-nausea
meds, I'd take you up on that.
And for the gold...
Protein 65, glucose 70.
It's MS, start her on interferon.
Turn to the last page.
Sed rate's 95 ANA's weakly positive.
Positive? It's lupus.
Weakly. Not lupus, it's MS.
We obviously don't know what it is.
Treat for both.
No.
I gave in on the test.
I'm not treating her for two completely
separate diseases
because you think lupus
will win you a prize.
Still think it's lupus?
Yeah.
Me to.
In case of emergency,
go to the emergency room.
- Could be lupus.
- That's what we figured.
Then why are you here?
You're an immunologist.
We wanted to confirm.
Who are you looking for me
to help you sell down the river?
House or Cuddy?
Foreman.
Sorry.
He's pushing MS.
Thinks that because he's in charge,
he has to prove he's the smartest guy
in the room.
All I've heard about you. You put
the patient above everything else.
That's why everyone
finds you so annoying.
All House cares about is results.
I know. I'm talking about how
to do deal with Foreman.
So am I.
- Fever's down to 101.5.
- Treatment's working...
Trying to figure out
which treatment's working.
It's kind of tacky doing
it front of the patient.
You put her on steroids too?
We had no choice.
The sed rate pointed to lupus.
- And the a NA ruled it out!
- Doctors!
Legs hurt?
I can't feel them at all.
I don't think i can move them.
Vitals stabilizing.
- Tummy ache's gone as well.
- So the treatment's working.
Wanna ditch Dr. Killjoy and...
hop in the company jet?
Little trip down mexico way.
And I'm not talking about
the country or the plane.
Do you think acting like an idiot
and talking about sex works on girls?
Well, if it didn't, the human race
would have died out long ago.
You're pretty cheery for someone who was
just proved wrong about his
- pancreatitis theory.
- I'm appropriately cheery for someone
- who's being proved right.
- John hasn't vomited in six hours.
What's to vomit?
I'm eating his lunch.
With holding nutrients
is the treatment for pancreatitis.
That and the antibiotics you put him on.
I did unhook your iodine, though.
Didn't seem to fit with the whole,
I'm just jerking you guys
around gestalt.
You're unbelievable.
Well, let's ask John if he'd rather
be sick honestly or cured dishonestly.
John.
Any chance he's just...
Overwhelmed with gratitude?
Paralysis.
It's a new symptom?
Big white space on the board
where it would fit?
Nice, multicolored markers?
I'm not writing it because we can't know
if it's a real symptom.
When these two went rogue and
pumped her full of ste...
- Steroids don't cause paralysis.
- She was also on interferon!
Giving her both probably fried
her immune system.
Who knows what infection
you could cause...
We consulted an immunologist.
- She said we have...
- She?
You talking about Dr. Cameron?
- She thought lupus...
- She tell you to start treating?
Yes, they've ignored you.
They screwed up.
And it's fun watching you spank them.
But can we get back to the medicine?
The last thing any of you give
a damn about is the medicine!
Look...
I'm not saying
you're bad doctors or bad people.
But House is.
He created a nasty
little cutthroat world,
planted you in it,
and is watching you play.
And none of it works for anyone
except him.
And whoever wins.
Given its quick progression,
we gotta assume botulism.
I'll go to her place,
check out her fridge and pantry.
It's not botulism. It's polio.
Brilliant.
We should search her home
for FDR's remains or a time machine.
She could have contracted it from anyone
- who's been to Africa or...
- She's been vaccinated.
Vaccines wear off.
There hasn't been a single american case
in over 20 years.
I've seen this disease.
I know what it looks like.
That's why you're finding it,
because you're looking for it.
Polio... It's crazy.
House wouldn't think so.
So go find House
and tell him your theory.
Take a personal day.
Seriously.
Get outta here.
- You don't have the power to fire me.
- But I do have the power
to kick your ass off my case.
We're starting the botulism treatment.
The rest of you, look for confirmation.
- He should be brought up on charges.
- Okay, relax.
I'll take your book out
from under my piano.
He's dying of radiation sickness.
He's obviously in pain.
All of which could have been avoided
if you hadn't interfered with...
What was that for?!
Radiation sickness kills specific cells
at specific times.
His hair should be coming out in clumps
before he's writhing in pain.
Since it's not,
I know who's trying to kill him.
God.
It's blood cancer. Waldenstrom's.
Radiation can cause infections,
which set off...
If had any real evidence of foul play,
you'd be torturing Bolivians
instead of putting me into a state
of anticipatory sexual arousal.
- Can we treat for both?
- Bad idea.
Unless you're the one
who's trying to poison him.
I'll arrange
for plasmapheresis and chemo.
Are you gonna trust him
after what he did?
I don't have to trust him
to agree with him.
You make a good point.
I've been wrong every time,
and she still won't listen to you.
So either she really likes me
or she really hates you.
And I got a ride in the jet.
Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- Just came to say hi.
Hi again.
Where's... Mrs. Bearman?
Sent her home.
I was scheduling her for an MRA.
If we gave MRAS to every patient
with a headache...
This wasn't just a headache,
it was the worst in her life.
Then lucky for you, I'm a neurologist.
She went to a wine and cheese tasting.
- Both triggers for migraines.
- She's never had a migraine before.
And I never hagel
before the first time I had one.
Bagels don't kill people.
This is a classic ticking-bomb aneurysm.
This taught me a lesson.
I guess when I mess
with other people's patients,
I risk looking like an officious bitch.
We're gonna have to track down
Mrs. Bearman.
Wait...
Never mind.
- That's funny.
- It's not funny. It's totally immature.
It is funny.
You just can't appreciate it
because you're the victim.
Yeah, I deserve shame and ridicule
for offering a consult.
Unheard of for a doctor.
You didn't offer a medical consult.
You offered a
"dealing with Foreman" consult.
For the good of the patient.
It's what House would have done.
Maybe House will hear about it
and tear up with pride.
You think I'm trying to impress him.
I think that, for someone
who's not involved in his team,
you're remarkably involved in his team.
Let it go.
Let him go.
And that's mature?
120 over 80.
Let 'er rip.
Now we got the medical stuff
out of the way.
Why don't we meet back at your place
for some enhanced
interrogation techniques?
My safe word is,
"help, please, please stop."
It's two pleases.
Anything less than that, you keep going.
You actually cure this guy,
I'll show you my private water board.
We need to consult an oncologist
about the chemo.
Oh, I'm sorry, I thought...
You were still euphemizing.
My valet knows a little oncology.
I was wondering when you'd grow bored
of avoiding my calls.
Oh, I can never grow bored
of ignoring you.
What's the latest protocol
on Waldenstrom's?
- Where are you?
- CIA headquarters.
How much fludarabine...
Either you're sprawled naked
on your floor with an empty bottle
of vicodin, or collapsed naked
in front of your computer
with an empty bottle of viagra.
Please tell me which,
because Chase has another pool going.
They flew me in to help deal
with a sick employee.
- How much...
- Hallucinations. Damn! I shouldn't
- have bet on the viagra.
- Okay, call the langley switchboard,
- ask for extension...
- 3578
3578.
He asked an awful lot
of questions for a valet.
You know, I happen to have
a position available on my penis.
Wait a second...
I think I screwed up that joke.
You offering me a job?
I'd settle for that.
As tempting as a position
on your staff is,
- I like it here.
- Pays better.
And we've only had one
assassination attempt.
And I'm sure you're a great boss.
That's why your fellows left en masse
a couple of months ago.
I have satellite images.
Inspector Gadget.
My God.
You're actually at the CIA.
You've gotta get down here.
They've got a satellite aimed
directly into Cuddy's vagina.
I told them the chances
of invasion are slim to none, but...
Waldenstrom's.
Recommended dose is
25 milligrams per meter squared.
- They do a background check on you?
- 25 milligrams?
They did a background check on you,
they did a background check
- on your friends.
- Relax.
I'm sure they already know that you
brought heroin back from Afghanistan.
That... That's not true.
I've never been to Afghanistan.
House?
- She's getting worse?
- Fever's risen slightly.
But it's definitely...
Botulism?
Right?
Because if you're wrong again,
and you're treating her for something
she doesn't even have...
The antitoxin hasn't had time
to work yet.
I know it's hard, but try to be patient.
Excuse me.
I know you're pissed I interrupted,
but you're gonna be
even more pissed in a second.
You tested her without telling me?
Yeah. And I know,
I'm really, really sorry. But...
On the other hand, it's a positive.
She has polio.
Now what, boss?
Where's House?
He's blown off four hours of clinic.
He's consulting for the CIA.
Seriously.
Call langley and ask for extension 35...
3536?
There's definitely two threes.
I... I wrote it down.
I have it somewhere.
He's gonna make up twice
his skipped hours in the clinic.
- Okeydoke.
- And for protecting him,
- you're gonna make up twice that.
- Why are you punishing me
- worse than him?
- Because House never learns.
You might.
How are you feeling?
- Like crap.
- Yeah, cancer can be that way.
My hair is falling out.
That the chemo?
No, it's too quick.
So what does it mean?
It means you don't have cancer.
Someone actually did try to kill you.
You're stubborn.
- You're arrogant!
- There's no need to yell.
- You may have cost that man his life.
- He's getting the radiation treatment.
24 hours too late!
I didn't yell at you
when I thought you were wrong.
- I wasn't wrong!
- This isn't productive.
There is no productive. It's too late.
Because of your inexperience,
your poor judgment.
And your failure to recognize
a reckless fool!
Cordyceps sinensis.
It's... It's an herbal treatment
derived from a parasitic fungus,
comes from caterpillars.
Along with dimercaprol chelation,
it's been shown to mitigate
bone marrow damage
from radiation poisoning.
In monkeys.
I'm sorry.
I was stubborn and arrogant.
Self-recriminations won't help her.
Nothing's gonna help her.
She's got polio.
There's no cure,
but there are treatments.
- She's dying.
- Yeah. Every death's a tragedy.
Funny how you weren't so depressed
when she just dying because
me and Amber screwed up.
And I'm also self-centered.
Thanks for clarifying.
Don't forget self-pitying.
Vitamin C.
Extremely high doses.
It was experimental treatment
protocol in the '50s.
- And they haven't finished yet?
- They... Lost funding.
That's because there's no logical reason
vitamin C would cure polio.
- Well, someone thought there was.
- Someone thought black people
made excellent farm implements.
I'm not talking about hurting anyone.
I just wanna force feed her
some orange juice.
You wanna throw in
some bacon and eggs as well?
If there's anything you learn today,
it's gotta be that you can be wrong.
John, can you hear me?
We're going to start you
on an experimental treatment.
Tea?
It's a chinese herb.
- Which has been effective in...
- I'm dying, aren't I?
Probably.
We're gonna attempt
an experimental protocol.
- A new drug?
- An old one. Vitamine C.
Ultra-high doses have been shown
to destroy the polio virus
and heal nerve damage.
- She could regain use of her legs.
- It's unlikely.
But, we're gonna try.
Don't give up.
Nausea's...
Not as bad.
Radiation sickness has a latency period.
You'll get better before you get worse.
You wanna know
what I really did down there?
Only if it's interesting.
The women there...
During carnival they...
They do this dance.
They call it the "Devil Dance".
Not interesting.
I spent all 40 days with this...
Attache to the minister of defense.
The most...
Buttoned-down woman you'd ever meet.
You know?
'Cept when she did this dance.
She agreed to tell me stuff...
Okay, we have half a good story there.
Karma.
Best way to rid yourself of that guilt
is to confess your sins.
This pain is... Right.
It's comforting.
It makes me think that...
Somehow, it all makes sense.
What do you mean, 40 days?
When they found out.
What she...
Told me.
Carnival in Bolivia's only eight days.
You have any idea
what a chestnut looks like?
You idiot.
Who are you calling an idiot?
Whoever knew that John
was stationed in Brazil, not Bolivia.
Brazil?
Well, then, I guess
I'm talking to you, idiot.
It's the same region.
- It's the same parasite, same diseases.
- But not the same language.
In Bolivia, chestnuts are chestnuts.
Brazil, on the other hand,
hascastanhas do para, literally,
"chestnuts from para."
Because it would be stupid
for people from Brazil
to call them Brazil nuts!
So he ate Brazil nuts. Big deal.
No, he ate a lot of Brazil nuts.
Which is a big deal,
because they contain selenium.
Which, in high doses, causes fatigue,
vomiting, skin irritation,
discharge from the fingernail beds,
and hair loss.
Any of that sounding familiar?
Can you treat it?
We've already started.
Treatment's chelation,
same as for radiation sickness.
The only difference is it works
a lot better on nut poisoning.
So what's the problem?
You're an idiot.
Why is she shivering?
Low serum calcium is
a side effect of the treatment.
- I can give her a calcium supplement.
- My arm hurts.
Infusion rate has to remain high
for the treatment to work.
Is it working?
- You feel that?
- Yeah.
It hurts.
It's working.
This is fantastic.
There's a lot you can learn
in my fellowship.
A few new procedures I could teach you.
Course, we'd need a nurse to prep.
I know how to kill a man with my thumb.
Actually, I was just trying to make
another euphemism for sex.
- So was I.
- Oh, God.
How can you flirt with this idiot?
He lied to us again and again.
He broke laws, ethical codes...
I was right.
- That doesn't mean everything.
- It means a lot.
Dr. Curtis.
Dr. House.
Appreciate your help.
When...
When you were dying,
you tried to infect me.
Because you knew I'd fight for you
if I thought I was dying too.
You bringing this up now so I'll
forgive you for messing with my patient?
I'm happy I changed jobs.
But I know...
I'll never have that sort of...
Excitement.
- You Miss people trying to kill you?
- No.
I miss...
People doing whatever it takes
to get the job done.
I guess that's why
I'm having trouble giving it up.
I shouldn't have helped them
mess with your patient.
They had to screw with me.
I've gotten everything wrong.
I don't believe it.
You're not...
Gonna get everything right.
But you're never gonna get
everything wrong.
Morning!
- Where have you been the last two days?
- Overslept.
- We saved speed racer. She had polio.
- We cured it with vitamin C.
Yeah.
I cured depression
with tonic water once.
Actually, I think there was
some gin in it too.
150 grams over six hours. It worked.
No, it didn't.
I told you you can't cure polio.
That means either she's not cured
or she never had it.
Since she's walking out of here...
I tested her blood from admittance.
No polio.
That means Brennan
screwed up the lab tests.
Or you screwed up your lab tests.
- You must have. She got better.
- So it's relapsing and remitting.
Maybe... Porphyria.
No, that's a stretch.
If she had porphyria,
you would have seen purple urine.
You think it's more likely
he cured polio?
They believe it.
Her symptoms fit perfectly.
And the alternative
is unbelievably convoluted.
Some doctor would have
to poison her with valium
so it looks like polio,
then fake a lab test,
then give her vitamin C and stop the
poison so she magically gets better.
Actually...
It is kind of doable, right?
So what do you think?
Should we test her for thallium
before you contact Stockholm?
You poisoned her?
The really shocking thing
is that Foreman was right
about the heatstroke.
Vitamin C cures polio. I've seen it.
Yeah... In some Bush clinic.
You need polio in a place
with a proper lab.
The only problem is that places
with proper labs don't have polio.
There is no money
in finding cures
for diseases that only kill poor people.
This will make them do research.
And what do you care
if I faked a lab test
if it saves a few thousand lives?
I did what I had to do.
Isn't that what you hired us for?
Which is why I'm not gonna fire you.
You're gonna quit.
Go on, get out of here.
So you're just gonna let him go?
Absolutely.
I'm gonna let him get
as far away as possible
before you call the cops.
Guy's a nut job.
Who the hell did I leave in charge?
- Foreman.
- There was a reason for that.
Next time, listen to him.
Where have you been?
And don't say the CIA.
Okay.
- By the way, one of my employees...
- Either you're gonna have to get
someone from the CIA to call and confirm
your story, or you're doing
eight clinic hours
and Wilson is doing 16.
I was in the Hamptons.
I was helping some rich hedge fund jerk
treat his son's sniffles.
Fascinating as that sounds.
For your honesty,
I will forgive your hours.
Thank you.
No!
The only thing less likely
than your helping the CIA
is your helping some rich guy
on Long Island.
You're doing your hours and Wilson's.
I know how to kill a man with my thumb.
Who doesn't?
Hi.
I'm going to take you up on your offer.
Yeah?
I... I live a couple miles from here.
That's not the offer I meant.
I gave notice today.
You said you were happy at the company.
I lied.
Doubt you'll hold it against me.
I'll see you at 9:00 on monday.