How about the name Brooke?
She just doesn't seem
like a Brooke anymore.
Brooklyn.
She's a baby, not a city.
What do you think, Bud?
Got any suggestions?
Toadette.
I'm hungry.
I'll get you guys something to eat.
You're okay.
I was paged?
What are you doing here?
Can we talk somewhere?
I was thinking Doroth...
Sarah?
Where's the baby?
No one saw anyone go in or out,
and the baby's not in the nursery.
- What was her condition?
- Five weeks preterm.
C-section
because her mom's preeclampsia.
Is that the father?
Mr. Lozinski.
I'm Dr. Lisa Cuddy, dean of Medicine.
How long were you out of the room?
15, 20 minutes tops.
- Was there a proximity alarm?
- No alarms.
What's that?
The bracelet on your baby's ankle
has a microchip
that would set off alarms
if she was carried through an exit.
Call the police.
Shut down all the exits.
We are on lockdown.
Nobody moves
until we find that baby.
.:: La Fabrique ::.
R[H]ésus AB+ Team
Arrow - Benj - ShalimarFox
Why won't you sign
the divorce papers?
It's been on my to-do list.
Sorry.
Will you sign them?
Not until we have a real conversation
about our marriage.
I made a mistake coming here.
I'm sorry. I'm gonna leave...
this copy here.
Code seven. Code seven.
All non-essential personnel
and guests
please remain where you are.
Security personnel should report
to their staging areas
and await further instructions.
All patients,
please remain in your rooms,
and use call buttons
if you need medical assistance.
Please remain calm
and wait for hospital personnel
to come to you.
Do not try to leave your room
until the code seven has been lifted.
Please clear hallways.
- You need to get into the room now.
- Please notify hospital personnel
or police immediately
if you see anything suspicious.
We cannot allow anyone
to leave the hospital at this time.
All personnel should remain
in their staging areas
unless otherwise instructed
by security.
Gotta clear the...
Thank you for your patience
and cooperation.
And did anyone
other than your nurses
ever come by
asking about your daughter?
No, just those two.
- I'll check in soon.
- Wait.
- What are you doing?
- No, I need to help them look.
You have to stay in bed.
You pulled a stitch.
Lay back down.
I got it.
Why don't I give you something
to help you relax?
I don't want to relax.
I want to find my baby.
- The police are searching room by room.
- Who would take her?
- What if she needs to be fed?
- We're gonna find her.
Why aren't the police
talking to our nurse?
What now?
- Truth or dare?
- You don't want to mess with me.
True or dare queen at Newton north.
I was kidding.
We can find something interesting
without relying
on some juvenile game.
Sure.
Truth.
They think I took the kid?
- Do you think I would do something...
- No, I'm just asking questions.
The day I let the older brother
hold the baby for the first time...
so I put her in his lap.
After a few seconds, she shrieked.
I'm pretty sure he pinched her.
I need to know this stuff.
Anything out of the ordinary.
It was sibling rivalry.
I thought it was kind of ordinary.
- What are you doing down here?
- I was looking for McKenna's file.
You mean this file?
- The one I said I'd get?
- Two hours ago?
Seriously, you don't trust me
with the immense responsibility
of fetching a file?
- Why are you looking through those?
- Do you know what these are?
The staff credentials files.
- Those should all be in H.R.
- Down here to be digitized.
And we're locked in,
and whoever's supposed
to be watching 'em is locked out.
We could look up anything on anyone.
- Malpractice records, felony histories.
- Put them away.
Come on.
We have a tiny window of opportunity
to gain some insight
into our colleagues.
What if we just snoop on the boss?
I think I can live with that.
You're on two milligrams
of morphine an hour.
How the hell are you still awake?
No, don't tell me.
Ischemic cardiomyopathy.
If the blood's not reaching
your gut,
you have intestinal hypoperfusion.
That'd be stronger
than the narcotics.
The nurse said I might only have
a day or two left.
She was being kind.
You're Dr. House,
aren't you?
Oh, God, don't tell me
we used to date.
The limp. I read about you.
I sent you a letter
before they knew what was wrong.
I tried to get you to take my case.
You should have kept reading.
Heart disease
is kind of below my pay grade.
It started as tooth pain.
No one got it
that it was a heart problem.
Till I had a series
of massive heart attack...
This doesn't bother you?
You talking with your mouth full?
A little.
I meant the fact that you're standing
here watching me die
because my file bored you.
I take maybe 1 in 20 cases.
A lot of the people I turn down
end up dying.
It's really a good argument
for there being more than one me
when you think about it.
- Truth.
- All right.
Have you ever had a threesome?
- You haven't?
- Wait, just because I'm bisexual?
Do you understand
what bisexual means?
It doesn't mean you have sex
with two people at once.
And by the way, you didn't ask me
if I'd had a foursome. Truth or dare?
- You've had a foursome?
- Now you've asked me two questions,
so I get to ask you two.
You see why I was the queen.
Walker wouldn't do anything.
He's my son too.
I don't mean to sound cold,
but he's your stepson.
We can't ignore any possibility.
Walker's been getting
in fights a lot
at school lately.
Last week,
he hit another kid with a book
hard enough to draw blood.
If he did something to the baby...
We were working on it.
- And we failed.
- No, you had a conversation with House,
then came back, informed me
I'd been forever poisoned by him,
and started packing.
It's interesting
how you leave out the part
where you murdered
another human being.
A dictator who was committing genocide.
You thought about doing it yourself.
- But I didn't.
- Right.
Because you're not toxic like I am.
What do you think
is gonna happen here?
You're gonna logic me
into coming back?
There must be over 30
malpractice settlements in here.
He did a brain biopsy
without CT mapping,
causing brain herniation and death.
Look at this one.
Patient lost four liters of blood
from a botched penisectomy.
On a patient named Lisa Cuddy?
Damn.
They're all named Lisa Cuddy.
He's not even here,
and he's screwing with us.
Where's the joy in that?
You really want
to get into his head?
Yeah, but I decided against
stabbing myself in the leg
or getting addicted to pain pills.
You can... skip the stabbing.
- Where did you...
- Confiscated them from a drug seeker.
Didn't get a chance to turn 'em in.
It is after hours.
I'll take one.
Walk in House's shoes for a night.
One?
I believe he wears a larger size.
No cards, no flowers,
not even a phone call.
Let me guess.
Lighthouse keeper.
I was a classics Professor
at Princeton for 26 years.
Mostly research.
So your closest colleagues
died 2,000 years ago.
That must be it.
Not that you have no friends
because, say,
you're a miserable bastard.
What do you care?
The next few hours
are gonna be grim.
There'll be nausea, pain,
no company,
as soon as I can
get myself out of here.
I can unlock the regulator.
You can put yourself
in a narcotic haze,
sleep blissfully to the end.
Is that a favor to me or to you?
Win-win.
No, thanks.
Are you trying to guilt me
for not taking your case?
You think a classicist
doesn't believe in fate?
You think Odysseus would lie whimpering
like a loser in a hospital bed?
Come on, take my offer.
Take the drug holiday.
Numb yourself out.
I think you're the one
who wants to numb himself out.
Truth.
How did your dad react
when you came out to him?
He made me tea.
Doesn't matter what I tell him,
he smiles, tells me he supports me,
and makes me some peppermint tea.
- Truth or dare?
- Truth.
Are you dating anyone?
Now? No.
Interesting, you added a modifier.
Truth.
When you were dating Foreman...
If it was something personal
about him or us,
I don't think that's right to answer.
We work together.
That's the point!
Something personal, embarrassing.
- Pick something else.
- You see, this is your problem.
You act like you're so liberal and open,
but you are the least...
I changed my mind.
Dare. Just no nudity.
Yes, nudity.
I want you to show
your breasts
to Taub.
That is the most idiotic dare ever!
Have you ever played this game?
I thought showing me your breasts
would be a little exploitative.
Your dare is in the future, genius.
If you're saying you won't do it...
Of course I'll show my breasts
to Taub.
Tomorrow, perhaps,
or maybe some time next year,
you know,
because I'm honor-bound.
Truth or dare?
It's understandable
that you wouldn't be happy right now.
Your world is changing.
You scared?
How do you feel about your sister?
I hate her.
Walker, this is important.
Did you do anything to the baby?
Did you move her somewhere?
Hide her?
- Nobody'd be mad at you.
- I said no,
so stop asking me.
Bad pain day?
Bad pain month.
Since I'm not using it...
If you don't want the morphine,
you must have something of your own.
I was in rehab.
I had a little problem
with the something of my own.
Now all I take is ibuprofen,
and it's two flights up.
- For the whole month?
- The pain's migrated.
I think the arterial wall
is damaged.
- What, you don't know?
- I haven't had an arteriogram yet.
And you don't want the test.
In case the arterial wall is fine.
Which would mean that the pain
is coming from something else.
What's her name?
Interesting...
That you jump from physical pain
to long-lost love.
You're projecting.
So what's her name?
- What time is it?
- What does it matter to you?
It's T minus four hours.
8:20.
Now tell me who she is
and what are
the pathetically long odds
that she's gonna visit or call.
And why that's a reason
not to take the morphine.
Dude.
Is the room still spinning?
Mine is.
Maybe we shouldn't have taken
so many.
I'm gonna try to stand up.
You be careful.
That's working.
I can't feel my face.
No way.
Way.
Hit me.
What?
Hit me in the face.
Seriously?
You know you've always wanted to.
- Now's your chance.
- That's a great idea.
We start a fight club.
Maybe we...
Oh, my God!
That is so cool!
I can still feel my hand.
- I wasn't ready.
- What were you gonna do?
Flex your goatee muscles?
Wait a minute.
This is your credentials file?
Give me that.
That's why you came down here.
Not for the patient file.
You wanted...
I will answer
whatever questions you want.
But then you sign the papers.
Did you ever love me?
How can you even ask that?
The first time you slept with me
was because you were high.
I was on the drugs
because I was emotional.
The emotions led to the sex,
not the drugs.
Not true.
After that, you refused
to let it go further.
Because I knew I was falling for you
and I didn't want to.
And that never changed.
You broke off our vacation
because I bought you a ring.
I got cold feet. I'm not proud.
You almost called off our wedding
because you couldn't give up the idea
- of having your dead husband's baby.
- Don't bring him up!
Because even then,
you weren't sure about me.
Maybe if I was dying,
- it would've been different.
- That's unfair.
It's exactly the point!
He was dying when you met him,
and gone just a year into the marriage.
So it was all a honeymoon with him,
and I could never match up to that.
- The first time reality intruded...
- Stop this.
- Tell me the truth.
- About what?
- Did you ever love me?
- I don't know!
Thank you for finally telling me.
Truth.
You said
you weren't dating anyone now.
Does that mean
you recently were, or soon will be?
Look who's guarded now.
You had no problem
talking about your sex life,
but your love life...
Fine. Dare it is.
No nudity now or in the future.
You're too much
of a nice boy, Wilson.
Let's let the bad boy out for a bit.
You have to go steal
one dollar
right now.
From who?
Come on.
Interned at Hopkins.
Old news. Here we go!
Academic probation.
I am asking you
to please stop reading.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Faked a lab result.
Very wrong!
And you came down
to destroy the record
before it gets digitized.
Permanentized.
Even wronger.
I needed to beat
all those elite,
spoiled kids around me.
To show no weaknesses,
to win at everything.
Why'd I just tell you that?
I always talk too much
when I'm stoned.
Why'd I just tell you that?
It was stupid.
You had great grades.
One lab result shouldn't have mattered.
Except I didn't think
I deserved to be
at a top med school
in the first place.
Again.
Faking lab results is one thing.
But you needing to come down here
to destroy the records
12 years after the fact...
This isn't about med school.
You don't think you belong here.
At the hospital.
Dr. Taub,
Christopher Michael.
So this is what it comes down to
in the final hours.
Deifying some lost love.
Hoping to get her on the phone
and make everything perfect.
It's pathetic.
Either you left her for a reason
or she left you for a reason.
- A phone call is not...
- It's my daughter.
Why isn't she here?
I left my family...
When Gracie was six.
I was sort of...
forced out, actually.
After I'd had an affair
with a student.
For sex or love?
Neither.
I'd only married Gracie's mother
because of the baby.
But I didn't think
I could handle commitment,
and, like any decent academic,
I proved myself right.
And what time it is matters because?
She's a dance teacher in Atlanta.
She gets home from work at 9:00,
and I just wanted to speak to her
one more time.
That's my story.
What's yours?
Same thing, pretty much.
I'm gonna be dead in a few hours.
Your secrets couldn't be safer.
Unless you're keeping them
from yourself.
I like being alone.
At least I convince myself
that I'm better off that way.
And then I met someone
at a psychiatric hospital,
of all places.
She changed me.
And then she left.
We're better off alone.
We suffer alone, we die alone.
Doesn't matter
if you're a model husband
or father of the year.
Tomorrow will be the same for you.
But yesterday
would have been different.
Could you cook me up
a chicken sandwich?
Grill's closed.
It's important medically.
Dr. Hadley needs
a high-protein meal right now.
She doesn't like to talk about it,
but she has hypoproteinemia.
- We got chicken salad.
- Yeah. That's cold.
She needs to eat warm protein
for this disease?
Well, we could give her cold protein
whose uptake enzymes
haven't been activated,
as long as you don't mind her
risking liver and kidney failure
and eventual death.
But, it's worth it
so you don't have to flip on the grill.
You don't have
to be obnoxious about it.
How do you look...
so okay?
I spent months
wondering how I made it go bad.
If you never loved me, then...
Then I didn't do anything wrong.
Allison, come on.
It's all right.
I still don't know why I said that.
It's not even true.
I did love you.
Just...
Not in a way
that would have ever worked.
- Why not?
- Because...
everything you said is true.
I'm a mess.
I married a man I knew was dying.
So God knows how screwed up
I already was.
Him dying messed me up even more.
I pushed you out of my life.
And...
I'm unfixable.
Not you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
Truth.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
- It's not your fault.
- No, I didn't even play fair.
You asked me how my dad reacted
when I told him I was bisexual.
And the Huntington's.
- No tea party?
- I never told him.
He's been through enough.
So he just visits his heterosexual,
healthy daughter,
and you go out to dinner and a movie
- and talk about your garden?
- I work late.
He's staying at my house.
It's easier if I stay elsewhere
as much as I can.
You can't suppress your life
for his convenience.
You don't see
a little irony in that?
That's exactly
what you do for House.
When he moved in with you,
you bought a bigger place for him.
No wonder you're not dating anyone.
You're right.
That woman,
the woman I'm not involved with,
her name is Sam Carr.
But in 1990 and 1991,
it was Sam Wilson.
Your ex-wife?
No, my mother.
Yes, my ex-wife.
Ex number one.
She friended me a few weeks ago.
We started emailing.
It turns out she's recently divorced,
and I wanted to ask her out.
You can't take a woman to dinner,
or else House will go running
straight back to the loony bin?
You're not worried about House
but about yourself.
Because she's an ex.
So even dinner will mean
it's immediately serious.
What are your favorite parts
that you remember?
I liked how...
I would wake up
in the middle of the night,
you'd put your arm around me,
and you wouldn't even wake up.
I liked watching you stand up
to your dad at Christmas
when he yelled at your mom.
How you didn't even know
you were strong.
But you were.
What do you miss?
I miss a lot.
But when I think about missing you,
I think about that dance class
that we took for the wedding.
It's weird.
I think,
he's never gonna hold me
like that again.
I'm gonna miss this too.
Published in
The New England Journal at 26?
Finished all the lab work
a year earlier.
Led a group of surgeons
to fix cleft palates in Bangladesh?
What can I say?
That concert was very moving to me.
I have to take a knee.
I don't get it.
This has got to be
the most spectacular file down here.
Why are you pretending
to be ashamed?
I would trade mine for yours
in a second.
When I was in med school,
I thought I'd be House some day.
Instead,
I am a fellow working with...
working for people
years younger than me.
So...
we both have a few regrets.
You should be proud of yours.
Your life's been trending up.
No news.
How you holding up?
You let them sedate you?
- Do you have kids?
- A little girl.
I adopted her last year.
I adopted Walker
right after Donald and I got married.
What if I can never love Walker
the way I love my daughter?
Does that make me a horrible person?
Let me get you some tissues.
Did you request some extra towels?
What, why?
There are eight towels
in Sarah's room.
- There should only be four.
- House keeping handles towels.
I need you to track down their logs,
figure out who was up there and when.
- Because they got extra towels?
- Just find the logs. Now.
- Adrienne, you okay?
- Sure.
What's wrong?
Adrienne, give me your arm.
The hair on her left arm
is standing up.
Asymmetric neurological function.
She's having a pilomotor seizure.
- She seemed fine a minute ago.
- She was.
She's probably been having
complex seizures all day.
She would be basically functional,
but more or less acting on autopilot.
She probably dropped
the towels off twice.
She could have taken the baby.
We never really
did have a proper good-bye.
It's 9:00.
It's Gracie. I can't come to the phone,
so please leave a message.
I guess she's running late.
You don't seem that surprised.
That's what you expected to get.
You waited until you knew
she'd be out.
Her aunt...
said that she starts work late.
Every now and then, I just call to hear
her voice on the machine.
I was never there
when she needed me, so...
What right do I have
to need her now?
None.
Just means you're a hypocrite.
'Cause apparently you do.
Forget about rights.
Just tell her
what you need to tell her.
It's Gracie. I can't come to the phone,
so please leave a message.
This is...
your father.
I love you.
Anything?
We've covered every room
on Maldonado's logs.
Been everywhere she's been.
Where's the other cart?
Isn't there usually
another cart in here?
Anyone in there?
Lockdown's over.
I should go.
I just asked Sam to dinner.
Little baby's all growed up.
You gonna tell your dad?
I'll stop by his hotel, talk to him.
Hotel?
You said he was staying
at your apartment.
Was there any truth
in anything you said?
The part about it being
a good idea for you to call Sam.
That was true.
Good night.
Code seven has been lifted.
Repeat, code seven...
You want your file?
Good for you.
We don't have
to tell anybody what we...
- You got the patient file?
- I'll grab it.
Thanks.
See you tomorrow.
I think I'm ready
to take you up on your offer.
Lockdown ended a few minutes ago.
Yeah. I know.
I'm sorry I didn't take your case.
Me too.
Gracie...
was the cutest six-year-old
you ever saw.
Interesting night?
Interesting.
www.sous-titres.eu