previously on prison break
LJ and sara will be traded for Whistler
are we clear?
this can't be done in a week.
You have a week. That's it.
No one's ever broken out of this place before,
let alone with a week to plan, so you tell these people
I'm gonna break this guy out of here
or I'm going to die trying.
You're going to stay on as my ears.
You'll report back to me everything you hear
when I'm not around.
I know you've got a brother helping on the outside,
I know he ran into my girlfriend,
and I know he took a book from her that belongs to me.
This is what they took from me.
So let's be clear,
this is what matters to me.
Not you.
And not your book.
How's LJ? How's Sara?
They told me they're fine.
What are you not telling me?
You're not the only one affected...
They killed Sara and put her head in a box!
And they got my son!
you are running out of the time
what's that?
A rat.
J.P. Getty had a formula for success.
"Rise early, work hard,
strike oil."
Just trying to get a drink of water, Alex.
As a devoted student of your work a skills,
I-I really look forward
to progress on your plan, Michael.
I'm looking forward to you getting off my back.
Buenos, welcome to Sona.
Is that your wallet?
Dame tu billetera.
No hablo Espal, uh?
You know what I said.
No.
That's the wrong answer.
I am so ready to get out of here anytime you are.
Scofield,visita.
scofield, you have a visitor.
You look like you had a long night.
Yeah.
I spent most of it feeding chocolate to a rat.
I don't have a whole lot to work with these days.
She's got the book, man, the bird guide.
She worked it out.
So we have no leverage.
-No.  -Tell me
When you were handing over the book,
did you ask for a recent photo of LJ and Sara?
Yeah.
And where is it?
She showed me the pictures, but she wouldn't let me keep them.
Man, I'm not in a position to bargain with these people.
I mean, they're pissed.
You break out tomorrow.
Let's just focus on that.
Let's keep on track.
All right.
While I'm working from the inside,
I need you to take care of what happens
once we're outside.
We're going to need a getaway vehicle,
something inconspicuous.
Whatever you find, it has to be parked
a half mile from here by 3:00 p.m. tomorrow.
You mean a.m.
No, I mean p.m.
We don't have a choice, Linc.
I ran some tests last night.
Military jeeps patrol the perimeter at night.
There's no way of telling where they're going to be in the dark.
They were out there all night.
We need the dark, we can't just... Just...
Please.
Because we're doing this tomorrow.
In the middle of the day.
Who're you looking at?
That guy.
I know him.
McGrady, my friend, I'm going to need a watch.
Maybe two.
I'm not even going to ask why.
I'm also going to need some binoculars.
Old Guillermo has a pair.
There's no way he'll sell them to you, man.
But they shouldn't be hard to get.
Where can I find this guy?
We leave tomorrow.
This...
This is how we're getting out of Sona.
Getting out of the cell block
shouldn't be a problem.
The grate and bars are weak,
but we're going to need some kind of rope,
some kind of ladder, to let us down on the other side.
That's why I figured out the safest
line from here to the hole in the fence.
We do it in the day,
we'll only be visible to the two guard towers.
The perimeter guards are less predictable,
but they're only on at night.
Scurrying across the fld in the middle of the day?
It's the only way to avoid the jeep patrol.
Now, in the yard tomorrow, there's a soccer game at 2:00.
That should prove some distraction inside.
And yesterday when we were digging,
I saw the glare from the sun hit this guy
in the late afternoon.
Looked like he turned away,
like maybe his vision was blocked.
It's not much of a break.
No, but it is
one way to do what we need to do.
As far as thisther guard,
his weakness has yet to be termined.
If we're going to get around these guys,
we've got to get to know them.
It's not going to be easy.
There's only one real road that goes to the prison.
We don't want a real road-- that's not an option.
What?
Your brother's cutting it close.
You said a week.
Tomorrow's Wednesday, you didn't leave much room for error.
There's not going to be an "error."
Listen, I've got a lot of stuff to do and I just...
Which is why I won't waste yourime.
When Whistler's free, I need to get to him
as soon as possible.
I'm still trying to work out what's going
to happen once they get past the fence.
Once I know all the details, I'll let you...
Lincoln, calm down.
It sounds to me like you
and your brother are in over your heads.
There's a bad joke about Sara somewhere in there.
Listen...
I'll let you know all the details
on I know them, and then I'll call you.
I want this to work out just as badly as you do.
MoreI'm sure.
LJ?
LJ's fine. You have 34 hours.
What did she say?
Nothing we don't already know.
Let's get out of here; we got a lot of stuff to do.
Seir Rivera?
Who?
You're Jorge Rivera, right?
Gravedigger at Sona?
so?
Would you like a ride?
No no, someone's coming to get me in a little bit.
I had an arrangement with your predecessor.
I need you to get this inside the prison.
I don't go inside the prison.
Neither did he.
How about this?
You find a way to get this delivery
inside the prison
just this one time.
Why would I?
Becuase I would give you
five thousand dollars.
Five thousand dollars?
For just one time?
Couldn't you do that?
I think you could do it.
In this?
You're crazy!
Only you can do it.
I wouldn't let 'em see you do that.
Who?
Anyone. It's a drinking fountain.
They put their lips right on there.
You'd think it spits straight Jack Daniels.
You understand what happened, don't you?
You're a-- what's-it- called?-- a pariah.
I made the same mistake when I walked in here
tried to hang on to my wallet.
Next thing I knew, I spent the next two days kneecap deep
in human feces.
In Sona, it's every man for himself.
Here, cheese.
I'm not hungry.
Yeah, you will be.
I saw the other Americans.
So none of you have called the embassy, huh?
Us gringos ain't all butt buddies.
You want it? Cause I'll keep it.
Let's get this done.
We're gonna have to tch both guards simultaneously.
Your cell should provide
a good view of the guard I saw yesterday.
Keep track of everything he does and when he does it.
Look for that glare, see if it shows up again.
What will you be doing?
Watching the other tower from here.
While our back's turned, we're gonna need a lookout.
Well, find Mahone.
I thought we were stringing him along?
Looks like we're out of string.
Teodoro.
Si, patron?
What they say about all work d no play, huh?
Boy need his rest.
Your clientele keeps a tight schedule.
Got to make sure I see to their needs.
I gave you a more important task.
But I haven't heard a thing.
en listen harder.
Mi amor.
Ah, mi vida.
Into my office.
Sit down, watch the game.
Excuse me.
Anything yet?
Nope, not yet.
So what's your story, man?
I mean, the next chapter,
when we get out of here.
Suppose you were married to the job,
drank too much, rabid insomniac, typical lawman.
Yeah, just like you reek of live bait,
have a girl in every port,
tell fish stories
or so I've heard.
Prior to this experience,
I had the utmost respect for the law.
This guy hasn't so much has scratched his jock in an hour.
It's not gonna be easy to get around that guy.
I don't know.
We might just have a break.
I'm gonna go check on Scofield.
Sorry.
Did you see thglare?
13-- he turned to his right
and ignored everything to the west for six minutes,
as far as I could tell.
This guy thinks he's auditioning for Buckingham Palace.
He's also a sports fan.
He's got a TV.
Twice in the last four hours the signal went fuzzy.
He had to turn to adjust the antennae.
That's nothing we can count on.
True.
But there is a device we can build
out of some pretty common materials.
It's almost like a radio, except it...
transmits signals.
Pardon me.
You're the new guy.
Yeah. And who are you?
Not the new guy.
So what's your deal?
Public intoxication, tourist in trouble-- what is it?
I don't like people asking too many questions.
when I've done nothing wrong.
Oh, you're an innocent man.
As a matter of fact, yes.
Is this your first time in prison?
Uh-huh. Why? Because it's obvious--
Rule No.1
you mind your own business.
You know, you might want to do the same.
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
You got me?
Yeah.
I got you.
Go take a walk.
When'd you meet your boyfriend, Whistler?
My last year of school.
I worked in this place in San Isabel.
He used to come around
by himself and sit down in a bar.
Hitting on the waitress. That's romantic.
He is!
Every time he goes away,
he brings me back a present
like this
Those are from Sedona.
His mother lives there in a retirement home.
What's going on?!
Out of the car, Juan Bobo!
This is a private road.
I can explain. Callete!
What'd we do?
Shut your uth, American.
u?paso
This is state property! No vehicles allowed!
All roads within two miles of Sona are closed.
We, we didn't see any signs.
Where were you going?
San Isabel.
San Isabel? Yeah.
This your car?
It's my car.
The papers in the glove box.
This is why my friends don't visit Panama.
You cops bother everyone.
This road is not for tourists.
If I ever catch you out here again,
I'll remeber you.
It ain't gonna happen again.
Okay, go on.
Anda.
You okay?
Yeah. This is not gonna work.
Where's the coast from here? I don't know, maybe three miles.
All right, time for plan B. Come on.
Found some more of these.
We can make rope out of this hammock.
Come on. You don't want to go in there.
If you want to get out of this place I do.
Stay here.
he Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Move it!
Come on!
What is it, chained down?
It's hanging by a thread.
It'll have to wait.
30.
We've got less than 24 hours. We'll make it.
Tell me why.What?
What's so urgent we can't get
you out of here the day after tomorrow?
I don't know. I don't have all the answers.
You don't me, I don't know you,
but it's your job to get me out of here.
We'll come back later.
I'll take this as well.
Down here for the summer? Yep.
That's what I thought, back in 1985.
Two wives, 20 years later.
Want everything in here?
Yeah, thanks.
International waters far out?
That's 12 nautical miles.
12 nautical miles, huh?
Is that gonna do it here?
Uh, yeah.
$99.25.
Here.
All right.
Thank you.
What did you get?
Supplies. Can you pop the trunk, please?
Who am I gonna tell, honestly?
You could be a Russian spy for all I know.
Live out of this thing?
I have to be
prepared in case of an emergency.
Well, we got an emergency.
I'm not going anywhere
until you tell me where we're going.
Solana Beach. Why?
They killed Sara.
I'm trying to make damn sure they don't kill my son.
You don't think for a second
your boy's not on that list, stay here.
I couldn't care less.
What is it?
It's... Augusto.
He won't
pay the payment for you anymore.
I went to him for payment like every Monday, and...
he said it's not his responsibility
and that I should ask you.
No, no, no, no.
You tell Augusto
I don't pay for sex.
I know, I did.
But... what I do?
I don't see anyone else...
Yeah?
Well, neither do I.
You in charge of the food now?
No boss. I'm the new gravedigger.
You need to sign in
before you get on the truck.
I was just about to.
Have you read the rulebook?
Yes, sir.
Read it again.
On the other side, when we get out of here,
what's gonna happen?
We're gonna meet someone from this mpany...
Apparently.
And then they're gonna kill me.
You know that.
If they wanted to kill you,
you'd already be dead.
I don't see why they keep me alive.
It's like you said-- you've got something they want.
Once I give it to them, I'll be no use to them.
Right?
I don't have all the answers.
All I know is it's my job to get you out of here.
Let's go.
It's twofer Tuesday, my one-time special just for you.
But there's a price.
Lechero's getting pret sensitive about the cash flow.
Well, I'm a little short right now.
No worries, Alex.
I am notgonna leave you hanging, all right?
We can just start you a tab.
Think he saw us?
Guess we'll find out.
My third year in school,
we studied electrical engineering with a focus on EMPs.
That's electromagnetic pulses.
If you hook up a pow source to a transmitter,
it generates a pulse.
That pulse crashes anything electronic.
What's that, like an intro
an intro into anti-terrorist tactics?
Basically. These days,
they have to teach students how to defend
their structures.
Fortunately for us, that guard tower is...
It was engineered a long time ago.
I'm guessing you always won the elementary science fair.
Plug this in.
Did it crash the telly?
We're too far away.
But it is doing exactly what we need it to.
Okay.
Get out! Why?
They're coming in.
Ahora mismo.
Stay here. Do not let them see her.
Do not!
Colonel.
We received no word of this!
A rifle scope waseen from the tower.
Capitan Hurtado saw it with his own eyes.
That's impossible.
There is a gun in your prison,
and it was pointing at one of my men.
We are going to find it.
This looks good.
For what?
Have a seat.
What am I supposed
to doing here?
Look like you're having fun.
When was the last time you saw your son?
You know, Lincoln,
I don't automatically trust people either,
but at least I can tell when they have good intentions.
Good for you.
You know, I'm not gonna try to prove myself anymore.
You do your job, and I'll do mine.
You need something?
What? You need something?
No.
Good.
Don't you worry. It's all gonna be okay.
No, it's not. I promise you, I will not let
anyone find you in here.
Oh... Lechero hate me.
Lechero does not hate you.
You hold a very special place in his heart.
So many girls can take my place.
No, he's smart. He knows you're better than them.
You're a real woman.
A woman of her own will, her own desire.
You know what I am.
In this world, sister, we are all prostitutes.
You are a queen.
Whose cell is that?
In the corner?
Is that your cell?
You
It's mine!
It's mine.
s mine.
I found this.
It's not a weapon.
I know what it is.
Why were you watching me?
i want to ask you
one more time.
Why were you watching me?
I wasn't watching you -- I saw you.
Answer the question!
I don't know what you think you saw but i wasn't watching you.
Lie!
I wasn't watching you.
It's mine.
Why were you watching him?
I... I wasn't. I was, uh...
I was watching birds.
Yes.
See?
Why did you not speak up before?
I, uh...
I was scared.
Coward.
Hurtado! Ya. Dejelo.
Come on.
Come on!
please, please, please.
come on.
He's coming back up here.
Now, don't worry.
It's all going to be okay.
You have a little mascara right there.
You need to look pretty for Lechero.
Thank you.
Wait right here.
A patrol passed through, but they didn't stay.
Knock some things over then walked away.
I hid your woman in a safe place,
but I'd be lying
if I didn't say it was a close call.
Is she alone?
Yeah.
Hey.
Don't be afraid.
No, no, my dear.
They're gone.
I should go, too.
No, no, no. What's the rush?
Come on. No, I should
get home.
Patr,
I gave her the money.
I was going to replace it myself
at the end of the day, when I get my cut.
I just didn't get a chance to tell you.
She had no money to get home.
Is this true?
Yes.
With all due respect.
Surely you don't want your mistress travelin' broke.
She'd end up in a taxi
with no way to pay the cab fare.
Ah, you did this?
For me?
Si, patr.
Teodoro.
The one that does all
the useful things for me, huh?
And now you do the thinking for me.
No, no, it's not like that, patr--
Get the bucket.
Wash my feet.
So what do we do now?
I don't know.
Well, I'm afraid that's not good enough.
Please just give me a moment to think.
Wasting time is not an option for me, Michael.
I need to be out of here by tomorrow.
I know, just in time for be out your next fishing trip,omorrow.
or is it a bird-watching trip? I forget.
That's my trip log, I've told you.
I need to retrace my steps.
I'm doing everything they tell me, the same thing you are.
just, just leave me alone, please.
You know, before I was arrested,
a man came to my flat and took my addresses.
They know the name of everyone I care about
and how to find them.
Well, they already found everyone I care out. Okay?
If you can't get me out of here, tell me now.
because time is running out.
Huh?!
Look, it's hot today.
Yeah.
Prefer the heat than the cold any day.
You know my brother and I wanted to come
down here to Panama
and start a dive shop like the one we were at today.
My boy, he was gonna leave school and help us
start the family business.
When this is all over, why don't you do it?
Too much bad stuff's happened.
Still, you can make it work.
It's only gonna work if... if Whistler cooperates.
he plays games, people get hurt.
You understa that, right?
He doesn't want anyone to get hurt.
I hope you're right.
I want to show you something.
Our getaway vehicle.
Now,
the next time you see him,
I want you to tell him what you saw.
Tell him we're all in this together.
We're part of a team.
You understand?
Okay. Yeah.
All right, get up.
We're coming back.
No, this way.
What?
This way, come on.
Okay
If all goes well,
we'll see them tomorrow.
Job well done. Thank you.
I thought you said I was gonna get five thousand dollars.
That's what I'm talking about.
Nono, no, no, no.
You said one time.
Was it difficult?
That's not the point.
One time is one time.
This can work out for both of us.
If we're gonna do this today,
we got to replace everything we lost.
Like what?
For starters, a new exit point.
It's got to be on the south side of the building.
Look at this guy, again.
I know you, huh?
Afraid not. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're McFadden, right?
Nice, 1997?
Sorry.
You've confused me with someone else.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I swear.
You were with the ambassador.
You've mistaken me for someone else.
Chap's insane.
Come on, guys, got something to show you.
I'm sure I didn't observe the guards' behavior
in as much detail as you guys,
but I did notice something yesterday.
Right around this time.
That's the day shift.
They start by 6:00
Just keep looking, keep looking.
There.
Where'd you get your cup, Alex?
I got it in the courtyard, but apparently it's from him.
He has one in the morning and one after lunch.
Man's got to have his fix.
If we get  that cup...
We get to the man.
We got to move.