Previously on Prison Break...
I'm on it.
Is pursuing her
the best use of your time?
- It is.
- I'll let the President know.
I contact the President directly.
I'll contact her.
No family with Patoshik? Nothing?
Until about four years ago
when he killed them all.
Fernando Sucre,
he was in Las Vegas around 2:00.
Out west,
just like Bagwell and Franklin.
You know D.B. Cooper?
The money's in Utah,
and they're all going to get it.
You're one of them
Fox River boys.
Come on. You got the map?
No. Someone else does.
Before I destroyed it,
I committed it
to my photographic memory.
I have the information,
you have the manual requirements
necessary to unearth
Westmoreland's buried booty.
- Get in.
- Okay.
Should be dead ahead.
The bastards built over it.
It's gone.
We have to open up in 15 minutes.
- So, it doesn't matter. I dare you.
- I said... I said no.
I dare you. Please?
The ranch is gone, Michael.
Well, the five million might not be.
And you gonna find it how?
What, you got a divining rod
tattooed on your ass?
I don't want to hear anything out
of your mouth
other than what your photographic memory
spits out regarding that map.
You watch your tone with me, boy.
I will watch you get tossed
to the side of the road
to fend for yourself, boy.
Because if you can't remember
where that silo was,
you're worthless to us.
Yo, let me out!
Shut up!
The map!
Okay, okay, all right,
all right, all right...
Let me out !
The ranch...
The ranch was in the center of a box,
Sheep Road on one side,
Kokosing Road perpendicular.
In the center of the property
was the ranch house.
And the ranch house
was surrounded by trees.
Every tree here is a year old at most.
Except those.
Where is the silo?
In... side the trees.
I want to say on the left,
but that may have been a barn.
I remembered the best I could, gents,
but I didn't know this place
would now be smothered in tract homes,
so, you know, I'm sorry
that I'm not Rainman over here.
Alex Mahone, how are you?
Lyle Sands.
We've been briefed
on all the men at large.
The full force and resources
of the entire Salt Lake City
field office are at your disposal.
Thank you. Do you have those files
my office requested
on the D.B. Cooper case?
We're pulling them now.
And this is the D.B. Cooper case
from 30 years ago?
Correct. If I can get those files
immediately, I'd appreciate it.
Hey, sorry, but I have to ask.
Aren't you here for the Fox River Eight?
I am, and they're here in Utah
to get D.B. Cooper's money,
so how about those files, Lyle?
This is stupid.
We're gonna get made out here.
Ah, shut it. I think I remember.
If I had to bet, I'd lay it all
on the silo being on the left
of the ranch house
inside the trees.
No. It's outside the trees.
Right there.
You see those two trees?
They're shorter than the rest.
They were all planted at the same time,
but those two didn't get
as much sunlight.
Something was in their way.
The silo.
Our money should be right there,
under that garage.
You better be right, boy.
This isn't a high-end subdivision.
They slapped this place up overnight.
The silo's foundation
might still be there.
To save money, they probably just laid
the concrete
for the garage floor right on top of it.
We'll dig straight down.
If we hit the foundation, we stay.
But if not, we go.
Let's do it.
Oh, man.
Ain't no problem that a screwdriver
to her temple won't fix.
Synchro : www.sub-way.fr (V.1.20)
Transcript : FRM Team
People die all the time, boys.
Five million dollars
comes once in a lifetime.
Let me out of here, men! Come on!
Well, we got to do something.
And it's not going
to involve hurting anyone.
I got an idea.
First, we're going
to need some supplies.
110% do not agree with this.
Everybody's got to pitch in
to make this happen.
But back in the big house,
the boy proved he couldn't be trusted.
Which is why we're doing it here.
If he gets caught in town,
he ain't got a clue where the house is.
Besides, you're the one
we can't turn our backs on.
I could have died in there, man.
Well, guess what?
We need you to do something.
I need you to do something for me.
I want my cut of the money.
Well, we'll talk once
you prove we can trust you.
What do I got to do?
I want you to go back to that Garden
Center and get everything on this list.
Then gas up the car.
And we'll meet you
right back here in an hour.
- All right.
- And David...
Don't screw this up.
This ain't Fox River no more, man.
You're looking at the real deal now.
But I want my cut.
I'll be back in an hour.
Let's go.
Mistake.
Big mistake.
Oh, come on man!
I am very glad to see you.
Did you walk here?
Well, no... it's...
it's... it's just a long story, man.
Thought you were meeting up
with your family.
I met a... I met a few roadblocks.
And you?
Yeah.
Let me guess... you're going to Tooele.
Yep.
Well, it looks like we're going
in the same direction.
Hopefully we're not too late.
Can I hitch a ride?
Very well...
I'll make it worth your while.
Got some good news, sir.
Got our first tip on Patoshik.
Spotted at a burger joint
in Cedar Grove, Wisconsin.
Just hand it over
to local authorities for now.
The only thing
we're working today is Utah
and D.B. Cooper.
Got it.
Lyle.
There's a guy here
listed as having the only
D.B. Cooper bill ever found
in circulation, Harold Jenkins.
Yeah, D.B. bought gas from Jenkins
with a hundred
on the day of the hijacking.
We checked the serial numbers
and they matched.
You worked the case?
Fresh out of the academy.
And nobody's cracked it yet.
What makes you think that these escapees
know where the money is?
Because they may have been locked up
with the real D.B. Cooper.
This Jenkins from the gas station,
he still alive?
Should be. He was only 18 at the time.
Let's go say hi to him.
We're sorry. Your call cannot be
completed as dialed.
Please check the number and dial again.
Do you have updates on Sara Tancredi?
I assume that's why you're here.
Yes.
Scofield sent her a message
through the mail.
That phone number
that was disconnected...
You know, to be honest...
I was expecting to brief the President.
Yeah, about that...
Right now, as you can imagine,
Caroline's quite busy.
She's always been busy.
I've been working side-by-side
with her for 15 years.
Paul, she's the President
of the United States now.
Yes, Bill, and I helped put her there.
Well, if you'd like for her
to remain in office,
you'll take my advice
and just stay on the sidelines for now.
She needs to be completely insulated
from anything regarding Lincoln Burrows.
I want to talk to her.
You report to me now, and only me.
You're not to try and contact
Caroline again without my approval,
and you don't show up here unannounced.
Finish the job
you were given. Get Burrows.
If you're telling me the road
to him leads through
Sara Tancredi, by all means, pursue it.
And once that's been accomplished
and this whole thing goes away,
we'll go about transitioning
you back into Caroline's life.
Now do you have anything else on Sara?
The President has
unwavering faith in you.
Wants to make sure you go through
the Senate approval process
with your eyes wide open.
So what are we up against?
Key allies in the House and Senate
are Meyerhoff, Barnwell and Summerville.
We're counting on them
to sway the middle.
But who's the opposition?
Senators Blake and Killoren
have openly vocalized
their opposition to you as VP.
Any indications to why?
Political payback for the President's
vote on the energy bill last month.
Took them by surprise
and they don't like surprises.
Dad.
Lance, this is, my father Frank.
Pleasure to meet you, sir.
It's nothing to lose sleep over.
Frankly, the biggest issue
we have to address are the charges
facing your daughter.
Governor, are you with me?
Absolutely.
No, just chill, dawg.
Once we roll out, we bounce out of town,
we'll drop a dime
and they will find you.
Just be quiet. Just chill, man.
Woody?
Where you at?
I need Sheriff Williams.
Yeah, I'll hold.
When'd you learn about electricity?
I used to steal copper wiring
from transformer boxes.
Sell 'em on the docks, make a few bucks.
When you were at school, of course.
I was just looking, Pretty.
What's that old chestnut?
"I can look at the menu.
Doesn't mean I'm gonna eat."
We get in, we get the money,
we get out. That's it.
No, absolutely.
We're good.
Now it's just up to the kid.
Did you get everything?
Yeah. Yeah, I got it.
What?
Nothing. It's cool. I handled it.
Okay.
Check it.
This fool came in the shop.
He was acting all shady.
He got a bad vibe, so he picked up
his celly phone, he started
to make a call, so I popped him.
You did what?!
I hit him with a shovel, man!
I didn't know what else to do!
So I just... I tied him up
and I put him in the back room
with that other country hick.
Here we go. Here we go.
I came through, you gimp!
Who was he calling?
The sheriff.
Man, man, I... I don't know, dude.
- It just, it set off...
- Did the call go through?
- Maybe, man...
Yes. No, I don't know!
I don't know, man.
Yo, but I got the gear.
We got to move on this now.
Yes?
Sorry to bother you, ma'am.
Is your electricity out?
Excuse me.
I'm looking for a Harold Jenkins.
Right here.
Alexander Mahone, F.B.I.
I'm staying 50 feet away
from her at all times.
What the hell else does she want?
I'm not here about that.
What are you here for?
D.B. Cooper.
People still want to know
about that guy?
Unbelievable.
You worked the gas station
in American Fork where he filled up.
Yeah. Normal-looking guy.
Barely said a word.
There were some discrepancies
in the statement you filed 30 years ago.
In the report, it's noted
that you said he filled up at 7:00am,
but on another occasion,
you said it was 7:00pm.
Which was it?
Both.
He gassed up twice?
Yeah.
Full tanks both times?
Why?
A systems... what?
It's a systems diagnostics test.
Footage from our gopher cam
picked up exactly where
your line was corrupted.
And who corrupted it, you guys?
Maybe.
All I know is my supervisor called
and said he wants
me and my crew to get over here
and fix that problem
double-quick, double-time.
So... you're not
with the electric company?
No, ma'am.
Now feel free to call your company,
but I should tell you, all they'll do
is send over some tech,
maybe tomorrow if you're lucky.
And he'll spend a whole day
trying to find the problem
and another day trying to fix it.
But we're here right now
and we're ready to turn
your juice back on.
My juice?
That's right.
And...
and that's your... crew?
Yes, ma'am.
Yeah, D.B. Cooper was driving
a 1965 Chevy Nova.
There's no record on file
that Cooper even had a car.
But Charles Westmoreland did,
and the car
registered to him at the time
was a 1965 Chevy Nova
with a 16-gallon gas tank.
Back then, a Chevy that size
probably got what,
eight miles to the gallon?
Now, D.B. stopped
at the station in American Fork,
gassed up once early that day
and then came back
later that same night
and gassed up again.
Now, why would a guy headed to Mexico,
which is a straight shot south,
drive off the main road
for an all-day detour?
- The money.
- Exactly.
Cooper/Westmoreland
jumped out of a plane with $5 million.
But Westmoreland didn't have
the money on him
when he was arrested.
He ditched it before he got caught.
Give me that Magic Marker.
From American Fork,
he couldn't have gone further
than 64 miles in any direction.
I want everything
you've got in that perimeter.
Those cons are in one of these towns,
and if there's so much as a cat missing
in one of them, I want to know about it.
The defective cable
runs right beneath your garage.
We're gonna have to dig up
the floor to get to it.
Well, who's gonna pay for this
and what about
the cleanup and the repair?
Well, the company will cover all costs.
We'll just dig a small trench,
once we're finished,
we'll re-lay the cement.
It'll look as good as new.
How long is it going to take?
One way or another,
we'll be out of here today.
We really need to get started, ma'am.
We wouldn't want
a pretty little thing like yourself
sitting in the dark tonight, now do we?
Now that depends
on who I'm sitting with.
Touché.
Fine,
that's okay, y'all go ahead
and do whatever y'all need to do.
Jeanette, the noise
might be substantial.
You might wanna take in
that tennis game after all.
Oh, no it's...
It's too hot for that now.
Plus, I'm gonna keep an eye on y'all
and make sure you don't steal anything.
Ma'am.
- How are you?
- Good.
All right, where's Tweener?
He's next door plugging
in the extension cord.
We're going to have to cut up
the cement.
Yo, we gots company.
What's up, snowflake?
Well, as always, your timing is flawless.
I don't follow.
Well, let me try to explain it to you.
We're trying to run something here
and we can't have people
walking in off the street.
Okay, so you want us to leave
and then you can just mail us the check?
Sucre, I know you trust me.
And you know I'll cut you
in on that money.
But the two of you being here right now
jeopardizes everything.
I'm not going nowhere.
I want my share of the money.
Wait a minute. Hold on, man.
Ain't we did this dance before?
You know, I say I want in,
you say no.
Then I threaten to tell somebody
about what's going on here.
Then you decide to play nice
and then we're one big, happy family.
Why don't we just stop wasting time,
all right?
Thank you.
Damn, man, you still alive?
And kickin', home boy.
How'd you find us?
Man, if I can do rapid deployment
of satellite communications
for Uncle Sam all over the world...
How are you guys doing?
Who are you?
Who are they?
I had to call my supervisor.
He sent them right over.
This job is a top priority.
We want to get this done
as quickly and efficiently as possible.
Well, Jeanette, like I said,
there's a lot of work to do
and it's going to be noisy.
Oh, drinks. I forgot to ask.
We're good. Thanks.
Yo, man, this is not good.
We got her up in our grill
checking in on us all the time.
The boy is right.
And since I can't dig,
I'll volunteer to keep her occupied.
You don't touch her.
Who are you, Sister Mary Francis?
I know how to play nice.
I'll be watching.
Billy? Is that you?
Yep.
Thank you kindly.
Well now,
how did you get out of working?
Union rules.
One crew member always has to supervise.
I'll check on them in a bit.
Lemonade?
More ice.
And I like mine with a little...
But since you're on the clock,
I guess you can't...
join me?
Just two fingers.
Been a while.
Yeah?
Whiskey always makes me feel...
irascible.
I don't know what that means.
But I do like the sound of it.
Are you wearing Angel perfume?
I am.
That reminds you of an ex, I take it.
Yeah.
Now, was that good memories...
or bad memories?
Both.
Did you talk to Maricruz?
I don't want to talk about it.
I got to get some water or something.
Use the hose
on the other side of the house.
Sucre...
Down the road, if you're in trouble,
europeangoldfinch.net.
It's what we can all use to communicate.
Post a note on the message board.
What's it called?
Europeangoldfinch.net.
That's a board, right?
I got something.
It's the silo's foundation.
Hells, yeah.
Thank you, Charles.
We just need to find the edge
and dig underneath it.
We'll get the money...
hit the back roads.
What's wrong?
We gots to stop in Tooele first
and gas up the ride.
I thought you already did that.
Man,
when the Garden Center thing happened
I just forgot, all right?
I want you to go back into town...
I want you to gas up that car.
Because I'm not driving around
with millions of dollars in the trunk,
do you understand?
Man, why do I gots to do it...?
Better check in on our friend.
...about the old time.
Miss Tinsel Toes.
Billy?
Yeah.
I made you a sandwich.
Peanut butter and jelly
with the crusts cut off.
Just like you like.
I'm so glad you came back.
I don't want to say I told you so,
but that was just not the girl for you.
Where is that?
Where's what, sweetheart?
That painting.
It's Holland.
Where I grew up. You know that.
It's beautiful.
Oh, there's no place better.
It's so peaceful, so...
So protected from this crazy world.
- Operator.
- Hello, Operator?
There's an intruder in my house...
Hello, ma'am?
Ma'am? Are you there?
Is anyone there?
Heard you had some activity
in Tooele today.
A bit.
Don't see how it warrants
a visit from the F.B.I.
A stolen car was dumped
just outside of town,
belonging to a woman who went to school
in St. Louis, am I getting that right?
Yes, sir.
And then here, the owner's
girlfriend reports him missing,
and then his buddy comes by to check it
out and he... goes missing, too.
Yeah, but Woody and Chet
have been known to drop everything
and go boar hunting
when the opportunity presents itself,
and they don't tell their old ladies.
Mr. Mahone, I'll bet you my lunch money
there's nothing amiss around here.
But Woody's dad'll be
showing up soon with the keys
and... you can look for yourself.
What are you doing?
Mr. Mahone.
They're here.
Those escaped convicts.
They're here in town.
Who's there?
It's the police, ma'am.
You okay?
Yes.
Can you tell me what happened?
There was this strange man.
I made him a peanut butter
and jelly sandwich.
I thought he was Billy.
And once the kids went to sleep,
we'd take a bath.
A long... bath.
And afterwards, I'd just sit there
and watch her...
do her routine, see.
Rub a lotion on my hand
Dress up in her nighttime fineries.
Oh, you're killing me.
She had this spot on
her neck right... here.
Gave her goosebumps every time.
And that perfume...
My ex.
He was an accountant.
He was really buttoned up.
He was ram, damn, thank you, Sam.
Well, shame on him.
Why did it end
with that lady you were talking about?
Just went out separate ways.
Do you know...
what I think the best cure is
for a broken heart?
Do tell.
Get back on the bike.
Whatever bike it is.
Amen to that.
Speaking of.
Could you do something for me?
I'm certain of it.
Come here.
Only you have to be very discreet.
They don't come any discreter.
You know that... That big guy,
the strong guy that, that doesn't...
speak much?
Would you go in there
and ask him if he would like to have
a drink with me after he punches out?
Please.
You've just been playing me
this whole time, haven't you?
Come on.
Don't be like that.
Would you just go in
and ask your friend? Please?
Hey, Dad.
Sara. I've been trying to reach you.
Yeah. I've been meeting
with my defense attorneys all day.
You in Washington?
Yeah, but I'm coming back
on the next flight.
I thought you were going
to be there for a while.
No, no. Plans changed, okay?
Sara, do you remember that guy
that I met with you in your apartment?
I want you to stay away from him.
Who? Lance? From my, my group?
Yeah, yeah, that's him.
He is not who he says he is.
I found out some other things, too.
- What are you talking about?
- You were right.
I got to go.
Just one second, sir.
How can I help you?
Just put $40 on three.
I'm sorry.
- What pump was that?
- Three.
Oh, that one's been sticking.
- Okay, well, then, I'll move the car.
- Ah, no. Don't...
Don't trouble yourself. I'll have the...
mechanic come out and pump it for you.
Hey, we got a customer waiting on three!
All right, I'll be right there.
Look, man, I'm in a hurry, all right?
He'll be right out. Just one second.
Put your hands behind your head
and drop to your knees.
Drop!
Where are they?
Where... are... they?
All right, man.
One hand or not, I think Hillbilly
needs to be up ahead digging.
What you think?
Good man.
What the hell are you doing up here?
I'm sorry, Jeannette.
I just didn't see you downstairs.
I heard something.
I apologize for barging in.
Don't bother. She's got the hots
for the big, strong one.
I'm sorry, Jeannette. We're gonna...
We're gonna get back to work now.
No, I think y'all are done,
and I think y'all need to leave now.
We're almost finished.
No, I think you are finished, okay?
And I want you to leave my house now.
Sucre, check it out.
Cop.
Thank God.
Where are you going?
- Let her go!
- Oh, God.
She's our only way out of this, pretty.
Don't say a word, you old whore,
or I'll cut your throat out.
Transcript: FRM Team www.sub-way.fr