- Previously on The O.C.:
- Looks like I'm dateless.
- We'll be your date, right?
- Yeah, right.
The guy seems cool, right?
- We don't have a lot in common.
- Besides your girlfriend.
- So you chose Anna?
- Kind of, yeah.
- Can we still all hang out?
- Sure.
All this talk about plans,
about growing up, it's a routine.
You're not even nice to Kirsten.
She's the reason we put up with you.
- Hey!
- I'm a cop. He tried to buy coke from me.
- You must like me to get me out of jail.
- That was Sandy.
- You gonna tell her?
- You are.
- Howdy.
- Hey.
Sorry to just pop in.
Is it okay if I come in?
Yeah, sure. Of course.
It's just temporary.
The place. It's just temporary.
- My dad lost his job, so my parents...
- I don't judge.
I do, however, apologize.
- The other night, Marissa, was...
- It's okay. Really.
No. No, it's not.
I hit rock bottom.
A new low, even for me.
But it was eye-opening.
A call to arms. I called my parents.
I came clean about everything.
And they were so supportive.
I talked to my sponsor.
I'm going to meetings again.
And I totally was honest with Natalie
about all our issues.
We're getting back together.
Wow. That's amazing.
And it never would've happened
if Ryan hadn't come to my rescue.
He called Mr. Cohen.
I mean, busted trying to buy coke?
I should still be in jail.
Ryan helped me get a second chance.
I want to say thanks.
Oh, so do you want his number?
I want to take you and him
to Palm Springs.
My family has a place there, right on
PGA West. It'll be great. It'll be great.
We can bring all your friends.
Seth, Anna, Summer.
Even Luke.
You can meet my folks, meet Natalie.
Palm Springs?
Oh, it's so much fun.
The weather there is perfect.
- Do you golf?
- No. Not really.
I'll teach you. Ryan too.
Well, I do really want
to meet Natalie.
She's dying to meet both of you guys.
A little getaway, just the gang.
On me.
- It's the least I can do.
- It sounds amazing.
You know, let me
just call Ryan and ask him.
All right, knees bent.
Not quite that much.
Back straight,
eyes right over the ball.
Feet a little closer together.
Just off your left foot. There you go.
Not quite that close together,
but that's okay.
All right, just let it hang
like a pendulum.
Nice and easy.
Nice and easy. Keep breathing.
Nice...
I'll stop.
I'll just go right over here.
I got it.
- All right, one more.
- No. No more.
Come on, you were so good
at the driving range.
- I don't play golf.
- Not true. You just don't play well.
You know, there's more to do
in Palm Springs than play golf.
- You can spa.
- I don't spa.
You don't play golf, you don't spa.
What do you do?
What exactly do you do,
besides musicals and punching people?
- Well, he's very good with the ladies.
- The ladies.
- He's very good with the ladies.
- Very good with the ladies.
- He's right here holding a golf club.
- Yeah, but you don't know how to use it.
Which is why I'm not going
to Palm Springs.
Hey. Yes, you are going
Listen to me.
You did something nice for Oliver.
Now he wants to repay you by taking us
to his mansion in Palm Springs.
Without you, there is no deal.
Why can't you understand?
- He has a mansion on a golf course?
- And a ski chalet in Mammoth.
- I guess sometimes it's good to be Oliver.
- Sometimes it's great to be Oliver.
But you or I don't care
about those things, do we?
- Or Marissa. I don't think she cares either.
- You think?
I don't know. But even if she's
a little bit impressed, look over there.
Who's got himself a pool house?
With ocean views.
Here, take another shot.
Nice and easy.
- So Oliver's parents are gonna be there?
- Yeah.
- Have you met them?
- No.
But, if they're anywhere
near as cool as Oliver...
I don't do nice and easy.
- Do we trust this Oliver kid?
- No. Not at all.
But we trust our guys,
and his parents are supposed to be there.
- And Seth knows to call hourly?
- Yeah, and...
...we're just gonna worry
all weekend.
They're golfing.
When we gonna get you
on the golf course?
Not today.
Do you know
who's coming home today?
God, the ugly Americans are coming back.
When do your father and Julie get in?
They arrive from Paris
this afternoon.
After confirming Europe's worst
suspicions of Americans, I'm guessing.
Well, I'm guessing that this means
that Hailey will be on the way out.
What's she gonna do? Hit your dad up
for a blank check and then take off?
Was there ever any doubt?
I mean, last time she was gone
for two years. This time it could be three.
Who knows what trouble
she can get into.
- Morning.
- Hey, Hailey. Can I get you anything?
I got those pumpkin muffins.
And there's coffee
and there's orange juice without pulp.
- Dad comes back today, huh?
- Right. Yes, he does.
- So, what time will we be seeing him?
- Dinner. Seven.
I'm sorry, I'll have to miss that.
Julie Cooper's not coming, is she?
I can't believe Dad's with her.
She's only with him for his money.
And that is such
an unattractive quality.
- Pumpkin muffin?
- Yes, darling?
- I think it'll be fun.
- You do?
What could be more fun than joining
you guys for Couple Fest 2004?
You and Ryan, Oliver and Natalie,
Anna and What's-His-Face Cohen.
Me and Luke.
God, it should be all-time.
It won't be like that. It'll be a chance
to get out of town, hang out. It'll be fun.
What's more fun than watching
some nerdy neurotic bat...
...his eyelashes at his pixie chick?
So clearly you're okay
with being just friends with Seth.
- Clearly.
- I was being sarcastic.
So was I.
Which we never were before Cohen
showed up and taught us all irony.
- Jackass.
- Hey, Summ.
Look, if it's too hard to be around him,
then why go? Why do this to yourself?
Because I told them
that I was fine with it.
I told them I was cool
just being their friend.
I have a reputation.
- And I can't sabotage the trip from here.
- Summer.
Okay, what do you think about
laxatives in his coffee, huh?
No. Okay, dead frog
in his X- Men Underoos?
That's good. No.
No. I've got it.
While he's sleeping,
I slip his hand in warm water.
It makes you pee your bed.
Anna wakes up, sees he's a bed wetter...
...and that is awesome!
That is just...
...awesome.
- I've lost my mind, haven't I?
- Yeah, little bit.
And over Seth Cohen.
Jimmy. Hey, I'm glad I ran into you.
We're still on for dinner tonight, right?
Dinner? Yeah.
You okay?
No, I'm not really.
I just got turned down
for a manager's position in this place.
Apparently, that kid is better suited
to the rigors of the job than I am.
We should reschedule.
I'm not feeling social.
We can't reschedule.
The Lighthouse closes down
tonight forever.
It's the last chance to get
the best chicken parmigiana around.
First The Lighthouse leaves Newport
and then me. How poetic.
- What do you mean?
- There's nothing here for me.
There's no opportunities,
no second chances.
I got a brother in Phoenix.
He called me this week and...
- You can't leave.
- Well, I can't stay.
I'm headed to work.
I know we have positions available.
No, Sandy, you can't. You've done...
It'll be nothing glamorous, just entry-level.
Paralegal work, that kind of thing.
Thanks. I mean, whatever it is.
Just as long as I can stay with Marissa.
I can't afford to support
the both of us much longer.
- We'll figure it out.
- Thanks.
You can't bail on me tonight, because
I'll be stuck with Hailey and Caleb.
- It's the least you can do. All right.
- Yeah. Thanks.
- Hey.
- Hi.
All right. And so it begins. Guess I'm
just gonna have to get used to this.
Seth's in his room.
It's upstairs to the left, right?
I'm just gonna make sure he's packed,
so he doesn't hold us up.
You know, we need
to be nice to Summer.
She's afraid this weekend is just gonna be
a bunch of couples doing couple-y stuff.
And it's not?
So we'll be hanging out with,
say, Oliver?
Oliver and Natalie. They made up.
- Do you have a problem with Oliver?
- No.
I mean, a guy shows up
out of nowhere...
...and suddenly he's hanging
around all the time.
Yeah, a guy shows up out of the blue,
knows no one, abandoned by his family.
Sound familiar?
A little bit.
Look, you did something nice for him,
and now he wants to repay you.
- By playing golf?
- Yeah. Well, it'll be fun.
You've never seen me play golf.
Then I guess
it'll be especially fun for me.
I love Palm Springs.
A little golf, a little shvitz.
I don't know.
It all sounds kind of old.
Yes. Anna, it does sound old.
And somewhere inside me there's
an old Jewish man who's very excited.
- That came out a little disgusting.
- Kind of.
But, seriously,
there's the geriatric part of me...
...that actually loves
a good early-bird special...
...a little bit of shuffleboard,
some mahjong.
Well, when you put it that way.
Seriously, think about it.
Most old people are too actually old
to enjoy being old.
Not me, though. I'm ready to retire
right now to a life of leisure.
- Palm Springs is my Mecca.
- Well, what I'm looking forward to...
...is a weekend alone
without our parents.
I see where you're going with this.
We can have dinner as early as we want.
It'll be a couples' weekend.
We can have our own room.
- Be still, my pacemaker.
- You dirty old man.
Hey, if the orthopedic shoe fits...
Hello, friends.
Are you guys almost ready to go?
- Yeah, totally.
- Hey, Summer.
Well, that is just great, you guys.
Sorry. God, Anna, it looked like
you were doing so well too.
- Don't worry about it.
- Thanks for being so forgiving.
We are gonna have so much fun
this weekend. All of us hanging out.
As friends.
- Did you rob a liquor store, Luke?
- You can't play golf without a buzz on.
Hey. Good tip, Bagger Vance.
A blender. Nice thinking, Cohen.
Yeah, no. It's actually a humidifier.
I get nose bleeds.
- How romantic.
- I think it's sweet.
- It'll make our room a tropical paradise.
- It will.
You know, it is so nice how you find all
of Cohen's weaknesses so adorable.
I'm not weak, okay?
I'm just delicate.
Well, looks like you and I
are the only ones without anyone.
Okay, I'm just gonna lie down
in the driveway.
Just back your truck right up over me.
- What's up, guys?
- Hey.
- What's the matter?
- It's Natalie. It's over.
I don't know. Sorry.
Maybe we shouldn't go.
Yeah, maybe we shouldn't.
- What happened?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
No, you need to. And, you know what,
we need to get out of town.
I mean, maybe we could talk
about it on the ride down.
Well, is that okay?
If I ride with Oliver?
- Or maybe we could all go together?
- No, you guys go. I'll see you down there.
Hey, Chino!
Why don't you ride with me.
- Can I ride with you guys?
- Yeah, sure.
Shotgun.
Thanks for understanding.
Dad. Julie. You're early.
Bonjour, Kiki.
- Cheese wheel? It's brie.
- Oh, thanks.
- How was France?
- Aside from the French...
Where's Hailey?
She's showering, I think.
I wasn't expecting you guys so soon.
He couldn't wait to see his precious
Hailey. Couldn't even let me shower.
How is she? How's she looking?
Too thin?
She looks good. Her spirits are high.
- She's high?
- No, her spirits. Her mood. She's up.
- So she's on uppers?
- No, she seems balanced.
- You changed your hair.
- Do you like it? Isn't it Fran Ìais?
- Cal says he doesn't like it.
- Hey, Dad.
Hailey.
It's great to see you.
- Julie. Your hair.
- Hailey. You're here.
I haven't seen you since...
How long has it been?
Dad, are you gonna
start with me already?
Fair enough. Just tell me
what you been up to.
- All your adventures.
- I thought we could swing by the house...
Kiki, could you make us some lunch?
I'm starved.
So tell me about Costa Rica.
How about lunch? We have brie.
- Brought enough beer?
- Oh, you never know, buddy.
You never know.
- Hey. You made it.
- Yeah.
We tried following you,
but it was hard to keep up.
Sorry. I guess I got all wrapped up
in my saga. I got a little distracted.
This place is awesome.
Where's the fridge?
- I don't want these to get skunked.
- Yeah, I'll show you the kitchen.
- Think you brought enough beer, man?
- Everybody keeps saying that.
- How was it?
- It was okay. We talked.
He talked mostly.
He just wanted someone to listen.
How's he?
He's a little fragile. But, hey,
I think getting out of town will help.
Hope you guys weren't talking
about me when I was gone.
Sorry for taking your girlfriend away from
you. But don't worry, she's all yours.
- I wasn't worried.
- Right.
Okay...
I was trying to give you
some culture, Cohen.
The audio version of The
Da Vinci Code is not culture.
- Yeah, well, it's a true story.
- Hey.
God!
Hey, Dad. How are you doing? Six calls
in two hours. That's a new record.
Yeah. No. We...
We're still fine,
believe it or not. Okay.
Okay, what I can do, then,
is call you from every hole. Cool?
Okay, great. Bye.
Where are your folks?
Yeah, their plane got delayed
in Zurich.
I don't think they're
gonna make it this weekend.
- Welcome to their humble abode.
- Thanks, man.
Now let's get everyone settled
before we hit the links, huh?
I set up two tee times. I figured Seth,
Summer and Anna could be a threesome.
Let me show everyone to their room.
And last but not least...
Oh, I forgot this is the room
with the two twins.
Do you want to switch rooms?
Or we could push them together?
Oh, no, this is fine. It's great.
- I'm just gonna go change.
- Okay.
I'll help you with the beds.
Hopefully it won't be
too uncomfortable.
All right, thanks.
I really appreciate you being so cool
about Marissa and I being friends.
Well, yeah, no problem.
I mean, with everything you two
just went through with Luke...
...the last thing you need
is another guy not to trust.
- With Luke?
- Yeah.
You thinking that maybe he and Marissa
were getting back together.
That was a while ago.
I'm not judging. I mean, if anyone
should have trust issues...
- What does that mean?
- Just your background.
Marissa was filling me in
on some of the details on our ride down.
- She was?
- Yeah.
But, I mean, just in terms of how amazing
it is that you're so healthy.
Well-adjusted. Considering.
Considering?
- So how do I look?
- Perfect.
Yeah, great.
Sandy Cohen working on a Saturday.
Tom Wellington, how are you?
Playing catch-up, huh?
Buying some time
away from the wife and kids.
How touching.
Listen, I got a question for you.
Celeste in Records is going on maternity
leave, and we haven't found anyone yet.
- You know Jimmy Cooper, right?
- Jimmy Cooper?
- Yeah.
- Are you out of your mind?
This is one of the most
reputable firms in the county.
What's it gonna do for our profile,
hiring a notorious criminal?
There's no such thing
as bad publicity.
Before he went down,
there was no one smarter than Jimmy.
- Everyone in this town loved him.
- Till he ripped them off.
He made a mistake, he's paying it off.
He doesn't deserve a second chance?
Not in our firm.
Not in this lifetime.
The best thing you can do around Jimmy?
Stand upwind. Don't get his stink on you.
He's a good guy, Tom.
Yeah? Well, then, why don't you
go into business with him?
She so looks like Mom, it's scary.
He takes one look at Hailey
and he can't say no.
And right now,
she's telling him of her plan...
...to help the indigent population
of some depressed country.
And all she's looking for
is some all-expense-paid bender...
...to Amsterdam or Thailand.
It's amazing he can't see it. She's only
being nice to him for his money.
Every time she vanishes,
it's for a little while longer.
The trips get wilder and wilder.
One of these days,
I don't think she's coming back.
You know you're the only one
he listens to, Kirsten.
If you're really scared
she's gonna disappear again...
...you need to stop him
from letting her.
- How's this?
- Pretty good.
You just gotta get your hips
into it a little more.
You know, you gotta go:
I think she's got the idea.
Rock and fire.
For a beautiful girl,
that is one ugly swing.
Got to follow that, huh?
Don't suppose you were using
creative visualization?
My face as the golf ball?
Can't wait to see
your short game, buddy.
- I think your ball's in the trees.
- That's bad, right?
Thanks for carrying my golf bag,
Cohen. I really think I threw out my back.
If your back hurts,
why don't we take a golf cart?
What? Are you, like, against nature?
- This isn't nature. This is a golf course.
- I have a hernia.
You guys, this way we can spend
more time together as friends.
How come when she says "friends,"
it sounds like a threat?
It's her inflection.
What? We did say we'd try and be
friends. Who's she gonna talk to? Luke?
The guy only recently
learned how to walk upright.
Cohen...
...could you help me find my ball?
Anna, stay back.
There might be poison ivy.
- Summer, I don't wanna get poison ivy.
- Cohen, I thought you were my friend.
Okay.
Looks like Summer's not
the only one who lost their balls.
- Too bad.
- I could hurt that guy.
So could I.
Am I trying too hard with him?
All I want is to be friends.
I just feel like he hates me.
No. I mean... He likes you.
- He just...
- Right. Trust issues.
- Can't win them all, I guess.
- Hey, nobody's looking.
Oh, nice shot, buddy!
Okay. I think we've torn up
the course long enough.
Last guy back buys the first round.
Come on.
Step on it. Come on.
Come on, they're gaining on us.
You better run!
Look out! Ryan, stop, stop!
Dude, nice driving.
You made that thing dance.
What the hell is your problem, man?
Hey, man...
- I thought we were just joking.
- Yeah. Good joke.
- Come down here, tell me another one.
- Oh, sorry, man.
See you back at the house, okay?
Are you okay?
You know, he was just playing.
Fine.
That guy was not playing.
- Hey.
- You look nice.
You look like you're not
having dinner with your father.
I'm gonna give them one-on-one time.
It's not a dinner I want to be at.
I feel the same way about my meal.
Jimmy's right. He is done here.
His best shot is starting over
somewhere else.
So we'll have a nice meal, a couple
of drinks and talk about his next move.
Alcohol? Yes. Inspired.
How do you think
I got you to marry me?
So you were drunk.
Explains everything, Kiki.
Hey, Dad.
It is always such a pleasure.
You two have the time of your lives.
- You're not dressed.
- I'm not going.
- We both know why Hailey's here.
- She wants to catch up...
...with her family.
- Dad, you honestly don't believe that.
Don't be jealous of your sister.
I love both my daughters equally.
You don't, but that's okay.
What's not okay is that she wants to take
advantage of how much you love her.
- You want me to cut her off?
- I know you do too.
Dinner at 6, in bed by 8.
Anna, my old Jewish man
is very happy right now.
It's pretty humid, Seth.
I think you could stop futzing.
No. No, I can't. Futzing's what I do,
my darling. Besides, I almost have it.
And there we go.
She's purring like a kitten.
So, Cohen.
You and me, alone in a bed.
Polyfill. It's not as comfortable as down,
but it's good for our allergies, our sniffles.
And this bed, huh?
It's Posturepedic for my back.
And your back.
- Yes?
- My catheter fell out.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Luke's hogging the remote,
and it's either football or porn.
So could I watch TV with you guys?
- We're not watching TV, Summer.
- Yeah, we were about to go to bed.
- But it's 8:00. What are you, 70?
- On the inside, yes.
I thought this was a weekend
where we could hang out as friends.
- It is.
- Totally.
Oh, I get it.
It's, like, specific friend hours, right?
Whatever works for you?
A friend on-off switch.
A friend appointment book.
- Do I schedule friend time in advance?
- No, that is not it at all.
- It's not it.
- Great. You guys.
That's great.
That Enrique is so hot.
I mean, can you imagine
being with a guy with abs like that?
Yeah, apparently not.
You don't have to do that.
I don't mind.
Well, at least let me help.
- Where's Marissa?
- Getting changed for the hot tub.
You going in?
Right.
Can...? Can we just start over?
Start over?
Yeah, I feel like
we got off on the wrong foot.
And I wanna make this right. Get this
thing straight, so we can be friends.
What can I do?
Next time you wanna be
alone with my girlfriend...
...let me know so I can stay home.
This always happens.
Natalie. My friends at Pacific.
And now you.
I'm so stupid!
- Take it easy.
- Damn it!
Everybody who knows me for more
than five minutes ends up hating my guts.
- That's not true. Nobody hates your guts.
- What's going on?
We were... We were talking.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm...
I'm gonna go get some
fresh air and...
- I'll get some stuff for breakfast.
- I'll go too.
No, just... Just stay with Ryan.
I'll be back soon. Just...
Just leave the kitchen, man.
Everything's okay.
You managed to drive him
out of his own house?
I don't know.
We were talking, and he went off.
What were you talking about
that was so upsetting?
- You.
- Me?
You and him.
You know what? Oliver's got problems,
but you're the one who's paranoid.
- What's your problem?
- I don't know.
Maybe that you spent the ride
telling him about me.
I wasn't. I was talking about my life.
And you're part of my life.
You know what? I don't understand
what's going on with you.
- There's gotta be more I can do.
- Sandy, you've done everything you can.
- No, no.
- You know what?
You're right, it's for the best.
Like you said, I can start over,
have a new life.
I never really wanted to be
a financial planner. Or a thief.
Okay, so figure out right now.
What is it you really wanna do?
What I really wanna do is not be
40 years old, divorced, with two kids...
...and trying to figure out
what I really want to do.
- What is it you used to want to be?
- A pilot.
You know, I always liked
stewardesses. You?
I always wanted to be left fielder
for the New York Yankees.
It was that dream that
carried me through law school.
The most enjoyable job I ever had,
actually, was working here.
Yeah. I managed this place
the summer I married Julie.
- And look at it now. It's closing.
- I mean, John Wayne used to come here.
- Gary Cooper.
- Yeah.
This is the real deal, you know.
This is the last bit of old Newport.
Look at it, all it needs
is just a little facelift.
The land value alone would be enough
to secure a decent renovation loan.
You know, you update the menu a little
bit, you bring back happy hour, it'd be...
- It would be fun.
- The kids would come in. It'd be fantastic.
I mean, a lot more fun
than whatever...
...high-priced nuisance lawsuit
I got waiting for me on my desk.
A lot more fun than moving
to Phoenix without my kids.
What?
Katie!
Two more martinis, please.
Egg McMuffins.
- Sounds so good.
- Why can't they serve those all day?
Totally. Like, what technological
innovation is preventing that?
They can put a man
on the moon, correct?
And they can't serve
an Egg McMuffin past 10:30 a.m.
Can't figure it out.
It doesn't make sense.
Cabbage Patch Kids.
They still sell those? I don't get the legend
of the cabbage patch. It freaks me out.
What? Babies harvested
from the heads of cabbage?
- Exactly.
- What's so freaky about that?
It's all about
some child-slavery ring.
It's disgusting.
It makes me want to vomit.
Smurfs, dude.
Do you know how tall they were?
Three apples.
- Really?
- Three apples.
There should be a channel on television,
I think, of us watching television.
- We're that good.
- Yeah.
Yeah, you are. You're so that good.
Your whole witty-banter thing
is so cute, you guys.
You guys are like brother and sister.
Yeah, you guys could totally
be related.
I'm gonna go to bed.
I'm going to bed too.
Hey.
- He's not back yet?
- No. And he still hasn't called.
I'm really worried.
It's been two hours.
- What's wrong with him, exactly?
- He's been battling depression for a while.
And he's had some
substance-abuse problems.
I'm sorry.
I just hope he's okay.
It's him.
- Hey.
- Marissa...
...something happened.
What's wrong? What is it?
- I messed up real bad.
- Where are you?
- What did you do?
I just drove back to Newport...
...and took a whole bunch of pills.
Whole bunch.
- Call an ambulance.
- No, no. No doctors.
- Please. Just...
- I'm so scared right now.
Maybe I could throw them up.
Do that.
Just get them out of your system.
I'll try.
But...
...do you think you could...
...come back?
I'm sorry, but I am so scared.
Okay, we're leaving right now.
See you soon.
- He's not okay.
- He just took a bunch of pills.
- He's not picking up.
- It's okay. You just talked to him.
That was 20 minutes ago.
Hi. Marissa Cooper
for Oliver Trask, please.
- I thought you said he was okay.
- He said he was.
He said he spent the last hour
in the bathroom...
...getting the pills
out of his system.
- But if that's true...
- What?
Why isn't he picking up?
What the hell did you say to Dad?
I know you're behind this.
Hailey, we had a conversation
and we both agreed...
How convenient that the one thing you
two agree on is how to screw me over.
- Hailey, you don't have to do this.
- I thought this is what you wanted.
Me not taking Dad's money
or taking up room in your house.
I never said that you couldn't stay.
No. You said you wanted me to live my
own life, be on my own, be independent.
Then you went and sabotaged
my relationship with Dad.
What relationship with Dad? You take
his money and then you take off.
My relationship with Dad
is between me and Dad.
- Was between me and Dad.
- I just don't wanna see you in trouble.
Well, now you won't have to.
There's my cab.
Oh, Hailey, where are you gonna go?
You don't have any money.
Yeah, well, whose fault is that?
I'll find another way to get by.
- You could stay here and work for Dad.
- Why?
So I can be as independent as you are?
Living off his money
in the McMansion he built you?
I'm sorry...
...but you were right.
I need to have my own life.
And the only way that I can do that
is to get as far away from Dad...
...and as far away from you as I can.
I'll see you.
Oliver. Open up, please.
It's me.
- We have to call security.
- I'll go.
Oliver. Oh, my God. You're okay.
Yeah, kind of.
- You all right, man?
- Yeah. A little embarrassed.
- When you didn't pick up the phone, l...
- I was in the shower. Sorry about that.
I got kind of messed up,
but I'm good now.
Yeah.
You guys should go,
enjoy the rest of the weekend.
What are you talking about?
We're not going anywhere.
So, what did you take exactly?
I don't know.
A bunch of sleeping pills,
some painkillers.
Well, how many?
I don't remember. But I got them
all out of my system, I promise.
Well, did you drink any water?
Because you're probably dehydrated.
You know, we should call room service.
You want any ginger ale or Gatorade?
Maybe we should take him
to the emergency room. I mean...
...he swallowed all those pills.
If they were in my system,
I'd have felt them by now.
Yeah, but why take any chances?
We can take you now.
The thing is, if we go
to the emergency room...
...they'll put me under suicide watch
for 72 hours.
They'll call the cops, and then
they'll call my parents in Zurich.
I mean, the truth is that I'm fine.
Really. I just want to just crawl into my
bed and forget this day ever happened.
- Sandy.
- Hey, you're awake.
Oh, shoot!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Are you drunk?
- Don't worry, I took a cab.
- Yeah, so did Hailey.
Dad cut her off, and she cut me off.
Oh, I'm sorry.
So how was your night?
That good, huh?
You know, I'm not sure, but...
I think Jimmy and I might have
gone into business together tonight.
Really?
And what kind of business is that?
The restaurant business.
- Oh, you are drunk.
- In an adorable way, I think. Yeah?
- And what about the firm?
- They'll have my body.
And so will you, by the way.
But the restaurant will have
my soul and my income.
- And my savings.
- How can you do that?
Look, I'm making more money
than I ever made in my life...
...and I'm having way less fun.
I used to help people for a living,
you remember that.
I'll tell you, your buddy Jimmy Cooper,
man, he needs some help.
Oh, man, if he doesn't get a job,
he's gonna have to leave town.
I don't want him to leave town.
You know, it's been a long time
since I've had a friend in Newport.
I don't want to have to find
another friend in Newport. Am I crazy?
Oh, I'm crazy.
You have to be crazy
to be in the restaurant business.
But I think it's great
that you wanna help Jimmy.
Well, you know...
And be friends after all this time,
it means a lot to me.
Sandy?
They're sleeping.
Hey, we're home.
Thanks for the ride, buddy.
Great weekend, huh?
- Bye, Summer.
- Bye.
See you guys. Have fun. Drive safely.
So you're into Cohen, huh?
It must be kind of weird
to see him with somebody else.
- It was for me with Marissa.
- Whatevs.
I'm over it. Moving on.
Ready for my next victim.
Well, just for the record...
...whoever he turns out to be,
he's a lucky dude.
You're looking pretty hot
these days, Summer.
Real hot.
Thanks.
Oh, my God!
Oh, God, I'm sorry, Luke. You're cute
and everything, but there's just no way.
No worries.
What are you doing?
What are you looking for?
Nothing. Is he gonna be all right?
Yeah. I think so.
I told him I'd stay tonight.
- What?
- Well, I can't leave him alone.
What if he tries it again?
- Lf he tried it the first time.
- What?
What if he didn't try
to kill himself tonight?
- What?
- He wouldn't go to the hospital.
Maybe he didn't want to be
shipped off to an institution.
Maybe he belongs there.
I mean, what kind of person does this?
- No, not... I didn't mean...
- You should go.
- You weren't trying to kill yourself.
- Maybe Oliver wasn't either.
But he's my friend,
and I can't leave him alone tonight.
So, you know what, just go home,
and I'll see you in the morning.
Sorry to interrupt.
I just want to say thanks, Ryan.
For everything, man.
Sorry for ruining your weekend.
Good night.
I'll call you tomorrow.