- Previously on The O.C.:
- How could he do it?
- Lf Marissa found out...
- No, she cannot find out.
You have sex with Julie today?
- We've got a connection.
- It's gonna end.
Oh, my God. That's Hailey.
- My mom's gonna freak.
- So don't tell her. Not that she'd care.
- She would if she knew.
- They found Hailey working as a stripper.
- So you wanna come home?
- Yeah.
You're dead! Don't ever come home.
You hear me?
- It never could've worked.
- You're breaking up with me?
I'm done having sex with Julie Cooper.
- Marissa.
- I've gotta go.
Think. Where else could she be?
I don't know, man.
We've been all over town. Twice.
I'm sorry, I just don't know
what to do at this point.
We're not giving up.
We just gotta figure this thing out.
All right, when she left she was upset.
So she probably went somewhere
she would feel safe, right?
Yeah, well, somewhere no one's even
gonna think to look for her.
- Including us, apparently.
- Well, maybe she called. Where's Cohen?
Yeah. Maybe she called,
and he went after her.
Maybe he's asleep. Hey, Cohen.
- Get up.
- It's my precious. You can't have it.
- Hey, what's wrong?
- You were asleep, that's what's wrong.
- I was adjusting my back.
- Did Marissa call?
I would've heard the phone even
if I was sleeping, which I wasn't.
I was adjusting my back.
There's a missed call, though,
which is weird... Okay.
Meanwhile, Ryan and I are driving
around all night like idiots.
Well, none of this would've happened
if it wasn't for you, so...
Shut up. It was an accident.
Did you accidentally sleep with Marissa's
mom or accidentally tell Marissa?
- I'm in no mood.
- Keep it in your boardshorts next time.
That was her.
- What'd she say?
- Not much.
Just that she's okay.
And not to try to follow her.
Where is she?
- She's not here.
- Why don't I believe you?
Luke.
What's going on in here?
Marissa took off
when we got back from L.A.
- She ran away.
- Why? What did you do to her?
- I didn't do anything, you did.
- What?
- They know.
- Shut up, Luke.
They saw us outside the motel.
Marissa knows too.
Will you boys excuse us, please?
Ryan and I need to have a talk.
- Whatever you think you know about me...
- I don't care about you.
I just wanna get her back home safe.
- You really don't know where she is?
- I know she's okay.
She left a message
saying not to look for her.
So, what am I supposed to do?
Last time she took off, she almost died.
I'm gonna call the police.
Yeah, what are you gonna tell them
when they ask why she left?
- I have to at least call her doctors.
- So you can have her locked up again?
If that's what it takes, yes. I will not
have her hurting herself anymore.
Maybe you should've thought of that
before you slept with her ex-boyfriend.
I would love to stay
and chat with you, Ryan...
...but I have to find my daughter.
Not if I find her first.
- So, what's the GP, RA?
- I have no idea what you just said.
Game plan, Ryan Atwood.
- Just using initials now?
- They save time.
- Not if you have to translate them.
- GP.
- Game plan?
- Good point.
You gonna ride around Newport
looking for Marissa's car...
...while I go talk to Summer?
- You have a better idea?
Not yet. But maybe
after a nice, healthy...
...massively over-the-top breakfast.
Hey, guys. We've got eggs, waffles,
three different kinds of pancakes.
- Wow, Hailey, what's the occasion?
- I was in rough shape last night.
I didn't get a chance to thank you guys
for convincing me to come home.
So, hungry?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my... What is going on here?
Mom, Hailey made three different kinds
of pancakes and waffles.
They're deliciously redundant.
Have a blueberry, they're good.
Coffee? Here, have a seat.
Let me just get this out of your way.
Hailey. The want ads already?
Yeah, it's mostly restaurant gigs.
But it's not like I have any other
marketable skills, so...
I know of a hostess position available.
A speakeasy I call The Balboa Lighthouse.
That's a good idea, except you have
to ask Sandy when he's in a good mood.
We have to get all the bread
out of the house.
Now's not really a good time.
Hailey made three different
kinds of pancakes.
Enjoy them now. We only have
two hours to unleaven the entire kitchen.
- What does that mean?
- My mother's plane lands at noon.
If she sees us eating pancakes on the
first day of Passover, she'll plotz.
I love when the nana comes,
and Dad's all Jewish again. I have to go.
- Yeah, me too.
- Yeah, I should probably get dressed.
Honey, do we have any brisket?
The Ackermans are looking after the
food for the Seder. We're bringing wine.
Right. Except we're not going
to the Ackermans'.
- Since when?
- Since I told Ma we're having Seder here.
- You what?
- Which, if she asks...
...is something we do every year.
I also told her you converted.
I'm kidding.
About the conversion part.
Honey, you're not gonna have
to lift a finger. I'll shop.
She'll cook. The kids will help. Hailey and
Jimmy'll be here. Ryan can invite Marissa.
- Seth can invite Summer.
- What am I gonna do?
Sit back and let your mother
take over the entire house?
She was gonna do it anyway. At least
this way, we get a decent meal out of...
- Are you done with these?
- Sandy, don't.
We don't know where she is,
but she called to say she's okay.
I know, she called me too.
- What? Summer, why didn't you tell me?
- She told me not to.
- Summer, if you know where she is...
- I don't. I swear.
She's gonna be fine.
She just needs time.
Me and Ryan don't have time.
My nana gets into town in an hour.
Wait, your nana? That is so sweet.
I wanna meet the nana.
- You really don't, believe me.
- I love old people.
- They're so cute.
- Yeah, well, the nana, not so cute.
- Really, she's ugly?
- No, she's just scary.
- I can be scary too. I think I can take it.
- Yeah, I don't think I can.
The nana's very judgmental,
and she's political and opinionated.
Right. And I'm dumb and shallow
and have no opinion whatsoever.
- I didn't say that.
- Not out loud.
- You're ashamed of me.
- That's not true. Okay?
I'm not ashamed of you, Summer.
I'm protective.
You're gonna thank me for this,
I promise.
- I have to go.
- Where are you going?
I have to pick up some stuff
for the Seder.
- The what, now?
- The Seder, for Passover.
Yeah, you're not meeting the nana.
Sandy, what are you doing?
Rosa just put those on.
Yeah, I know. But I thought maybe
these sheets were a little too fancy.
They are fancy.
They're 700 thread-count Pratesi sheets.
- I don't want her to know that.
- How would she know?
- She might check.
- Why would she care?
She's a social worker in the Bronx
and has been for 40 years.
Whatever little bit of extra money
she can scrape together...
...she gives it to the ACLU
or Franklin Armory Women's Shelter.
- She's not out buying fancy sheets.
- Technically, I bought the sheets.
You with your sheets, and me,
I've left the public defender's office...
...so I can make a ton of money
and open my own restaurant.
- I think they call that success.
- No.
Not according to Sophie Cohen
and not even Sandy Cohen.
You know why she's coming out here.
It's not for a visit, not for a holiday. No.
She's staging an intervention.
To put me back on the path
to righteousness.
- Or, in Mother's case, self-righteousness.
- That's not true.
- No?
- Your mother just wants you to be happy.
No, she doesn't believe in happy.
If you're happy,
you're not working hard enough.
I know where Rosa keeps the sheets
that don't feel so fancy.
- Hey.
- Hey. I was headed to the restaurant...
...and I thought I'd visit, see how you're
doing after our big adventure last night.
- You okay?
- Yeah. Just embarrassed mostly.
Embarrassed? Why? Come on.
You found me at a strip club.
Hey, there is nothing wrong
with a good strip club.
Not that I would know or anything,
because I, you know, just...
- I wouldn't know.
- No, right, of course not.
So, what are you gonna do? You gonna
go back to L.A.? You gonna stay here?
What do you think I should do?
Well, it's not my decision...
...but you've got family and a place
to stay and people who care about you.
Yeah?
Yeah.
So if I were to stay...
...would that mean that...?
- Hailey.
Be right there.
- You wanna come in?
- No, I gotta go back to work.
- Will I see you later?
- Well...
- You gonna be around?
- Sure.
- Well, then I'll see you later.
- All right, then.
Hi. You guys want some help?
- Thanks, Ryan.
- No, they're fine, man. Have a seat.
Any luck?
I looked everywhere.
The house, the restaurant, the beach.
- Yeah? We'll find her.
- All right.
Who's coming with me to the airport?
Come on. Seth.
Ryan, come on.
Anybody?
You're not ready for the nana?
No one's ever ready for the nana.
That woman is scary.
Hello?
- It couldn't be.
- The front door's wide open.
A person could walk in here,
take everything and kill us all.
It is. It's the nana.
Ma, what are you doing here?
I was just coming to get you.
Well, you would've been very late.
I'm kidding.
The plane was early.
I took a taxi to surprise you.
Are you surprised? You look surprised.
- I'm surprised.
- Sweetheart.
Hello, Kirsten. Look at you.
So beautiful with the hair and the nails.
Those classic features.
And there's my grandson.
Who never writes, never calls...
...because he's too busy
being chased by the California girls.
- How are you, Setheleh?
- How are you, Nana?
You must be Ryan.
I'm very happy to meet you.
- Welcome to the family.
- Thank you.
- You, I don't know.
Sophie, you remember my sister, Hailey.
Oh, right. The bad seed.
I always liked you best.
Don't tell the others.
Look at this house.
And this yard.
And that view of the ocean.
I'm sorry, but I just gotta say it.
- Here it comes.
- California.
Not so terrible.
All right. Where else could she be?
I don't know exactly
who that woman was, Ryan...
...but that was not the nana.
- She was nice.
She was nice, Ryan.
That's the problem, okay?
The nana's not nice.
I love her, but she's not.
- Who haven't we thought of?
- I hate to say it, but what about Oliver?
I talked to the hotel.
He's in the hospital.
She was even nice to my mom, Ryan.
The nana has never
exactly cared for the Kirsten.
- Really?
- Yeah. Are you kidding me?
She's the Green Arrow
to my mom's Hawkman.
The Wolverine to her Cyclops, dude.
Two people who have nothing in common
suddenly getting along. It's not right.
It's just not natural.
I know where she is.
- Took you long enough.
- Is she here?
Yeah. She won't be happy to see you.
How is she? Is she okay?
I can't believe she came here.
- I was surprised too.
- You should've called.
- I couldn't. She asked me not to.
- Her mom's freaking out.
She's about to call the cops,
so I better just get her and go.
What the hell is he doing here?
Did you call him?
- No.
- This is unbelievable.
So he just shows up on the day of?
You just stay the hell away
from me, okay?
Excuse me.
Day of? Day of what?
Our engagement party.
- Everybody finished?
- Thanks.
Sophie, is there something special
that you'd like Hailey to pick up for you?
No, sweetheart, I'm sure that whatever
you kids do every year will be just perfect.
We were kind of hoping we could
talk you into the Sophie Cohen special.
- The brisket, the macaroons.
- I don't do macaroons anymore.
- Come on, Ma. It's Ryan's first Seder.
- How do you know that?
They have Jews in Chino. Why do you
think they want a P.F. Chang's?
I like that he goes back to the old
neighborhood. Speaking of which...
...guess who asked about you recently.
Sean Sullivan.
- Sully.
- He and your dad were in a gang together.
- Did you know that?
- Yeah? Bloods or Crips, Father?
- It was a youth group.
- After his father left us...
...I had to work so much, he was pretty
much raised by the entire neighborhood.
Yeah, well, somebody had to do it.
Well, when am I gonna see
your new restaurant?
- You want to?
- What did I just say?
I'll just go freshen up
and then we can go, huh?
- Who is that woman?
- Not the nana.
Come on, guys.
Maybe she's changed.
Maybe she's mellowed.
Maybe she's genuinely happy to be here.
- Yeah, something's up.
- I'm gonna find out what it is.
Sandy, don't.
Whatever that woman is, I love her.
She's sweet, she's kind, she's helpful.
I'll get it.
I'm begging you, leave it alone.
- Hello. May I help you, dear?
- Hi.
You must be the nana.
I'm Summer. Shalom.
Oh, well, hello.
Are you a friend of Seth's?
- Well, as a matter of fact, I'm his...
- Summer.
Hey. What are you doing here, buddy?
I was in the neighborhood and
thought I'd bring macaroons by...
...for the Seder tonight.
- Oh, how sweet, Summer.
- You shouldn't have.
- Really, you shouldn't have. Okay.
- So are you two...?
- Yes, we are.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wonderful. Then you'll be here tonight,
yes? You can ask the Four Questions.
Thank you, nana, I'd love to.
I was just getting my Haggadah
to get copies made.
Oh, no, I can do that for you.
I love a good Haggadah.
You know, it's the prayer book
containing the Seder ritual.
Somebody knows her stuff, huh?
Seth Cohen, you're a very lucky man.
Thanks.
- Listen. Wow.
- She's not scary. You're the scary one.
You're scary with the hitting
and cookies.
Are you afraid I'll embarrass you
in front of the nana? I'm not.
I'm gonna study this thing so hard,
I'm even gonna out-Jew you.
You're reading it backwards.
Thanks for the cookies.
Wow.
So when's the wedding?
June.
- I wanted to call you and tell you.
- Yeah?
- I thought you didn't want this.
- He really loves me, Ryan.
How do you feel about him?
You don't get to show up the day of
my party and ask questions like this.
It's not like I knew this was happening.
- I knew you'd be this way.
- What way?
You ran away to Newport
to get away from him.
Yeah, like when you left Chino?
Ryan, you made it.
You see, Theresa?
I told you he'd come if we invited him.
- Yeah, Mom, he didn't come for the party.
- No?
He came for me.
- Hey.
- You promised you wouldn't call him.
- She didn't.
- Then why are you here?
I'm here to make sure you're okay.
Get you home.
Then you wasted your time,
because I'm not going anywhere.
Hey. What's all this?
Pasta, cookies, cupcakes,
in all their leavened goodness.
And an invitation to Seder dinner
tonight. All courtesy of...
...the Nana Cohen.
- Wow.
- Today is my lucky day.
- You have no idea.
Look, Hailey, we can't...
We can't do this.
But I thought when you showed up
at the house this morning...
...when you came to L. A to find me...
- I was worried about you...
...and wanted to be sure you were okay.
- I can't believe this.
Kirsten's my best friend.
Sandy's my partner.
- This restaurant is all I have.
- What are you doing?
Showing up at the house?
Showing up in L.A.?
Telling me how much you care
about me? You don't care about me.
- Of course I care about you.
- Right.
Just not as much as
Sandy and Kirsten and the restaurant.
- Wait.
- For what?
I'll see you, Jimmy.
Marissa, come on.
Everybody's worried about you.
- Who? Luke? My mom?
- That's over now.
Maybe for them, but I still have to live
with it. I just don't have to live there.
- You can't hide out in Chino forever.
- Maybe not, but I can for right now.
Theresa said I can stay in Arturo's room,
and that she'd help me find a job...
...until I can save enough money...
- To what? Run away?
Your mom's already threatening
to call the cops.
- And your doctors...
- So, what am I supposed to do?
- I can't go back there.
- I'm not going back without you.
Then I guess you're not going back.
I wish the floors had been finished
before you saw the place.
- The floors were fine.
- How was the restaurant tour?
- It was nice.
- It was nice? That's all I get? It was nice?
It was very nice.
- What? What do you want me to say?
- Ma, what do you wanna say, really?
Come on, this Jewish Mary Poppins act,
I'm not buying it.
- What are you doing here, really?
- You invited me.
I've invited you every year
since Seth was 13.
I've been working.
You know what my caseload is like.
That's why I left the PD's office.
So I could spend more time at home.
That's not why you left, Sandy.
And I have more time and resources
to help the people in the community.
You're not helping,
you're opening restaurants.
- That's not true.
- Who's talking to you?
Do not speak to her like that
in this house.
I'm sorry.
But you know what?
You won't have to
put up with it much longer.
There she is. She's coming back.
The Sophie Cohen we all know and love.
Think it's funny? You'll see
how funny it is when I'm dead.
You're kidding.
You're gonna outlive us all, out of spite.
Well, Dr. Talley disagrees with you.
He gives me four to six months, tops.
He says I have advanced lung cancer.
You wanna know why I came?
I came to say goodbye.
- Why are you still here?
- Look, man...
I ask Theresa to marry me,
and she goes and finds you.
We work everything out and on the day
of our engagement party, you show up.
- I'm here for Marissa.
- She doesn't want you here.
And I sure as hell don't want you here.
You understand?
Look, it's my engagement party, okay?
I'm going to get a drink,
when I come back, don't be here.
- I'm not leaving without her.
- Yes, you are.
- Look, you don't wanna do this.
- No, you don't wanna.
He told you to go. Now, go.
- Hello?
- Did you just call me?
- Yeah, but...
- Well, where is she?
- I'm not telling you that.
- Don't make me call the police.
I would hate to tell them
you're holding her against her will.
- You wouldn't do that.
- Just get her home, now.
Ma, please, come on. Sit down.
We have to talk about this.
No, we don't. What we have to do
is put this brisket in the oven...
...or we'll be eating at midnight.
- I'll get that for you.
Thank you, doll. Sandy said
you were a lox in the kitchen.
- Don't change the subject.
- There is no subject.
- I'm not talking, I'm cooking.
- You can't drop a bomb like that...
...and not talk about it.
Why tell me then?
I didn't want to. You kept hocking me.
It slipped out.
- Have you told anybody else?
- No.
Not your sister. Not your brother. And
don't tell anyone either, especially Seth.
- Why not? He deserves to know.
- Because it's my business.
I will tell him when I'm ready.
Now, he's coming back here
with Summer any minute, so...
Well, what about the treatment?
What did Dr. Talley recommend?
- The surgery? The chemo? What?
- Sure, but what's the point?
By the time I saw Talley,
it had already spread...
...so that's that.
- So, what are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna make dinner.
I'm gonna enjoy what's left of my life,
and I hope you'll do the same.
- I want you to see a doctor out here.
- Well, that's not gonna happen.
We have an incredible oncologist.
When my mother had ovarian cancer...
She had the treatment? The chemo?
With the hair loss and the nausea?
- Did it work?
- No.
But we had a chance
to spend more time with her.
- You wanna spend more time with me?
- Yeah.
You left home when you were 16
and moved clear across the country.
I had a scholarship and a chance
to make something of myself.
You married a woman
whose father represents...
...everything I have fought against
my entire life.
I didn't marry her because of
her father's politics or principles.
Oh, what politics? What principles?
Oh, God, what am I doing here?!
I hate this state! I hate the sunshine!
I hate the ocean!
I hate Schwarzenegger!
- Come in.
- Hey.
- You look...
- It's Theresa's.
- What happened to your arm?
- It's just a scratch.
Eddie and his guys
don't really want me around.
- I'm so sorry. This is all my fault.
- It's okay. We just need to leave.
We need to get some alcohol
and clean this arm.
No, look, it's fine.
We can just deal with this later.
We're not going anywhere.
So just get the phone. I'll talk to Eddie.
No, look, I...
You don't wanna...
- Hello?
- Hey. Come home right now.
- What's going on?
- I don't know. The nana's scary again.
Mom and Dad keep asking when
you're coming home, and I'm at a loss.
- Is Marissa okay?
- How's Marissa doing?
She won't leave. So now
Eddie's threatening to kick my ass...
...and Julie's threatening
to have me arrested.
Why is this night different
from all other nights?
Okay, just come home, man.
You said it yourself,
Marissa's fine, all right?
There's nothing more to do.
It's her mom's problem.
- I can't just leave her here.
- You can't stay, either. Please.
- We have the nana happening.
- For on all other nights...
...we eat either "chamitz" or "matzah."
- Chametz or matzo.
- Look, I'll try, but...
- No. No trying.
Come home. Now. I have to go.
Summer's having a Hebrew hernia.
Cohen.
Luke.
You can't be here.
Kaitlin's in the kitchen.
I know, I know.
I just wanted to say I'm sorry.
It is not your fault, okay?
I'm the grownup here.
I'm the one who should know better.
I'm the one who's lost her daughter.
You're not really gonna
lock her up, are you?
Honestly, I don't know what else to do.
She's a kid, Luke.
She's run away again.
And if she doesn't come back
on her own...
...what other choice do I have?
I need her to be safe.
You gotta be kidding me.
Darling, the only nice thing about having
cancer is that I can smoke all I want.
Try not to ruin it for me.
I called Dr. Talley.
Please tell me you did not do that.
- He says you haven't returned his calls.
- Well, I've been busy.
And while he says there's no cure,
you can slow it down...
...if you take the chemo and radiation.
- And slow me down too.
- Might not be such a bad thing.
- Sandy.
I have kids in the Bronx
who are counting on me.
You got kids of your own who
are counting on you. And grandkids.
Oh, please.
Counting on me for what?
To be there. That's all.
- That's all I ever wanted.
- You're gonna start with me again?
When I left home at 16,
I was surprised you noticed.
That's nice. That's what a mother wants
to hear. Especially when she's dying.
Please, continue.
You were never home.
You were working all the time.
You were taking care of other
people's kids, or marching for causes...
...or circulating petitions,
or picketing city hall.
Look...
...it felt like you had no time for us.
- It was your father who ran away, Sandy.
- Not me.
- Well...
...now who's running away?
Enjoy your cigarette.
- He's pretty great, isn't he?
- Yeah, he is.
You both are.
And I can't thank you enough
for putting me up last night, but...
- What?
- Are you sure it's okay for me to stay?
I mean, now that Ryan's here too, I know
you guys have this history together...
Ryan's my oldest friend, but that's it.
Really.
- I thought when you came to Newport...
- That was a mistake.
I was afraid, so I ran to Ryan
because he's safe.
But it wasn't till I came home and was
honest with Eddie about everything...
...that I realized that I have
nothing to be afraid of.
Neither do you.
As for Ryan, like you said...
...he didn't come here for me.
He came here for you.
Let's go. Come on.
- You still here?
- Not by choice, believe me.
Yeah, well...
...that's too bad.
I've been thinking about it. How
your brother and Arturo are both in jail.
You and I are the only ones
from the old crew left.
I thought you didn't want me here, man.
I thought you came here
for Theresa, okay? It freaked me out.
But I talked to Marissa, you know?
And...
I don't think Marissa
wants me here either.
Come on. Of all the places she
could've picked to go, she chose Chino.
Dude, she picked the one place
she knew only you could find her.
- Setheleh? You in there?
- Yeah, I am.
I'm just gonna be down
in a second, though, okay?
Or I could save you the schlep.
- Can a person come in?
- Yeah, of course.
Come in.
- Where's Summer?
- She went to change for dinner.
- So were you just not gonna tell me?
- Not if I could help it.
- Did you think I couldn't handle it?
- No, doll, I knew you could handle it.
Me, on the other hand...
...I wanted to spend this time...
...getting to know you.
Not be the dying nana, where every
conversation could possibly be the last.
- Yeah, but it could, right?
- Yeah, sure, that's always true though.
Cancer or no cancer.
We could all be dead tomorrow.
You never know.
- That's really comforting, thank you.
- Don't mention it.
So tell me about Seth Cohen.
You like comic books? Music? Videos?
Yeah, it all seems pretty trivial
right now, though, compared to...
...oh, I don't know, cancer.
See, that's why I didn't want to tell you.
You don't wanna do the chemo?
You're not interested?
Wait. Listen.
It's very complicated.
Are you scared?
What do you think?
I don't know.
Dad said you're not afraid of anything.
Your dad doesn't know me as well
as he thinks he does.
Yeah, well, you're the one
who doesn't wanna stick around...
...so whose fault is that?
- Hi.
- Hey.
- What do you think of Chino?
- Actually...
...I think I can get in more trouble
where I'm from.
I'm sorry about everything.
The trip to L.A., your mom.
But we have to get back.
- The longer we stay, the worse it will get.
- How can it?
- She can put you away.
- Let her try.
- She tried it before, it almost worked.
- This time she'll have to find me first.
- What are you doing?
- Getting out of here.
- To go where?
- I don't know, okay?
I don't know where.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I don't know anything,
except that I can't go back there.
- Well, I can't keep chasing after you.
- Who asked you to?
I don't know why you're here.
Maybe you should think
about it instead of yourself.
- Out of my way
- I'm not going anywhere.
- I mean it!
Get out of my way!
Move. Move.
I can't go back there.
Okay.
You're okay.
Okay. It's okay.
Ryan? You in there?
Yeah, just a second.
There's someone here to see you.
Okay.
Hey. Seth told me you were in Chino.
- You can't be here. Why are you here?
- I'm here for Marissa.
- Look, you can't be here now, okay?
- Julie's gonna call the cops if...
You think she's going back with you?
You're the last person she wants to see.
- Well, she's gonna.
- You need to get out of here.
- You need to get out of my way.
- Look, guys...
...this is my engagement party.
Just calm down, okay?
Ryan, get away from him.
Marissa, hey. I just...
Get out of here, Luke.
- It's not what you think.
- She told you to tell me that?
That it's all in my head? That I'm crazy?
- It's not her fault.
- Get out of here.
- Marissa, if you'd just come with me...
- Just go, now.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it smells so good in here. Is it true
we can't eat for another six hours?
The nana's Seder won't take that long,
will it?
Have you seen her Haggadah?
- You're reading it backwards.
- Don't tell anyone.
- Hey, it's okay. Being Jewish is hard.
- You have no idea.
So do you know what happened
to make the nana scary again?
Actually...
What? What's going on in here?
Nothing. I'm gonna go study.
I'll see you at dinner...
Seder. Sorry.
- You told her, didn't you?
- I would never do that.
Then what were you talking about?
How scary you are.
I am scary.
I'd be scary too if I was sick and
suddenly I had to depend on my kids.
Well, see the difference is
I'm not gonna be dependent on my kids.
- No, you would rather die.
- Oh, that's good, Kirsten.
With the honesty.
I didn't know you had it in you.
That's because you don't know me.
You never wanted to.
- And it pretty much cost you your son.
- My son made a choice.
Maybe. But now you can make one.
You can get the best treatment,
you can get to know your grandson...
...and you can have Sandy
back in your life.
But, that's not important to you.
Oh, guilt now, huh?
That's very impressive.
You sure you're not Jewish?
How's she doing?
She's great.
Luke's the one I feel sorry for.
He's gonna have a handprint
on his face for, like, a week.
Sorry about that.
- Showing up, ruining your party.
- Hey, does it look ruined to you?
Besides, it's my engagement party.
If you'd have missed it,
I would've kicked your ass.
I should've invited you.
So invite me to the wedding.
Yeah. You'll bring Marissa.
All right, who wants cake?
Actually, I can't. I gotta get back.
Dinner at the Cohens'.
Seth's grandma's in town.
Can't miss it.
Yeah, well, you two are welcome to stay
as long as you want.
Come on, Eddie, my mom needs
help in the kitchen.
- I'm eating cake.
- No, you're not.
Oh, okay. I got it. See?
Not even married yet,
she's already bossing me around.
- I don't wanna go back.
- I know.
But you didn't do anything wrong.
They did. They know that.
Your mom's freaking out.
She's afraid you'll tell.
Why would I tell?
I don't wanna see them ever again,
and I don't wanna go back.
Yeah, but what about your dad?
Kaitlin? Summer?
What about me?
What am I supposed to do without you?
I mean, I'd get over you eventually,
but it'd take a while.
I couldn't find an actual Seder plate,
so I'm using this one.
Well, that's because we don't have
an actual Seder plate, Ma.
This is the first actual Seder we've ever
had. We usually go to the Ackermans'.
But you're here this year, and Ryan.
I've been finding homes
for kids like Ryan...
...for over 40 years.
- I know, Ma.
Yeah, but I never once thought
to bring one home with me.
- Had to show up your own mother?
- He's a good kid.
You should spend some time with him.
I can't.
I'm flying home early tomorrow.
Well, you don't want me to miss
my first treatment, do you?
Oh, Ma, thanks.
Hey, you know, you could
have it out here, if you want.
No, honey, thanks, but I like Dr. Talley.
And your sister's there
and your brother.
- And, you know, I hate California.
- So maybe I could come visit.
Please, your mother's
gonna be having chemo.
It's the least you can do.
- You sure you wanna do this now?
- I have to. My clothes are inside.
Maybe she won't be home.
- Oh, thank God you're back.
- I'm not.
- I just came to get my stuff and go.
- The hell you are.
You are not leaving this house.
Or what? You're gonna call the police or
Dr. Milano? You know what? Go ahead.
In fact, why don't you call up
Dad while you're at it, and Caleb too?
I'd really love to tell them
why I ran away.
Get your stuff and leave.
Gladly.
Hey. You're here.
Yeah. Is that okay? I wasn't sure.
No, of course. Come on in.
Here's a little...
...holiday-appropriate bouquet.
- Thanks.
So, listen, I was thinking
about what you said today...
...as I ate most of those cupcakes
and, like...
...that whole box of cookies
you brought by...
...and you're right.
You're right about everything.
No, you were right. I'm sorry.
I was? Are you sure?
Because that's rarely the case.
No, I mean, Kirsten and I
are finally getting along.
And I have a second chance
with my dad.
So why risk all of that?
Because it'll be fun
and because I'm self-destructive...
...and because you're incredible,
and I can't help myself.
Really?
- Are we really gonna do this?
- I think we already are.
But I think the real question...
...is how are we gonna tell Kirsten...
...without sustaining bodily injuries?
Well...
...she doesn't have to know
right away, does she?
For on all other nights,
we do not dip our food into salt water.
But tonight we dip karpas into salt water
and maror into charoses.
Did you just do that all by heart?
- Was it okay?
- It was perfect.
You can use the book.
Didn't I tell you that?
- No! Cohen!
- You're good, you're my little chachem.
- Hey, sorry we're late.
- Hey.
- I'm so sorry, Coop.
- It's okay. Really, we're fine.
- You see Luke?
- We won't see him for a while.
- How'd you manage that?
- I didn't. Marissa smacked him.
- Nice, Coop!
- She's hangs out with you too much.
- Hey, you guys ready to eat?
- Yes!
Well, that's too bad, because
the Seder's about to begin. Come on.
- How was everything at home?
- You tell me. I was in Chino.
"Tonight we celebrate
the first night of Passover.
A celebration of rebirth,
of new beginnings...
...and of freedom.
Freedom from the constraints
that have bound us.
And freedom to join together
to take responsibility for ourselves...
...for our families, for our community...
...and for the world."
Do we eat now?
Ryan, we've got, like, six more hours.
Yeah, strap in.
Let's all raise our glasses.