- Previously on The O.C.:
- Can we just start over?
- Wait.
- Don't you want to?
No.
- Ryan.
- Theresa.
- You ever think about coming home?
- Sometimes.
I know I shouldn't be here.
Would you like to come in?
It's always been you, Summer.
You're undeniable.
I'm a man now. I had sex with a girl.
Summer, to be more specific.
Hi, Marissa. Theresa.
Okay. Bye.
So you and Marissa, you guys broken up?
You guys taking a break? What's the deal?
I don't know.
We're just not seeing each other.
Except you will see each other, at school
every day for the next couple years.
Right. Well, we'll just
go back to being friends.
When were you guys ever friends?
Was it when you were beating up her
boyfriend? Or spooning in a Tijuana motel?
- Is that when you were friends?
- Doesn't mean we can't be friends.
I don't know.
Think I'll see her today?
Friends, Coop?
What are you guys gonna do together?
Lift weights? Try on wife-beaters?
Sorry. Guys like Ryan
aren't friends with girls.
I don't wanna just be his friend.
But after the whole Oliver thing...
...I guess I need to show him
he can trust me.
Who knows if he'll
even wanna be friends.
- So how goes it with Seth?
- Weird.
In public, he's like this huge geek
who mumbles.
I don't even know what he's saying half
the time. But behind closed doors...
...underneath the sheets,
he's like the anti-Cohen.
You think I'll have to see him today?
I think me and Summer are finally
over the hump, by the way.
So to speak. I just hope, man...
...that she can keep it in her trousers
when she sees me today.
She'll probably have her little paws
all over me.
That's probably her now,
a little phone sex.
Who do I know from the 909?
Nobody.
- Hello?
- Ryan?
Hi, it's Theresa.
- Yeah, Seth's mom gave me this number.
- Hey. How are you? Everything okay?
Yeah, fine.
- I'm actually coming out there today.
- You are? How come?
- I mean, for work?
- Yeah...
...but they can't make us
work all the time, right?
- I was thinking we could hang out tonight.
- Tonight? Sure.
- Don't sound so excited.
- I am. I'm just a little surprised, that's all.
Oh, you know me, full of surprises.
So I'll come by after dinner.
Yeah, sounds good. See you then.
Hey, baby. Who's that?
Wrong number.
That was Theresa.
She's in town, wants to hang out.
As a friend.
Well, first Marissa, then Theresa.
Who knew Ryan Atwood was so friendly?
- Summer.
- Cohen.
- Ryan.
- Hi.
- Summer. Can we talk?
- Hey, Brad, what's up?
Brad.
Dude, I didn't recognize you
out of the Speedo.
Not that I'd recognize you
in a Speedo, but...
Okay. Come on.
Jeez.
- So how are you?
- I'm...
I'm late. See you.
So we're doing a fundraiser for the team,
a kissing booth.
I'm gonna be the guy,
and we're looking for a girl...
...who's comfortable being paid
to make out with a bunch of guys.
- Naturally, I thought of you.
- Really? You thought of me?
God. Totally. I mean, why not?
- Thanks, Summer.
- Sure.
He talked to you like I wasn't there.
Does he know we're going out?
It's not like he wants to kiss me.
He just wants me to kiss
a bunch of other dudes for money.
I'll see you tonight. My place?
You can help me practice.
- Anna.
- So you guys are together now?
Well, that didn't take long, did it?
Yeah, Summer and I are...
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
I mean, I did see it coming.
It's the reason I broke up with you.
- Hey, how was Pittsburgh?
- It was good to be home.
Pittsburgh's also the home
of Andy Warhol, Mr. Rogers and ketchup.
- You can't compete with that.
- You can't.
Yeah, it was really great.
I got a tuna melt at my favorite diner...
...and I saw Some Kind of Wonderful
at the midnight movie...
...and hung out with all my friends.
It was really nice.
Guess I didn't realize
how much I missed them.
Hey, Dad.
You wanted to see me?
Kiki, we got a problem.
- Uncle Shaun was arrested last night.
- You're kidding. For what?
He was drunk, stumbled into
another guest's room at the St. Regis.
He's been stumbling around drunk
since you met him...
...which was in a bar.
I'll have someone in Legal handle it.
- I was thinking you might ask Sandy.
- Very funny.
He knows people at the DA's office.
He can make this go away.
- He'll never do it.
- Why not?
- Because it would be a favor to me?
- Pretty much. Yeah.
You could tell him
it would mean a lot to you.
Actually, it would mean a lot to me.
But if you want Sandy's help
after all these years...
...then you need to ask him,
because that would mean a lot to Sandy.
- No.
- You should see these two guys.
- Oh, come on.
- Honestly, it was unbelievable.
I swear to God.
- Hi.
So this is you and Summer
being a couple?
- Ain't love grand?
- I can really sense the bond.
It's like, your closeness,
it's overwhelming.
Oh, my gosh. Wait.
Is it last fall already?
- Come on, she's totally ignoring you.
- Anna, she's not ignoring me.
Summer just has her priorities in order.
You know how she feels about charity.
- Yes?
- Yeah. Good luck with that.
Mrs. Cooper.
- What are you doing here?
- Parent-teacher conference.
- It's good to see you.
- It's good to see you too.
Really good. You... I mean...
God, you look good.
Luke, I'm Marissa's mother.
You're a student at this school.
- We can't do this.
- You mean it's over?
No, I mean in the hallway.
I'll see you tonight.
- Hey, Julie.
- Jimmy, hi.
- You remember Luke.
- Who could forget?
- Luke.
- Hey, Mr. Cooper.
I'm glad you're here. I didn't want to go
to Dr. Kim's office alone. She scares me.
Okay, well, goodbye, Mrs. Cooper.
And Mr. Cooper.
I'll see you.
Both.
Have a good day.
Hey, I'm sorry about this morning.
That...
- It shouldn't have to be...
- Like this?
I was just sort of hoping
we could be friends, you know?
- I mean, as long as that's okay with you.
- Yeah. No, we should hang out.
Okay.
What are you doing tonight?
- Tonight's no good.
- It's okay. We don't have to do this.
What about after school?
Actually, after school's good.
It's better...
...because I'm supposed to have dinner
with my dad. Your place?
- Yeah, see you then.
- Cool.
Well...
...the restaurant's coming along, Sandy.
At this rate, you'll be open by 2008.
And there goes my appetite.
Caleb, hello.
- What the hell is that?
- It's my mother's meat loaf.
- God, your mother's here?
- Her recipe is.
- We're trying out a chef. You want some?
- The sight of your mother's meat loaf...
...has turned me into a vegetarian.
I know you're a big fan of the pop-in, but
is there another reason why you're here?
I've come to ask a favor.
I'm sorry, what did you say?
- You didn't hear me?
- I heard you. I want you to say it again.
- A friend is in trouble. I want you to help.
- I didn't know you had friends.
- It's Bill Shaughnessy.
- Uncle Shaun.
You pay Uncle Shaun to be your friend.
I guess he qualifies. What did he do?
He was drinking, stumbled into
someone else's hotel room.
They called security,
and now it's a legal matter.
- You've got lawyers at your beck and call.
- He came to me as a friend.
I want it handled like a friend.
Quietly.
By someone who has a relationship
with the DA's office?
I'm asking you.
I've known Shaun for over 40 years.
It would mean a lot to me.
- Did Kirsten tell you to say that?
- She thinks you'll say no.
My wife knows me pretty well.
But, you know,
sometimes I like to surprise her.
I don't want her to go and get all
conceited and stuff, you know?
You have a copy of the police report?
Now, I'm not saying that I'll do it.
I'm saying that I'll look at the report,
I'll make some calls and then we'll see.
- Got any more of that meat loaf?
- Maybe.
Well, that was a relief. Dr. Kim seems
to think Marissa's doing well.
I was sure she was gonna revoke
my license to parent.
You know, Jimmy,
I don't think I ever thanked you.
That's not true. You've thanked me
for alienating the community...
...destroying the family.
- For doing a wonderful job with Marissa.
I'm serious.
Listening to you in that meeting...
...you're totally involved in her life.
- You and Caleb must be doing really well.
- Why would you say that?
- Because you're being so...
...nice.
- Well, actually...
...Caleb and I aren't
seeing each other anymore.
And I'm much happier.
And to think, you've spent a lifetime
wanting to be rich and married...
...when what agrees with you most
is being poor and alone.
Isn't it better when we're alone?
Just the two of us?
- Why did you ignore me at school today?
- I didn't ignore you.
Okay, maybe a little.
I just... I want our relationship
to be private, okay?
I don't like other people
knowing my business.
- Why not?
- Because it's none of their business.
Look, there's, like, pressure...
...and scrutiny in the spotlight.
- What spotlight?
When has being in the public eye
ever helped a relationship?
Sure, we're this week's hottest couple,
but then the world gets sick of it.
The shopping sprees, the strip clubs.
People turn against us, okay?
"How many Juicy sweat suits
does she need?"
"That goatee is so mid-'90s." Pretty soon,
the movie bombs and the wedding is off!
But I'm not gonna let that
happen to us, because, Cohen...
...what we have is special.
Summer...
...that's maybe just...
- Guess I'm not very good.
- Yeah.
Want a rematch?
Because I couldn't possibly get any worse.
No, I should probably
start on my homework.
Oh, yeah, me too.
I mean, my dad's probably waiting.
- Is this...? I don't know, are we...?
- Why...? Why is this weird?
- It shouldn't be.
- We used to hang out all the time and...
Make out?
- We could always fight about Luke.
- Or Oliver.
Sorry. I just...
Hey, Ryan.
Hey, Marissa.
I'm early. Sorry.
I'll go and come back later.
It's okay.
We weren't doing anything.
Yeah, I was just leaving.
He's got a lot of homework.
Good to see you, Theresa.
It's nice to see you too.
The ninja game?
You're dead now.
Considering he is your "Uncle" Shaun...
...don't you think it's weird
we have never met?
He's not really my uncle.
- And he pretty much works all the time.
- Doing what?
He's a consultant.
Could you please be a little more vague?
He knows people.
You did it.
That was more vague.
The guys at the permit office,
the union guys.
He's our liaison.
Well, I looked over the police report,
I put in a few calls...
...and I'm sure I'll hear something back
before we get together tonight.
- Thank you.
- Overexposure, Ryan...
...it's a major source of conflict
in new relationships.
"Summereth." "Sethummer."
You understand what I'm saying?
- No. No. That's normal.
- Ryan, your friend Theresa called.
- I'd like to meet Theresa.
- Yeah, she'd like to meet you guys.
- What's she doing here?
- Taking a semester off, making money.
Catering a tennis tournament.
Her mom got laid off.
So she's out here a while.
Does Marissa know? I'm curious.
They kind of bumped into each other.
Look at you, the friend guy.
Bringing friends together.
- I sense sarcasm.
- You're perceptive.
This mysterious caliente female from
your past just shows up out of nowhere...
...with all this time on her hands
and no one to spend it with but you.
- Marissa okay with this?
- She's fine. They're back to being friends.
So when were they ever friends?
You are so beautiful, you know that?
You're very sweet.
- I wish we could stay here forever.
- Why?
We got everything we need here.
We got our bed. We got our cable.
We got each other.
- This place is awesome.
- It's not awesome.
It's $ 79 a night.
I gotta motor.
I don't wanna be late for homeroom.
You have homeroom.
Right. Because you're in high school.
And you're only 18.
Kaitlin, are you okay?
You're in front of the house?
Chester's mom was supposed to pick you
up at Grandma's and take you to school.
Your diorama.
Yeah, I think it's
in the living room, honey.
Okay, just wait there with Grandma.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Okay. See you soon.
- See you tonight?
- Oh, Luke.
Motels, homerooms, dioramas.
- This is not the stuff of great romance.
- But, Mrs...
Julie.
I'm sorry.
- No worries.
- Good.
Hey.
- You mind if...?
- No.
Thanks.
- So, sorry about...
- Sorry I was such a...
- I should've told you she was coming.
- You didn't have to.
But you could've.
I mean, now that we're friends, right?
- Right.
- So you and Theresa...?
- We're friends.
- And she's back in town for...?
Work. She's staying
till the end of the week.
- Where's she staying?
- The motel by the pier.
The Seashell? Sea Monkey?
- The Mermaid.
- Right.
- Next week we could have that rematch.
- Think you're up for it?
Hey, what I lack in nunchaku,
I make up for in saber.
So...
...did you talk to Summer yesterday?
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah?
- We talked about school...
...and sports and the weather.
But if you're referring to the part
where she's ashamed of me, no.
Didn't get to that.
Were you gonna say something?
Something very wise and helpful, Anna?
- No.
- You got nothing? No advice at all for me?
- I feel like you did.
- Why do I do this?
Because you're so wise, Anna.
You can't not.
All right, fine.
Look, you have to take a stand, all right?
You can't let her get away with it.
Otherwise she has something
to be ashamed of...
...because then her boyfriend
is a coward.
I'm just going to help with the kissing
booth, you know, because I love to help.
Right, coward. Got it.
Hope you don't mind.
I let myself in through the back.
It's what you do.
Famous Uncle Shaun.
Here. Famous Grouse.
I haven't seen a bottle of this
since Bob Mitchum passed.
- You knew Robert Mitchum?
- Yeah. He and his wife Dorothy...
...they used to have a place over there
on Linda Isle.
That was their favorite booth.
Sunday dinners. Chicken parm.
I'm partial to the parm myself,
and a lover of blended Scotch.
And Caleb keeps saying
you have no redeeming qualities.
So I read the police report.
I just have a couple of questions.
This fellow who's pressing charges,
he's in the construction business.
- Really?
- Yeah. Yeah, he's a lumber supplier...
...one of the biggest in the country.
In fact, he was in town on a negotiation...
...with one of the Newport Group's
chief rivals.
- Imagine that.
- Yeah, I'm guessing...
...that in that room
that you accidentally stumbled into...
...were documents
containing information...
...that would be very valuable
to somebody like Caleb.
- You think?
- You expect me or the DA's office...
...to believe a bellyful of liquor or a wild
coincidence would put you in that room?
You were there for Caleb.
That's an interesting theory.
And one I, you know, hope you don't
explore too much, because...
What is it, "Sandy"? You know, Caleb
and I have been friends for many years.
And if I were to sit down with the DA...
...there's no telling
what we might talk about.
- So, what do you think?
- It's good.
- They call them Balboa Bars.
- It's just ice cream.
No such thing
as just ice cream in Newport.
Like, instead of car washes,
they have auto spas.
Dogs have daycare.
Fashion Island has valet parking.
It's a weird place.
Still, it's beautiful.
I can see why you wanna live here,
start over.
Is that why you came back here?
Start over?
No, I couldn't.
I've got my mom to think about.
My brother. And Eddie.
You guys are still...?
We're taking some time apart. You know,
to see if we really belong together.
- What about you and Marissa?
- Kind of the same thing, I guess.
We're trying to be friends,
but it hasn't exactly been easy.
- Actually, it's never really been...
- Like this.
- That's because I never really liked you.
- True. Makes things easier.
Do you need to stretch
so you won't pull a hammy?
- Or are you ready for your workout?
- I'm sorry, Summer.
I need to take a stand. This separation
of the public and private spheres...
...isn't working for me. I can't do it.
- But I told you how...
One day you might have
some MTV-driven radio hits...
...and then a moderately priced
clothing line.
I could get offered $20 million to portray
a blind superhero in a red leather unitard.
But until then, as long as we're
complete faceless nobodies...
...living in obscurity...
...I can't acknowledge you privately
if you won't acknowledge me publicly.
Let me know when you're ready
to come to the bargaining table.
Until then, just consider me on strike.
You'll cross your own picket line
in no time.
Fight the power.
- Eddie.
- Hey.
- Hey, man.
- How's it going, Ryan? Good to see you.
You look good.
You look good, man.
Yeah, I went up and visited
your brother last week.
It kills me he's still serving time.
- Sucks, huh?
- Yeah. Yeah.
It's been a while, man.
What are you doing here?
Well, actually...
...I'm looking for Theresa.
Theresa?
Yeah, you know, her mom said
she was working out here in Newport...
...and your brother said you were living
the life out here, you know, so I...
- I thought maybe you'd seen her.
- She didn't leave a note or something?
No.
Nothing.
Some thanks for the ring I got her, huh?
- Ring?
- Yeah, we're engaged.
Engaged?
Damn, Eddie, that's great, man.
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
So she...
I mean, she hasn't looked you up at all?
No, sorry.
- You're living the dream out here, huh?
- Yeah, you said it.
That's all right. You deserve it.
You know, putting up with Trey
for all those years.
All right.
I'm gonna get out of here.
But...
- Hey, if you see her, you know, just...
- Yeah.
I don't know, I just...
I can't believe she'd
run out on me like that.
Neither can I.
- Were you gonna tell me you're engaged?
- I'm not engaged.
- What the hell are you doing?
- He asked, I didn't say yes.
- So you took off. That'll fix everything?
- You did.
Sorry.
You're gonna have to face him
sooner or later.
- I just need time to think.
- Yeah, you need about five years.
- You're 17.
- What's gonna be different in five years?
Or have you forgotten
where you come from?
Not everybody has an infinity pool,
goes to private school...
...and drives a Range Rover.
- What are you saying?
Eddie has his own place, he's a foreman at
work and isn't a screwup like his friends.
- All good reasons to marry him.
- And he loves me.
- And you?
- I just need time.
- What are you doing for dinner?
- Nothing.
- Don't say you're not hungry.
- I didn't say I wasn't hungry.
I'm starving.
Why do you think I'm being a bitch?
What are you gonna do, eat out of
the vending machine? Come on.
Come on.
Come to my house with me.
You just need a ride.
Upstairs, alone. Now.
Upstairs alone? I'm afraid I'd have to
file a grievance with the union.
- I've had enough.
- I left you two hours ago.
Well, it feels like four.
I've been thinking about what you said...
...and I find it totally insensitive.
- I'm being insensitive? Really? How?
Can't you accept that I'm uncomfortable
with public displays of affection?
You're offering yourself for $ 10 a pop
at a kissing booth.
How much more publicly
can affection be displayed?
I know there's a strike,
but technically...
...you wouldn't be considered a scab...
- Summer, don't say "scab."
If you didn't have to do anything.
Well, your strike-busting techniques
are no good here.
Sorry, the rank and file
are holding strong.
Solidarity.
Cal.
- What a surprise.
- A welcome one, I hope.
Well, that depends.
You've brought flowers?
Thank you. They're beautiful.
- I missed you.
- I've missed you too.
Neither of us are love-struck adolescents
looking to be swept off our feet.
We're both adults. Our lives
are full of responsibilities, difficulties.
Well, isn't this romantic.
We should be able
to come to some arrangement...
...where we both get from a relationship
what we want.
Is this a booty call?
What's a booty call?
It's when you show up at night,
unannounced, no apologies...
...no compliments, no commitments...
...just some crappy mini-carns
from Ralphs...
...and a very mistaken idea
that I just might wanna...
Guess it was a booty call.
How much are you involved
with Uncle Shaun, day-to-day?
Not much.
He spends most of his time
out of the office...
...on site with the crews,
suppliers, inspectors.
You gotta be a hard-ass to be good
at that job. Lots of tough characters.
I'm sure Shaun can be persuasive
when he needs to be.
Convincing-argument persuasive,
or baseball-bat persuasive?
If you don't wanna help him, I understand.
I didn't think you'd do it in the first place.
Hey, dinner's ready.
Slaved over hot take-out containers.
- Ryan here?
- Hey.
- This is Theresa.
- Hi.
- Hello, friend.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm Kirsten. And this is...
Sandy. Hi.
I've heard so much about you.
It's nice to meet you all.
Can I help? It looks great.
Sure. The key is taking the food
out of the Styrofoam containers.
But her real specialty is ordering.
Is the silverware in the drawer or...?
What's going on? Don't say "nothing,"
because it's not nothing. It's something.
- She's engaged.
- Wow. You make quick work of the ladies.
- To this guy Eddie.
- Oh, she just told you?
No, he did, when he showed up
looking for her.
What's going on here?
- And don't say "nothing."
- Because it's not nothing. It's something.
What we have here
is our very own telenovela.
- Telenovela?
- Yeah. Spanish-language soap opera.
Ni Ía Amada M Âa.
I hope Isabela gets Victor.
I love his handlebar moustache.
- You do it.
- Give it to me.
Previously on The Valley:
Hey.
What are you doing home?
I thought you'd be over at Ryan's house.
He's kind of busy.
A friend from home.
- Theresa.
- And you're okay with that?
- Yeah. It's not a big deal.
- It is kind of a big deal.
- He's important to you.
- What's important to me...
...is that we not talk about this right now,
because I'm fine.
It's just high school.
Hey, that's supposed to be my line, okay?
You're supposed to say...
...I could never understand. And how Ryan
is the most important thing in the world...
...and without him...
- We're just friends.
- Or at least we're trying to be.
- Look, at the risk of embarrassing you...
...you and Ryan...
...never friends.
- So I've been told.
- But if we can't be friends, then...
- Let him know what you wanna be.
See? There's still room around here
for me to be the adult.
Okay?
So we're all dressed up
for my brother's 16th birthday.
Not this one. Don't you have anything
that doesn't involve me falling down?
Did Ryan fall down when he did musicals?
Tell us.
You did musicals?
I did a musical or two myself in college.
Someone stop him before he starts
singing "Greased Lightnin'."
Do it, Dad. Travolta's your bitch.
- Thank you, son.
- Go ahead.
We were at the Holiday Inn,
at the revolving restaurant...
...and Ryan has this thing about heights...
- I'll get it.
Excuse me.
- Hey, sweetie.
- Hey.
- Is Ryan here?
- Yes, he is.
- I love revolving restaurants.
- Who doesn't?
Motion and digestion,
unbeatable combination.
Look who's here.
- Hey.
Does everybody know everybody?
- Yeah. Hi, Theresa.
- Hi, Marissa.
- You hungry?
- Actually, I'm starved. Is it okay?
- Sure.
- Absolutely. Have a seat.
Let me get you a plate.
So, what's everyone talking about?
Hey, man, phone for you.
It's Eddie.
Hey, man, I can't find him.
Do you want me to take a message?
Apparently not. He hung up.
So dinner last night,
entertaining for the rest of us...
...but for you, wow.
- What, last night?
The whole dinner-theater/telenovela thing
you performed.
- Telenovela?
- Yeah, Spanish-language sudser.
Telemundo, dude. Univision.
Victor, with the sexy
handlebar moustache.
So you still have the mindset
that you're the friend guy, huh?
Befriending any beautiful woman
who cares to dine with us?
- I'm working on it.
- Right. Well, if I may...
...speaking from
a recent personal experience...
...the triangle's not a friendly shape,
okay? It's pointy. It's got sharp edges.
- Triangles hurt people.
- There's no triangle.
Marissa and I aren't together.
Theresa's here for work.
Except Marissa still obviously
has feelings for you...
...and Theresa obviously
has feelings for you.
In fact, the only thing that's not obvious
is how Ryan Atwood feels.
- I don't know. It's complicated.
- It is complicated.
It's complicated by the fact that
there's an Eddie who still obviously...
...has feelings for Theresa. That would
actually make this romantic triangle...
...more of a romantic rhombus.
- So, what am I supposed to do?
That I don't know.
But I would do something soon...
...otherwise someone's gonna get hurt.
Judging from Eddie's phone voice,
it's probably gonna be you.
What the hell do you expect, Sandy?
Construction's a dirty business.
Bids accepted below cost.
Permits mysteriously approved
at the last second.
Guys like Shaun
are the lifeblood of the industry.
Well, that was a touching speech, Cal,
but still the answer's no.
Good luck.
You're opening a Pandora's box,
you know that? Shaun's old. He's tired.
If the DA starts asking questions,
he's got lots of answers.
If you build your empire on quicksand,
sooner or later it's gonna sink.
What about Kirsten?
She's complicit in all this too.
- She doesn't know anything about this.
- Because I didn't tell her.
I was trying to protect her.
But she's number two at Newport Group.
She signs Shaun's paychecks.
So like it or not,
we're in this mess together.
Hey.
Hi.
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
It's not like Cohen and I planned to
get together. It sort of just happened.
And if it makes you feel better,
I don't think it's gonna work out.
Well, that makes me feel great.
I just can't be like one of those
couples, you know...
...who hold hands in the hallway
and make out in between classes.
Let the whole world
know what's going on.
It's none of their business, you know?
You don't have to ignore him, Summer.
I don't ignore him.
Okay, maybe a little,
but only in public.
You spent so much time
trying to get his attention.
I mean, you dressed up
as Wonder Woman.
Well, Wonder Woman
is supposed to have an invisible jet...
...not an invisible boyfriend.
I mean, either you're really evil
or there's something else going on.
I just don't know why he likes me.
I mean, he's way smarter. And we have,
like, less than nothing in common.
And he's just gonna get bored with me,
because, pretty much, all boys do.
If everybody knows we're dating...
...they'll know when he breaks up
with me, which he will.
I mean, dumped by Seth Cohen?
It's real good for my reputation.
- Hello?
- Luke.
- Hey, Mrs...
- Do not say my name out loud.
Come to the motel.
Park across the street and walk.
I'll get the same room.
Knock twice so I know it's you.
And, Luke...
...this is a booty call.
It turns out you're not the only one
who's a coward.
- Oh, it's nice to see you also, yeah?
- Summer's scared too.
I know. She's scared to be seen
in public with me.
Come on, Cohen. She fought for you.
She was fearless.
Ruthless, in fact.
Now she's got you.
There's nothing scarier than that.
Nothing scarier than being with me,
or do you mean, like, anyone?
Look, once you get what you want...
...that's when you've got
something to lose.
She's afraid of losing you, Cohen.
Why? I'm not going anywhere.
Maybe you need to let her know that.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Can we talk?
I know it's weird, me being here...
...but I just really needed to know...
- Am I still in love with Ryan?
Because you still are.
I don't wanna be.
It would be a whole lot easier
if I wasn't.
- Hey, man. What's up?
- Hey.
It's a long drive just to come say hello.
Last night, when you asked me
about Theresa...
...I wasn't completely honest.
Carl.
- I'm gonna take a break, all right?
- Okay.
- So why lie?
- I'm sorry, man. I didn't...
- She staying with you?
- No. She's working, like her mom said.
Still, I...
I mean, I pop the question...
...and she runs away...
...to you.
Married?
- Wow.
- Yeah, that's the plan.
You must really love him a lot.
Do you love her?
- I don't know.
- Yeah, well, I do.
Okay? I do.
And I wanna take care of her.
Do you?
I mean, can you?
Look, I know this is tough. L...
I can't tell you what to do.
But if you wanted to,
you could talk to her.
You know, convince her to come home.
Otherwise, be ready to fight for her,
because I'm not just gonna walk away.
I can't.
You got a long ride home.
You got a lot to think about.
In the church where my mom goes,
there's a stained glass window...
...of Teresa of Avila.
Her heart's being pierced
by the arrow of an angel.
Her eyes are closed.
And even though it hurts her
to love that much...
...she has the most beautiful smile.
I remember my first communion.
I was wearing a white dress and gloves.
And I looked up at that window
and I thought...
... someday someone
would pierce my heart...
...and I would walk down the aisle
in a real white dress...
...and understand why she's smiling.
I know it sounds lame.
But I guess life's not really like that.
You can't get caught up in wishing
for something that's not gonna happen.
You gotta hold on to the next best thing.
I guess I should call Eddie.
Yeah.
I should get back to school.
So thanks.
I can see why Ryan likes it here.
Here you go. Full refund.
Thanks for coming. The show's over.
Thanks so much, though.
It was great having you.
- This kid bothering you, Summer?
- No, it's okay. Thanks.
- Thanks.
- You're making a scene.
- I need to talk to you.
- I'll IM you later.
Okay.
- Let's talk up here.
- Oh, my God. No.
- Summer, I know you're scared.
- Yeah, of you.
You kiss these other guys, but you won't
kiss me? Acknowledge me now...
...or lose me forever.
- You're dating this emo geek?
Yes, Brad, she's dating this emo geek.
Yeah, that's right. I'm a big dork
and I listen to emo. And I'm dating her.
- Why are you doing this?
- Because, Summer, I like you this much.
And if you don't feel
the same way about me, then...
Someone will have to give me
a hand down. It's high up here...
...and I could fall and that would be
embarrassing. More embarrassing.
I can't believe this.
It's all over but the big,
public make-out session.
That'll be 10 bucks, Cohen.
That's for a worthy cause.
Hey, Carl, can I talk to Eddie?
Yeah. Yeah, I'll hold on.
- Hi.
- Hey.
You packing?
Yeah.
I think I should probably go home.
Seems like the right thing to do, right?
You gotta do what's right for you.
You and Eddie.
I gotta figure out what's right for me...
...and Marissa.
Right.
So if it's the right thing to do,
why don't I want you to go?
Why don't I wanna go?
I can think of a reason.
Hello?
Theresa, are you there?
Theresa?