Dad?
You're home!
Hello, Brian.
Waverly?
Damn girl, look.
I don't know where you been,
but time's sure been good to you.
You said if we were gonna sue anybody,
it was gonna be the school, Dad.
- You said nothing about Coach Taylor.
- Jason. Take it easy, okay?
This was not Coach Taylor's fault.
Coach Taylor did not make that tackle.
I did.
- What did I tell you about using the stove?
- What?
You're acting like a damn child.
Calm down, it's just--
it was an accident.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
I don't even know
what happened.
I thought you were gonna come home from Iraq
and actually be able to help,
but you've only
made things worse.
- Now get in the truck.
- Go to hell, Dad.
Well, it is just
a couple of more days
until the future of Dillon football
is determined by the outcome of
the Buckley-Arnett Mead game.
Buckley's star running back, Denny,
is hotter than a pistol right now, folks.
And if he can help his team
overcome powerhouse Arnett Mead,
that means our Panthers
will be in the playoffs.
It all comes down
to Friday night, Panther fans.
The hog's out of the gate,
the clock is ticking, and it is on.
We are not gonna sit
on our asses
to wait and see if Buckley
beats Arnett Mead this Friday
or not, gentlemen.
We're gonna stay focused,
and we're gonna stay working.
Some things you can control.
Some things you cannot.
Time, you cannot control.
Time's our enemy.
I do not want y'all driving
yourselves crazy this week.
What happens, happens.
Ain't no spell or no bag of juju
gonna change that.
So what we're gonna do
is we're gonna stay out here
and we're gonna
work our asses off.
If the good Lord
and/or Buckley defense
decides we should get
one more shot at this thing,
well, by God,
we're gonna be ready for it.
Arnett Mead's got Johnson.
Everybody say he's one of
the best QBs in the state,
but he can't win a game
by himself.
The way I see it,
Buckley need to play Denny.
He had three sacks last Friday.
He's cold-blooded.
Ain't got nothing on me,
but he cold-blooded.
Hey, where you going?
I got a trumpet needs polishing.
She gonna try to play me.
She don't even get it.
Buckley's got to make them
spread the defense.
Not be so one-dimensional.
That's the only way
they got a chance.
Well, I'll tell Coac-
Oh, shoot.
Damn it.
I'll get it. I'm sorry.
She making any sense at all?
Think Arnett Mead
could possibly lose?
They're favored by a lot,
but Buckley does have Denny.
I mean,
he can be surprising.
He can just break a game open, so...
Well, I hope Denny
kicks Arnett Mead's ass.
'Cause I'd like to see you QB
in that playoff game.
You won't even
be here then, anyway.
Denny, Denny's good.
Actually, I will.
I'm not gonna go back to Iraq.
He's been good a long time.
I'm gonna stay here
with you and Grandma.
Really?
Yeah.
If that's all right with you.
Yeah, that's fine.
All  right.
Spread the defense!
I got you spreading the defense--
Arnett Mead tries to key on Denny,
eight in the box.
Honey?
Will you just think about something else?
What do you want me
to think about?
There's things going on in the world.
You could think about...
- the little children in...
- Oh, my heavens.
India...
You know what, there is nothing else
to think about.
Oh, baby.
There is nothing else
to think about.
You can think about how much you love me.
That's a good idea.
Why wouldn't you think about that?
Coach Eric Taylor?
- Hi.
- Yeah?
- What's this?
- You've been served.
Served by who?
Jason Street's family.
What?
That was it.
Uh, hey, Coach.
Uh, you think old Buckley's
got a shot against Arnett Mead?
Friday Night Lights - 1x12
What to Do While You're Waiting
Transcript: Raceman
Sync: Tauri41
..:: www.forom.com ::..
I can't believe
they would sue us.
You raised Jason Street.
You raised him
on that football field.
How could they possibly
blame you for what happened?
Oh, it's--
it's one of those things.
You can't make it personal.
They were probably
advised to do it by lawyers.
It's what people do now.
It's what they do.
We're covered by the school,
and it's...
It's not personal.
You just gotta look at it that way.
- Mmm...
- That's just what people do.
Ah. Morning, Clint.
How you doing today?
Busy.
Got a big game Friday night.
I got some interesting theories
on Arnett Mead, if you--
if you got some time
to talk about it.
Can't shoot the bull today.
I've got a lot of work
waiting in the back.
Okay, I'll just, uh...
I'll leave the money
on the counter.
Are--are we asking if Grandma's tests
are covered under-- under the F1 provision?
No,  'cause I think the F1,
it only covers the bloodwork.
I mean, I can't make heads or tails
of any of this.
So how's the, uh,
job hunt going?
Not really
a boom town here, Matt.
Hold  on.
Yes, I need to speak to somebody
about my mother's coverage?
Name is Lorraine Saracen.
Jason Street should not be
suing the Panthers.
Why not, Bob?
'Cause they've done
so much for him?
What, they bought him some flowers,
gave him a football, threw him some
lame-ass pancake supper.
You know, I'm sure that
just about covers everything.
Well, look who it is.
Tyra the mouth.
Your money, honey,
is on the counter for lunch.
- Honey? Honey.
- Yes, uh...
Seen these jeans
your daughter's wearing?
- What?
- You okay with these?
What?
Man, you ladies have
a genetically superior ass.
It runs in this family.
- Bye, Mom. I'm leaving.
- Oh, bye.
- I'll see you later.
- Okay.
I'm telling you,
I was at Clint's store
and he wouldn't even
look me in the eye.
I told you
that this was going to happen.
Now it's in the papers?
It's done, it's done.
On top of being
the crippled kid,
- now everyone's just gonna hate me.
- Jason...
Thanks a lot.
- You knew we had no choice.
- You had it.
You don't go against the Panthers
in this town and you know that.
Jason, you knew
this was gonna happen.
And I said it was a bad idea!
All right.
Jason...
Honey.
I'm your mother.
And there is nothing
that I wouldn't do for you.
To give you what you need
to survive right now,
we need money.
I'm just...
I've come to terms with the fact
that there are people
in this town who aren't gonna
understand that.
I'm...
I am so sorry I have
to put you through this.
- Mom...
- You have no idea-- You have no idea.
- I mean...
- It's okay, I'm not--
Coach should've put you
through tackling drills, right?
He should've done that.
I'm sorry, honey.
May--maybe he should've.
Maybe he should've.
Everybody in?
All right, listen up.
Little issue has come
to my attention, gentlemen.
The annual Women's Booster League
Rodeo Fundraiser and Fair.
- Shut up, shut up.
- Hey, hey, hey.
I know y'all would rather be
sweating out game night by yourselves
instead of being at the rodeo.
So would I.
But you know what?
These women work hard.
It's a good cause.
So we are all
gonna show our asses up there
with smiles on our faces.
Now let's go
have some fun.
Oh, really?
That game...
Hang on just a second.
Matt Saracen.
- Hey, Mr. Garrity.
- How you doin', son?
- I'm doing all right.
- What can I do for you?
- Well, if you're busy, I don't want to--
- Wait a minute.
That's all right.
Roger, Roger.
Take care of that for me.
I'll be right back.
Are you sure?
I really didn't want to interrupt you...
- Oh no, no, nonsense, son.
- Okay.
Those are just people.
You're my quarterback.
Okay.
My dad's decided
to stay here in Dillon
and not go back to Iraq.
So that I--I can stay here,
and I don't have to move
to Oklahoma with my aunt.
Well, that's damn good.
We'd hate to lose you.
Thanks.
Well, anyway, since--
Since he's not gonna be
working in Iraq,
he needs to be
working here.
And--and there's not
a lot of work here.
So I was just curious
if maybe you...
If you know of anything.
That--or--
Have  any suggestions, maybe.
Well, Matt...
I'll tell you what you do.
If you will send your dad
over to me,
I can put him to work
immediately.
You know, I probably--
I could use a new salesman.
Our sales are going through the roof right now.
You send your daddy over to me,
and I'll take care of him.
- How's that sound?
- Are you-- Th--
- thank you so much, Mr. Garrity.
- Oh, you're welcome, son.
- Come back and see me.
- I will, I will.
Yeah. Hey, you like to hunt?
All right.
Oh hey, listen.
I was just gonna let you know,
your bill's up to about $294.04.
So you can bring a check in
sometime, that'd be great.
- Thanks.
- All right. Bye.
Hey, Mitch.
Can I talk to you a minute?
Eric, man, I am so sorry.
I don't know who it was
behind this.
I know it's not you.
- I-I just didn't know what else to do, man.
- I understand
You know, I--
Hey, listen,
when I got served the papers,
I said, "I know this isn't
coming from Mitch and Joanne.
I know it's not."
Expenses are astronomical,
Coach.
- Look, I understand.
- Eric--
You probably realize, too,
it's not a great idea
to get yourself involved
in a lawsuit
that's gonna cause you
that much additional pain.
And you know this is
gonna get you nowhere.
I'm not so sure
that's the case.
Well, hell, Mitch,
what are you gonna do?
What are you gonna do?
You're gonna sue the school?
What are you gonna prove?
That the school was negligent?
And how the hell
are you gonna do that?
I was there.
You were there.
- Everybody was there.
- I can't talk to you about this.
Mitch, it was a horrible accident,
but it was nobody's fault.
- It was nobody's fault.
- I cannot talk to you
about this.
You think this is tough
for you?
You wanna try
losing your child's legs
and losing
your child's future
and every penny
that you ever saved.
Try that on for size.
And then after that, try-
try finding where in the hell
you're gonna come up with money
to put up the ramps and doorways
all over your house,
and  pay for the unending equipment
and physical therapy.
Hell, I don't want to sue anyone.
It's killing me to do this.
But since
I'm already dead...
It doesn't matter anyway,
now does it?
Just get the hell
out of here, Coach.
Get out of here.
Hey,I don't know anything
about selling cars
- Hello, Matt!
- Hey, Mr. Garrity.
- How are you, son?
- This is my dad, Hen--Henry Saracen.
- Henry, very nice to meet you, sir.
- Very nice to meet you.
- Welcome to Garrity Motors.
- Thank you.
We are very proud to have our very own
quarterback's dad on our team.
I can tell you that right now.
- Well, I appreciate that.
- You bet.
Just step back here
and we'll set you all up.
Easy as pie.
Matt, take a look at some cars.
- Test-drive one if you want to.
- Yeah, okay.
This way, Henry. I--let me tell you,
this is really, really simple.
And we got
a friendly, friendly place.
Lot of people I think you'll enjoy working...
Hey, Waverly.
How's the tuba looking?
Bright and shiny
like your forehead.
And it's a trumpet.
How's the endless speculation
of who's gonna win
that game you guys
were talking about going?
Yeah, well, it's not like my whole life
don't hang in the balance.
Is that why you walked out on me
at the diner yesterday?
I didn't walk out on you.
You weren't talking to me,
anyway.
I was sitting
right next to you.
That is so not
the same thing.
All right, look.
Look, I know
you been gone a while.
But there's a few rules about
what's right and what's wrong
that you need to know.
Number one,
don't nobody walk out
on Smash.
Oh, good. The return
of the third person.
You know,
as fascinating as it is
to sit there
and listen to everyone talk
about how great you are,
the Waverly
has better things to do.
What's wrong with you, girl?
You know you like me.
I do like you.
I just...
I don't think we have
anything in common.
Yeah, we do.
Look, you tell me what you want
to have in common,
and I'll get it in common.
Come on, work with me, girl.
I'm trying here.
All right.
Um...is there anything
about you
that isn't football 24/7?
Hell, yeah.
- Uh...
- Anything else that you talk about?
Do you have
any other friends that...
Matt Saracen
and Julie Taylor.
We chill all the time.
Talk about a whole mess of stuff
besides football.
I mean... Immigration,
Iraq...
books, music.
Stem cell research.
Global warming. You name it.
In fact, I'm going to the rodeo
with them on Friday.
You should come along.
See what I mean.
All right.
We'll give the Waverlash
one last try.
The Waverlash?
That's what you called it?
Oh, that Smash mouth
contagious, girl.
Matt, sweetie?
Don't forget
about my tea.
I know, I won't, Gran--
The water's almost ready there.
You know, I hate for you
to wait on me,
but I promised y'all I wouldn't
mess with that stove.
Oh, shoot.
Um, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I've been sitting at the library
for an hour.
And that's my fault. And I apologize.
It's just that my--
My grandma called,
and she thought
that there was this really
big mouse in the house,
so I came home, and then
this whole place was sort of a mess.
So I started cleaning it up.
And then I remembered
that I had to get dinner ready
- before my dad gets home,
- Matty, I sure could use that tea.
and I gotta make tea
for my grandma.
It's on its way, Grandma.
- Um, so I gotta be--
- Okay, how about
you make dinner and I'll
make your grandma some tea?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Well, thanks.
Would now be a bad time
to tell you that I told Smash
that we'd double-date
with him and Waverly
and we'd pretend
that we do that a lot,
and we talk about all sorts of
neat stuff besides football?
- I heard you!
- The last time you went out
with this loser, you were gone
for three days.
- I won't have that again--
- All right, all right, all right!
No!
- I said no. You heard me.
- No?
What the hell
is the matter with you?
Are you telling me when I can
and can't leave this house?
- It has nothing to do--
- Are you high?
Bob, it has nothing to do
with that--
You know why people leave you?
Because you
drive people crazy!
Put a bullet in my head.
Get  out of my way!
Get out of my way!
- Don't you dare touch her.
- Tyra!
Get the hell away from her!
Get the hell out!
Don't you ever
touch my mother again.
I will kill you!
I'll kill you!
Get the hell out!
You understand?
Do you understand me?
Get out, get out.
Do it!
Get out of here!
Do it.
- Get out, get out.
- Do it.
Get out, get out.
Get out.
Oh, my God.
Hey, babe.
I love you guys.
And you guys are the best parents
in the world.
Good night.
No, honey.
Something terrible
must've happened.
Julie?
There's no adult
looking out for him.
I mean, it's crazy.
He's just by himself,
doing the cooking,
and the cleaning,
the shopping.
He takes care
of his grandma.
His dad's been home
for two weeks,
and there's still a table
full of insurance forms
for his grandma.
And he has school,
and work, and football.
I just...
I feel like
it's just gonna crush him.
Nothing's going to crush
Matt Saracen.
He's like a little stinkbug.
You can't crush him.
He's tough.
He'll be fine.
Well...
I do think it is an awful lot
for one 16-year-old to have to handle.
I might be able
to do something.
I don't know. Have him
come see me at school.
Okay.
Thanks, Mom.
Good night.
You're the best.
What do you mean, she's the best?
What about me?
Hey!
Aren't you gonna get up?
I don't think he's coming back.
God, Mom,
he's just a stupid guy.
It's not like Jesus Christ
just left you.
I'm just not used
to being alone.
But you're not alone.
You got me.
Nice, Henry.
Bagged 'em.
Oh...
God.
Where'd they go?
I thought they were ready
to take delivery
when I handed them to you.
Well, it turned out it wasn't
a good time for them, financially.
Henry...
It's never a bad time
with 5.9% financing.
Never a bad time.
I got an idea.
Come with me.
I tell you what I'd like
for you to do,
I'd like for you
to wear this.
And it'll just
help to remind people
that you served this country
for 20 years.
I don't know if I would
think that was right,
using that to sell cars.
Well, Henry...
um, salesmen...
they sell themselves.
I mean you are what you are.
And that's something
to be proud of.
And I'll just tell you right now,
I have the greatest respect...
for our men in the military.
You guys are what
makes this country great.
And God bless you.
All right.
Yes, sir.
I think that'll help.
Looks good.
Someone sleeping over?
There's sheets on the couch.
No, that's my dad.
Him and mom are just
fighting a lot now.
They're just like pissed at each other
even when nothing's going on.
I think it's just all...
All this, you know?
Jason, do you think this lawsuit
is the best idea?
- You been talkin' to Buddy?
- No.
I'm just asking you
as someone who loves you.
And is on your side.
I can't come up with
anything else. I mean...
Everything costs so damn much.
I mean, there's just...
But everyone would have
looked out for your family.
The town cripple?
How long do you think that charity
would have lasted, huh?
It's killing me to have to
do this to coach.
And it's killing me to have
to do this to the team.
But maybe they're all right.
The lawyers, my parents,
maybe they're right.
Maybe someone teaches me
how to tackle somebody,
I'm not in a chair.
We're not in this mess.
If you think this is
for the best, then...
I'm with you.
What is it with you
that you wanna
screw your life up for me?
Love makes us
kind of stupid.
Well, thank God for that.
Hey, Dad!
How was the first day
at work?
It was great.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Sell a bunch of cars?
Actually, no.
What are you up to?
Um, you know, history.
All right, I'm gonna
wash up for dinner.
Hey.
So what are you doing
out here?
Honestly, I was just kinda
wishing that Arnett Mead
loses to Buckley
and then we get to go
to the playoffs.
And then I don't have to spend
every day of the rest of my life
wondering what if as
I'm punching at the feed store.
The feed store?
Yeah, okay.
What is all that?
This is some kind
of frozen casserole.
My mom made it.
Just thought
it would help out.
Am I really that pathetic?
No, you're not pathetic.
You just...
You just do so much, that...
I just thought
you could use some help out.
I don't know
what I was expecting
to be different
with my dad living here.
Maybe he just needs some time
to settle in.
It seems like
the more he settles in,
the more uncomfortable he gets.
I don't know.
I guess I wanted him
to want to be here,
not just to be here.
It makes sense, though.
He's been in the Army
for 20 years.
That's what he does,
what he's good at.
That's what he takes pride
in doing.
Now he's trying to be a dad.
And that means he's gotta
wake up and sell used cars
every morning
for Buddy Garrity.
I can't take it personally
that he's not happy here.
Matt, you can just
get angry.
No, I can't.
He's trying.
I mean, what else
can you really ask of anyone?
Welcome,
ladies and gentlemen
to the annual Women's
Booster's Club Rodeo Fair!
I'm getting gray hair
over this Arnett Mead game.
Getting gray hair
over this damn lawsuit.
I'm getting a lot
of gray hair this week.
And I'll tell you,
if this job gets cut out
from under me, there ain't
gonna be no more coaching.
- That's not gonna happen.
- No, that's what'll happen.
Don't forget how good you are
at what you do.
That's the problem,
it's not up to me.
- I know we gotta go to the rodeo.
- Sorry, I know.
So there's this art house theater
about 40 miles from here.
I saw just Cocteau's
Beauty and the Beast.
It was really cool.
I mean, even Matt liked it.
Wait, pause.
- Matt goes to foreign art films with you?
- Yeah.
Uh, Smash does too.
He thought it was really interesting.
Really?
Man, what the hell is Julie
getting my ass into?
Italian cinema?
Hey, have you heard anything
about the game?
- Oh, you ain't hear?
- What?
Danny blew a knee.
No!
Oh man, we're finished.
Man, this is over.
We're done.
Man, this ain't exactly
going the way I was hoping.
What?
What are you talking about?
Man, I've never
known a girl like this.
Like what?
Like she won't pay attention to me,
but I know she likes me.
Maybe that's just her way
of getting you to pay attention to her.
I don't wanna
pay attention to her.
I want her to pay attention to me.
- Okay.
- That's how I'm used to it.
If you like her...
maybe you should
get used to a new way.
Wait, seriously,
Denny blew out his knee?
Yeah, baby!
Yeah!
I never thought
I'd be rooting for Buckley.
- Buddy Garrity.
- Yes, Ma'am.
I'm sorry, it was just on,
I swear.
- You promised.
- No, I know--I'm here.
Hey, I'll be back.
Would you come on now?
You're with me, Buddy.
Thanks.
Hey, Mom,
did you ever think
of moving out of Dillon?
I did leave Dillon.
I moved to Dallas when I was 18.
So then what happened--I mean,
why'd you leave?
I fell in love with your father.
I came up here to visit and
he wouldn't go to Dallas, so...
You never know.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Just one second.
One second.
Just for a minute.
No drama.
Just for a minute, please.
I can't explain this to her
anymore, I can't.
This was too much, Bob.
It was too much.
- You ready for this?
- Yep.
Let's go.
Tyra, people have fights.
People do have fights.
They don't
have fights every day.
They don't let men
beat the hell out of them.
Don't look at me
like that, honey.
Mom,
you know, I love you more
than anything in this world.
So much.
You're an amazing woman
and you are a damn good mother.
But God, you are such a loser
when it comes to men.
You're gonna let that man
back into our house
and I will not accept it.
Well,
- it is not your decision.
- I'm making it my decision.
I love you too much to watch him
do that to you anymore.
He comes back,
I'm moving out.
- Oh, Tyra, don't be silly--
- I'm serious.
It's him or me.
You choose.
I could so take that guy.
So, uh,
how'd you like that concert at UT?
Concert at UT?
Yeah.
Oh, you mean the one
I went to with Matt and Julie.
Yeah, that one.
Come on, man.
Keep your feet solid!
Okay, who'd you say you saw
perform at the concert?
It was, uh, this band.
What were they called?
Do you even know?
I mean, was it a band?
Or was it a man?
Or was it a woman?
Was it a symphony orchestra?
Do you ever hang out
with Matt and Julie?
I...
You got 'em to lie to me?
It's your own damn fault.
You can't even see
what's right in front of you.
I'm Smash.
Who wants to see me take on
this sorry ass arm wrestling champ?
That's right.
Yeah.
I got five on it, baby.
That's all you do is talk.
Come on, baby, let's go.
Hey.
You okay?
Not really.
What's wrong?
My mom's gonna be an idiot
and let that jerk
back into our house.
I'm sorry.
There's a trait in the women in my family
that just drives men crazy.
They treat us like crap
and always come back for more.
That's, uh...
That's actually what I was
here to talk to you about.
I am truly sorry.
For everything
that has happened.
For what
I've put you through.
Everything that happened with Lyla.
I was a complete jerk
and I am so sorry.
If you would even consider
giving me a second chance, Tyra,
believe me, it'll be so different.
Sorry.
You know, so many times,
I would have loved...
to hear those words
come out of your mouth.
God, I'd love to say yes.
But I'd hate myself for it.
I'd be a hypocrite, you know?
I guess timing's everything.
That's what I'm talkin' about!
The Smash, baby!
Ladies and gentlemen,
our first cowboy out tonight--
And, ladies and gentlemen,
here's a little treat for you.
...has blocked the kick!
They've got the ball!
No one in front of him
Across mid-field!
He's gonna score!
The 20, the 10!
Touchdown!
Panthers fans, get ready!
We're going to the playoffs!
Comin' for
to carry me home
Thank you, Lord,
for letting Buckley win.
I know that it was nothing
short of a miracle.
And I thank you
for that miracle.
I know you truly are
an all-powerful God
to let such a crap team win.
I know I've sinned,
but I have to ask
for one more thing.
And I know that you know
what it is before I ask for it.
The playoffs.
State.
If it's your will, let us win State,
dear God.
In Jesus' name.
Amen.
Coach.
Listen.
I just came out here
to let you know...
that no matter
what anyone says,
no matter what happens
with this whole lawsuit thing,
just know that it was...
it was not in my hands.
And I was against it.
And that you'll always
be my coach.
Hey, Dad!
How's it goin'?
Goin' good.
How you doin'?
Can I interest you in a Malibu?
Uh, yeah,
I wouldn't mind one.
Um...
Look...
I know that you hate it here.
It's kind of obvious in the mornings
when you're getting dressed.
And you're putting on the Buddy Garrity
American flag pin.
- I'll get used to it.
- I don't think you need to.
I can keep taking care of grandma
and going to school,
it's okay.
No, really, Dad.
She's been
doing really well lately and...
Look, you
can go back to Iraq.
I know how much it means
to you to be there.
And it means so much to me
that you wanted to stay here.
But it's okay.
I don't know
if I can agree to that.
- You can have no legal guardian.
- Dad, I don't know that I can let you not agree to that.
Not really
much of a car salesman, am I?
Yeah, but you're
a really good soldier.
Sometimes
that doesn't mean much.
Yeah, well,
sometimes it does.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
I told you, it was him or me.
I wasn't kidding.
Tyra,
did you really think that
I would choose a man over my daughter?
Well, I wouldn't.
I'm sorry about last night.
I'm sorry that I got
Matt and Julie to lie for me.
They feel bad, you're pissed.
And it's all my fault.
And I'm truly sorry
about that.
- Yeah, me too.
- There's something else I gotta say.
Yeah, I like myself.
And I love football.
I love it.
I love the game.
I love the crowds.
I love the attention.
I love being a star.
I can't help it.
It's a beautiful thing. It's just who I am.
It's how God made me.
I like you a lot, Waverly.
I mean...
more than I've ever liked
any other girl.
But...
if you don't like me
for me...
then I gotta live with it.
'Cause I can't be nobody but the Smash.
And yes, I like talking
about myself in the third person.
Something tells me
deep down inside you like it too.
I'll see you around, Smash.
Sometimes the problem is
that what's gonna happen
just isn't up to you.
Then fate takes a turnaround
to the backyard
and suddenly it is all up to you.
Brace yourself, Dillon.
We're going into a hell of a game.