Kissing you was great.
There's this part of me
that's still hung up
on this other girl...
Touchdown, East scores!
The Lions may have found
a quarterback
that is the real deal.
Maybe I should have left already.
Do you even want me to stay?
Of course I want you to stay!
He's leaving.
He's really leaving.
I'm trying to hear
if she's still crying.
Take her.
- He'll call eventually.
- He hasn't called yet.
- You want some coffee?
- Yes, please.
Hi, sweetie.
How you doing?
Fine.
Go, cattle. Go, cattle!
- We'll be all right, Maggie.
- Yep! Get up, cow!
They can't get out,
they can't get stolen.
What idiot would steal these cows?
- Cow rustlers.
- Cow rustlers?
What is this, the wild west?
- This sucks.
- Don't say sucks. Have a vocabulary.
I'm sorry, mom.
Luke and I'll get that fence fixed.
We'll be fine.
Luke, you'd best plan on missing
some school this week.
You want me to miss school for a week
'cause some idiot stole our cows, dad?
I got to go to school.
If I don't, they won't let me practice.
We got a huge game coming up.
I got to practice, we can win this game.
I'd hire someone if I could, Luke.
We don't have any money...
What do you want me to say?
Wait, shh, shh.
What's going on?
Nothing is going on,
except for the fact that you won us
a blue ribbon award
for academic excellence!
- Congratulations, Tami.
- Take a look!
Tami, one year as principal,
and you got Dillon
- the blue ribbon award. Incredible.
- Dillon High is a blue ribbon school.
This is great news!
- How about that?
- It's yours!
He's here!
Daddy!
He's cute!
- I missed you.
- Look at you! Look the hell at you!
- Stop growing up!
- There's not much I can do about that.
Put your stuff in the guest room.
I rented out the airstream.
- You all set? You got to go to school.
- I drove all night. I'll take her.
Well, we got all her stuff ready.
Go settle in, you'll see her later.
- All right. Bye, bye.
- Bye.
How you doing?
- You're the renter?
- I am, yeah.
I'm Tim, by the way.
Nice to meet you.
Let's go, bring it in!
Come on, let's go.
Hey, listen now.
Campo Park...
two weeks.
This is a game we are gonna win.
And we're gonna be going
into this game
a little bit different.
You've got about 30 seconds
before this gentleman puts on
that uniform and get some licks on him,
'cause you're looking
at our new quarterback.
Let's get it together.
We got work to do!
4x07: IN THE BAG
Subtitles: Team Lions
With the participation of:
Benj!, Collioure, DarKsh, GillesSilb,
Jenn, Ju, Loky, Nam, Ouazo
Julie may I ask...
why you are signing up
for every club that is available?
'Cause I can.
You're really signing up
for the school beautification committee?
And you're signing up for the book club,
which would normally be fine,
except for this week's book
is Twilight.
Just leave me alone, okay?
You do realize that he was
my best friend too, you know?
Yep. And that's why I signed you up
for the academic smackdown.
- What is that?
- It's like quiz bowl.
It's after school.
I'll see you in the cafeteria.
Right. Well, I...
Yeah. We got the invoice
two days ago.
Well, I can't pay the invoice a week ago
if I just got it two days ago.
Hang on one second, would you, please?
Come here.
You were absent today, you can't go
to practice. You got a good excuse?
Yes, sir. My dad's making me fix
our fence.
You have to fix a fence?
Are you kidding with me?
We don't have any money.
We can't hire nobody.
Can I tell you something?
We need you, you understand that?
You're absent, you can't practice.
You can't practice, you're not playing.
So here's what you need to do.
Fix your fence.
In the middle of the night,
I don't care, or in the morning,
before you come to school,
but you make it to school on time.
You get here on time,
you go to practice.
- Okay.
- Good. I'll see you tomorrow.
Don't be absent again.
Go.
You there?
Yeah, listen, we just got
the invoice, though.
Let move that piece already!
Calm down!
- What?
- I got a buck.
Sorry... funding right now.
Billy, I need more money.
- One sec.
- God, the baby's... baby on board.
$1.75...
- It's that simple.
- I got it, 37 cents...
Oh, god!
No, please stop.
- Calm down! What is wrong?
- Contraction.
- Still not there? What?
- Contraction!
You're 7 months pregnant...
- Please go to the hospital.
- We got food there...
Oh, god!
Please go!
- Get the food.
- Oh, god!
Thanks.
- Go, go, go, go, go!
- Sorry...
- Baby, you okay?
- Oh, god!
Do you have any idea
what kind of losers
are gonna be at academic smackdown?
You realize the irony
behind the term academic smackdown?
Shut up, Landry.
- Goody...
- Is this one taken here?
Fancy seeing you here.
This isn't gonna be awkward
or anything, is it?
Well, if it's gonna be
awkward for you, you can leave.
I do this smackdown
every single year, so you being here
is of no consequence to me.
Welcome to East Dillon
academic smackdown team...
who have an event this weekend
against another school
in our district
at West Dillon, our sister school,
our blue ribbon sister school.
I need you to perform well at this.
All right, study.
This is exciting.
Learning...
Your mom is gonna kill me!
Well, what's she gonna do,
divorce you?
Oh, wait.
She already did that.
- A dog's a lot of work, Beck.
- I know.
I can do it. Besides, I get
really lonely when mom's at work.
Do you ever think
you're gonna move home?
I mean, I know you and mom
aren't gonna get back together, but...
if you lived in town,
we could see more.
Give me a little time, all right?
I'm working on it.
Puppies!
I like this one.
He's gonna do 50 sit-ups in 30 seconds.
Hit the floor. Let's go.
- You're challenging me.
- Yeah.
You ready, Coach?
Go!
Hey, Levi...
- Gentlemen?
- We need to see Vincent Howard.
- What's going on?
- We got a report that
he had a gun on school grounds. These
officers need to search his locker.
Report from who?
We need to check the locker.
Well, look, maybe we should...
clear something...
The police are here.
Go.
Second one on the end.
It's got a name on it.
- It's clean.
- Thank you, gentlemen.
I'll meet you in front.
- All right, dad, I'll be back later.
- Where you going?
I'm going to school, dad.
Luke, get back here.
Dad, I cannot miss practice.
I cannot miss school.
I'll build it,
I'll stay up till midnight, I'll get up
at dawn, but I'm going to school.
Luke, you get your ass
back here now!
I'll be back later, dad.
I want to admit you
to the hospital overnight.
She needs to be on the magnesium
sulfate for at least 24 hours.
Everything's gonna be okay, right?
I mean...
the baby and everything.
She's gonna be fine?
It should be, but she's going
to need to go on bed rest.
Okay, um...
- For how long?
- 2 months. Until the baby's full-term.
I'll check back later.
Oh, my god.
Everything's gonna be fine, okay?
You aren't gonna have to do anything.
Me and Tim will take care of everything.
You won't have to lift
a finger, all right?
Uh, doc?
Look, I don't exactly have
insurance right now.
I mean, I was... I was gonna pay
for the birth out of pocket, but...
I wasn't exactly expecting it
to cost this much.
Is there anything...
we might be able to work out
or some kind of deal or...?
You know, it...
It costs what it costs.
There are payment plans,
but still...
The contractions are waning.
You can take her home
and keep her on her side
and well-hydrated...
It may be enough.
Then, we'll keep her here overnight.
Premature labor is something that
usually happens more than once, okay?
Yeah...
What am I supposed to do?
It's not like I've much of a choice.
No... I mean, I guess not.
I mean, I don't know.
You know,
if they'd come in saying...
open up Landry's locker,
would you have just done that?
I don't know
what I would have done then.
I think the real question is
do you think that he has a gun?
- Well, I sure as hell hope not.
- But do you think it's possible?
I-I don't know, honey.
Anything's possible, isn't it?
Seems like maybe
you ought to just ask him.
I mean, he's never gonna trust
you unless you trust him, you know?
Okay.
What year was the battle
of Stalingrad?
- 19... 1941.
- Wrong.
- 1942.
- Thank you.
Can you lighten up?
Jeez, you're making me go blank.
I'm making you go blank?
How do you think you're gonna feel
when you're having to answer
these questions in front
of all those people?
You're gonna...
Hey, come here.
These are very basic questions
I'm asking right now.
What? He knows nothing
about World War II!
- Hey, hey. Come here, come here.
- What?
Just take a deep breath, okay?
I understand that you're going through
a lot, that you're in a lot of pain...
This has nothing to do with Matt.
I want to do well on the smackdown, OK?
- You know what? Just climb off my back.
- You're lying, it's about Matt.
- It's not about Matt.
- Deal with the fact that...
Come here.
Close the door.
- Sit down.
- What's up?
How you doing?
I'm good.
A little sore, but I'm good.
I got to ask you a question.
You got a gun?
I'm just asking you straight up.
Have you got a gun?
Do you have gun, do you carry a gun,
do you have a gun in your locker...
I don't know, a gun.
Give me an answer.
Talk to me.
No, I ain't got no gun.
That's all I wanted to know.
I don't know.
Do the swaddle-and-shush thing.
Babe, I don't know.
I'm not a friggin' midwife.
So I don't know.
I'll be home in a few days, all right?
Then I'm yours.
Yeah, yours and the baby's.
All right.
Love... love you back.
Trouble at home, huh?
Becky says you were some kind of big
football deal around here. Is that it?
Something like that.
Yeah. I bet that was
pretty good times, huh?
Yeah, it had its moments.
You're young yet.
It'll change, believe me.
- You're not married, are you?
- No.
Don't ever get married,
don't ever have kids.
You don't like your kids?
No, I love my kids.
It's just that it... it never ends.
Right. I mean...
A baby and all,
I'm sure it's a lot.
All right, look,
I got a baby
with this girl in Seattle.
You know how it goes, right?
Now she wants to get married...
There's just never enough to go around.
Yeah. You're spreading
yourself pretty thin.
- Becky know about Seattle?
- Oh, no, no.
And I don't want her to.
It was a present!
Forget it!
I'm walking!
I'm not going anywhere with you!
You are being ridiculous.
You've got one hell of a nerve bringing
that dog in here without asking.
There's nothing wrong
with her having a little dog.
Julie.
- Julie Taylor.
- Hey, Mrs. Saracen.
Oh, it's so good to see you.
Come in here, sweetie.
Shelby, look who's here.
It's Julie.
It's so good to see you.
- How you doing?
- Good.
Well, we're doing just fine, honey.
Shelby here,
she's taking real good care of me.
Well, I'm trying.
That's good to hear.
I'm sure this whole Matt thing
must be so hard on you.
Lord, Julie, at first...
it was just awful.
But, you know,
now that I know he's fine,
then I'm fine.
You talked to Matt?
Yeah. He even called again yesterday,
and let us know he got the place.
He told you, I'm sure.
Yeah, he did.
Well, you know what?
We were just about to have an ice cream
sandwich. Let me get you one.
He's just going through
a lot, you know?
He'll call.
He'll be in touch soon.
You're broke, I'm broke...
We got to sell something.
What do we have to sell?
We don't have anything besides Kit Kat.
No, we're not selling Kit Kat.
He's the face of Riggins' Rigs.
You're right.
I love that damn cow.
Cheers, boys.
Couple beers on me.
- Thank you.
- How's my girl doing?
She's doing good.
She's doing better.
Her mom's taking care of her right now,
give Tim and I a break from the...
- ringing of the bell every 5 seconds.
- That bell...
What? I don't want her
to stress out about things.
Me and the girls been talking,
and we wanna throw Mindy a baby shower.
- Sweet, that's great.
- But we also wanna tie in a fundraiser.
Make it a co-ed shower,
girls dance and whatnot,
guys pay admission and whatnot.
All the proceeds go to help Mindy,
baby, and all the medical bills.
Yeah.
No, I-I like this.
Mindy and I have been friends
since she was 17, okay?
She's like a sister to me.
I want to do this.
Where...
where would we do it, though?
- Your place isn't big enough?
- Not for something like this.
No, he can't host it.
He lives in a trailer.
- What about...?
- Riggins' Rigs.
That may be the smartest thing
you've ever said in your entire life.
- Could work.
- Riggins' Rigs.
Sounds like a plan, okay?
Enjoy the beers.
Thank you.
Great call.
- Thank you, Hannah!
- Yeah.
What about Stephen Crane? Does anybody
need to read Stephen Crane anymore?
I think we can do without Stephen Crane,
go on to something a little fresher.
Did you, uh, get a chance
to go out and celebrate, last night?
Well, we kind of did.
- Kind of?
- We had a little dinner last night.
There's a lot going on
in my house at the moment,
so it was...
sort of a celebration.
Well, this is kind of a big deal.
You know, you ought to take a night
for yourself, go out,
you know, cut it loose.
How about this?
What would you think
if I got a group
of the teachers together,
some of the staff,
and all of us together, we went out,
and we celebrated you
and your accomplishment?
I think that would be so much fun.
It doesn't have to be about me.
It's about celebrating everybody.
I think that's a great idea.
How about this...
you, me, the staff...
Karaoke?
Let's do it.
Hey, man.
What's going on, man?
You dead or something?
Doing this whole drunk-out wino thing
gonna get you nowhere with the ladies.
No, I was just up all night.
Probably gonna be up all night
every night this week.
What the hell was you doing?
Got to rebuild the entire fence
at the ranch. Some idiot's been
stealing all the cows.
Maybe I can ask the team. Maybe some
of us come out and give you a hand.
Right.
You think they'd do that?
Man, I'll ask.
It don't hurt to ask, dude.
All right, you do that, and...
I'll just be here
sleeping, all right?
Okay, cool.
Damn.
These are pretty good fries.
Thank you.
- Can I help you?
- I'm Vincent's mother...
Regina.
Oh. Oh, I'm sorry.
How are you?
I'm well.
I'm afraid the last time
you saw me, I was...
in not such good shape.
Well, I'm working on it.
That's good.
I just wanted to come by
and say thank you...
Thank you for making my son
quarterback.
You know, things like that
ain't supposed to happen to us.
We don't get a lot of good breaks.
You should have seen
the look on his face
when he told me...
It was like he was a kid again.
I haven't seen that face
in a really long time.
I didn't give it to him.
He earned it.
I thank you...
for believing in my boy.
He's a good kid.
You're welcome.
Nice.
That was great!
I can't believe that!
Have some shots
coming to the table, folks.
Pass them around, pass them around.
- Who ordered shots?
- I ordered.
Everybody's taking a taxi home.
That's it.
- Thank you, Glenn.
- Thank you!
So I, uh...
I would like to propose a toast.
I think we've all been
at Dillon for a while now,
and I think most of us know
what it was like before Tami got here.
- Yeah, it sucked.
- It did suck.
But what matters most is that we know
what it's like now that you're here.
- To a job well done.
- Always smart, always professional.
That's right,
you get the job done every time,
in spite of all of that political crap
and that football stuff
and just the district and everything.
No, I mean, it's... It's really meant
a lot to us and to me.
To our fearless leader.
Well, to all of y'all.
To everybody.
Congratulations!
- Well done. Cheers, y'all.
- Cheers.
- When do you think the cabs come?
- I don't know.
They'll be here in a minute.
That was...
pretty awesome, wasn't it?
That was really fun.
We should do it more often, you know?
We should do it all the time.
I don't know if you'll feel that way
when you wake up with your head banging.
Be totally worth it. I wanted you
to have a good night, you know?
You're so sweet.
Thank you.
Well, there you go.
Oh, here's a cab.
Great, great. All right.
You go ahead.
I'll, um, wait for the next one.
I'm gonna take you up
'cause you're a gentleman.
All right, thank you, that was...
It was such a... such a fun thing, and
it was good for everybody, I thought.
You're the best, Tami.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry.
- No, it's okay, I...
- No, it's...
You get yourself home safe, okay?
I'll see... I'll see you
at school, all right?
Why are you here?
How you doing?
You like being quarterback?
Quarterback's a leader.
Quarterback makes decisions,
makes choices.
Quarterback has got to be clear
on what has got to be done.
You've got to make a decision.
Why do you care
about what I do so much?
What you getting out of this?
Ain't I just another player
that can throw the ball and run fast?
If I break my ankle and can't play,
you still gonna come around here?
You still gonna check up on me?
This is my life.
I been living here ten years
and seen three of my best friends
get killed walking to school.
When I leave your practice,
I'm the one looking over my shoulder,
hoping I don't get jumped,
robbed, killed...
You get any more trouble with the law,
you're going straight to juvie.
Who puts the food up there
on the table?
Who makes sure the bills get paid?
Who's gonna take care of that
if you're locked up?
I'm offering you...
everything I got.
This is not just about football.
Think about that.
I beg of you,
think about what I just said.
Welcome to
the 2009 academic smackdown.
Testing, testing.
Hi, Glenn.
- How you doing today?
- Good. Good, good, good.
Almost set up.
How you feeling today?
I feel like the...
like the biggest idiot
that ever lived.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not okay.
I mean, I-I-I practically
raped you, you know?
- No, you didn't.
- Well, no, I mean, not...
not literally, but with my mouth...
It's like I mouth-raped you.
- No.
- I can't believe I did that.
I mean, I'm Mr. Liberal,
you know? I grab...
a beautiful married woman,
and I-I-I kiss her
like I'm some sort of,
you know, Neanderthal,
unevolved caveman or something,
and I am not that type of person.
- I'm not somebody who does that.
- I know. Glenn, I know.
I don't want you to beat
yourself up about it.
You did such a nice thing for all of us
last night, for me and for everybody,
and it was such a nice party
that you planned, and...
That last part...
can't ever happen again, that's all.
Okay, this is for East Dillon High.
Name the first novel
and the last novel
by the mid-century American novelist
Thomas Wolfe,
both of which deal
with the American theme
of the wanderer.
I know this.
Anyone want to take this?
Here we go.
The first and last novel
by mid-century American novelist
Thomas Wolfe,
both of which deal
with the American theme of...
the wanderer...
The first is...
Look homeward, Angel,
and the second is...
You can't go home again.
That is correct.
East Dillon takes the lead.
Now for Remington High.
Take a break.
We got you covered.
Come here, sweetie.
Come here.
He called his grandmother...
and his mom.
I thought he was the one.
I know.
He can't even call
after three years?
I don't know what to do...
I'm so tired of feeling like this.
I know.
And you're gonna survive,
and good things are gonna start
to happen again.
And one day, you may even look back,
and even this will not be
such a bad thing.
Who the hell's that?
- I thought you bring the whole team.
- They all had some party to go to.
Who is he?
That's Tinker. He's on my team.
He came to help out.
Thanks for coming, Tink.
Hello, Tyra.
This is Landry Clarke calling.
I am here at the...
designated rest stop
that we agreed upon.
It's kind of obvious that you are...
not gonna show up, which is fine,
I just kind of wanted to...
see you face-to-face
and kind of find out what the deal is,
if I'm supposed to wait for you or not.
Because if I'm supposed to,
I will wait.
I will...
wait like one of those
British foot guards
outside of Buckingham Palace.
I will keep my eyes straight ahead.
I won't look to the left
or to the right.
I kind of have a feeling
that you're probably...
looking to the left
or the right or both...
Which is fine...
I guess I kind of
just answered my own question.
I guess I will...
see you around, then.
Everybody, thank you
very much for coming out.
Remember that every
raffle ticket that you buy,
every dollar that you stick
between the thighs
of one of these luscious,
beautiful women goes to help me,
goes to help you, goes to help my family
and my future kid, all right?
Thank you for coming out.
I can't open it.
You got to help me.
Everybody rip it!
Come here.
Let me holler at you.
- It's a nice place you got right here.
- Thank you.
Ready to make some real money?
Yeah, I...
I need to make some money.
I got a business opportunity
that can really make you a rich man.
What kind of business opportunity
you talking about?
I can't talk
about that right now, man.
- Okay.
- But...
Let me holler at my man.
I'll get back.
Congratulations on the kid, man.
Hey, Tim Riggins.
What are you doing here?
- Surprised to see me?
- Yes, I am surprised to see you.
- Why are you here?
- Mom's at work.
Dad's at a bar.
Mom gave the dog back.
She always has to have
everything her way.
Can't wait till my dad comes back.
Come on, let's dance.
Becks, come here for a second.
Come here,
listen to me for one second.
Your dad's not coming back.
How would you know that?
I know he's not coming back,
because I heard him on the phone.
He's got a kid.
He lives in Seattle.
He's got a whole family there.
That's why he bought you a dog.
Listen to me.
This is what they do...
Your dad, my dad.
They leave, and they don't come back.
They buy you these things
so it's not uncomfortable for the five
minutes a year they're in your face.
You start to blame yourself,
the people around you,
because they've tried,
and you pushed...
- Listen to me.
- Could you not do it here, please?
- I want you to know it's not...
- Can we just talk about this at home?
Can we just talk about this at home?
Tink, where'd you learn
how to build like this?
My granddad worked in construction.
You know what you're doing.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
No big deal.
Luke's a good guy.
He's one of those players
that's holding this team together.
He's pretty much a star.
Never acts like it, though.
I figure you know that.
I figure if I'm helping out Luke,
I'm helping out the team.
You're a good man.
I told you not to tell her!
- What?
- I said I was gonna tell her.
I told you not to tell her.
What the hell did you do?
- You weren't gonna say a thing.
- You think you're hot stuff, don't you?
I find out you touched my daughter,
I'm gonna kick your...
Funny thing is, you don't give
a damn about your daughter.
You know what else is funny?
I had sex with your wife.
I know it's late.
I'm sorry.
But is Coach home?
Yeah. One sec.
Hon?
What you doing here?
You all right?
Yeah. I'm getting there.
There you go.
All right.
- Sorry for coming by so late.
- It's all right.
That kid trusts me.
What do we do with it?
It's gonna disappear.
It's been a strange week.
It's all right...
How you doing?
I'm here to get a dog about way big.
A disgruntled redhead
dropped him off yesterday.
And you're not gonna
bring him back tomorrow?
Because people aren't always
very responsible about these dogs.
Are you gonna be
a responsible person?
Yes, ma'am.
After this pen,
you want to call it a day?
If we don't finish up now,
we'll just have to do it again tomorrow.
All right, then.
Round them up.
- Nobody says that anymore.
- I just did.
Dad!
Get out of there!
Get out!
You all right?
Where'd he get you?
Son, you all right?
Hey, Jess.
I was looking for you,
'cause I wanted to ask you something.
Plus, I was hungry,
so I figured you make
an unbelievable pulled-pork sandwich,
Will you go out with me?
Things between me and Tyra
are 100% over.
My life is no longer complicated,
and I really would like
to go out with you.
I'm really happy for you.
Congratulations.
Just one date.
Why would I do that?
I don't...
I have a car.
Play guitar.
I might write you a song someday.
You'd be the girl... I don't know.
Would you please go on a date with me?
So, yes?
All right, you tell me
what your name's gonna be.
'Cause Julien it's not.
Yeah, I know.
It is boring, isn't it?
How about Skeeter?
Oh, look at that.
Skeeter it is.
It's Skeeter.
Your new name
is skeet man.
You're the skeeter.
You're still whining,
and I don't know why.
Whatever you do,
don't go in here, okay?
That's lesson...
lesson number one.
Here, don't go in here.
We're gonna pull in right now.
Here we go.
Just please don't go in my truck.
I'm gonna let you go.
Okay. Do your thing.
Do your thing, Skeeter.
It's pretty great.