Franckly, you're not a mother.
You have no idea what was the situation.
Sometime, we're gonna have a whole
conversation where you don't say that.
- You come out of there.
- You gotta calm down.
You don't just open the door.
This is not your house anymore.
What I say you had to do to stay here?
Did I tell you how to feed the furrets?
You take care of yourself,
everything else take care of itself.
They're not pressing charges.
We're interupting your programing
for some important wheater information
from the south west regional
wheater center.
They've issued
a severe thunder storm warning
for Hart and Reed counties
and a tornado watch continues
for Alan and Carr counties.
- Very heavy rainfall.
- I know that look.
- Someone's hungry.
- I know that, it's time.
Come one baby.
Thank you.
Would you something nice?
Oh my God.
I'm out of formula.
You are such a little pig, you know?
You eat so much, you gotta stop.
What happens
when you shame people with food?
- What ?
- Anorexia. Especially in girls.
Thank you, Oprah.
Very helpful.
- Okay, maybe I did see it on Oprah.
- Oh, busted.
I don't know
what I'm gonna do because...
I mean, Shelly's boobies,
there're not gonna do the trick, right?
I'll go to the store.
- I don't want you to go in this weather.
- See you soon.
God, he's cute. No, but he's jailbait.
We stay away, okay darling?
I'm heading to the store,
you need anything?
Can I go with you?
So, are you going to the dance,
this week-end?
Are you going to fall formal?
No, I'm not going.
Are you?
No. I mean, it's kinda lame, right?
So I heard, Matty dumped
that cheerleader, is that true?
I don't know, I mean,
we don't talk.
It cleared up pretty good.
Let's go!
What are you doing?
Nothing. Let's go.
She's gonna teeth soon, right?
Yeah, in like a year.
... tornado warning from the south west
regional weather center for Alan, Carr,
Hart and Reed counties.
We've unconfirmed reports
that a tornado is near Laribee,
moving to the North East
toward the Dillon area.
Let's check the radar, this storm
is very large and dangerous
and may produce a tornado at any time.
Hey, it's a tornado!
Everybody gets away from the glass!
Come here!
Leave it!
Get down!
You okay?
- You sure?
- Yeah.
2x10: THERE GOES THE NEIGHBORHOOD
Transcript: www.swsub.com
Subtitles:
Andy, DarKsh, GillesSilb, Ju, Sixe
www.top-series.net (0.90)
All right,
I'll see you later this afternoon. Bye.
Y'all, listen to this.
The school...
The high school in Laribee...
That whole... half of that school
got completely lifted up
and knocked out by the tornado.
All those people are displaced.
What's going on with the TV?
- It's not working.
- Why?
- The cable's out.
- Oh, my lord.
I mean, those poor people are just...
What's going on?
Oh, come on.
Are you ki...
Get ready for school, please. Right now.
You are seriously no fun whatsoever.
Oh, I know. I'm so boring.
- And you, really?
- What?
Then I'll talk to you
when I get over there.
All right.
All right, good-bye.
That was our fearless leader
principal Brecker.
This storm has screwed everything up.
He wants to let the Laribee team
use our practice field
and our locker room.
- What is wrong with this TV?
- Cable's out.
What do you mean cable's out?
- How long is Tim Riggins gonna be here?
- A couple days.
- How long has the cable been out?
- Well, since the tornado.
You know, I don't necessarily think
this is gonna work out so well.
Having Riggins here
with our 16-year-old daughter
it's like putting a can of gasoline
right next to a lit match.
He'll only stay for a few days.
The kid's in trouble,
he needs a place to stay.
What're you gonna do?
I like having another guy around here,
'cause it evens up the gender team.
- It's sort of nice.
- There are no teams.
- It's not about teams here.
- You know what would be nice?
It'd be nice to show
a little bit more christian charity.
I am made of christian charity.
Now, that's not the issue at all.
How'd you sleep?
- I slept good.
- Good.
- You?
- I'm good.
Just wanted to come in and talk to you.
Okay.
Guess who's got engaged!
Who?
Me.
It's beautiful.
Kevin and I are geting married.
He proposed last night.
I love him.
Sweetie.
Congratulations.
That's great.
Let's go, let's go!
Grab that bag! Check that bag!
Is that yours?
It's gonna be a good Friday,
Football in Texas
is what it's all about.
- So how long are these guys gonna stay?
- As long as they need to.
That's awkward,
considering you're district rivals
- and you play these guys two weeks.
- What should we do?
Send them on their way?
We're not gonna do that.
The one with the hair is Eddie.
What's he got, a twin?
From the wrong end of the gene pool.
We're gonna be good hosts
and good guests.
I've kno coach Dickes for a long time.
As long as he don't stir things up,
everything will work out just fine.
- I'd give anything for that hair.
- Get out of here.
Napoleon dynamite.
- Who's the dude behind him?
- His older brother, QB1.
Thinks he's God's gift.
Can'stand that dude.
Who do you think we are, Tyra?
You think we're the Sharks or the Jets?
You know, West Side Story?
You got two rival gangs,
The town's not big enough
for the both of them. It's a classic.
You never heard of West Side Story?
No. Don'think I want to, either.
You never ever...
Well, you're missing out.
Can you hand me one of your napkins
that you're holding over there?
I only have four napkins.
Don't make fun of me.
'cause I'm neat.
I don't know how to eat this.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- You just grabed my hand.
I just thought that...
You know,
since this is all finally over, we could
free us up so we could finally
just hang out, whatever.
Yeah, look, I'm sorry. I'm just,
you know, just in a really bad mood.
And this food is horrendous.
So...
I'm gonna go.
I'll call you later.
All right?
Okay.
Is this fun? This is fun.
- It is fun.
- Lot of fun.
The most fun we've had together
in a long time.
- Relaxing, it's perfect.
- OK, dad. I'm sorry.
I feel like there's a big elephant
in the room
you're not talking about.
There's a big elephant right over there.
What elephant?
What are you talking about?
Mom and Kevin's wedding, Maybe
they're getting married over Christmas.
- I don't know.
- Wait. What did you just say?
What did you just say?
Mom and Kevin's wedding.
What are you telling me?
- That's not funny
- She didn't tell you?
Are you telling me that mom told you
she's gonna marry
that little treehugger?
Is that what you're telling me?
Dad.
Dad!
God!
Listen up!
Here's how this is gonna work out.
We gonna split this up and take shifts
between the practice field,
the showers and the weight room.
We got one locker room.
That means we're gonna be sharing.
I don't wanna hear any guff about it.
How about the visitor's locker?
Girls soccer got
the visitor's locker room.
Kick 'em out.
You're the athletic director.
All right. Now listen:
after final bell at 4:30
one team's gonna take the practice field
while the other'll take the weight room
- and the film room, all right?
- I don't know, Coach.
It's gonna be difficult to get
a 90-minute cycle in with what you got.
- What do you mean, what we got?
- The weight room's too small.
And hell, some of the machines...
Well, I guess my wife could probably use
some of the machines.
They may not even
be good enough for your wife,
but they're good enough
for a State championship last year.
Alright, quiet. Hey, quiet!
That's a fair point.
You know, maybe if you
would have stayed at TMU,
you might have won one in college, too.
Welcome to Dillon.
It's our privilege to have you here.
We are your hosts.
Understood?
Y'all know what's going on today?
Yes, sir.
All right, I think we're all understood.
I'm trying to help him out, and all
he does is keep bitching and moaning.
He's pissing me off.
He's like coach crybaby.
No, I'll tell you what I wanna do.
What I wanna do is to crush that team
and take that ball after the game
and I wanna shove it up
the s.o.b.'s rear end.
All right.
- What are you doing out here?
- Fixing the cable.
Just trust me.
Whatever you hear out here,
that stays here, all right?
It's on now!
Good job.
Tim Riggins was, like, holding you?
Like, holding me. Like, protecting me.
Not like, oh, I love you.
- What does he smell like?
- No, really, Lois...
That's, like, pathetic.
Like, here's you and there's pathetic.
You're going below yourself.
- How y'all doin?
- We're in the middle of something here.
You can finish talking.
I just got a quick question.
I'll be in the bathroom.
Basically I'm coming to you despite
what you did to my best friend
because I have a question
kind of in the female arena.
And I need to know:
are you still friends with Tyra Colette?
Last I checked...
This is kind of a sensitive area here.
Kind of on a need-to-know basis only.
'Cause me and Tyra have kind of a,
beautil,
like, a thing.
So you and Tyra have a beautiful thing?
And basically, I'm taking her
to the dance on Friday.
I needed to know if it should be a rose
or a carnation in terms of a corsage.
OK. So you're taking Tyra Colette
to the fall formal?
Does she know that?
That was funny.
Look, I realize that
our relationship may be
a little bit over your head.
If it's a question about a flower
for her, why don't you just go ask her?
OK, I have a math test in 30 minutes
and I really need to study for it.
- I'm Chip.
- That's nice.
What do you say we go somewhere
and get you out of those wet clothes?
If you ever touch me again,
I'll kick you so hard
your balls'll be nonexistent, all right?
I like that.
Heard you guys got a dance next week.
- You wanna go with me?
- No.
Why? You got a boyfriend, don't you?
Of course you do. Look at you.
- You're beautiful.
- Bye, Chip.
Will you please go to the dance with me,
unnamed goddess girl?
- Unnamed goddess girl? Who's that?
- Some douchebag named Chip.
Who names their kid Chip, anyway?
I don't know. It's kind of corny.
But, I mean, he's decent.
OK, Landry came up and talk to me today
about asking you to the dance.
And wondered whether
you like roses or carnations.
If I tell you something,
do you promise to keep it private?
You mean about you and Landry
and your thing?
Wait, how'd you hear that?
I heard it. I mean, it's not like
it's flying all over school or anything.
But personnally, I had you pegged more
for an orchid kind of girl.
- Maybe like, a purple...
- Okay, it's reay not a thing.
You know, it's a lot more
complicated than that.
So do you like him?
I don't know, I mean, he cares about me
and he's funny and sweet.
Funny.
So then what's the problem?
Yo, Smash, check it out.
Check it out, man.
Oh yeah, that's real funny.
That's real funny.
Yo, guys, check it out.
Here we go.
Hey, here we go, guys.
We'll show 'em what's up.
- Yeah, baby!
- They did it to us!
Works both ways, gentlemen.
What the hell are you doing?
The hell you doing to my locker room?
- Look what they did...
- Shut up!
You clean it up right now!
You clean everithing up,
you put it back exactly where it was.
You understand me?
Now!
I don't understand why we gotta sit
and wait around for them
- to finish their practice on our field.
- For sure.
Oh, no! Rod!
What is that? Get over here!
Come here! You don't like the helmet.
Is it the pads in general?
Something you don't like,
you gotta tell me!
Coach, it's past 4:45.
What? Already?
Waow, look it there.
- Y'all need to wrap it up, coach.
- Okay, all right. We'll wrap it up.
I'd appreciate it too
if you'd tell your players
to respect our boys' property
and stay out of our lockers.
Come on now, Eric.
It was probably
just some harmless prank.
I tell you something.
I don't mind being a good neighbor
as long as y'all play your part as well.
You don't, something's gonna
happen around here.
and I'd like to avoid that situation.
Let's get off the field, boys!
These ladies want their dance floor.
Everybody up!
What are you drinking?
Dr. Pepper, alright.
You got it. I'll be right back, y'all.
Excuse me, ma'am,
but my riblets are cold,
and it unacceptable.
You always use that one. Might wanna
come up with something original.
I don't use that every...
I guess I do use it every time.
I should probably come up
with some new material.
All right, I just wanna say I'm sorry
about what happened the other day.
Holding your hand, that was stupid.
I know you're not into pda.
And I wasn't thinking.
I just wanna say that I'm sorry.
I'm in the weeds right now.
I can't really talk about this.
I know, I just wanna ask you something.
It'll just take a second.
I think that we should
go to the dance on Friday.
Well, it's a bye week, and
we don't have a game on Friday, so...
I figured a lot of people are
going to dry creek before.
- So we could start the party there.
- I don't think I'd be interested.
Tyra, these are our golden years here.
And these high school memories
are what we're gonna have to draw on
- when we're old and in nursing home.
- not really selling the pot for me.
I know how this works,
you're gonna keep telling me no,
you gonna play hard to get
and I'm gonna keep asking you.
But you wanna go.
You owe it to yourself.
- I can't go with you.
- Why? We'd have fun.
I'm going with somebody else.
I'm sorry.
All right, well...
- Hey.
- Hey, Shelly!
Hi, what's going on?
Hello, darling.
Pretty good.
No, sir, not in this house.
Put that away, please. Thank you.
So bad.
50 bucks to finish this essay.
- Okay?
- Come on. You've got to be kidding.
You're doing that in front of me?
I don't think so.
I've got homework.
I've got ten pages
on transfer of title.
Lucky me.
- I wonder who's on Oprah.
- There is a great call.
No, we're working here.
Now, don't turn the tv on.
We're working here. The baby asleep,
and I don't want the tv on right now
to watch Oprah.
- What is that?
- Oh, my God!
That's not Oprah.
- Turn it off!
- That's my bad,
It's supposed to be football.
I'm sorry.
You know what, y'all, get out.
I gotta get work done. Get out.
Everybody out.
Go in your room.
I'll block that channel
when I come back.
- That would be a big help.
- Good luck with your paper.
- Shelly, just go. I need quiet.
- You're sending me to my room?
- Until you start acting like a grownup.
- Don't try to tell me you're not gonna
watch that tonight, because I know you.
Donald Dickes is a little jackass.
He's just trying to get under your skin.
- He's getting under my skin.
- Don't let him.
Don't sweat the small stuff.
That's what my dad used to say.
Did you hear about Pam
getting re-married?
She's getting married?
- You all right? I mean...
- No.
I mean, that woman
is the love of my life, Eric.
I mean, we've`known each other
our whole lives.
She was there in the stands watching me
win the state championship.
I married her right after high school.
You know that.
We opened this little car lot together
that little bitty place, remember?
We used to work together as a team.
I'd sell, you know,
and Pam would do the contracts.
And she'd always say:
"Buddy,
you could sell a pig to a priest."
I don't even know what that means,
but I'll always...
I love that.
So... I guess...
What do you think
I should do?
Well, you're right.
I mean, here I am five years in a row,
I'm the Texas car salesman the year.
I'm a salesman.
I oughta be able to sell own wife.
I'm gonna go over there,
and I'm gonna sell her.
I'm gonna get my wife back, by God.
That's what I'm gonna do.
Thank you.
This is the best.
Barbeque pit.
So, um, is it true that rally girls
really do all of your homework?
You mean Mrs. Taylor's daughter. No.
- I do all my homework.
- Liar.
It's true.
Do you wanna go get ice cream or,
I don't know, some more food?
I don't really care.
- No.
- Why ?
Hey, Seven.
What's up?
Hi. Hey, Carlotta.
We're just picking up food, so...
We're just leaving.
- See you around, though.
- Yeah, man.
Hey, Buddy.
- Pam.
- She's here.
Yeah, just talk to her
for a second.
It's no big deal.
I don't need to come in.
Hey, babe.
- It's OK.
- OK?
Just give me a minute.
He can be there. I don't care.
What do you want?
I want you, baby.
I love you.
I have always loved you, Pam.
You know that.
We've always loved each other.
You must forgive me.
You are the mother of my children.
You are my wife.
I swear I...
I know what I've done.
I was an idiot but it doesn't mean
I ever stopped loving you, Pam.
I swear to God, Pam.
I swear to God almighty,
I would never hurt you again.
Or the kids.
I've hurt you so much, baby.
Wait, and...
I love you.
Buddy, I love you too.
Yes.
But it's over, okay?
I'm happy now.
Just...
It's gonna be okay, all right?
Pam.
Don't. Don't.
Please?
Pam.
I'm sorry.
What are y'all doing?
Wh the...
Hey hey hey! What the hell?
What the hell is going on?
- We're playing ping-pong.
- At 5:00 in the morning?
We're having fun,
we're playing ping-pong.
We've got house
full of people sleeping.
All right, I'm sorry.
Hey, wait wait.
Since you're up, though,
you ose you could make us
some of those egg sandwiches
with swiss cheese... Canadian bacon?
- Hey, Rig. Hey, Riggs.
- Yeah?
Check out who's back on the block?
Oh, see,
I mean, her only problem is,
there's just too many guys,
too little time.
Riggins, why is that you always have
to point the finger at everyone else?
Not everyone's just as easy as you are.
Maybe Tyra's over there
having a nice conversation,
welcoming him to our school.
You don't know what
they're talking about.
I don't know if you know this,
but I'm a virgin.
So I don't know where you're getting
your info from but it's wrong.
You got a date for the dance yet?
'cause you know, I hear
Matt's granny ain't doing thing.
I heard your mom
was triple-booked.
My granny is a nice, elderly woman.
She can't defend herself.
Tyra, may I just have
a word with you real quick?
May I talk to you for just a minute?
May I have a word?
Who is this homo?
- Hey, don't.
- I need to talk to you about the dance.
- Can we just... Can you please..
- Right now is not a good time.
I realize...
- She doesn't wanna talk to you.
- ...that these asshats here
are distracting you.
You're just trying to get your lunch.
She said she didn't wanna talk to you.
Is your name Tyra?
Geek squad.
You shut up and you,
come with me.
She'already got a date
for the dance, skippy.
But I'll get you a text
to let you know how it went.
I was very sad to hear
about that tornado,
It must have been horrible
when your double-wide blew away.
Is it okay for the goats
and the chickens and everything okay?
- What's your problem, dork?
- You want me to go slower,
Richard Simmons? Cause I wasn't sure
it was you that was the remedial one
or was it you
I don't remember.4
This ain't right, Coach!
Everybody was fighting.
- Not just us!
- I don't care.
I want y'all to set an example!
From what I understand, Landry Clark
started the whole damn thing.
Broke 12 chairs
and a $300 cream machine,
which y'all are gonna pay for
by each one of you running one lap
at a penny a piece.
Eric!
- We'll pay o...
- This about the fight,
tell you what, told my boys
absolutely unacceptable!
Even if they were provoked.
Hey, boys will be boys.
Don't you think you're being
a little hardass, Coach?
Tell you what,
you coach your game, I'll coach mine.
Let'go, gentlemen!
Let's pick'em up now!
Yeah, it's mama.
How was your day?
Oh, it was ridiculus.
These Laribee kids
are a pain in the ass.
They had a brawl in the lunch room.
- Oh, my God.
- I know.
- What's this?
- Oh, okay.
That is so awesome,
it makes one cup at a time,
You're always leaving,
and leave the pot half full.
This way you've got gonna waste any.
That is sweet of you Shelly.
I appreciate it.
Eric's kind of particular
about his coffee.
I think he's gonna love it, honestly.
It makes hot chocolate, it makes tea.
But look, this is what I wanna show you.
- Who's that for?
- This is for Tim.
- For Tim Riggins?
- Don't you think it's perfect?
- Shelly.
- What?
Don't you think it's completely
inappropriate? He is a teenage boy.
Tamy, it's a shirt.
I realize it's a shirt. But are you
aware of the way you're behaving?
Walking around,
you're all flirty with him.
Oh, my God.
I've not been flirty!
You are being flirty.
You're jealous
because he gets along with me
better than he gets along with you?
This has nothing to do
with me being jealous.
That is absurd. Do you realize
what your life has come to?
- My life?
- Your ftasizing after a teenage boy.
Please, don't comment on my life
until you have your life, your family.
Don't you dare come into my house
and talk to me about my life
and my family.
You can comment on my life
but I can't comment on your life?
You come into my house
and talk to me about my house.
No, I don't think so.
I'm not being judgemental,
but frankly, I'm worried about you,
I really do wonder why
you just refuse to grow up.
I can tell you what. Because then
I might end up just like you.
Is that right?
Then, why don't you continue
to spend the rest of you life
behave like a teenager?
I mean, it's no wonder
that you're single.
Oh, my God.
- Well?
- Yeah, no, great.
I'm just so amazed you're comfortable
leaving your 2 month old baby
with such an irresponsible little slut,
so, I'm a little confused
by that choice.
I put a fresh bottle in the fridge.
I changed her diaper.
I'm gonna go to my room
and I'm gonna read Tiger Beat.
And by the way,
your baby is in the 70th percentile
for height and weight,
and your pediatrician says hello.
We don't know where I got 'em.
Why...
Why is my nose smelling pee?
Yo, check this out, man.
Somebody...
There's pee in this locker.
That's where it's coming from.
Are you serious?
Smash, somebody done pissed
in his locker, man.
What?
No, hell no.
Oh, no.
Hell no.
We're gonna see how tough
these kids really are.
Get 'em, Rigg.
Who's the hero?
A football team
is working out here, son.
Just go ahead and hit the showers.
You heard me.
Go take a shower!
Sorry about that, dude.
Couldn't hold it.
It's funny.
You're gonna do something about it,
tough guy?
You need to go cool off.
I might just do it.
Hey, no!
What are you doing?
Don't you push me!
Don't you ever lay your hands on me!
Listen to me.
You ever, I mean,
ever touch one of my players again,
you'll never coach another football game,
you understand me?
And after that, I will kick your old,
tid ass six ways from Sunday, Donald.
Shut up.
I want all my players
outside by the bleachers.
Coach, take 'em out
then have a litte walk.
Right now!
- Let's go!
- Get outside right now!
Get out, let's go!
What are you looking at?
Get back to work!
Who else want a cup?
This thing is so cool.
Thanks, Aunt Shelly.
You're right,
it's a better coffee maker.
I thank you very much.
So glad you like it.
Seems like they really like the coffee.
You're in a good mood 'cause there's
no game tonight, isn't that right?
- It's good coffee.
- Yeah.
- Morning.
- Morning, Tim.
Good morning.
- Hi, Timothy.
- Shels.
Hi. You know,
I'm gonna go to my room.
I don't wanna do anything inappropriate.
I'll just excuse myself.
Let's talk about dinner.
Who wants to eat what
before the dance tonight?
I'm not going, so...
Me neither. I told you, remember?
I go hang out with Lois.
I'll have lasagna.
Well, no, if y'all aren't going,
forget it. We'll go out.
Ready for school?
Yeah, gimmie a minute.
Okay, yeah.
Bye, dad. Bye, mom.
- Sweetie, hold on, come here.
- Why can't we have lasagna?
About yesterday,
I just wanna say...
I wanna say thank you...
for helping me out there.
So...
Yeah.
All right.
I'll see you at practice.
There you go.
You know what?
- What?
- Relationships suck.
- I'm just learning this.
- If I remember correctly,
I believe you're the one that ended that
with Matt, not the other way around.
It's complicated
and you don't get the full story.
What, are you still hung up on Tyra?
No.
You ju...
You just gotta let it go, sometimes.
You just gotta let people...
be who he wanna be and just...
let 'em go make out with whoever
they wanna make out
in front of whoever they feel like.
You don't just give up, though.
If you really care about something,
you don't just give up.
You do what you do whatever it takes.
Screw it, I'm not just gonna give up.
You can't just leave!
We were playin'.
- I know you.
- Yeah.
- From?
- Riley, we're in english lit together.
You wanna play quarters?
I'm pretty good.
Where's your date at?
Well, apparently,
he's in the bathroom puking.
So...
- I don't know what I was thinking.
- What were you thinking?
I just don't get it.
Landry, will you sit down with me
for a second, please?
You know how I feel about you.
No, I really don't.
I like you...
a lot.
Actually, I...
I've never felt like this about anybody.
You make me feel too much, Landry.
It freaks me out.
I don't know what that means.
What does that mean?
It means...
It means I'm sorry.
Look, all I need...
is just a little time
to think about things.
Figure it out.
Does that make sense?
No, it doesn't.
It doesn't make sense at all.
You know, I'm...
I'm really sorry about this too.
The thing is that I know
that you're better than this.
Better than the girl
that has to sit over here alone
because her date is too stupid
to stay sober for one night.
I know that you're better than that.
The thing is that you don't.
I don't know what I have to do
to make you see that.
But I can't just keep waiting around
until you finally realize that I can't.
'Cause I've tried to show you,
but I don't know what else to do.
So...
So have a good night.
The little God guy things.
With the... With the...
With the yarn and you bring them home,
and your mom would be like,
"Oh, my God!
It's so beautiful."
And you'd be, like, on moonshoes.
Hey, Jules.
I think it's time we go.
I...
I don't wanna go.
You wanna?
I grab you a beer.
- Come here for a second.
- You're getting beers?
- Yeah, you want one?
- Can I get a beer?
- How you doing?
- Good.
You good?
How's that going?
Good. I think I might be maybe
one beer away from getting laid.
- No kidding? That's great.
- Yeah.
Yeah, she is great.
Hey...
If you ever look at her,
even tonight, again...
at school, anytime for that matter,
I swear to God, I'll hang you.
- Okay?
- Right on.
- Are we cool?
- Yeah, absolutely.
All right.
No, seriously.
That way.
Okay.
Later.
Hey.
Yeah, it's time.
Time for what?
Where's my beer?
Remember what I said
about being quiet.
Yeah, but she likes you.
She always talks about you
and I just told her...
I told her, I was like, you know what,
you should just tell him.
It could be, like, 15 minutes.
You know what I'm sayin'?
- I know what you're saying exactly.
- And she likes you.
She wants to be with you.
- You know?
- That's awesome.
I told her she shouldn't...
The whole world's spinning.
I know what it is.
I've been there.
It's spinning!
Listen to me,
keep your eyes open, you'll be fine.
I'm gonna vomit on the bed.
I'm gonna vomit on the floor.
Let's move you up so you can actually
pass out without falling off the bed.
Ready?
Three, two, one.
- Okay, you good?
- I'm good.
It's time to let go.
What are you doing?
Hey, Jules.
Let go.
Coach...
What the hell are you doing?
- What the hell are you doing?
- It's not even close to what you think.
- Okay? Listen to me.
- Shut up.
You shut up.
You shut your mouth right now.
- Coach, you have to understand...
- Shut your mouth.
Go get your stuff
and get out of this house now.
and get out of this house right now.
Son, don't make me throw you out.
Go get your stuff
and get out of the house now.
Right now get your stuff
and get out of the door.
Go.