Oh, I will play the game,
Mr. Garrity.
Do it, do it.
I will, and when I make
the national team
and start touring all over the world,
I'll take your daughter with me.
'Cause we're getting married.
I just think that we're
too young right now.
And we're rushing into this,
and I don't wanna make a mistake.
Message received, Lyla.
Loud and clear.
That color looks good on you.
I don't have the money for it.
- Coach, I didn't mean--
- You didn't mean what?
You didn't mean to risk
my reputation, my career.
Is that what
you were gonna say?
- I'm sorry, Coach--
- You thinking about that?
He made a mistake.
And he is trying so desperately
to get back in your good graces
that he's losing
his confidence.
He's losing his passion.
I'm sorry, I was--
I was on
the other side of campus.
You're starting
at tailback tonight.
What the hell?
You want a hug or something?
Get outta here.
Julie finds out about this,
- that's not gonna be good.
- Listen,
you're gonna take a few
pictures,
it's for charity.
Nothing happened at all.
I don't appreciate
getting lied to.
So why don't you go
with your little rally girls
and just leave me alone.
Come on, fellas, let's go!
What do you wanna run?
Slot right 28 Gun-sling.
- You serious?
- Slot right 28 Gun-sling. Go on.
Okay.
What?
Come on, Panthers
Bring it home, boys!
All right, gentlemen,
this is serious.
We're going
slot right 28 Gun-sling.
Okay?
Oh, yeah.
All right, slot right
28 Gun-sling on one.
- Ready.
- Break.
How's those hands
of yours, seven?
- Feeling good, Riggins.
- All right!
Arw you ready for this?
Set!
White 44.
Hut!
Saracen takes the snap
and pitches back to Riggins.
To Smash.
What in tarnation?
They got some kind of
a halfback option.
Oh! And Saracen, he's open!
Wide open down
the right sideline!
Oh! He caught it!
Unbelievable!
The Panthers cruise through
their first playoff game.
And the celebration begins
on the Panthers' sidelines.
They said--
They  said we couldn't do it.
Yeah, they did.
They said--
They said we didn't have
what it takes.
Joke's on who?
We got it done,
didn't we?
Yeah!
We got it done!
Yes, Sir. Yes, Sir.
Yes, Sir.
We went out there
and we did it together.
Y'all outta be proud
of yourselves.
And I want you to know
that I am damn proud of you!
Nobody pushes us around.
Whose house?
Our house!
Now that's what
I'm talking about.
You worried about next week's
game against Dunston Valley?
Why, you know something
we don't?
Almost all-white team.
Had some trouble recently
with that hazing
of a player in black face.
Oh, we don't give a dang
about all that.
We're just goin' down there
to play football,
and, God willing, come away
one game closer to State.
Are you saying that race
isn't an issue
for the Dillon Panthers, Mac?
No, sir, it's not.
Yet Dillon was one of the last
high school teams in Texas
to be integrated.
Only one black quarterback
in 40 years.
Voodoo Tatum, he left
after two games.
Which had nothing to do
with his skin color.
Look, you show me a red or
a  black or a green player
here in Dillon that's better
than Matt Saracen,
he's got the job, all right?
What about Smash Williams?
He played quarterback on JV.
He's got quite an arm.
Smash for quarterback?
Yeah.
I believe Smash is better suited
for the position he's in.
- How do you mean?
- Well, guys like Smash
and Baxter and even Voodoo,
they got a natural gift
for running the ball.
All three are black.
Are you saying this gift
has something to do
with their skin color?
What I'm saying, Karen,
and I'm saying it in a good way,
is that guys like Smash
are--
are fearless.
They're dangerous.
They're like junkyard dogs.
I mean, you want them
carrying the ball.
You want them
tearing up turf out there.
So let me get this straight.
Whites like Saracen
make better quarterbacks
because they're
inherently smarter?
Well, if you wanna put it
that way, you could.
But I'm not saying that
all black guys are--
are dumb.
I'm just saying
that they got diff--
Mac, I need to talk to you.
- Coach, a couple more.
- Coach, we're not done yet.
Sorry, folks,
we're outta time right now.
It's getting late.
You know how it is.
Well,  I think
you got your story.
Friday Night Lights - 1x15
Blinders
Transcript: Raceman
Synch: Tauri41
..:: www.forom.com ::..
Mac McGill didn't
use the word "monkey."
He said, "Junkyard dogs."
Monkeys, dogs, frogs--
Mac McGill said
blacks are inhuman.
That they don't think
before they act.
Like they're workhorses
for the white man.
Weel, now, you know
I'm not sure that's what he meant,
but thanks for the call.
Next.
Just 'cause rednecks like Mac
learned it that way
don't make it right.
You can bet if
he's saying this filth
about black folks in public,
him and his kind are saying
a lot worse behind closed doors.
Mac said blacks are shiftless.
That it's the white kids
who are hard workers...
Why everybody so mad at McGill?
God, I mean,
he ain't that bad.
He just says
dumb stuff sometimes.
And that's an excuse?
Y'all need to stop.
We got bigger things
to worry about.
Now there she is.
- Oh, it's nice.
- That's the house you're talking about?
I mean, that's a real house.
Yes, I know it.
Dang, this is so nice.
Wow, Mama, did you see
the size of that closet?
Oh, that's gonna be
my dressing room.
No it's not.
Only if I get
the second bathroom.
Listen. Listen.
Wait a minute, child,
we don't own any of it.
That could change if you let me
submit the bid we discussed.
Well...
Mom, you said
with the 10% down
we could cover it
come on.
Well, that is until I get sick
or, God forbid, one of y'all
has an accident.
Well, I guess we could
just keep dreaming then.
Come back every few days
'til somebody else buys it.
I knew I shouldn't
have brought y'all.
But it is nice, huh?
- For real.
- Yeah.
You skipped class?
Julie, you skipped class?
It was only one time.
Ms. Carroll told me
you skipped three classes.
It was just P.E.
Look, Ms. Taylor,
we're really sorry.
We will never do it again.
Well, Tyra, that really sounds
like a hollow apology to me.
So you can just save it.
But I'll tell you
what you are gonna do
is you're gonna be in P.E.
for every class
for the rest of the semester.
And in terms of making up
the classes that you missed,
Ms. Carroll made
a real good suggestion.
Which is that both of y'all
are gonna play
in the Powderpuff game.
Practices start this afternoon.
You will not miss one of them.
You have got
to be kidding me.
- You wouldn't do that.
- Do I look like I'm kidding y'all?
You wouldn't--
You wouldn't do that to me.
Yeah, I would.
But...
Now, listen up
Why is he here?
This is gonna be so awkward.
Ladies.
Over here.
I'm Landry Clarke.
Your official
Powderpuff referee.
Just wanted
to start things off,
and say, uh, let's just
keep this clean.
And let's just play this--
this beautiful game in--
in the spirit that it
was meant to be played in.
Thank you, Landry.
Now ladies, let's meet.
this year's
Powderpuff Panther coaches.
Huh?
We've got Matthew Saracen
and Timothy Riggins.
You can shoot me now
if you want to.
All right, Tim,
- you call it.
- Tails, ma'am.
Matt, you get first pick.
Okay.
Okay, uh, I pick Tyra, please.
All right, Tyra.
Tim?
Does anyone here
know how to chop block?
I do.
Nice, let's go.
All right.
Uh...Laurel.
Good call, Laurel.
Let's go, Garrity.
Um, I'm gonna pick
Julie Taylor, please.
- Please.
- Come on, Julie!
Great.
Hey, how you doin'?
Good, how're you?
How ya doin'?
I'm doing good, man.
Little bit crazy for me
to come back to school.
Had a free pass here
for a while but...
I'll catch y'all later.
Only applies to certain
rural interstates
in specified counties.
Y'all  just think about that--
Hey, guys.
Can I talk to you a minute?
Yeah.
Uh...read your books.
I'll get the questions later.
You guys wanna get
a driver's license,
you gotta know
the finer points.
Been listening
to the radio, huh?
I just got done talking
to the superintendent.
They're getting calls
from newspapers and stations
all over the state.
Like they got nothing else
better to do.
You need to issue
a public apology.
Apology for what?
For being truthful?
That's not the way
people heard it.
What--what people?
A bunch of damn P.C.
sons of bitches
trying to get my job?
Afraid it's not just
a bunch of sons of bitches.
Well, all right.
You're telling me
that you think Matt Saracen
has as much natural ability
as a Smash?
What I'm telling you
is that it's not
too damn smart
to be making generalizations
about people's abilities
based on their color.
Think about that.
That's what I'm saying.
All right. All right.
What's done is done.
No apology's
gonna change that.
I'm not making a request.
And you ain't gonna share?
I thought you were
on some kind of special diet.
I  am.
No sweets.
Except for sweet chocolate.
Here you go, baby.
I wasn't talking about
the cake.
Mmm, okay enough.
Enough.
I can't believe
I picked Julie third.
I mean she--
Now she hates me.
I'm tellin' you, I was reading
up on pheromones last night.
I really think they work.
There's no smell
that's gonna make Julie
not hate me anymore.
A lot of studies
have shown that
responses to odors,
you know,
depend on emotions
felt whenever
that odor was first smelled.
Okay, even if that wasn't
the stupidest thing
that I've ever heard,
I mean, I don't even know what
kinda smells Julie would like.
Well, I mean, she likes
her dad, doesn't she?
So, why don't you figure out
what type of soap he uses.
Then you can go out
and get that kind of soap.
You're retarded.
Hey, at least just try it.
Hey, guys, guys,
check it out, man.
Mac's on TV.
Let me turn it up.
I believe that all of our
players, regardless of color,
contribute to the spirit
and the success
of the Dillon Panthers.
My comments were not intended
to hurt anybody.
And I apologize if they did.
Thank you.
Has there been any talk
of suspension?
Are you gonna meet
with the players?
Coach, just one question.
What was that?
You call that an apology?
Tell me what else
you'd call that, then.
A lame-ass excuse.
What is the big deal?
I mean it's not like he yelled
out racist slurs or anything.
Yeah, but if we were up at UT
right  now, he'd be fired.
Exactly.
Fortunately for us,
he's not.
Yeah, that's easy
for you to say
'cause you're white
and obviously selfish.
Come on, y'all,
it ain't that deep.
What you want Mac to do,
pay out reparations
to all the Negroes in Dillon?
Bye.
Wave.
We was just playing.
Yeah, well,
enjoy your sandbox, boys.
A year of detention
is preferable to Powderpuff.
Okay, I don't need
to spend a week
watching Tim Riggins teach
rally girls how to tackle.
It's pathetic.
Oh, and then he has the gall
to pick that bony little--
- Lyla.
- Hey, guys.
Hey, Tyra, my dad says
your mom's doing
really good on the job.
Really?
Wow, maybe she'll get
her own dealership one day.
Yeah, I just thought
it'd be good to know
she's doing really well.
That's real nice to know.
Hey, Tyra.
I was surprised to see you
on the field today.
Thought you hated football.
You know what,
I changed my mind.
I'm gonna get real
into Powderpuff this year.
If you want, I'll jack up Greer
for disrespecting you.
Okay, you know
it's not about me.
It's about you taking
this Mac thing seriously.
Wave, I'm not Jesse Jackson,
all right?
My cause is football.
Okay then, who are you?
Because it shouldn't mean
playing dumb.
Look, I don't see Matty or Rigg
jumping up on a soap box
every time a brother
says something messed up.
You know why, 'cause it's
a completely different thing.
Well, then,
that's racist right there.
Me being expected to act
differently 'cause I'm black.
That's kinda the burden
that you were born with, baby.
The burden
and the blessing.
You know, you get all
sexy, sexy
when you get all preachy.
You know what, Brian,
don't do this, okay.
Don't turn this into a joke.
It's important, I want you
to really think about this.
Wave, I respect
your opinion on this.
I do.
But could you please just
recognize for one second
that I just got through
some real drama.
I mean, I'm just getting
my swagger back.
I can't be sidetracked with
things I can't control, baby.
Look...
I know that you're dealing
with a lot right now.
Okay, and I'm here for you.
But sooner or later,
you're gonna have to peek out
from behind those blinders.
Okay, I wanna see
both partners
using the scalpel.
And both partners
taking notes.
All right, I'm ready.
You ready?
- I guess.
- You sure?
Now, look, if it's--
if it's any consolation,
I--I heard that these frogs
had a very long
and fulfilling life.
So it's all right.
Lots of flies.
And lots of...
Tadpoles.
You want me to do this?
'Cause I can.
No, no, no, I got it.
Don't worry about it.
All right, well,
just give me a minute.
Is everything good?
Yes, sir, Mr. Utz,
we were just...
just getting started.
Now, Jason, if you just
wanna observe, it's okay.
It's all anybody expects.
No, I'd like to just go ahead
and finish the incision.
It's up to you.
Let's go for ten, ladies.
As one, count 'em out as ten.
- One...two...three.
- Let's go!
As one, come on.
D-split 45, Garrity.
Hut--hut.
Let's go, ladies.
Let's go.
Nice.
Good execution.
I'm starting
to see something, ladies.
Get some blocks, here.
- Let's get some blocks.
- Ready, 44...
Hot--hot crossfire.
Set, uh, hut--hut--hut.
There ya' go.
Now go, now go.
Oh, bad, bad, okay.
We are a team of one, ladies.
That's fine um, you just wanna
make sure you catch this.
One unit.
Let's go, let's go.
We've got to get this together.
Hey, Matt!
- Yeah?
- Figure out what the hell
you want me to do.
You see that team over there?
Yeah.
Looks a lot better than us.
Set.
Hut--hut!
Yes, you got the snap.
What was that?
You throw like a damn girl.
Are you serious, Matt?
That is your quarterback?
She's really good
at handing off.
Good job, Coach.
Hut--hut.
Oh, I'm--
I'm sorry.
- Really? Really?
- I'm sorry.
Hold on.
Not her, not her.
It's all right.
It's all right, we're a team.
Teammates.
I'm starting to see a "W"
in my eyes, let's go!
Matt, okay,
this isn't working for me.
It's not working
for me either.
Hi.
Julie?
Yep.
You think maybe you could
play quarterback?
Hmm, let's see,
I was your third pick.
Am I even qualified
to talk to QB one?
You're the only one
who knows how to play.
I do know how to play.
But, uh,
frankly.....
I don't care.
Um, excuse me.
Lovebirds.
Let's go.
Practice.
Please.
You're pathetic.
This is now
about victory.
Line up!
Let's go.
Strength and stamina.
One of your teammates gets hurt,
gets tired out there.
You step in,
help carry the weight.
You give 'em a hand.
Let's go!
Come on, man,
stop slackin'.
Oh, yeah? Wait 'til your turn.
We'll see how fast you go.
Stop the chatter,
let's get it done.
Yes sir, Massa.
What'd you say, Seale?
I love this drill, sir.
Get your ass down the field!
- Love it.
- Move it.
- Yes, sir.
- Move it!
Yes, sir.
You shut your mouth!
Hey, baby.
Honey,
I just broke up a fight
in the hallway.
Over this whole
Mac McGill thing.
Well...
I don't know
what to tell you, babe.
Well, I don't know.
I mean, just it's clear to me
that it's not--
This thing is not going away.
I mean, these kids
were riled up.
And it was a lot of kids.
And it was black against white.
It was racial.
Look babe, he said
something stupid, all right?
He said something stupid.
He made an apology.
- I know.
- There's gonna be fallout,
- there's no way around that.
- I know, I know, I know,
but I feel like--
I feel like I--
I wanna do--
I wanna have
some kind of a dialogue
for the kids, you know.
I wanna create, maybe, something
after school later this week.
- Like a forum or something.
- A forum?
Yeah, you know,
where the kids can come
and talk to each other
and air it out.
So that it's not just
coming up with their fists
in the middle of the hallway.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Will you tell your
football players about it?
I think it could certainly
be good for them to come.
Sure.
Appreciate the support.
- I'll see you later.
- All right, have a good day.
Okay.
You got a steering wheel.
You got your brake, you got
your accelerator, all right?
Where would they be?
Well, look,
this lever over here,
you wanna go ahead and push it.
Yeah, go ahead
and push it forward.
Forward?
Okay.
Forward is brake, right.
If you wanna accelerate,
you wanna go ahead
and push it on down
toward your knee.
There ya go, down--
Woo-hoo.
There ya go.
All right, all right.
All right, so you wanna
put it in drive.
And let's check it out.
See how this puppy rolls.
Off on the brake.
Oh, don't be shy.
Don't be shy.
Straight on through?
All right, all right.
Next stop, Indy 500, huh?
Shut up, I'm trying
to get used to it, all right?
Just give me a minute.
I got it.
And once you get comfortable,
how's that feel?
It feels okay.
Yeah?
Yeah.
This is pretty easy,
- I could get the hang of this.
- You like it, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's nice
Yeah, a little bit of freedom?
I could get used to it.
Speaking of
getting used to it,
how's being back at school
treating ya?
It's okay.
I guess.
Yeah?
Listen, when you
got out of the hospital,
was everybody
just weird to you?
Man, I felt like
I was 100 years old.
You know, like, uh,
there was some sort of secret
knowledge no one else possessed.
You know.
I mean, for a while there
actually I
wanted to go back
to the hospital.
Of course, that was partially
'cause there was
this hot-ass nurse that just
could not get enough of me.
Oh, I'm sure she couldn't.
You know, I just want things
to feel normal again, you know?
Yeah, well,
I hate to break it to you,
but high school is not normal.
- Brake.
- Brake?
Brake.
Brake!
There ya go.
You have a good one.
Think I'm gonna take off.
Okay, so, uh--
Don't worry,
I got your numbers.
I got your numbers
and everything.
- You good?
- I'm good.
Okay.
Cool.
Hey look, Smash,
I don't think it's right.
What Mac said, I don't--
I don't agree with it.
So you think
I should quarterback?
No--I mean, yeah.
I mean, I don't know.
- I mean, I don't know if you play--
- I'm just playing with you, Matty.
I know what you're trying to
say, but I ain't sweatin' it.
Neither should you.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's cool.
All right.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- All right, later.
- Hello?
- Hey.
Hey, honey, how you doin'?
Grand.
How was Powderpuff?
It was great.
Oh, was
Powderpuff tiring?
Where's the supper?
Oh, I don't know.
Why don't you sit down?
Don't--
Don't roll your eyes.
Something else
is gonna happen
other than
this Powderpuff thing
as a punishment
for you cutting class.
I promise you
your mom and I will
let you know
what it is when we
figure out what it is.
Yep, that's understood.
And when you figure out
what my punishment is,
- I'll be in my bedroom.
I don't want you
to be flippant with me.
to be flippant.
- Did you hear what he just said?
- Can I tell you something?
- Yes, I heard.
- No, no, look at me.
Please, don't do this.
Don't break our trust.
Don't take our trust
from us.
Please.
I'm sorry, today's just
been really...
Really kind of
a crappy day.
Matt's been yelling
at me all day about...
Stupid quarterback stuff.
Matt Saracen's got you
at quarterback?
Wait, honey.
Hey, come here.
What do you mean
he's got you at quarterback?
Two-zero.
Hey, what up, Dutch Boy?
- Get a new haircut?
- Get a new hat?
What's your order, man?
I've actually been
doing some thinking.
You know all this friction
between the team?
It's just not helping
right now, man.
And State's coming up, so...
You got that right.
So, I mean,
I figure you talk to your boys
and settle 'em down.
And we can just refocus
on the game. You know?
You got some nerve.
The same dude who shows up
half-drunk to workouts,
walks off practice, and throws
a glass bottle at my head
wants to tell me to talk to my boys?
I didn't tell you.
I asked you, Williams.
No, first of all,
they ain't my boys.
You want team unity,
why don't you talk to your boys?
This football done brought us
together, but on the real,
we ain't even cool like that.
You're a lost cause,
Williams.
Mom?
Hello?
Hey.
Here, honey.
Hey, Mama.
Ready to go?
Uh, you know...
I'm so sorry
I didn't call you.
I--I--I--
I gotta get through a...
Stack of papers.
I'm so sorry, honey.
It's okay. Well, it's good
to see you working.
Hey, Tyra.
Hi
How you doin'?
I'm great.
How're you?
Good.
Oh, we're just fine.
Your mom is the greatest.
She volunteered to help me out
and finish out tonight.
She knows everything.
Well, she's a smart woman.
I'm just gonna--
I'll just call, you know,
I'll just call Mindy for a ride
later, when we're done.
Yeah.
Okay.
Good.
All right, honey.
See you later.
Oh, good to see you, Tyra.
Yeah.
See ya.
Pro-left
25 sprint option.
Now say it.
Pro-left 25 sprint option.
Nice, what that means is--
That means that you're gonna
fake to the two back
through the five hole.
You're gonna be moving down
and you've got the option then
to continue your run,
or you make the pass,
depending on what's gonna be
more efficient for you, all right?
All right, I'm gonna do down
about 15, cut across.
You good?
On two.
Hut--hut!
Watch this, hon.
Here.
All right, that's pretty good.
- I gotta admit--
- Pretty good?
That's a very good throw.
All right, listen, I want you
to bean me with this
as I make it for the house.
You ready?
On two.
Hut, hut!
No matter what happens today,
we're all gonna be winners.
Please.
We will not accept a loss.
We will not accept it.
One...two...three...
Win!
Let's go!
Touchdown!
Great job, ladies.
Bring it on!
Blue 42.
This is supposed to be fun.
Oh, honey, this is fun.
This still
about Riggins, because--
Oh, please,
not even close.
- What is your problem?
- My problem?
My problem is your dad,
Buddy Garrity,
and him having his dirty hands
all over my mom, his employee.
What are you talking about?
You know what?
You are just a spoiled little snob.
You're not gonna
win this game.
Come on, throw it!
You wanna throw it!
She got the ball off.
That's a sack.
What the hell
kinda call is that?
Son, you're blind.
- Honey.
- What?
- Calm down.
- Excuse me.
Stay off of my line.
- What'd you say to me?
- My line.
Right there, that line.
That one right there
that's mine.
Excuse me.
That's your first one.
This is it.
This is our last chance.
We can either
go home with a tie.
Or we can go home
with a win.
How 'bout we run the 25-right
sprint option?
Hut!
Get her
Kick her knees!
Keep runnin'.
That a girl!
Keep runnin'!
We won!
Good game.
Are you kidding me?
What's crack-a-lacka, y'all?
What's happening?
Eric didn't tell me
you guys were gonna be out here.
What's the occasion,
how you guys doin'?
Surprise!
It's not my birthday.
We know it's not your birthday,
but we are here for a reason, QB.
And that reason is...
As a designated member of
the National Quad Rugby Squad,
I am here to inform you that
you have been invited
to training camp in Austin.
No way.
Whoa, don't get so excited
there, young buck.
Training camp
is two weeks
of the most intense,
painful, exhausting
workouts of your young,
wheelchair-bound life.
And at the end
of that two weeks,
coaches evaluate the players.
Then choose the new members
for the National
Quad Rugby Squad
for the U.S. of A.
I--I don't know what to say.
I mean,
you think I got a shot?
Uhh...no.
Like a snowball's chance in...
But, I'll tell you what,
we got four open spots.
You make one of 'em,
we're Beijing-bound.
- That's China.
- That is China.
Can you say chopsticks
and hot chicks?
Yes, I can.
But now, you said
my credit score was fine.
I'm sorry, Ms. Williams.
But I did tell you a pre-approved loan
isn't always guaranteed.
Oh, yeah, it wouldn't have
anything to do
with me being single parent
or that little box
on the application
where you had me
to check off my race.
No, no, that's
federal monitoring
to prevent racial bias.
Oh, it worked like a charm,
didn't it?
We want to talk
to your supervisor.
It won't make a difference.
Well, let's do it anyway.
I can leave him a message.
- We're here right now.
- I'm sorry, it's not possible.
Let's go, Brian.
No, Mama, they can't do this.
They can't just
take back the loan.
Oh, there will be other loans.
No, we want to talk
to your boss now!
It's not gonna do anybody
any good to get crazy.
Look around you.
Look at all these eyes on you.
Lookin' at you.
Waitin'.
Expecting you
to do something violent.
Become that junkyard dog
of Mac McGill's, uh-uh.
Don't give 'em that.
You ladies
have a good afternoon.
Thank you very much.
- Hey.
How's my QB one?
Hi.
- How you doin'?
- Good.
Can I ask you a question?
Well the answer is "yes."
You do look super-hot
- in my football jersey.
- No, umm...
Do you think
I'm a spoiled snob?
- I'm serious.
- Where'd that come from?
Answer the question.
A little.
A litt--I'm--
I'm kidding.
Someone say something to you?
Want me to go beat 'em up?
Well, I gotta tell you
what happened to me today.
- Yeah, I know--
- I got invited to Nationals.
- What Nationals?
- Nationals. Quad Rugby
National Team
is having tryouts
in Austin for a couple of weeks
- and they got four spots open.
- Austin?
And if I go
and I make the team,
then I'll possibly be going
to Beijing later this year.
What does that mean?
What about--
What about our plans?
What about school?
School was a mistake.
It wasn't--
- School was a mistake?
- It's not--
School's not a mistake.
Fitting in was a mistake.
- You fit in fine, Jason.
- No, I don't fit in fine.
And even if I did fit in,
I don't want to.
This is going backwards,
I wanna move forward.
I wanna go later this month
and get my GED.
- And bam, be done with school.
- Your GED?
Yeah, my GED.
I'm this close.
I'm this close, Lyla.
Me going to Austin
for just a couple weeks
doesn't change anything.
We're just here to--
to have an opportunity
to talk about race relations
at this school and what's been
going on this week,
and air your feelings, and
and have people listen to you.
So who wants to go first?
Ms. Tami.
Anton.
I got something to say.
I mean,
when it comes to,
like, whites and blacks,
man, we just--
we just different.
That's a gross generalization.
Dog, no, it's not, fool.
Stereotypes happen
for a reason.
Hey, this is not a debate.
Just so we're clear.
This is just a chance
for everybody to talk
and listen.
So if you wanna speak,
you can hold up your hand.
Let's let Anton finish.
Like I was saying,
if you look at who's with who,
you know, in the lunch room
or, you know what I'm saying,
after school.
At the end of the day,
we just naturally
go with our own.
I mean, that's just how it is.
I mean, that's all I'm saying.
All right.
Landry.
I mean, I think a lot of it has
to do with how we're socialized.
If that makes any sense.
I mean, um
science says that my DNA
could be closer to that of a
black person in Kenya
I suppose that
I don't know, the white
person sitting next to me.
That's interesting.
Waverly.
Let's face it, you guys,
people say things like Mac said
all the time and worse.
But the real problem is
people just refuse
to acknowledge that racism
even exists in Dillon.
So we need to have more
forums like this,
- we need to talk about it.
- Don't get your panties in a wad, Waverly.
It's not like this is
a big conspiracy.
It is not like being white
gives you the right
to interrupt either.
Thank you.
And it's not like we're
at a movie theater.
Hey, hey, hey,
quiet down, y'all.
Man, what you trying to say,
Thompson?
He's trying to say
that I can't even
go to a movie anymore
to a decent movie
without some black person
in front of me yelling
and talking all the time.
Sit down, please.
Why don't you keep your dumbass,
ignorant, racist comments--
Guys! Guys!
Stop it!
Hey, Mac
What you're doing
here so late?
We never got a chance to talk.
About what?
Well, about what you said,
and how you may or may not
perceive the black players--
What I perceive
other than football
is none of your business.
Whoa, look, I'm just trying
to have a dialogue.
Well, you save your dialoguin'
for your mommy.
Now, wait a minute,
you said--
No, you wait a minute, son.
You wait just a minute.
I've been here
for 27 years.
And I am not about
to be interrogated by some
too-big-for-his-britches
teenager, you got me?
What the hell you mean,
too-big-for-my-britches, Mac?
You don't wanna see--
This is done, all right?
This is over.
I'm done with this.
I am done.
Look,
if I hear you whining,
or anybody else whining
about this anymore,
you're gonna be warming your ass
on the bench Friday night,
- you got me?
- Oh, no, you can't do that.
Oh, I can.
Yeah.
And I will.
I'm tired of this crap.
Hey, babe.
Hey.
Well, it didn't go very well,
honey.
I mean, first of all,
hardly anybody showed up.
But then, I mean,
I wish you could--
I wish you coulda seen the way
these kids were yelling at each other.
Calling each other names.
It's real hard
to make a change around here.
You know you're an example
to aspire to, don't you?
You gave them an opportunity
to express themselves
that they wouldn't have
otherwise, you know that.
Because you're always there
ready to listen to them.
You never shy away
from difficult subjects.
They know they can trust you.
That's a rarity.
You're my wife,
and I am damn proud of you.
Come here.
Oh, come here, come here,
come here, come here.
Hey, Smash.
Matt.
So, I--
I heard that forum
was kinda crazy.
I heard.
Look, I was thinking
that maybe we should
- get the team together--
- No disrespect,
but I'm really not in the mood
for chatting right now.
Let's go, gentlemen.
Let's go.
Got a lot of work to do today.
A lot of work.
Everybody feelin' good today?
I can't hear you.
All right, I like to hear that.
Mac, let's call it.
All right, you heard the man.
Let's go, get on the line.
Stride it out.
On my whistle.
You boys deaf or something?
I said on my whistle!
Ready!
I'm not gonna tell you again.
Get your asses down there.
On my whistle!