Sports Illustrated
has this team...
as the number one high school
football team in Texas.
Got yourself
a heck of a quarterback.
- Is it true, Mr. Street?
- That I love Lyla Garrity?
Street the only one
to be able to get to him.
A gigantic hit on Street.
Jason's paralyzed.
This is not just some game,
you realize that,
after what's happened
with Jason.
It's about this town.
It's about the spirit
and keeping this town alive.
You think little Matt Saracen
can get it done?
You got a job to do.
This is all yours
for the taking.
You know, Jason's been
asking about you.
You know, you wait too long,
he might start taking it personal too.
You want to help, then stop pretending
that everything's okay.
He's never gonna walk again!
What happened with us came from
all these feelings about Jason.
They're trying to bring in
this Katrina refugee.
We got ourselves
a quarterback, Coach.
Can you tell me who
you're thinking about starting?
If you want it to be you, you're
gonna have to show me a lot more
than what you've been showing me
on the field this week.
I can't stop thinking
about you, Lyla.
Morning.
- No hospital today?
- No, I'm going for a run.
I think this is--
Hey...
I think it's really great.
You're doing something for yourself.
Thanks, Mom.
Have a good day, sweetie.
I own this place,
it's part of me
It fills me up
and swallows me
And I am oceans,
rocks, and vines
Reaching for
the sun that shines
Oh, I must say,
I adore you
But sometimes
I seem to ignore you
That's because
I don't deserve you
Or have your love
for me ever
All this time
I wanted you to know
That if you're ever...
Yeah?
Hi.
You hungry?
Yeah.
It's not much, but--
Is your brother here?
No.
Hey, Sammy, it's Wednesday.
When are we gonna get
the decision from Coach Taylor?
Is it gonna be Voodoo,
or is it gonna be Saracen?
Well, we're on
the same page there, Fred.
We're all waiting
for that answer.
Voodoo's a star, man.
We gotta see that kid play.
A team does not function with
a quarterback controversy.
He's just gotta go out
and pick one.
Well, my friend, as I said,
I don't think
you're alone there.
I found this national web site
listing all these open
high school coaching jobs.
You did not.
There's one in Miami.
There's another school in New York.
There's even a head coaching
job in Seattle.
And it comes with a house
in "Pudget" Sound.
Puget Sound.
You know what I heard once?
I heard that a daughter
is supposed to be a comfort
and a blessing
to her father.
Texas isn't even a state.
Technically, it's a republic.
It'd be nice to live somewhere
that's actually a part of this planet.
Do y'all think that they actually
have football in Seattle?
Not the same thing.
Come on, on the hop, guys,
let's get out of here.
Mike, get Voodoo
out of the weight room.
- Tell him I want to see him.
- In the office?
- Yeah, in my office.
- All right, I'll send him in.
Voodoo!
- You wanted to see me?
- Yeah. Sit down.
How you doing?
Listen, we haven't
had much time to talk.
And, uh, it's been
pretty busy around here.
I just thought that--
Well, you know I'm gonna
be making a decision soon about Friday.
This is where you might want
to chime in about
how you relish the opportunity.
Or, you know, you're not gonna let me down.
You might want to add something about
the insight you've gained into the game of football
in the short time you've been lucky enough
to be a Dillon Panther.
I'm not here
to make friends.
This ain't my home.
This ain't my school.
It never will be.
Yeah?
I don't like the food here,
the music, the weather.
I can definitely do without
everybody going on and on
about the great state of Texas.
I'm here to get noticed, get recruited,
and get my ass to LSU.
And you?
You're just trying to scrape by.
Trying to win some games,
keep your job.
You and me are
an arranged marriage.
Nothing more.
You've seen what I can do.
You want to start Saracen,
you go right ahead.
You wanna leave that door open?
Friday Night Lights
1x05 - Git'er Done
Transcript: Raceman
Synch: Tauri41.
Hey, look, you're doing
pretty good out there.
- Blowin' it out in practice.
- Yeah? You think so?
- Yeah, man.
- Cool, thanks.
You and me, State and Main.
- Okay.
- For real.
Hey, hey, where you goin'
there, girl?
Hey, baby, come on back here
and bless me.
Hey, you guys seen Lyla?
Lyla?
What about the Smash, baby?
And don't forget about my boy here,
Matty Saracen.
Hey, Matt.
Are you starting on Friday?
I-I might be.
I might.
Oh, boy.
You're drawing up plays.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you. I'll take it.
Oh... We're having dinner.
You can forage for them later.
This looks good.
Here you go.
One triple-chocolate meltdown.
You're not my waitress.
Shift change.
Lucky me.
I'm not sure how
I feel about this.
I mean, it's kind of abrupt.
I had a thing going
with this other lady.
She was bringing me
napkins and mints.
See, you know, that's rough.
But at her age,
Carlene can only handle
the day shift.
Plus, there's a
"Murder, She Wrote" marathon
- on this weekend, so--
- I'm stuck with you.
- Yeah.
Whoa, what's going on
out there?
Just a bunch of overheated jocks,
too dumb to know
they have no future,
fighting over a game
that has no meaning,
in a town from which
there is no escape.
That's, uh--
Wow.
Anyway, my name is Tyra,
and I'll be at your service
for the next six hours.
Okay.
All right, good. Good.
Let's go, let's go!
Get 'em over there!
Lookin' good, yeah.
Stay low and drive.
Aim for the "B."
There it is.
All right, good.
Now pass.
Bring it down.
Nice, nice.
- Yeah!
- What's going on, Coach?
The guy's looking good,
Coach.
How come Saracen isn't
rotating in with the first team?
I thought last week we said
we were starting Tatom.
I think you said that, and I said,
"Thanks for the opinion, Coach."
Saracen, put your lid on.
Strap up, son. Get your ass in there.
We're rotating him with the first team
until I say otherwise.
Yes, sir.
Get in there, son.
Hey.
You know, there is more
than one restaurant in this town.
I'm just...saying.
Oh.
Well, I just came by
to give you something,
but now, maybe I'm not
feeling like it anymore.
What is it?
You remind me of him.
I remind you of an old,
wrinkled black man
- wearing a weird hat?
- Yeah, something like that.
Okay.
- Well--
- That's it.
Thanks.
Hey, you want to come
for a ride...with me?
A ride?
Yeah, I work for
an investment bank,
and we're looking to see if the oil fields
are worth reopening around here.
I gotta go out to the fields
an do an evaluation.
You know, financial
feasibility, analysis.
- And I'm just boring you to death.
- Yeah, totally.
Anyway, look, I gotta go out to the fields,
meet some geologists.
I was wondering if you'd
want to go for a ride.
I'm not gonna sleep with you.
What?
I wasn't--
I'm not--
I just like your company.
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
I have two parents who work here,
and I can't get either one of them
to sign my stupid
driver's ed form.
Uh, are you--
Are you gonna come to the game on Friday?
Uh, yeah.
My dad's the coach.
He'll have a heart attack
if I don't show up.
So, do you think
you're gonna start?
Uh...I don't know.
That's the coach's decision.
You know, whatever he decides,
I'm there for.
But I've been working hard,
so I'm ready.
I feel good about it.
I just-- You know, whatever he feels
is best for the team,
that's--that's what
I'm ready to do, so.
Dude, you need to chill out.
I'm not ESPN.
Sorry.
No, it's cool.
All right, I'll...
I'll see you around, then.
- Bye.
You're so stupid.
There you go.
Now try throwing it
back to Raines.
You're doing great.
There you go.
Try to throw it back.
Use your biceps.
You got 'em.
All right, here's the play.
Go about 15 yards, run a post pattern.
I'll hit you by the water cooler.
Phil, get QB in a van this afternoon.
Get him downtown to the center.
You know I can't authorize that.
Authorize this, Phil.
I want to show this boy his future.
What's happening
this afternoon, Phil?
Shoot the runner
Shoot, shoot the runner
I'm a king
and she's my queen
Shoot the runner
Shoot, shoot the runner
I'm a king
and she's my queen
Dream, dreamer
get in your way
Always do this to where?
Lose yourself to the sea
Am I only a dream?
Shoot the runner
Shoot, shoot the runner
I'm a king
and she's my queen
Hey, miss Lyla Garrity.
Come in here and sit down.
Well, it's not true what
they say about cheerleaders.
That you're all just a bunch of T and A,
and nothing between the ears.
Excuse me, Mrs. Taylor?
Well, I mean, you got
straight-As, girl.
Good.
- Thank you.
- That's awesome.
Yeah, so, what are you thinking?
Are you thinking about colleges?
Well, I always figured I'd wait to see
what school Jason was gonna play for.
Probably Notre Dame.
So, I'd probably end up taking
classes at St. Mary's.
You know, and enroll full-time
once Jason was settled in.
Well, college football is so much
more demanding than high school.
- I'd want to be there for him.
- I understand that.
But, you know,
I was actually thinking,
separate from that,
what you might want to do.
I guess with Jason's
recovery and all,
I really haven't had the time
to give that much thought.
I know, I know.
But that's why I thought maybe it'd be
a good idea for you to come in here.
Maybe it's time to start
thinking about it.
What do you think?
What the hell are you doing?
Copying the playbook.
What do you think I'm doin'?
Tatom's been borrowing mine,
so I thought it was about time
he got one of his own.
You got a problem with that now?
No, I just like to know
what's going on in my office.
Like I like to know
what's going on with my offense.
You know, I don't really care for
what you're insinuating there.
Mac, I'm not insinuating anything.
But since we're broaching the subject,
I can tell you one thing that I don't like.
I don't like
my offensive coordinator
chatting up Buddy Garrity,
like he's on a date.
I don't care for that too much.
Look, who I have a drink with
is none of your damn business.
Easy.
You think I want your job, right?
Well, you're damn right I do.
'Cause the way I see it,
you're sitting in my chair.
But I'll never do anything
to hurt these kids.
I want to win, just like you do.
These are my boys too.
So you pull it together.
Got me?
See, this is what i fear about.
We've got mass-producing
Borden County,
mass-producing Howard County.
We move over here into Dillon, though,
and we've got, you know, almost--
Yeah, again, I suggested
like you did, boss.
You guys know better than I do.
I don't know.
I guess I just have to laugh.
All these people so caught up
in their tiny little lives.
It's ridiculous, don't you think?
What?
Nothing.
You're opinionated.
I like that.
You know what else I hate,
just for the record?
- What?
- Oil.
Ok.
Why?
I know it's a widely held belief,
but any particular reason?
I hate what it did to my father.
This whole town, really.
My father, he lost his job
as a rigger in the last bust.
I mean, it's worse than crack.
These dealers come in promising
good times will last forever.
And just as fast, it's gone.
And all the money's gone with it.
You want to know a secret?
Hmm?
I'm not a big fan of oil either.
Oh.
Really?
Back home, I drive a hybrid.
You like it out there in Los Angeles?
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
You know, you'd do all right out there.
So, um...
how long are you gonna be here for?
I don't know.
As long as my boss wants me to be.
Another week, at least.
So what would you say
to dinner tomorrow night?
Real dinner, I mean.
Yeah. I'd like that.
One scotch, one bourbon
And one beer
Hey, QB.
Oh, hey-- Hey, Herc.
Sorry.
When was that?
Well, that was a while back.
Ooh, you're getting good at that.
Look at you.
Very nice.
Very put out.
What's your injury?
The same as you.
C7-T1.
We got our fingers.
We're the lucky ones around here.
Oh, yeah, real lucky.
It's all relative, QB.
How, uh-- How long before you, uh,
you started playing
quad rugby?
About a year.
Of course, I wasted a good six months
drowning in a sea of self-pity.
Six months?
Six months.
How's that calculus going?
What calculus?
You know, you were talking
about it the other day.
I don't know.
Advance-placement trig?
Yeah.
How's that going?
It's going fine.
I know you were worried about it
the other day.
You had some big test
coming up.
- Tim, just don't do this, okay?
- Do what?
Pretend that you're interested
in my schoolwork.
It's obvious that you're not,
that you're just trying to--
Have a conversation, Lyla?
Yeah, I thought we may want
to try and do that sometime.
Okay.
What do you want to talk about, Tim?
The fact that you're sleeping with
your paralyzed best friend's girlfriend?
Is that what you want
to talk about, Tim?
No, I don't think we're going
to be doing a lot of talking.
I just wanted to see if you might be
coming home for dinner tonight.
I don't think I'm gonna
be home for dinner tonight.
Your daughter was asking
for a picture of you,
and so I just thought you might
like to weigh in on which one--
That's not funny.
Don't do that.
We sure would love to see you.
How was your day today?
- It was all right.
- Yeah?
How was yours?
If you listen to
the TV or the radio,
I'm the coach that can't
get the decision made.
Can't make a decision.
Can I help you
make the decision?
Sure, go ahead. Make the decision, Honey.
What's your decision? You make the call.
Start Saracen.
Start Saracen?
I cannot start Matt Saracen.
Then start Voodoo.
I don't want to start Voodoo.
Then start me.
I would love to start you.
Well, you know, it seems to me here
that at this point, there's just not gonna be
a decision that's gonna feel good.
So the good news is
you can make the decision
and come on home and
have dinner with your family.
See your kid.
Problem is, I've just got
a little, slight problem,
being that...
Matt Saracen, one, is good for the team.
The team will play for Matt Saracen.
There is no doubt about that.
He's done everything I've asked him to do.
He's left it all on the field.
No problem.
I trust the kid.
He trusts me.
This kid Voodoo,
I don't like the kid, one.
Two, I don't trust the kid.
But three, I believe he can
get it done for us.
I believe he can
win this game for us.
That's it.
That's it right there.
That sounds to me like you've
made your decision, Coach.
Yeah, they said something
about bedrock.
The crude's made up of this stuff.
Could you put Angela on the phone anyway?
Thank you.
Angela, hey, it's Connor.
I'm gonna need a flight back to L.A.
Tomorrow morning's perfect.
Thank you.
All right.
Bye. Hi.
- How you doing?
- I was waiting for you.
That was my boss.
My boss needs me back in L.A.,
so I've gotta cut the trip short.
But I would really like
to go out tonight still.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
- I'll see you later.
- Work.
Bye.
Yeah?
- You wanna talk to me, Coach?
- Yeah. Come on in.
Sit down.
You gave a hell of a week of practice.
I couldn't have asked for anything more.
Thank you, sir.
I just want to let you know that
I really appreciate all the encouragement
you've been giving me.
- And I feel ready for this.
I mean, I feel readier for this
than anything in my whole life.
I'm gonna start Voodoo.
I want you to be ready.
I want you to stay on the playbook.
- Be prepared.
- Mm-hmm.
Yes, thank you.
Thanks for letting me know.
I say if we do our best,
we will have success.
And that we own
the fourth quarter.
The fourth quarter is ours!
Hey, hey, hey!
It's going down tonight!
The Panthers ain't even
began to fight!
Look, they wanna trash
our locker room,
we're fittin' to hit 'em
with a sonic boom!
The Panthers gonna have
the last laugh,
'cause we
breakin' our foot off...
Love you, Daddy.
How you feeling today, Mr. Street?
Well, hello, Miss Garrity.
You look pretty tonight.
What are you doing here?
You're gonna be late for the game.
I know.
You have a visitor.
I do?
Mm-hmm.
- Hey.
- Hey, Coach.
I thought I'd bring up
a little something.
Decorate the room a bit.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
God bless, coach.
Good luck.
Clear eyes, full hearts.
Can't lose.
What's up, Street?
What's up, fellas?
Man, look, we just came by
to say we love you.
- We're gonna win for you.
- I know y'all are gonna win.
Get the balls, right?
Yeah, sure.
How you doing, Matt?
Play well, all right?
Thanks.
You get better.
Thanks, Coach.
It's good to see you all.
How you doing?
Get out of there.
Thank you for coming, y'all.
I miss you, Street.
Where the hell you been?
You know.
Around.
Go.
- See you later, okay?
- Okay.
- Love you.
- I love you.
I love you too.
Hi.
I thought I was picking you up.
- You're--
- Can I come in?
Um, yeah, of course.
It is Friday night, and Voodoo madness
has put its spell on the Lone Star State.
And 16,000 people have gathered together
to witness the debut of superstar phenom
Ray "Voodoo" Tatom.
And for Coach Taylor, he better hope Voodoo
can get it done tonight.
I can't remember when there was
so much riding on a game
this early in the season.
This is a bitter rivalry,
and no one is about to back down.
Oh, Riggins gets leveled!
And Tatom goes down.
It's another offensive line breakdown.
You know what, Ray Tatom is not happy.
Frustration starting to mount here
as this game plan by Coach Taylor
is not going the way he'd hoped.
Halfway through the second quarter here
as the Panthers are down by a touchdown.
Pro right, 27 China.
Screen pass to Riggins.
We worked on this play
all night--we're setting 'em up.
We can get 'em with this.
Now let's go.
Looks like Smash is gonna shuttle in the play.
I hope Coach Taylor's found
the key to this Tiger defense.
- Pro right, 27 China.
- No, hell, no, man. Forget that.
Hey, you can't change the play.
We gonna win, we gonna play my way.
Let's go, Voodoo, come on!
Tatom's over the ball.
Set!
Hut!
He takes the snap.
Hit him!
- Riggins wide open in the flat.
- He's open! Hit him!
All I want is what's mine
I don't care who I hurt
Go, Voodoo!
He's on his way!
Voodoo Tatom!
He's gonna get it!
It's a touchdown, Dillon Panthers!
Whoo, I tell you what, that is the Voodoo
Tatom we've been waiting for, Sammy!
And Dillon is right back in this thing.
Come here, come here.
You run the plays I call.
You understand?
I give you that one, and that's it!
That one.
- Look at the scoreboard, Coach.
- That one!
And Voodoo has fired up this team
after that stunning touchdown.
And you can feel the momentum shift--
Oh, what a shot!
And the defense is really
bringing on the pain now.
They are playing with purpose,
trying to get that ball back in Tatom's hands
to try and get a lead before the half.
Hey, listen to me.
Listen, Tatom, c'mere.
Tatom. Tatom!
Tatom!
Tatom, get over here!
Seems like a little confusion
over on the sidelines, Sammy.
What's he doing?
Pro right, gun,
triple nine ranger... On one.
Ready?
Coach Taylor seems
a bit perplexed out there.
I don't know what's going on.
Oh! Ohh!
Move, 35!
Hut!
Tatom drops back.
Quick three steps on the right side--
Oh, and it's picked off!
The ball is picked off by the safety,
Fowler, and he's up the left side.
And it doesn't look like
he's gonna be touched.
And that is a touchdown.
Dillon is gonna go into the locker room
down by a touchdown.
Hey!
You pull another stunt like that again,
and you are off this team, you understand me?!
- Move off.
- You understand me?!
Move off me right now!
- You get out of my sight!
- Who?
- What?
- You're done!
- Done with what?
You are done!
Get out of my sight, son!
- I don't care!
- You are done here!
I don't need Texas!
That make you feel big?
Go ahead, you're done, son!
You don't pull that crap
on me out there!
- No one does!
- Fade to black.
- Saracen!
- Yes, sir?
Go warm it up, son.
It all comes down to this, folks.
One minute 18.
Panthers down by 7.
This is our time.
The fourth quarter's ours.
We have worked for this.
We have earned it.
Matt Saracen continues as the quarterback,
and still no sign of Voodoo Tatom.
Bold move by Coach Taylor.
Now we'll see how this
is gonna turn out.
Listen to me, we're gonna
run this team ragged.
- You can lead this team.
- Yes, Sir.
Lead 'em now. Bring it home.
It is a tough road to home for Saracen.
84 yards to go.
All right, we're gonna
wing right, 28 rocket pitch.
Let's do this.
All on one. Ready?
Go!
Set!
Dillon setting up
with three wide to the right.
And with so little time, they probably have
only three or four plays left.
Oh, he goes to the short man, Dolia,
and he's out of bounds at the 32 yard line.
Hut!
There's a pitch out to Williams on the right.
He picks up a block.
He's heading up the sideline.
He gets to the 46 yard line.
Another first down.
And that'll stop the clock.
Let's go, Matt.
Keep it rolling.
Here's Williams on the left side now.
He's running him left!
And Williams got a little bit of room.
And he is pushed out of bounds.
That'll stop the clock
while they move the chains.
Seven seconds. This is the last play
of the game for the Dillon offense.
Let's see if Matt Saracen
can pull this one off.
All right, we're doing the same play,
just with a little twist!
Blue, 8!
Hut!
Saracen with another pitch
to Smash Williams on the left side.
Reverse! Reverse!
It's a reverse!
Riggins on the right side.
Look at that block by Saracen!
Touchdown!
Touchdown, Dillon Panthers.
I cannot believe
what I have just seen.
Oh, folks, we have seen
something truly special here tonight.
And now, we got an opportunity
to tie this ballgame
with just one extra point.
Dillon's gonna be thrilled
to get out of here with a tie.
Saracen, get in here.
Turn around, son.
What do you see out there?
We got 'em right where we want 'em.
We're gonna go for two.
What do you think?
Give it to Smash.
He's been doing it all game, Coach.
- Coach, we need a play.
- 18 option, Matt. 18 option.
- Do you understand that play?
- Yes, sir.
- You got the play, you understand?
Get 'er done.
Well, I don't know if I like this.
But Coach Taylor has Saracen
back in the game.
And it looks like they're gonna be going
for the two-point conversion and the win.
You are looking at a man
who is betting his entire career
on this one play.
Green, 20!
Hut!
Williams takes the pitch.
Heads up the right side.
He gets airborne--
Oh, he takes a lick at the goal line.
Did he make it?
It's good! It's good!
Smash Williams has scored
on a two-point conversion
and the Dillon Panthers
have taken this game.
- Damn fine game, Coach.
- Just doin' my job.
I can't believe Coach T would've put
the whole season on the line,
but boy, that was a beautiful call!
I'll tell you what,
Coach Taylor rolled the dice
- and he came up a big winner this time.
- Coach, good luck for the season.
- That was a fine game.
- Thank you, sir.
Connor?
Hi.
- Morning.
Breakfast.
Someone should enlighten
this town about room service.
It looks like it's just
for one person.
Yeah, well, I gotta
catch my plane.
- Right, right.
- You knew I was...
Yeah. Yeah, I did.
You know, Tyra...
you're a really great girl.
- And, um...
- Please, just...
Don't.
Look, I have to be honest
with you, Tyra.
I'm involved.
You know, in L.A.
I'm, I'm in a pretty serious--
- Relationship?
- Yeah.
Yeah, well...
you know, this was just
a one-time thing.
- And I have a boyfriend, so...
- Right.
Yeah.
Okay, well...
- I really have to, um...
- Right.
So I'll see you soon?
- Yeah.
- Ok.
Bye.
Let's get out of this country
I wanna get those, um, those
chocolate-covered blackberries.
- That sounds good.
- All right.
Hey!
Hey, you know what I like about me?
That you're married to somebody
as fantastic as me?
That is what I like about me.
- Good morning, cheerful.
- Hey, thank you for doing that.
Tonight, what do you say
we go grab some dinner?
- Uh-huh, I like that.
- Catch a movie.
- And then we'll do the...
- Oh, really?
Okay, okay!
Wait, wait, wait!
Inappropriate. Inappropriate.
- Eating breakfast.
- We're gonna get down tonight.
I'll see you after
the meeting this afternoon.
- Good-bye. I love you.
- Tell Buddy Garrity,
uh, he can shove it.
Find a cathedral city, You can
be handsome, I'll be pretty
What does the city
have to offer me?
Everyone else thinks
it's the bee's knees
I'll tell you what. Eric Taylor coached
a hell of a game last night.
Those Arnett Mead boys had
a tremendous size advantage
over our Panthers. And he just ran
those Tigers flat into the ground.
- Hey, you're a hero,man.
- Well, my hat's off to Coach Taylor.
And young Matt Saracen has really emerged
as a force to be reckoned with.
That was a hell of a performance.
Hey, Jeff, how are you doing today?
I appreciate that, thank you.
- Hey, good one. Good one.
- Thank you.
Smell the Jasmine,
my head will turn
Feel like gettin'
confessional
We'll find a cathedral city
You can convince me
I am pretty
What does the city
have to offer me?
Everyone else thinks
it's the bee's knees
What does the city
have to offer me?
I just can't see
Coach Taylor, a couple of gentlemen
I'd like for you to meet here.
Buddy.
It's, um..
I'm sorry. What was your name again?
Lance Jennings. Ryan Johnson.
Nice to meet you.
We're from the district executive committee.
Some questions have arisen
about Ray Tatom's eligibility.
And I thought we had this
all squared away, Coach.
I thought we did too.
Well, we're here to inform you that
there's gonna be a formal investigation.
And we'll notify you
of our findings.
Your "findings."
And if he is deemed ineligible...
Ray Tatom won't be playing
football here anymore.
And Dillon will be stripped
of last night's victory.
Well, y'all have a good day.
Buddy, I'll talk to you later.
Yeah, I'll talk to you later, Coach.
www.forom.com
Capture: Raceman
Sync: Tauri41