I really do wonder why it is
that you just refuse to grow up.
I can tell you why. Because then
I might end up just like you.
My phone is ringing off the hook
day and night.
My kid is acting
like he needs a Hollywood agent.
These recruiters wanna try
to get you to commit
to any other school any way they can.
The high school in Laribee...
Half of school got completely lifted up
and knocked out by the tornado.
We're gonna be good hosts and guests.
I know coach Dickes
and as long as he don't stir things up,
I think it's gonna be just fine.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- He pissed on my shirt.
Don't you push me!
Don't you ever lay your hands on me!
You ever, I mean,
ever touch one of my players again...
Hey, Jules.
- It's time we go.
- Where's my beer?
Remember what I said about being quiet.
- Okay, you good?
- I'm good.
- Hey, Jule.
- Coach...
It's not even close to what you think.
Go get your stuff
and get out of this house right now.
... used to be
we had to wait till February
in the national letter
of intent signing day,
but folks, the times, they have changed.
It is all about verbal commitment now.
- And the race is on to see which one...
- Hey, Smash.
Where you at? Alabama's
and Oklahoma Tech on their way.
Yeah, I'm just coming up.
Oh my God, Alabama!
- Hurry up.
- Okay.
I'm coming up right now, bye.
I have been to the mountain top
and Tuscaloosa is here.
God bless America
and God bless Alabama football.
Here she is.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
That's all right.
This is my girl. Her brother plays
for the Miami Southern,
- so, she's like my advisor.
- Nice to meet you too.
- Hi, Mrs Williams.
- I was just telling Brian here,
that we got a slot all ready to go
for him there in Tuscaloosa.
National Championships,
it's pretty good resume.
Young lady knows her stuff.
Now, all we need is verbal commitment,
and red carpet'll roll
like the tide itself.
Great. But are you willing to weigh the
physicals and garantee all four years?
That's something we'll definitely
have to consider. She knows her stuff.
Yeah, she knows a thing or two.
Oklahoma Tech, where legends are made.
- All real, all real.
- Yeah?
Alright, now. Do you ever play
football in a snow storm, son?
It's epic.
Michigan is
the harder college football, Brian.
And we'd like
to make you part of our team.
You're gonna be our next big star.
You gotta come play in Georgia, Brian.
They'll love you there.
Y'all are definitely top 5.
Look, all I need is a verbal...
We'll let you know, okay?
But, thanks for the peanuts.
They boil these things.
So good, they'll make you
wanna slap your grandma.
- Thanks for coming out.
- Alright.
- Take care. You'll call?
- Yes, sir.
How you doin'?
Good.
About last night,
I put you in that situation.
- No, wait...
- No, just listen to me.
I should not have trusted
Tim Riggins being in this house,
I should have talked to y'all before,
I made any decision on having him here.
He so much even looks at you at school,
I want you to tell me about it,
you understand that?
Please?
You gotta pick it up,
or we're gonna be late, okay?
Yeah.
2x11: JUMPING THE GUN
Transcript: www.swsub.com
Subtitles:
Andy, DarKsh, GillesSilb, Ju, Sixe
www.top-series.net (0.90)
You cannot be in here after hours.
You understand me?
I want you to clear this stuff up
and clear out.
You got it?
Noannie!
Are you messing with my phone again?!
No.
It was in my room, so somebody took it.
- I didn't. Bug off!
- Don't just up walk on outta here!
Noannie, I'm not playing.
Where's my phone?!
What are you doing to your sister?
Is that what your little girlfriend
tells you college boys do nodays?
Look, don't start, mama.
"Don't start, mama"?
Who you think you talkin'to?!
- Somebody took my phone.
- She didn't take it. I did.
- What?
- Oh, yeah.
You've been on it day and night.
So now get your head back in school
and leave this recruitin' mess alone.
I've to make a verbal commitment.
You understand?
Yeah, I understand that.
I also understand
you need to use your head.
If you commit too soon,
and you don't think
about everything that's involved,
you're gonna be makin' a big mistake.
I'm gonna do this, mama.
With you...
or without you.
Now I gotta get to class.
Hey, Shel.
- How ya doin'?
- Good.
It smells good.
- Is that my shirt?
- No.
- It looks like it.
- OK, it's your shirt.
But you should give it to me.
- It's too sexy for you.
- I beg your pardon?
It's too tight.
You can't wear this to school.
What about the boys' hormones?
They'll think you're hitting on 'em.
Oh, that is ridiculous.
- It's not too tight...
- Here's your bowl.
- or sexy, or anything like that.
- Tami?
- What?
- My results.
- You got it?
- What is it?
Open it. Open it.
- It's the results from her exam.
Oh, my God, I passed!
You did!
- That's great, sweetie.
- I know.
I'm so proud of you!
She passed!
Shelly Hayes passed the test.
That's excellent.
What are you gonna do now?
- What are you gonna do now?
- I don't know, I mean...
I take y'all to dinner.
Oh, that's so sweet.
- Let's have some dinner at Applebees.
- Wait, now.
You just passed the test,
you gotta figure out a few things:
how you'll jump start the business,
where you'll go, how you'll set it up.
And I can talk to a bunch of people,
get you involved
with a lot of folks that can give you
answers to your questions.
Oh, my God, Eric.
That would be so amazing.
No, anything I can do
to help you with that.
That's the sweetest thing
you've ever said to me.
It's my pleasure.
I was gonna talk to you about this,
but when you're starting out
as a real estate agent,
you have to do these cold calls
as the fondation of your business.
I don't want to make all those calls
and tie up your phones,
so I did a little bit research.
And it would only cost $9 a month
to put a new phone line in here.
And I was thinking
since you have a teenager
we could share a phone line.
- That sounds good to me.
- That sounds like something
we should definitely talk about.
Absolutely.
For sure, but let's go to Applebees.
That sounds like a great idea.
This stuff'll keep till tomorrow.
All right?
Let me get my stuff. Hold on.
You here?
Look, it was just
a friendly gesture, that's all.
I understand,
but I can buy my own groceries.
Miss Williams,
I know being a single parent's hard.
You've done a great job with your kids,
supporting them as a nurse.
I just want you to know
Oklahoma Tech is here for you.
In many cases, we can provide
a first-class relocation.
Mister, you need to think about
relocatin' your butt up out of my way.
Housing near the campus
for the athletes' parents
- so the families can stay together.
- Stay together?
Yes, ma'am.
And we'll arrange for job for you too,
with good pay at the local hospital.
And you get
all your weekends off,
so you can catch all Brian's games.
You might be
the nicest person I ever met,
or you might be Satan himself.
But either way,
this conversation is over.
Miss Williams, just hear me out.
No, what happens if he gets hurt, huh?
What happens to my house and my job,
my son's education?
- He's not gonna get hurt.
- You tell me that.
- Hey.
- Everything all right?
Everything's just fine.
Seems like you need to step away.
- Ladies, please.
- That's the right thing to do.
- You need to step away.
- You heard what she said.
Have yourself a good day, okay?
How was your day?
It was good. How was yours?
Let's go.
Learned anything interesting?
Not really.
It's that girl.
She got my son's head spinnin'
every which way direction.
- I don't like it.
- That girl Noelle?
- I raised these kids by myself.
- I know.
My whole life has been about
taking care of them.
And she waltzes in
and is trying to turn him
into some rich fast-talking
blinged-out football star,
or some kind of hot prospect.
He ain't gonna do nothin'
but get chewed up and spit out.
I just want him to be a good man,
you know?
I know.
But what he's trying to do is
he's trying to take responsibility
for his future,
in whatever way he knows how.
I just didn't think
it would be this hard letting him go.
I know, that's for sure.
I know that.
I... I just...
I came over to apologize
about the other night. My dad just...
He jumped to conclusions,
and... and I just...
I couldn't tell him.
That's fine.
I'm really sorry, though.
Don't worry about it.
And I wanted to say thanks
for saving me from that whole...
Riley thing.
It wouldn't have ended good.
I agree.
Yeah, I don't...
I don't think so.
But really, it's...
It's fine.
It'll blow over, I'm sure.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Okay, well, I will see you later then.
Good night.
Coach Taylor and the Panthers
have been hard at work all week, folks.
The big game this Friday has become
even more of a rivalry
due to the fact the Lions
have set up camp here in Dillon.
Close quarter have led to
more than a few altercations,
including a reported dust-up
between Coach Taylor
and Laribee's Coach Dickes.
Coach.
- You want to get a beer with me?
- I don't drink, Coach Taylor.
You don't drink,
or you don't drink with me?
Look, I know y'all been uprooted.
I know it's not easy,
space beg around here...
it's very small.
I know times are tough.
Thanks for acknowledging
that times are tough.
Thanks for helping me out with that.
By the way,
I went ahead and spoke
with Coach Roberts.
And it seems tomorrow
we'll be moving my team
into the girls soccer team locker room.
I'm really busy, Coach.
Just go ahead
and take that country charm of yours
and go buy somebody else a beer.
He have you talked to TMU yet?
They playin' hard to get,
but you know, so am I.
So we'll see how it works out.
Yo, what's up, Swash?
Hey, what's up, chippendale?
Yo, man, TMU came a callin'.
I'm playing football
in Austin this fall.
Hey, man, listen,
we gonna be teammates or what?
Hey, look, listen up.
I got better thing to do than TMU.
Like what, you get the manager job
at the Alamo Freeze?
Alabama, baby!
Alabama!
What?!
S-E-C.
You gave Alabama the verbal?
You know what?
It's gonna be the shot
heard around the world.
- You just gonna have to wait and see.
- Oh, I will.
Good luck.
I thought, like, 'bama's sweet,
but I thought...
You sure you don't want to go to TMU?
You don't wanna hold out
and see what they got to offer?
- Ask me what I'm doing.
- What are you doing?
Getting some paper towels
to clean up a dozen eggs
that are on our kitchen floor.
Shelly went to the store
which I asked her to do:
to go get eggs, because we needed eggs.
And then she comes in and dropped 'em
all on the floor, like a dingbat.
And then she just looks at 'em,
she just stares at 'em
and says, "oh, no,"
and then walks back to the back bedroom.
Maybe it's time for her to fly the coop.
You ever think about that?
She keeps telling me that
I need to cut my hair all off.
Because of the baby and everything.
That it's too long.
It's starting to get me insecure.
Do I need to get my hair cut?
No, you don't need to. Your hair
is perfect, stop listening to her.
- She's driving me crazy.
- She should cause she's crazy.
Hey, hon, you know what
I've been meaning to tell you?
- What?
- I ran into Corrina Williams,
at the market.
And she was being accosted
by a recruiter.
And she just seemed at her wit's end.
It seems like she's real worried
about Smash,
about this girlfriend of his,
she thinks is a bad influence.
There's nothing I can do
about all his girlfriends, so...
I'm just saying,
you know, it might be good
if you had a talk with him,
because he does not have
a male role model in his world.
I'm gonna do that too,
as soon as I figure out how not to get
my ass handed to me on Friday night.
Okay? Thank you.
Oh, God.
Tami...
I was just blow drying my hair,
and all this black smoke
start to coming out.
I think it's probably broken.
Do you have another hair dryer?
No. Actually, Shelly,
that's the only hair dryer we have.
I think you better go get another one.
While you're at it, maybe pick up
some eggs. That'll be great.
No, I never said I sent the payment.
But I'm gonna send that money
right now, actually. Okay.
How you doing?
- All right.
- What's up?
Just moving our stuff out.
How you and Billy doing?
We broke up.
Sorry to hear that.
You know, uh, if you want
to finish that Riggins trifecta,
I think my dad lives in corpus still.
I could probably give you his address.
That's just mean.
You're awful.
I think you kind of deserve it,
don't you think?
Yeah...
I do.
You want to tell me what happened
between you and Billy or what?
Look,
I know you're gonna hate me forever,
and I don't blame you
but I want you to know...
that I was alone and I was scared,
and I was just trying
to build a life for my son.
- So what happened?
- It didn't work out.
He lost his job.
And I can't handle two mortgages.
I mean, I could been
the first to tell you
that guy can't hold a job
for more than six months.
You know...
I hope you can patch things up with him,
'cause he loves you so much.
Maybe...
Maybe you need him too, you know.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to get in the way.
Have a safe trip, wherever you're going.
Bye.
Is that The Office? Oh, my God,
I love this show. I'm so addicted to it.
I was so scared that it didn't tape.
Have you ever seen it?
It's so good.
Actually, I don't know if you would
really like it. It's very talky.
You taped over my game.
I'm sorry.
It was an important game?
Yes, it was a very important game!
You taped over my game.
I'm sorry.
I mean, I didn't know.
I just...
I just used the tape that was in there.
You know, you guys...
You should get a TiVo.
Can I ask you something?
You got any concept
about personal property?
You know, like how about
personal private moments
in the privacy of one's
personal, private space?
Do you understand what I'm saying?
- I know what privacy means.
- I understand
that you're my wife's sister
but we've been wondering
when is it, exactly, that you're
gonna get a place of your own?
I didn't mean it to come out like that.
- Oh, my God.
- That came out wrong.
That came out wrong.
I'm sorry.
Just stop talking.
- I didn't mean to say it like that.
- No, I heard you,
it's fine. I'll take the laundry.
I just feel kind of stupid right now.
It's fine.
Come on in.
Oh, she's with me, Coach.
Noelle.
Yes, hi.
It's so nice to meet you.
I'm a very big fan.
The way you took down West Cambria
at the state championships last year
was the best coached game
- I think I've ever seen.
- I'm glad you noticed. Thank you.
You're welcome.
So imagine your phone is
ringing off the hook.
You're getting text messages
till 4:00 a.m.
What's it all mean?
Well, playing at Alabama
is at the top of the list.
Alabama?
Anything else?
Lots of places, Coach.
We're thinking
a national championship run
would be beneficial.
It's lots of coverage, good exposure.
So I roll on over to Alabama.
Coach has got good ties to the pros,
and I'm living the NFL dream.
TMU?
I still haven't heard from 'em.
They're getting back
at you for walkin' on 'em.
Any history between me and TMU
has nothing to do with you.
They want you,
they're gonna come after you.
Look, the point is
I gotta make a verbal, Coach.
Before you hear from TMU,
you gotta make your verbal?
I mean...
What am I supposed to do?
All right, let me tell you what I know
about Alabama, then.
They got the best running back
in the conference: Demetrius Walsh.
And another thing:
he is not going pro either...
- He's staying his senior year, we know.
- That's one year.
I can handle it if it means Alabama.
What about Waters? 500 yards this year.
He's a freshman backup.
He's already mastered their offense,
which is extremely complicated.
Now, that's your sophomore, junior year
on the scout team.
That's three years on the bench
before you even touch your foot
on that turf on a Saturday.
Or there are other situations out there:
schools that need you to play now.
It's gonna be a fight.
You gotta give yourself
the opportunity to play,
the opportunity to be seen.
You might want to
settle down, take a breath.
And you definitely want
to look at the fine print, son.
I'm saying: be patient.
Don't let 'em pressure you.
And don't end up making any
emotional decisions.
That makes a lot of sense.
What does your mother say?
My mom?
The woman who gave you birth,
what did she say?
Honestly,
I don't think my mom knows
the difference between Alabama
and Dillon Junior College.
Let me tell you something.
My last piece of advice for you.
Listen to your mother.
You listen to her, and you respect her.
You understand what I'm saying?
Now get the hell out of here.
- Let me finish my lunch.
- Appreciate it.
- Let me know you need anything else.
- All right.
- What are you doing?
- I'm checking into a motel.
- Why? What happened?
- Eric asked me to leave.
Well, hon, he's in a terrible...
He's such a grump this week.
No, he didn't mean it.
Come on, let's go back in the house...
- Sweetie, come on now.
- Honey, it's for the best, OK?
I don't want to be an imposition.
I just wanted to help with Gracie...
Well, hon, listen.
Now come on, we need to talk about this.
Come on, Tami, you want this.
Yes, you do, honey.
OK, I mean, you didn't want to tell me,
that's fine. You got Eric to do it.
But you know...
It's fine.
I'll call you when I check in.
I understand.
Coach.
You left your playbook on the field.
You're just
a regular boy scout, aren't ya?
You're welcome.
What are you doing?
I lost my keys.
You look like crap.
How you doin'?
I left Julie down at the sandwich shop.
Did you kick my sister
out of the house today?
No, I didn't.
What happened?
I asked your sister
when she was gonna leave.
And your sister got very upset
and she pretty much inferred the rest.
And that's pretty much what happened.
I wish maybe you'd talked to me
before you'd had that conversation.
OK.
And in the future, if there's
a family member of mine
that's gonna be kicked out
of this house,
I would prefer that I do
the kicking out.
OK.
It's like everything happened at once.
I got laid off. I got no severance.
They didn't give me any kind of notice
that this was gonna happen.
So now I'm broke,
And Jackie's going crazy
'cause she's got a kid,
and I got no money to pay for the house.
And, you know, that's when
she bailed on me.
I don't know what else
there is to say about that.
Look...
Tim?
I'm sorry.
I know I screwed up.
All right?
I never should have gotten
with that girl.
And I'm sorry if I hurt you.
It was selfish and...
I'm sorry.
Looks like it's just us two, hu?
What are we gonna do
about the house, Billy?
We gotta come up
with $2,000 in two weeks.
I don't know, unless you got
some great idea,
I think we're gonna have
to start packing our bags, man.
Ready?
Before I go, I want you to know
that I'm sorry
I went off the handle with your sister.
And I apologize.
It's just, you know, there is nothing
in the world I hate
worse than hurting her.
No matter how much she's irritating...
I know that, and I'm gonna call her
and I'm going to apologize to her.
And we will work it all out.
- She was here for a long time.
- You damn right she was.
It'll be nice to have our house back.
Damn right it will be.
What I dread now is what in the world
we're gonna do with Gracie Belle
while we're at work.
I just... I hate it.
Can I tell you something?
That's not our burden.
And it's our gift.
Go win a football game, please.
All right.
OK.
- Dad, can I talk to you?
- I gotta go.
I really need to talk to you right now.
It's about the other night,
and the whole Tim thing.
It wasn't his fault.
What do you mean?
It was my fault.
We were at this party,
and I was drinking,
and there was this other guy
named Riley.
And I was about to get in trouble,
and Tim stopped it, and he took me home.
And he was trying to sneak me in, and...
Then you came in and...
And I'm just trying to say
it was my fault.
Damn, Julie.
I'm sorry.
Damn.
- Attaboy!
- You gotta pick that up!
This contest has turned out
to be a good old-fashioned shoot-out,
a day gun duel in D-Ville:
Taylor vs Dickes.
We got a corner
that's missing every time!
The corners gotta step up!
It's late in the fourth.
Panthers are down by five
with 1:34 left in the game.
It's third down, Panthers need a first.
Take 70. He's been there all night!
Time!
What's that, eight?
Fourth and eight?
The safeties
should watch for play-action,
he's gonna try to bust the seam.
- You wanna go cover-three?
- No! Have bandit come up and cover.
I've been baiting this hook
all night long. He's gonna take it.
If we go x-seam on the safeties,
we get Matt to hit it quick. It'll work.
Unless he wants us to go to the seam.
You guys are stinkin' up the field!
- One play, girls. You got in in ya?
- Yes, sir!
Listen up, listen up!
Let's go 26 fake keeper.
Matt, you take it on the boot.
This is what they're gonna do.
They're gonna fake on tackle 26.
Let's make sure
you get to the outside, son.
- You understand?
- Yes, sir.
They're gonna bring Saracen
around the edge.
He'll go wide. Nail him there!
- Let's show 'em what we got.
- You gotta be aggressive.
Let's get this done!
Let's get this done.
- Let's take this home right now!
- Get out there!
- One, two, three... Panthers!
- Let's go, baby. Let's go!
Here we go, the game comes down
to this play.
The Lions will win
if they can stop the Panthers here.
Been reading your mail, Coach Taylor.
It's time to take you to school.
Let's go!
Hang on to your hats, folks.
This is it.
Fourth down.
Saracen is over the ball.
It's a handoff to Smash.
No, Saracen keeps the ball on bootleg.
He's got nowhere to go.
He's looking to pass.
He dishes it to the flat. Tim Riggins!
Gotcha!
And he's got some blood, baby!
- Get him! Pick him up!
- There you go!
To the 40, the 45!
Take it in, baby!
He's in Lions' territory
Go and get him!
Tim Riggins could go all the way.
Holly cow!
What the hell was that?
You see that?
All you gotta do is take him down!
Get off of me!
That's all it takes to take somedy down!
You stick 'em!
You say good-bye to playoff!
Coach interferce.
The game's over.
- All right, that's it. Take it in.
- Let's go!
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go.
Can I have a word in here alone, please?
Thank you much.
What the hell was that?
Don, what the hell was that?
You know what I think?
I think you owe this school an apology
is what I think.
And not only that,
but you owe the players over there
an apology. That's what I think.
- I got it.
- You got what? What's it you got, Don?
I've done everything I can.
This school has reached out,
it has opened its arms to you.
- You don't know what I'm going through.
- No, I don't know. But you know what?
For two weeks now,
we've done everything that we can
to help you out over here.
I've been putting up with two weeks.
- Why don't you share with me?
- My wife's got three months to live.
And I don't have a game plan for that.
I'm not using that...
as an excuse, please know that.
I do owe you an apology.
You tell Riggins he's a fine player.
And I'm deeply sorry...
for what I've done to him.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I'm not gonna be coaching anytime soon.
I'm very sorry.
Thanks.
Guy.
Guy, it's Riggs.
Buckle up.
Just get your crap
and let's get out of here.
I'll just be down here
becoming a meth addict.
All right, we're good.
Let's go.
Come on.
I gotta put that back, Billy.
I'm not just gonna leave his gun
down there, he'll know.
Hurry up, put it back,
and let's get the hell out of here.
What are you doing?
Come on!
Really?
- Cash.
- Put it back.
Come on, just put it back
and let's get out...
It's a lot of money.
It's our mortgage.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Put the gun back
and let's get out of here.
Let's go.
Come on.
Billy, this is like,
a good chunk of change...
Look, she just woke up.
Hey.
Could I get a decaf, please?
Thanks.
- How are ya?
- I'm good.
So I brought the real estate section.
And actually, there are a couple
of really cute-looking places,
like, right in the neighborhood.
Okay, Tami, I've been doin'
my own homework,
and I have found some really good leads.
Oh, really?
In Dallas.
You're going to Dallas?
How come?
Because I'm driving you crazy,
that's how come.
- No, you're not.
- Yes.
Come on, Tami.
You know, Hon, it's just
the house is a little bit small.
Thank you.
And I do think that it's probably good
for Eric and me
to have some privacy again, and...
Yeah.
But that doesn't mean
I want you to go to Dallas.
I have got to get my life together,
and I don't think
that's going to happen here in Dillon.
I kinda like the idea
of having you around.
- We're gonna miss you.
- Thank you.
And I can't thank you enough.
Thank you for asking me.
Hey, what are we gonna do
with the extra grand?
What are you talking about?
We got the mortgage covered,
plus a grand.
That's the last thing I'm worried about.
We just stole $3,000 from a drug dealer.
You don't think there's gonna be...
No, you gotta relax, you know why?
He's probably so high
he doesn't even know what hit him.
- Who the hell is that?
- That can't be him.
- Don't answer it...
- I'm not gonna, relax!
Oh, it's coach.
It's coach.
We're fine.
- Hey, Tim...
- Hey, coach.
- Coach, how you doin'?
- Hey, how you doin'?
I'm good, I'm good.
Things are good.
All right.
I'll let you guys...
do your thing.
Come here.
Let me talk to you a second.
I jumped to conclusions.
I'm well aware of
what happened the other night.
I apogize.
I was wrong.
- It's fine, coach.
- No, it's not fine.
I couldn't have mishandled it any worse,
and I apologize.
The last couple weeks
have been giving you hell.
And not once,
have you come to me and complained.
And then... Then you got it
where you protected my daughter,
and you're not letting me
think bad of her.
And again, you don't say a word.
Not a word.
And I'll tell you something,
not as a coach, but as a father...
You realize
what an honorable thing that is?
That is very honorable.
Thank you, sir.
All right.
Rest this weekend.
- Will do, coach.
- Betcha, buddy.
You betcha.
What's your game plan with that burger?
Cool out, just cool out.
Hey, Smash.
- Congratulations. Good game last night.
- Oh, thank you.
You got a minute?
Can we talk?
Yeah, sure, I got a minute.
Yes, sir.
You were really good last night.
You really played well.
And I'm here because we want you
to play football for us at TMU.
We're offering you a full scholarship.
And all we need to get this done is
for you to give me a verbal commitment.
Yeah, but there's no reason
to rush, right?
I mean, we need to talk
about the fine print.
Well, the fine print is this:
it's gonna get down to trust.
Who are you gonna trust?
No other program is gonna work harder
at getting you to the NFL.
That's why we recruit so well:
we get guys to the NFL.
All we need you to do, come play for us,
work hard, earn your spot,
and I promise you
you'll get a shot at the pros.
Trust me.
If you trust me, we can make it happen.
Well, thanks.
I'm real glad we had this talk.
Thank you.
I'm too.
- I'm gonna be waiting to hear from you.
- Okay.
Of course you know, it's always been
my dream to play for TMU.
Can I take that as a verbal commitment?
Hey, y'all, the Smash is gonna
play for the "U," baby!
- All right.
- I'll take care of you.
I won't let you down.
How you doin', baby?
I gotta go tell my mom, yeah.
- I'll see y'all later.
- All right, go, Smash.
Turn that off.
Slide over.
I cannot tell you
how disappointed I am in you.
You lied about Tim Riggins,
you lied to me, you lied to your mother,
and that's something
we don't teach in this family.
I don't know when it is
I'm gonna be able to trust you again.
I'm beyond angry, honey.
I think the best word to describe it
would be "hurt."
As far as you drinking...
You're too young.
You, your mother and I
are gonna sit down
and have a talk about that as soon
as she and I sort this whole thing out.
And I think she would also
want me to tell you
that, yes...
people do make mistakes...
and I understand that too.
I love you so much...
and that will never change.
Capiche?
Capiche.
Hey, babe.
- Everything's all right here?
- Everything's just fine.
How is your sister doing?
She is doing all right.
She's gonna be great.
Movie night?
- What are we gonna see?
- Great.
I rented this movie
from the library: Cinema Paradiso.
It's mama's choice.
Let's watch Foul Play again.
All right, it's mom's choice.
Foul Play tonight.
- I'll get the popcorn.
- Goldie Hawn, Chevy Chase.
Go see your daddy.
But I'm making butter, real butter.
It's gotta be real butter.
Now, this is the most important thing
that a man can...
What are you doing?
Ooh, don't hit yourself.
Take them damn shoes off. You know
I just scrubbed this floor yesterday.
- What is this?
- I'm in, mom.
I'm going to TMU.
They want me.
- You sure that's what you want?
- Yes, ma'am.
Oh, baby!
Oh, I'm so proud of you.