- Hey, you got a boyfriend?
- No. Why?
- 'cause that's the guy
that should be doing all this,
Giving you rides everywhere.
- Maybe it'd be more efficient
if you were my boyfriend.
- Got luke here, a new player.
Y'all make sure
that he is welcome.
- You're a long way
from home, boy.
- I guess so.
- I'm julie,
matt's girlfriend.
- So you're the ball and chain
that keeps dragging him down.
- Do you think
I'm holding you back?
- No, you're the most important
thing in my life.
- If you can't finish games,
I can't keep this program going.
You turn it around,
or we gonna shut it down.
[cheering]
- Vince howard
puts the lions on the board
For their first touchdown.
[cheering]
- It's still
a sad state of affairs
For the panthers.
In a single week,
The team got a forfeit
on the books,
And a great player,
luke cafferty,
Shipped out of school.
Callers, you say what?
- Sammy, I got to correct you
on something.
That cafferty kid
wasn't shipped out.
He was hand-delivered
by principal taylor
To east dillon,
her husband's team,
And everybody knows it.
- [sighs]
- Taylor.
- Good morning, levi.
- I see you finished
the game last night,
Way to go.
Sis boom bah.
Rah, rah, rah.
- Hey, levi.
- Huh?
- Pep rallies...
They build excitement.
They're good for the school,
good for the team.
- Pep rallies
don't cost, correct?
- Nope.
- Good.
Don't let me get in your way.
- Come on, how much
retyping you got to do?
Just put your test scores in,
tell them how awesome you are,
And we can move along.
- It's too long.
I have to cut it down
at least by half.
Did you hear that brown
used to make you
Handwrite your essays?
- Wow.
Well, that's so that they could
weed out the serial killers.
- [chuckles]
- So what's the, uh--what's
the final list of schools?
- Um...
U.C. Berkeley,
u.C.S.B.,
Brown, amherst,
Um, mount holyoke,
N.Y.U.,
U.T. Austin--
Hook 'em horns.
[chuckles]
- Good splits, good splits!
Come off the ball, now.
Come off the ball.
- Step up.
Come on up.
- Fumble!
- Oh, man.
- Come on, now, 5.
- Get it together out there.
- What are you doing?
- Do you know how to read
the "d," man.?
Read the end, dude.
- That defensive end
didn't move.
- He did move.
You're supposed to take him.
- Next time, give me the ball
and get out my way.
- Come here, come here.
Shut up.
Shut your mouth.
Come here.
You read the end.
You stay in the pitch lane.
You keep your personal crap
off this field,
And you quit
letting me down
And quit letting
the team down,
'cause we are all
getting tired of it.
Is that understood?
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go, now.
Come on.
- All right, huddle up.
Let's go.
Get in the huddle.
Good jab step, three-two.
Good jab step.
Good fake in there.
Now let's go.
Right there.
[overlapping shouting]
- Come on, now.
That's on you.
- What the hell?
You trying to be funny?
I didn't even have time
to make a move out there.
- I don't understand.
Why aren't you in the end zone?
I got out of your way.
- I will break you up, boy.
Next time
you give me the ball,
You make sure you mean
to give it to me.
[overlapping shouting]
You, you,
you're my problem.
- You're your problem
right now.
- No, you're my problem.
- That's enough.
- Yeah.
Deer and beer, here we come,
two days away.
Let's get after it, billy.
- Tim, what the hell
are you doing?
This is how accidents happen.
- Minds, I don't think
they're loaded. We're fine.
- Tim, just put them
in the corner or something.
All right, she's not supposed
to have any stress right now.
- Where's the gun cleaner?
- Why do you have
to clean your guns?
- Wait.
You didn't tell her, did you?
- I totally see now.
So y'all just get to go hunting
And get drunk
and leave me here by myself.
- No.
No, no, no, no, no.
- I have an ultrasound
this week.
- I understand that.
And I want to be there
for that ultrasound.
- So I just get to shove this
fat ass behind a steering wheel
And drive myself to the doctor,
is that what's gonna happen?
- Baby, I will be there
for that ultrasound, okay?
Timmy and I
can go hunting anytime.
- No, we can't.
That's why it's called
hunting season, billy.
- Seriously, I'm gonna put
your head through a wall.
Would you shut up?
[whistle blows]
- let's go.
♪ ♪
[whistle blows]
Go!
Let's go!
[players shout]
- All right, jokers.
Who took my wallet?
Seriously, it's not funny.
- You know what I do
when I lose something?
I retrace my steps.
Maybe that's what
you should do, retrace them.
- I didn't lose it.
It was in my locker,
and now it's missing.
- I mean, you want us
to get together?
We could help you
look for it if you want.
- All right, cut the crap.
Seriously, I'm not gonna
tell you again.
Give me my wallet back.
- You're so sure I took it.
- Mm-hmm.
- Go and get it, then.
- Oh, oh.
[overlapping shouting]
- All right, all right,
all right.
- I got a pep rally
to organize this week.
I have got papers to grade.
I've got a family to raise.
I've got a wife to love,
And then I've got
you two bozos,
Trying to teach
you two something
You seem just damned determined
not to learn.
What makes you think
he took your wallet?
- It's obvious, coach.
- It obvious?
You're gonna make a hell
of a lawyer, aren't you?
Do you know where
his wallet is?
- No, sir.
- You don't know
where his wallet is?
- This is a bunch
of bull, coach.
- Hey, coach crowley!
- Yes, sir?
- Coach, would you take
these two gentlemen
To the gymnasium?
Have them run those stairs
for the next 30 minutes
Or until a wallet shows up,
Whichever one might come first.
- You bet.
- Thank you, coach.
Y'all enjoy.
- Let's go, boys.
- [scoffs]
♪ ♪
- 7.
- Riggs, what's up?
- Slinging dough instead
of 60-yard bombs now, huh?
No chicago?
- Nah, I kind of felt
like I should stay here,
Take care of my grandma.
- Right.
- San antonio?
- Negative.
- What else is new?
- You playing any ball?
- No, not really.
I've been working with this
artist on some art stuff.
Yeah, and then working here,
you know?
- Right.
I forgot about that.
- You, uh, gonna be watching
any football this weekend?
- No, I'm going hunting
this weekend, my friend.
- Oh, yeah?
- Get me some whitetail.
Maybe wrestle down some boars.
- Nice.
- That's my weekend.
- All right.
- Anyways,
it's good to see you.
- You too, buddy.
- Let's go for a beer sometime.
- Yeah, sure.
Hey, riggins, actually, um...
Is it cool if maybe I go
hunting with you this weekend?
- You hunt?
- Well, I mean,
my--my dad took me
A couple times
when I was little.
- Thursday morning...
5:15.
- All right.
- See you there.
- Yeah, man.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's nasty.
It's nothing but used goods.
Oh, landry, hey.
- Hey. What's going on?
You know devin.
- Hi. Hi.
- Hello.
- How you doing?
- You have a car.
He hit me with it.
- Yeah, I heard about that.
- Yeah, we all know
about it.
- I think you should use
that car
To drop me and my friends off
to this party
In kilroy tomorrow.
Yeah.
- That's an idea, huh?
- Yeah.
- Although I think
I might have to decline,
'cause I've kind of been down
that road before,
Where a girl asked me
to do something,
And I just kind of said yes.
And all of a sudden,
everyone's calling me a word
That I don't like to use.
- You're invited to the party.
You are too.
- Well, you could've just
said that to begin with.
- Thanks for the invitation.
- So you cool?
You want to come?
- Yeah, I think
that sounds great.
- It's gonna be a lot of fun.
- It's gonna be fun.
- All right, see you later.
- Okay, bye.
- Okay.
- All right.
- So you're gonna go
to a party in kilroy.
- Yeah, I am.
What is that?
Why with that tone?
- But I have to tell you
that when I die,
I hope people will say
that she gave
More than she took.
That would be
true success to me.
Mom.
I'm in.
- Oh, my god!
I could not be any prouder
of you, becky.
You make it look so easy,
and it's not.
It is not easy at all.
It is such hard work.
- Thanks, mom.
- You know what?
You need a new gown.
- Yeah?
- Absolutely.
A portrait neckline.
I know, how about tomorrow
before my shift,
We could go find
the perfect dress,
The perfect shoes,
and then get a bite to eat.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, tomorrow's great.
- Okay.
I can't wait to watch those
other girls eat your dust.
- I got to ask you something,
And I need you
to not be weird about it.
- What's up?
- There's this place
right outside of dillon
Called steers,
And I was wondering
if you'd go there with me.
- Steers?
- It's--
It's gay.
I mean, it's a gay place.
- Are you hitting on me?
- No.
You're not my type.
- Oh, I'm not your type?
- Look, I just need somebody
to go there with me.
This is a new experience,
and it's kind of weird.
And it'd be nice
to have a friend go with me.
- I'll go.
See what your type is like.
[engine turning]
- Well, I think
where we need to focus
All our attention right now
is library, library, library.
It's been since 2005
since we've had any updates.
It'z where we should focus
our funds.
- Yeah, but, um, you know,
I'm--I'm really sorry.
Our budget is already
tapped out.
Maybe we can do this
next year.
- But, no, I mean, you know,
We had actually pushed it
last year,
And we had talked about
that this--
This would be where
our focus was this year.
- Look, there are
a lot of people
Who are pretty angry
out there, tami.
I mean, you realize
that a substantial portion
Of the school's revenue
is generated by football,
Don't you?
- Oh, so you mean
people are angry
Because I told luke cafferty
that he had to go
To the correct school
for his district?
That's why we're not gonna get
our library?
That seems like
a shame to me.
- Look, after what you did
with luke,
We're gonna be lucky
To reach half
the normal amount this year.
I mean, you cost yourself
and the school
Any chance we might have had
to improve that library.
Now, I'm sorry, tami,
if you'll excuse me,
I do have another meeting.
- [gasps]
What?
- Hello, mr. Rc collins,
class of '79?
Mr. Collins, I would like
to talk to you about football.
I would like to talk to you
About east dillon
high school football
And coach eric taylor.
Hello?
- Try the next one.
- How's it going?
- Good.
- What are you doing exactly?
- We're looking up alumni from
the east dillon lions of past
To try to get them
to join the pep rally.
- Yeah, your husband
had the inspired idea
To make the pep rally
a sort of a homecoming.
- That is inspired.
- The lions of east dillon
are not roaring.
- He's not home.
- Try the nine, three--
- Honey, honey, come here.
Come here.
- Hello, is this
mr. Eddie boare,
Class of '79?
- Honey, you need food.
- Huh?
- You need food
for these people.
If you want to bring people in,
you got to make them some food,
Just like we do,
just like we've always done.
- You offering to cook dinner?
- Oh, lordy.
Well, perhaps I am.
Perhaps I am offering
to cook dinner, babe, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
You're welcome.
- That's real sweet.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
All right, well, I'm gonna
get myself ready for school.
Y'all, good luck.
- Hi.
- I'm stan traub,
Assistant coach.
- Julie, daughter.
[chuckles]
nice to meet you.
- Hey, mom.
Mom, are you ready to go?
- What?
- Can I borrow your truck?
- No.
- Please.
- You can't borr--you don't even
have your license.
- I know how to drive.
- I don't care.
- Thanks.
- What's wrong?
- My mom blew me off...
Again.
- There is a gay bar
in dillon?
- It's not in dillon.
It's outside of dillon.
- It's the same difference.
- Mr. Matthew,
"za" is not a word.
- "za" is a word.
And if you look at it,
it spells "za,"
As in "pizza."
It's vernacular
in certain places, but wait--
- You are such a liar.
- Don't try and distract me
from the fact
That you're going
to a gay bar.
What are you gonna do
at--at a gay bar?
- Dance and make out
with some chicks.
- I-I knew it.
I knew you wanted
to experiment.
- No, I'm going for devin
to be her moral support.
- Whatever,
I don't even care.
I'm going hunting
with riggins anyway.
- That's a joke.
You're going hunting
with riggins?
- It's not a joke.
- So you're just gonna go shoot
some poor defenseless animals
For the hell of it?
- Uh...
Yeah, well, to eat.
- You are so much better
than that.
Why would you stoop
to that level?
- No, I'm not.
I'm not better than that.
- It's disgusting.
- Whoa, hold on.
Hold the phone.
I live in dillon.
And people in dillon,
what they do
Is they go hunting
and shoot animals.
That's just
the way it works.
- That is an awful excuse,
first of all.
And second of all,
I live in dillon.
I don't go hunting.
- You don't live
in dillon for long.
I need a word...
Word.
- Is this about
my college applications?
- No, it's not about
your college applications.
It's not even about you.
I don't know why you think
everything's about you.
- No.
No.
All of this says runner-up.
None of this is good.
- I'm sure your mom
wanted to be here for this.
- Yeah, or she hooked up
with some dude.
You know, whatever.
- Hey, look, cut her some slack.
I'm sure--
- Don't.
[voice breaking]
okay, because every time
Something really important
comes along,
Every time, she does this.
She has an emergency
or a date,
Or she takes another shift
at that stupid bar.
- Hey, look,
this one's nice.
It's pretty.
- You think it's pretty?
- Yeah.
- Is that a portrait neckline?
- This is stupid.
You don't even know.
Can we go, please?
- No, wait, we can't go.
We're here.
We got to pick something.
And what's that saying?
Doesn't the dress find you?
- Can we please just go?
This was such a dumb idea.
- [sighs]
I'm gonna tell you something,
all right?
And you can't tell it
to anyone else.
Well, my mother never took me
shopping for a pageant gown.
And because of that...
I never placed at miss texas.
That's why
I got into football.
That's a fact.
This is what
we're gonna do.
We're gonna start
with the wheels,
And then we'll work
our way up.
By then,
hopefully they'll have
A new shipment
of dresses in.
♪ ♪
- Hey, landry.
Y'all, look at his shirt.
- Oh, my god.
What does he have on?
- How's it going?
You all ready for some
good old-fashioned revelry?
- What's this music?
- Oh, I'm glad you like it.
This is actually--
It's this local band.
Their name is crucifictorious.
- Do we have to listen
to this the whole ride?
I'm just saying.
- You look nice.
- Oh, thanks.
What's this music?
- Here, hold on,
just give it a--
♪ ♪
- Feel his hair.
It's like grass.
[laughter]
[indistinct chatter]
- Jess, you are looking
really good tonight.
I'm surprised
to see you here.
- Really?
- What's up with you?
What's your problem?
- I ain't got
no problem with you.
I think I'm the only person
who sees how disposable
You treat girls.
- Well, I can only
treat a girl
How she allows me
to treat her.
Maybe I been talking
to the wrong girls.
- See, now you're trying
to piss me off.
- You're sitting here frontin'
like you don't--
You don't think about me.
Not even a little bit?
- You wish I thought
about you.
I have a boyfriend.
- You got a boyfriend?
♪ ♪
- What's up with that, man?
I know that ain't
that opie-looking dude
I hit in football practice,
is it?
- I guess so.
- Looks like jess
hitting it now.
- Ah.
It's over.
I'm not a panther anymore.
And it makes me--
I feel ill.
But I don't know why
I'm saying this to you.
You know what it's like
to be a panther
And have it
taken away from you.
I'm sorry about it.
I'm sorry
about all of it, eric.
- Tami and I are having
Some east dillon alumni over
This week for dinner.
Why don't you
come over and join us?
- You can't fake
"boosterism," eric.
It comes from the heart.
That's the beauty of it.
- Hey, what's up, landry?
I was surprised to see youat .
You have fun?
- That was fun.
That was a lot of fun.
Someone spilled something
on my shoes,
But other than that,
it was fun.
- You had a good time.
You was dancing and stuff.
- Yeah, I had a good time.
- Yeah, you had
a good time with jess?
- Yeah.
I mean, you know, just as...
I was just her ride.
- Really? 'cause she told me
you were her boyfriend.
- Is--no.
I'm definitely
not her boyfriend.
She said that?
- Yeah, she did.
- No.
That's crazy.
- You're not lying to me,
are you?
- No, I'm not.
That's news to me.
[chuckles]
- All right.
You good.
Be safe.
- Okay.
- Hey, how you doing?
- Hey.
- Uh...
- What'll it be?
- You're not by chance
virgil merriweather?
1983 state championship,
quarterback,
East dillon lions?
- What'll it be?
- Well, I'll have
A, uh, pound of brisket,
if you would, please.
I'm eric taylor.
I'm the new coach
over at east dillon.
- $8.50.
- You don't by chance
rent this place out
For events or anything,
do you?
- Nope.
- Well, that's too bad.
We got our first pep rally,
homecoming coming up.
- That's nice.
- Look, this may sound odd,
but my wife and I
Are having a dinner party
for some ex-lion players.
- Nope.
- I got some really great
kids on my team.
They're good kids,
And they could sure
use someone like you
To come over and speak
some words to them.
- Brisket will be out
in a few.
- Hey, luke,
let me get this straight, man.
This guy steals your wallet,
And you don't do anything
about it?
- What do you want me to do?
- Get your wallet back.
- Look, luke,
I know east dillon's
like a prison or whatever,
But I didn't think
you'd become someone's bitch.
[laughter]
- Hey, I know, right?
- Stop the car.
- What?
- I see you brought
your boyfriends with you
To help you look
for your wallet.
- Why don't you shut up
and give it back?
- You don't know
when to quit, do you?
- Oh!
- There you go, luke.
Take him down.
- Don't know when to quit!
[siren wails]
- Come on.
Let's go.
[siren wailing]
- Go, go.
- Come on, man, let's go.
- Forget him. Let's go.
- Break it up, boys.
Break it up.
- Hey, deacon,
how long have you
Been over there
at bethel baptist?
- 18 years.
- That's a long time.
- Coach taylor,
can I ask you something?
- Yes, sir.
- Why are we here?
- Oh, lord have mercy, deacon.
I'm trying to enjoy
my meal here.
Man.
- No, that's, uh--
that's a good question.
Listen...
I just started coaching
at this school.
I would imagine that you
would think of it
As your high school too.
With that said,
We are facing--
I am facing a lot
of challenges over there.
And we've got some problems
that I want--
- With all due respect,
People from your part of town
Pretty frequently tell us
about our problems,
Our crime problems,
our education problems.
You know how we got
these problems?
Back in the '80s, the west side
of dillon got developed.
They got the mall.
They got the hotel.
The west side of dillon
got the money.
- What did we get?
- We got forgotten.
- We got
our high school closed.
- And so listen, we thank you
for your hospitality,
But I think I'm gonna
skip that lecture
About our problems.
- Well, I know nobody
needs a lecture here,
That's for sure.
- That's right.
- I think the truth is,
We just--we just wanted
to get to know y'all
A little bit better,
and I was just hoping
Y'all would get to know
my husband a little bit better,
Because if there's
one thing about this man,
He loves football.
He loves those boys out there.
Lives and breathes it.
You know,
it's family to us.
- Fact of the matter is
it's pretty damn hard
Playing football when you've
got nobody out there
Appreciating the effort
that you're putting into it.
- You like losing
with everybody watching?
- Well, deacon, that's what
we're trying to fix.
[doorbell chimes]
we're trying to fix that.
- Hmm.
- Hello.
- Oh, hey, buddy.
How are you?
- How are you?
- Is that buddy garrity?
- You know buddy?
- Do I know buddy?
[chuckles]
- Y'all,
this is buddy garrity.
- Buddy garrity.
[laughter]
- Mo hall,
you got to be kidding.
Big mo lost some weight.
- Nobody never hit harder
than buddy garrity,
I'll tell you.
- Hey, buddy.
- Damon gaston,
good to see you,
Good to see you.
- Honey, buddy's here.
- Buddy's here.
- Hey.
- Hello, coach.
- Hey, buddy, how are you?
It's good to see you.
- Good to see you.
Good to see you.
Hello, deacon.
♪ ♪
- So is this what you
expected it to be like?
- Not exactly.
But I really like
the lighting in here.
- [chuckles]
- I just don't know
how anybody meets anybody.
- You are asking
the wrong person.
- But you've--you've got
the forever boyfriend, though.
- Yeah, well,
Forever boyfriend is...
I don't know.
It's like he seems
pissed off
About, like,
the stupidest things,
And then we get
in these ridiculous arguments
That go absolutely nowhere,
and it's like--
It's like I don't know
how to fix us.
It's like something that's
broken or--I don't know.
You're not even
paying attention.
What are you looking at?
- Don't look over there.
- Is that your type?
She's cute.
- I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Don't flirt
while I'm gone, okay?
- You know me.
- Almost what?
[laughs]
- I was gonna help you
with those dishes,
But I somehow got stuck
to the couch.
- Mm-hmm,
so it seems.
Thank you so much.
I think I got it.
- I almost made it
back in there.
I just got
a little tired here.
- Mmm.
I heard deacon malone
say that he was gonna
Make some calls for you.
- That's because you make
a damn good steak,
Is what it is.
Hey.
- Hmm?
- Thanks for tonight.
- Don't thank me.
Thank buddy garrity.
- Buddy garrity
ate all my damn steak.
- [chuckles]
he sure did.
- Hey, you know what?
- Hmm?
- You're good at what you do.
You wear a lot of hats.
- Thank you.
[phone rings]
- Oh.
- Goodness gracious.
[ringing continues]
- It's not buddy.
Hello?
Yes, sir.
- The white kid,
he's got no record.
He can go.
The black kid,
he's going to juvie.
- His name is vince.
Has he made mistakes?
Hell, yeah,
the kid's made mistakes.
You know what, though?
He shows up.
He gets the job done.
He works hard.
I vouch for him.
All I'm asking, you give him
a second chance.
- Coach, he's used up
his chances.
- Can I see them?
Thank you.
- Coach, I can explain.
I didn't--
- Shh.
Just listen.
We are at a crossroads
right now.
You are gonna admit
that everything was your fault.
- My dad--
- quiet.
You are gonna cut
the tough-guy crap.
You are both gonna say
Exactly what
I tell you to say,
And we are gonna fix this.
Understood?
- Yes, sir.
- You get one chance
in life, fellas.
You can either
take advantage of it,
Or you can piss it away.
You do the latter,
And you're gonna regret it
the rest of your lives.
Get out.
[locks open]
Get out of the car.
- He really took off.
He really did.
- Hey, howard,
it's this way.
- You sure?
Thanks.
- [scoffs]
- Go, go, go, go.
Go. Go.
Caleb, go ahead!
Beat him!
[chuckles]
Wait, y'all slow--
okay, be careful.
- Lunches.
Line up, line up, line up.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Pop! Pop! Pop!
Hey, hey, come on,
get over here, boy.
Come on over here.
Give me some.
Ahh!
Go get on the bus.
Hurry up, catch 'em.
Catch 'em, now.
- Go get 'em!
Daddy, they got pop warner
practice after school today.
- Okay, you take your brothers,
and I'll make sure
They get a ride
from mrs. Turner, all right?
- Okay, you think maybe you can
stop by just for a second?
- Look, go on before
you miss the bus.
- Dada, I heard
what coach taylor
Was talking to you about
the other day.
- That ain't
your business, jess.
- Daddy, oka
look, I'm sorry.
I-I like football, okay?
Andre loves football.
Darius loves it so much,
he throws up
Because he gets so nervous
before each game.
But it's fine,
it really is.
It's not your thing anymore.
But it's still in us.
We're still
a football family.
- Jess, it ain't
for you to decide.
- Daddy, I'm not trying
to decide anything.
I'm just asking if we could
hold a pep rally here.
It'd be fun, dad.
- Get on before
you miss the bus.
Go ahead,
take the boys to school.
- Yes, sir.
- I'm hoping we get something
over that fire tonight.
So keep the eyes peeled,
light feet.
- What kind of things you think
we gonna--we gonna get?
- Whitetail, boar.
[gunshot]
- 7, stop!
- What?
- What was it?
- Well, I--
I don't--I don't--
I don't know.
- What do you mean
you don't know?
The wind?
- Well, I thought
I saw something,
But I think it might have
been the wind.
- So you're shooting--
give me that.
- Hey!
- No gun.
No gun.
- Really? Come on,
let me have my gun back.
- The number's 555-0101.
- Sammy, this year the panthers
were destined for greatness.
But now we got
to run the table
Just to make it
to the playoffs.
You ask me, tami taylor
should send a resignation
And a written apology.
♪ ♪
- Come on, y'all.
I just did what was right!
I did what I had to do!
I'm sorry I messed up
football for everybody!
♪ ♪
Hey.
I need some chocolate, please.
So am I your boyfriend?
'cause it--it really seemed
like vince thought
That I was your boyfriend.
He said that
that's what you said.
- I didn't say that
to him at all.
I just said
I had a boyfriend.
- Oh, okay.
Just wanted to clear that up.
- But it's not like
we're dating,
So what does it really matter?
We're not.
- Okay, 100% not.
Both: All right.
- See you later.
- College.
I'll tell you
what college was like.
7:00 a.M. Mandatory wake-up.
Then these fantastic
one-on-ones
With this robotic coach
that tells you
What you're doing wrong
every single day--
Nothing like coach taylor.
We were spoiled.
Plus, college is boring,
And you get a curfew
every night.
- You miss lyla, though?
- I think we had
different paths.
- So does that mean yes?
- Yeah.
How about you?
How's dillon?
- It's okay.
Not as bad
as I thought it'd be.
I mean, I'm getting to spend
a lot of time with my grandma,
So that's good.
And I don't know, I make a lot
more money delivering pizzas
With tips and stuff
than I used to make
Over at the alamo freeze.
- So basically you stayed
in dillon 'cause of jules.
- Yeah.
- Now she's--she's applying
to colleges and stuff, right?
And I knew that was
gonna happen.
Obviously, I knew that she
was gonna go to college,
But I guess
I just never realized
The fact that all the colleges
she was gonna be applying to
Were, like, on the other side
of the country.
And now, you know, I started
just getting mad at her
For no reason.
It's like I resent it,
But she never asked me
to stay here, you know?
That was my decision.
I decided to do that.
I decided that.
Well...
Texas forever, right?
- Yes.
Absolutely.
Texas forever, 7.
- I don't know
why he changed his mind.
- Well, I think it's gonna be
a great pep rally.
- We'll see about that.
Watch your step.
- Hey, if it's not great,
You still get
to come home with us.
- There's always that.
- There's always that, right?
Go ahead.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
Where's your brisket?
- Oh, um,
I don't eat meat.
- Oh, come on, let me
go get you a plate.
- It's okay.
Um, I actually
kind of wanted to talk to you
About the other night.
Um, I just wanted
to let you know
That I'm not gonna
tell anybody or anything.
- Tell anybody what?
- I want to thank everybody
for coming out...
- Uh, it's okay.
- To east dillon's
first pep rally of the year.
[cheers and applause]
I'd like to introduce
One of texas' great
high school football teams--
1983 state champions
from east dillon high...
[cheers and applause]
And what they brought home
to this school
26 years ago.
[applause]
Come on up, guys.
- Yeah!
- Let us pray.
Lord...
We are gathered here today
For a reason.
We ask you, lord,
what is a group of lions?
It is a pride.
And we stand before you
today, lord,
Your pride.
We need pride in this world.
[man shouts]
- And what do we have here?
I said, "what do we have here?"
All: Pride!
[cheers and applause]
We are the lions.
And we stand together.
Who are we?
All: Lions!
- Who are we?
[cheers and applause]
- This--yeah.
Put this one there.
I never really wash this.
It's kind of weird.
I just--
♪ ♪
- We're not dating, right?
- Definitely not.
No.
♪ ♪
- Lorraine, I'm tossing
this half-and-half.
- Well, all right, but we're
gonna have to go to the store.
I cannot drink coffee
without cream.
- Well, me neither.
- Oh, I remember how you took
your coffee.
[knock at door]
Well, who could that be?
[scoffs]
you failed me.
♪ ♪
- Mrs. Saracen?
- Thanks.
♪ ♪
Hey, uh, look.
I'm sorry, you know, that
I just stopped by, but I--
What's the matter?
- Have you talked to your mom?
- Why?
Is it--is--is something wrong
with grandma?
- I'm sorry.
- What's the matter?
Julie.
- It's your dad.
He was killed.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.