How about we go somewhere and talk
about anything but football?
That sounds good.
You're some cowboy who wanders around.
I like to think there's more in you.
Sometimes, it just takes the right
woman to make it more in your heart.
So look, about 30 days time.
And get you a 20% profit
on your investment.
It's flipping houses.
I saw it on TV, it works.
- I'm in.
- You're in.
Daddy bought a house today. I'm gonna
fix it up and I'm gonna sell it.
And you and me, and your mommy,
can live together.
We'll turn it over in about 30 days,
make a lot of money, and it'll get us...
I'm moving back East,
with my parents.
Freshmen, listen up!
We all seniors want to thank you
for coming out of your busy schedules
to meet us here tonight.
We've all been here.
And you guys will look back
at what you're about to do
and understand
that there's a strong purpose to it.
Time has come for a Panther ritual.
Drummer, please.
The naked mile.
- I thought it was a myth.
- What'd you say, Charles?
- I said I thought it was a myth.
- I wish it was
so I don't have to see your fat ass
running naked.
You heard me, ladies.
Let's go!
Strip down, strip down!
Take your shoes off,
strip down everybody.
Take it all off.
- Take it all off.
- Listen up! Tell 'em Jamarcus.
Look, you all know the rules.
You're going to the water tower
and back.
No shame, no fame, baby.
McCoy, they're all running
to the water tower and back,
but you, superstar,
you're running to the field house.
I mean, wh...
Why do I have to run to the field house?
'Cause you're the quarterback, bro.
You gotta go the extra mile, dude.
Get your ass over there.
Go, get out of here.
Go!
Come on, you can do it!
Come here.
Where are your pants?
Tonight was the...
Naked mile.
- Yeah.
- You fell for the naked mile.
Take it to your team there and put some
clothes on, I'll give you a ride home.
Please don't tell my dad, okay?
Son, I wouldn't dream of it.
Okay.
You know, mum's got a light foot?
So make sure that you howl at her
if she starts going too fast.
I don't drive that fast.
- Yeah, you do.
- No, I don't.
Whenever I'm in the car with you, I feel
like I'm in a chase out of a Bond movie.
Your daddy doesn't have any tickets.
He never got one speeding ticket.
Unlike some people around here.
I gotta go.
I wanna get as far as possible
while he's still kind of calm.
I love you, buddy, okay?
Wish I knew how to stay here.
That's pretty easy.
You just park the car,
and stay.
When you get to your parents' house,
you just tell your mom that...
he gets his good looks
and perfect manners from me.
While you're heading East,
I'll be fixing up this Garrity house.
We're gonna turn a major profit.
And have a nice cushion, so...
you and Noah and I
can get a house or...
just something...
Just be together.
We'll see what happens, okay?
Goodbye, honey.
I'm scared.
Don't be, don't be.
- It's gonna be okay.
- Don't be scared, okay?
It's gonna be great, okay?
You know, your parents... You're
gonna have a great time with them.
Be safe, okay?
I love you.
I love you both, okay?
Call me.
Subtitles: Team Panthers
With
benj!, DarKsh, GillesSilb, Ju,
loky34, ouazo, tactactac, Teardrop
Episode 3x06
It Ain't Easy Being J.D. McCoy
- Thank you for making coffee, honey.
- You're welcome. Coming at you.
I'm excited about the dance
on Saturday night.
You're gonna be
my hot husband date.
The principal has the obligation
of being the chaperon at the dance.
And you as my husband have
an obligation of being my date.
I'm not gonna be able to do that
cause I've got other things planned.
No, honey, come on.
Of course, you're gonna do it.
- Would you get here for a sec?
- Honey, and I need you to chaperon,
and be my date most importantly.
- Julie's coming.
- I'm not going.
Of course, you're going.
Honey, it's your dance.
- Not going.
- What do you mean? No, you're not.
Y'all, come on, seriously...
I would like to propose a toast.
- Oh, really?
- To QB 1...
of the Dillon Panthers.
Cheers, pal.
Congratulations.
No cheers?
No, I just save the toast
for after the game.
It's Westerby.
You're gonna smoke 'em.
Here's an important question. Is there
any cheerleader who thinks you're cute?
- Oh yeah.
- Really?
There's two actually.
I have not actually proposed to them.
We can talk about that now.
You can only propose one at the time.
J.D. isn't getting serious about
any girls right now, he's too busy.
No, honey, that was a joke.
Let me tell you something.
I know that you've experienced
a lot of pressure recently,
but you have worked hard,
and you have shown everyone
what you are made of.
And for that,
I am very very proud.
- Thanks, dad.
- You're very welcome.
I want to give Coach Eric Taylor
a piece of my mind.
You are QB1!
You won State!
I did.
I did win State.
He must've lost his natural mind.
To think some old boy
could step into your shoes.
- What's his name, again?
- McCoy.
You're all on your way to school,
when you get there, all you do...
you just go in,
you talk to the coach, you tell him.
You've made a big mistake, all right?
It's all right, you can fix it.
You wait until I deal with it.
I gotta get going okay?
I'll get you during lunch.
He thinks he knows football!
- ... to make some money.
- OK.
Timmy...
Glad you could join us, today. How did
you get outta school? What's your alibi?
I just told them I'm pregnant.
So I just need a few days to relax.
Let's get to work.
Let's start with this, here, work list.
I told you miss bossy pants
had a work list.
- Is there a problem with the work list?
- No you get organized, it's all good.
Why do we have to do
everything upstairs?
- We'll forget you just said that...
- Oh, yeah...
I was thinking, maybe the first place
we could start would be the bathroom.
But we need a sledgehammer to...
To start working on it.
If you can pick it up, it'd be awesome.
- Whatever.
- I was just asking.
- What the hell is wrong with him?
- You're bossy.
- I'm not bossy.
- That was abrupt.
What is this song about?
Really, this song is about
a lot of stuff so...
- it's hard for me to explain that.
- It's really slow.
It's slow for a reason.
Not all songs can be...
as fast as most of our songs.
Listen...
Jimmy, I hate to be
this brutally honest with you
but you're really not all that good.
I don't think it's all the drummer.
I don't see anyone else with any
sort of... Where are you going?
I am gonna leave.
I don't need this.
- I will see you tomorrow, Jimmy.
- That's it, Landry. I quit.
That's fun.
I could care less, Caster.
You know, this sucks.
I really thought we were gonna
be bigger than Crimson Thorn.
Okay...
Well, Caster, for you information,
I chose the name Crucifictorious,
so therefore, I keep it, and also
I will see you tomorrow, Jimmy
cause I know you're gonna be right back.
No, you won't cause I'm out of here.
What did you say?
I'll see you tomorrow.
So I was thinking, how about
you take off a little early tonight...
and come by the pool hall.
I would love to, but I can't.
Really, why? You got
a date with boyfriend number two?
Yeah, how d'you know?
No, I've got to make decorations
for the school dance and...
I have to work overtime
for this entire month.
I don't know, college applications
are like 150 a piece so...
I'm lucky if I get three.
How about...
I make things
a little easier on you?
What are you doing?
Just making sure my girl gets to go
to a college she wants to go to.
- No, I can't, I cannot do that.
- Yes, you can. Please.
Please...
Do you...
- Do you wanna go to this dance with me?
- No, I don't.
I don't wanna go to the dance
but I'd love to pick you up
from the high school dance, though.
Alright.
- OK.
- Alright, babe.
- Gimme a call when you're out.
- Talk to you later.
Big tipper?
Hey, it's for my
college applications.
Sure that's all it's for?
All that and my, you know...
high-class sucker job.
Open, open!
Set blue 8!
Blue 8!
Hut!
There he is!
- Set your feet, J.D!
- Come on, naked gun, you're good...
QB blind.
Settle down into it.
Settle down, man.
He's right there.
- You gotta be naked next time.
- Watch these steps.
Come on, naked gun.
- Sit down.
- Yes, sir.
Naked mile.
That's a Panther tradition, Coach.
Big game coming up. Team needs to be
focused. Team captain should know that.
J.D. is a young quarterback. He needs
to know this team is behind him.
We are, Sir.
Especially on the field.
- Does he know that?
- Yes.
He does, huh?
You know damn well
this team respects you.
You accept this kid,
this team is gonna accept him.
I need that.
I need you to fix it.
I don't understand.
What do you mean, fix it?
You're a senior...
You're not gonna be wearing
the Panther uniform much longer.
I want you to think about that.
Think about everything it means.
I'm asking for your help.
- You understand what I'm saying?
- Yes, Sir.
Good.
Get in!
I, huh, no...
I was just gonna get on the bus.
Get in the truck, 1-2.
You've uh...
You've had a tour of Dillon, right?
Well, not my Dillon, my friend.
Let's go.
Where exactly are we going?
It's on your right.
Look right.
You need to know this spot, OK?
It's called The Landing Strip.
My sister in law,
my brother's future wife...
works there and probably will
for the rest of her life.
You are not ready for that, son.
And when you are, you will know.
Up here, on our right,
we have Fran's hamburgers. 24/7.
Best hamburgers, best fans
in all of high school football.
The real rally girls.
And I hope you know what that means.
Good times, man. I can tell
what kind of support we get.
Alright, we got Smittie's dive bar.
They know me as Toby,
two times Iraq veteran.
If you ever wanna get away from
anything, anyone, you will go in there.
You hear me? Smittie's.
Best bar on the planet.
- Lisa lives down this road.
- Who?
You'll know, you'll know.
She's good times...
This is the place, uh?
Alright, man. It was fun.
Coach put you up to this?
- Really?
- Good night, man.
Look at you, my beautiful baby!
- I think this might be the one.
- You do, honey?
I had no idea I would get
so emotional.
You look just like an angel.
Tyra! Doesn't she look
just like an angel from heaven?
Mindy, I love you,
but I can see your crack.
It's just a smidge.
It's just a little bit, there.
- It's very tasteful, it's subtle.
- Yes, it's subtle.
I could've used your support, today.
You could've left the paperwork at home.
- What are you doing? What is this?
- It's my application.
For the University of San Francisco?
How are you gonna hang on to that cowboy
if you're out there in California?
I don't wanna hang on to anybody.
That's mistake #1.
You know,
Cash is very supportive of me.
I know. They are all so supportive.
And then try to actually do something...
He gave me money
for my application fees.
- He did?
- Yeah.
Well, this is a very good man.
They don't normally like
to take care of you just like that.
You hang on to that man.
I'm telling you!
And I'm speaking from experience.
You know it just occurs to me, if you're
dropping a truckload on a dress,
doesn't someone
give you some champagne around here?
Anybody?
- Don't do that.
- You're not getting a burrito.
That's disgusting, dad. Do you realize
there's not even real food in it?
It's all like, preservatives and...
Hey, how are you doing?
Well, Coach Eric Taylor.
- How are you, ma'am? Good to see you.
- I'm not that good. You wanna know why?
I'd be doing the heck
of a lot better
if I thought you were gonna do
the right thing
and make my grandson
starting quarterback like he should be.
- Grandma, it's OK.
- No, hush!
- Hush, he needs to hear this.
- Yes, ma'am.
This boy has played
his heart out for you.
I know it's difficult...
We should just let 'em talk, maybe.
Awkward!
A little bit.
Do you think we could go grab
a cup of coffee or something?
We can get lunch if you want.
She'll talk about this all day.
So I take it she's taking
your demotion pretty hard.
Demotion?
That's a little harsh.
What do you want me to say?
OK, I guess demotion is appropriate.
- How's practice been?
- It's good.
It's good.
I'm on the bench a lot now, but...
I just get to talk to Landry more
cause he's always there.
- Alright, you think about it.
- I will.
It's hard to be mad at you,
Coach Taylor.
- It's good to see you.
- You'll be thinking about what I said.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Alright, bye-bye.
Hey guys, good news, I got the...
- Did you get the permits?
- What the hell is going on, here?
I'm just improvising, man.
Just look, look. Bigger, uh?
- Man, that is the Cadillac of toilets.
- Yeah, check it out.
- Bidet.
- Bidet?
- Right here. Bidet.
- Cleans your butt.
$1,700?
You spent $1,700 on a toilet?
- You gotta spend money to make money.
- We're on a budget, Billy!
And guess what? If we exceed that budget
we're not making any money.
So you just wheel this back out
to the truck, cause that's going back.
That's going back now.
And who decided to bust out this wall?
Maybe it was mine.
It was a load-bearing wall.
I'd have been better off getting
my grandma and her bridge club
to finish this house.
Were you even looking
at the work list, anymore?
I got your work list right here.
In fact, why don't we post it on
this wall, so that nobody will miss it?
Good idea, Billy. I like that.
Don't talk to me like I'm a freaking
moron, I've worked construction before.
Son of a bitch...
- Does that hurt?
- Yeah, it hurts.
Shut the hell up
and get me some pliers!
No, Mindy. I can't come.
Cause I gotta do these damn decorations.
I'll probably be doing them all night.
Will you get me some dessert?
You know, like,
chocolate fudge pie thing that I love...
Thank you.
Bye, love you, sis.
... first game
where freshman J.D. McCoy
will start as QB 1.
Hi, can I talk to Cash?
Cash doesn't live here.
I heard he's been
hanging around a lot.
Well, you heard wrong.
Seriously, he's not here.
He doesn't live here.
Well, when you see him,
could you tell him that I came by?
- I don't know what this is all about...
- Really? What a surprise.
The pretty girl's out of a loop.
When you see Cash, just tell him
that he owes Ali and Tucker
$1,600 in child support, okay?
Can you do that for me?
It's gonna do it, folks.
With only 25 seconds left
in this contest,
all the Panthers have to do
is take a knee, and they
can put this one in the books.
Blue 8!
Hut!
And that's official.
This game is over.
Young gun J.D. McCoy's debut
in the Westerby game
unbelievable, folks.
This kid has lit it up
like a Whitesnake concert.
Another check in the win column for
Coach Taylor and the Dillon Panthers.
There you go!
Big W tonight, gentlemen.
We earned it.
Damn right, I'm gonna be there.
Guess who else's gonna be there tonight.
- Who?
- This cab right here.
1-2, great game, tonight.
We're gonna go celebrate. We're gonna
create some memories, alright, 1-2?
- No regrets.
- There you go, naked gun.
Where is my boy? There he is.
That's what I'm talking about!
That is what I'm talking about,
young man.
That was one hell of a ball game.
Way to go.
I'm so proud of you.
Riggins, what the hell?
You were bringing the heat, boy!
You were on fire!
Way to go, boy!
- Excellent game!
- Yeah, he played great.
Great job, guys, thank you so much.
Great game!
We're gonna go celebrate
with your mom, over at Applebee's.
Come on, now. We're gonna celebrate.
- Come on! Here we go.
- Okay.
Alright...
Alright, boys, see you later.
Great game, great game.
I told you, man.
Daddy got him on a leash.
Good practice.
Hey, good video session.
You look pretty sweet, you know?
I came to see about...
just to check in with you about tonight.
Tonight?
The dance. The Dillon dance.
You totally forgot.
- The Dillon dance...
- Where is it?
Come on. It's in Dillon.
I just thought it'd be fun to go.
You know, do one together
before it's all over.
Are you gonna wear something
as cute as this, tonight?
- Maybe...
- Then I'm going, with bells on.
We're gonna have the time of our lives
at the dance, tonight.
- I love dances.
- I do, too.
Alright, this looks good.
I'll take this whole palette.
I need it delivered to 213, Pinehurst
by tomorrow morning or noon.
- You got it.
- OK. Thank you. I appreciate it.
- Jason, how are you doing?
- Good, Coach. How are you doing?
- How are you?
- Doing well. What brings you down here?
I got a honey-do list.
I see you got one, too.
No, not quite.
The Riggins brothers and I have bought
Buddy Garrity's house, and so we're...
fixing it up, so I had to come
and pick a bunch of stuff up.
You what?
Riggins brothers and I have bought
the Garrity's house to flip it.
- Tim and Billy?
- Yeah, and Herc.
We all got together,
and put the money in.
We got a good deal on the house.
And we're flipping it.
- Buddy Garrity's house?
- Yeah.
You know, we're upgrading it,
making it a lot more upscale
and we gonna sell it. I know it sounds
crazy with the market nowadays...
We got a good team, working 24 hours
a day. We gonna make this thing happen.
And... I'm excited.
Haven't had any snags
or anything, so...
That's great.
I gotta get going.
It's good to see you. You'd stop
by the house, check it out.
- I'll do that. I'm sure it is.
- It's looking real nice.
Alright, Coach.
You just put it right here.
I'll just take the whole thing.
I am a stupid, stupid girl.
You are not a stupid girl.
He's a stupid guy for thinking he can
get away with something like that.
You know what the worst part is?
I liked him.
I even think
I was falling in love with him.
Maybe there is some sort of
random explanation
and it's not really
as bad as it seems.
Julie, a woman came to my house
telling me that my boyfriend
owes her child support.
How much worse could that get?
She could be his sister.
I mean, theoretically,
that'd be a lot worse.
Something Landry would say.
Tyra, 3 o'clock.
Turn around.
- How's my lady?
- Don't touch me.
You need to leave now.
You need to leave, right now.
Slow down, hold on.
What's going on?
Just calm down...
What am I talking about?
How about some woman
comes to my house with a baby
that she says is yours.
My house!
- Tyra, look...
- No, you know what? Don't touch me.
I want you to leave, right now.
- You're not gonna let me explain.
- No. You know, here...
Why don't you give this to her,
for child support, OK?
Go!
This is good!
You got everything
that you need for...
- Yeah, it's good.
- It's good? It's gonna be fun, man.
Thanks for coming back and everything.
I appreciate it.
Alright, man. Let's do this!
Just follow him and me,
just relax, and...
Let's see what you got!
Alright, ready?
Thank you for coming. It's just not...
It didn't feel right.
- Did you have fun?
- Yeah, man.
Hi, guys. My name is Devin.
I'm in freshman course
right now, and...
I really just wanna expand more,
like, music-wise.
So I decided I'd come
and audition today.
Well, we appreciate
you coming up, Devin.
So, I'm just gonna
plug in real quick.
Alright, let's just give it a shot
and see what happens...
That was...
- That was pretty fun.
- good.
I mean she's in, right?
- I think so. That was good.
- I think so.
I think you're in, congratulations.
I think we're all set on vocals,
pretty much.
But we'll see what happens.
I'd like to be in this band, so...
That'd be great.
Great!
Hey, Coach!
Come on in.
It's work in progress,
as you can see.
Yeah, I can see it is.
We progressed so far, as to
take a perfectly livable house
and turn it into a place
that if a bum saw, would say, "Thanks,
I'll go back to sleep under the bridge."
So, we're, you know...
getting there.
My dad used to say,
"It always looks bad
before it gets better."
I don't think
it's gonna get better, Coach.
I think I've made
the biggest mistake in my life.
The mother of my child and my son are
in a car on their way up to New Jersey.
I decided that the smartest thing to do
would be to buy a house and flip it
with the Riggins brothers and Herc.
Cause I didn't know what else to do.
I love them so much,
I just don't wanna be
a debt beat dad,
I just wanna be able to provide a
little bit, some security, something...
anything for them and...
Slow down. Slow down a second.
Wait a second.
First of all, you're not gonna be a debt
beat dad. You need to calm down, here.
Look, you're 20 years old.
You're not supposed to know what you'll
do with the rest of your life, yet.
You're doing what you think is best.
You're following through it.
That's what you should be doing.
You had a plan, you're executing it.
What's wrong with that?
But you gotta give it a chance,
give yourself time.
You can't beat yourself up
cause you're taking chances on things.
But don't start giving up on what
you set forward to do in the beginning
cause that's gonna get you nowhere.
I promise you that.
I borrowed Landry's car.
And you drove it over here...
Do you wanna go to the lake?
Have you ever been
fired from anything?
One time, when I was 12 years old,
I babysat for the Griffins
and I never got asked back.
- You still carry that with you, huh?
- I still carry that until this day.
That's rough.
I don't know, I mean...
I never thought I was gonna play
professional football...
but I kinda thought it might help pay
for college or something, and now...
I'm a senior
and I'm sitting on the bench.
Bottom line, it just...
sucks.
Yeah, it does.
But you know what's kinda cool?
It's the first Saturday I can remember
waking up and not having to think about
everything I did wrong the night before.
- Well, see, that's a good thing.
- Yeah, that's a good thing.
- So, do you feel prepared?
- Prepared for what?
Prepared to get
your but whipped by a girl.
That was rude.
I'm gonna get you!
Good job.
Hey, honey!
What is it about rice crispy treats
that they're just so darn good?
Let me tell you something.
You've been doing a great job.
- It's quite an achievement.
- Honey...
I'm serious.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you.
Of course I'm thinking
my husband is in the process
of blowing me off which is not
making me very happy.
These men! It's typical, right?
Well, I don't know. In his case,
he usually has something else come up
- but I thought he'd be here tonight.
- I broke up with Cash.
- Sorry, honey.
- No you're not.
Yeah, I am.
What I didn't want to happen
was for you to get hurt.
Well...
I always have this, right?
I'm just gonna go home.
Alright, now just keep in mind
as you're reading these
that these are all
works in progress.
Very rough...
Some of them aren't even complete.
I know what a work
in progress means, so...
I'll just read it.
- Do you dance, or anything?
- I took ballet when I was little.
Me too! That's...
- I was joking.
- I thought you were joking.
Can I say something about these songs,
just one musician to another?
Of course.
Well, they all kinda feel like
they're one song about one girl.
I mean, if you think about it,
that's basically the majority
of all rock music is about: a girl.
But I just...
I think our band could be really great.
- So do I.
- I just kinda think
that you need
to get over this girl, then.
Is she here?
Nope, she's not.
Footloose, here we come.
I love this kind of style.
- Yeah?
- It just feels right, you know?
Stop it.
There he is.
You look good, tonight.
- What are you doing here?
- My mom...
- thought it'd be good to have some fun.
- Did she?
And, are you having fun?
Not really.
- You know Lyla.
- Hi, J.D.
How is it going?
You gonna cut a rug, or what?
- Tell me you don't wanna go get a beer.
- I don't wanna go and get a beer.
No, I'm serious.
Let's go somewhere fun.
- It is fun.
- No, it's not fun.
You know what type of people have fun
at these dances? The type of people that
when they grow up, they'll look back
and have regrets. We don't want to.
Right, right?
- So you're gonna come for a beer.
- I don't drink.
- What do you mean?
- There you go, he doesn't drink.
My dad gave me an article,
it disrupts protein and senses...
- What does?
- Alcohol.
Fine, who doesn't need a driver?
We're gonna get wasted.
I can't drive.
I don't have a license.
I only have a learner's permit.
- He doesn't have a license.
- You're coming anyways.
Let's go. Hey, just believe me,
trust me on this one.
Just this one time, we're going.
I got... We're gonna have some memories.
- All right? Come on.
- Pants-off.
Alright, no regrets, let's do this.
Safety first.
Let me know when you and your date
need a ride home.
Is she mad at me?
Yes, McCoy.
- Let's just have some fun.
- Okay.
Memories, tonight.
Nice tie!
Tyra, it's me. Open up.
Tyra, I know you're home.
Open up.
Go to hell, Cash!
Tyra, please,
just let me talk to you.
How about you go talk to your girlfriend
or your wife or whoever?
She's not my girlfriend or my wife!
If you let me explain,
you'd know that.
Please.
Tyra, come on.
What part of "Go to hell"
don't you understand?
- Just hear me out, please.
- Why?
Because I think
I deserve at least that much.
As far as I'm concerned,
you don't deserve anything right now.
Well, I'm sure
you don't think I do.
The girl that came here, her name
is Ally Darcy. And that's not my baby.
I did hook up with her.
One time, five years ago.
And it's not gonna
happen again, because...
you met her, she's crazy!
I shouldn't say that,
but she is crazy.
After we hooked up, she started
showing up at my work, making a scene,
so, I just left town.
I was in Wyoming doing
the rodeo circuit, and now, I'm back.
And who comes knocking on my door
a couple months ago?
Ally Darcy, with a two-year old.
I hooked up with her five years ago.
There's no way that kid is mine.
And if it was, I wouldn't be
lying to you, telling you it wasn't,
cause I'd step up.
I'm telling you the truth. I have
no reason to be dishonest with you.
That's it?
Yes, that's it.
That's all of it.
She made me feel so awful.
I'm sure she did,
I'm sorry about that.
- You're not lying to me?
- No, I'm not lying to you.
I would never lie to you.
I'm sorry.
Do you forgive me?
Maybe.
- How many girlfriends do you have?
- Just the one, McCoy.
God, she's so pretty!
Yes, she's pretty special, man.
Alright, you're on your own
for a bit.
No, wait!
What am I supposed to do?
If you get in trouble,
Act like you're looking for someone.
Secondly,
relax!
Have some fun, laugh!
There's a lot of pretty girls.
Have some fun, alright?
I'm gonna steal her for a minute,
if that's cool?
She doesn't have the choice, sorry.
There he is, naked gun!
Ladies and gentlemen,
J.D. McCoy cutest buns in Dillon.
Are you getting ready
to run another midnight run?
No, no, I did my work-out
early this morning.
J.D., man,
help yourself, bro.
- Y'all didn't know?
- What?
This guy's body is a temple.
He doesn't drink sodas,
doesn't eat candy,
definitely can't drink beer.
Your dad runs
a tight little ship, doesn't he?
Have a drink, man!
This is a party.
- A beer sounds pretty good right now.
- Move around, baby.
To J.D. McCoy!
Well, look at that!
Come on, let's go.
You're like the prettiest girl
I've ever seen in my life.
You and Riggins are gonna make
some cute babies.
You're like the coolest, man.
You're like the last American dude.
He doesn't listen to my dad,
he doesn't listen to your dad,
you don't listen anybody's dad.
That's pretty... quite odd, man!
I thought you were Mr. Stackhouse.
What are you doing here?
Do you know how late it is?
Where have you been?
I've been getting dressed,
shaving...
Don't just come in here
and try to slow down smalls with me.
- Why do have paint in your hair?
- I don't have... Don't worry why.
No, I do worry.
You know, you stood me up.
- I could fire you.
- No, you can't fire me.
You can't fire me, you'd have to go
through the board supervisor, boosters,
This, that, and everything else...
- It'd be a lot of trouble, wouldn't it?
- How was your day?
How was my day? I've been sitting here
at this dance with no date.
He's here.
Veggie hot dogs are amazing!
No.
I'm just gonna stick to...
You know,
good old fashioned, all American...
hot dog!
Do you realize what you're eating?
It's like...
cow eyes,
and like a pig intestines.
And you know what?
That tastes good.
Real good.
I think food is better outside.
I would have to agree with that.
But I'm really stuffed,
then we should probably get going.
Well...
we probably should.
That is the cutest baby
I've ever seen.
- She's adorable.
- She is such a stylish...
Excuse us for a second,
we'll be right back.
Coach?
Hey, how you doin'?
- Hey, how are you?
- Good, good.
Listen, J.D. has got something
he needs to share with you.
I got... really drunk, last night.
I had a lot of alcohol,
I just wanna say I'm sorry.
A lot of alcohol?
He came home... drunk.
Not so much of one sip of wine
his entire life. 3 weeks before
the playoffs, he comes home...
drunk. Now, he knows
that he has disappointed his father,
he has let down his coach, his team,
and I felt that it was imperative
that he'd come to you
and apologize personally.
- I hope you understand.
- Understood.
Anything else he's done
that I should be aware of?
No, he works hard.
Good, we got to keep our star
in a straighten arrow.
- Thank you so much.
- Excuse me, all.
- Don't mean to interrupt.
- Not at all.
Seemed a little more serious for church
but she had to see her daddy.
She said,
"I need my daddy immediately."
Thank you, Coach. We'll talk soon.
Nice to see you.
- Okay y'all, happy Sunday.
- All right, bye.
- Take care, now.
- Okay, bye bye.
- I told you to say that.
- We gotta go get that stove later.
So, I guess when you finish with that,
we'll go ahead and...
- Soon.
- Who's that?
Hey, Erin.
Did you guys make it there yet?
No, we still got another day to go.
I just pulled over
to give him a little break.
I don't even know where we are
right now. Some park, somewhere.
I miss you guys, like crazy.
Well, we love you too,
we miss you too.
Put the little man on.
- Am I really that boring to talk to?
- No.
I just don't want my son
to forget my voice.
He won't... forget your voice.
Here he is.
- Come on. It's your daddy.
- Hey Noah, hey my man.
It's your daddy.
Hey, I miss you.
Well, I love you.
I love you very much.
And I wish I'd be there
with you, but...
I thought maybe
we could sing together, though,
in my duet
So, I'm gonna start singing,
you just join whenever you want, okay?
There's a hole in my bucket,
dear Liza,
dear Liza.
There's a hole in my bucket,
dear Liza, there's a hole.
Now, it's your turn.
You don't wanna do the girl part today?
Okay, I'll do it.
Then fix it, dear Henry,
dear henry, dear Henry.
dear Henry, fix it.
I love you, buddy.
I'll talk to you soon, okay?
- Tami, what did you do?
- Why?
Because if I don't have my fullback
on Friday night, I'm screwed.
Therefore, I'm telling you,
I should've been part of that process.
Every time a decision is to be made,
you wave that baby around like a gun.
Erin is up in New England with my kid.
Her parents are putting him in daycare
which I can't afford.
How am I supposed to compete with that?
You're leaving?