- I got into Vanderbilt.
- Congratulations, baby.
Not that I'll be able to go.
Lyla, baby!
Tim, I need to get Lyla back.
I don't know what to do next.
You gotta give her some more time,
Mr. Garrity, that's what I think.
The Panthers of Dillon Texas
are going to State!
- Hey, honey.
- Huh?
Look.
- Stay here.
- No, I'm coming with you.
I don't care what you do, Dad.
Screw you!
You don't talk to me like that!
Joe, stop it!
He hit him.
He hit my baby.
And here are your soon-to-be
State champions...
the Dillon Panthers.
All right, I wanna hear you...
State, State!
The problem is, Clint, is that
I just spent the entire weekend
giving support to J.D. and to Katie.
And now, for me to have to turn around
and call Child Protective Services...
You have a mandate, you're the boss.
Your husband does too, by the way.
I honestly just don't think
I can do it, Clint.
Tami, you don't know anything.
You think this might've been
the first time it happened,
but you don't really know that.
All you know is that you
and a lot of other people
witnessed this guy beating up his kid.
That's child abuse!
I know, I know...
It's not like we have a choice.
No, I don't think
we do have a choice.
Do you want me to do it?
No, I should do it, I'll do it.
I'll do it.
3x12: UNDERDOGS
Subtitles: Team Panthers
With the participation of:
benj!, Collioure, DarKsh, GillesSilb,
Ju, ouazo, tactactac, Teardrop, TVnut
This is it, folks.
Three days till football Christmas.
Yes, it's no secret
that many of us are worried
that the Panthers are about
to get their stockings stuffed.
South Texas is the best high school
football team I have ever seen, period.
Best ever?
What about the '81 Panthers?
Even the '81 Panthers would have
a tough time beating this squad.
I'm just saying, Coach Taylor's gonna
need help from above to beat these boys.
Billy! Get out,
I'm going to the bathroom.
- I've really gotta pee, so how long...
- Close the door, I'm in the bathroom!
Fine!
I'll just piss in the sink!
Tim, wake your ass up!
Seriously, man.
I got something to show you.
This is big.
Billy, we have school!
Well, you're gonna have
to skip school, Lyla!
Tim, get your ass up!
This is your future.
Stop!
- Love it.
- No, seriously, check it out.
What do you think?
- It's beautiful, right?
- It's perfect, man.
It was either this or Quiznos,
- but I couldn't pass this up.
- No-brainer.
Yeah, I'm gonna name it
Riggins' Rigs.
- It's gonna be awesome.
- That's perfect, dude.
Put a hydraulic lift there,
where that car is...
a little refrigerator over
in the corner, stocked full of beer...
A must-have.
24/7, fixing cars, drinking beer.
I mean, what more do you need?
It's awesome, man.
It's awesome.
Don't expect them to be confused
by a spread offense.
They faced four of 'em this year, and
none of 'em scored more than 10 points.
Hahn, you gotta give
our quarterback time to throw.
That's gonna be key in this game.
Are you seeing that secondary?
I do.
Coach, you're not
worried about them?
Can't afford to be worried.
Doctor's orders, bad for the ticker.
They're big, they're fast.
There's no doubt about it.
We've never seen anyone like them
yet this year, but you know what?
That's the one thing... They've never
faced us before either, gentlemen.
Keep that in mind.
It's gonna be a good fight.
It'll be a damned good fight.
Look at that!
I'm so impressed
with this portfolio!
- Thanks.
- Oh, my Lord.
It's kinda crazy thinking I might
actually go to school in Chicago.
I know, but you could...
I think you could really do it.
The portfolio's the most important
thing, and you've got great grades...
I think your teachers can give you
great recommendations.
I still gotta get in, though.
So...
- What d'you think, Jules?
- I think it seems like a really...
bright possibility,
and it's in a real city,
so you have coffee houses
and museums and...
culture.
- That's right, that's for sure.
- Yeah, more than here.
- So, are you done?
- Hold on one second.
OK, I believe I am finished.
- Come sit down, we'll go over this.
- Wait . OK, well? What do you think?
What do you think?
How do you feel that colleges
are going to respond to this essay?
You hate it.
No, you hate it.
No, I didn't say
that I hated this paper at all.
I did not say that I hate...
OK.
Tyra, I really do hate this paper.
It's because there were a lot of...
there were a lot of...
- a lot of things that weren't great.
- Well, OK, like what?
Would you explain to me why
every paragrah has a tie back
into Applebee's, and why...
'Cause I use it as a metaphor.
It works.
"Sometimes it gets busy.
You just have to roll with the punches."
"Just like in life..."
It reads like a five-page
needlepoint... pillow.
And it...
And it's painful.
That's not fair,
it's due this weekend.
Well, you just have to dig
a little bit deeper, and... fastly.
- I hate you.
- All right.
Joe McCoy?
I'm Mark Enderland, this is Jodie Russi.
We're with Child Protective Services.
We'd like to speak
with you and your family.
I want a lawyer present
for this questioning.
You can't divide us up like this
- and play good cop/bad cop.
- Joe, Joe, calm down.
Has your dad ever hit you before?
Are you afraid of your father now?
No, I'm not. I just want
this whole thing to be over.
Has he ever hit your mother?
Are you guys gonna take him away
from me or something?
OK, no.
This is outrageous.
- What country do you think we live in?
- Mr. McCoy, I need you to calm down.
If you don't cooperate with us,
we can take your boy out of your custody
- pending our investigation.
- Oh, my God. Joe, just shut up!
Please!
The coolest thing is, of all the places
to study art, I mean...
Art Institute of Chicago, they got like
one of the biggest Van Gogh collections
in the country, and...
there's just art everywhere in the city,
like they got Picasso
sculptures just in the...
in the streets and stuff.
And the thing is, Mrs. Taylor seems
to think I can actually get in there.
Of course you can.
Matt, I told you, you're talented.
The only thing is, even if I get in,
I don't know how I'm gonna pay for it.
Well, I've got a little saved.
And I can send you
some money each month, and...
you know,
people always need haircuts.
Where are you sending money?
Where are you thinking about going,
honey? What's that?
There's just this art school
at the Art Institute of Chicago.
Mrs. Taylor, Coach's wife,
she thinks I got a really good chance
of getting in there, maybe.
Chicago?
Chicago, that's...
That's way up in Illinois!
That's too far, honey, I mean...
- What would I do here without you?
- I don't know.
Well, Lorraine, you know,
I still could stay here,
- I'd like to do that.
- I think I made it perfectly clear.
I'm not living with you.
Grandma, it was just an idea.
And Matthew, what's this nonsense
about art school?
In't that just gonna waste
a whole bunch of money?
- Yeah, I mean, it was just an idea.
- Wan't a good idea, was it?
Yeah, you're probably right.
- Get in!
- Go, go!
Push that ball!
Get back in the box, let's go.
Let's run it again.
- Come on, guys, let's get in there.
- This offense plays on Saturday
like we're practicing today,
we will win State, gentlemen!
Now, coaches and I wanna
recognize someone today
not just for what they do on the field,
but what they do off the field...
which is what we expect
from the players out here.
Where's Lance?
- 8-5! 8-5!
- Step in the middle, son.
Lance deserved himself
a spot on special teams, gentlemen!
- In the State?
- Do us proud.
Let's go, Coach,
you wanna bring 'em in, let's go!
Break it out!
Let's break it in!
- So what do you think, Coach Spivey?
- We need to spike their Gatorade.
Kids are huge!
We gotta shut down their penetration,
we'll get killed on that one.
Coach!
Was that you that called
those people from CPS?
Give us a minute.
Yes, it was.
Why?
Because it's the law, that's why.
Why would you call the cops
on my dad?
- You think I don't know you hate him?
- Son, it's not a matter of that.
You didn't have to do anything, you...
You wanted to!
I'm sorry you think that.
That's not the case, though.
Sorry?
That doesn't help me.
I play football for you, Coach,
that's it!
So how are you?
Oh, honey, I've been knocked down
millions of time before,
I can get back up.
When the going gets tough,
the tough keep going.
But that's not...
I just wanna tell you, Lyla, that...
I owe you an apology.
And the only reason I did what I did
was because I didn't want
to disappoint you.
But I know it was stupid.
Yes, it was.
But Lyla, I'd really...
I want you to move back in.
I really want that.
OK.
- OK?
- Yeah, OK. I mean...
The Riggins house is disgusting,
so sure.
So the honeymoon's over.
No, the honeymoon is not over.
Tim and I are doing great, actually.
And in fact, the reason
I'm not mad at you anymore
is 'cause the whole college thing
worked out.
- What do you mean?
- I'll go to San Antonio State with Tim.
And we're probably gonna get
a place together.
It's like the whole Vanderbilt thing
not working out was like fate, you know.
Well...
OK.
San Antonio State.
- Tyra!
- I'm in here!
Hey, how's it going?
So I'm going to be playing
in the State game.
Are you understanding what I'm saying?
I'm playing at the State game.
I'm not gonna be on the bench, I'm
gonna be on the field... this time.
I'm sorry.
That's... that's... amazing.
Well, thank you.
So, listen. Whatever crappy seats
that you have, throw 'em away,
because I have some less crappy seats,
and you'll wanna be as close as possible
- whenever the magic happens.
- Landry, I can't go.
I'm sorry, I know that's lame,
but I have to finish this.
No, you're right.
I know that I'm being selfish.
I know I should be happy for her,
she's, you know,
pursuing her dreams,
but at the same time,
this is huge for me, and...
You are being selfish, 'cause you're
really starting to bum me out.
- You're killing my buzz.
- Dude, that's pathetic.
If a tree falls in the forest
and there's no one there to hear it,
- does it actually make a sound?
- What are you talking about? Who cares?
- Would you smile?!
- Stop talking! You grab this drink,
we're gonna celebrate, OK?
We're gonna take a shot
- I don't really do well with alcohol.
- ... to your hard work and to State.
- To State. You tilt your top, like so.
- Don't taste it 'cause you'll be sick.
- Hamilton, Hamilton.
- We've got the best, I think.
Listen, I hope that you and I can find
some time to get together and...
find a way to maybe help J.D.
through some of this.
Trying to put out that fire
you started, Coach?
Joe, I'm not talking about
any kind of blame
and I'm sure you're not either.
I'm talking about helping your son out.
Well, I deeply appreciate your concern
but I tell you what,
I can handle J.D.
He's just fine.
Good luck, Joe.
Let's go, gentlemen!
Everybody ready?
- Yes, sir!
- Let's hear it!
All right, sit back, enjoy the ride.
Have you seen Landry?
- You know where he is?
- Naw, haven't seen him.
You haven't?
What the hell?
- Where the hell are you?
- Where are you at?
I'm on the bus on my way to Austin.
Oh, my God...
You better start driving
'cause we already left.
I gotta... I gotta...
Mindy!
- Tyra!
- Stop yelling.
Oh, yeah, totally gotta puke!
- Rough night?
- You gotta get all your stuff together.
- Shouldn't you be on a bus?
- Actually, I missed the bus,
- and I need you to take me to Austin...
- Well, I can't.
I can't drive
because I'm pretty sure I'm still...
I'm still, like, legally drunk.
- So will you please...
- You need to calm down for a second.
OK, hey.
So, deal?
Deal is, you help me with this,
and I will drive you.
That's... that's fine.
I'll help you with whatever it is...
Panther, Panther, Panther,
blue and gold,
take the ball off the field
and then we score.
Hope is number one,
hit squad's the best.
Panther, Panther, Panther
say forget the rest.
- I said, hey! Hey!
- Hey! Hey!
- I feel all right!
- I said, hey! Hey!
- Hey! Hey!
- I feel all right!
- I said, Panther, Panther, Panther.
How y'all feel going into the game?
I really do feel
like we're gonna get the W here.
You really think...?
Marty Booker used to play quarterback,
now he's a receiver.
Seneca Wallace, you know,
he's the backup on Seattle
but he plays receiver.
And Hasselbeck's in there...
Has Matthew ever said anything to you
about wanting to be an artist?
Well, he's really good at drawing,
and it's something
that he really loves...
You've seen his stuff, haven't you?
Oh, yeah, I've seen it, all that...
artwork, and it's good,
but I never thought he was serious.
He loves football, honey.
Well, he does love football, but...
I just don't think
it's a career path he wants.
He's really, really good at art.
Well, I always encourage him.
Everything he does, I encourage him.
I know.
He knows that too.
I don't want to be the one
to hold him back from anything.
But I... I just can't stand
the thought of losing him.
I know. Me neither.
I'm ready to take us
to win the State.
I'm ready to win
the championship, so...
- But I... I'll see y'all later.
- I thank you so much for your time.
How're you feeling?
I know this is a difficult situation,
I understand that, it's not lost on me.
This team's depending on you.
That means there's a freedom.
That's not pressure.
I want you to at least acknowledge
what I'm saying.
Yes, sir.
Just try to leave it off the field.
Let's see if I can find
my sunglasses in here,
Gracie Belle.
Katie!
Hey, I've been trying to reach you.
- I was just heading off to my room.
- Listen, I know, I know, but...
I know you must be furious at me.
I've been thinking about you, I just...
want to know how you're doing.
Well...
Let's see.
Two flunkies from the State of Texas
barge into my house
and scare me and my boy.
Joe and I have to take parenting classes
from a 23-year-old without kids.
And for the next year, CPS can just
drop by whenever they feel like it,
and if they don't like what they see,
they can take J.D. away.
So that's how I'm doing, Tami.
Thanks for asking.
Katie, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Really, I just...
I wanted you just to know,
I had no choice.
OK? I had no choice.
I would never do that to you,
you are my friend. And I'm so sorry.
Well, you do what you had to do.
Now you'll forgive me
if I want nothing to do with you, right?
Yes.
Read back what we have so far.
OK. "Facing the challenges
of being student body president"
"has helped me develop skills..."
"an appreciation..."
- "... tion"...
- When did you become so mean?
You obviously don't believe
any of what you're saying.
Why don't you tell me what to write?
- This is your essay!
- Should I write about my trashy family?
About the fact
that my sister's a stripper,
or my mom is a high school drop-out
who drinks boxes of wine
like it's water?
Or about the fact that I lost
my virginity when I was 13?
Or the fact that my papa wasn't around?
How about that?
I know what I should write about!
The fact that up until 2 years ago,
I had enough hate in my heart
to start a frikking car!
What changed?
- What?
- What changed from 2 years ago?
Why did you stop having enough hate
in your heart to start a frikking car?
Jason Street got paralyzed.
I realized that...
He was this great guy,
I mean, like, this hero.
And it happened to him?
And it made me realize that...
life isn't fair for anybody.
Not just me.
Uh-huh, and what else?
I don't know, I...
became friends with Julie,
and Mrs. Taylor started
to take some interest in me,
I started doing my homework...
You.
I met you.
I started to feel like I was
on the inside instead of the outside.
What are you doing next year?
Guess I'm going
to San Antonio State.
Does that mean...
Are you excited about that?
Am I excited?
I guess I'm kind of focusing
on tomorrow and...
don't really wanna look
that far ahead, you know?
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
It's a Frisbee!
You're sure you wanna touch that, 7?
It's probably covered in dog piss.
It's not covered in dog piss!
It's just a Frisbee.
Last game, 7!
No regrets.
What are you doing over there, running
in place or something? Come on, now.
- I can't get comfortable.
- Well, I can't either.
Come here.
- What are you doing?
- Come with me outside, come on.
Put your shoes on.
It didn't go off.
I have no idea
what's gonna happen tomorrow, babe.
Well, you're gonna win.
Or you're gonna lose.
Either way, the sun's gonna
come up the next morning.
"Two years ago,"
"I was afraid of wanting anything."
"I figured wanting
would lead to trying,"
"and trying would lead to failure."
"But now I find
I can't stop wanting."
"I wanna fly somewhere
in first class."
"I wanna travel to Europe
on a business trip."
"I wanna get invited
to the White House."
"I wanna learn about the world.
I wanna surprise myself."
"I wanna be important.
I wanna be the best person I can be."
"I wanna define myself
instead of having others define me."
"I wanna win
and have people be happy for me."
"I wanna lose and get over it."
"I wanna not be afraid
of the unknown."
"I wanna grow up to be
generous and big hearted,"
"the way that people
have been with me."
"I want an interesting
and surprising life."
"It's not that I think
I'm gonna get all these things."
"I just want the possibility
of getting them."
"College represents possibility."
"The possibility
that things are gonna change."
"I can't wait."
What'd you think?
I thought it was...
unbelievable.
It's great.
I think it's great, too.
Let me just ask you one question.
- Can you play like champions?
- Yes, sir!
Let's go get 'em.
It's the Texas 5A
State Championship,
the Dillon Panthers
facing the South Texas Titans
in what looks like a real
David and Goliath match-up.
The Titans have scored early and often
on their way to an unbeaten season,
and they're as big and as fast
as anyone has ever seen.
Tails!
We called "tails."
The Titans have won the toss,
elected to receive,
and Coach Taylor hopes his defense
can hold the Titans
on this first possession.
Titans on offense.
Quarterback drops back to pass...
He throws deep!
And true to form,
six points on the board in a hurry.
Come on!
All of the Panthers' hopes
are riding on the shoulders
of the freshman phenom, J.D. McCoy.
He drops back...
Pressure's on...
- He gets taken down hard!
- All right!
McCoy drops back...
He looks for a receiver downfield...
Interception! It's picked up,
and he can walk that one in...
- Touchdown number 2!
- Goddamn it!
Come on, guys!
- Seriously, just run your routes!
- Look 'em up before you throw the ball.
I'm not getting
no time out there, Coach!
J.D. drops back...
He looks...
He's running out of time...
He just gets that one off...
It's incomplete.
Titans on the blitz...
And he goes down again!
McCoy back to pass...
He better get rid of it!
And he's sacked for another loss,
as the Titans make J.D.
pay for his inexperience.
Come on, you guys!
- Gimme the time to throw the ball!
- Relax!
Huddle up, right now!
- Huddle up!
- J.D.!
- J.D., come here!
- What, Coach? What do you want?
You settle down.
Don't you talk to me like that.
Second of all, you settle down.
We've got a lot of game ahead of us.
You understand me? Look at me
when you say that! Do you understand me?
- Yes, sir!
- Let's go.
First half is almost over,
and Taylor would really love
to get something on the board
and go into the locker room
on a positive note.
McCoy drops back...
He's got Riggins in the end zone...
Hit thrown, and it is intercepted!
The Titans have it.
He has got a ton of room,
one man to beat...
and he is off to the races!
That is the second Titan touchdown
off a Panther turnover.
- Aren't you proud of the image?
- Damn good! You're good!
You give me no protection.
None!
God, guys! Come on!
All right, listen up.
We need more.
Offensive line, you look like
you're on roller skates.
We have got to stay in our splits!
Everyone has got
to come off the ball!
Backside, you have got
to pick up the stunts.
Coach Spivey, we're gonna readjust.
Base defense, press coverage.
We are not gonna allow any
more big plays tonight, gentlemen!
What are you looking at?
You wanna be on that field so bad?
- Yes, sir.
- Well, then, show me something!
J.D., you're out.
Matt, change up your pads,
you're in.
There's a fight going on
out there, gentlemen.
Why don't you get in it!
- Clear eyes, full hearts...
- Can't lose!
Only 24 minutes of football
left in this season
as the Panthers take the field.
Let's hope they've learned their lessons
from the mistakes of the first half.
And the second half
is under way.
Panthers have it at the 5.
He brings it out to the 10...
to the 20...
He's got some room to the 30!
- He's got a head of steam!
- Go, baby, go!
To the 40...
And Landry Clarke
puts an incredible block,
and the Panthers have it at the 40,
the 30...
He could go all the way!
Touchdown, Panthers!
We started right, gentlemen!
In a huge reversal,
Coach Taylor has gone back
to veteran QB Matt Saracen,
trying to get his Panthers
back in this game.
He dumps a screen pass
off to Riggins.
Riggins has got some blockers
in front of him...
He breaks one tackle,
he's into the end zone...
Stiff arm!
And touchdown, Panthers!
And the Panthers
have come out firing
by putting 14 unanswered
points on the board.
Saracen with a play-action pass...
He looks...
Oh, and he takes off,
and look at him go!
He breaks a tackle...
and another...
Touchdown, Panthers!
And Coach Taylor's
move to the old offense
has his team a touchdown
from the lead!
We have to do the same thing,
all right? Same thing!
Vice quarterback back to pass...
And intercepted by the Panthers!
With less than 2 minutes to play,
the Panthers have the ball
on the Titan 30-yard line.
A touchdown and a conversion
gives them the lead.
Blue, 80.
Hut!
Saracen takes the snap
and pitches off to Riggins.
Riggins runs right...
and he's looking to pass!
And he throws deep...
and he's got Matt Saracen
on the logo! Touchdown!
Unbelievable, folks!
The Panthers have taken
the lead with just
over a minute and a half to play!
There we go!
- That was all good.
- That's how you goal.
The Panther fans are celebrating
like they have the game won,
but as the Titans
and Coach Taylor well know,
the game is not over
until the final whistle blows.
Thirty-seven seconds
left in the game,
and the Titans are driving
down the field.
Davis back to pass...
a quick slant, and he's got it!
The Titans are into
Panther territory.
Inside, play inside!
All on the Panther 45
as the Titans approach the line.
Bring 'em inside!
There's the snap.
- No! Down! Down, no!
- He is gonna run...
- Stay in there!
- He picks up a block,
and he is sprung to the 40
and wrestled down
at the Panther 36.
It's a hurry-up offense.
The clock is ticking.
White! You have
got to stay in there!
Davis is back to pass...
He's got a man...
Oh, and it is complete
at the Panther 19-yard line!
This is it, folks.
Just 6 seconds left, and this game
comes down to one last play.
The Titans are going
for the field goal.
Bad news for the Panthers,
the Titans' kicker
hasn't missed
from this range all year.
This has been a valiant
effort by the Dillon Panthers.
I wanted everyone's friends and family
to be in here to hear this, gentlemen.
I have never...
been more proud of a team
than I am right now.
I am in awe of each
and every one of you gentlemen.
You played great football tonight.
This is the game...
that people are gonna talk about
for years to come.
This is the game
you're gonna talk about.
There's not a single person in this room
that's ever gonna be the same.
You be proud of yourselves...
'cause gentlemen,
you are champions.
Is that everybody?
No, Riggins hasn't made it on yet.
Want me to send somebody out there?
No, let's give him a minute.
He'll be here.
From a small town
in the heart of Texas,
the lives we've come to know
will change forever.
Dreams realized.
Dreams lost.
Don't miss the season
finale of Friday Night Lights
next week, on the 101 Network,
only on DirecTV.