What are you doing?
I guess I feel closer to God
if I'm with you.
Did you think that line
was gonna work on me?
What if I told you
I could make him go away
and you could have your job back?
I'd say you're crazy.
- I wish I was the one who killed him.
- Don't say that.
If anything happens to you
because of me...
I would never forgive myself.
I'm going to Mexico.
Gonna have surgery.
- Probably be walking next time.
- Mexico, huh?
Hold up. Hold up.
- We're good.
- I'ts gotta be here somewhere.
This is it.
The place where miracles happen.
- You're ready for this?
- I'm ready.
I'm sorry, but this is ridiculous.
You know how long
it took us to get here?
I'm sorry. Whoever made
the appointment made a mistake.
All right, when's the doctor
gonna be here then?
Probably some time next week.
Probably some time next...
probably some time next week?
This is insane!
What... kind of office is this...
You don't even know, like,
really when he's gonna be here?
Do you run this office, or...
Look, the doctor is on vacation
with his family. I don't know for sure.
Here's a card. Call us in a week,
and we'll fit you in.
Westcott is on fire.
A hand-off up the middlefield.
And another first down.
Pass! Pass!
He's got a man.
He's got it.
He breaks the tackle.
Touchdown, and Westcott goes up a punch.
Our champions gave up to the fight.
Did you see what happened? He threw it,
and the other team made a touchdown.
Our defending champs
are taken to the wood shed.
Saracen hands
the ball to Williams again.
And again, he hits a wall
of Westcott defenders.
That play just is not working.
Williams on the draw.
He's hippity hopping
and he gets nailed.
They're keying on Smash.
Every play. Every darn play.
Yep. Not much imagination.
Coach McGregor might want to think
about something else.
He's running attack with Williams
who is dead in the water.
And his team looks
absolutly frustrated out there.
- All right, let's go !
- Come on. Now.
All right, listen up.
Run the ball with Smash. This is retarded.
We're on the same play over and over.
Just run it.
They know we're about to run the ball,
you're not doing well without Riggins.
It's not your call.
C'mon !
Clock's running. Let's do this.
Draw to Smash. On one.
Ready.
C'mon !
Black 12.
Saracen back to pass.
No, it's another throw to Williams.
And he's got nowhere to go.
And he is drop for a loss.
And here come the boo-birds.
The Dillon Panthers' fans are not happy
about this coach
and situation tonight, folks.
Rightly so.
The nail that doesn't bend
gets hammered, and McGregor
and Mcgregor has gotten pounded
all night with his ground attack.
Our state champions
have gotten their lunch handed to them
on their home field.
It is a sad state of affairs.
- What a crock.
- Pardon me?
Don't piss on my shoes
and tell me it's raining.
That's a good one.
We just feel like the team needed to...
- go in a new direction.
- After two games?
- Yes, sir.
Two games? This is...
we wanna go ahead
and pay you for the entire season.
Plus we're gonna give you a severance
package just to show you our good will.
- I'm very sorry it worked out this way.
- There ain't no good will in this room.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
Pathetic.
Taylor, you got a phone call.
Hello?
Eric, it's Buddy.
How you doing?
I'm in the middle of a game.
How did you get this number?
Ah, you know me.
Never mind that.
Listen, the eagle has landed.
- What?
- It's a done deal.
We fired him this morning.
2x04: BACKFIRE
Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
Subtitles: Ju, Sixe
www.top-series.net (1.00)
Hi. Lyla Garrity.
Okay, guys. Come on.
I apologize for our boys.
They don't get visitors that often.
And so, those are just a few examples
of why it's helpful
to make choices in our lives
with Jesus in our lives.
- That's it.
- Great. Thanks.
Any questions?
Yo, I got a question.
What color panties are you wearing?
That was ery funny Doug, very funny.
Five points.
There's more for the rest
if you don't cut it out. Calm down.
Let me ask you a question.
I got a question.
If God's so great,
then why do we have wars, huh?
- Did cat catch your tongue?
- I mean, look at Tony over there.
Why's tony's parents drunkall the time
beating on him and his sister?
Well...
That's a good question.
No disrespect,
but you people are always coming in here
acting like you care, right?
When the truth is...
if you see any one of us on the street, you just run the other way.
- So, who's winning?
- I don't know, it's a tie right now.
So, um...
I was wondering if you could take me driving.
I can't do it right this second, honey.
I'm sorry.
Mom, I got my permit.
I need to practice.
- I'm aware of that.
- Okay, but it's kind of like homework.
Like you need to practice
in order to pass.
I'm not gonna do it right this second.
Gracie is almost asleep.
I'm exhausted.
I'm watching your dad's game,
I'm not gonna just drop everything when
you want me to go do something. Sorry.
Why is it always about the baby, mom?
I'm still here. You know that, right?
I'm still your daughter too,
just as much as little blob.
I'm know, but you don't have to act like
such a brat about it all the time.
Oh, I'm a brat. Okay.
You're just gonna keep me locked in,
not let me drive or date who I want?
What you're talking about?
I'm gonna go date the Swede.
Just to spite you.
Oh, well, that's really mature.
- I hate you.
- Come back here right now.
What are we watching right now, six?
For the past week.
"Siempre hay una segre."
We have a bag of money,
we're in Mexico for a week now,
a bag of money, booze, no women,
- no stories, no memories.
- Guess what,
You should have thought about all that
before you came down
in Mexico with me.
I'm here to see a doctor.
And this bag is not a bag of memories.
It's a bag of $10,000 for said doctor.
So, until I see said doctor,
we're not going anywhere,
and neither is the money.
Yeah, you are.
- I'm not gonna need that. Let's go.
- Don't touch me.
- Riggins, do not touch me. Stop!
- We're going out.
No regrets, six, none.
Stop!
- Personal reasons?
- Yes.
Well, you...
you knew your wife was pregnant
when you took this job, didn't you?
Yes, sir. That's true.
Look, coach, I...
I don't wanna leave you in the lurch.
I'll be here for the Rice
and the Oklahoma game.
The bye week,
we can make the transition.
We take Frank,
put him up for quarterbacks.
It's your decision,
bu I'm just thinking about it.
- That might be a smooth transition...
- You sure you wanna do this?
Coach, I have to.
All right. Then you turn in
your id downstairs.
I'll have human resources send over
a termination package tonight.
- Tonight?
- Yeah, tonight.
This isn't IBM, Coach.
I'm not interested in any exit
strategies or transition plans.
If you wanna go, go, and I'll deal
with the situation right now.
So good luck.
Hope you know
what the hell you're doing.
That damn thing kept
scratching up my favorite chair.
And, uh...
I told Landry, I said,
"it's either me or the cat."
'Cause one of us has got to go.
And that's when I initiated the...
the outplacement procedure.
That's what he's calling it.
Technically, Mr. Puddles...
If that's what you wanna call him...
Yeah, hello?
- Hold this up.
- Hold on...
His name was Mr. Puddles?
Ironically, he was she.
Of course.
Once again,
being a genius, and everything,
I hadn't quite figured out
the whole he, she...
However you wanna put it.
Sorry, guys.
I have got to go.
They just pulled a body
out of the river.
Sorry, baby.
Save me a plate, okay?
Tyra, it's good to see you again.
Landry, I'll talk to you later, bud.
Today we're looking at guilt
and redemption, sin and grace.
Consider the story of king David.
The beautiful bathsheba catches his eye.
He commits adultery with her
and decides he wants her as his wife.
This means getting rid of her husband,
so David plans a conspiracy
to ensure the husband's
murder in battle.
He thinks he gets away with it,
but God sees, and God knows.
I'm telling you. It was like everyone
in the entire church knew.
- You're just being weird.
- I'm not being paranoid.
- How would they know?
- This isn't some little thing.
This is ridiculous, me thinking
that no one's gonna find out.
I know what I've got to do.
- It's...
- What are you talking about?
I've gotta go turn myself in.
And explain that this was just...
this was a huge accident
and just hope that they, you know,
go easy on me because my dad's a cop.
That's not gonna happen.
What do you think they're gonna do?
Slap you on the wrist?
I have no idea
- what else to do.
- We're in this together.
I can't keep doing this.
We have no choice.
You understand we have no choice.
No, we... you're wrong.
We do have a choice.
I can turn myself in,
and that's what I'm gonna do.
- Spend the rest of your life in jail?
- Spend it in jail or what?
What's the alternative?
Spend the rest of my life like this?
We're in this together, okay?
It's us.
Pass, ma'am.
Thank you.
if this is your escape plan,
it needs work.
I was just kidding.
I heard you got out. Congratulations.
Yeah, I'm on probation now.
Congratulations.
Okay.
What are you trying to do?
I'm putting my money
where my mouth is. Come on.
So what are you gonna do?
Do you have any plans or anything?
Not really.
I mean, are you gonna go to school or...
I guess so.
Gotta get a job too. My probation lady
will be all over my ass about it.
What do your parents say?
Damn, you ask a lot of questions, huh?
Sorry.
I guess I'm just...
- ... interested.
- If I tell you, will you shut up?
- I promise.
- My parents are in Mexico.
They got deported two years ago.
Left me to live with my uncle
who has a son, my cousin the homey,
a real inspiration to me and told me
how selling weed to people like you.
Maybe not you.
Anyway, that's how I got picked up.
Spent two years in juvie.
Now I'm here. Happy?
Look, stop here.
I could take you in.
You don't want to bring
this car in here.
Gotta go.
Okay, well...
Can I? Can I get your number?
Just a way to keep in touch.
So if this surgery's so great,
why can't you just...
Why isn't it okay in the states?
Because, like I told you,
between washington and the AMA,
gonna take forever to get it legalized.
And I ain't got forever.
No more questions.
Yeah, but you... you're saying...
the parallel bars,
and the guy that could move his toes.
You know, I mean, that's...
I wanna know if any of these guys
have walked again.
What are you doing?
I was asking if any of these guys
have ever actually walked.
No. Nobody else has walked yet.
It doesn't matter.
I told you I'm a perfect
candidate for the surgery.
I regained feeling in my right hand.
The other couldn't feel anything.
The guy that's doing the parallel bars
had no feeling in any extremity.
They couldn't even move a muscle.
Señores...
Papeles, por favor.
- What?
- Papeles, por favor.
- Id?
- Wallet. Wallet.
- Put those down.
- He wants a beer, relax.
Put them down immediately,
don't talk back right now.
Here you go, sir.
Thank you, officer.
- Detenme esto.
- Six, relax.
- Yes, sir.
Been through this a million times.
He's not even talking to anybody.
He wants memories as well, six.
He wants a night on the town.
He wants some senoritas.
- What's it gonna take?
- What are you doing?
What's it gonna take?
You want some memories?
Some señoritas.
Cheers. Go cowboy.
Sweet, six.
Took you long enough,
now thosa gals are probably gone.
Shut your mouth. I should have left you
in there all damn night.
Sad sorry ass. I'm not supposed to be
spending my money on your bail.
Yeah, it's my fault that we found
the only honest cop in Mexico.
Your ass, Riggins.
You know this money for my surgery is not for your damn bail.
What's your problem, six?
You know what?
I came down here for a reason.
You think it's stupid, but it's not.
Go ahead and get loaded tonight
and catch syphilis from whatever
skanky jailbait random hooker
or whore you can find on the street,
but I'm going back to the hotel.
Can you at least buy me a couple tacos?
Oh, could it be, could it be?
Guess who's home?
Julie, dad's home!
Jules?
- What's up?
- Hey, come here.
- How are you? I missed you.
- I'm good.
Good to see you, kid.
- Hi, hon.
- How you doing?
How's my little one doing?
She's good.
- Why is Buddy Garrity here?
- What's wrong, my child?
Hey Buddy.
Look what I found sitting in road.
Look what I founf.
Look what I found on the road.
I put it in the truck.
Here it is.
Go to your mama.
He's dirty.
I'll be in for dinner in a second.
You just got home, so y'all don't stay
out here too long now.
I'll be in in just a second.
He just got home, Buddy, so...
- Nice to see you. Great to see you.
- You too, Tami.
Hey, man, how you doin'?
Y'all don't be long now.
What are you doing?
Have you been waiting at the beginning
of the neighborhood or something?
- You followed me in here?
- Mcgregor's gonna fight us on this.
Well I just got the call.
That's why I ran over.
Evidently he's apparently
got some lawyer,
and he refuses to sign anything. There's
an emergency board meeting tomorrow.
Are you telling me I don't have a job?
No.
It's just... it's just a little
complication, that's all.
You understand I signed
a no-compete, don't you?
I can't take on any college jobs
for two years.
You understand that, don't you?
"Done, done." That's what you said.
You said "it's a done deal."
"It's a done deal, Eric,"
that's what it is.
- What the hell happened?
- I'm sorry, it just...
- You're sorry?
- Now, we just got a little...
It's just a little hitch
in our get-along. That's all it is.
Trust me.
I'm gonna do my best.
What about...
What about painting the garage?
Dad's obviously never gonna do that.
The garage is fine.
Well, there's got to be something, mom.
If he has a job,
it helps him with his probation.
Okay, do you even hear
what you're saying?
I mean, this boy is an ex-convict.
Mom, he's just a kid.
You want him hanging around
with your brother and sister?
It's not safe.
Oh, my God, mom.
You don't even know him.
And neither do you.
Look, I appreciate what you're trying
to do here, but the answer is no.
I'm sorry.
Slow down a little bit.
Use your mirrors.
What's over your righthand shoulder?
- Did you look?
- I looked.
Good job.
Thank you.
What's this about you
and the swedish kid?
That was really subtle.
Did mom even give you cue cards?
No, this doesn't have anything
to do with your mom.
She obviously has an opinion, however.
But this is me asking you.
I want to hear it from you.
Mom doesn't like him 'cause he's older.
How much older?
It doesn't even matter.
Mom has me in lockdown at our house.
Your mother loves you very much.
You have bigger things
to worry about, like your job.
Don't bring my job up.
I'll take care of that.
- That's none of your business, my job.
- It's none of my business?
No, don't give me that look.
Watch the road.
What's this about... what's this about
I hear you and this kid
carrying on in the driveway?
- Oh, we're carrying on now?
- Yes, carrying on.
Don't look at me like that. I don't like
your tone... Watch out for the road.
Keep your eye on the road.
Look out up here.
You got this turn up here.
Get on the other lane.
This goes on to the highway.
You gotta get over to the right.
Get in the other lane.
Watch out!
Look out for that!
Damn it.
You almost hit this guy.
I can't drive when you're yelling!
Look, just stay right where you are.
Just stay right where you are.
This is great.
We can do the operation on Thursday.
Those Texas docs nailed your fusion,
so we can skip decompression
- and go right for the injections.
- The stem cells.
Technically,
they're embryonic stem cells,
but the sharks don't
make the distinction.
Hang on. Wait.
Did you just say you're gonna give him a shot from a shark, doc?
Yeah.
Pretty cool stuff.
Sharks have one of the strongest immune systems in nature.
It decreases the risk of rejection
and runaway cell growth.
We don't want your friend here
going all "jaws" on us.
And again, uh...
why can't they do this in the states?
Because...
the FDA are a bunch or crybabies.
Okay.
I don't even want to go out with them.
Everyone's gonna think I jock Smash
as much as Smash jocks Smash,
And I don't.
We all know that I don't.
What's the point?
- He used to be cool, but now...
- Just go out with one of Smash's girls.
I mean, you need some kind of rebound
to get over Julie because it's obviously
- ... affecting everything.
- This is a gold mine.
- Would they people pay?
- Wouldn't they pay, real question.
Hey, space cadet.
Working on a business venture, here.
If that's what you wanna call it.
Look, I just don't see anybody paying y'all to walk around their lawns naked.
Half-naked, or whatever.
We're not walking around their lawns,
and you're being a snot.
- None of it?
- None.
You kinda in all of this on your own.
The Smash talking in the locker room.
What's the deal?
One loss and y'all quit practicing?
Oh, man.
- Just kidding, man.
- We lost the same game last year too,
and that worked out okay, so, you know,
we don't want to get too cocky.
- All right. Y'all be good.
- All right. Y'all enjoy.
What's the matter with you.
You okay?
What's wrong, man?
You look like you're about to throw up.
Uh, just something's wrong with my...
my burger.
It don't taste-- I'm fine.
- No, ma'am.
- That is incorrect
- on the issue of cause for termination.
- Cause? Wait, what cause?
- Nobody ever gave a reason.
- Ma'am,
excuse me, we had a student get injured.
Had to go to the hospital
from a practice
that went over time limits.
That was against the rules.
He got a little overheated. They
gave him some fluids, and he was fine.
We're talking about Tim Riggins.
Everybody knows Tim Riggins.
He was probably hung over.
It's an excuse which you all
have just dreamed up in order
to justify the lynching of my client.
Coach McGregor...
was fired because
we simply do not like the way
he has abandoned
our tradition here in Dillon.
He has come in, he has changed
practices, closed them down.
He is not attending booster club meetings.
He has changed the pep rally,
and he's managed
to destroy our record-setting
offense in a very short period of time.
Which has angered
many parents and many fans.
Not to mention the players.
I believe I saw
I believe I saw our quarterback
and our star running back
in a fistfight at the end of the game
the other night in the middle
of the Daggon football field.
It was in a game you won, Buddy.
That's not the point, Barbara.
That's not the point.
You, being from Laribee,
wouldn't understand.
But here in Dillon, we win seasons.
we win seasons.
We don't win games.
State championships.
Unfortunately, coach Mcgregor
was not getting the job done.
We fired him.
End of story.
You're speaking for everybody here?
You bet your ass I am.
- Well, it's undermining me.
- It's not undermining you.
- How am I undermining you?
- Well, you were coming in here...
You don't know how it's been,
sweetheart.
She has been horrible.
She has treated me...
- horribly.
- I know I don't know what's going on.
But please, let's start new.
Let's just talk to her.
Come on.
Julie!
Jules! Please come in here, please.
- Hey, good morning, kiddo.
- Good morning, sunshine.
Good morning.
Mother has something
she wants to tell you.
Your father and I
have been talking, and,
I have-- we have together very, very,
very tentatively decided
that you are not gonna be grounded.
What's the catch?
No catch other than you need to behave
like I know you know how to.
There's four of us in this family.
You need to respect that?
Thank you.
By the way, congratulations, dad.
It's all over the paper.
What is?
What's in the paper?
Bring it in here.
Bring the paper here.
All right, all right.
Ouch, Jesus.
See, right on that line.
Right there. No.
First of all,
you have to-- remember
you have to go forward of the car
and back into it.
There's a car right there.
You just hit that car.
Honey, you need to pull outside the car,
and back up.
I'm backing up.
Now pull forward to the side of the car,
and then back to the curb.
Side of the car.
Okay, look at me go.
- Back to the curb.
- Honey, you're not even listening.
- I'm listening.
- Just turn the car off.
Just turn the car off.
Let's just take a break.
Let's just sit for a minute, all right?
Listen, I need to talk to you
about something.
When I was younger I--
There was a guy, his name was Doug Odom,
- he was a lot older than me.
- Mom, don't do this.
Listen, please.
Thank you.
I was obsessed with him.
And we went to this party once
on fourth of july,
I was with him
and all his fancy friends, and...
Anyway...
I slept with him that night.
And that was the first time
I'd ever slept with anybody.
I woke up the next morning, I thought
we were gonna be boyfriend and girlfrie
and I saw him the next day and...
He treated me...
like I didn't really matter.
Like what happened didn't really matter.
And you're spending
all this time with this...
boy who doesn't seem to have a name,
I know you like him.
- I know you think he likes you.
- His name is Anton.
And he does like me.
Well, he doesn't love you.
And that's the difference.
- Bye, y'all.
- Bye, dad.
- See you, dad.
- That was fun.
- See you next week.
- See you, Thab.
Remember what I said, little bud.
Did you have fun?
How are you?
I'll be in in a second, okay?
- I need to talk to you.
- Okay.
Has Lyla talked to you at all
about this boy?
No. We, uh...
We're sort of in a...
feeling each other out mode right now.
There's not a whole lot of sharing.
Well, let me tell you where she met him.
She met him in prison.
Okay? At some...
counseling session
for christ team messengers.
- Pam, we've had this talk before...
- She wanted me to hire him.
And when I said no,
she called me unchristian.
And just walked out.
Can you believe that?
- She tried to find him a job.
- Yes.
I mean, can you imagine this...
ex-convict in our house with the kids
and me there all alone?
- It's not right.
- Tell you what.
I'll handle it.
I'll take care of it.
- Good.
- Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Santiago, have you ever had
any sales experience?
- Not really, sir.
- Well, you ever worked on cars?
You ever do any mechanic work?
I usually take the bus.
Take the bus?
He had a job last year, right?
Doing dishes?
Yeah. I had a job last year.
Doing dishes like she said.
Well...
it's something.
It has nothing to do with cars,
but at least it shows he's responsible.
Can I talk?
Yes, sir. Please do.
This is an interview.
I'd love for you to talk.
Look, I know I don't have
no experience, sir.
I'm guessing she probably told you
I've been in juvie.
I don't mean no disrespect to you
or to this place, but...
I have to get a job, sir.
If I don't get a job, they're gonna send
me back to state, I don't wanna to.
I'll do anything you ask me
and try not to mess it up too bad.
I promise.
- I promise.
- I appreciate that.
And if Lyla vouches for you...
- I do.
- I'll go with you.
I'll do it. I'll give you a job
in the parts department.
It's only 8.50 an hour
and you have to work on weekends.
That sounds great, sir.
Thank you.
Sorry, we were supposed
to hang out, right?
Uh, yeah.
Come on inside.
Come on.
- Your phone was ringing.
- My what?
Your phone was ringing.
Oh, well, that's probably just Jonesy.
I told him we were going
to dry creek, and he got...
all excited.
What's dry creek?
You know, it's...
It's got foosball, you know, and, and,
I don't know two-for-one beer night,
and I think Kennedy
and Chris are gonna join us, so...
Jonesy called Spike
and Spike called Spencer...
and...
is there something wrong?
Yeah, um...
I just, um...
I'm just feeling really sick,
and I think I should go home, okay?
Yeah, um, but you know what?
Have fun, and I'll...
Hey, you need...
you need a ride home?
It's okay, I got it.
Hey, babe.
How was your night?
Jules?
What happened?
You all right?
Come here.
- This is yours?
- Now you wanna drink
a week later,
after I've been boozing all week.
They got a picture of John Wayne.
Let's toast to the duke.
- Here's to J. Wayne.
Cheers, my friend.
- Let's go. Round two.
- Round eight, soon enough.
Round two right now.
To walking.
To runnin'.
Is this in english?
What do you got, six?
Clear eyes, Timmy!
Tomorrow's a big day for me, folks.
It's a big day.
You know why?
I'm gonna walk-a, I'm gonna walk-a,
I'm gonna get out of my chair,
and I'm-a run-a, and I'm-a run-a,
and I'm-a get right outta there
because Dillon sucks, folks.
Dillon is an awful place to be,
and I wanna walk away,
and tomorrow, I'm gonna do it.
Look at me.
No, I'm serious!
No, I'm serious, I'm serious.
Tomorrow I'm getting a--
I'm gettin' a shot-a, I'm gettin' a shot-a
right in my spine and
it's gonna make me walk again, folks.
You don't even know what I'm sayin',
but you believe me.
I believe it too.
Timmy, you believe it, don't you?
Le it go !
I'm gonna walk, Timmy!
Timmy, I'm gonna walk again!
What's up?
Uh, I just got a call
from the Dillon police.
- What they'd want?
- Well, why don't you tell me?
I really don't know. We have to go
down there right now. Get dressed.
We pulled a body from the river
a few days ago.
Male caucasian.
I need to ask you a couple
of questions about it if you're ready.
We found this in the wallet.
You recognize this person?
Yeah, it-- Yes.
- How do you know him?
- He, um..
He attacked me.
He tried to... He tried to rape me.
What? Honey, what?
- I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
- Why didn't you tell me?
Tyra, stay with me now.
Is this the man
who sexually assaulted you
in the parking lot
of the Alamo Freeze last november?
- Yeah.
- All right, then.
I really wanna thank you ladies
for coming out like this.
Wait.
- Is that it?
- Yes, ma'am.
You did a real good job
on your description.
We matched it
with a sketch this morning.
Look, here's your sketch.
This boy was wanted
for rape in two other states.
Oh, my God.
Honey...
I'm sorry, mom.
You can rest easy now.
We're gonna close this case.
There'll be someone to show you out,
ladies. Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I don't know,
it's some kind of experiment
where they're injecting him
with shark blood,
it's supposed to make him walk again.
Tim, are you drunk?
No, Lyla, I'm not drunk.
Maybe I'm not explaining
this very well, but...
I don't know. All this medical stuff
is just over my head.
You know,
Jason's parents are worried sick.
Yeah, well, I am, too.
He might actually go through with this.
So what am I supposed to do?
Come down here.
Help me talk him out of it.
Come to Mexico?
Are you outta your mind?
I swear, J's gonna die
if he goes through with this, Lyla.
I haven't asked for anything from you,
I'm asking you to come down here
and help me help J.
He's not listening to me.
Help me.
Please.
I'm gonna tell you one
of my favorite things about myself.
But Gracie'll start.
Gracie, start tellin'.
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
Because you tell her every five minutes.
You're filling her head full of it.
Hey, Coach.
Coach, how you doing?
I was filling up the truck,
I was rolling outta town,
and I just thought I'd come by and,
congratulate you, because it worked out
just the way you wanted.
- How's that?
You know, Eric,
I've been a coach a long time.
I been fired before,
and I'll probably be fired again.
But this is the first time
I been screwed by another coach.
Just wait a second here.
- You were involved in this thing.
- I don't appreciate that accusation.
It's the truth. You're not gonna lie
to me here at your doorstep.
I don't think you are.
I know you were involved, maybe you had
your reasons, maybe you didn't.
But I want you to know that I have
a family too, you just remember that.
I'll be seeing you again.
Listen up.
We got Westerby in two days.
I know y'all don't want another loss
pinned on your asses.
Quarterbacks and receivers
are gonna be with me today.
Linemen on the boards with Mac.
Any questions?
No, sir.
- What's that?
- No, sir.
- I didn't hear you.
- No, sir!
Let's go. Let's have some fun today.
Let's get out there!