- Are you gonna be faithful to me?
- I'm gonna try.
- What's all this?
- I'm going with you.
Really?
Let Matt play on
wide receiver this year.
He thinks like a QB,
you should at least give him a shot.
I'm gonna take a little trip to New York
and get a job in a sports agency
with my friend Grant that I met,
and that's what I'm gonna do.
Texas forever?
Texas forever.
All right.
You're always gonna be
my best friend.
- This is perfect, right here.
- Right.
- Thank you, sir, it's all yours.
- Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
My God!
Guess who's paying for my truck?
Whatever it takes, Billy,
you're paying for it, to get it back to
better condition than where I left it.
Three days!
I leave for three days, Billy!
You're a write-off, too.
Look at you!
- What I am...
- She dumped me.
- For real?
- Yeah, for real.
Mindy dumped me.
The wedding's off.
Sorry to hear that.
You, uh...
You wanna talk about it?
Sorry about your truck.
Throw it, throw it.
Good arm.
Now that you've got that,
I've got Mr. Bear.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Who put the milk away all empty?
What? Gracie is trying
to tell me something.
Gracie and Mr. Bear inform me
someone's birthday is coming up.
I don't know
whose birthday that would be.
- It certainly isn't mine.
- Yes, it is!
You know, I don't think
I'm gonna have my birthday this year.
I think I've decided against it.
- You what?
- Against your birthday?
Yeah, you know what?
It's just, I think,
better not to have it.
I feel old.
I feel like if I have a birthday,
Gracie Belle is gonna have a birthday,
and you're gonna have a birthday.
I think it's just better not to.
It'd be the best present
you can give me.
Agreed?
We gotta leave in 5 minutes.
All right, listen up! It's the playoffs,
gentlemen. This is where the fun begins.
For those of you who've been out here
before, you know what I'm talking about.
For those of you who haven't...
you will.
I want y'all to think back to September
when we played Arnett Mead.
I'll tell y'all something.
We were a good team back then,
but we are a better team now.
Y'all look at each player
around you.
You take a close look, you think about
what you've been through this year.
You think about the good, about the bad,
you just think about that, gentlemen,
and then you ask yourselves
this one question:
how much are you willing to sacrifice
of yourselves out on this field?
I guarantee
the answer to that question
will determine the outcome
of this game.
Let's have a good practice,
let's go!
Blue, 80, set, hut!
Get off the line!
Hey, Ned, what are you doing?
Put a body on him, let's go!
That's my fault. I told 'em not to
touch him so he doesn't get hurt.
If he's gonna be a receiver, he's
gonna have to take some hits.
Matt, you wanna take some hits there,
or you wanna take it real easy like?
Blue, 80, set, hut!
Coach! Eric!
- Eric! One minute.
- Get back here!
You're gonna want to hear this,
I promise. Hey, boys!
- Everyone should hear this.
- Guys, we didn't wanna say anything,
because we weren't sure what was
gonna happen, but we just got the call,
the TV people have picked
the Dillon Panthers to be
the High School Game of the Week.
Now, what that means is, Friday night,
you're gonna be playing
on national television, baby!
Are you ready for some football?
3x09: GAME OF THE WEEK
Subtitles: Team Panthers
With the participation of:
benj!, Collioure, DarKsh, GillesSilb,
Ju, loky34, ouazo, tactactac, TVnut
You got an idea what this is?
... to receive a full credit
for community service,
you may sign up for that
this afternoon after third period,
outside of Mr. Conahan's class.
I'm sure y'all have probably noticed
this morning we've got some interesting
visitors around the school,
and I am pleased to announce
that, on behalf of Coach Taylor
and the football team,
our game against Arnett Mead
on Friday night
is going to be
on national television.
So that's real exciting news
for all of us,
it's gonna be a great opportunity
for the school and for Dillon,
and I know y'all are gonna
represent us well...
so everybody,
each and everyone of you,
get out there and make me proud.
Have a great day, today.
All right, smile, y'all.
Thanks, folks. Enjoy the rodeo.
I'll just check out the board.
- Yes! I'm riding Estop!
- Good.
- That's money, baby.
- Steak dinner tonight?
{\- Hey, Cash!
- }Hey, buddy.
- Might I have your autograph, please?
- Yes, you can.
Sit on up there, man.
Let my girl get a good look at you.
- Hey, I saw you ride at Nashville.
- I appreciate your support.
All right, enjoy the rodeo.
- Thanks, Cash.
- No problem, buddy, see ya.
- That was me a long time ago.
- I'm sure it was.
Hey, Cash!
Come over here.
This is Brooke, right here.
Hey, Brooke, how you been?
- Who's this pretty girl?
- This is my girlfriend, Tyra.
Hi, Tyra. What are you doing
without boots and a hat?
Well, real boots and a hat.
Come over here.
You guys have some fun girl time,
I'll see you in a bit.
You go do your thing,
I've got her under control.
OK, let's get you a hat.
Come over here.
So, how long have you two
been going out?
- A while, I guess.
- Well, you're a very lucky girl
'cause he is quite a catch.
So, what do you do?
Barrel racing, roping?
I'm a waitress, actually.
Good for you.
All right, so...
What do you think?
I love it, but...
I can't afford any of this stuff.
We'll lie them on Cash.
The money I win from this,
I will pay you, calm down.
- Does your mom still pack your lunch?
- No. How're your steak fingers?
So where is Tyra?
I don't know,
am I supposed to know where Tyra is?
She's been missing for a week,
I need to talk to her.
Well, if you want,
you could probably give her a call,
- I'm sure she'd love to hear from you.
- She picked a bad week to be ditching.
Winter formal is in 3 weeks
and we don't have a theme.
What are y'all gonna do...
without a theme?
She's president of the student council
and she keeps blowing off our meetings.
If you talk to her,
tell her to give me a call.
Otherwise, we're gonna pick
a theme without her.
You don't wanna do that.
They're gonna pick
a theme without her.
Have you seen Tyra? I mean, she has
been gone for a while, it seems like.
I think she said her aunt was sick.
Well, I'm sure that
she's fine wherever she is...
you know.
- He has a girlfriend, now?
- Mental note!
- Tim!
- Yeah.
Mr. Riggins.
- Scotty Simms, San Antonio State.
- How you doing?
- Good. How are you?
- Good.
I'm the one who's been sending
those recruiting letters.
You're a hard man to track down.
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
I meant to call you.
We've been, like, there's practice
and State coming...
Don't worry about it, I know
what it's like, you got a lot going on.
- Hi, it's nice to meet you.
- I'm Lyla.
{\- Sorry. Lyla, Scotty Simms.
- }Nice to meet you.
So, listen, I don't mean
to blindside you like this,
but like I said in my letters, we're
graduating our entire backfield in June.
We really feel like you'd be
a great fit for our team next year.
- Thank you.
- I'll be at the Marriott next few days.
Come by tomorrow night. We'll have
a sit-down, talk about our program?
- Tomorrow night isn't a good...
- They make a hell of a rib eye.
Tomorrow night's not really good, sir.
My truck's in the shop, right now...
I'll give you a ride.
I'll give him a ride.
Great.
Eight o'clock?
Yeah, sounds good.
{\- All right, see you then.
- }See you then.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
Scotty Simms...
Hey, Jen.
Can I see Jules for a second, please?
Come here.
Thanks.
If l could just be a second...
Come on, hurry up.
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
Listen,
Friday night, all right,
after the game...
I've set up a reservation at a hotel
for your mother and I.
It's a little surprise for her,
all right?
I'm gonna get some champagne, flowers,
chocolate, so we can spend some time...
- I don't wanna hear about it.
- Here's what I need from you.
While mom's not looking, set up
an overnight bag for her, all right?
The other thing is, I need
for you to look after Gracie.
- Can you do that?
- I can set up the bag and watch Gracie,
but dad, I'm pretty sure mom didn't want
her birthday being celebrated at all.
That's her problem.
- You're good with Gracie?
- I'm good with Gracie.
Thanks, thanks.
- Get back to your Shakespeare.
- Dad, it's math class.
- Tell Mr. Newton I say hello.
- Dad, Mr. Newton's not...
Yeah, baby!
Go, Cash!
That's it, baby, that's it!
7-9, 79!
Cash Waller takes second place!
- Baby, that was so good.
- Stow that, all right, honey?
Second place is the first loser.
That's not good enough at all!
- You should eat that in the kitchen.
- I'm sorry.
- I was too tired to get a plate.
- I'll get you one.
This is my house and Matthew can eat
wherever he wants to.
Grandma, that's OK.
I should probably eat in there anyway.
- You can eat wherever you want to.
- Maybe I should use a plate.
This is just dirty.
- Here's a plate.
- Thank you.
And when are you leaving?
- Excuse me?
- I mean it.
How much longer is she planning
on being around here?
Well, since you brought it up...
I think it's OK, we should discuss it.
- What?
- Matthew might go to college next year.
And I think that's so great,
and I told him that
if he did get into college,
that I could help
take care of you, and I'd probably
be staying here a lot longer, then.
Maybe, just maybe.
You two...
have been talking about me,
in my house...
No, not like...
Haven't you?
Well, you know what?
That's just about the worst idea
- I ever heard and I'm not having it.
- Lorraine, calm down.
I'm not gonna calm down, missy.
Not at all.
Matthew is not going anywhere,
he wouldn't do that.
I think that's a little bit selfish,
you know,
after everything
that Matthew's done for you...
Me? Selfish?
We wanna talk about who's selfish?
You can't expect him
to stay here forever.
- He's a kid with a whole life to live.
- You know what? You're the devil.
No, no... Really.
The first day I met her, I knew.
She ruined your daddy.
That's a horrible thing to say.
She would have ruined you
if I hadn't been here!
- That's enough.
- No! Get away from me, both of you!
Now, let me tell you something
right now.
You can get rid of me,
but don't leave me with her.
You promise me,
if you really want to, get rid of me,
but don't leave me with her.
You can't listen to her
when she talks like this.
She doesn't... even know
what she's talking about.
So the angle that I'm gonna go for
is that it's really
about climate change.
Am I boring you?
It's my shoulder, it's killing me,
so I just kinda...
It's from getting hit all the time
at practice?
I kinda hope we lose on Friday
so your daddy gets off my back and
- stops having everyone beat up on me.
- You know what he's doing, right?
- Being a jerk?
- No.
He's trying to motivate you.
It's like basic psychology.
- He probably read it in a book.
- It's not working.
Hey, Matt, you're not gonna believe
what just happened to me.
Some lady just asked me
to do an interview for her tomorrow.
I guess she's some sort of
- producer or director.
- For what?
For the profile on the Panthers team,
the pre-game stuff.
Apparently, I'm gonna speak
as a scholar-athlete.
- You're a scholar-athlete?
- I never thought about it, but...
- They want to interview you?
- I gotta go rehearse
or figure out
what I'm gonna talk about,
- you know? Ain't that cool, Matt?
- Yeah.
I gotta get to class.
I was gonna name
my first-born after you.
I was gonna name it Timmy.
Seriously, man, even if it was...
a girl.
I mean that.
That's sweet of you.
- Cheers.
- Cheers, no regrets.
No regrets.
- That one hurt.
- Didn't sit right.
Beer me right now.
Beer it.
I've been honking
and screaming outside
- for about 5 minutes.
- Sorry, I lost track of time.
Just been...
tending to Billy and his broken heart.
- I'm ready.
- You want a drink?
You have an appointment
in about 15 minutes.
You know, when you talk
close to me like that,
we should just go have a shower.
You have an appointment in 15 minutes.
This is important.
- I'm ready.
- I can't believe you're drinking.
I'm not drinking.
I had a shot and half a beer.
Riggins is in his game face.
Putting my game face on.
I'm serious.
I'm good.
- I'll be in the car.
- I was gonna tell him, you know,
"you need to get ready
'cause you got your meeting"
- and everything, but...
- Well done, Billy.
He's gonna do fine.
I mean, it's gonna be awesome.
- So you knew about the meeting?
- I forgot, but...
- You forgot?
- I knew.
You knew...
You're a mess.
Sorry about Mindy, too, by the way.
A few things are
that it was founded in 1917
and their big thing is
small classroom sizes,
- and student-faculty ratio...
- You're absolutely right, but I...
I  think he's just gonna want to talk
about football. That's probably just it.
- But it doesn't...
- Keep it simple, you know?
hurt to be informed
about the school, so that maybe...
Well, yeah, I just...
It's not really a job interview, so...
Actually, that's exactly what it is.
- I know what you're doing.
- What am I doing?
With avoiding all the meetings,
and the drinking with your brother...
- You're afraid.
- Afraid?
You're afraid that, you know,
if it doesn't work out
for some reason,
that you'll feel like a failure, but...
To be honest with you, what I'm really
afraid of is that if it does work out,
then I have to go to college.
You have a shot at being
the only Riggins
to go to college.
That's huge!
What are you laughing at?
At me?
OK, kinda, sorta.
Because these meetings are crap.
They get you alone, they hot-box you,
fill you up with empty promises,
and that's about it,
it's a waste of time.
- Waste of time?
- I can't wait.
I'm excited for my free steak.
- I have nothing to be scared of.
- I'm an idiot.
No, I am! I'm an idiot
because I thought
that you actually cared
and you don't care about any of it.
You don't care about the meeting,
or about your future. None of it!
I'm trying to do some research
before my big meeting.
Get out of my car.
- Seriously?
- This is not a joke.
Get out of my car.
Out...
of my car.
I don't appreciate being laughed at.
I was just trying to help.
Get out of my car.
OK, but...
- I don't have my coat.
- Get out of my car, Tim!
- So if I get a cold...
- You're drunk, so you'll be warm.
I got the playoffs.
I might get sick!
Shut the door!
You actually gonna leave?
For real?
OK, seriously, it's cold.
I don't understand.
You're still going to Houston...
Houston's in three weeks.
Screw Houston.
OK, you know what?
We need to get out
of this hotel room.
Let's go get something to eat,
I'm starving.
We're not going to get
something to eat.
- You're acting like a little baby!
- I'm acting like a baby?
- Yes, 2 grand is a lot of money!
- Two grand's not enough money!
Look, I'm sorry, but...
you know that guy I was getting
heated with the other day?
That's 'cause I owe him
a lot of money.
And if I don't pay him back, guess
what's gonna happen. Can you guess?
Can you fathom all that?
Thank you.
- How much money?
- A lot more than 2 grand, all right?
This isn't high school.
This is the real world, Tyra!
- How dare you talk to me like that!
- What am I gonna say?
You want me to sugarcoat this?
'Cause this is what's really happening!
You know what?
Don't worry about it,
I'll figure it out...
- Where're you going?
- I'm gonna get some fresh air.
Dammit!
Should I turn my chair?
Is this gonna be...
No, you just look at me. OK,
associate editor of the school paper,
volunteer tutor, and you're also
in the Physics Club, right?
Technically, not anymore,
'cause there was only two of us,
me and one other person.
- But I did start the Physics Club.
- All right, great, great!
- What's your GPA?
- It's actually a 4.6,
but are we gonna talk
about football, 'cause I'm on...
Oh yeah, but this is good stuff,
this whole student athlete angle
is very inspiring.
Sorry, can I take this for one second?
Hello?
- It'll be just one second.
- Sure.
It's... It's me.
What are you doing?
I'm just getting ready to do
this interview... thing, here.
Really? You're gonna do an interview?
They're doing this thing for the
Panthers, so they asked me to do it.
So that's what I'm doing.
What are you doing?
Where are you at?
Well...
I'm actually in Dallas.
Cash had a rodeo,
so I came with him.
It's, um...
It's raining, here.
- Is everything all right or...
- Yeah!
Everything's fine.
I just...
- I wanted to hear a familiar voice.
- You know,
April Keegan is
frantically searching for you.
She wants to get a theme
straightened out for the dance,
she keeps bugging me about it,
- so it'd be nice if you talked to her.
- I'm sorry.
I know. I'll get on that,
I'll call her.
It'll be my next priority.
- 'Cause I know...
- Mr. Clarke?
Can I get one more second? I'll be
right over. We're about to start?
- Do you need to go?
- It's OK. I think it's fine.
I don't want you to miss
your big interview. You should go.
You sure?
I'm fine. Everything's fine.
I just, you know...
Break a leg!
All right, bye.
What up, Garrity?
Hey, Mindy.
I heard about you and Billy.
I'm sorry.
What happened?
He's a dumbass,
that's what happened.
- Right.
- Wanted me to quit working.
Really?
And I'm like, all right, genius,
so you're gonna support us now?
That boy hasn't held a job for more
than a month since I've known him.
Yeah, well, they're both idiots.
Big plan in the future for them is like,
what kind of beer they want on Sunday.
- Trouble in paradise with Wonderboy?
- Yeah, we're in a fight.
We're in a fight, because...
he had this recruiter interested in him,
he kept blowing him off and just...
He's just... being typical Riggins.
- So you're not going to the game?
- No.
No game.
Feel like hanging out?
Tonight, only one team survives.
It's win, or go home.
With four victories needed
to reach the ultimate dream,
the Texas state football title.
It's the SHSC High School
Football Game of the Week,
and tonight, the Dillon Panthers
host the Arnett Mead Tigers.
It appears the glare
of this national spotlight
has these Dillon receivers
dazed and confused.
Incomplete on a busted route,
and the Panthers are forced to punt.
Todd Jenkins is really struggling
with this spread offense tonight, folks.
Arnett Mead over the ball...
Inside hand-off,
he cuts to the outside, he's got a lane!
He's got a cut in, touchdown!
Reservation for six,
Arnett Mead, touchdown.
Let's go now, let's go!
Panthers back on offense.
J.D. McCoy takes the snap,
he steps back...
he's got Bird
on the dig route, fires...
Oh, my!
- What the hell is he doing?
- What are you doing? Get over here!
Get outta there!
Get him outta there,
give Riggins the ball!
- Run the damn ball!
- How many times did you run this play?
Just step around, just clear.
All you gotta do is clear!
McCoy opens right.
It's a drive to Riggins,
cuts through the hole,
he's got a lane!
Panthers down inside the 30.
McCoy on the pitch,
it's Riggins going wide right,
powers through...
Down he goes, and Riggins
has the Panthers in the red zone.
Take it.
It's up, and it's right through
the middle, folks.
That makes the score
7 to 3, Arnett Mead, at the half.
And thank goodness for Tim Riggins,
because the Panther aerial attack
has been completely MIA tonight.
You're blowing your cover,
letting them get all over you,
you're like this. Just sweep off,
that's all you had to do!
We do that block, defense will bunch up,
we'll shut down, OK?
You understand?
All right, we go no huddle?
... mistakes, you understand?
We're losing right now!
Listen up, listen up!
Two minutes till we go out.
Y'all wanna end this season?
Pack your bags, just go home,
you know where the door is.
Otherwise, I suggest you wake up
and get your heads in this game.
This defense is not gonna carry
this team all night long.
The offense has got to execute.
Or else, I guarantee you...
our season ends tonight.
Understood?
- Yes, sir.
- I can't hear you.
Yes, sir!
Let's go show me something then!
Matt! Come here!
And here come the Panthers,
and this is interesting...
Looks like backup quarterback
Matt Saracen
is in the game at wide receiver.
Now we talked about this
in the open votes. Maybe...
- Are you seeing this?
- Oh yes, there's Matt, look at him!
It is! We gotta go!
I'm gonna get my coat.
- Can you get that blanket?
- Yeah. This is so great!
- He didn't think he was gonna play.
- You know what? Tickets.
Doesn't matter. Jerry's in my
Sunday school class, he'll let us in.
- We have no problem for the tickets.
- Get your coat on right now!
Wait a minute! I can handle it.
- Heavens to Betsie!
- I know...
I can do this myself.
Let's go.
Come on!
Here we go!
7, up!
Go, Saracen!
Third quarter,
Panthers with the ball.
McCoy steps back,
he fires across the middle, he's got...
Saracen has the ball!
Big hit!
Oh, he held on!
That boy held on
like he was holding on to his mama!
First down, Panthers.
McCoy back to pass,
he's looking deep.
No, it's a shovel pass to Riggins!
He's got some open field,
one man to beat!
Saracen makes a huge block!
Touchdown, Panthers!
The Panthers are scoring here
in the second half
and Matt Saracen is making
the difference out there, folks.
We're late in the 4th quarter,
time is running out for Arnett Mead.
The Panthers have to get a first down
and this game is in the bag.
It's a hand-off to Riggins
up the middle.
Chris Cagen makes the stop.
And that's gonna bring up
fourth down and a long seven
as Arnett Mead
calls its last time-out.
Coach, let's just punt it, we're way out
of field-goal range. Good job, good try.
It's decision time
for Coach Taylor and these Panthers.
They have to get this first down,
or Arnett Mead will get the ball back
in great field position.
Coach Olep, let's go for it.
Let's go.
- Coach, that's quite risky!
- Let's go for it.
- Side right, 44, fire.
- Side right, 44, fire?
That's you, 7!
- Side right, 44, fire.
- All right, you heard him, let's go!
You catch and we're done!
And here we go!
It is white-knuckle time
as Dillon is going for it, fourth down
and the game
hanging in the balance.
Saracen has the ball.
He shakes the tackler,
stays on his feet!
He stretches out!
I don't know if he made it, folks!
He might be short!
First down!
Panthers have it, folks!
They will not have
to run another play.
Panthers win, Panthers win!
It was the right call.
Good call.
There you go, baby.
There you go.
I didn't know ya'll were coming.
- You were so great, I'm proud of you.
- Thanks.
- When did y'all get here?
- A long time ago.
You guys came together?
Count five, Queen bets, round.
Last card, gentlemen.
Pair of tens.
All right, call.
- Aces win.
- I'm busted, damn.
Look, I need more.
- You're into us kind of deep...
- Gimme more!
- You know I'm good for it.
- I can't do it.
Really?
This is how it's gonna be.
Afraid so.
The hell with you all!
- I'll get some cash and I'll be back.
- You get some cash, come on back.
- Are we going?
- No. Sit down! I didn't say, "get up."
Sit down in that chair
and I'll be back.
Why are we rushing out so fast?
They wanna interview you in there.
- What are you up to?
- Just get in the car...
- You're very sneaky.
- You're being very suspicious.
If you're not taking me
to the party,
that would be the best birthday present
I could ever ask for.
- Get in the car.
- OK.
- That, and a clicker for the lock.
- You think a clicker is a good thing?
I don't want you to weasel booze,
this time. Bring your own, you know?
- Can we go get something first?
- We're not getting food right now.
- Tim!
- It doesn't matter, I was just saying.
- Congratulations.
- How're you doing?
- You played a heck of a game.
- Thank you.
- They kept it pretty interesting.
- Yeah, they did.
Look, about last night,
I'm sorry I couldn't make it.
- Something just...
- Don't even worry about it.
Here's the deal.
Coach Powers called me
about you again today.
He said you are
number one priority right now.
- Really?
- Yeah, quote unquote.
How about you let me buy you a quick pop
and you keep me from losing my job?
I love that. You are...
I love you, honey. Look at...
Thank you.
Look at this beautiful...
Everything with the rose petals...
Honey, look!
Hotel robes.
- Something to steal!
- I love it.
We can steal 'em.
How exciting.
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
This is the only birthday party
I could have ever wanted.
Maybe we should take a shower,
wash some of that game dirt off...
put the robes on...
Hold on, let me just get that
in case it's Jules.
Or Tyra.
I don't know, I better...
I just...
- Mrs. Taylor?
- Yeah.
- It's Tyra.
- Hey, Tyra.
What's going on?
I'm sorry to bother you so late,
but, um...
I'm in a little bit of trouble.
What's going on?
What's the matter?
- Please don't be mad, but...
- I won't be mad. What's happening?
- I'm in Dallas right now.
- What are you doing there?
I came here with Cash,
but now he's gone.
I don't know where he's at,
and I don't have any money.
And my mama's out of town,
and I can't get ahold of Mindy,
- and I didn't know who else to call...
- I don't like that look.
OK. Well, you know what?
Listen.
What do you need from me?
Sorry, can you come and pick me up?
Yeah, I mean...
Yeah, hon. Where are you right now?
Are you some place safe?
I'm at the Econo Lodge
at LBJ and Central.
Can you stay there?
Can you lock the door?
- Yes, ma'am.
- All right. You just stay put, OK?
We'll jump in the car
and come get you.
And you just stay there,
and keep your cell phone right by you
'cause I'll need to call you, OK?
OK. I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
You just stay tight. Don't move,
all right? I'll see you soon.
OK, bye.
- Maybe we can still take a shower.
- Honey...
I'm so sorry. What else can we do?
Honey, I'm taking the champagne,
I'm taking every bit...
- of this chocolate.
- Gotta get some coffee.
- Get the chocolate, that's important.
- I'm taking all of these things.
I read this article in Cosmo.
"More pearls, less swine." It's about
bad dating habits and how to break 'em.
- I've read that one.
- Shut up! That list
of toxic signs?
I swear to God, Billy's ten for ten.
"Does he put his happiness
before yours?" Check.
It's true, maybe you gotta...
let the loser go.
That's a great idea.
I think that you should...
I think that you should move on!
I mean, do you know
how much time I have wasted
on Tim Riggins?
But I have to focus on me.
- I'm going to Vanderbilt next year...
- Shut up! You got in?
No...
but I will.
OK. Well,
I don't know where that is,
but it sounds fancy pants
and I have a little present for you.
- You know that I really like this song?
- This is...
mom's favorite
man-hater breakup music.
It makes me wanna dance.
Yeah, it gets a lot of playing time
around here.
- To man hating. Ready?
- OK.
I love this!
It's so good.
You know this, right here,
what this is?
An anti-Riggins force field.
There ain't no...
- Billy in my chili, yo.
- No Billy in your chili.
- What was that move you were doing?
- Thought I'd, like...
Mindy!
Oh, God!
Now, shake it!
Shake it up!
Shake it! Shake it!
What is that?
What are you doing?
No, no!
- Mindy, come on, open up.
- I gotta go pee.
- I can totally see you.
- Go away, Billy! Nobody likes you!
Come on, open up!
- It's a Riggins brother.
- Come on, baby. I'm sorry.
You can go back to your job,
I don't care.
I just want you back.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
I love you.
Give me one more chance, please.
No, no!
Mindy, no!
- Oh, Mindy.
- Shut up, shut up!
- Don't ever leave me.
- I'm not gonna leave you.
- What's that tape?
- Love that music,
- you still don't like it.
- No, that music is awful, honey.
... I said the Hilton,
I didn't say the Woodson.
- Wait, slow down.
- Why? I got the money.
- I don't care.
- I'll pay 'em back.
I don't care.
You left me with all those men.
- I said I was coming back!
- I don't care!
Damn it! Tyra!
We're talking about this!
You're not leaving.
Damn it, Tyra!
Tyra, sit down!
- Help me, please!
- No, I'm not letting you leave.
Easy.
- Damn it, Tyra!
- Get in the car, get in.
Tyra, please!
Baby, I'm sorry.
- Calm down a second.
- I'm not calming down.
Tyra, please, come on!
- Get in the car.
- Let me explain.
I'm sorry.
Come on, babe.
- Damn it, Tyra. I'm sorry.
- All right? Easy now.
Damn it!
Tyra, come on.
Son of a bitch!
You all right?
Yes, ma'am.
Really?
Thank you.
7 = 5x + 4...
- What are you doing?
- Calculus.
I got you something.
I did a little research
and found out that most of the colleges
have January 15th
as the deadline for fall admission.
Yeah, I think... I think Mr. Shea
said something about that.
You can fill out
your application online
and that still gives you a whole month
to get transcripts, write the essay...
You can still do it, Matt.
Yeah, but what am I gonna do
about grandma?
I'm sure we could work
something out.
OK, but then, how am I supposed
to pay for it?
We could rob a bank.
I drive the getaway car, you go in,
grandma covers the door.
There's an image!
I don't know,
we'll figure out the money thing, too.
There's still scholarships
for children of the military.
That's an option.
It's gotta be good
to get the ball rolling, you know.
Yeah, you're probably right.
There was one of them that had...
this really great
Fine Art Department.
This one, in San Francisco.
Come on, catch the football.
There you go.
It's alive!
I thought I was gonna have
to send in Search and Rescue.
- Dad, you don't have to yell...
- It's already
beer thirty in here. What are you
doing, with sleeping so late?
Let's see.
It's not your mother,
I don't have any friends...
Who could that be?
I got it.
I'll bet I know.
What are you doing?
- What do you want?
- Wanna come outside and play with me?
- Why don't you wanna play?
- Tim, I'm not in the mood for this.
OK, I got in.
- You got in what?
- I'm in. College, in.
I'm in college.
I'm going to college.
I met with the recruiter, I sat down,
we filled out some paperwork,
he said I'm in. There's more paperwork
to be done, but apparently,
even some half-scholarship,
or even more, I don't even know yet.
But I'm in.
Still nothing.
Do you need me to say you were right
and I was wrong? Cause you were right.
It's not working yet, is it?
Let me cover my bases here.
One,
I'm sorry.
Two, I mean it,
I'm really sorry.
Three, thank you.
Four, I wanna go celebrate.
I only want to celebrate with you,
'cause I wouldn't be here without you.
Five, say yes. At this point,
come on. I'll keep going.
- Did you really get in?
- Yes.
Only Riggins to get in, yet.
Probably the last.
I knew you would.
I told you.
Kinda crazy.
That's great.
Hey, because of you.
I'm in because of you.
So, yeah, you can...
Are you on a bender right now?
I almost got a buzz
off your breath, there.
That's, like, I don't think
it's safe for me to drive strong
right now, and for me to say that,
that's a lot, you know.
- Sorry.
- Don't be, it's fantastic.
Let me get drunk then.
I'll come with you, I'm on board.
I'm on board.
I found Matt and Julie
in bed together this afternoon.
You're, like,
this young, wholesome,
milk-drinking quarterback.
There we go.
I took the savings money
and made a risky investment,
- and I lost the money.
- So I'll get a job
and I'll help out
until I go to college.
Lyla, I used the college money.