That's why I'm here, Coach.
My boy, J.D,
he is the real deal.
He is a great quarterback
and I want him mentored
by a great coach.
And that is why I moved my family
to Dillon, Texas.
If you only did what you wanted to do
your life'd be all about football,
beer and sex, wouldn't it?
- What's the problem with that?
- Letter of interest from Oklahoma.
You didn't tell me
you were getting interest from colleges.
We're talking about
the rest of your life.
And maybe, if you're really nice to me,
I might give you a ride to school.
Will you marry me?
Damn, let's call it.
Women can eat.
And you, what the hell
are you doing ordering a Bronco?
- That's like a $30 steak, man.
- Do you want to remind your soul mate
not to point out to everyone in the
restaurant who she gave a lap dance to?
Kinda made Lyla feel uncomfortable.
- You're so whipped, it's pathetic.
- Where are we, anyways?
I got a business meet.
What do you mean?
What kind of business meet?
Gotta get us a little scratch together.
Get us out of this hole.
If we're so broke, why do you keep
picking up all these checks, Trump?
What do you want me to do, dumbass?
Have my fiancee's mom paid for it?
- Why not?
- See, you're an idiot, that's why not.
Hey, Lou, how are you doing?
How about next time you call?
Who is he?
It's my brother.
Don't worry about him, man, he's cool,
he ain't gonna say nothing to anyone.
Wait out here.
Watch the target.
Keep it coming.
Roll around, roll around.
- That's it.
- How long has he looked that good?
I'll tell you, Wade has made
a great difference in J.D's game.
Arnett Mead's gonna be coming after you.
They're gonna be making it personal.
You stay light on your feet,
read the blitz, keep the tone up.
- You're gonna be fine.
- Yes, sir.
Line 'em up. Don't hit one.
- Good job, really good.
- Thank you, Coach.
Hey, they flew that coach down
from Dallas with him.
Square fire.
Hey, Buddy.
You listen to me.
That is not my quarterback, you're
my quarterback, you understand that?
I want you concentrated on Friday night.
You go out there and you play with what
we've taught you, what you know.
Everything is gonna go just fine.
- Yes, sir.
- Go warm-up the arm.
Let's go.
Let's go gentlemen, bring it up.
Hey, Coach.
Thanks for letting us use the field
earlier, I really appreciate that.
All right, circle it up.
Didn't know you were gonna
bring along cheerleading section.
They just want to see him
throw the ball, you know...
I know everyone is talking about
switching to the spread offense
for that Arnett Mead game and I want you
to know I support your decision 100%.
- I appreciate that.
- But...
I also want you to know
that if you do decide
to switch to the spread, J.D. is ready.
J.D. will light it up.
You know what?
I only got these boys until 8.
How about you clear those cones off?
Sure enough.
Let's go, gentlemen, stretch it out.
3x03: HOW THE OTHER HALF LIVES
Subtitles: Team Panthers
With the participation of:
benj!, DarKsh, GillesSilb,
Ju, loky34, ouazo, Teardrop
Buddy, I don't give two farts
about the booster's anxiety,
I'm not gonna choose my quarterback
by committee.
I don't even know why
we're having this conversation.
Fine, you tell 'em that it is gonna be
my decision. End of conversation. Done.
Goodbye.
What's wrong with people?
Tell me about it.
I gotta throw a party for them.
We win first 2 games this season
and everyone is breathing down my neck.
You think 200 cups is gonna be enough?
You know that Joe McCoy spends
thousands of dollars a month on his son
- for a quarterback coach.
- Thousand of dollars is what this party
- is gonna cost us.
- Did Julie take the keys again?
Maybe next year we could think about
not having this party at our house.
- What are you talking about?
- I don't think our house is big enough.
And those boys are slobs, they get
the corn chips all over the floor,
they clog my toilet,
they break my things.
- At this point, it's a lot of work.
- Listen to me, I understand, please.
Look...
Next year, I promise...
Maybe, we'll have it
somewhere else, all right?
Did I tell you
how sexy you look today?
Did I tell you that
you're the best friend,
mother, and lover
that a man has ever had?
I need your truck,
I have to pick up your ribs.
You can have my truck
as soon as you can find the keys.
So, you think I should call him?
No, don't call him.
You're supposed
to let him come to you.
You got to get your head
on straight.
I mean, the Smash ain't gonna be around
to give all his free advice.
- You're just nervous about next week.
- Smash don't get nervous.
He gets ready.
She's not here.
Miss, time to get up from there,
come on help me. Get up your butt and...
I think you got the wrong information
'cause my mom already has a job.
What are you doing?
Give me this phone.
This is she.
Yeah, Saturday would be just fine.
All right, bye-bye.
What was that all bout?
- You're taking another job?
- Yes, it's no big deal.
Just some home health care
on the weekend.
- Like changing bedpans?
- What do you think nurses do?
Sit around and flirt
with doctors all day?
Why are you taking a second job?
Well, you're going to A&M,
who's gonna pay for this?
- No, mama...
- No, no mama nothing.
It's just a situation, baby.
We're gonna make it work.
Bring the rest of these groceries
so I can get this dinner started, baby.
No, I ordered 20 racks of ribs. Not 2.
I had somebody special on the phone.
- I don't know anything about it.
- I talked to a woman.
Maybe it... Could that be her? I'm sure
there must be somebody around here...
Excuse me, I just need
2 New York Strips. Real fast!
You know what? Can we get through this?
Sorry, I'm in the middle of something.
I'm telling you, I only have
2 racks of ribs, lady.
Don't call me lady, I hate that.
Thanks so much.
I did speak to somebody.
Is there another woman?
{\- Maybe you got some pounds in the back.
- }I'm gonna check in the back.
- Either way, anything will work for me.
- You got it.
Atkins diet?
It made me real cranky, too.
- Sorry, I don't...
- Never mind.
You're principal Taylor,
I'm Katy McCoy.
My son goes to your school.
- Oh, J.D, right.
- Yeah.
Nice to meet you. I'm sorry if I was
a little rude, I got to get those ribs.
No, you're kidding, I think it's hot.
I like a woman
that speaks her mind.
I do.
You know what?
Speaking of which, I'd like to come by,
visit with you
and talk about getting involved.
- What do you want get involved in?
- I would like my son to go
to a school that has enough books,
maybe even a music program.
I know, you and me both
but you know, it's...
There's a money issue,
you know, so it's...
That's what I mean
about getting involved.
See we got a little bit of money
and I'd like to give some of that away.
But I also love to throw parties, right?
And get other people to come
and give some of their money away.
I'm a connector... Ever read
The Tipping Point of Malcolm...
- What's his name?
- I don't think...
A connector{\ is somebody
who} knows everyone
and brings them all together
to get things done.
- Neat!
- Yeah, that's me.
Now what's a little thing like you
doing with 20 racks of ribs?
It's a long story... You know...
My husband...
Don't make it obvious.
Seven o'clock.
Creep.
Don't make it obvious.
Tim, stop it.
Seriously, I can't focus.
- It's a library.
- I know it's a library.
- You win, buddy. He wins.
- No, wait, Tim, stop.
Please?
You're gonna work
on this thing and...
you're gonna ace this test and...
you're gonna improve your grades
and you're gonna get a scholarship.
And we're gonna go to colleges
that are really close to each other.
You are coming over
tomorrow night, correct?
- Mindy and Angela are gonna be there.
- OK, no Mindy, what... No.
I don't know if you notice or not,
but Mindy and Angela hate me.
What?
They don't hate you.
They don't even know you.
If they did, they'd love you.
And you know what?
Somebody...
wants his girlfriend to be there.
Okay? And you know what?
If they even look at you wrong,
and you don't see it and I do?
I'm gonna blindsight them
with the worst...
block they'll have ever seen.
So, what I want...
from you right now
is for you to say,
"Yes, Tim,
"I can't wait to see you and hang out
with you tomorrow night."
Just... That's what I want from you.
So... Just give me that much.
Perfect.
Okay, really? Still...
You're still...
- Honey?
- Hey, babe.
Hey, honey.
Guess what?
I just met Katy McCoy
at the grocery store.
You know, Joe McCoy's wife.
And she is so nice.
I think she's gonna be really
a great asset to Dillon.
And the best part is, she has agreed
to do the whole barbecue at their house.
Done and done.
Don't eat those sad beans.
I bought Marcello's.
I don't want Marcello's.
What is it you said about the barbecue?
I was telling her
how difficult it's been,
how much work it's been
and how I don't have time for it.
And she said:
"Why don't I take it off your hands?"
Explain something to me.
How can we be a host...
of our barbecue at their house?
Isn't the definition of hosting
when you have something
at your own house?
Well... I think it's like co-hosting.
What the hell is co-hosting?
This is my barbecue.
It's funny that you say that.
I've been the one doing all the work.
But...
You know...
This time of the year,
there's a lot of scrutiny going on
I can tell you that I don't plan to be
in someone else's house being
scrutinized. I wanna be right here.
- Right here.
- You are not the only one
who has been scrutinized.
And I frankly would rather
not be scrutinized in my own house.
This reaction surprises me.
This morning you said
we could do the barbecue
somewhere else.
Next year we could. I was telling you
what you wanted to hear, anyway.
And as far as this barbecue...
It's not just important to me.
It's a symbol of trust
to have the kids over here at the house
so they can be in our home
and feel welcome.
And you're being played right now
and you don't even realize it.
That is silly.
I don't even know what that means.
I tell you what it means.
It means scotch, cigars,
Now they got the party.
And the next thing you know
we are gonna be indebted to them.
I don't want that.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm not being played.
She's nice.
Set!
Blue 8!
Hut!
Oh, come on, Matt.
- Come on, now. Spread release.
- Yes, sir.
Square, baby!
There it is!
What are you doing?
Matt!
What you short-arming it for?
Loosen up.
Let's loosen up out here
and have some fun!
Come on, let's have some fun out here
and play some football!
Maybe we ought to get little JD
a few reps just in case.
Matt will take the reps.
- I'm just saying...
- Matt will take the reps.
It's my job, like you, too.
I'm not looking forward to U-haul
for sales signs at my yard
if we loose, too. You know what I mean?
Well, I'll bear that in mind, Mac.
Fine.
I'm trying to fight
this media machine JD McCoy.
He's got like a 3-page spread in there.
Well, it's the freshmen preview.
So that makes sense.
People like this.
- I don't wanna hear...
- But look, you don't have an angle.
Can you please just go away?
Go away, just leave.
So people know who you are,
and know what you gonna bring.
I'm just trying to help you.
His angle is that he's young, he's new.
I don't need an angle.
Who cares? No one cares.
He's not hip.
He's not hip. You heard him talk?
He's not hip. Hello how are you?
- I'm OK.
- I don't care.
I'll leave this here.
If you want to...
I'm gonna get a Coke.
Julie, how are you doing?
- Doing good?
- I'm good.
- See you later.
- Bye.
What's up with him?
He's an idiot.
He's stupid.
Half eaten tacos!
Those are all yours right there.
He won't mind.
He doesn't want them.
I'm pretty good.
So...
Big game, Friday?
It's huge.
Enormous.
Yeah, it might alter my life,
in fact.
Bad subject matter?
It's not...
This is...
I'm starting to worry about
beating Arnett Mead on Friday.
That's all I wanna be thinking about.
And that's hard.
I don't know if you're aware.
But we never beat Arnett Mead.
Not even Jason Street
ever beat Arnett Mead. Ever!
I'm trying to worry about that.
Meantime, I've got some freshman named
Joe Doyle breathing down my neck.
If I hear anyone talk about this
70-yard pass he threw, ever again,
I'm gonna loose it, because...
I don't even care, he was in practice.
There wasn't defenders.
I can throw a ball 70 yards
when no one is running at me.
It's hard to do...
- Sorry, you don't care about this.
- No! I do care. I asked.
No, you shouldn't.
I'm just ranting. I apologize.
You're really adorable when you rent.
Thanks.
Are you gonna eat your tacos?
I didn't come over here to eat tacos.
Brian, they told me
I'd probably find you back here.
Hey, Mr. Pollid.
What's up?
I came here to see you.
I was wondering if you thought
about a future with Alamo Freeze.
Honestly, sir.
No, I have not.
We're impressed with you.
You're smart, you're reliable.
The employees like you.
The management likes you.
And the company is expanding.
We're opening 4 new stores.
And we need a regional manager
to oversee them.
Well, sir...
I don't know...
It's a $10,000 raise to start.
Plus bonuses and a company car.
Brand new.
For real?
Think about it.
I think it's just
a really good fit for both of us.
All right?
- All right. We'll see you.
- Hey, thanks.
Let's have a margarita bar
around the pool.
- We all should have some fun.
- Amen to that.
I love that idea.
Maybe we could play some silly games
like "Toss the orange".
- Hey, how you doing?
- Hi, hon.
- This is Katy McCoy, my husband Eric.
- Nice to meet you.
Pleasure to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you.
Pleasure to meet you as well.
As far as the games
and the barbecue and everything,
I mean just to let you know that
the important thing is
getting everyone ready
for the Arnett Mead game.
Right. Sorry. I guess I just got
a little carried away.
No, that's all right. That's fine.
I've got some work to do.
Hon, could you?
There's a little dirty diaper
that would love to say
"hi and welcome home".
- Oh, OK.
- Hi Daddy.
Bye sweet angel.
Now, you're gonna feel better.
- Goodbye.
- Thanks, honey. I appreciate that.
He's mad at me
cause I took the barbecue?
I really appreciate you're doing this.
I really appreciate
you're doing this at your house.
Making it so I don't have to have
all these mean boosters yelling at me
about the jumbotron in my house.
You know what this is?
Grown pains.
Honey, it's great, but...
Do we really need this many people?
Cousin Floyd isn't bringing Vicky.
They split up.
Big surprise. So that's one less.
Keep him away
from my friends at the club...
- Hey!
- Oh, yes mama.
- High school memories.
- I'm dying. Gimme one, please.
- I'm dying over here.
- Angela? Beer?
Thank you, Timmy.
Timmy, I want you to hear this.
You too, Lyla. It is our vows
to each other. Mine of course only,
- cause Billy hasn't written his.
- I'll get to it.
Ready? Billy Riggins...
No one has ever stuck with me
so long before.
It's there. I know it is, because
when I look at you, I can feel it.
When I look at you, I'm home.
I don't want that to go away.
I don't want to forget.
Come here.
That's Finding Nemo, right?
I don't think it's very nice
to laugh about it, honey.
Oh, no, no, no.
I thought it was a joke. Sorry.
I thought it was a joke.
I'm sorry. I think it's great.
I really do.
I think it's really romantic.
What's your problem, Garrity?
- What's that?
- I'm saying I think it's great.
I love Finding Nemo.
Where are you going?
There's somebody outside.
I can't...
Damn it, Falcon!
- Wait. Rehab Falcon?
- Shut up, OK?
I gotta deal with this real quick.
I'll be back in a second. It was...
It's real pretty.
It was very pretty.
Finding Nemo has great messages...
Finding love, and family.
Tim, tell them how much
I love Finding Nemo.
Sweet fish.
I'm sorry that
my daughter's wedding vows aren't up
to Garrity standards,
but then, not much is.
I'll be right back.
- Where are you going?
- It is not everybody's taste.
- You guys just let it go.
- Of course. It's only my wedding.
You know, you stop being
your little princess.
- Jackass!
- Alright. What's going on?
Nothing.
- What's going on?
- I just lost my wingman.
There is this abandoned power plant
out by Route 6. It's...
They got copper wire out there,
and copper wire is worth a lot of money.
- So we were gonna go out there...
- And steal it.
You're kidding me.
No, Lou set the whole thing up.
He's got the truck for me.
All I gotta do is get out there,
grab the stuff, and then I'm home free.
What about cops?
I mean...
You go down Route 6.
That's gonna be littered with cops,
and speed traps.
You should just take Pans Road.
At least, that gives you
a backway out of there.
You're right.
That's just...
That's good.
And much better than
Falcon would do.
What?
Forget it, Tim.
- OK.
- Look, hey, hey. Come on. Look.
I really need this, man.
It'll be 2 hours
- and no danger whatsoever.
- I got a barbecue tomorrow night.
- 8 o'clock. Team function.
- Can't do it. No.
Where is everybody going?
Please don't go.
- See you later.
- What happened?
We are going home where life
is just not so pussy and judgy.
- What happened?
- I said I'm sorry.
- Come on, Tyra.
- Thanks a lot, Lyla.
- Shut up, Billy.
- Nice girlfriend, Tim.
Thanks for throwing the block, Tim.
Mindy, I call you.
I don't even know what's going on,
right now. What just happened?
- Don't drive away.
- Watch your feet.
This gotta be it, right here.
1512...
Wow! That is a big house.
Looks like a sanatorium.
A sanatorium?
This is just gonna really boost
Matt Saracen's confidence. Fantastic!
It's got nothing to do with Saracen.
He's gonna have a good time.
They got valet.
Oh my Lord!
- Good evening...
- I'll park it, thank you.
- There's no charge, sir.
- I know,
- I'll park it.
- That's what they do...
- I know. I'll park it. Thank you.
- That's what the valet's for.
And make sure they have food all times.
We don't want hungry guests.
Hey y'all!
Hey you!
Look at you!
You're the sexiest principal
on the planet.
- You look great!
- Look at this beautiful house!
I'm gonna be monopolizing her
all evening. So you go find the fellas.
Mr. Shepard, how you doing?
What's the plan for Friday?
Tim is gonna show up late
at the party?
He's not even... I'm taking you
to the party. What is that?
- Something with his brother.
- What?
He's got something
with his brother.
What is it?
I don't know.
Well...
It's a lot different than it used to be
back in the olden days.
If a guy was gonna take a date
to a party, then...
I mean, I'd take her to the party.
- Dad listen. I know you don't like him.
- No, honey. I like him.
I do. It's just some things
I know about him
that you don't know.
Honey, listen.
Your daddy just...
doesn't want you
to have a broken heart. That's all.
He isn't who you're thinking,
alright?
- Alright?
- Alright. Alright.
Holy shoot!
Come on. Let's go!
- Wait, wait, wait.
- What?
What the hell is that?
- That's dogs! Go, Billy!
- Get in the truck!
There they go.
They're gone. They're gone.
When Tim was so hungover for kick-off.
You remember that man?
He shows up at the stadium at 8:30.
They wouldn't even let him in.
- He had to scalp a ticket to get in.
- Riggins is a beast, man.
This is a huge house.
Probably the biggest in Dillon,
Hello. I think, you forget about
the Saracen estate.
I'm a little offended, actually.
But that's fine.
I just keep forgetting, cause it's
2 different sections.
You have the north wing
and you have the south wing.
Actually, it's the east wing,
and the west...
wing.
- Look at this.
- It's like a giant shrine to JD.
Oh my gosh. Look at this one.
It's from 1999.
That would make him... 6.
Seems a little extreme.
Why did he put all these
participation trophies up in here?
Even the fat kids get these!
Hey man!
Sorry we were just...
You know, they actually bronzed
my first diaper.
It's kind of... I can show it to you
if you want. It's in the garage.
That was awkward.
So, Tim gonna show?
I know he's coming.
He just had a thing...
- A thing.
- with his brother or something.
Rally girl and a free 6 pack
on his way.
Sorry. I did not mean that.
It's okay.
- Hey baby.
- Hi daddy.
- Hi Tyra.
- Hi.
- Hi daddy.
- Do you need me to take you home?
- No, I'm fine.
- You're okay?
- Yeah.
Just let me know if you need anything.
Okay. I'll be with the boosters.
- Let me know if you need anything.
- I'm fine.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Help me with this.
Hold on a second.
What?
Let's get the other 3.
- Come on, man.
- No, Billy.
I'm already late for the party.
Plus I promised Lyla I'd be there...
Forget about Lyla for 2 seconds.
I'm your brother, okay?
I know you're my brother, Billy.
But I don't feel like getting busted
cause you wanna take Mindy and her mom
- out for a nice steak dinner.
- You think this is what it's about?
- I do think it's what it's about.
- I need this. Okay?
I need this.
I got a second chance here, Tim.
Maybe start a little business.
Have a decent life.
Ain't no football games
or rally girls for me anymore.
I'll never ask you for anything else
ever again. So help me God!
But, please...
I need this.
Get down, get down! Get down!
Unbelievable...
Let's load 'em up!
Oh, here he is.
Here he is.
- Hey, Buddy.
- Good shot! Can we crash the party?
Not my party.
- How you doing?
- Good. Having a good time?
- I am having a good time.
- Good.
- Wayne, it's a pleasure to meet you.
- Nice meeting you.
- I've heard a lot about you.
- Likewise.
I'm gonna go ahead
inside this real quick.
I wanna get it out of the way.
Cause we've been talking about it.
I just wanna know.
What do you think about the spread?
What he's trying to say is we wish
you'd think more about the run issue.
Most 5A schools
are going spread, now.
I think you need the right person
to run that kind of offense.
You're saying you don't think
you have the guys?
I don't think we're ready to install
something like that is what I'm saying.
Well Coach, I don't know.
Maybe you just need a shot.
Wait, I don't know...
what you're being paid.
But I'm not paying you.
- So I don't really need your opinion.
- We're just talking about football.
Eric, just admit...
Look, JD...
is a great little quarterback.
He's got a great arm. Great feet.
- You can admit that.
- Is it what you want me to admit?
Well, that's easy to do.
I admit that your son
is an incredible 15 year old.
Most of the kids out there
hit puberty about 5 years ago.
Your son hit it about a month ago,
as far as I can tell.
I know Matt Saracen.
I don't know your son.
Then I would say
this would be an ideal time
for you to get to know my son.
Why don't you just
give me a chance?
- You have a good night.
- Alright, alright.
Thank you very much for the party.
That was fun!
That house is gorgeous.
And that chocolate fountain.
Did you have some of that?
- That was so good!
- Chocolate fountain.
I even had some boosters
be nice to me.
Of course a lot of them were
staring daggers in the back of my head.
I could feel that.
I spent my whole time
getting my ear chewed off about...
Matt Saracen...
Boy wonder...
I'm sorry you didn't have
a good time, honey.
You know who I miss?
I miss the Coach's wife.
You know who I can't wait to meet?
The Principal's husband.
Touché
It's Friday night, folks,
and if you're in Hermann Field
in Dillon, Texas,
you're exactly
where God wants you to be.
It's the Tigers of Arnett Mead
versus the Dillon Panthers,
in what should be
a real knock-down-and-drag-out.
It's about heart,
it's about commitment,
it's about who wants it more.
Alright, listen up, this is it.
Anyone doesn't think we can win,
he get the hell of my O-line, alright?
28-cross-5 on one, ready?
Coach Taylor is putting all his money
on quarterback Matt Saracen,
over the much ballyhooed JD McCoy.
And there is not a soul
sitting for this one, folks.
Saracen's back to pass,
he's on the pressure.
He fires...
He takes a hard hit,
but completes the pass to Tim Riggins
for a first down.
Saracen feints back to pass,
all the protection breaks down,
he's gotta scramble
A nifty move inside,
he's running off the left side line
to the 15...
And he's gonna be
out of bounds about...
He gets a late hit out of bounds.
How about a flag?
Coach Taylor is absolutely livid
after that late hit.
I'd guarantee that
he's gonna feel that one, tomorrow.
Saracen hands off to Riggins,
Saracen gets drilled again
and Riggins is heading
to the house, folks.
Touchdown, Panthers!
Saracen's tenacious play
has inspired his team.
That's nice, that's your game!
Yes, sir.
Arnett Mead comes out
that big spread offense.
He's back to pass.
He lets one fly,
he's got a man open...
Touchdown as Arnett Mead's
powerful pass in attack
has put them back in the lead.
It is an opens up.
It's a reverse option.
No, it's a late pass to Riggins.
Riggins leveled,
and Riggins is down...
Matt Saracen just keeps
taking it for the team!
All we have to do is stay in the I!
Saracen back to pass.
Pressure's coming.
He just gets rid of that ball.
He's got a man open.
Touchdown, Dillon Panthers!
We're back in this long one.
Arnett Mead back to pass.
He's looking deep.
Touchdown.
Arnett Mead takes the lead,
with less than two minutes left
in this contest.
Can you see all that?
Yes, good.
We're gonna get the ball back,
we need to take some more.
- You got one more in you?
- I always got one more.
Alright.
This is it.
The clock is running down,
it is all or nothing, here, folks.
Saracen brings him over the ball.
Touchdown, touchdown, no...
No, the ball has come out!
The ball is on the ground!
And Arnett Mead has it!
He didn't control that ball
going over the goal line,
that is not a touchdown,
and this game is over, folks!
A brave effort,
where the victory that was promised
was not to be.
The Dillon Panthers have lost.
I'm sorry,
I didn't know you...
I was just waiting for you.
I don't really want...
I was just trying to wait everyone out,
so I don't have to talk about the game.
We don't have to talk about the game
if you don't want to.
Or we can if you do.
No.
How about we go somewhere
and talk about anything but football?
That sounds good.
Cool.
They made me employee of the month
at Alamo Freeze.
Again.
There's some more pie in there,
you want it?
I'm not going to the walk-on
next week, mama.
What?
Alamo Freeze made me an offer.
They want me to be regional manager.
- It's a good job...
- Alamo Freeze...
Hell no.
Look, I've decided.
- And I'm gonna tell Coach tomorrow.
- All you gonna say is thank you.
After all that man has done for you.
He could've lost his job, Brian.
This is not
what it was supposed to be.
I was supposed to buy you a house.
I didn't have kids
to buy me no house.
What is wrong with you?
I've done everything right.
I've done everything
I was supposed to do,
- and it's still not enough.
- We will keep doing things right.
That's what makes you a man.
The son I raised... is a man.
So, you're going to that try-out,
and you're going to play
like God made you do,
and you are going...
to go to that college.
- What if I don't take your help?
- You're gonna take my help.
I am your mother.
Maybe you'll get this scholarchip,
but if you don't, I'm going to help you!
You let me be your mama,
that is my job!
- I'll pay you back.
- You bet you will!
When you graduate.
And I wouldn't mind
seeing you play football again either.
I think you got game tape
to watch, don't you?
Hey, Mr. Garrity.
Is Lyla around?
Hello, Tim.
Yes, she's in there.
You got you a nice set of cojones,
coming over here
after standing her up like that.
Seriously,
it's not what you think.
Let me tell you something...
Dad, can I talk to him
for a second, please?
- Yes, honey.
- Thank you.
Please.
It's okay?
I screwed up,
I'm sorry.
So many people warned me about
getting into this with you.
You know what I tell them?
I tell them that
they don't know you like I do.
I tell them that you're a good guy.
You are, right?
You're a good guy.
Please, don't make a fool out of me.
I won't.
Come on, honey.
Listen closer,
like you've never listened to me before.
Right now, right here,
do what you do best.
Next week
on an all new Friday Night Lights.
Honey, it's obvious.
You're right, they're wrong.
Doesn't matter,
'cause I'm gonna lose tomorrow.
Do not keep throwing this to me.
Maybe I should have been clearer.
We're not together!
Yes, I'm choosing him.
Let's go, fellows.
We're gonna shake things up
on Friday night.