You can't assume too much about anything
from the outside.
Like a house... you have
to get inside and explore.
You never know
what you might find.
Hey, mom, i think
that this might be
one of our more successful
showings ever.
I found ham and that mustard
that i love so much.
And as usual,
i'm doing all the work.
You know, i should have
just left you in the car
with some water
and cracked a window.
Well,
i'm starving, okay?
- We have been here all day.
- We've been here 20 minutes!
I am just trying
to build a business
that we can be proud of.
But you know, i'm not angry.
I- i'm just disappointed.
Okay. I am not 5 years old.
Do you really think that
that's gonna work?
Because it's...
it's not gonna work.
Okay, fine.
I'll try harder. God!
You got mustard
on your face.
Go away from me!
Okay.
Hello. Welcome. I'm samantha.
- Would you please sign in?
- Lindsey.
Hi.
We really like the house.
Oh, good, good.
Let's see what we have here.
It's nice. It's, uh, very much
like one we're interested
- over in elk ridge.
- Elk ridge?
Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
- You do not want to live in elk ridge.
- Why? What's wrong with elk ridge?
What isn't
wrong with elk ridge?
Look, lindsey,
you seem a lot like me,
and walnut valley is really
the place for people like us.
People like us?
You mean because elk ridge
is a black neighborhood?
What? Wait. It is?
- As if you didn't know.
- No. I...
- people like you make me sick.
- No, i don't!
What did... what did i do?
- Roger?
- I don't understand what you're...
this is my husband.
Oh. Hi. Hello.
Look, i-i really...
i didn't know about elk ridge.
I've never even been there.
Okay? Not that i wouldn't
go there. It's just that...
look, i'm just trying
to sell you a house, okay?
I mean, i love black...
african... american...
black people.
You want a ham sandwich?
Wait a minute.
Ham... that's not offensive,
is it? Right? Mom!
I don't even
want to be doing this!
Samantha who 212
Synchro: Flolo
Transcript: yyets. net
They called me a racist.
I am not racist.
I voted obama, you know?
I- i watch "oprah. " My life
is full of black people.
Mrs. Butterworth...
she's technically black.
Do you actually know
any black people?
I feel like i know oprah.
So what? What, if i don't
know any black people,
then i'm automatically
a racist?
It's not like you have any black
friends, right? Uh, five. No, four now.
Shondra and i
had a falling out
when i didn't invite her
to my kwanzaa party, but...
don't look at me. I'm dating
tony dane... black and gay.
Two birds.
Wait a minute.
Before the accident, did i do
anything that was racist?
No. A black guy,
a white guy and two asians
were in the mailroom one day. Okay.
You fired them all.
Oh. I'm sorry. I thought
you were telling me a joke.
Ooh! Andrea,
your boyfriend's on tv!
Oh! Oh, turn it up, turn it up.
Maybe he'll mention me.
Well, it looks like
pro basketballer tony dane
is giving new meaning
to the term "swish. "
Caught here by paparazzi,
the great dane
is making a full-court press
on an unidentified
male companion.
Representatives for dane could
not be reached for comment,
but an unnamed source
within the organization
did confirm that thatho was taken last
night. Oh, my god. It's all over...
the private jets, thparties,
the club openings.
Oh, sweetie,
it's gonna be okay.
I- i'm sure you'll find another
gay guy to pretend to love you.
Not like this one.
Hey.
Ms. Newly.
Frank.
Frank! You're black!
Shh! Keep it quiet. I'm trying
to get off for passover.
No! No, i thought i didn't
have any black friends,
but you're black,
and we're friends.
No, ma'am.
No? 'cause you...
you seem kind of black.
I mean we are not friends.
Of course we are.
W- we see each other every day.
We talk. We're friends.
What's my last name?
It's, um...
where am i from?
What's my wife's name?
What's my son's name?
Marcello.
Close. I don't have a son.
Fine. I'm not sure what it is
you're doing, miss newly, but don't.
Friendships grow through time
and shared experiences.
You carry my groceries.
You sign for my packages.
I mean, if those aren't shared experiences,
then i... good night, ms. Newly.
Samantha.
Ms. Newly.
Frank, seriously,
you don't think we're friends?
Because that's
just not okay with me.
You know what?
I'm not gonna stop
until you and i are true-blue,
pick-me-up-in-the-middle-
of-the-night,
drive-me-to-the-airport,
hold-my-hair-back-when-i-puke
kind of friends.
But i've already done
all those things for you.
Not as friends.
Hey.
Oh, hey.
Look at that on your lip.
That's, uh, it's, uh...
oh, shoot, what is that called?
It's, um, it's like a mustache
but not one.
Joke all you want,
but you don't have a say in it.
You're not my girlfriend. And
apparently, you don't plan on having one.
Hi, frank. Wassup?
Hey, todd,
it's my friend frank.
Is there any reason why
you wouldn't come down
and sign for this? Because
all the fun is up here.
Come on. Join us.
We've got food,
and we have fun.
We got frank. It's "f" day.
I can think of many other words
that begin with "f,"
but i'd get fired.
"Fired"... there's another "f. "
Sam?
Yeah?
You didn't order my black
bean sauce again. I'm sorry.
You always make sure
your order's right,
but you never think of me.
I always think of you.
Mm. I just think of myself first.
Some people find that adorable.
Well, frank doesn't.
He'll come around.
He won't come around. He doesn't want to
be your friend. Yeah, well, you know what?
He also didn't want to drag out
our dead christmas tree,
but he did that. I'll wear him
down. Why is this your project?
Because for
the last two years,
i have been walking
past that man,
and i know nothing about him.
What does that say about me?
Exactly. About you.
You want more friends?
Maybe think of their needs, what they
want. You know what? You're right.
And what frank wants
is to be left alone.
I'm gonna bake him a pie.
* my friend frank *
* how are you tonight? *
oh, hi. Can you please hold this for
a second, please? Give me the purse.
No, i've got the purse fine. Just... can you
hold the pie? Give me the purse. Hurry up.
What? Oh, no.
Come on. No.
I can't have you do this right now.
Oh, when would be a good time for you?
No, you don't understand
what i'm going through,
and i really... i cannot
have you reinforcing
a racial stereotype, okay?
I'm really sorry.
You know, if you can't look
past the color of my skin
and see me as a man
stealing your purse,
i feel sorry for you. How about
this... give me your address,
and then i'll send you something later? Okay,
uh, it's 4-2-2... give me the damn purse!
What? No!
I just got the... but i...
there's a card in there
for fra... for frank.
Hello, andrea.
Hello, gin.
Andrea, it's me.
Heard about tony.
You passed on
a relationship with me
to be with a gay guy.
Believe me, that's the least
of the reasons i passed on you.
Wow, it must be rough knowing
you turned a guy gay.
I didn't turn anyone gay.
Hey, i'm not judging, okay?
In fact, i'm willing to let you try
it out on me. Tony was already gay.
He asked me to pretend
to be his girlfriend.
Okay, so what was in it
for you? What do you think?
The limos, the parties,
photographs in "us" weekly.
I was so airbrushed
and pretty...
and happy.
And now it's all gone.
I'm meeting
with his people tomorrow
so they can give me
the big kiss-off.
I think i'm gonna miss
the airbrushing the most.
Man, you are so afraid
to be with someone.
What are you talkin' about...
afraid?
Of being seen by someone
who sees what you need
and can really
give it to you...
to take you in his arms
and really, truly love you.
You want your olive back?
Frank, you didn't have
to call the police.
I only told you
that i got mugged
because i needed a ride home.
I want this guy caught.
My family lives
in this neighborhood.
You do not live
What are you doing in this neighborhood?
You're welcome for the lovely pie, frank.
What a nice friend.
I did not ask you for pie.
I did not ask you for balloons.
I did not ask to be your friend.
You're talking like
a dr. Seuss character.
Just a little bit. Look, why don't we
both just admit what this is all about?
What? You're only pursuing
this so you can ease your guilt
about not having a black
friend. No, that is not true!
I just want to be your friend,
frank. Period.
It's not about color.
That is everybody else's
hang-up. I have no guilt.
Okay? Thank you for coming, officers.
This here is ms.
Newly, the victim. Yeah.
Hello, ma'am. Can you tell us
what your attacker looked like? Hi.
Yeah. He... he, um...
white guy.
Very white.
Blindingly so. Yeah.
Morning, frank.
Uh, could you... could you
call me a cab to my mom's house?
I'm sorry. Todd is still
picking up my car at your house.
And he's just taking forever.
He thinks
it's really funny
to change all my radio stations
to gospel.
* hallelujah! *
sorry.
Thank you for the pie.
Oh. You're welcome.
Was it good?
The important thing is
you were reaching out,
and i'm sorry.
I've become accustomed
to shutting people out.
To your offer of kindness,
then you wouldn't have
needed to go to my home,
and you wouldn't
have been attacked.
Did you try the pie?
The important thing is...
if you still want
to be friends,
que seamos amigos.
I suppose that would be okay,
ms. Newly.
Thok..
what?
Samantha.
Yay! Oh! No, no. Get
off of me. No. Come on.
Oh, yes. I'm gonna grab...
so... mr. Tony dane couldn't
be bothered to show up, huh?
Fine. Let's do this.
First, i get to keep
all the gifts.
Second, i still want
to go to the grammys.
I was looking forward to that.
And i don't care how
you arrange it, but i want
to meet tiger woods,
james gandolfini and captain
jack sparrow. Are you finished?
And i want to carry
the olympic torch. Okay, now.
Here's our counteroffer.
Andrea belladonna,
will you marry tony dane?
Hey. Hey!
Where's your hideous red coat?
If i have to wear
the hideous red coat, so do you.
The showing has been cancelled.
The sellers fired us. What? Why?
Remember the potential buyers...
that couple you insulted?
Well, they apparently
own the hottest
new steak house in town,
and they're telling
all their customers that
we're a racist company. What?
Oh, and two other clients
have fired us.
Okay, well, you know what?
You can't blame that on me,
'cause there could be a million
reasons why they fired us.
First of all, you know, we're not very good. You are
going to convince that couple you are not a racist...
unless, i don't know,
maybe you really are.
Oh.
I mean, when you were a baby,
you cried all the way through
"the jeffersons. " Mom!
And you don't have any
black friends. Uh, yes, i do.
I have frank. If they
could see that, then...
this is a real nice steak house. Mm-hmm
thank you for inviting me. Yeah. Yeah,
sure. You know, when you do real estate,
you don't just
know about houses.
You know about steak houses,
you know?
Oh, excuse me, miss. Um, hi.
Can i please talk to the owners?
I, um, i don't like my steak, so...
i'm sorry. I can get you another one.
No. I'll eat it. I just need to... just need
to tell someone. Okay, i'll get the chef.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
I need to talk to the owners.
Okay, i'll see what i can do.
No.
Skirt.
All right, thanks.
This is fun, huh?
It is.
I'll admit as a rule
i try to avoid being
someone's first black friend.
They try too hard.
They start talking
about halle berry,
how they voted for obama,
how much they love oprah.
Yeah.
Where are those owners?
Hello. I understand someone
wanted to speak with the o...
you.
You own this place?
I didn't know that.
I love it. I love it.
So does my friend frank here.
This is frank.
Ah. Your friend frank.
Yeah.
Yeah. So now i guess we can just
stop all that jibber-jabbering
about who my friends are. Oh,
right, because you thought showing up
with a black friend
would stop us from reporting
your racist company
to the real estate board?
Pardon me?
Whoa, whoa. Hey.
Just because frank here
might be black...
i mean, is he? I don't know.
Are you black?
'cause i don't even
see color at all...
does not mean that
he is not my actual friend.
Okay?
Please, frank, tell her.
Yes, ma'am!
Why, miss samantha here...
she been real good to me.
See what i'm talk... what?
Oh, yes, yes!
You see, lots of people,
they don't take they doorman
out for no fancy meal.
But miss samantha here... she
don't mind eatin' with the help!
He's your doorman?
No!
He... he's not just my doorman.
Oh, no! No, ma'am!
Why, i also carry her thangs
to and fro.
Why, she a real nice lady.
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
First of all,
dinner's on me.
I... frank, come on.
Frank, please come back!
Look, we... we've preordered
the soufflé!
So now frank thinks
that i was using him
just to prove that i had...
a black friend. Which you were.
No, i was not!
I only used him after we had
already become friends, okay?
And then, yes,
i behaved very badly.
You know, i don't think
he's a good influence on me.
I might have to cut him out
of my life. So that's it?
You're not gonna even try to be friends
with him? What am i supposed to do?
Quitter.
He doesn't want it.
He hasn't even filed
a restraining order yet.
I mean, i waited 20 years
to be your friend.
You put up a fight,
but look where we are w.
Yep, here we are.
I mean, you'd be amazed
at the beautiful friendships
you can force on people.
Wow.
Hi! So what are you two
losers doing in three months?
Because i'm...
getting married!
What? Oh, my god!
Married to whom?
To... to whom.
Tony dane. What do you think?
What do i think? I think he's
gay. He's really gay, andrea.
And i think i've waited my
entire life to tell my friends
that i'm engaged.
So if you would just put aside
the pesky details for one night
and just get on board, okay?
Yay!
Oh, my god. Let me see that.
It is stunning. It's so pretty!
See, tony's entering
a contract year,
and they don't want
any bad press.
So they're gonna announce
the engagement,
and then all the designers
are gonna bid to see who's gonna
make my dress, and the wedding
photos are already presold
to "people" magazine,
and they're paying gwen stefani
100 grand to show up and be my
best friend. It's like a fairy tale.
I know. I'll get us some
champagne. Oh. Good. Okay.
Se she called me a friend.
That didn't happen overnight.
Yeah, well, she's also
marrying a gay dude,
so she might not be
in her right mind.
Three champagnes.
I'm engaged.
What about the other night?
Did you not just hear
what i said? I'm engaged.
You felt something
between us,
and i know you
weren't that drunk.
Little tip... don't ever
underestimate how drunk i am.
You don't fool me.
I think i know
the answer to this.
But do you care that i have
a little girl in here
who's trying to sleep? She'll be
fine. "Marceo" will take care of her.
If you came here
to apologize...
no. For wanting
to be your friend? No.
Am i perfect, frank? No.
But we don't get
to choose our friends.
I mean, do you really think
that i chose dena and andrea?
But there we are.
It's late, ms. Newly.
Samantha.
Ms. Newly. We're going back
to the way things were before.
Before dinner?
Before your accident,
when you were as mean as a snake
and never gave me a glance.
I didn't have to know you.
I didn't have to care
about you.
Aha! You said "care. " I heard
it, frank. You said "care. "
Let's go.
Give me the money.
Oh, this is ridiculous.
Seriously, guy, branch out.
Meet new people.
Oh, damn.
It's the chatty white lady
with no money in her purse
is this the man who mugged you? How
can you have $5 and 10 lipsticks?
You lied to the police.
Maybe.
But hey, you know what?
If i had told them
who my real mugger was,
we wouldn't be sharing this right
now. Yeah, i'm aware of that.
Shared experiences,
frank. Remember?
Plus you care about me.
You know what?
If this guy shot me
right here and now,
you would miss me. Hey, oh. Well,
hey, who's got a gun? Not me.
That's... that's armed robbery...
whole different thing.
Just say it, frank.
Tell you what.
I'll close my eyes right now.
You kidnap my friend...
and if anybody asks,
i'll say it was a white guy.
Now why are you talkin'
about kidnappin'?
Excuse me. Hello?
Oh! It's the police.
They found my mugger.
Hey, forget this.
I'd rather just get a job.
Um, are you...
are you sure it's... it's him?
'cause my description
was sort of vague...
and useless.
So, ma'am, just tell us
if the man who robbed you
is inside this room.
Mm. Yeah, okay.
Wait a minute.
They can't... they can't really see me,
right? Why, do you see... do you see the guy?
'cause we caught one of them
breaking into your car
with your keys.
Hey, todd, seriously,
i am so sorry. All right?
Look, i-i'll bet you soon
we'll... we'll tell this story,
and we'll just laugh and laugh.
Yeah. What was your favorite part?
Huh?
Mine was the delousing.
Look, i'm sorry, okay?
I- i had to come up with
something really quickly,
and i guess i just described
the first guy i thought of.
Really?
Yeah. What?
I was the first guy
you thought of.
Oh, don't get all cocky.
Am i always the first guy
you think of...
like in the morning,
when you wake up?
This... you know what?
Shut up.
It was probably just that
stupid little ratty "mustache. "
Well, i'll grow it in some more
if you like it so much.
Yeah, okay, you do that. I'll see you in six
months. You can't even look me in the eye.
Should have had them
put you away.
Ohh. That was almost
worth getting tasered.
Okay, so anyway,
here's how to cure racism,
and i want credit.
If everyone on earth
just looks into the eyes
of every other person,
we'll all be friends,
and there will be no racism.
Of course, the logistics
will be a nightmare
and require exceptional
organizational skills.
Maybe the chinese can do it.
Hey!
Hey.
We're friends now, right?
Yes, absolutely!
Good.
What?
I need you to cover for me.
My band has a gig tonight. Oh!
* the color of
your skin don't matter to me *
can you call me a cab?
* as long as we can live
in harmony *
* why can't we be friends?
Why can't we be friends? *
* why can't we... *