Signposts... they say
very clearly,"you are here"...
even if "here" isn't
where you want to be.
And especially when, inevitably, the
billionaire you let get away shows up.
Hello, sam.
Funk. Hi.
I... oh, it was so weird. I was
just walking by, and I found this arrow.
Uh, so things are going well
for you since you left my company?
Yeah, super-duper, yeah.
No, I mean, I, uh, get
to work outdoors, you know?
It's not all cooped up in some limo.
You know, it is so good to see you.
I'm glad I didn't
take the helicopter.
Probably still could've seen me.
You can probably see me from space.
Well, I'll let you know.
I'm actually gonna be hitching
a ride on the shuttle in june.
Really?
Oh, eating meals through a tube.
No, thank you.
You take care, sam.
And say hi to your
mom for me, all right?
Yeah.
Hey, you're making it
look like you made food.
Who are you apologizing to?
Well, my mother is coming
over here to discuss our business,
and I am going to quit.
Okay, so I'm just gonna go.
She'll understand, right?
I mean, she has to.
I just can't do it anymore.
How did I get here, you know?
I mean, a year ago, I make this big
old deal about leaving chapman & funk
to go do great things with my life,
and now here I am, working
with my mother in this dead-end job,
and my ex-boyfriend's sleeping
on my couch because I need the rent.
I mean, is that not the
lamest thing you've ever heard?
Well, it's up there, but no.
I just have to do something. I
have to do anything.
God. It was so obvious when
I was talking to funk today...
funk?Where'd you see funk?
Oh, on the street corner
that I work.
That didn't come out right.
- He's sitting there, in his limo...
- The "limo.
" I bet he looked like a dork.
Yeah, he was pretty
jealous of my big arrow.
- andrea, I hate to bother you...
- then don'T.
that's funny.
The school I'm substitute teaching at
is having a fund-raiser auction...
you're a teacher?
You knew that.
What happened to that flower shop?
I-I've never had a flower shop.
I guess we'll have
to agree to disagree, then.
Okay, yeah.
Um, anyway, I was thinking, maybe
if I donated a ball
autographed by tony dane that maybe
the school would hire me full-time,
and then I'd get that insurance.
Since when am I someone
you can ask for a favor?
Since I heimliched
that olive out of your throat.
Oh, some favor. That was my dinn.
Look, andrea, I-I need that dental.
I keep trying to chew every
bite 20 times like I promised my mom,
but I get to, like,14, and
I just taste blood.
Listen to what I'm dealing with.
According to research
from tony dane's publicist,
people think I'm heartless.
Wow, I don't... I don't know where
they're getting that. I mean, that's...
six out of ten people surveyed
would rather see tony gay than marry me.
If I don't start testing better, they're
gonna call off my wedding.
What if... what if you
get this ball signed for me,
and then people won't think
you're as horrible as you really are.
Better idea.
I'll get that ball
signed for you, but first,
how do you feel about
choking to death?
I don't know. I always
thought I'd be stabbed.
I've always envied
this about you, samantha.
I can never relay hoin
mme unless it's clean.
Yeah.
Sit down, mom.
Pizza bagel?
Oh, Lord. You pretended
to make food.
What have you done?
Okay, mom, now listen.
I love working with you, but
this is just not my dream job, and I...
don't say another word.
I understand.
I don't think you do.
I don't feel horrible yet.
This is not the job for you.
I get that.
It's like when I used to
help you with your math homework,
and finally I just stopped
trying to push that rock up a hill.
And I said,"she's
not gonna need this math.
She's pretty.
" That was a while
ago, but, you know, still...
you know what you need to do?
Yes, something meaningful
with my life.
- Go to vegas.
- What?
Vegas?Why?
I got an invitation
to a motivational seminar.
They promise to focus you on
your dream and help you achieve it.
Plus, I got tickets to bette midler.
Yes. Mom, that is exactly
what I need.
Except for betting on the midler thing,
because I don't know anything about gambling,
but vegas... yes, let's do it!
Real estate. You tricked me.
- No, no, no, no.
- Unbelievable.
No, no, no, no, no. Not really, no.
And I j... I'm just trying
to light a fire underneath you.
And they have somereat
motivational seminars here...
I-I mean, one where they actually
light a fire underneath you.
Okay, here's $20 for
the poker machines.
That's all you get, okay?
So have fun. See you in a while.
- Where are you going, daddy?
- Oh, I like keno.
You know, you can watch sports, drink
and have an exotic woman
take your money 5 bucks at a time.
It's like the navy again.
Come on. We're gonna be late.
No. I'm already late
starting my life, mother.
I am leaving. Okay?
You're gonna miss
out on the free tote bag.
* you got the moneymaker you got
the moneymaker you got the moneymaker *
* this is your chance
to make it out, out, out *
oh, yeah you'll get
out, out, out oh, yeah *
* you've got the moneymaker
they showed the money to you *
* you showed them what you
can do show them your money.*
miss newly
It's been a while, ma'am.
Meaning I've been here before, meaning
you probably want me to leave.
- I'm really sorry.
- Would you like to play?
Um, oh, no, I don't
have any cash on me.
I could get some quarters from
my mom, but she's in the conference...
this is in your account
from last time...$5000.
$50--$50,000?
This is... is... this is mi...
I could... that's, uh, that's money?
That's like...
I could ch-change that?That's
mine?That's my money?
You mean I could just walk
away fromere with all of that?
Just free and clear?
Yes.
Or you could play some.
New shooter!New
shooter!Place your bets.
- you wanna blow on 'em for good luck?
- Sure.
Maybe a little.
Welcome back, miss newly.
Thanks, bill.
- It's good to be back.
- New shooter.
Good evening.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=- Proudly Presents
Season 02 Episode 13
Sync: YTET-ÅÝÅÝ·É
- =www.ydy.com/bbs=-
 Point is six. Odds on the six.
Cover the hard ways. Vodka
martini, dry,2 olives.
Another $500 on the
come. Place the 10, and yO.
Come on, baby!Who likes money?
How do you lose $100,000?
Well, first you have
$50.000, and you lose that.
Then they lend you another
$50,000,and you lose that.
That's $100,000.
See, mom?That math paid off.
You're just li your mother.
She lost her whole $20
while I was in the bathroom.
Oh, yeah, that's gotta hurt, dad.
Why e you smiling?
I'm not smiling.
I'm sad for you that you have to keep working
with your mother to pay off your debt.
That's a smile.
It's the way my mouth is set.
I'm like a dolphin.
Forget it. No, I saw it.
I saw freedom and autonomy. I
had it in my hands.
I know what that feels like.
Daddy, were you gonna leave
me anything when you died?
'Cause, you know, that
day is sneaking up on us.
Oh, can't help you, kiddo.
The support group I went to
after your mom's last bingo bender...
they taught me the worst
thing you can do is be an enabler.
Come on, honey.
- Regina. Regina, no, no.
- J-just one quarter.
I can feel it. This machine
is about to blow. I can feel it!
Here you go.
How am I supposed to
choke on this?It's soft.
You don't have to really
choke. Just pretend.
Hey, I did three summers of
theater camp. Don't question my process.
All right.
It's showtime.
Dena!
Dena, are you choking?
Oh, my god!She's choking to death.
It's me, andrea
belladonna. I'll save you.
Come on. Come on, girl.
Don't worry. I'm a scout. I
know exactly what to do.
Kid, it's all right. I got it.
No, come on.
Ieed my lifesaving badge.
Kid, get back!
My arm!
He's fine. He's fine.
Andrea belladonna broke my arm!
And scene.
I'm just trying to help you, bill.
I mean, how can you stay
in business if people lose?
You know, that is just not
a model for success, you know?
I really wish I could
help you, miss newly.
Okay, here's the
thing, bi... I have amnesia.
Yeah. Yeah.
You can get in a lot of
trouble for letting me play.
So, uh, why don't you
st give me back my money,
and I won't go to the
department of casino rules,
which is very real.
It's good to see
you again, miss newly.
No, bill!Bill. Bill.
Bill, what if I can't pay?
I'm not worried
about that. You'll pay.
Okay, but what if I can't?
- You will.-How?Bill...
they're gonna break
my kneecaps, aren't they?
I need my knees, bill.
I mean, how can I beg
without my knees?Right?
Bill?Bill?
Sam?
Funk.
Be with you in just
one second, okay?
Who makes this carpet again?
I'm gonna be homeless.
God, this is all my mother's fault.
You know, I see homeless
people on the street,
and I wonder how does something
like that happen to these people?
And you know why?Th know my mom.
I know. It... it hurts.
Oh, god. Why didn't I
just go to that conference?
I'd have all
that moneyand a lovely tote.
You would have loved my seminar.
I did this thing where we
lit a fire under someone's chair.
Why didn't I just walk
away from that table?
Because you loved it.
What?No, I didn'T. I hated it.
Oh, really?
Come on. The action, the
buzz, money flowing in and out,
people hanging on your every move...
oh, I loved that...
for a moment.
One...
sweet, ecstatic moment of pure joy.
I just... for one
moment, I-I was just...
you were in the game.
Yeah.
Come on. Come back and work for me.
What?No.
No, I'm not going backwards.
Come on. I'll advance you the money.
You can work it off
and leave when you want.
Where's the downside here?
So do you like them?
They make you look very attractive.
Thank you.
You're very generous to accept.
Without recipients
like you... just you...
The winston funk foundation would
fail to keep its tax-exempt status.
They give so much.
It makes me want
to give something back.
No, it's just another street corner.
No, thanks.
All right. At least
let me cover the debt.
I want to do something here to help.
Oh, god. Will you please stop?
- Where are you going?
- I don't know, but you know what?
I'm a smart and creative woman, and I am
sure there are millions of ways for me
to raise that money on my own.
You sure you don't want any shoes?
I've got some brand-new jimmy choos, never been worn.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't come to your work
and sell my undergarments.
I expect the same courtesy of you.
I'll give you a free football phone.
A half-hour more, but that's it.
Ll, course I wanted to do
something nice for young jason here.
I mean, I felt so bad after
he tripped and he broke his arm.
After you pushed me to the ground.
Oh, you.
Well, I mean, what really
matters here, as tondane's fiancée,
is that I was able to get a signed,
autographed basketball that i'd like to present to jason now.
Thank you.
You know, the basketball's
great and everything,
but what I really want to ow is...
will you go to my prom with me?
I'd love to.
Sam!Sam, come and look.
We have to get a new tv,'cause
I'm keeping that picture on this one.
That is so not fair.
It's my blood. Who says
I can only sell it twice a week?
Well, if it helps, I can sell
some of my sports memorabilia.
I have a football phone
worth a couple thousand dollars.
That's okay. Don't even look for it.
Please.
Well, what are you gonna do?
I mean, you can't raise 50 grand selling your underwear.
No, at least not without me in it.
I don't know at I'm gonna
do, but it cannot involve my mother
or being taken care of by
some rich guy who just wants to
love me and be with me and
make everything so much easier.
Wait a minute.
Why don't I want that again?
Because that won't make you happy.
Really?'Cause it
sounds like it would.
Sam, you're better than that.
- Maybe not.
- You know this.
You go anywhere near this guy,
you might as well stamp "property of winston funk" all over your forehead.
You'll be another acquisition.
Wait. Come here. Come here. Just...
- what?
- Look. Look what this guy already owns.
Where on the list
do you think you go?
What are you doing on his web site?
I had some microwave popcorn.
A bunch of kernels didn't
pop, and on the side of the bag,
it said,"a division of funk
worldwide," so I e-mailed a complaint.
Look, whatever. Just look. Dyotyne
electric, labasoche champagne...
parkington brand.
No, no. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. What
was that?What was that?
Son of a bitch.
He owns that casino.
Seven out. Shooter loses.
Oh,come on,b m lete
sign for another $30,000.
Cut her off, bill.
Then you'll get cut off.
That looks like a nine from here.
- Nine pays.
- It does, doesn't it?Thank you.
Oh, my god.
He's been playing
me this entire time.
He lured us to that conference.
Puts $50,000 into myaccount,which
I couldn'tosbly have won.
So then when I lose it all, he
can just show upsaand ve the day.
It's flattering.
I gotta give him that.
And now you know you
have to stay away from him.
Why?
I mean, if he wants me that badly,
that just gives me leverage to get what i want.
Look, sam, you can't beat him.
You should know this
by now. The house always wins.
Well, then there's only
one thing left to do.
Beat... the house.
Look who's been sitting in my chair.
Well, I wanted to see how it
blew smoke up your butt all day long,
but I can't seem to find the button.
Wait a minute. I know that outfit.
If I remember correctly, it
has a tricky zipper.
Well, I decided to dress
up for my job interview today.
- How am I doing?
- I don't know.
Where do you see
yourself in five years?
Still beating you over the head
with this stapler if you don't hire me.
So you want your old job back?
I don't want my old job back.
I want to run something...
something philanthropic to match
my new, more charitable reputation.
I believe we'll find
a position you like.
We always have.
You look beautiful.
Just go.
I don't care how drunk I get. You
do not get to touch my boobs.
Listen, in case we end up together,
I just want to let you know that
tricking u into this wasn't my idea.
Yeah?Then whose idea was it?
Andrea!
Oh, you look great.
Maybe they'll vote you queen.
- You.
- Me.
Jason, you got my ball?
God, you guys look so grown-up!
Makes me want to cry.
Some scout. See if
I ever buy your cookies.
Look, I'm sorry.
She wanted the ball, and
I-i knew there was a chance
you wouldn't go with
me if I asked straight up.
You probably prefer the
cool guys like in e marching band.
There was a tuba player in the
tenth grade... didn't know I was alive.
Your poll numbers
came in low, too, huh?
Turns out being a scout isn't exactly
the chick magnet my rabbi said it would be.
What the hell?I look hot. Let's go.
I'm not wearing that. No.
Look, this shouldn't take too long, so
if you want to get a bite afterwards,
bloody mary's in bora bora
has an amazing monkfish on friday.
Mm, that sounds good. Let
me just do this first, okay?
Right.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the business press...
- ooh. Save it.
- I am... sensitive.
Oh, okay. I'm sorry.
Sorry about that.
- Do I...
- just...
Ladies and gentlemen of the
business press, I am samantha newly,
vice president of the
winston funk foundation.
Today is a great day,
because although the foundation has fallen short of its giving goals in recent years,
today mr. Funk is pledging...
$30 million a year various
charities at my sole discretion.
I'm sure mr. Funk and i will make fine
partners because he told me personally
all he wants to do is help.
Now...
mr. Funk will answer
all of your questions.
Yeah, I'm gonna take
a rain check on that lunch
'cause I'm gonna be awfully busy.
Mr. Funk, I was just curious...
you know, just because your life
is already pretty far down one road
doesn't mean you
can't take it forward.
Hey, mom!
I'm returning your arrow.
I can't have it at my place. I
keep making a wrong turn at the kitchen.
- Guess what?
- what?
I sold a house!
Sorry. I didn't hear you.
All I heard was
"chardonnay. What happened?
You know, they told us at that seminar
that we have to find our motivation,
and my disappointment in you
was the only motivation I needed,
so as long as you keep letting me down,
there's gonna be no stopping me.
Don't worry if there's
no sign to point the way.
Just trust your own compass
and follow the arrow.
The point is to take
the wheel and drive.
Sometimes the side roads are
where you find the best surprises.
Hey.
You know, it's hard to play the
ukulele without looking like a dork,
but you keep at it.
So yna g wano out on saturday night?
Yes.
It's a game, right?
I mean, you can't
win if you don't play.
- =www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents