The guy on
13th street,
i told him,
go see gigi.
You call beansie?
Gigi, beansie?
Us italians,
i think we're
the only ones
that use nicknames
to that extent.
No, your chinese.
Nah.
Yeah, this
violinist, yoyo ma.
"Soubriquet"...
it's another word
for nickname.
I'm sorry.
What's the
matter, hon'?
Nothing.
Tony?
How you doing,
sweetie?
Good, good.
I took danny
to the doctor
like you said.
My son.
Oh, yeah, yeah,
right, right.
How's he doing?
Good, you were right.
Just a chest cold,
not pneumonia,
thank god.
Oh, great, great.
I'm glad to hear it.
I made you
some bread.
You know, like
a "thank you".
You didn't
have to do that.
Oh, really, i wanted to,
it's datenut for breakfast.
Listen...
tracee, right?
The bread'
s very sweet.
And you're
a great girl.
Don't take thi
s the wrong way,
but you can't be doing
stuff like this.
No good.
But i just wanted
to say thanks.
I know.
But i already got a family,
they give me gifts.
What we have is an
employer- employee thing.
Can't we be friends?
Well, i'm not so
sure that's such a
good idea either.
'Cause, you kn
ow, you and ralphie...
yeah, ralphie.
I'm glad your
kid's okay.
Let's go,
betty crocker.
Bread.
So, russell crowe,
i mean, he's
trapped, right?
They're gonna
sever off his head.
And he's telling them
how to do it?
I know, and they
he yanks the sword
from that dude.
That was so phat.
What about when the guy gets
hit with that spike thing
and chunks of his
head go flying?
Enough already.
We're making
conversation here.
People are
trying to eat.
Thank you.
Why do you let him
watch this garbage?
"Erin brockovich",
that was a nice one.
I didn't
care for it.
You did
too, what are
you talkin'?
See who that is.
Since when did i
become the butler?
It's probably jackie jr.
, he locked himself out.
No accountability,
this kid.
What, people forget
their keys.
There he is...
fresh prin
ce of new jersey.
Hey.
How you doing?
Don't get up,
don't get up.
I'll fix you
a plate.
Sit down, have
something to eat.
No, i can't,
dino zerilli's
out in the car.
You sure,
something quick?
Why don't you
go bring him in?
Next time.
I'll leave the
m in the mailbox.
That's alright,
we'll use my set.
I'll put the
m on the counter.
What am i, the
invisible man here?
Hey.
Hey, man,
your sister around?
She decided to stay
at school and study.
Any message?
No, just,
you know, hello.
Alright, i'm gonna
hit the road.
Sorry to interrupt
your dinner.
Stay out
of trouble.
So handsome.
Good kid.
Little pig- headed,
if you ask me.
Every advantage,
this kid.
College,
good home life.
I had to quit school
when i was in 11th grade
to help my mother.
Supposed to be
an architect.
So...
when did you
first notice me?
I don't know.
"History of film",
i guess.
The way you talked,
you know?
Turned around to
see who you were.
And?
Nothing.
What?
Say it!
No, no, no!
Leave me alone!
I'm not gonna stop
until you say it.
Okay, okay, wait.
I thought you
were cute, alright?
Ahh...
i knew it.
Ah, hello?
I'm sorry.
I just don't know
where else to go.
You guys
hanging out?
We were.
You okay?
I went over...
to see that movie over
at the student union.
Old, like, horror film
or something,"freaks".
Tod browning, 1932.
All these horrible
people in it with
pointy heads and stuff.
This one guy
had no legs.
He just hopped around
on his hands.
Caitlin...
we talked
about this.
You can't keep exposing
yourself to things
that upset you.
I know, it's just...
why is other people's pain
a source of amusement?
Caitlin, what
the hell are
you doing?
It's just a habit.
Well, stop it, alright?
You're gonna be bald.
It's obsessive
compulsive.
I'm gonna
head upstairs.
Don't go on
account of me.
I have that
poli- sci paper anyway.
Please,
don't be mad.
I'm not mad.
It's just you're
really moody, you know?
I think i miss
my ferrets.
You gotta snap out
of this, caitlin.
Maybe you need to
talk to somebody.
Yeah, well, i'm already
taking those buspar pills.
Well, maybe
that's not enough.
Where are you going?
To the library.
See you later.
I'm sure coming here
has been a culture
shock for her.
I mean, for us,
l. A. , new jersey,
we're kind of
used to the mean
streets, you know?
Someone like caitlin
from bartlesville,
oklahoma...
new york's
probably a little
overwhelming.
Maybe we should
try and be
patient with her.
What?
Nothing.
You're sweet.
Most guys wouldn't
even give a shit.
Well...
i'm not most guys.
Do you
have a condom?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
A. J. , call
lindsey blundetto.
Hi.
Hey, what are you
doing home, don't
you have class?
It's friday, o
nly in the mornings.
I got a postcard
from the dentist.
It's time to
schedule a cleaning.
God, i just went.
Smells gre
at, what is that?
It's a bunt cake
for a. J. 's fund raiser.
Nice shoes.
Is daddy home?
He's upstairs.
What's with you,
you seem...
what?
Nothing,
i don't know.
Hey, you know
what i read?
They're making a
movie with eloise.
Oh, really,
that should be cute.
It's supposed to come out
around christmas or something.
Remember at the plaza
that time?
That kid who kept
calling her heloise
and i almost got
in a fight with her?
Yes, that little
spanish girl.
She was so annoying.
I can't believe you
even remember that.
You were like,
nine or something.
Hey.
Hello.
Anyway, so, when it opens,
we are so there, you and me.
I know you're exci
ted to see me, but try
to control yourself.
So...
how is school,
what's new?
Caitli
n's still a pain.
She cries over
like, everything.
She probably
misses her family,
the poor thing.
Thank god for
noah, though.
He's the only one
that can calm her down.
She started pullin
g her hair out last night
'cause she saw
a scary movie.
She does it
all the time now.
Her scalp is like,
all raw.
Oh, my god.
Nothing a straight
jacket wouldn't cure.
Sorry, i forgot,
it's mr. Sensitivity
who doesn't have any
problems of his own.
I'm agreeing
with you.
Like you have a clue.
Jesus christ, what
the fuck already?
Cut her some slack, tony,
she's under a lot of strain.
And you did
start this.
Did you see?
How i didn't rise
to the bait?
The mulignan?
A lot of good
it did me.
Does anybody!
It's still going on!
Whoa, you're on
the poles tonight, honey.
Why the hell's
mandee in?
Vip work,
vip prices.
It's 50 bucks to me,
plus a blow job later on.
You know you're gonna make
at least half a "g" in there.
Oh, look at that.
It's like an
ad for a fucking
weight loss center.
Before...
and way before.
This guy ever stop
breaking balls?
Hear what i
said, ton'?
They're like an ad
for a weight loss center.
Before and after.
Come here.
I want to show you
where the horse bit me.
Hi, tony.
Hey.
Look at
this vision.
How you doing,
sweetheart?
Hey, ralph.
I have come
to reclaim rome
for my people.
How you doing?
I have come to reclaim
rome for my people!
I don't get it,
what do you mean?
Fucking "gladiator",
ya fuck!
Oh, the movie.
I didn't see it.
You're an
asshole then.
Ho, ho, ho.
What do
we have here?
What is this, a
handsome contest?
Ralphie.
Yo...
behave you.
Hey...
hey, baby, i was
wondering where you were.
Oh, oh, oh,
fucking kiss me!
How many cocks
you suck tonight?
Go on.
Get me a drink.
Skipper!
Where's tony?
Getting hi
s weasel greased.
Oh, your kid
brother's here.
Ralphie.
Word to
the wise.
I'm just fuckin' around,
breakin' balls.
Yo.
I got a cousin
who's a fag.
Oh!
Fucko!
This weekend...
get the video.
There'll be a
quiz next week.
They're gonna find
this piece of shit
in the trunk someday.
We are
all dead men,
as russell crowe
said, ahh...
hey, c'mon.
All we can do...
is choose...
how we die!
That fucking hurts!
Nah,
all that fat?
He's out of control,
this oobatz.
Hey, ralph.
C'mon, man.
Alright, c'mon.
Put it down,
ralphie, c'mon.
I am father...
to a murdered...
son, husband...
ralphie!
To a murdered wife.
...my vengeance.
Jesus christ!
Goddamnit!
Ralphie!
C'mon!
The fuck you doing?
My fucking eye,
i'm blind, i'm blind!
The fuck's the
matter with you?
What are y
ou, hopped up
on something?
It was an accident.
What did you do?
Nothing, we were
fucking around.
It was an accident,
stop being such
a crybaby.
Take him to
the emergency room.
What?
Just take him.
C'mon, pussy boy.
Fucking stunad,
this guy.
Did you li
ke the bread?
What?
The datenut bread.
I have recipes--
hey, sweetheart,
not now, alright?
I was up
all night.
You could've called
or something.
Sorry, i didn't realiz
e i needed your permission
to visit my house.
I'm sorry.
It's just--
i kept having this image
of you in the hospital
with your throat cut.
I apprecia
te your concern,
but maybe you should focus
on your own problems, okay?
You know, there was
this thing on tv once
about that pilot,
charles lindbergh,
and about how his baby
was kidnapped and killed--
jesus christ,
already!
Don't go.
I'm go
ing to noah's.
Well, at least
you have a boyfriend!
Now she's got me
all wound up.
Put her out
of your mind.
Duh, if i could
do that.
Maybe we shoul
d find her a guy.
Don't you have
any friends?
Do you really think
i'd subject one of my
friends to caitlin?
I have an idea.
I think
her birthday's
coming up.
Why don't we
take her out,
like to celebrate?
You mean l
ike to live bait?
Get her drunk, maybe
it'll cheer her up.
Please, she's bad
enough sober.
I bet i know what
would cheer you up.
Oh, yeah?
What?
Go to the fuse box.
In the cellar,
janice.
So, call the gas company
, what do you want from me?
You chose to l
ive there, remember!
Well?
What do you think?
About what?
What am i
looking at?
My teeth,
i got braces.
What do you want,
a parade?
Oh!
What did i tell you
about fraternizing?
I'm not, i was
just showing
tony my braces.
Yeah?
I didn't shell out
three crackers
for you to be
modeling your teeth.
Get to work.
C'mon.
Anything else?
Ralphie's the one
sticking her,
why don't he pay
for her teeth?
It's a loan,
i'm juicing her.
Usually it's fak
e tits they want.
Yeah, well, she
don't need those,
that's for sure.
That kid's
a thoroughbred.
But, madonn'
, those choppers.
A fuckin
g train wreck.
Well, happy
birthday to
us all.
That was a barrel
of monkeys.
That guy jeff
kept staring at me.
What do you think?
You want to
check out "smokes"?
I'm a little
tired, you know?
Yeah, yeah, right.
It is getting
a little late.
Oh, my god.
That is so sad.
The chairs,
the pears, the bears,
the social security cards.
C'mon, caitlin.
We should give
her some money.
Caitlin!
Excuse me, miss.
Miss!
Oh, my god!
Not bad, chrissy.
Decent week.
Not bad?
I'm running
ragged here.
If i wanted to work
18 hours a day,
i could get
a job at denny's.
Like they'd
fucking hire him.
What, are
you crying?
Keep it up...
i'll give you
something to cry about.
Watch the
braces, honey.
God, it was
so horrible.
It's over,
caitlin, okay?
How can you be
so callous?
That was the most
horrific thing ever.
It was a homeless
woman with "the dail
y news" up her butt.
Every time i close my eyes,
i just keep seeing her.
Oh, my god.
Caitlin, why
don't we go over to
the health center?
They'll help you.
They'll give you
something to calm
down at least.
No.
No more drugs.
Caitlin, don't start
drinking, c'mon.
Listen...
i have to get up
really early tomorrow.
Josh is on the red eye
from l. A. And...
my friend, josh, from
crossroads high school,
i didn't tell you?
No.
Sorry, i
thought i did.
Anyway, he's coming in
and we're gonna head up
and see his brother
at hampshire.
Try and get
some rest, okay?
Where do you think
she sleeps at night?
Hi.
When did you
come in?
Just now.
Sorry, were
you sleeping?
It's a good thing we're
paying for that dorm room.
It's caitlin again,
i can't sleep there.
Forget about studying.
Like you were studying
at two a. M.
Noah and i took her
out for her birthday.
She's all depressed
to begin with
and then she starts
having conniptions
over this homeless
lady in the street.
And how are things
with noah?
He's going up
to hampshire college
with his friend from l. A.
He said he told me about
it, but i know he didn't.
Don't you think that's weird
that he would just do that?
I don't know, i
don't really know him.
And his friend,
josh, i mean...
i guess he's okay.
So, you two ar
e still dating then?
Is that a problem?
You started
this conversation.
The hygienist from
dr. Maceras called.
You never scheduled
your appointment.
I'm sorry, i forgot,
i'll do it.
And jackie jr.
Says hello.
Noah's great, but he
can be odd, you know?
It's like...
one minute he's all
affectionate and
then the next,
he's like a totally
different person.
Meadow, are you in
love with this boy?
I don't know.
I guess so.
At this point,
i better be.
At what point,
what does that mean?
Sorry, but we are so not
having that conversation.
Tony?
You ha
ve a second?
I know you said
we can't be friends,
but there's no one
else i can talk to.
I'm pregnant.
It's ralphie's.
Congratulations.
I don't know
what to do.
He acts like he
doesn't give a shit.
Did you ever think
he's not acting?
Well, what
should i do,
should i keep it?
I don't get involved
in affairs of the heart.
But if i have it...
you think he'l
l help me support it?
Oh, sure, it'll
be father knows
best over there.
Look, you want
my advice?
You already
got one kid.
Problems with that,
burning him with cigarettes,
whatever the fuck
you were doing.
I got help for
that, i had a lot
of repressed anger.
The county social worker
says it all goes back
to my mom and hold
ing my hand on the stove--
whatever,
okay?
Your age,
your situation,
you need another kid like
you need a fucking
hole in the head.
You're young,
still got your figure,
you're making money.
So, you think i should
get an abortion?
Believe me, with
ralphie as the father,
you'll be doing
this kid and the next
three generations a favor.
Hey, urban outfitters
is having a sale.
We're out of syrup.
'Cause you use a whole
gallon at a time.
Shut up.
A. J.
You wanna go?
What do you
need, shoes?
Shoes, some new tops.
I need underwear.
So, you wanna
go or not?
I put your whites
in at 10:30.
I need to wait until
the dryer's free.
Let lilliana do it.
Lilliana's off.
It's gonna be a zoo by
the time we get there.
Meadow here?
She paged me,
she's at her parents.
Oh.
Want to hang out?
I'm writing my paper.
You mind if i just
sit and study then?
I'm fine, really,
it's just...
you know, it's creepy
up there alone.
Um...
alright.
What are we,
short?
Who we missing?
Tracee.
Left sick on saturday,
haven't seen her since.
For three days?
Fucking twat.
I talked to my mom.
And she wants me to go
to vermont this weekend.
For what?
Friends of
my dad's.
Paul and
irione dudley.
Paul's a psychiatry professor
at dartmouth medical school
and they have a horse farm
and ride and talk.
Paul's very inspiring.
Sounds good.
I just feel
better already.
Irione is
an amazing cook.
Now, if i just don't
get freaked out
by the sound of
the pine trees at night.
I'm going to noah's.
This moltisanti kid, he's
got his head up his ass.
This is a great
gladiator movie?
Look at kirk douglas'
fucking hair.
They didn't have flat
tops in ancient rome!
What do you want
to drink, baby?
Get me a fresca.
C- fucking- minus and
it's all her fault.
You know, six hour
s i'm trying to work and
she just won't stop.
Tell me about it.
The questions,
the whining,
the crazy
goddamn nonsense.
She starts crying about
her economics class.
She doesn't get it,
so i give her my notes
from last year.
I'm talking primo
notes, i got an "a".
But even
that's a problem.
She doesn't understand
my writing.
"What does this word mean?
Blah, blah, blah, blah."
Nothing's ever
enough with her.
I mean, i know
i'm the r. A.
But technically she's
not even on my floor.
C- minus.
Really beautiful,
noah.
It's not
that bad, okay?
I want options when
i graduate, meadow.
I'm going to law school
in two short years.
A c- minus is
fucked for me.
It's early in the semester,
you'll make it up.
Is that alright,
honey?
Fine.
You know i take
care of you, right?
You, danny,
our gorgeous
little baby.
Who's that?
How the fuck
should i know?
Ralphie, open up!
Ah, shit.
Ralphie!
Where's tracee?
She's busy.
Hey, sil.
Put your shoes on!
Oh, what'd i say?
I don't know, what'd
you fuckin' say?
Three days
she missed work.
I've been sick, sil.
Oh, yeah?
I called your house.
Your mother says you
haven't been there
for two days either.
I was here, ralph's
taking care of me.
You got a little
kid at home!
Her mother
's watching him!
Mind your fucking
business, ralph!
Oh, where do you get
the balls to come here?
Three grand this
cunt's into me,
and where do i get
my fucking balls?
Go on, get out
of here.
Let's go!
What's the mat
ter with you, huh?
You know how m
any girls would kill
for the opportunity
you've got?
What, working for you?
Oh, go ahead
, keep it up.
Give me a break,
in two seconds i could
get a job at any other--
listen to me,
you little boochiac'.
Until you pay
what you owe,
that shaved twat of
yours belongs to me!
You understand?
I asked yo
u a question.
Yeah, now,
get in the car.
And then i go to pour the milk
and the carton is empty.
I keep telling you,
it's not me, it's a. J.
Nice try, mister.
How about the
football trance?
I swear to god, we can have
an entire conversation,
but if that tv's on, he's no
hearing a word i'm saying.
One time
this happened.
Forget it, gab,
you might as well be
talkin' to the furniture.
Well, that's because men
have the attention
span of children.
Sorry, honey
, what'd you say?
This cake, rosalie.
Really, ro,
delicious.
The whole meal.
I'm glad we could
reciprocate.
Hey, college boy
, how's school?
Good, you know.
Crackin' the books.
Almost dean's list.
What's this,
almost?
Give me his name,
no more almost.
I'm going out.
I'll probably end
up staying at bobby's.
No drinking
and driving.
C'mon, he knows
better than that.
Right, tough guy?
Yeah, whatever
you say, ralph.
Get lost.
Enjoy your youth.
I'm gonna kill you.
Why didn't you tell me
this place was so fancy?
Calm down, it'
s just my father.
Believe me, it'l
l be nothing compare
d to meeting your dad.
There he is.
Hey.
Hey, dad.
Meadow.
This is my
father, len.
Hello.
Len tannenbaum,
please sit.
How was
the flight?
Aside from tim daly
chewing my ear for an hour,
it was wonderful.
The guy from "wings",
you know him?
He did his deal
for "fugitive".
Usually i enjoy
l. A. To new york.
Five hours
without interruptions,
it's the only time i get
to do some real work.
Unbelievable.
He flies first class,
personal dvd player
with any movie he wants
never even
opens the case.
Bad enough representing
these people,
i have to suffer
through their movies too?
God, it must be
so exciting being an
entertainment lawyer.
Get to meet all
the celebrities.
It beats working
for a living.
He's in town to
meet with dick wolf.
The sportscaster?
Actually, he's
a tv producer.
"Special victims unit,
law and order".
"New york undercover".
I used to
love that show.
Good evening, may i offer you
a cocktail before dinner?
Guys, are we
drinking wine?
Clos pegase, the'94
if you've got.
So, meadow,
what business is
your father in?
Actually, um,
he's in waste management.
Ah, toxic chemicals,
medical waste,
that sort of thing?
Yeah, sort of,
environmental clean up.
Let's give a big bada bing
welcome to tracee.
Hey, that guy
cut the line.
What's the matter?
I told caitlin
if we went to th
e movies i'd call her.
I'm starting
to feel bad.
I stopped feeling bad
the second i saw that grade.
Did i tell you my father's
filing a restraining order
against her?
What?
You're kidding,
right?
You obviously
don't know my father.
He totally freaked when
he heard about the c- minus.
Well, i mean...
couldn't you try
talking to her first?
At this point?
She thinks
we're her friends.
Well, you have
to set limits.
The girl was
ruining our lives.
Think about it, we
couldn't do anything
without her horning in.
We certainly couldn't
take her to see this.
Mrs. Custer
grabs the artist,
"oh!
"I tell you
i want a painting
"commemorating my husband's
last thoughts,
you give me cows with halos
and indians making love?"
"Mrs. Custer,"
he says.
"Those are your husband's
last thoughts."
"Holy cow,
look at all
those fucking indians."
Oh, what,
not even a hello?
Fuck you, asshole.
Oh, that's nice,
very nice.
That's how you talk to a man
in front of his friends?
Yeah, right.
What man?
Oh, a double.
You tell him,
sweetie.
I like this girl!
Women, women, women.
Why was i born handsome
instead of rich?
Leave me alone.
What's the matter
with you?
What are you being
like this for?
Fuck you, three days
you don't call eve
n to see how i am.
Baby, i'm busy,
i gotta work.
How else am i gonna
take care of you
when you're nine
months pregnant?
You serious?
Of course
i'm serious.
We'll get
a little house...
in a cul- de- sac.
I know that guy who's
a mortgage broker.
Really?
Ralphie,
i love you.
I love you
too, baby.
Hey...
if it's a boy...
we'll name him
after me.
If it's a girl,
we'll name it
tracee after you.
This way she can grow up
to be a cock sucking slob
just like her mother.
Are you out of
your fucking mind?
Guinea motherfucking
piece of shit!
That's right, that's
right, get it all out.
Get it all out,
you little whore.
That make
you feel good?
You feel like a man?
Look at you now.
Oh...
give me a
fucking drink.
What happened
to you?
Tracee.
She slipped.
We were arguing,
i don't know.
She fell.
Holy fucking
shit.
Get a sheet, chrissy,
cover that up.
Where is he?
Inside.
Go get him.
She fell?
That's my story.
You stupid
motherfucker!
How fuckin
g dare you!
Take it easy.
You don't think.
You disrespect
this place.
That's the reason
why you were passe
d the fuck over.
It's my fault
she's a klutz?
Motherfucker!
Are you out of your
fucking mind layin'
your hands on me?
He's the bos
s of this family!
Shut the fuck up!
I'm a made guy!
Ton', we gotta
get you out of here.
Is this place open?
No!
Get the fuck out
of here, ralph!
Keep that
back door locked!
And get her th
e fuck out of here.
You got a rug,
a piece of carpet?
Cocksucker was
way out of line.
20 years old,
this girl.
That too.
Let's go.
What?
I think we
need to talk.
I think that maybe
we've been seeing
too much of each other.
And?
I don't know.
I mean...
i really like
you, meadow.
It's just...
i don't think we shoul
d see each other anymore.
Are you breaking
up with me?
Are you really
that surprised?
Why, i mean...
things were
going so good.
Look, honestly,
you're too negative.
It's like you have
this underlying cynicism
about everything.
What are you
talking about?
I really didn't
want to get into this.
So...
things are
better then?
Since our
first session?
Yes, i guess.
We seem to
talk more easily.
Sometimes even painful
sessions can break
the log jam.
Yes.
And then this.
You're being
particularly
quiet today.
Sometimes i got
nothing to say.
Anthony.
Carmela is here.
She's giving up her time to
talk about your panic attacks.
A young man who...
worked for us...
barone sanitation, he...
he died.
Who?
You don't know him.
He died, that's all.
Work- related death.
It's sad when
they go so young.
How was
the dentist?
God, is ther
e nothing to eat
in this house?
Who knows,
maybe she quit.
I heard she went
outside with ralphie
and never came back.
Do yourself a favor, keep
what you hear to yourself.
Parties are usually
friday night.
A lot of high rollers,
a lot of big tips.
You want in
the vip room?
It's 50 bucks to me
plus a blow job lateron.
Captions copyright 2001
home box office
a division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.