Anybody home?
Hello?
What's this?
Oh, my god,
tony...
here, allow me.
Happy birthday.
Oohhh...
oops.
What?
Look at the ring
your father gave me.
I already saw it.
I was gonna
wrap it, but,
it's wasteful
to the environment.
Thank you,
young man.
"The matrix".
I haven't
seen it yet.
Hello?
Happy birthday,
mama.
What are you
doing here?
Don't you have
an exam tomorrow?
Nice to see you, too.
I'm sorry, honey.
I'm just surprised
to see you.
See what your
father got me?
Mmm.
Big ring.
Happy birthday.
Oh, my god,
so many gifts.
"A day of beauty
and pampering
at the belladonna
day spa."
It's in soho,
my friend batshe
va says it's awesome.
Massage,
mud treatment,
everything.
I got myself one,
so we can go together.
I put it on
your credit card.
12 years, i took
this club from nothin'!
Give him
a drink.
What do you
drink, rocco?
Johnny black.
This place was
a shit hole when
i took it over.
You could use
a little help,
make this place in
the 21st century.
Yeah, it's like
permanently 1987 in here.
Goddamn vikings!
Nobody misse
s the extra point.
That's all they had to
do, one little kick,
and now i'm ruined!
Don't bitch to me!
Bet with your head,
not over it!
You still a partner.
You got a problem
with us?
One, two, three!
I'll get it.
Did you invite some
stray dog up here?
You short
of food?
Sorry i'm late.
We didn't even know
you were comin'.
Meadow told me it was
carmela's birthday.
It is so nice
of you to join us.
Hi, mr. And
mrs. Deangelis.
Jackie.
Hey.
Have you heard
the good news?
We met thanksgiving?
Happy birthday,
carm'.
Oh, jackie,
you didn't have to.
I'll put it on ice
in a minute.
Thank you, sir.
Alright, come
on, let's go,
the wax is
melting here.
I heard you got made
defensive captain.
Yeah, five and
a half sacks
and two
recovered fumbles,
almost sco
red a touchdown
on one of'em.
Excellent, man.
You know i played
linebacker for boonton?
Senior year,
i was all- county.
Wow.
Maybe we could work
out a little together.
Sure, you should come
to the blessed sac
game on tuesday.
It's the last game
of the season.
We were supposed to
play last month,
but, the r
efs were on strike.
I'll be there.
I wanna come to.
My little brother's
football game.
No champagne,
the good lord
doesn't want us
to drink alcohol.
Didn't jesus
drink wine?
He was jesus, ton',
we can't make comparisons.
Who invented
these things?
You people are all
out of your minds.
Mom, is it alright
if i sleep at egon's
if i promise to
be in bed by one?
I ordered one for
you so you don't disappear
when i send you
to the market.
Lights out by one,
in bed by 12.
Be careful.
I smell fish.
We're near
the ocean.
Now i smell piss.
What?
It's yours.
What is?
This is the lollipop
in long branch.
This is your club.
I'm a partner here
now, me and furio.
But, we're gonna
be silent.
You're gonna be
the owner- manager.
You book the bands,
you find the talent,
whatever
you wanna do.
It's yours.
Oh, my god!
I can't
believe it!
You're gonna
turn this place
into the biggest
jersey club
since "the stone pony".
Thank you,
christopher!
I'm so excited.
Can we change
the name?
Whatever y
ou want, baby.
This is rocc
o, he works for you.
The ring looks
beautiful on you.
It is gorgeous.
Tony, is there anything
you need to tell me?
About the ring?
I don't know.
You didn't buy that little
car you were talking about.
The mercedes?
I'd look like a douchebag
in one of those.
Jean cusamano calls
those sports cars
mid- life crisis
mobiles.
What the fuck
does she know?
Is this 17- 26
pearl ave.?
No.
Is there a pearl a
ve. In this neighborhood?
Hello?
Hey, ro.
No, jackie took
meadow to the movies.
They said,
"not late".
Alright.
Bye.
What?
I don't know.
I'm not thrilled
about this thing
with jackie and meadow.
I think she came home
and he came over,
so that they could
go out tonight.
So, what?
He's a good kid.
He comes from
good stock.
He's been on his
best behavior lately,
i can't deny that.
I just never pictured meadow
with someone like him.
"Someone like him"?
He's one of us.
Don't tell me you
were happier when she
was going with that
jamal ginsberg,
the hasidic homeboy.
We scraped through that
by the skin of our ass.
I just don't want her
to miss the opportunities
that are
available to her.
She should be at
the museum of modern
art in her free time,
not watching t
v at rosalie aprile's.
You'd rather have her
looking at pictures
of soup cans,
instead of being
close to home?
I don't know.
You talk to her,
and i'll talk
to jackie jr.
Here's your edgar
allen poe paper.
You did it
already?
No problem.
Thanks.
I would have
done it myself,
i was gonna do it,
i just couldn't ge
t through the books.
I never should've took
literature of obsession.
I owe you big time.
Thanks.
How can i
repay you?
I don't know.
Why don't you
surprise me?
On your ma
rk, get set, go!
I kicked
your asses!
You cheat!
Ow, my eyes...
there's too
much chlorine.
I think i swallowed
some water.
You girls see me
out there?
Yeah, it looked
like you were
cheating.
Hey, guys!
We got
mr. Goodwi
n's office open!
Check it out.
Let's go for it.
Hey, everybody!
Boo- ya!
C'mon, let's
go, c'mon!
Don't cut
your feet!
Hey, it's sunday morni
ng and you're listening...
good morning.
Hello.
'Morning.
Did jackie call?
Vince lombardi's out
back with your brother.
So, i've been
thinking about a car.
I knew i was gonna
get hit up
for someth
ing on this trip.
What, you can spend
thousands on sapphires
but, a hardworking
student has to take
the bus everywhere?
You live a block
from the school.
What do you need
a car for?
It'd be nice to hop
in a car after class
and come have
dinner with you
guys once in a while.
They steal cars
left and right
in new york,
parking is
impossible.
Besides, the bus
gets you here
in 45 minutes.
I'm not asking
for anything fancy,
just something
to get me around.
You could've had
a car last year,
but you spurne
d your nose at it.
Eric's car? Is
that a sick joke?
It may interest you to
know that his father's
now in a mental health
facility in nevada.
Why don't you just
wait and see how
this semester goes?
You were just complaining
about how much work
you had to do!
Don't you think you should
concentrate on that?
I am concentrating
on that!
What do you
think i am?
Jesus christ, you're
like a broken record!
Take it down a notch! Hey!
God.
We just want to make sur
e that you take advantage
of all the city
has to offer you.
Culturally, socially,
educationally.
Right before the
snap, the ball
isn't doing anything.
But the qb's eyes
can tell you whether
he's gonna drop back
to pass or hand it off.
It happens in
a split second,
but, over the course
of the game,
you can learn
what his habits are,
and once you know
these habits,
he's fucked.
Hey.
Good morning.
Okay, a. J. , tr
y what i told you.
I will,
thanks, jackie.
The wall
of pride...
what kind
of animals?
I don't think
they stole anything.
They just did a number
on the place.
They left this.
You make
this pizza?
Who make
We're asking you.
This your
store logo, sir?
That's my box.
This pie was found
at a crime scene.
My pizza never
hurt nobody.
Come again, sir?
You no find any
bacteria in here.
Some kids broke into
verbum dei high school,
broke things,
they left this there.
You tell me
their names,
i'll go put my foo
t up their ass!
I got it, pop.
That's a custom job.
How's that, sir?
Double meatball,
pepperoni, sausage,
peppers, onions,
extra mozzarella.
This pie
fit a pattern?
Come again,
officer?
Any customers
order this combo
on a regular basis?
Only one i know.
Who's that?
I'd rather
not say.
Tell me right now,
i find these bastards!
Pop, go in the back,
make meatballs, go ahead.
Sir.
Yes, officer?
Word to the wi
what's that? Se.
Technically, you're an
accessory after the fact.
I cannot believe this!
Do you know how
serious this is?
Do you?
Answer me, right now.
Yes.
Yes, what?
I know
it's serious.
So, why did
you do it?
I don't know.
Why did you do it?
Do you hate
the school?
Do you have a problem
with someone there
or something?
Then, why? No.
It just happened.
We went in,
swimming as a goof.
Someone threw
something in the pool.
A couple of guys
started throwing stuff in.
We just did it.
And if they were jumping off
the george washington bridge,
would you just
do that, too?
No.
What are you
doing here?
Answer
your father.
I got
sent home.
Why?
I got in trouble.
Your son, broke into
his school friday night
and vandalized
the swimming pool.
How do you vandali
ze the swimming pool?
They threw a bunch
of stuff in it,
they broke things.
What'd you d
o that for?
Screwin' around?
On your mother's
birthday!
It wasn't...it
was after midnight.
What, are you
fuckin' stupid, huh?
So, what now,
you're suspended?
I don't know.
Tony, do you know
how serious this is?
He may be expelled.
What'd they say?
Nothing.
They just
sent me home,
and said to bring
you guys into the
principal's office.
On your mother's
birthday.
They're gonna
call you.
Just when everythi
ng was going good, huh?
You're gonna
miss the big game.
You're screwin
' everything up.
Your football career,
down the drain!
There it is.
What a
beautiful ring.
I know.
I want you ladies
to try this.
Mozzarella a
nd string beans?
I was gonna get
the hot antipast'.
It's not mozzarella,
this is called buratta.
I had it flown in
this morning,
by fed ex,
from italy.
It's a lot more
subtle and smooth
than mozzarella,
with an almost,
nut- like flavor.
Thank you,
artie.
I'm not that
big on nuts.
A little pepper?
No pepper.
'Carm, on your half?
It's all about the contrast.
The crispness of the beans,
the smoothness of the cheese.
Uh, no, i'm fine.
Buon appetito.
Tastes like mozzarella
and string beans.
You have it, 'carm,
i want the hot antipast'.
I'd like to
make a toast.
To the blossoming friendship
between our two children.
I'm very happy
to see my son
spending time with
someone like meadow,
she'll be a very
good influence on him.
You did a great job,
she's a wonderful girl.
Thank you,
salut.
It's nice to see
our families united.
Like with ralphie,
he goes on and on
about tony and
the promotion.
He's very happy to
be getting closer to him.
Well, ralph is a
real find, ro,
you hang on to him.
You know, it was
tough at first.
I was afraid everyone
was gonna think i rushed,
that i didn't
mourn jack enough.
Oh, artie!
I think he's under
a lot of stress.
I hear charmaine
hired a lawyer.
Divorce?
It's funny, but,
you'd think,
you know, the men in
our lives have been,
you know what, and
we've stayed together,
and here's artie,
a regular guy,
hardworking,
and his marriage
is in the pisciadood.
You can push a
man only so far.
True, very true.
You know what?
If you wait
inside for me
i'll be in there in
just a second, okay?
Hello.
Who's the
douchebag?
That douchebag buys
a new 600 from me
every year.
This was last year.
Nice.
Been shopping?
It's for you.
It's very
beautiful.
So are you.
What are my chances
of kidnapping you
for the rest of
the afternoon?
I'm closing
on a car.
Come on.
Let hans and franz
do the paperwork.
I'm goin' nuts
thinking about you.
I've gotta work.
Trabajar?
Come on, come on!
I'll take you
anywhere you wanna go.
The pierre, the
sherry netherlands,
you pick it, come on,
anywhere you wanna go.
Wanna go to the zoo?
The zoo?
Yeah, i try to g
et there once a year.
Alright, we'll go.
I'll call you.
Amazing thing
about snakes
is that they reproduce
spontaneously.
Whaddaya mean?
They have both male
and female sex organs.
That's why somebody
you don't trust,
you call a snake.
How can you trust a guy
who can literally
go fuck themselves?
Don't you think
that expression
would come from the
adam and eve story?
When the snake tempted
eve to bite the apple?
Hey, snakes we
re fuckin' themselves
long before adam and
eve showed up, t.
...been studying these
snakes for over 15 years...
hey, how ya
doin', kid?
Alright.
Hey, jackie.
Thanks f
or coming by.
How are you?
Have a seat.
Want something
to drink?
What are you
having?
A litt
le red wine.
Okay.
I'm goin' to get
a couple of slices.
You want
anything, t?
Yeah, get me
the usual.
Jackie, you
want somethin'?
No, thanks.
So...
i hear you're taki
n' meadow out tonight.
Yeah.
Where?
A place in the city
called "chez josephine".
The food's
supposed to be good,
and they have
live piano music.
Harry connick jr.
Used to play there
before he became famous.
A friend of mine's brother
is the bartender there.
Don't you two
got class tomorrow?
She's got a 2:00
and i'm off.
How many days off
they give you at rutgers?
I got class
three days a week.
Listen, i think
you're a good kid.
You show respect
at my house,
and you come fro
m a good family.
Thanks.
As far as my
daughter goes,
and you know i only
want the best for her,
i'm gonna be ver
y protective over her.
You can understand
that, right?
Of course.
So, if you want to
spend time with her,
i want the best from you.
If you're in school,
you gotta give i
t everything you got.
Yeah, right,
i know it--
shut up,
listen tome.
I know i been sayi
ng this to you all along,
but, now
it's different.
You understand what
i'm saying to you?
I just got an "a"
on my lit. Paper.
You did?
Edgar allen poe.
Good writer, what
a fuckin' nut job.
He's the guy
who did all the,
the vincent price
shit, right?
The guy smoked opium
and married his cousin.
He was from the bronx,
you believe that?
So, you got an "a", huh?
I'm doing
good, tony.
Let's keep it
that way.
Keep your
father in mind.
I will.
Listen...
here.
Have some
dessert on me.
No, that's okay.
Take it, just don't
keep her out too late.
I won't,
thanks, tony.
Welcome, everybody,
to opening night
at "crazy horse".
I'm very excited
to have, from u- dub,
our very first band.
Please welcome
"the miami relatives"!
What do you think?
What?
What do you thin
k of this place?
I can't hear a
word you're saying.
How do you
like the band?
Matush, you don't got
those maserati's any more?
Only versace
, you try it yet?
No, i like the
maserati, though.
Try the versace,
you won't be sorry.
Hey, hey!
What's up?
Come on,
let's go, out!
I got friends
here, man!
Let me call
my man carlo!
I see you again, i'm
gonna crack your head!
Call carlo!
You have to wonder
what they're thinking.
They're thinking,
"madonn',
"you guys ever
smell yourselves?
'Cause you're
killing us over here!"
You're probably
right, huh?
'Cept for you.
What you got on,
even a baboon
would love.
The eyes are innocent.
Like a baby's.
Yeah, he could innocently
maul you into 10 pieces.
Usually, they just engage
what's called threat behavior.
That's'cause they did
all their mauling.
Now all they gotta do
is give you the look.
You know h
ow the primates,
they groom
each other?
That i like.
What's this?
It's a tibetan talisman,
for protection.
I knew it, i
knew there had
to be something.
What?
What is wrong with that
? it's a buddhist symbol.
My sister
was a buddhist,
she's a whackjob.
Ah, i see, so i gott
a be a whackjob too?
Well, it is a
little wacky.
What's wrong with
fuckin' catholicism?
Oh, which you
fuckin' practi
ce every fuckin' day,
i'm sure.
So, i pray
a little bit,
and i meditate
in the morning.
It clears my mind and
my heart for the day.
A buddhist selling
$150, 000 cars.
The first
noble truth is
life is suffering,
but, the buddha preached
"joyful participation
in the sorrows
of the world".
So, you make a sal
e, you don't make a sale,
it's a tiny
little thing.
What's so funny?
You came
here today.
What, the zoo?
I said,"zoo",
and you came.
This is a fuckin'
head trip now?
Huh? Nice!
Sorta.
I don't like that.
You're very sweet.
You came.
I'm crazy
about you.
You know that,
don't you?
I've never met
anybody like you.
Okay, class, come
on, come this way.
Stay together,
kids, come on.
We're gonna see
some tigers.
You all remember
yesterday...
you take your ki
ds to the bronx zoo?
Yeah.
And, now
we're here.
See ya later.
Who was that?
Oh, that was
my hard- on.
Oh...
between the buddhism
and talk about the family,
poor you.
Let me see if
it's really gone.
You lie.
You know snakes can
fuck themselves?
Give me your hand.
Oh, jesus christ.
Don't move.
What?
See...
...if you...
...cannot...
so, what happened?
He was at "the
crazy horse",
and some zip, he
told my man here
"new management,
new rules".
So, i asked around,
heard about some guy,
multi- something,
some made guy in
the soprano family
was runnin
g things now.
I go,"whoa!"
Chris moltisanti.
Yeah, that's
the name.
I know chris.
What's you
r name again?
Matush.
Normally, i woul
d never get involved
with a stranger,
but, if carlo, here,
is vouching for you,
i'm willing to
make an exception,
and take
care of it.
Thank you.
What'd i tell you
about my man, jackie?
You know who
my father was?
The golfer?
U. S. Open?
Chris and me
are associates.
You got nothin
g to worry about.
I'll call carlo in
a couple of days.
Meeting over.
Verbum dei has a strict,
zero- tolerance policy
in cases of vandalism.
It is a policy
that demands the
immediate expulsion
of the offending
student.
I told him.
You see?
Having said that,
in this case,
after much deliberation
and assessment,
we have decided upon
a suspended sentence.
This consideration has
only been arrived at
based upon anthony's
academic performance
and his involvement in
extracurricular sport.
His academic
performance?
He's brought his
gpa up to a "c- ".
So, what is
the punishment?
We suggest,
and hope,
that anthony's punishm
ent be meted out parentally.
So, it's not exactly
zero tolerance.
Each child is special.
That's a guiding principle
of this school, too.
Well, what
about detention?
A lawsuit a
few years back
forced us to eliminate
our detention program.
Well, he's off the
football team, right?
No.
Studies done at
harvard, and elsewhere,
have shown that boys
have greater success
in avoiding
the pitfalls
of adolescence
when they remain
committed to,
and involved
in, sport.
You better wipe that
smile off your face.
Look, i told him he wa
s gonna be off the team.
Now, i mean,
you're kind of...
undermining--
it's not only skill
that anthony has shown
on the football field,
it's leadership
qualities as well.
We feel that it would be
against his best interests,
and the team's,
to sever his relationship
with the squad.
Well, if you think
that's best...
however, and i can't
say this strongly enough,
if there is but one more
infraction of our code,
the sentence will
immediately go into effect
and anthony
will be expelled.
Do you understand
this, anthony?
Yes.
You completely
sold us out in there.
What'd i do?
They are not punishing
him at all, tony,
and you went
right along with it.
I suggeste
d detention.
That whole thing was
a disgusting charade
so that the fucking
freshman football team
can win the big game.
We've been waiting
for years for him
to get off the couch,
this is good for him.
Oh, please!
We should keep thi
s in the family,
punish him at home.
He ain't getti
ng off that easy!
Overall, it's been
a good two weeks.
What about
the nightmares?
None.
I had a wonderful dream
where i lit the big
torch at the olympics.
What do you think
that represented?
Well, work
has been good.
My sales are way up.
And my performance
has been commended
by mercedes benz u. S. A. ,
with a little plaque.
What's going on with
your social life?
Nothing...
...right now.
But, it's okay.
What i'm going to say
is a little delicate,
but, i think
it's important.
When you called me
last week to cancel,
i heard a man's voice.
My car broke down.
It could've
been the mechanic.
I see.
I'm a little offended th
at you put it to me that way.
Offended, why?
Well, i don't
pay you to be under
your surveillance.
How dare you?
You came to me after
attempting suicide
over the break
up with barry.
I ask you because
you're under my care.
I think it's very
unprofessional ofyou
to confront me this way.
Suicide is something
i take very seriously.
Well, the doctor
in the e. R. Said
it was only
suicidal ideation.
Is he trained to give
those diagnoses?
My car broke down.
Fine.
I'll believe you.
Thank you.
To "the crazy horse",
buona fortuna.
Salut.
The club business
ain't easy,
i'll t
ell you that.
With "the bing",
everybody only
sees the glitz
and glamour.
Nobody really know
s what goes into it.
There's a lot
to deal with.
I know.
See, it's one
thing to have
a bar and sell drinks,
but, when you're
dealing with performers,
i don't care
if it's music,
tits,
fire- eaters, it's a
whole other game,
'cause ultimately,
you're relying on them
to get the customers in,
and spend money.
Alright,
i'll take it
upstairs.
How you doin'?
Alright.
Somebody's
sitting there.
I'll t
ake a 7 &7.
And whatever my
friend here wants.
I'm good.
Just 7 & 7.
Congrats
on the club.
I only have admiration
for your progress
ever since you got
your button.
Thanks.
Sure.
I wanted to
have a little
sit- down withyou
about a friend of mi
ne who was doing some
business at your club.
And when did you
want to do this?
Now, if it's okay.
Now's okay for a chat,
not a sit- down.
Okay, this friend of mine
was movin' a little x
at the club before
you took over,
and the other night
he got thrown out
on his ass.
And?
No, i wanted to ask
you, as a favor to me,
to let him keep a little
action goin' on.
You'll get a piece
of whatever he does.
X is federal
territory now.
They got task forces
with dogs and shit,
i don't want
it in my club.
It would m
ean a lot to me.
You got a lotta balls.
Did you hear what i said?
Yeah.
What'd i say?
No.
End of chat.
Okay, thanks.
It's all
taken care of.
Thanks, man.
You just can't
do it in the club.
Have your customers
meet you outside.
Outside where?
Near the club,
use your car,
or their cars,
find an alley...
i gotta fuckin' th
ink it all out for you?
That's gonna make things
a lot harder on me.
This all happens for
good reason right now.
Reasons beyond anythin
g you could possibly know.
In time, everything
will be revealed to you.
Couple of weeks you'll b
e back inside, don't worry.
If that's the way it is,
that's the way it is.
I'll see you.
Are you
forgetting
something?
What?
I'm looking out
for you here.
I gotta eat
too, right?
Yeah, sure, i'll
take care of you.
I'll be by
every sunday.
Cool.
Your father an
d i have discussed
your punishment.
You're grounded
for a month.
That means no nintendo,
no dvds, no skateboards.
And no computer.
I use the computer
for school.
Get the typewriter
out of the basement.
Dad threw it out.
Then use a pen,
it worked for einstein,
it can work for you.
And, on top of that,
you're gonna work
your little ass
off around here,
which you should've
been doin' anyway.
Okay.
Okay or not,
you got no choice.
Number one, you
go to the garage,
you clean it out,
you make it neat
and organized.
Jackie jr. Did tha
t the other day.
See what i'm sayin'
about him?
You oughta take
a few lessons from
jackie aprile, okay?
Get your act
together.
The kid's pre- med
at rutgers,
he finds time to come
down here and help out.
And, you are going
to clean the gutters.
What gutters?
On the roof.
Where?
On the edge, the things
that collect the water?
I don't know
what you mean.
Don't get smart
with me!
I don't know.
The drainpip
es for the rain?
C'mere.
Very good.
Obviously a lady
of discerning taste.
Come on!
I told you once.
My man
jackie said--
don't fuck
in' name drop me!
We're gonn
a take a walk.
Well, right arm's
still good, no?
You think that's funny?
Sorry.
Tell me
what happened.
I did like you said,
i stayed outside.
You musta disrespected
them or something.
Ugh! I--
i didn't do fuck!
Did you mention
my name,
that i sat down
with chris?
They didn'
t give a shit.
I don't think
they like you.
I gotta pee.
Can you give me
the thing?
You should get the
nurse to help you.
That's what they
get paid for.
Maybe she'll be fine and
give you a cheap thrill.
Hello...kelli?
Hiya, hon.
It's your
sister.
Now, this is t
he most crucial part.
You put the pa
sta back in the pot,
you add
a little gravy...
and a little butter,
then,
you put the
fire back on,
for 45 seconds,
stir it up, real nice.
45 seconds?
Yeah, that
way the macaroni
absorbs the gravy
instead of
just coats it.
This is for flavor.
I need a favor.
What?
I need a piece.
I mean, i don't
need one, but,
you know.
Anything you
wanna tell me?
No, it's just i
think it's time, i...
you know.
What are you
lookin' to get?
I don't know,
what do you suggest?
Me, i like to know
the motherfucker's
gonna work.
And a. 38...
it'll never
jam on you,
plus, it's small.
But, if you're lookin'
to make a point,
you might wanna go
with something bigger.
Nah, it's not really
for intimidation.
It's just in case.
I'd go with
the. 38.
You can have
this one.
I got another one
under the bed.
How much i owe
you for it?
Get outta here,
your money's no good.
Macaroni's
ready!
I just wanna
tell you,
that i don't expec
t anything from you.
Well, kindness,
but, that's it.
Okay.
God!
You really are in
love with yourself,
aren't you?
What do you mean,
conceited?
Self- centered.
Okay, there's a bunch
of alternates
you could've said.
You deprive
yourself of nothing.
You th
ink i'm vain?
I think
you're wonderful.
"And her name
is "g".
A- ha.
Some of my accounts
are in bad neighborhoods.
I know why you lie...
but, you don't
have to.
Can i hold it?
It's heavy.
Is it loaded?
Nothing's more useless
than an unloaded gun.
Here you go.
Mr. Waste management.
Come here.
I mean we're
paying the school,
we're buying
a service.
And if it's their opinio
n that he shouldn't get
treated too harshly...
you gotta listen to
the experts, right?
What else
is going on?
How was the rest
of your week?
To be honest
, very good.
Why is that?
Well, that's h
ow life is, i guess.
Sometimes it's goo
d, sometimes it's bad.
Things com
e, things go.
How are things between
you and carmela?
She was moody for
a little while,
but, now she's
her old self.
Maybe it was
coming here.
Possibly.
Well, you do look
happy, i must say.
Yeah.
I went to the zoo
the other day.
The zoo?
Yeah.
Sometimes you gott
a get away, and,
stop and smell
the gorilla shit.
It was good to
be in nature though.
And the zoo
made you happy.
Yeah.
I think a lot of it'
s'cause of you, too.
You put a lo
t of time into me,
and, now,
it's payin' off.
The progress
that you make
is entirely
up to you,
and how willing you are
to be honest with
yourself and with me.
Well, i am improving.
You have to
joyfully participate
in the suffering
of the world.
Your thoughts
have a,
kind of eastern
flavor to them.
Well, i've lived in
jersey my whole life.
I mean eastern
in terms of asian.
Like buddhist
or taoist.
Sun tzu...
i told you about him.
We have to
stop now.
Alright.
This is the co- pay
i owe you
from last month.
You gave me
too much.
Well, i gave y
ou a little extra
for the good results
this week.
I can't
accept it.
Give it to your
favorite charity.
You better
get your phone.
I'll see y
a next week.
Hello.
Hi, mom.
Hi, jason.
How are you?
I hate all of them!
Who?
My patients,
all of them!
Lying to my face,
full of shit,
with no concern
for what i do
or the positio
n that they put me in.
I just hate them.
Fuck'em,
quit.
Right now, that doesn't
sound like a bad idea.
I'm sorry.
How are you?
I'm okay.
I need to buy a couple
of expensive books.
Como sta.
Hey ton'.
How's it goin'?
Hope you're
doin' alright.
Excuse me.
I don't want
no teammates.
Tony!
How ya doin'?
You up?
No.
Take a hit.
Hit me.
You shouldn't
have listened to me,
it's your hand.
I would've
hit anyway.
C'mere, i wanna
talk to you a minute.
What the fuck are
you doing here?
You're here.
What?
I was at a bachelor party,
i got dragged here...
this is exactly what
the fuck we talked
about the other day.
Now get your money, and
get the fuck out of here!
Sorry, tony.
I never wanna
see you here again.
You won't.
Smarten up.
Good morning.
New earrings.
I went out and
treated myself.
They match.
I almost bought the necklace
that goes along with them,
but...some restraint.
Although christmas
is coming, so...
maybe.
Any cannolis l
eft from yesterday?
I think you can answer
that question yourself.
Meadow still here?
Jackie jr. Took her
to the city to see "aida".
"I eat her"?
It's the elton john
musical on broadway.
Oh.
I have to say, you
were right, tony.
Jackie jr. Has
really surprised me.
He's been a
perfect gentleman,
he takes her to the city
for a little culture,
he's great with a. J.
So long as she does
good in school,
things could be
a lot worse.
Captions copyright 2001
home box office
a division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.