Tell me he's asleep.
Dr. Byers saw to that.
Gave him Percocet before she left.
If I were her, and he called
me in at 2:00 in the morning,
I would have killed him.
Yeah. It's Gibbs.
No, you did not wake me up, DiNozzo.
Okay, I'll meet you there.
Hey, can you drop me by Bethesda?
Ho. You got here quick.
Where were you?
Home asleep.
Asleep, maybe, but not at home.
I got you on your cell.
Drop it, DiNozzo.
Do not make this a challenge, Kate.
I will find out.
See ya.
Bye-bye.
Looks like you and I were the only
ones flying solo last night, McGee.
Speak for yourself.
'Morning, Boss.
Where?
First floor.
A- wing.
Some kind of explosion.
Guy went up in flames.
Name?
Commander Michael Dornan,
Safety Officer on the Kennedy.
It just got back from the Gulf.
Yeah, Friday.
Been complaining of chest pain.
Had open heart surgery four days ago.
Doctor who led the team
that operated on him
is on the way in.
I'll talk to him.
Uh, that would be a her, boss.
Commander Janice Byers.
Come on!
Whoa, that had to hurt.
What the hell happened here, Duck?
The source of t conflagration
appears to be internal.
The majority of the damage
is confined to the torso.
He was receiving oxygen
through a nasal canula.
Still, it would have needed
a source of ignition and
I seriously doubt it could've
caused this kind of damage.
Could he have been smoking in bed?
Corpsman saw him ten
seconds before the explosion.
Dornan was out cold.
Hey, boss...
Listen, I know this may
sound far-fetched, but...
Will you spit it out, McGee?
Spontaneous human combustion.
Where's the surgeon?
She's in the waiting room.
Just got here.
Probie, what are you thinking?
Spontaneous human combustion?!
It's an urban myth.
Actually, Tony, we shouldn't
disregard the notion.
Stories of the phenomenon go
way back- to the Bible, in fact.
Although it wasn't
popularized until Dickens.
Charles Dickens?
Yes.
He used spontaneous
combustion to kill off one
of his characters, Mr. Krook,
in the novel Bleak House.
It caused a minor uproar.
Dickens was accused of perpetuating
the age-old superstition.
I saw that movie.
The silent version or
the British mini-series?
They were talking.
Commander Dornan was
complaining of pain.
He insisted the night staff call me in.
"Insisted"?
The commander liked to
throw his weight around,
especially with the junior
nurses and the corpsmen.
Normal post-op pain?
To appease him, I did an
echocardiogram and he was fine.
I gave him a Percocet for the
pain so he could fall sleep.
Oh, Jethro,
I'll be... uh...
- You headed back?
- Yeah.
Commander Byers, this
is Dr. Mallard, our M.E.
Dr. Byers is the surgeon
that operated on the victim.
Dr. Mallard's a man of few words.
I don't have any more questions
for you right now, Doctor.
Thank you for your time.
Sure.
What exactly was the procedure?
Aortic valve repair.
Congenital aortic stenosis?
Acquired.
and the prognosis?
Everything went well.
I was expecting Commander Dornan to
be back on active duty in two months.
Ah... thank you.
Uh, I may have to ask you a
question or two after the autopsy.
I'll give you my numbers.
Too bad you didn't get
to bed at a sensible hour.
I mean, to sleep, cause
obviously, you were in bed.
I get it, Tony.
McGee...
Yeah, boss?
Stay here.
Meet with the engineers
and the plant manager.
I want this oxygen system
completely checked out.
On it, Boss.
Everything in this
room goes back to Abby.
Everything?
Right.
Background the victim.
This is the beginning
of a very long day.
Yeah. Too bad you had
such a short night.
I must say, I was very
intrigued by your doctor.
I'm not quite re why.
Did you find her that way, too?
Looks like he burned
from the inside out.
It does, doesn't it, Mr. Palmer?
Oh, that's the remains of his stomach.
Make sure they get to
Abigail for content analysis.
Uh, Doctor?
Yes?
Does it help you to talk to them?
They're still human.
What we do is very
invasive and impersonal.
It helps me establish a relationship.
Hey, Gibbs.
I hear you're not a fan of SHC.
That a band?
No.
Spontaneous human combustion.
Don't waste my time, Abbs.
If you read my Master's thesis,
you may become a believer.
Doubt it.
I can show you photos of what
was left of a 240-pound woman.
Yeah, but you won't.
She was sitting in a chair.
All that was left were
blackened seat springs,
a section of backbone, one foot still in
a satin slipper and ten pounds of ashes.
The rest of her apartment was untouched.
Abby, you know what?
Just tell me what caused the explosion.
Ooh! A bribe!
That always works.
So I checked out all
the electrical equipment
from the hospital, trying to
find the source of ignition.
Nothing; everything's
in perfect working order,
including this monitor, which
recorded the victim's vitals
up until the point of blastoff.
Somebody went a little postal
with the fire extinguisher.
It complicates finding trace evidence.
The commander was being barbecued.
I doubt they were
concerned with forensics.
- True.
- You don't know what caused the explosion?
Other than SHC?
All right,
get with Ducky.
Maybe together you can solve it.
Roger that.
When he's finished slicing and
dicing, we'll go bang heads.
Don't cause any sparks.
No, that's more than enough for now.
Thanks for your time, Doctor.
I was thinking of becoming a doctor.
You. A doctor.
Anthony DiNozzo, comma...
M.D.
Let me guess: a gynecologist.
Ooh, no, I was thinking
more dermatologist.
Normal hours. Big bucks.
Never an emergency.
I mean, nobody ever died from a zit.
I had a terrible case of acne as a kid.
Of course you did, Probie.
Boss, plant engineer
says oxygen is supplied
to the rooms through a central system.
They did a complete check
and everything was in order.
Day shift concurred with night shift:
The commander was a pain in the ass.
Divorced, ten years ago, no kids.
Wife's happily remarried,
living in Santa Fe...
Parents are retired.
One sister, and they're being
notified by CACO. DiNozzo...
Harrison...?
Hi.
It's Harrison.
I'm glad you called.
I never cease to be
amazed by your skill, Abby
You know, when I was a young M.E.,
we used to recreate crime
scenes using interns.
You also used to listen to
"records" and do the jitterbug.
Actually, I was quite the hoofer.
Let's see it, Abbs.
Based on the condition of the body,
the burn patterns and debris scatter,
we were able to recreate the explosion.
Doesn't tell us much.
Watch when I rotate it
180 and play it in slo-mo.
That's the point of ignition.
What caused the explosion?
Well, this was taken from
that area of the mattress.
I also provided Abby
with epidermal scrapings
from the victim's upper left torso.
And the spectrometer found minute traces
of antimony sulfide and
potassium chlorate on both.
Matches.
Light my fire, McGee.
Someone struck a match
and ignited the oxygen.
Well, according to the corpsman,
the commander was asleep.
This was no accident, Gibbs.
Barbeque Boy... he was murdered.
Get back to Bethesda.
Review their security tapes.
Find out how someone got
into that hospital room
and then managed to get
out without being seen.
On it, boss.
Start a timeline.
24 hours before the explosion.
I want to know every
doctor, nurse, orderly,
visitor that went into
that hospital room.
Okay.
You two are going to Norfolk.
Dornan spent the last
nine months on the Kennedy.
I'll get the car.
What are you so jazzed about?
He knows that the first person you'll
be talking to is the NCIS Agent Afloat.
Special Agent Paula Cassidy.
You're kidding.
She was reassigned there.
What am I missing?
Paula Cassidy is a rather
attractive agent that
DiNozzo drooled all over last
year when we were at Gitmo.
Enough talk, Agent Todd.
Let's go.
Okay, Zero-two-32-eight-Q
would be this way.
Last time we were on a carrier, you
were the one who got lost. Not me.
I wasn't lost.
I was momentarily disoriented.
Like you were with Paula in Gitmo?
I'm not the type to
kiss-and-tell, Kate.
It's not like you to be discreet, Tony.
She's something special, isn't she?
Is he something special?
Who?
Mr. Short Night Harrison.
Six is two down this way.
No. It's this way.
Trust me. I'm right.
We have to check in with the XO.
Why don't you take care of that?
Why don't you?
Because I outrank you.
That'll be six up and three to the left.
She is something special.
Enter.
I was expecting Gibbs.
Disappointed?
Hi. You've been back a week.
You didn't call.
Oh... I've been gone months.
I didn't get any e-mails.
Well, I figured you'd
be too busy to reply.
You were at sea with 5,000 men.
I had trouble choosing.
Guess I'm a hard act to follow.
Actually, I was afraid of
making the same mistake.
Ooh, wow. Full contact. There.
Nice. Let's start over.
I'll go back outside and do this again.
It won't change anything.
Commander Dornan really blew up?
Literally.
There was no accident?
Doesn't look that way.
Was he having trouble with
anyone aboard the ship?
Safety officers are generally disliked.
They have the authority
to stick their nose
in anyone's department;
no one can say a word.
That sounds like Gibbs.
So Commander Dornan made enemies.
Made an art of it.
Definitely sounds like Gibbs.
So I've just been pulling files
of all the people he put re...
...put on report.
Could be the record for a cruise.
How the hell did pure oxygen
accumulate in the chest cavity?
I do not know, Jethro.
I mean, lungs, I can understand.
The commander was receiving
oxygen through a nasal canula.
But the fire originated
outside the lungs in the cavity.
Dr. Byers!
You're early.
No traffic.
Copies of Commander
Dornan's medical records.
Ah! Thank you.
We were finished, weren't we, Jethro?
We were, Ducky.
Ducky?
Yes. It's something I was tagged
with in school in my youth.
I used to resent it.
Now I quite like it.
So do I.
Well, have you finish the autopsy?
Yes. Oh, oh, yes, there was one question
I wanted to ask you.
Why did you choose to perform a valve
repair as opposed to valve replacement?
It was a close call, but
Commander Dornan was insistent.
If we replaced the valve,
he wouldn't be able to
go back on active duty.
Ah, yeah. True.
But the team felt that the
valve was repairable, and it was.
Ironic, though, isn't it?
We saved his life only to have
him die in a freak accident.
I'm afraid it wasn't an accident.
I reviewed the hospital's
surveillance tapes with security.
Between the end of visiting
hours and the fire, all but five
people can be identified
as hospital personnel.
I downloaded them onto my laptop.
You eliminating the
hospital personnel, McGee?
No, boss.
No. Definitely not.
I'm gonna check them all out.
In the meantime, I'm going
to run the five images
through the face-recognition system.
Just give me one second and I
will have them up on the plasma.
Agent Cassidy.
Special Agent Gibbs.
Agent Cassidy pulled files on everyone
Commander Dornan put on report.
Not a people-friendly guy.
Yeah, we'll have to get
into all that. You ready?
Yeah. My first pass at facial
recognition will be against a database
of military personnel
and government employees.
I can save you the trouble.
That's Ensign Evan Hayes.
He's in the Engineering
Department on the Kennedy.
Commander Dornan rode his ass.
More than the other young officers?
Yeah.
He did not like him,
and I'm not sure why,
but it got so bad that Ensign
Hayes verbally threatened him.
DiNozzo, give me the
Report of Investigation.
There isn't one.
Commander Dornan asked
that I not write one up.
That he would handle it himself.
NCIS special agents do
not look the other way
because they're asked to, Agent Cassidy.
That wasn't what happened.
Yeah? What happened then?
I felt sorry for the kid.
He didn't deserve the abuse.
Some people can handle
it and he couldn't.
And I didn't think it
should show up on his record.
Get Ensign Hayes in here, Agent Cassidy.
DiNozzo, you go with her to make sure.
Is that Dornan's surgeon with Ducky?
Ducky's older, Kate.
He's not dead.
Ensign Hayes went U-A, Agent Cassidy.
Isn't most of the ship on leave?
Not Ensign Hayes.
Commander Dornan put him on Rivet Watch.
He was restricted to the ship.
Two days ago, he walked off.
This is his quarters.
We've put out calls.
Can't find him.
Thank you, Chief Velat.
We're going to take
a little look around.
Scuttlebutt's Commander
Dornan was murdered...
...and Ensign Hayes did it.
You've been in the Navy long enough
to know not to listen to scuttlebutt.
Yes, ma'am.
But I wouldn't blame him.
Dornan rode him from the
minute he came aboard.
Why do I get the feeling
you know why, Chief?
Captain Dornan and I both served under
Ensign Hayes' father, Captain Hayes.
Dornan was a lieutenant
then, who needed to be
put in his place, and,
boy, did the old man do it.
This cruise was payback time.
I got to go topside and
make a phone call. Thank you.
The EKG and the IVAC
recycle at timed intervals.
I was able to salvage the last
seven minutes of Dornan's vitals.
I thought you could use them.
Thank you.
Are you making a statement
with this tie, Ducky?
Oh, too much, you think?
Oh, no, no, no.
You can pull it off.
So, what's the big event?
Dinner date?
Oh, too... ordinary.
What then?
I thought I'd show her
something that reveals who I am.
If she gets turned on, too,
we haven't wasted our time.
You're the man, Ducky.
Mm.
Why can't I find someone like you?
Well, if this doesn't
work out, I am available.
I'll be right back.
Evan!
What're you still doing here?
You promised me you'd
go back to your ship.
I can't, Coach.
Now, come on- a two-day
absence can't be that serious.
It's more than that.
What?
Did you call your father?
No.
He could help you.
Commander Dornan put me
through hell because of him.
You can't blame
everything on your father.
You've got to take
responsibility for yourself.
You're throwing away your career.
I... I never wanted to be in the Navy.
But you are.
Promise me you'll go back
to your ship, all right?
Set things straight.
Hey, Coach!
We're ready.
All right, all right.
I'll be right there.
Hey, you're going back.
Hey, Coach.
Thanks.
Keep me posted, huh?
Ensign Hayes was recorded on the
hospital security tape at 0203.
The explosion that killed
Commander Dornan wasn't until 0317.
Where was he in between those
time Find him and you can ask him.
Any hits on his cell
phone or credit cards?
Nothing.
Kate, what you've learned?
Dornan punished Hayes with port watch.
He was one of the few left on board.
Most of the others have scattered.
They were away for nine months.
The few I could track down
haven't heard from him.
Ensign Hayes was your typical Navy brat.
His family moved around
a lot when he was young.
Went to high school in Alexandria
when his father was
assigned to the Pentagon.
Talk to the parents?
The mother.
When Captain Hayes retired,
they moved to Scottsdale.
She seemed a little
concerned because she hasn't
heard from her son since
the Kennedy made port.
E- mail his photo to the locals.
It's done, boss.
DC, Virginia, Delaware and Maryland.
You need anything from
your sleeping quarters?
What you're thinking...
that's against regs.
Great. You can handcuff me.
It's not going to happen, DiNozzo.
We're both game players.
Too much alike, huh?
We would drive each other crazy.
Crazy's good.
Yeah.
Hey. What you working on?
Stomach contents.
Gastric juices and glandular secretions.
This is whacked.
What... is whacked?
Something's is missing
that should be here.
I going to have to lock you
up for the night, Commander.
No! Don't put me back in the dark!
Abby, you made me almost...
Made you almost what?
Jimmy...
You know what!
Where's Ducky?
He left early.
Can you get him on his cell?
Something wrong?
I guess he doesn't want to be disturbed.
When you asked me out, I didn't expect
to be touring the basement
of the Smithsonian.
This is where they prepare the exhibits.
Can't you just feel the history, Janice?
Where do we start?
This is my favorite.
These were used by army
surgeons Joseph Woodward
and Edward Curtis at the
postmortem of Abraham Lincoln,
performed in a guest
bedroom at the White House.
The Lincoln Bedroom, hence
the popular misconception.
Lincoln never slept there.
How do you have access to this?
Oh, I consulted on Lincoln's autopsy.
That is the ball fired by
Booth that killed Lincoln.
These bits of bone are skull fragments.
You're are an unusual man, Ducky.
Would you care for a bite to eat?
We just got here.
How does a woman like
you end up in the Navy?
My father's a retired
Chief Petty Officer.
You ever contemplate private practice?
Actually, my obligation
to the Navy is up.
I'm leaving next month to accept
an offer from Columbia Pres.
New York.
Now that is exciting.
Thanks.
NCIS, Special Agent McGee speaking...
What?
Why are you being so,
tough on Agent Cassidy?
I haven't done anything to her yet.
You made her spend the
day, alone, with DiNozzo.
She survived. They're on their way back.
Wait, boss, one second.
Okay. Got it.
Thank you, ma'am.
Ensign Hayes just made a
charge on his credit card.
A hotel on Braddock Road, Alexandria.
Contact DiNozzo and Cassidy.
Have them meet us there.
You man the phones.
Kate, come on. Let's go.
Gibbs, NCIS.
May I see that, please?
Okay. What can I do
for you, Agent Gibbs?
You just checked in an Evan
Hayes. What room's he in?
It would be illegal to
release that information.
We're investigating a crime
and we need to speak with him.
Then I suggest you get a warrant.
Hayes is in the United States Navy.
As you just saw, I'm a Special Agent
with the Naval Criminal
Investigative Service.
I don't need a civilian warrant.
You are absolutely correct there, sir.
You need the military
equivalent, a DD-553.
You a law student?
Second year at Georgetown.
Gonna give you a lesson
tonight in practical law.
I'm going to ask for
Hayes's room key, politely,
and you're going to hand it over.
Key? Hotels haven't used keys in years.
If he has to wake up a judge,
nobody is going to be happy.
Okay. But announce yourself first.
That's in compliance with the
recent Supreme Court decision.
All right, Tony, you're with me.
Kate, seal off the hallway.
Paul, you got the service elevator.
We announce, and then we go in.
Okay.
NCIS! Get your hands up!
Get your hands in the air.
Up, up, up!
Get 'em up!
Party's over.
Get up!
Where's Ensign Hayes?
Put your hands down.
One of you checked in as Evan Hayes.
DiNozzo, search them
and find the credit card.
Let's see some I.D.
Just give it to him, Jonathon!
Thank you, Jonathon.
Where'd you get this?
A guy gave it to me.
Gonna have to do better
than that, Jonathon.
Look, I swear it's the truth.
Okay, we were hanging out after swim
practice and this strange guy just walked in.
Really spaced.
He... he just handed
me the card and said
that we should have a good time with it.
That he didn't need it anymore.
It's true, mister. He was
trying to get rid of us.
He said he wanted to use the pool.
And you didn't think
that was a little weird?
Well, yeah, but, I mean, he said
could party with his credit card.
Where's the pool?
Alexandria Central High.
Agent Cassidy!
You and DiNozzo baby-sit these
people until their parents get here.
And collect their car keys.
Aw... Come on, man.
Nobody likes a whiner, Jonathon.
Nice shirt.
See? I knew we'd end up
in a hotel room tonight.
Special Agent Gibbs, NCIS.
Get down on your stomach.
Spread your arms and legs. Quickly.
I'm done taking orders.
Do it now, Ensign Hayes!
No, son. You don't want to do that.
Then put the weapon down.
Can't.
I've got to cover my partner.
Isn't that right, Kate?
Right.
A woman?
I would never hurt a woman.
Okay.
I'm holstering my weapon, okay?
All right, your turn.
I've been trying to pull
this trigger all night...
but I can't...
'cause I'm a coward.
You're not a coward.
You just don't want to die.
I can't spend the rest of
my life taking his orders.
Commander Dornan pushed a lot of
people's buttons. Not just yours.
Commander Dornan...
he's... he's not my problem anymore.
This is the only place I ever felt safe.
It's the only place, I was ever happy.
All right. Let's talk about it.
It's too late to talk.
Don't do it.
That's Evan.
He was troubled...
...but I had no idea he was suicidal.
He was suspected of murder.
Murder?
Evan? No way.
We think he killed a superior officer
at the Bethesda Naval Hospital Tuesday.
Tuesday?
When?
A little after 03:00.
3:00 a.m.?
That's impossible.
He was with me.
He called.
He woke me and my wife up.
He wasn't making any sense.
I told him I'd come get him.
I picked him up in front
of the hospital around 2:00.
You must have the wrong time.
No, I'm certain.
Well, it's not possible because...
Agent Todd, I'll meet
you up in the squad room.
No, Gibbs, that would mean...
How long were you with him?
We sat up talking all night.
About what?
Mostly his father.
They had a lot of problems.
Ensign Hayes tell you why
he was at the hospital?
Said he wanted to confront
someone who was giving him
a hard time, but he lost his nerve.
Ensign Hayes has an alibi?
What's going to happen?
Nothing. You did everything by the book.
I killed an innocent man, Gibbs.
It was
suicide-by-cop, Kate.
Get over it.
We focused on the wrong guy.
No one went in or out of
Commander Dornan's room
between the time the corpsman
checked up on him and the explosion.
What about the corpsman?
I checked his record
against the commander's.
Their paths never crossed until
the commander came in for surgery.
There were four others on the
security video you couldn't identify.
Right. I've cleared three of them.
One is still unknown.
And I'm on it.
Go back to the ship.
Go over your files again.
Agent Gibbs, I need to explain...
There's nothing to
explain, Agent Cassidy.
You didn't file a report.
Now two naval officers are dead.
Would it have mattered?
We'll never know.
DiNozzo, go down to the lab.
Go over all the physical evidence
from the hospital room again.
Uh, what am I looking for?
I'll figure it out.
Good morning, Mr. Palmer.
Oh. Is that the Ensign Agent Todd shot?
Yes, sir.
Oh, dear.
Oh, Abby wanted you to see
this as soon as you got in.
Mr. Palmer, I want Commander
Dornan's remains back on the table.
Kate, how are you?
Well, I shot an innocent
man, That give you you ideas?
I'm sorry.
I need a service record.
Stop playing with my equipment.
Well, I haven't had a woman
say that to me in a long time.
Sorry.
You break anything, you're dead meat.
What you working on?
Evidence analysis report, DiNozzo.
I think you misspelled...
tetrafluoroethylene.
I'm a great speller.
Don't you have somewhere else to be?
Gibbs told me to go
through physical evidence.
Oh, he expects you to find
something that I didn't?
Just another set of eyes, Abbs.
I really need to finish this.
Sorry.
Dornan's personal effects?
Yeah.
Ooh.
He didn't only have heart
problems, this guy was blind.
Did you find any trace of cigarette ash?
In an oxygen fire?
I don't think so.
Wait.
I did find something that
might be a cigarette filter...
Abby...
I think I know how
the oxygen was ignited.
Here's the service record
you asked for, Ducky.
Thanks.
Thanks, Kate.
Abby, what do you got for me?
Not me.
Cecil B. DiNozzo.
Stalag 17.
GI uses a cigarette as a time
fuse to blow up a Nazi train.
Come on, guys.
Don't try this at home, McGee.
It's for grownups.
DiNozzo...
How do people do this?
Okay, cigarette becomes a time fuse.
Check this.
In real time, it takes about 12
minutes for it to reach the matches.
Cool, huh?
The killer placed it next to Dornan's side, under
the tented sheet, next to the open oxygen line.
Then he left the room.
Who was there 12
minutes before the fire?
Dr. Byers.
She was the one who murdered him?
He wasn't murdered.
Commander Dornan died as
a result of his surgery.
Only Dr. Byers made it
look as if he was murdered.
Who was she trying to frame?
No one.
She was covering her mistake.
In 1995, she was the subject of a malpractice
investigation on a heart valve repair,
almost identical to the one
she performed on the commander.
So how do you know that he was
dead before the fire started?
I compared Dornan's previous
EKG's to the last IVAC recording.
That heartbeat wasn't his.
She still could have murdered him.
Well, not intentionally.
Duck...
You trust my gut on this one.
Everything is fine.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Ducky, what a pleasant surprise.
Special Agent Gibbs.
Janice, there was no Percocet
in Commander Dornan's stomach.
I'm glad it's over.
Dornan was in pain and
demanding to see me.
I rushed to the hospital,
did an echocardiogram,
and realized not replacing
the valve was a mistake.
It was failing.
Why didn't you operate immediately?
When I told him, he became hysterical.
He went into cardiac arrest.
I tried to resuscitate him...
but couldn't.
A second failed valve repair would end
my career and the job at Columbia Pres.
I panicked.
I tried to cover up.
I placed the EKG
sensors on my own chest.
I turned off the audible
alarm, cleared the record data
and reset the time/date stamp ahead 15
minutes, disconnected the oxygen tube
from his nasal canula and
inserted it into his incision
so the oxygen could
accumulate in his chest cavity.
Then using one of his own
cigarettes and a matchbook...
I placed it on the bed.
On my way out, I stopped the
nurses' stationand told them that
I had sedated him and he was resting
and to check on him in a half hour.
Janice...
...you didn't kill him.
But I did...
by not replacing the
valve in the first place.
This is Paula.
Leave a message.
Hey, it's me.
Come on, just cause you're pissed at Gibbs
is no reason not to return my calls, right?
So dial the number,
'cause you've got it. Okay.
Sometimes, you've just got
to know when to let go, Tony.
You don't really expect me to take
advice about women from you, do you?
I could stay here and argue
the point, but I have a date.
So now what?
I don't know.
You can't let any woman
affect you like this, Duck.
Especially one you
didn't know that well.
My concerns are more immediate.
I have two tickets
for the opera tonight.
She was going to accompany me.
Jethro?
No.
I wonder if Kate would be interested.
Do you know where she is?
No.