"Destiny."
The design is clearly ancient,
launched hundreds of thousands
of years ago.
Where the hell are we?
Several billion light-years
from home.
We're on a ship,
but we have no idea where we are,
in relation to Earth.
This ship could be
the most important discovery
mankind has made
since the Stargate itself.
These are the wrong people
in the wrong place...
We've got wounded,
and we need to get home.
We barely have enough power
to operate the main systems.
This ship simply doesn't have
the capability to dial Earth.
We've got a problem when
one of the air vents shut down.
Our first priority must be
to seal off any of the leaks.
We can maybe buy ourselves a day or so
before the build-up of CO2 kills us.
We can't ask someone
to sacrifice themselves, period!
Dad! No! Wait!
- Looks like we've dropped out of FTL.
- The ship detected a Stargate
on a planet within range
that may have what we need.
What we need's on the other side
of that wormhole.
Hot.
Cool.
- Make sure we can dial back.
- Already on it.
- Looks like gypsum.
- That would be good.
Why?
- We're looking for calcium carbonate.
- Calcite.
Gypsum is calcium sulphate,
which is 36% calcium carbonate.
It dissolves.
Can we use this sand
to fix the scrubbers?
- That would be convenient.
- No.
It's a fair indication
that the components may exist nearby.
For the sake of portability
and efficiency,
I'm hoping to find
high-concentration granular limestone.
We are looking
for the dried lake bed
or salt-water body
all this sand came from.
It's a desert.
Lime is formed mostly from the remains
of marine organisms.
- Are you saying there was life here?
- Not likely anything we've seen before.
The water may be gone now,
but this desert was formed
by H2O evaporating on a playa floor,
causing gypsum to be deposited
in a fine crystalline form
- called selenite.
- Where're you going?
Higher ground.
What's supposed to happen?
If this sand is high enough
in calcite concentration,
the solution would absorb the acid.
- Right.
- The liquid would turn clear.
It's not.
We're good!
This is Scott.
Unfortunately, there's nothing useful
in the immediate vicinity of the gate.
You have 12 hours, lieutenant.
Make 'em count.
Copy that.
We're moving out!
Too bad we can't just use this sand.
There certainly is enough of it.
Projet-SG (1.00)
- I'm fine.
- No, you're not.
And neither am I, but we're...
We're still alive
because of what he did.
- For what it's worth...
- It's worth a lot.
And as long as we're still here,
I promise you...
Colonel,
I've edited lot of my father's speeches
to know what you're going to say,
You don't have a clue,
because I don't.
We brought along,
an ancient device,
communications stones,
- they allow us to...
- I know what they are.
Good, I'm about to use one of them
to report to my superiors on Earth,
tell them our situation.
I want to tell her myself.
You've been sitting here
since he made contact.
Let somebody take a shift.
I'm not leaving this chair.
I've been on this for the last 6 months,
and I'll be damned if I...
Colonel?
This is strange...
Dr. Rush, is that you?
It's Colonel Young,
and I need you to put me in a room
with General O'Neill.
And I'm going to need you, too.
Sir, I told you not to get up!
What did he do to himself?
He's got cracked ribs,
more bruises than I can count,
and a concussion
that resulted in neuropraxia.
That's just great.
- Dr. Mehta.
- Can you help me, please?
I had some of my favorite arguments
with your father.
Are you saying you won some?
Depends on who you ask.
Major Green'll be escorting you
to see your mother.
Please...
Give her my condolences.
Thank you.
So how is it going out there?
Really.
I don't know what Rush has told you.
We may not have much time left.
The ship's very old, falling apart.
- Fix it.
- We're trying.
Even if we can get
the life support working,
- we don't have much food and water.
- Go get some.
We're not supposed to be there, sir.
These are the wrong people
in the wrong place, and, as a group,
they're just not qualified.
Please.
I wasn't qualified to lead
that first team through the Stargate.
- I understand that, sir.
- In the past dozen years or so,
we've sent hundreds of teams
through that thing...
And, the bottom line is...
None of us are qualified.
I just think we're gonna get
to a point very soon
where everyone on board
should get a chance to say goodbye.
Understood.
Save it.
That's not very smart.
Temperatures like these,
the human body needs...
Walk, don't talk.
Just FYI,
he's right about the whole
human body-and-water...
Walk, don't... Right.
Look.
More sand.
- This is pointless. We should go back.
- We just got here.
I still think we should be checking out
the other planets in range of the ship.
I still think you're wrong.
The solution's here.
I know it was a mirage,
but when we were walking
over that last dune?
I thought I saw the statue of Liberty
sticking half out of the sand...
Just for a second there,
I was all ready to yell:
"Damn you!
Damn you all to hell!"
Come on! That was funny.
Was it?
Because! It would mean we were really
on Earth, but in the future...
And the apes had taken over...
And then buried the statue of Liberty
for some reason.
- Have a drink.
- Greer, hold up!
Hold up!
It's not gonna work.
- Not if we keep stopping.
- I'm saying we need to split up.
Fine with me.
- I agree. You should come with me.
- No, no, you're with me and Greer.
Sun's been moving that way,
we'll call it west...
Eli, Franklin, Palmer...
And curtis,
- you head that way.
- We'll test every 20 minutes or so.
After two hours,
you head south-east...
That should take you back
to the gate.
Wait a second.
Do we really think
that splitting up is the best idea?
I say we head straight back.
There's no point in crossing over
the same territory we've just crossed.
Or...
We could just stick together.
Look, Matt...
I'm sorry,
I just have this really...
Really sick feeling
that you're gonna go that way...
And we're going to go this way...
Eli, I need someone that I can trust
to lead the second team, okay?
That is you.
Curtis is a good soldier, a tough guy.
He's not gonna let anything
- happen to you.
- Truth is...
I'm slowing you down,
you want to get rid of me.
I'm doing what I think
will best accomplish this mission.
You asked to come.
I'm telling you how you can help me.
Now suck it up.
Okay, guys...
we're going this way.
Move out!
Radio if you find the lake bed,
we'll double back.
When you see the statue of Liberty,
you know what to say, right?
Right.
Now we can make some time.
She's here?
- Right now?
- Yes, ma'am, but as I've explained...
Mrs. Armstrong...
I know I look different,
and I sound different,
but it's me.
Mom, please.
I have something to tell you.
Mom...
Stop!
I'm sorry... It's just...
The thought
that you're actually on some ship...
So far away, I can't even imagine.
Mom?
Just tell me you're coming home?
I don't know...
Mom, please!
The ship is old and damaged.
We were losing air
and somebody had to...
He's dead.
He's dead, isn't he?
Where is everyone?
Able bodies are searching the ship
for anything that might have
CO2-sequestration properties,
and the rest are in crew quarters.
Colonel, we were able
to dial out to the planet again.
Colonel Young and Chloe
are using the communication stones.
This is Colonel Telford, Dr. Mehta.
Right, okay.
Did you make radio contact
with the off-world team?
Yes, nothing to report yet.
They've split up.
How much time before
the ship jumps back to FTL?
Roughly nine hours.
Dial out every 20 minutes.
Maintain regular contact.
We do have power issues to be aware of.
Dialing the gate is a significant drain
on what seems to be limited resources
at this point.
The away mission
is priority one right now.
- Sir?
- I'm fine.
I understand that there are
other Stargates in range?
Four other addresses
came up in the system,
- but we seem to be locked out.
- Have you tried working around it?
Rush think that wasn't a good idea.
It makes sense to know
what our options are. Do what you can.
There is a reason why these addresses
are being disqualified.
If I wasn't being clear,
I was giving you an order.
If there are good reasons,
find out exactly what they are.
- Let's keep moving, I want to see more.
- You should rest.
Sir, Colonel Young's body
needs time to recover.
- Give me something for the pain.
- The body feels pain for a reason.
- I would rather not mask it.
- Just do it.
From the sounds of things,
you need my help here.
All right, come on. Let's go.
You better save some of that.
- We need to slow down.
- We need to cover more ground.
It's gonna be impossible
to maintain this pace on the way back.
Maybe for you.
How tedious...
Little boys playing "soldier."
I've no interest
in playing that game.
I'm not playing, I'm trying to save
the lives of everyone on this ship.
If you continue at this pace,
we're gonna die...
Then maybe we will.
... light-years away
from the admiring eyes of your father,
or your drill Sergeant...
Or whoever's approval it is
you so desperately seek.
How dare you!
- Get up and move.
- Did you see that?
What?
I don't know...
Nothing.
Let's move.
One hour... one hour,
and then we start circling back.
All right, fine.
- Just hold that there.
- Thank you.
What did you...
That was supposed to be for the pain.
What did you give to him?
A strong sedative,
which we are desperately short on
and I should not have had to use
so that Col. Young
can return to a body
in working condition.
You are out of line, Lieutenant.
Disregarding the health
of another human being is out of line.
I am well within my rights
as ranking medical officer.
He'll be out an hour or two.
What am I supposed to do?
I don't care.
I have other patients to attend to.
Something wrong?
No, I'm fine.
Good a place as any
to stop and test.
I take it that's not good?
No.
Hey, guys.
Another negative over here.
I'll radio Scott
and tell him we're moving on.
Yeah, but...
That's not what's going down.
- It's not?
- No.
There are four other viable addresses
in this thing.
I think I found an override
that'll allow us to dial from here...
- But...
- Look around.
This planet is a dead zone.
We should've been trying to dial
these other planets.
- Rush said...
- We don't care what Rush said.
We don't trust him.
Rush doesn't want us all to die.
That doesn't mean we trust him
to make the right decisions.
You too?
What about the lake bed?
It could be hundreds of miles
from here.
We could be blowing our only chance
of finding a place to evac.
Maybe the ship
did bring us here
because there's lime on this planet.
For all we know, the Ancients had a way
of locating it that we don't.
For that matter,
they could've stopped the ship
for longer than 12 hours to find it
and recover it with the proper tools.
The fact is, the Ancients wouldn't have
let the life-support system
get that screwed up
in the first place.
Rush is set on fixing the ship.
He's deaf to any other logic.
We need to find a planet
we can survive on.
This might be our last chance.
Gotta keep goin'.
Here.
Take it.
- I have my own.
- No, no.
I can't go on.
I'm never gonna make it back.
I know it's here.
You have to find it.
Take it.
- We're gonna leave him here?
- I'll make my way back to the gate.
- Go with him.
- I'm not leaving you here alone.
- Make sure he gets back alive.
- What difference does it make?
Because if I don't
find what we need,
he's going to be the one to find
some other way to save his own ass
and yours along with it.
You're losing it.
I'll be okay.
This is Eli. Come in.
If you can hear me, please respond.
This is Scott, what's up?
We have a problem.
Franklin, Curtis, Palmer have given up
and are headed back to the gate
to try dialing the other
addresses in the remote.
They have the kino. They don't think
we're gonna find the lime here.
They want to look for another planet
that will support life.
- They'll get themselves killed.
- We need that remote
- to get back to the ship?
- That's not the point.
A few hours is
nowhere near enough time to determine
whether a planet is even safe,
let alone viable
for sustaining life.
The ship...
The ship's our only real hope
of ever getting home.
Stop them if you can.
I'll turn back when I have to.
- Yes, sir.
- Go!
You lead.
I'm sorry, excuse me.
Miss Armstrong,
we've got to get going soon.
You get my daughter home.
Everyone is doing the best they can,
I assure you.
- That's not good enough.
- Mom, it's not his fault.
I'm a personal friend of the President
and of the first lady.
You tell your superiors
that if anything happens to her,
- I will go public with what I know.
- Mom...
I'm sorry, she's upset.
My husband...
Gave his life for my daughter.
You get her back to me,
or the whole world is going to know
what has been going on these past years.
- I need water.
- We're almost there.
I thought since I gave Scott my canteen,
we'd share.
And you were wrong about that.
I should've known.
You think you know me pretty well,
don't you?
I helped choose the personnel
for Icarus base.
I read your file.
And neither you nor Captain Marvel
were on my list, I can tell you.
You think I care?
Give me some water.
Keep walkin'.
You think,
just because you were born poor,
that it gives you the right
to be angry at the world, how pathetic.
You think that's why I'm angry?
If it wasn't for the army,
you'd be in jail, or worse.
- That's what all you rich people think.
- Rich?
My father works in a shipyard
in Glasgow.
I earned a scholarship to Oxford
while I was working two jobs.
I have got a right to make decisions
without explaining myself to you
or anyone else.
You give me some of that water!
Keep walkin'.
Give me some of that...
Don't you ever touch me.
Give me some...
And you do that again,
and I'm gonna put a bullet...
- in your face.
- Really?
I don't think so.
You need me.
Otherwise,
you'd have gladly done it by now.
Right now, I pray to the God above
that dehydration will shut you up.
Walk!
Or die here!
It's your choice,
mister...
"decision-maker."
Looks like it's worth a shot to me.
Let's do it.
Wait!
Stop!
Look, it's not perfect,
but it's better than here.
Vegetation, water, air...
- It's not too late to come with us.
- Don't go.
We'll dial back when we know it's safe
to evacuate everyone.
- You'll never get back home.
- You don't know that.
Maybe there's a way to use
the gate system to connect the dots.
There has to be a reason
the ship locked out those addresses!
Don't.
Please?
Shoot him!
Why did you do that?
He told me to.
We saved his life.
- By shooting him?
- He'll live.
You just stranded them.
We'll send them another remote.
I wasn't taking any chances.
- Where's Scott?
- Still looking for limestone.
It's almost half-time.
We only have six hours
before the ship leaves.
Lieutenant, this is Greer. Come in.
I hope he's turned back by now.
Lieutenant!
Come in?
You must keep going, my boy.
Don't give up.
I don't need you to tell me that.
I'm not going to let anyone else down
the way I let you down.
You really don't have
to follow me around to remind me.
He has his plan...
For all of us.
He's either out of radio range
or he's lying face-down in the sand,
dead, or soon-to-be.
I'm going back for him.
Well, that's great... suicide.
I'm not leaving him out here.
- I'll go with you.
- You're gonna slow me down.
This man has to get back.
He needs medical attention.
Dial.
He can take Franklin back.
You wait here for me.
You have five hours to find him
and get back here.
It has not been a pleasure
knowing you.
- What do I need that for?
- Just in case.
In case what?
I don't even know
how to fire this thing.
You'd better be here.
I will.
I have a gun.
Why do I feel like
I've been drugged?
- Good to have you back, sir.
- Son of a...
What the hell was Telford doing?
You're going to need this.
There they are.
Hurry up.
- Come on, help him.
- What happened?
Greer shot him.
Water?
That was my ration for the day.
What's going on?
We've had a lovely day at the beach.
How about you?
I have sinned, father.
I've failed you.
I've failed him.
I've failed myself.
We have redemption
through his blood.
This is Eli.
If you can hear me, please come in.
Please, respond.
Do you love her?
She's not going to have it.
You're sure?
She's 16.
We barely even know each other.
What are you going to do?
I don't know...
About anything.
I thought...
He was my calling.
But now...
I am sorry.
Why?
I'm the one who's weak.
It's my fault.
It isn't.
It's not yours.
This is Scott! Come in!
I found it, I found the lake bed!
I've got the lime!
Oh, my God.
If you can hear me, wait!
Just wait, I'm coming!
Which way?
Move out.
Drink!
Come on, Scott, come on.
Take the bag!
There's no time!
- You have to take it.
- Yes you can.
- No, I can't make it.
- Get the hell up! Come on!
I can't make it.
I can't carry you and this!
Get your weak ass up!
Come on!
Come on, soldier!
Less than three minutes
before the ship jumps again.
Incoming!
I'll stay.
It's okay.
I got it.
Sorry, sir.
You did your best.
Less than one minute.
I see them.
They're carrying something!
We've got it!
Don't go! We've got it!
They've got the lime!
- And they're not going to make it.
- 40 seconds.
Give me the radio.
I want you to stick your arm
into the event horizon of the puddle.
Seriously?
Are you sure?
No, but I'm betting there's some
kind of a safety protocol prevents
someone being cut-off while en route.
But what if there isn't?
20 seconds.
Eli, do it now!
Come on.
Come on!
Five, four, three,
two, one.
Thank you.
Scott, look at me.
Lieutenant, look at me.
Look at me!
Well done, Eli. Well done.
Look.
I brought you some water.
I still have some.
- You really need to drink it.
- I'm fine.
Everyone appreciates what you did.
Rush say how long it will last?
He's not sure.
How are you?
My parents died in a car crash
when I was four years old.
I'm sorry.
The priest, who raised me,
he pretty much drank himself
to death when I was 16.
- My God.
- I'm sorry, I'm not trying to,
diminish what you're going through.
- I know.
- I think my point is...
There's just some things
you never get over.
That's just the way it is.
You go on, though.
The best that you can.