This is what Destiny intended
from the moment it entered the system.
We are going to survive.
We are going to make it home.
The ship came here for a reason!
Destiny is powered
by the stars themselves.
He and Young are bumping heads.
Not sure which camp
is the better choice.
We pretend nothing happened...
We need to be ready
for the next encounter.
For the sake of the crew.
- Do not let him take over any system.
- He's doing it anyway.
We've sealed off Colonel Young
and most of the military personnel.
- We've taken the ship.
- You've got our attention.
- What do you want?
- All military personnel
to hand over their weapons.
I'm just a little surprised
you're taking Rush's side.
Rush was an inconvenience,
so Colonel Young left him
on that planet to die.
He has a transmitter
implanted in his chest.
That's how they were following us.
Even if we survive to the next jump,
they'll track us again.
We need to find a way
to work together.
Pretend it never happened?
You shouldn't have left him.
You think I don't know that?
Projet-SG (1.00)
www.projet-sg.com
Should you be out of bed?
There's too much work to be done.
We'd best get on with it.
"We?"
Ready.
All right,
go ahead and re-pressurize.
Re-pressurizing.
It's holding steady.
- And we've got atmosphere.
- Very good.
Continue with the repairs.
Begin with navigation and propulsion.
Roger that.
What the hell are you doing?
Repairing the damaged shuttle,
if that's all right.
- You just had surgery.
- I'm fine, thank you.
You look like you're ready
to drop dead.
And that would be a bad thing?
That would be a bad thing.
The civilians aboard this ship
didn't try to take over
because I was doing a bang-up job,
I get that.
Good for you.
I also get
that I have to make this work.
So I've ordered my people
to make a special effort.
I would like to do the same,
even with you.
That must have taken
quite the effort.
You have no idea.
Scott, we just dropped out of FTL.
Please have a team ready on standby.
- But the gate isn't dialing.
- Why not?
Because there's nothing there.
What?
It appears we have dropped out of FTL
into empty space.
No planets, no stars, nothing.
You might want to
re-check that data.
The ships that are seeding the gates
ahead of Destiny,
I thought they send a record
of the star systems in our path.
They do.
That star...
is not supposed to be here.
All right, sit tight, guys.
Gate's not dialing.
They think it might be
some kind of a glitch in the database.
And here I was worried
I'd have to cut short my delicious meal.
You okay?
Look like you might be
coming down with something.
I'm fine.
Just tired.
We call that...
Cold.
It's gonna take a little time.
"A special effort on our part
towards a spirit of
"cooperation."
The Colonel's right about that.
We have to live with these people.
Doesn't mean I got to like it.
You do.
At least, you have to look like.
Good luck with that.
Am I wrong?
Does she look like she's
coming down with something?
It's a G-2 star.
Yellow dwarf,
similar to our own sun.
Because Destiny
didn't know it was here,
the star's gravity well
disrupted our propulsion systems,
causing us to drop
out of FTL prematurely.
It's a glitch in the technology.
So what happens now?
We've entered a parabolic course.
Once we're 'round the star,
we'll be far enough away
from its gravitational influence,
back into FTL,
and on our way.
How long's that going to take?
A few weeks.
There is, however, a silver lining.
A planet?
Only one in the solar system,
so far as I can see.
About the same size as Earth.
Looks close.
It is.
Within shuttle range.
Atmosphere?
In a word?
Perfect.
I've been over the database
a dozen times.
No evidence of any glitch
or anomaly.
I couldn't find anything either.
It's like this star
just appeared out of nowhere.
Vigorous surface activity,
strong stellar winds,
bipolar outflow.
It's brand-new.
It's straight out of T-Tauri phase.
Which would still make it like,
a hundred million years old?
It's 200 million.
How far ahead of us
are those gate-seeding ships?
It doesn't make any sense.
The ships would have noticed it.
And dropped a shiny
new Stargate on the planet.
That's the weirder thing about this.
If this star really is this young,
then that planet should still be
a ball of molten rock.
We're through the upper atmosphere.
Everything looks good.
I'm going to set her down
on that land mass directly below us.
No sign of any wildlife.
That we can see.
It's pure.
- How you feeling?
- Great.
A little sunshine,
fresh air, water,
just what I needed.
Check this out!
There's a whole grove of trees
back there
loaded with these things.
It's like a kiwi.
- We'll do an edibility test...
- I'll do it.
What the hell are you doing?
- That's nice.
- We don't even know if it's poisonous.
We will.
We're getting
a ton of plant samples.
TJ thinks there's all sorts
of medicinal possibilities.
That's great.
We also found some fruit.
Greer went ahead and ate one.
So far he hasn't had
any reactions to it.
- How about water?
- Tons of it. Pure, too.
We'll bring back
as much of it as we can.
No alien creatures
slithering around?
No, nothing.
It's weird,
but it's daytime,
so who knows what comes out at night.
Load up the shuttle,
and head on back.
Do a fly-over of the area
on your way.
Copy that. Scott out.
There you are.
This place.
It reminds me of home.
We used to go camping,
Olympic Peninsula.
My dad and I, we'd go hiking
for days at a time,
find these amazing
vistas and canyons,
waterfalls...
Time to go, TJ.
Damn near perfect.
It doesn't makes any sense,
the ship not knowing about this place.
Of all the planets
to put a Stargate on,
I would think that...
Looks like
we weren't the first ones here.
It's massive.
2,000 feet high, at least.
We detected a faint em field around it,
but nothing else.
Those markings.
Like some kind of alien language.
Do you think it's the same ones
we keep running into?
Not with this level of technology.
What, to build this thing?
To create a planet.
They actually built this planet?
The Genesis Device.
The end of wrath of khan.
The reason why Destiny
had no knowledge of this star system
is that it was placed there
after the gate-seeding ships had passed.
You're telling me
they built the star too?
That would make them
the number one all-time
advanced civilization.
That would be an understatement.
So, what do we do about this?
We send a team back down there.
What?
Look, our orbit has been refined.
It's going to be four weeks,
two days, seven hours
before we jump back to FTL.
I'm proposing
we take advantage of the wait.
You said we were almost
out of shuttle range.
We are, but...
We're going to swing back into range
once we circle the star
and before we jump to FTL.
We send a team down now,
and we can pick them in a month,
loaded with supplies.
We time it right on the return,
we could take two, maybe three trips.
What about the aliens?
We didn't see them.
It doesn't mean
that they're not around.
Look, we have three hours left
before we're out of shuttle range.
If we're going to do this,
we have to do it quickly.
Just to say this out loud,
assuming that this star
and this planet
were created
by the most incredibly advanced
aliens ever,
maybe they don't want anyone
messing around with it.
We need the food and medicine.
I agree.
- The gains outweigh the risks.
- Do they?
We're 0-for-3 on close encounters
of the third kind.
What makes you think
that these guys
are gonna be different?
I'm not sending anyone down there
without protection.
And we'll have the shuttle
in case we got to bug out.
Everything we do out here is a risk.
I heard you found some plants
with possible analgesic properties?
High concentration of salicin.
Similar to aspirin.
You got a headache?
Only since I've been on this ship.
Take these, steep them in hot water,
and drink it.
So, you're joining the team
going down to the planet?
Yeah, all types of medicinals.
I can't pass it up.
- How about you?
- I don't know.
I mean, part of me wants to, but...
What if Rush's calculations are off?
Can we trust him?
You tell me.
I want 'round the clock watch
on camps.
Guard details on every science team
going into the woods.
Hopefully we'll be able to fix
the damaged shuttle before you return,
and double up on supplies
we can bring back.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
You're coming too?
Is there a problem with that?
Happy camping.
You all set?
Cole will be looking after Franklin
in the infirmary while I'm away.
I told her to contact me
if there's any change in his condition.
Anything else?
We're clear.
We'll see you in a month.
All right, folks, you got
the whole month to enjoy the scenery.
We need to set up camp,
establish a perimeter.
Sun moves that way.
Guys?
Over here?
Sun moves that way,
so that's west, okay?
River's back that way
about half a klick...
kilometer.
We'll sleep in the shuttle for now,
but I want shelters built ASAP.
How many of you guys
have gone camping before?
Well, okay, that's fine.
Just watch, ask, and learn.
You guys know your team assignments.
Let's get going.
I don't have a team yet.
Oh, yeah, right, sorry.
Do you feel like
helping TJ with plants?
Sure.
- What's going on over here?
- I'm not digging the latrine.
Is that what you told him to do?
Somebody's got to do it.
True enough.
Start digging.
What?
No, you can't make me.
You too.
- But sergeant, I...
- You're going to dig, okay?
You're both going to dig,
and you're gonna love every moment,
or you will keep digging
until you do.
The spirit of co-operation.
We're all friends now.
So we'll photograph and log
every plant we find.
Don't ingest anything
until we do a proper edibility test.
You all right?
Yeah, just...
It's passing.
I'm fine.
The amount of food and water
we get on that ship,
it's a wonder we're not all fainting
from malnutrition.
Well, I just got the word.
Destiny is now officially
out of range.
No turning back.
We are stuck here.
How's it going?
Well, I hope they bring
back tons of food.
The last of that fruit
that they brought back is already gone.
Or so you think.
Snuck this earlier.
I'll split it with you
if you promise not to rat me out.
Deal.
So, tell me...
Thanks.
You think it's possible
to create a star?
No way.
Now, being transported to a ship
on the other side of the universe
by a wormhole,
that's totally doable.
That star just appeared
out of nowhere,
and the planet's age doesn't match.
If some all-powerful alien beings
didn't create it,
who did?
I'm sorry.
I'll go somewhere else.
No, that's okay.
I wanted to thank you.
I know all the military personnel
are trying to mend fences,
but you're one of the few
who actually seems to mean it.
We've got to work it out, right?
It's interesting that we've now been
given the time down here to do that.
We were pretty lucky
to find this place.
My mom used to say
there's no such thing as luck.
Only the hand of god,
giving you a little help
when you need it most.
Somewhere along the line, I mean,
I stopped believing all that,
but now...
I look at this place,
put right in our path
for us to find.
Tell me that isn't a miracle.
How's it going?
- Terrible.
- Great.
Which is it?
Propulsion's almost completely shot.
Might be able
to fly down to the planet,
but it won't
have enough power to get back up.
So there's that.
We're making some progress
on navigation.
We can turn left,
but not right, or up, or down.
Why did you say "great"?
We can turn left.
Go ahead.
While Destiny's engines
are off-line,
I'd like to use the extra power
to strengthen the shield,
maybe explore
some damaged areas in the ship,
possibly make some repairs.
Reclaim some real estate.
Exactly.
You go ahead. I'll have
Lieutenant James put a team together.
You two, you keep at it.
You have a month to get this thing
to fly to and from that planet
and do more than make a left turn.
- Fate brought us here?
- I don't know, maybe.
Maybe that's
what brought us to Icarus
and then Destiny.
You don't believe that?
You miss your flight, the plane crashes.
You weren't spared for a reason.
God doesn't have a master plan for you.
Things just happen.
So we're born, we live, we die?
It's all random?
And along the way, you do the best with
whatever crap you happen to step in.
I'm starting to get a bad feeling.
Me too.
I'm afraid we made a mistake
sending those people
down to that planet.
The mistake was not going with them.
You okay?
Here...
Gosh...
I thought you were feeling better.
I am.
Let me help you back to camp.
You should lie down.
I'm not sick.
How far along?
About 15 weeks.
Right before we left Icarus,
but nobody knows,
and I'd like to keep it that way.
- Eventually they're going to...
- I know.
I know, but not now.
I'll figure out when the right time is.
Sure.
Back on the ship,
I wasn't doing well,
getting anemic, but out here,
with all the food and water...
Actually, the morning sickness
is a good sign.
What about the father?
What the hell is it?
I don't know yet.
Looks like a robot.
Figure it out.
No problem, once I've attended
to the other hundred things on my list.
Put somebody else on it.
I'm not going to have anyone
touch this thing without me present.
I'm going to get to it, Colonel.
Close it up.
You okay?
Homesick for Destiny?
Only a few more days
till we head back.
Honestly?
I'm not.
I like it here.
I'm starting to wonder
if Dr. Caine is right.
That it's no accident
we found this planet.
We were brought here by god?
Or whoever.
I don't know.
If some alien beings
are powerful enough
to create this place...
Maybe there is some kind
of higher power in the universe
that knew we were in trouble,
put this planet here for us to find.
Maybe it's time we
stop thinking about...
What's that?
- When?
- Tonight, just now.
Coming from the obelisk,
shooting straight up into the sky.
Dr. Volker detected
some kind of a...
A strange radiation.
He's working on it.
It's like this whole thing
suddenly came to life.
Why now?
Why not when they first got there?
Perhaps their initial impact
wasn't enough to trigger an alert.
But now...
So this light,
you think it'll bring
the aliens back to the planet?
You won't be there to find out.
Destiny is almost in range.
Colonel Young wants us
to start breaking up camp,
get ready to head back.
- What about the obelisk? I need time...
- We don't have enough time.
We need to be ready to fly
as soon as Destiny is in range
so we can make a couple trips,
and get all that food
back to the ship.
All right, you heard the man.
Move your asses!
Let's go.
Again with this?
The shuttle can fly.
It can now go both left and right
and up and down.
But like I said before,
too many problems with propulsion.
Fact is, we may never be able
to fully repair it.
All kinds of Citrus-type fruits,
beans, potatoes...
Sweet potatoes.
Scott says they're amazing.
They cannot get back here
fast enough.
You seem concerned, Dr. Rush.
Something we should know about?
No problems with your calculations?
The shuttle will return
as scheduled?
And Destiny will leave this system
never knowing who created it...
Or why.
You might want
to give her some time.
We're breaking camp,
and she takes off without telling me?
She's thinking about staying here.
A lot of people are.
Come on, you can't be surprised.
You've heard people.
They like it here.
I like it here too,
but we cannot stay.
- It is out of the question.
- Why not?
If people want to stay,
they have the right...
Where have you been?
We've got to move.
I'm not going.
I understand how you feel.
I like it here too,
but we cannot stay.
- The Colonel gave us orders...
- Matt, don't!
- I can't go back there.
- Why not?
- It's safer here.
- Safer?
The aliens who built this rock
may be on their way back!
Good.
If they're advanced enough
to build a solar system,
I know they can help
us get back home.
Not if they don't wipe us out first.
Why do you immediately think
they're going to harm us?
I'm sorry, do you not remember
what the last aliens did to you?
This planet was created for us.
We were led here for a reason.
For God's sake...
What if they don't come back?
Then what?
I'm okay with that.
I'm healthier here.
There's food and plenty of water.
And we're bringing a ton of it back!
And eventually, it'll run out.
What about the winters?
Dr. Volker, you said you found evidence
it gets very cold here.
Yes, well below freezing,
- for months, TJ.
- So we'll build better shelters.
I don't even think
it will come to that.
The beings who created
this world will return.
And they will help us get back home.
I know it.
You would rather take your chances
out here than on Destiny?
We don't know where that ship is going,
or if we'll ever even make it home.
There's a Stargate on it.
As long as we have...
Matt...
I'm pregnant.
I can't go back there.
I can't stand the thought
of raising a child on that ship.
We are in range. You are clear
to make the first trip back.
We only have the one shuttle,
so time is of the essence.
Sir...
- We have a problem down here.
- What is it?
Some of the people have decided
they would like to stay on the planet.
You tell them no.
I tried.
They have pretty much
made up their minds.
Who are they?
11 people total.
Dr. Caine,
Chloe,
- Lieutenant Johansen...
- What?
No! Scott, you tell them...
And me.
- 11?
- Including some of my own people.
And Scott, he has the nerve
to ask me
to fly him back down to the planet
after he drops off
the ones returning to the ship.
I can understand
some of them wanting to stay,
but Lieutenant Scott and TJ?
Yeah, he says he feels an obligation
to help the people
survive down there.
- What are you going to do?
- I'm going to make sure
they don't stay down there.
You cannot force them to come back.
I think he can.
We're going to lose more people
through attrition aboard this ship.
We simply cannot afford
to shed that many people at one time.
What do you expect him to do?
Bring them back at gunpoint?
Well, if it comes to that, yes.
You allow Lieutenant Scott
to return with those
who want to come back to Destiny,
then send down a military
detail and round up the rest.
That's great, Rush, coming from you.
First you want to kick the military out,
and now you want us
rounding people up at gunpoint.
Those people have the right
to make their own decisions
about their future.
Not all of them.
Did you...
Dd you tell him about me?
I'll let you do that.
It's not my place.
He is the father, right?
I caught a few looks between you.
I don't think anyone else knew.
I haven't heard any rumors
or anything.
You are going to be okay.
I'll be here,
and I'm not going
to let anything happen to you.
- Have you gone mad?
- I really don't want to argue with you.
- You're letting them stay?
- Not all.
- You're giving them a shuttle?
- It's damaged.
It's not damaged anymore!
You said that the shuttle
may never be fully functional.
- We may need the shuttle...
- I'm not going to leave them down...
You cannot let them stay...
I have made my decision.
Is it ready?
Yeah, but there's still some issues
as to whether it can hold up
through atmospheric entry.
Questions that are about
to be answered.
Eli just radioed.
Colonel Young is on his way
down here.
Why?
How?
We're entering upper atmosphere.
So far so good.
Come on, hold it together.
Yeah, right there!
Destiny, this is Young.
I made it through.
Has anyone changed their minds
about returning to the ship?
Here's the deal.
I am leaving
the damaged shuttle behind
for those who want to stay.
You can use it
for shelter and power,
fly around in short hops
on the surface.
You will not be able to leave
the atmosphere, so don't even try.
What it will do
is give you guys a fighting chance
while you are down here,
especially with winter on the way.
Thank you.
I know this isn't...
I'm not finished.
I will leave it for you
only under one condition.
All military personnel
will return with me to Destiny.
Reject my proposal,
and we'll take you all back by force.
- You can't do that.
- That's not something you want to test.
Sir, some of these people
just don't feel safe on board.
None of us feels safe.
- That doesn't mean we give up.
- They're not.
That ship is the best chance we have
of getting home.
I disagree, sir.
I believe we were brought here
for a reason,
and that whoever created this planet
will provide for us.
They are our best chance
of getting back home.
What's it going to be?
You want to stay here
out of obligation to these people.
To protect them.
I can respect that,
but there are people back on the ship
who don't have a choice,
and you have an obligation
to them as well.
They need you.
Welcome home.
As predicted,
we've corrected our course
and jumped back into FTL.
I'm sorry you didn't get your wish.
And what wish was that?
Aliens advanced enough
that they could build a star system.
Finally somebody you could
have a decent conversation with.
I enjoy chess.
- Do you have a moment?
- Can it wait?
I wanted to better explain my reasons
for choosing to stay behind.
Look, I realize you're probably
not hungry, Lieutenant, but I am.
I hear they're serving up
a feast in the mess,
so why don't we talk about it later?
- Sir...
- Later.
What if we were meant to stay there?
All of us?
What if that planet was a lifeline,
and we just let it go?
I can't pretend to answer that,
Matthew.
No one can.