This is what Destiny intended
from the moment it entered the system.
We are going to survive.
We are going to make it home.
The ship came here for a reason.
Destiny is powered
by the stars themselves.
He and Young are bumping heads.
Not sure which camp
is the better choice.
I don't know what to do with myself.
I'm the last person who should be here.
You're the wrong man for the job.
You don't believe in the mission.
Neural interface?
A repository of knowledge
that can be downloaded into one's mind.
Do you know what this device
did to General O'Neill?
- The informations overwhelmed him.
- It damn near killed him.
Young is not going to listen,
and Dr. Rush,
well, like you said,
he's in no hurry to come home.
He's completely unresponsive.
You just couldn't wait?
Anyone who had access to that room
was ordered not to sit in that chair.
You wanted somebody there
because you didn't have the guts
to do it yourself!
This is someone trying to undermine
the Colonel's authority.
We cannot let that happen!
Somebody's trying to frame me.
Where's Rush?
He didn't make it.
No headaches?
Any blurry vision?
I'm fine.
You sleeping okay?
I'm good. I gotta go.
You lost someone under your command.
Most recently, three people.
Gorman, Spencer, and Rush.
It happens.
I know how much it affects you.
In different ways, I let them down.
- If you ever want to talk, I'm here.
- I don't.
You should.
I'm sorry?
You felt like you let
Sergeant Spencer down.
We all do.
There's been a lot going on
between you and Rush.
- What are you saying?
- That a lot has been left unresolved.
Another time.
Off to file your latest report
back to Earth?
That's right.
I'm curious about the details
you intend to provide
regarding the incident
with Dr. Rush.
Exactly what happened.
I'm scheduled to file my report
with Earth later today,
and it may cast some doubt
on your version of events.
There were only two people
on that planet, me and Rush.
I'm talking about the obvious issues
between the two of you.
That doesn't change anything.
If you want to accuse me,
you should have the guts
to come out and accuse me.
- I don't have proof of anything.
- You just want to be in charge again.
I'm saying you had plenty of motive.
Really?
Do you think that I want people
suspecting me of murder?
Maybe that burden is easier to bear
than actually dealing with Rush.
I'll admit it, I don't miss the man.
I say we're all better off.
That's reassuring.
So if you don't measure up,
you just get left for dead?
What exactly is the criteria, then,
for sticking around?
Do you agree?
Let's do this.
All good?
All good.
When you get a chance,
can you check the shower system?
- The pressure's been kind of low.
- Sure, once I'm done here.
Caine's pretty cute.
There is nothing sexier
than a widower.
A man who's proven
that he can make a commitment
and is single through
no fault of his own.
- What more could you ask for?
- I can hear you.
I'm so sorry!
How about we just...
Carry on like nothing happened?
Thanks.
God... Kill me now.
All right, I think we're ready.
Welcome aboard Destiny.
I'm Lieutenant Matthew Scott.
- You okay?
- Excuse me?
Who are you?
Sergeant, what happened?
I have absolutely no idea, sir.
Now, what do you think?
I'm an IT tech.
You know, I fix earth computers.
Not ancient communication devices.
Malfunction in the connection?
- That's quite a hiccup.
- I've seen worse.
We don't exactly know
what these stones do, do we?
Not personally.
I just got put on stone duty
'cause Riley's not back on his feet yet.
Sir, you have been
under quite a bit of stress.
You're not suggesting
that I imagined it?
Whoever took over your body
was acting...
- Kind of strangely
- Look...
There is no way that I hallucinated
that ship or that alien.
My imagination isn't that good.
I was on a ship, and I saw an alien.
Now...
I want to know exactly what happened,
what went wrong and why.
Until then, the communications room
and that device are off-limits.
Understood?
- Got a minute?
- Please, sit.
You know, I always figured
limited resources meant
that every day would be
a struggle for survival,
but I never thought
it would come to this.
- That's some sort of hint?
- Yeah, it's a hint.
If you're wondering what to get me
for christmas, I need socks.
I heard about today's incident.
Caine's looking into it.
You know, I find it interesting
that the device just happens
to malfunction moments after we had
our conversation this morning.
- I guess it's kind of coincidental.
- That's one word.
Another is "convenient".
And another is "surprising".
Okay, your turn.
You actually think that...
This will keep me
from filing my report back to Earth?
Actually, yeah.
No, I'm pretty sure it will.
When the time comes,
let's hope that those
who sit in judgment of you
grant the mercy you denied Dr. Rush.
I believe you mean
"allegedly" denied Dr. Rush.
Communications with Earth
will resume
as soon as I am completely satisfied
that the next attempt to connect
will not result
in another coincidence,
or convenience,
or a surprise.
Thank you.
We have tomatoes...
We finally have tomatoes!
More or less.
That's odd.
So I was talking to Dr. Inman,
and she said the hydroponics team
will have strawberries for us
in about a month.
Sort of strawberries.
Talk to me when they start growing meat.
Actually, they're working
on a soy-based protein.
Happy thanksgiving, everyone.
Enjoy your tofurkey.
You're in a bad mood.
- What's the matter?
- I haven't slept much.
Colonel Young has me working
round the clock trying to figure out
- everything that Rush was working on...
- You can't be serious.
Colonel Young was willing
to sacrifice his own life
so that one of us could have a shot
at getting on the shuttle
when the ship was heading
towards that star.
You think he's
a cold-blooded murderer?
I wasn't saying that.
It's fine.
Can you believe it?
Tomatoes!
What?
From the second we got on this ship,
they've been calling all the shots.
What we eat, where we sleep.
What we do and when.
And we just sit back and let them.
They're the ones with the guns.
I mean, we have every right
to be afraid.
Look at what happened
to the last person to challenge them.
So...
What do you think we should do?
I don't know...
Purple plants?
Are you kidding me?
Purple chlorophyll is sensitive
to red and infrared light.
The planet's probably
orbiting a red dwarf.
The kino says breathable atmosphere,
water, and oxygen.
I'm concerned about potential
stellar flare activity.
Spot radiation.
All right, then. We'll suit up.
You've got to see this.
It just showed up.
Bringing it up...
Now.
What is it doing?
Nothing, yet.
It's just sitting there.
We should try communicating with it.
How?
We have broadcast capability.
Of course, there's no way
they'd understand us.
But I guess there's only
one way to find out.
Two alien encounters in a day.
What are the chances?
I am thinking likely... Zero.
Okay, sending... Now.
Let's hope they speak Ancient.
This can't be a coincidence.
I bet you I was
on that ship this morning.
You piqued their curiosity,
they came to check on us?
I'm thinking they've been
checking on us for a while.
There's no other way
they can find us this fast.
They... Answered back.
That's not a translation.
- They answered in English.
- Now, how the hell is that possible?
What did you say?
"We're peaceful humans
from planet Earth.
We mean you no harm
and we'd like to meet you."
- What do I do? What do I say back?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
Get our weapons on-line.
This is Colonel Young.
All personnel,
report to designated areas.
I need you and Greer
in that shuttle.
Something's happening.
I think they're launching
smaller ships.
Oh, my god.
Only 30% of the weapons
are coming on-line.
Rush put limits.
Right, after what happened to Riley.
We were still in the process
of checking each gun's functionality.
Find a way around it.
Disengaging.
Come on.
First real space battle over here.
- You got it?
- Just about.
Activate the forward battery.
That's what I'm trying to do.
- Come on, get back. Come on.
- Let's go.
We're taking heavy fire!
- Can you boost power to the shields?
- I'm workin' on it.
Shield power is being
drained by the weapons.
Come on, move, go.
Stay back!
We've got surges all over the ship.
The weapons system wasn't ready.
Eli, everyone onboard this ship
is counting on you.
- I don't need to hear that.
- You can do this.
- No. No, I can't!
- Yes, you can.
- Why is this all on me? What about him?
- I don't care.
Both of you!
I need this ship working now!
You should've thought of that
before you got rid of Rush.
Just fix it.
You guys okay?
Check her!
They're pulling back.
Colonel Young, this is Airman Dunning.
Please respond.
- They're retreating.
- We got 'em on the run.
Let's give them something
to remember us by.
I need you to end pursuit
and fall back to Destiny.
But...
Do not engage.
I repeat, do not engage.
Chloe may be on board
one of those ships.
- What the hell happened?
- Easy, Lieutenant.
It was nobody's fault.
We were not ready for this.
- They gave up pretty quickly.
- The attack may have been a distraction
to try to come in close
and take prisoners, try to gain intel.
- Why are we the enemy?
- I don't know.
Sir, that ship is still
within shuttle range.
- Request permission to...
- Denied.
You wouldn't stand a chance.
With me.
- What are we going to do?
- I'm going after her.
- How?
- The communication device.
Sir, you are only assuming
that's the same ship...
Guess I'll find out
when I'm on board.
Let's elevate this.
Have a seat,
and I'll get to you as soon as I can.
Thanks so much.
- Anything I can do?
- Take your pick.
Grab some gauze.
Chloe was taken.
What? How?
One of the ships latched on,
cut a hole.
- I can't get a pulse over here!
- Grab the bag.
Keep the pressure on him, please.
Caine, we need you.
Okay, that's good.
Tighter.
Let me do it.
It's not going to happen.
For the record,
I think this is a very bad idea.
Yes, but it's the best
of the bad ideas.
Go.
I think I got most of the weapons
back on-line.
- How long is he going in for?
- 20 minutes, then we pull him out.
You can always go back in
if you don't find her.
We are not your enemy.
We mean you no harm.
I don't think it understands you.
They spoke English.
They sent a one-word message.
For all we know, they have a translation
device on their ship or something.
Then they would have
sent it in Ancient.
Why did you attack us?
Why did you take
one of our people prisoner?
Why did you do that?
You want to help me?
This is how you read my mind.
Do you understand?
This one transmits.
This one receives.
Like this. Here, like this.
Do not engage.
Chloe may be aboard
one of those ships.
- What happened?
- He's back.
What just happened?
The alien ship is closing in on us.
Send me back.
Send me back!
Good to go.
Ready.
It's not working.
Why isn't it working?
Untie me.
There doesn't seem to be
anything wrong with the device.
Did you find Chloe?
Guys? You may have noticed
they're attacking us again.
Our shields aren't
going to hold for much longer.
Bring the main weapon on-line.
Fire on the big ship.
Chloe is still on board that ship!
Do it now, Eli!
Return fire!
Everything we've got!
We can't keep this up.
The weapons system is overloading.
- Shields are down almost 50%.
- I know!
- Where are you going?
- To try and save Chloe.
It's okay, it's okay.
We have to go.
Here.
Oh, God...
Where are we going?
This way.
Report!
Bad and more bad.
Too much power
is going to the weapons.
- Our shields are going to fail.
- Bolster them.
Devote all remaining weapons power
to the main weapon.
Keep firing on the big ship.
Not like you,
taking the shuttle without asking.
He'll say no, and I don't want
to disobey an order.
- You got a problem with that?
- You want to save her?
Do it.
I'm going.
You don't have to.
I'm already here.
- They're retreating.
- Keep firing.
We fire again,
and we risk blowing ourselves up.
I don't have a choice.
Do it.
They're...
They're retreating.
All of them except that one.
Wait.
They're gone.
Colonel Young said you were dead.
Did he?
- Did he say how it happened?
- Rock slide.
Obviously, he was wrong again.
This is Greer.
Come in.
Go ahead.
You are not going to believe this.
I managed to...
activate the...
systems on the crashed ship.
Found a database.
I'd only just begun
to look through it when...
aliens showed up.
I guess I must have
accidentally activated
some kind of distress beacon.
Anyway, I'm glad I did.
I would have died out there.
There are a few people who thought
Colonel Young left you to die
on purpose.
I imagine there were.
He would have rightly assumed
that I was... I was gone,
in the rock slide.
So, what happened
when the aliens brought you
on their ship?
To be honest?
I don't remember that much.
The few times I was conscious,
they were... probing my mind.
I'd rather not think about it.
I know they were frustrated.
I seemed to be able to resist
giving them the information they wanted.
He used their own
neural interface against them,
getting what he needed
so we could escape.
Location of the fighter bay,
basic operating systems.
Anything else?
Like why they wanted to destroy us?
I don't think they did.
What they really want
is Destiny.
Probably only care about us
because we recently came aboard.
What they want
is a way past her defenses,
try and find out
what secrets she might hold.
Unfortunately, I didn't have time
to find out any more.
My first priority was getting
Chloe and I
off the ship.
It's good to have you back.
Both of you.
I suppose you're wondering...
- Why I didn't tell everyone the truth.
- It's your word against mine.
I didn't tell anyone you tried
to frame me for Spencer's death.
Well, that's true.
No, I just wanted to know
whether I can assume
that you are going to
try and kill me again
next chance you get.
I saved you from those aliens.
You fired on the alien ship
- while I was still aboard.
- Well, so was Chloe.
That was a command decision,
protecting the greater good.
Yes, indeed.
Look...
I realize...
That I did provoke you.
If it means anything...
Regret leaving you on that planet.
Don't get me wrong.
You deserved it,
but I regret that I lost control,
that I became a man that
I couldn't respect anymore.
You're here, I'm here.
We just have to live with it, don't we?
So does everyone else on board.
They don't need the distraction.
They don't need
to doubt their leadership,
and this ship needs to be ready
for the next encounter.
If we haven't found
our way home by then.
Of course.
So, what?
We just pretend nothing happened?
Well, it's not like
we were ever friends.
For the sake of the crew.
Hey there.
- Do you mind?
- No, it's okay.
You want to try some?
What is it?
A little something
that Dr. Inman's been working on.
She claims it tastes like gin.
I say it's a little closer
to rubbing alcohol.
Solid sales pitch.
No, thank you.
All right.
What do you think?
You and James,
any chance there?
It could just get really awkward.
You know, if things didn't work out.
Being stuck on this ship with someone
you've had a bad relationship with?
No thanks.
It's probably best
to just keep things...
professional.
For as long as we can.
Anyways, I mean, we'll see.
If we're here much longer,
I hereby reserve the right
to completely change my mind.
The Colonel's dangerous.
We need to do something about that.
I tried.
I know.
Damn near killed me for it.
Next time will be different.