And now dancing on stage three,
the pride of St. Paul...
Corvette!
That's the money for the orphanage!
That means, Mr. Lashade,
you're the Cobra.
Sorry, baby, it's just business.
All this time it was you!
Pretty and smart, what a shame.
Razzle dazzle!
Autumn, Crystal, bad news.
Corvette was working for the Cobra.
But fear not...
He will pay.
And... Cut!
- Check the gate!
- Checking.
Here, let me give you a hand.
Thank you. Billy Dee,
it was so great working with you.
No, the pleasure's all mine.
Thank you so much.
- You're sweet.
- Take care.
You, too.
All right.
That's a series wrap for Corvette!
Let's hear it for Nikki!
Well done!
Thank you. Thanks.
Brilliant, Nikki, as always.
You know, you don't need to die.
We can bring you back next season.
How?
Well, we could say that...
Corvette was wearing a bulletproof vest.
Bulletproof breast.
Look, I'm just a guest star,
and we all know what happens
to guest stars.
Now that your work's done here,
I suppose you'll be leaving Sydney
and heading back to L.A.
No, I'm not leaving Sydney.
I love you.
And I love you, too.
Son of a bitch.
All right. Come on. Let's go one more.
You said best out of five.
Well, now we're goin' best of seven.
You okay?
What happened?
Pa... l... s...
- What the hell did she say?
- I don't know.
Let's get her some water. Get help.
What are you doin'? Get movin'!
Dude...
Nikki's dead.
Who the hell's Nikki?
Subtitles : www.swsub.com
Howie, the frittada is amazing.
It's my new chef.
He's fantastic.
Paulo, come in here.
- Yes, sir?
- Paulo, my boy, you have a new fan.
I'd like you to meet Nikki.
The food is amazing.
You're too kind.
The secret is the shaved truffles.
Luckily for you, they are in season.
You know, you should ask for a raise.
Excuse me.
He just came to Sydney.
Heard I was hiring
and showed up at my office every day
until I gave him the job.
Apparently, back home, he's the...
Wolfgang Puck of Brazil.
Here.
Try one of his homemade rolls.
Please, please do.
It's...
Beautiful.
Howie, you shouldn't have.
I realize, of course, it's not a ring.
Not yet, but, when my wife...
He's gone.
I would have loved it
if you could've figured out a way
where I didn't have to eat
the same food as him.
So nobody else knows about this thing?
Everything in here is way off the books.
- What?
- Ashes are evidence, Paulo.
We poisoned him.
Let's not poison ourselves.
Razzle frickin' dazzle.
What happened?
We don't know.
She's got no gunshot wound,
no knife wound,
no polar bear bite, nothing.
Maybe it was something she ate.
Maybe she was poisoned.
We should check the food supply
to see if anyone else is sick.
She's got gunk under her fingernails.
Where'd you find her?
Right here.
She stumbled out of the jungle,
face planted.
She said something like "plywood"
and... sayonara.
Actually,
I think she said "power lines."
Who the hell knows what she said?
She was 5 seconds from dying.
She was probably seein' the light
at the end of the tunnel.
"Paulo lies!" That's what she said.
"Paulo lies," not "power lines."
Paulo lies.
Who the hell's Paulo?
Paulo's her...
husband or boyfriend
Whatever. They lived down the beach.
Well, where the hell is he?
'cause if he lies,
that might be a good place to start.
"English expat, Howard L. Zuckerman,
"the creative force behind
such hit shows as Exposé,
"Strike Team Alpha
and Dr. Kincaid, Esquire,
"was found dead
in his palatial Sydney estate
"from heart failure."
Are you chewing gum?
Nicotine gum.
I quit.
A toast...
To our new life together.
Cheers.
There's nowhere to sit.
No tables, no chairs, nothing.
Good call, Boone.
You want me to grab a chair
from the restaurant?
Forget it. Let's just leave!
You already screwed us
out of seats in first class.
Why would you be able to find them here?
Hey, can I have this chair, please?
Yeah. Be my guest.
Boone, let's just go!
Thanks anyway.
I'm coming, Shannon.
If you quit flirting with random guys,
maybe we could actually
get on the plane.
Promise me we'll never end up like them.
I promise.
Please help!
Get away from there!
Hey! Get back! Get down!
Are we alive?
Did we survive?
Look at me. Am I okay? Am I okay?
Do you have a pen?
Pen?
Does anybody have a pen?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Baby, look at me. Look at me.
Where's the bag?
- What?
- The bag.
Paulo, where is it?
I'm telling you, this is the trail.
What do you know about tracking?
- Well, I know what a footprint is.
- Over here.
I'm guessin' that's Paulo.
He's just like Nikki. No wound, nothing.
Yeah, I know.
Why are his pants undone?
- And why is his shoe in that tree?
- Maybe he stepped on something.
You see something?
Nothing.
Don't.
Dude,
what are you doing?
Two people are dead.
You ever think
they might have been poisoned.
That's evidence.
You're messing up the crime scene.
Crime scene?
Is there a forensics hatch
I don't know about?
Monster.
How many times do I have to tell you,
there's no such thing as monsters?
Maybe it was a dinosaur.
It's not "Jurassic Park," Paulo.
It's the South Pacific.
Then what was it?
You saw the trees move.
Would you start focusing?
We've been here for six days, okay?
The coast guard
is gonna get here any second,
and I really don't think
that they're gonna take,
"hey, you know what?
I'm looking for my script bag"
as an excuse
for not getting on the rescue boat.
Did you guys lose your luggage?
I lost mine, too.
I found some other stuff, though,
so if you need anything,
pants or sweatshirt...
I can help you find some that fit.
I'm Ethan, by the way.
Hi. I'm Nikki...
and this is Paulo.
And you are so sweet, Ethan, but
actually, we're not looking for clothes.
Paulo here lost his nicotine gum.
You might have more luck
looking inland.
In the jungle?
The plane split apart
when it was over the island,
so some of the stuff might have
rained down in there.
Boone took the water!
What is going on?
Someone had to take responsibility.
It would have never lasted.
Leave him alone!
It's been six days,
and we're all still waiting
for someone to come.
We have to stop waiting.
We need to start figuring things out.
Now I found water,
fresh water up in the valley.
I'm taking a group at first light.
If y don't want to come,
then find another way to contribute,
because every man for himself
is not gonna work.
But if we can't live together...
we're gonna die alone.
I'm with Jin.
It's the monster.
Yeah, because that makes
the most sense.
It does.
Locke said when Eko died,
his last words were,
"you're next,"
and Nikki and Paulo were with them.
He was talking about them.
He wasn't saying
"you're next" about them.
He was saying "you're next"
as in you're all next.
Yeah, that's not really better.
All right, so here's how I see it.
We wanna know what happened?
We gotta find out whatever we can
about these jabonies.
Ja-bo-nies?
Nina and Pablo.
Dude, show some respect.
You know their names.
It Nikki and Paulo.
Whatever, Hugo.
Where's their tent?
And we better get some shovels.
Hey, Dr. Arzt.
Oh, hi.
You're a scientist, right?
And an educator, yes.
What are you doing
with all this stuff?
Well, since we got here,
I've discovered 20 new species.
I'm gonna be the next Charles Darwin.
That is, latrodectus regina.
Very dangerous.
They call her the medusa spider.
Her pheromones are very strong,
one whiff, and every male of the species
would be here in seconds.
Not unlike you, I guess.
So you're probably too busy
to help me, then.
No, not at all.
I'm fine. I can help you.
What can I do you for?
Well, I'm trying to find my luggage,
and since the plane broke apart
over the jungle,
I was wondering if you knew
about trajectories and stuff.
Do I?
Do I know about trajectories?
Allow me to draw you a map, madam.
Are you sure we should be listening
to a high school science teacher?
Junior high, and yes.
What's your problem with Leslie, anyway?
Leslie?
You're jealous!
Of him? Never.
Yeah, his spiders
turned me on so much,
I had to sleep with him to get the map.
I wouldn't be surprised.
You slept with Zuckerman.
I did that for us.
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm just...
I don't trust that guy.
We should've gone to Ethan.
He would've helped.
Paulo, look.
Another plane.
Looks like it's been here a while.
Go up there.
Maybe there's a radio or some...
Are you insane?
If I go up there,
that thing's gonna fall.
You're not gonna fall.
What? You want me to die?
Come on. Let's keep going.
What is that?
Okay. Let's do it.
Let's check it out.
So our carry-on bag fell from the sky,
opened a manhole, crawled inside
and closed the doors
behind itself?
You don't wanna climb up to a plane...
but now you want to climb down
a ladder into a dark tunnel?
I don't think so.
Hey, man, be careful.
Why? They don't live here anymore.
So Sun checked the food.
They're eating the same as us,
and no one else is sick.
Could be a virus.
Dude... Monster.
Creepy. They collected bugs?
I think these were Arzt's.
He collected all kinds of
different creepy crawlies before he...
Exploded.
They must've been friends.
Exposé.
Did you just say Exposé?
What the hell's Exposé?
Only the most awesome hour
of television ever.
It was like Baywatch, only better.
You've got Autumn and Crystal--
two stripers that solve crimes
with the help of their suave,
smooth-talking club owner, Mr. Lashade.
How'd I miss that one?
Check it out.
Look at the cast list. Nikki Fernandez.
That's gotta be
why she was in Australia.
This must've been her big break.
Certainly sounds like it.
No way.
Mr. Lashade was the Cobra?
Is that supposed to mean something?
Dude, the Cobra's the big bad guy.
His identity's been shrouded
in mystery for four seasons.
They had a walkie-talkie?
Every damn one of those bastards
on the other side of the island
had one exactly like this
hanging from their belts.
So how did Nikki and Paulo get one?
I'll tell you how.
They were working with the others.
What gives you the right?
You have to understand.
We thought it was best for everybody.
I'm sorry.
Are you my mother?
Because she knows what's best for me.
Other than that, I decide.
Hey. What's going on?
Kate and her two boyfriends found a case
of guns that fell out of the plane,
but they decided not to tell the camp.
Look, the case is locked.
The key is around Jack's neck,
all right?
I promise you, they're safe.
You're all out of control.
The pigs are walkin'.
The pigs are walking!
So... where did you say
you found that case?
It's just water, Paulo.
Stop being such a wuss and dive in.
Why me?
Well, as you had
no trouble reminding me,
I slept with Howie Zuckerman, so
the least you could do is go for a swim.
And Kate said they found the case
on the bottom.
- Let me ask you something.
- What?
If you didn't need me to find that bag,
would we still be together?
That bag is worth $8 million.
Just dive in, Paulo.
Well?
Nothing.
There's nothing down there?
Just dead bodies.
Okay, so they had
a walkie-talkie.
You think they were working
with the others? Like, how?
Like Michael.
If that's the case,
then why'd they kill Nikki and Paulo?
Who knows why those people do anything?
What matters is they could be out there
right now waiting to get us.
I don't know, dude.
I was with the others,
like, two weeks ago.
They're on the total
other side of the island.
Then who dragged me into the jungle?
The others came into our camp.
They grabbed me, put a bag over my head.
And if I hadn't gotten away,
they would have killed me.
Look, y'all stay here.
Let me see if I can see any sign of 'em.
I'll do a perimeter sweep.
- Where'd you get the gun?
- Got it off one of them.
And when were you gonna let us know?
I guess right now.
What exactly is a perimeter sweep?
Shouldn't we cover them up?
Yes, of course.
Nice night.
- Whatcha doing?
- Nothing.
It looks like you're digging a hole.
Every man's entitled to his secrets,
but can I give you
a piece of advice?
Please, John.
You should put the shovel away
and save yourself some trouble.
Why is that?
Things don't stay buried on this island.
The beach is eroding.
Winter's coming, high tide.
Whatever it is you're hiding, make sure
you pick a spot that won't wash away.
See you back at camp.
Who left this open?
Tom was down here
a couple of days ago.
Well, have him cover it up
with the plane.
That him?
- Shephard?
- Yes.
He's cute.
Why are we doing this?
Shephard will never agree
to do the surgery.
No. I can convince him to do it.
How?
Same way I get anybody to do anything.
I find out what
he's emotionally iested in,
and I exploit it.
So what,
we just grab all three of them,
Ford and Austen, too?
No, they need to come to us.
And how do we make that happen?
Michael, of course.
Are we done here?
This place gives me the creeps.
You hear about what happened
to Nikki and Paulo?
Aye. Tragic.
So... do you know anything?
How do you mean?
Can you... you know,
use your psychic powers?
Doesn't work like that.
I only see flashes.
No offense, dude, but...
as far as superpowers go...
yours is just kinda lame.
Thanks anyway.
I do know she was
with your mate this morning.
My mate?
I saw her with your boy Sawyer...
The dead girl, Nikki.
He said he didn't know her.
Then why was she yelling at him?
Yelling?
At Sawyer, this morning?
Right before she died.
Vincent! Dude!
So he saw Sawyer and Nikki fightin'.
- That doesn't prove athing.
- Look at the facts and ask yourself,
why is Sawyer so gung how
about investigating this?
What's in it for him?
He pretended he didn't know their names,
but then he was fighting with Nikki.
Sawyer's not a murderer.
He went all the way across
the island to help Michael.
It is the others.
I know what they can do.
Okay, you know what?
I'll go get Desmond.
He'll tell you exactly what he saw.
It was me.
What?
It was me who took you, not the others.
I wasn't myself.
After Locke hit me...
After he humiliated me...
Sawyer told me I could get even
by helping him steal the guns.
We just made it...
look like... the others.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
Sorry.
Hey, everybody.
We're heading out to the pearl station.
There's a computer there that
might help us find our people.
- Anybody wanna come along?
- I'll go.
- Great.
- What?
Anybody else wanna come, meet us
at the tree line in ten minutes,
and bring water.
You're not serious.
What? You always whine
about not being included.
Now's our chance.
Hey, guys,
what are these other tvs for?
Sorry?
All these tvs.
This guy says
that there's six stations...
So maybe some of these tvs
are connected to the other hatches.
Well, I'm suddenly feeling very stupid.
Perhaps I could patch in
one of the other feeds,
see if we can get another picture.
The toilet still works.
Give me the gun.
What the hell you talking about?
Give it to me.
It ain't even loaded.
Then how are you
sweeping the perimeter?
Quit lying, dude.
Desmond saw you fighting
with Nikki this morning.
Oh, I see what this is.
The villagers have got
themselves some torches.
Did you kill them?
No, I didn't kill them.
Yeah, me and Nikki
went at it this morning...
'cause she wanted a gun.
Why didn't you tell us this before?
'cause of the dirt under her nails.
- What?
- She was digging,
and when we found him,
I saw a fresh mound of dirt.
She was burying somethin',
and if you take the time to dig a hole
right before you die,
then what you're hiding's
probably pretty damn good.
So what was it?
What did she hide?
Go ahead. Take 'em.
'cause whatever happened to those two,
I had nothing to do with it.
Did you know thanksgiving
was two weeks ago?
We missed it, Paulo,
just like we're gonna miss everything.
They're going to find us.
We'll get rescued.
You'll see.
Okay, where did this sudden
burst of optimism come from?
I don't know. I guess...
It's how you look at things...
Like the bag.
I mean,
maybe not finding it was good for us.
How do you figure that?
Look what it did.
It might have... torn us apart.
Wait here.
I'm gonna get us some breakfast.
Okay, I know you have them.
Give me a gun.
I don't have the guns.
- A- team took 'em all.
- Right,
except for the ones
you kept for yourself.
Even if I had a gun,
I wouldn't give it to you.
Judging by the fire you're breathin',
I got a feeling
no good would come of it.
Sawyer, give me a gun.
I got a better idea, sister.
How about you go stick your head
in the ocean and cool yourself off?
Thanks for nothin'.
And who the hell are you?
Charlie told me it was your idea...
to kidnap me.
You gonna tell Jin?
Why not?
Because then we'd have
to dig another grave.
Why are you giving me these?
Because they're worthless here.
See, I thought I was gonna
get out of this without a...
Nikki and Paulo...
I guess we didn't
really know you very well,
and it appears you killed
each other for diamonds.
But I know there are
good parts to you, too.
You were always nice to me,
and you were a member of the camp.
And...
I really loved Exposé.
Okay, then.
- Good-bye.
- Wait.
Rest in peace, Nikki and Paulo.
Come on, Nikki, just tell me.
It's a surprise.
We're almost there.
Okay, ready?
I found the diamonds.
What? Where?
Right here.
Give them to me.
What are you talking about?
What am I talking about?
What's this?
Your nicotine gum?
You wanted to stop looking for the bag
because you'd already found it.
I know you have them, Paulo,
so where are they?
Calm down, okay?
What the hell is that?
Are you out of your mind?
You remember Dr. Arzt's friend.
Did it bite you?
Does it hurt?
He told me why they call it
"the medusa spider."
Wanna know why?
What did you do?
Because one look from medusa
would turn anyone to stone,
just like one bite from the spider
will paralyze you...
For... oh, about eight hours.
It won't kill you.
It'll just...
slow your heart rate down to the point
where even a doctor
would have a hard time...
hearing it beat.
You won't be able to move a muscle,
so I'll be able to do all sorts
of nasty things to you.
And since it bit you on your neck,
I'd say paralysis will happen fast.
I'm guessing that
you have the diamonds on you.
In a shoe, maybe?
I think I know where.
Son of a bitch.
I'm sorry.
You're only sorry 'cause you got caught.
I was... afraid...
of losing you.
If you found the diamonds...
you wouldn't need me anymore.
Damn it!
You okay?
Hey, what happened?
I'm paralyzed.