Previously on Lost...
Desmond said I was gonna die.
He told me he has
these flashes... visions.
When I saw the lightning hit the roof,
you were electrocuted.
And when you heard
Claire was in the water,
you drowned trying to save her.
I dove in myself, so you never went in.
No matter what I try to do,
you're gonna die, Charlie.
There's a woman in Hurley's tent
who parachuted
onto the island yesterday.
She says that the boat she took off from
is about 80 miles off the coast,
and if she can find a way to contact it,
we'll all be rescued.
Why didn't anyone tell me this?
Because they don't trust you.
Kwon is pregnant.
Where'd you get that?
You really think
you're in a position to ask questions?
I told Jack what they were making me do.
Why didn't you tell us?
Because I hadn't decided
what to do about it yet.
Anyone wants to venture a guess
as to what Jack's gonna be showing us
out in the middle of nowhere?
I don't know. Stuff.
Probably secret stuff.
Why does everything
have to be such a secret?
How about some openness
for a change?
We kept the parachute lady secret.
Ah, that's different.
Different how?
Well, because we weren't out there
playing football with them.
What?
Nothing.
Wait.
You had one of your flashes
again, didn't you?
No, Charlie, I didn't.
We're here.
A couple of nights ago,
Juliet came to me,
and she told me everything...
That Ben had sent her here to find out
which of our women were pregnant.
So what, you guys
were doing tests on us?
No, but that's what he wanted me to do.
I've been leaving tapes
at the medical station.
You all heard what he said.
They're coming tomorrow.
Sun, I'm sorry that I lied to you.
While I appreciate your honesty, Jack,
it doesn't explain
why you brought us out here.
Show 'em.
When Juliet told me they where coming,
the first thing I thought was,
where the hell
are we gonna hide this time?
But hiding's pointless.
They're just gonna keep coming back.
So I went out, and I found some help.
And for the past few days,
she's been bringing dynamite
back from "the black rock."
For the very first time,
we know exactly what they want,
when they're coming to get it,
and they have no idea
that we're gonna be waiting for 'em.
So Juliet's gonna mark the tents
with the white rocks,
just like she was told to,
but there's not gonna be
any pregnant women inside.
There's gonna be plenty
of what we used on that tree.
So tomorrow night...
We stop hiding.
We stop running.
We stop living in fear of them,
because when they show up...
we're gonna blow 'em all to hell.
Subtitles: swsub.com
Bloody hell!
Why are we even doing this?
Chin up, mate.
- We're headlining.
- Headlining?
We're playing Clitheroe...
The arse end of nowhere.
A gig's a gig.
We're building our fan base.
Will our fan base pay
for a new sodding tire?
Only if we show up.
So let's just get on with it, shall we?
You know what, Liam?
You get on with it.
I quit.
- You're giving up?
- There's nothing to give up on!
We're broke! The album's not selling!
We're a bloody joke!
Hey, shut it!
Listen.
That's us.
We're on the radio!
That we are.
We're on the bloody radio!
I told you, baby brother!
We're gonna be bloody rock stars.
Can I ask you something?
Who are you people
about to go to war with?
Oh, that's a long story.
Want to ask me something else?
You having a laugh?
Of course not.
I'd never disrespect a fellow Mancunian.
- You're from Manchester, then?
- I am.
My band got its start at
the night and day bar on Oldham street.
- What band?
- We were called Drive Shaft.
Yeah. Yeah, I know you.
We had our moment in the sun.
No, not that... the crash.
You're the dead rock star.
They made a big deal out of you
when they found the plane.
Huge memorial service, new album.
There's a new album?
Yeah. God, it was everywhere...
A "greatest hits" thing.
Hey, look on the bright side.
You're not really dead, right?
Yeah, right.
We need more wire,
so we can trigger these
from a safe distance.
I can get people to start
stripping the plane wreckage.
Good. I should be able
to finish rigging these tents
in the next 24 hours.
We'll be ready by tomorrow night.
We need to talk about Naomi's phone.
- Not now.
- If you're angry I doubted you,
I'd be happy to make
a sincere apology later,
- but now we have a means...
- Look, I'm a little bit busy right now.
And I am trying to get us
off this island!
I can't transmit using this phone
because Danielle's distress signal
is overriding the frequency.
If you tell me where the radio tower is,
I can go there, switch off
your message and call for help.
My signal has been playing
for the last 16 years,
and nobody has heard it.
Why do you think
you'll have better luck?
Naomi's boat is only 80 miles offshore.
I know if we eliminate
Danielle's signal, they'll hear us.
No, they won't.
And why is that?
We're jamming it.
What?
Ben is using one of the Dharma stations
to block all of the signals off
of the island except for ours.
What station?
They call it the "Looking Glass."
- The looking glass?
- Yes.
But it's underwater.
I have no idea where it is.
I believe I do.
Look, I know...
I know Jack thinks it's best,
but, you know, what if
they're coming for him again?
Claire, listen to me.
I'm gonna protect you.
I'm gonna protect Aaron.
I promise.
Look, everything is gonna be fine.
Sorry.
Can you give me a hand with something?
Of course.
So you ready to tell me
what you saw this morning?
Aye.
Right. So how does it happen this time?
Come on, Des!
You can tell me. I can take it.
What I saw, Charlie, was...
Claire and her baby
getting into a helicopter...
A helicopter that...
That lifts off, leaves this island.
You sure?
Aye.
Rescue helicopter...
On this beach?
This island? That's what you saw?
We're getting bloody rescued!
I thought you were gonna tell me
I was gonna die again.
You are, Charlie.
Wait. What?
If you don't...
none of it will happen.
There won't be any rescue.
I'm sorry, brother...
but this time...
This time you have to die.
Come on!
Come on, Charlie. Jump in!
I'm gonna catch you, boy.
No. You're just going to back away.
Don't be daft. Jump in!
I promise, Charlie. I'm gonna catch you.
No, he won't!
Zip it, you.
Look, don't listen to your brother.
Just jump on in.
There's nothing to be afraid of,
Charlie.
I'll catch you. I promise.
I did it!
You got it!
- I did it.
- You're swimming, Charlie.
What you writing?
Nothing.
All right, tell me.
Are you sure you want to know?
I mean, it might be easier
if you just...
I want to know.
You're inside a hatch.
It's...
a room full of equipment.
There's a blinking yellow light
above a switch.
You flip the switch.
Light goes off.
And then you drown.
When?
I don't know.
You're sure you saw Claire and Aaron
get on that helicopter?
Aye.
So...
before I... drown...
I just have to flip a switch?
That's right.
Where is it, then?
Now this is the Looking Glass.
It's an underwater Dharma station.
Please, can you tell me anything
you might know about this place?
I've never been down there.
I don't know anyone who has.
Why not?
There was some accident.
Ben told us that the station
was completely flooded.
Well, if it's flooded,
then how does it still work?
How it still works is irrelevant.
The question is, how do
we get it to stop working,
so we could use the satellite phone?
The diagram shows
that the looking glass
is connected to the island by a cable.
I feel sure that this is
the very same cable
down the beach
which runs into the ocean.
So if we follow the cable,
it should lead us to the station.
So how are we gonna get in?
We swim in.
There's a moon pool...
A room with an open floor
at the base of the station...
Big enough
for a submarine to dock.
Even if the station's flooded,
I think I'll be able to find
the relay switch and disable it.
What about swimming back out?
No. I'm not letting you
go on some suicide mission
just to flip the switch.
Someone has to do it,
or we'll never leave this island.
I'll do it.
I can swim down, turn off that
bloody switch, swim back up.
Piece of cake.
Charlie, you don't even know
what we're talking about.
I was junior swim champion
in northern England.
I can hold my breath for 4 minutes.
I know exactly what
you're talking about.
No, and there's no reason
to do this now.
We're gonna focus on the others,
and then we'll deal with this.
Wait a minute.
We have a chance to signal for a rescue.
Look, for 90 days, I've been asked
to make decisions for this entire camp.
There you go.
I just made one.
Rose, that's a sailor's hitch.
It's not gonna hold.
You wanna do a sheet bend like mine.
Oh, so now you're a knot expert.
Well, trust me, it's...
How did you do that?
Watch and learn, dear.
Look there!
Look!
Get off him, damn it!
It's okay.
- What? He's one of them!
- I know! It's okay.
He was in the cage next to me.
I know this guy.
What the hell are you doing here, Karl?
They're... coming...
My people.
Sorry you came all this way for nothing,
but we already know.
Then why are you still here?
'cause when they'll show up tomorrow
night, we're gonna be ready for 'em.
Tomorrow? No, no,
they're coming tonight.
They're coming right now!
SIX HOURS AGO (del vo)
When did you get back?
Just now.
Where's Locke?
Here's your gun back.
Ben, what's going on?
Where's Ryan?
He's in his tent. Are you...
It's time to get them.
But you said tomorrow.
Jacob wants it to happen now.
Look, what happened out there?
- Did john see...
- John had an accident.
Ryan?
Yes, sir?
If you leave right now,
how long will it take you
to reach their camp?
Well, if I take my ten best,
we could set up to hit 'em by nightfall.
- Then you better get going.
- No, Ben, wait.
Moving up the schedule...
Juliet may not be ready.
What if she hasn't had time...
Then we'll take all their women...
And we'll sort out
the ones we need later.
And the men?
If any of 'em are stupid enough
to get in your way,
kill 'em.
All right.
Karl!
It's me!
I thought you were bringing rabbit.
You have to go... now.
What? Did he find out I was out here?
No, but he's sending Pryce
to their beach camp right now,
and you have to warn them.
- Warn them?
- You have to go now!
I thought they were just gonna
take the pregnant women.
If you take the outrigger,
you'll get there
a few hours before them.
- Wait, Alex...
- He's gonna kill them Karl!
Austen and Ford saved your life.
You owe them.
You better take this.
If I get caught, your father's
gonna kill me this time.
Is he my father?
Now go.
Is that everything?
Can we trust him?
You don't trust me?
What about her?
She's a spy.
She's supposed to mark the tents
of the pregnant women with white rocks
- so they can take them.
- They know, Karl, but thanks.
- So what are we gonna do?
- We have to leave now... Hide.
Where? It's their island.
f they wanna kill us, they'll find us.
The sun's gonna go down in a few hours.
- Do we have enough wire yet?
- Not even close.
We have to find out another way
to set the dynamite off.
- We can shoot.
- We don't have enough guns.
Ten of them are coming, armed.
Not the others... the tents.
We can camouflage the dynamite
next to the tents,
target it from our positions
at the tree line.
Juliet marked three tents.
That means we need three guns.
Here. You can have mine, too.
I'll be your third.
I'll take your gun,
but you're not staying here.
You're gonna lead everyone
to the radio tower... Everyone.
The radio tower?
If this doesn't work,
we can't risk losing the chance
of getting in contact with Naomi's boat,
so everything has to happen
at the same time.
You still up for a swim?
Yeah, I believe I am.
I'll go with him.
Okay, better get to it.
It's here, baby brother.
Christmas is here.
Are these the birds from row two?
Well done, mate.
Well, as you have spent another year
as the only drug-free
rock star in the world,
I'm gonna share
a little-known fact with you.
Father christmas lives
just down the street from here.
Father christmas lives in Helsinki?
Indeed he does,
and in case you haven't noticed,
baby brother,
Finland is the bloody north pole.
Therefore, I have a very special
gift for you this year.
Liam, no. Mum gave you that.
You're the firstborn.
It was her father's
and his father before that.
And it's a family heirloom,
and at's why we named the band
after Dexter bloody Stratton.
I know.
But, Charlie, let's be honest.
We both know I'm a sodding mess.
But you... You're different.
You're gonna get married,
have a family...
A baby.
I'll be lucky if I hit 30.
Don't say that, Lee.
The ring has to stay
in the family, Charlie.
So, please...
Take it.
Mum would have wanted it this way.
Pass it on to your little one someday.
I need to know it's safe.
I'll hold on to it...
but I won't take it.
Hey, it fits. Look at that.
Happy christmas, baby brother.
You need some help?
Why didn't you tell me
you were gonna do this?
I didn't want you to worry.
Well, it's dangerous, isn't it,
swimming into some underwater station?
It's what needs to be done
to get us all rescued.
I'll be fine, Claire.
But you gotta promise me something.
While I'm gone...
Don't worry about me.
I'll take him.
Thanks.
Alright, turnip head.
Now you take care of your mum
while I'm away, okay?
I love you.
See you soon.
Be careful, Charlie.
Okay?
Sorry, guys.
Thanks, man.
Help! Help me!
Please!
You, stop!
Get the hell away from her!
What are you doing?
Leave her alone!
You okay, miss?
Yes. I think so, yes.
Here you go.
Pardon me while I have a heart attack.
The last time I was in a fight,
I was 8 years old.
And I lost.
Well, that makes you even more
of a hero, doesn't it?
I just did what anyone would do.
Three people walked by the alley.
- What?
- They saw me,
but they just kept on going.
You are a hero, sir...
And don't let anyone ever
tell you differently.
- What's that?
- It's a weight belt.
It should bring you down
quicker than swimming.
Well, every second counts.
So I just take it off when I hit bottom,
swim up through the moon pool,
into the station,
swim into whichever room
has the yellow blinking switch,
flip it.
Nothing to it.
So how long
can you really hold your breath for?
Does it matter?
- Do you want me to hit another one?
- No, you've made your point.
Bernard, this is not pheasant hunting
in Montgomery county.
- I know what I'm doing.
- No.
- Pheasants don't shoot back.
- Nothing's gonna happen to me, Rose.
I just have to shoot a tent,
and I'll be right behind you.
Then I'm staying, too.
No, you're not, Rose.
Everyone's gathering down
at the south end of the beach.
No one's staying behind
but the shooters.
Says who? You wanna give me your word
that nothing's gonna happen
to my husband, then I'll go.
I'll give you my word
that if we don't kill everyone
who shows up here in about an hour,
it's not gonna matter where Bernard is.
I like you better
since you got back, Jack.
You're almost an optimist.
Come on.
If you're gonna be hiding in the bushes,
let's get you into somethin' dark.
You better get going.
Rousseau says it's about
a day's walk up to the radio tower.
I'm not taking them to the tower.
You are.
- Excuse me?
- You're not staying behind.
This was my idea.
And I'm perfectly capable
of executing it.
- I owe them!
- What are you more concerned with,
killing the others
or getting our people off this island?
This afternoon,
you said you were our leader.
It's time for you to act like one.
Lead them to the radio tower, Jack...
and then take us all home.
Dudes, wait!
I heard what you're doing.
I wanna come with.
Everyone...
They're all going to the radio tower,
and I'm sick of trekking and,
you know, explosions.
I think I can help you guys out.
I'm a really good paddler.
You can't go, Hurley.
Why not?
Because...
you're too big.
You won't fit in the boat.
That's uncool, man.
Wait.
Dude, it's fine. I don't even
wanna go on your stupid boat.
I'll catch up with you later.
Just remember I love you, man.
Yeah, whatever. I love you, too.
You got water in there? Good, good.
How about you? Bottled water?
Good.
So here we go again, huh?
Here we go again.
The tents are all marked. We're set.
Sayid find the third shooter?
Ready, Claire?
Need a hand with the little guy?
No, thanks. I'm okay.
How's my little sweetheart?
We're just gonna go for a little walk,
so hold onto mum, okay?
This is it!
Ready?
Do you want a blanket?
Oh, thanks. I've got one.
Well, you're warming for two.
Take mine.
Thank you.
So... first plane crash?
What gave it away?
Ah, you can always spot the newbies.
We're gonna be okay, you know.
Are we?
We're alive.
We're on a beautiful island.
We'll sleep under the stars,
and before you know it, the helicopters
will come and take us all home.
You really think they'll find us?
Well, yeah. Why wouldn't they?
Thanks.
I'm Charlie.
I'm Claire.
Nice to meet you, Charlie.
It's nice to meet you.
We're here.
I want you to give this
to Claire for me.
What is it?
It's the five best moments of my...
sorry excuse for a life.
My greatest hits.
You know...
memories...
are all I've got.
You don't have to do this.
What?
I'll go.
No, your... Your flashes...
Maybe...
I keep seeing you die because...
I'm supposed to take your place.
What about your girl...
Penny?
What about your girl?
Besides...
I might be luckier than you.
Keep your memories to yourself.
I'll take it from here.
I don't know what to say.
Well, you can tell me where the,
the weight belt is.
Right there behind you.
You and I both know...
You aren't supposed
to take my place, brother.
I'm alive.