Previously on
Lost...
Each one of us
was brought here for a reason.
And who brought us here, John?
The island.
It's destiny.
You and your partner will observe
a psychological experiment,
in progress.
Your duty is to observe team members
in another station on the island.
These team members are not aware
that they are under surveillance
or that they are the subjects
of an experiment.
Every single second
of my pathetic little life
is as useless as that button!
As long as you push it,
we'll never be free.
If you're so sure it's not real,
then just stop pushing the button.
Well, I have, except, unfortunately,
someone else decided to start.
Tomorrow we're gonna find out
what happens
if that button doesn't get pushed.
Who is he, Box Man...
the man out there pounding on the door?
His name is Mr. Eko.
Why does Mr. Eko carry around
a stick covered in scripture?
Because he's a priest.
- We need to push the button.
- No, we don't!
It's all bloody real!
Now push the damn button!
- You've killed us all.
- No, I just saved us all.
System failure.
I was wrong.
When John get back?
What's he doing?
Well, where's he been?
Where's everyone else?
Don't you think you should go find out?
So you're gone for a whole day
after a massive hatch detonation.
You don't call,
you don't write.
Sorry. Am I interrupting something?
What, you...
you can't speak, John?
You're mute?
I am sorry about that.
So where are Eko and Desmond?
Are they off being mute
and building structures as well?
I know. You can't speak.
You need to speak.
To me? What do you want to...
The sand. You need to speak to the sand.
Trees. Yeah, I've heard
they're wonderful conversationalists.
I don't understand.
Who do you need to speak to?
The... church.
Sky.
Island.
You need to speak...
to the island.
Transcript : adeout@frm www.1000fr.com
Sync : www.sub-way.fr (V.0.90)
3x03 - Further Instructions
"I need your help."
Since when do you need my help?
"I need u 2 stand guard."
Oh, yeah, so you can talk to the island.
Yeah. Sounds dangerous.
Well, amusing
as the mute game invariably is...
You are aware, John,
that I detest you, aren't you?
You do remember
repeatedly punching me in the face
and accusing me of using heroin
when I was not?
What the sodding hell
is a "sweat lodge"?
Where you headed?
Eureka.
Well, I can get you
as far as Bridgeville.
Come on, hop in. Come on.
- My name's John.
- Eddie.
- Hi, Eddie.
- Hey.
- Nasty day to be hitching.
- That's for sure.
If you don't mind my asking,
what's in Eureka?
I heard there was some work there,
cutting timber.
Is that what you do?
That might be what I do. I don't know.
All I know is that I had to get out
of where I came from.
Mom's dead, dad's a drunk.
Hey, look at that. The rain is passing.
What, did you rob a bank?
'Fraid so.
Can I see your license
and registration, please?
Was I speeding, officer?
Tail light's out.
Could you both please
step out of the vehicle?
What do you got back here?
Guns and groceries.
Now the transaction logs
and the paperwork
for all of 'em's in the red notebook
right there in that duffel.
So are we free to go?
I could still take you in
for picking up a hitchhiker.
Oh, that's my uncle.
I called him, and he picked me up.
Get outta here.
So what is with all the guns...
uncle?
I like the indoor fireplace.
It's very snazzy.
What's that?
You're not...
taking drugs, are you, John?
I only ask because of the strict
zero-tolerance policy you've enacted.
I wouldn't want you to have
to start punching yourself in the face.
Yeah, I know. I get it. You're gonna go
in your little magic hut,
and I'm gonna stand out here
in case you devolve into a monkey.
"Don't... come in."
Okay. I get it.
Hi, John.
It's good to see you again.
What's that, John?
You're sorry.
That's okay.
I was the sacrifice the island demanded.
Don't worry.
You'll speak
when you have something worth saying.
I'm here
to help you find your way again,
so you can bring
the family back together.
Come on.
I want to show you something.
You're gonna need that.
John, someone in this airport
is in serious danger.
You are the only one who can save them.
Not them. They'll be fine...
for a while.
I think Sayid's got it.
Next, please.
Not Hurley.
Forget it. He's helping himself.
There's nothing you can do for them,
not yet.
First,
you have to clean up your own mess.
Clean up your own mess...
first,
you have to clean up your own mess.
Come up here, John.
Clean it up, John.
They've got him.
You don't have much time.
What happened?
Are you all right?
What are you doing?
I'm going to save Mr. Eko's life.
Eko's cross.
He was dragged this way.
Dragged?
By what?
By the polar bear.
Sawyer killed the polar bear.
He killed a polar bear.
What's that, John, blood?
I'm gonna go on alone, Charlie.
You go back to Claire.
Well, I'll take my chances.
You don't want to go with me, Charlie.
Bad things happen to people
who hang around with me.
Hey, Bobby.
What's that?
That, Eddie, is our sweat lodge.
A what?
Anybody who wants
can go in there and light a fire
and get it nice and hot and meditate.
Then what?
And then you're supposed
to find what to do with your life,
you know, what-- what direction to take.
Go on in there and figure out
if you're a farmer or a hunter.
So which are you, John?
Hey, John.
Hey, Mike. Jan, this is Eddie.
He's looking for some logging work,
but I convinced him to come home
and have supper with us first.
- Nice to meet you, Eddie.
- Nice to meet you.
Any friend of John's
is a friend of ours.
Right. John's a very special guy.
Grab a spot.
So you like Geronimo Jackson, huh?
Yeah, yeah. They're all right.
It's one of my dad's old shirts.
Your dad has excellent taste.
Listen up, people.
John brought a guest to supper.
So, everyone, this is Eddie.
- Hi, Eddie.
- Eddie, this is everyone.
Nice to meet you.
John, you want to say some grace?
Yeah.
Thank you, Lord.
Thank you for the food and the friends,
and thanks for the rain today,
so that Adam will stop
grumbling about the drought.
And for me, thank you
for helping me stop being so angry,
And... and for...
helping me find a real family.
Because they're a hell of a lot better
than the one I used to have,
so let's eat. Amen.
Let's dig in.
Potatoes?
Thank you. Thank you.
Is that the hatch?
What's left of it.
What happened?
Looks like it...
imploded.
What is that?
It's an active kill.
Meaning that whatever
was eating this is coming back for more.
If you want to say polar bear,
you can just say it.
All right. Polar bear.
Run!
Dude.
They kept Jack, Kate and Sawyer,
And they sent me back
to tell everyone else
that we can't ever go over there.
Oh, and that dude
we had in the hatch--
Henry?
He was there. He's, like, their leader.
So... what do we do?
Do what they told you.
Go back to the camp and tell the others.
You're not gonna do anything?
I am doing something.
Go back to the beach, Hugo.
Wait. Where are you guys going?
The island told Locke
he has to save Eko.
Save him from what?
Well, apparently a bear's got him.
It's just made an active kill.
You may want to hustle.
Bear?
What bear?
What's that, more fur?
This way.
When I used to get high,
I'd watch nature programs on the "beeb."
Polar bears
are meant to be quite clever.
Very clever.
They're like the Einsteins
of the bear community.
She likes you, man.
Oh, yeah, she does.
- She does not.
- Yeah, she does.
She's like half my age, man.
You'd be better off with her.
No. Lizzie's too granola for me.
What she really wants is a daddy.
Like everyone else here.
You should take advantage of that.
That's not real funny, Eddie.
It was a joke.
It was a joke! I'm sorry.
How come you never talk
about your dad, John?
Nothing worth talking about.
What's going on
in that greenhouse over there?
Maybe they need a hand
with that fertilizer.
No, no, they're okay. They're okay.
Come on. We got orchard duty.
What's the big secret, John?
Sorry?
The greenhouse. What do you guys
got in there? What are you hiding?
'Cause every time I go near it,
you and everyone else acts all weird.
Look, you're a guest here.
These things take time.
I've been here for six weeks.
- Eddie, nothing's--
- I'm not blind, man.
Did you forget that you had
a duffel bag full of guns
- When you brought me here?
- Mike and Jan
welcomed you here with open arms.
They feed you.
- They give you a place to stay...
- And Mike and Jan
fold their hands every night before chow
and talk about how we're family,
but your family's got too many secrets.
Now I see the fertilizer
going into that greenhouse.
I know what's going on...
and I want in.
In on what?
Whatever you guys are trying to blow up.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
I'll talk to Mike and Jan.
You really think Eko's in there?
Let's hurry up and do this.
Maybe the bear's out
finishing his lunch.
- You're not going in there, Charlie.
- What?
I'm gonna do this alone.
You don't tell me
what I can't do.
If I want to,
I'll go in there.
- Why?
- What?
Why do you want to go in there?
I don't need a reason.
- Then go back.
- Go back?
You don't have a good reason
to go in there, either.
I'm going in there because
I'm supposed to go in there.
If it all goes to plan,
we probably won't even see
the bear, will we?
Hopefully he won't smell us.
Hair spray? Now I hate to be the one
- to point this out to you--
- It's not for me.
Bear?
Is that you?
Who's there?
Are you alone, brother?
Yeah.
Dude. I'm not alone.
The beach camp's right over there.
Can you get me some clothes?
What happened to yours?
I woke up in the jungle like this.
So...
like, the hatch...
blew off your underwear?
Fine. You wanna discuss this
in great detail right now, let's do it.
No, no, that's okay.
I got something in here.
How do you feel about tie-dye?
Hey, Kim.
Hey, Mike and Jan in?
Yeah. They were looking for you.
Good, good. Good timing, then, huh?
Go on in.
- You got all the cash?
- In the bag.
- Which bag?
- The one with the money in it!
- What about the bank records?
- Leave 'em.
Shouldn't we sort out
what they can trace?
There is no time, Mike.
What's going on?
What does it look like?
I don't...
you screwed up, John.
You blew it big time.
What are you--
what...
What are you doing?
Are you leaving?
- Why?
- That is why, you idiot!
John, your friend's a cop.
You know how much jail time
we'd get for this much weed?
Nice picture, huh?
Got him fresh out of the academy.
No, he was--
He was hitchhiking.
He told me he was going to Eureka.
He was waiting for you, John.
He has been here
for six weeks gathering evidence
because you brought him here.
- No, Mike, that's impossible.
- He played you for a sucker.
Now it's over.
No. Wait.
Wait. No, wait, wait. Stop!
We don't know what he's told 'em.
He hasn't even been in here yet.
If he's still gathering evidence
and trying to make a case,
- then it's not too late.
- Not too late for what?
To protect us. To protect all of us.
It's not too late to fix this.
I can fix this.
How are you gonna do that, John?
Is he okay?
He alive?
- Is he all right?
- He's alive.
Turn him over, turn him over.
Charlie, we gotta get outta here.
Okay. Let's get him up.
So, when you say "turned a key,"
you mean, like, a key key?
It was a failsafe key.
That seems kinda convenient.
I'm sorry?
I'm just saying, if you had
this magic key the whole time,
why didn't you, like, use it?
I didn't know what would happen.
So what did happen?
Well, the failsafe key
must have detonated
the electromagnetic anomaly,
made the hatch implode.
But you didn't implode.
You're not gonna, like,
turn into the Hulk or something?
So is that what made the blender noise
and the sky turn purple?
Afraid I missed that, brother.
Right. You were failsafing.
Well, F.Y.I.,
the whole island vibrated,
and Kate and Jack
and Sawyer saw it, too,
right before they had bags
pulled over their heads--
Don't worry.
Locke's gonna go after them.
- He said so in his speech.
- What?
What speech?
All he said was
he was gonna save Eko and kill bears.
Right.
Right, of course.
I'm sorry. I...
I'm just, uh, a bit shook up.
I burned that bear pretty good.
I don't think
he's gonna be coming after us.
Now that we've survived
this suicide mission,
do you wanna tell me what you saw?
What I saw?
In your spirit tent.
I saw Boone.
Boone?
What did he have to say for himself?
He told me I had
to clean up my own mess.
Well, dead as he may be,
I agree with Boone.
After all, if you kept pressing
that button like Eko told you to--
We wouldn't have had
to save him in the first place,
yeah, charlie, that's what cleaning up
your own mess means.
Spoken like someone who's had
a few too many messes to clean.
No deer, huh?
You talk to Mike and Jan yet?
Yeah, sure did.
Yeah? What'd they say?
They said that I should bring you
by the greenhouse
tonight after supper
and that they would explain everything.
Cool.
That's great.
What, did you see something?
What are you doing?
Did you know it would be me?
- What?
- In the truck.
Did you know it would be me driving?
Did they choose me?
They? John, I have no idea
what you're talking about--
I didn't load that one.
So how about you just
answer the question, Eddie?
Yeah.
They chose you, John.
Why?
Because you hadn't been here long,
didn't have a criminal record,
and the psych profile said
you would be amenable for coercion.
Amenable for coercion--
Lower the gun, John.
Okay? This isn't personal.
It's not personal?!
Stop, stop.
I'm sorry, John,
but you're not gonna shoot me.
You're not a murderer.
You're a good man.
You're a farmer.
I'm not a farmer.
I was a hunter.
I'm a hunter.
I'm gonna walk away now, John.
Hey, John. You hear something?
- It sounds like a stream.
- Yeah.
Let's put him down.
Maybe if we get some water in him.
I'll go. You stay here.
I'm sorry.
Sorry I ever doubted you.
Sorry I gave up
on my faith in the island.
I messed up.
Now our people are captured and...
if I'd just listened to you,
if I'd just let you...
keep pushing the button...
I could've gone with them,
protected them.
I could've saved 'em.
You can still protect them...
you can still save them.
I don't even know where they are.
You will find them.
After all...
you are a hunter, John.
- You say something?
- He's awake.
Maybe we should just...
get him back.
- You all right?
- Yeah. Just keep walking.
What happened?
We got him.
- Is he alive?
- We need Jack.
- Take him in.
- Jack's not coming back.
- They've got him.
- What?
What are you talking about?
- Jack's gone?
- I don't understand.
Okay, when were you planning
on telling us, Hurley?
What do you mean, "they"? Who's "they"?
"They"
are the others,
and yes, they've taken Jack...
and Kate and Sawyer.
How? What happened?
What about Sun and Jin and Sayid?
- Are they okay?
- I don't know.
I'm gonna find our friends.
I don't know how yet, but I will.
We're gonna find them--
all of them.
And then we're gonna bring them home.
But first things first.
We've gotta look after Mr. Eko,
so, Paulo, Nikki,
bring towels and water.
Claire, we gotta clean him up,
so bring all the first aid supplies you.
Not a bad speech.
"Whoa," what?
Just got hit with, you know...
déjà vu.
Well, when that wears off,
can you get, bandadges,
from the kitchen?