Previously on Lost...
Two days after I found out
I had a fatal tumor on my spine,
a spinal surgeon fell out of the sky.
We had such a wonderful plan
to break you, Jack.
My wonderful plan got shot to sunshine
when you saw my damned x-rays
and figured out I was dying.
You want me to save your life?
I want you to want to save my life.
All I can ask
is that you think about it.
Police. Open the door.
Everything's all right in here.
Ma'am, we have reason to believe
someone extremely dangerous
is in the motel.
We're conducting a room-to-room search.
I'm alone, officer.
This person could be holding you
at gunpoint,
forcing you to say that.
Please open the door.
I don't think I should.
Ma'am, you have three seconds
before I break this door down.
One...
two...
Hey.
Wanna get it on?
Hell, yeah.
Warning.
Hey.
Hey yourself.
Whatcha doing?
Throwing rocks.
- I thought you had to pull the lever.
- I know how to get a damn fish biscuit.
Then get me one.
What, you trying
to keep me feeling productive?
You took these blood tests,
made all the notations?
How old are the x-rays?
A week.
The tumor on your spine
is borderline inoperable,
and at the rate it's growing,
that borderline goes away in about...
one week.
The O. R.
We were in-- is that fully equipped?
Yes.
Anesthesia? Sterile?
You need to be in surgery yesterday.
All right, then.
Whatever you need,
it's yours. I'm ready.
No, I think you misunderstood me.
I didn't say I was gonna do it.
I just wanted you
to understand how you're gonna die.
You think I believe you people?
You think I trust you,
that I'm gonna just do the surgery
and hope that you let me go?
Don't!
Well, Jack,
I'm very disappointed in your decision.
Well, Ben,
at least you won't have
to be disappointed for very long.
Transcript : www.sadgeezer.com
Subtitles : www.sub-way.fr (V.0.90)
3x06 - I Do
You shouldn't have come here.
Yeah, you're right.
I've made a huge mistake.
I am just full of regret right now.
Seriously.
it's bad luck to see the bride
before the wedding.
It's bad luck to see the bride
in her dress before the wedding.
You, my friend, are naked.
Have you tried it on?
I have to hold my breath
to get the claspy things to clasp,
so I'm waiting
till the absolute last minute.
It's in about 12 hours.
You might wanna get clasping.
I know it's...
It's been fast,
but... this is right.
I know it's real...
and I love you, Monica.
I love you too, Kevin.
Come on. Time for work.
- What about him?
- He's got the day off.
Well, if he's not working, neither am I.
- Oh, you're not?
- Just go, Freckles.
Man wants to give me a day off,
let him give me a day off.
No, Sawyer. We're a team.
You break the rocks, I haul 'em.
All right.
Fine.
Lord knows I wouldn't want
to break up the team.
What happened to him?
Must have been an animal,
maybe one of the bears.
Are we gonna carry him back?
We're gonna bury him here.
Are we?
The people back at camp...
there's just been
a few too many funerals lately.
Nobody needs to see him like this.
I'll slip back to the beach
and get a couple shovels.
I'll come with you.
- No, I'll be back in an hour...
- it's not safe to go alone, John.
I appreciate your concern.
So what killed Eko?
Folks back at the beach
call it the "monster."
I don't really have a name for it.
You don't believe in monsters.
I believe in what I can see.
But obviously, you have.
So why don't you tell me
what you think it is?
It might be what brought us here.
So you believe that this monster
decided that Eko was meant to die?
I believe Eko died for a reason.
I just don't know what it is yet.
Is that why you lied?
We're not headed back towards the camp,
are we, John?
Sure, we are.
Just need to take a little detour first.
Compound breach.
Where is she?
Someone's on the grid.
I want him on the ground, her too.
If he moves, you shoot him.
- Yeah, they're here.
- Okay.
Did the doctor get out again?
You sure?
Well, does he know?
How the hell did she get over here?!
Get up! Come on! Get up! Go!
Alex!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
What, you gonna shoot me?
You know you're not supposed to be here,
so let's just calm...
what did you do to him, Danny?!
Where is he?
I want to talk to Ben.
Sure.
That sounds like a great idea.
So why don't we just
lower our little sling--
where is he? Tell me!
Don't-- no! Get off of me!
- Get her out of here.
- What do I do with her?
- Get her outta here!
- Put me down!
Listen, whatever they say,
don't believe them.
They're gonna kill your boyfriend
just like they killed mine.
I don't understand.
- It's supposed to be two weeks.
- Our schedule's been moved up.
- Is that an order?
- It's coming from him.
- That's stupid.
- It's not my call.
That's the way it is, Danny.
All right.
I would like for you to put this on
and come with me, please.
You think I'm gonna put a hood
over my head 'cause you said "please"?
No, I think you're going
to put a hood over your head
because the man standing behind me,
the one
who's burning a hole in my back--
that man is going to kill Sawyer.
But if you put this on
and you come with me,
there's something you can do for us
that will save his life.
Come in.
Oh, sweetheart.
You're beautiful.
Absolutely beautiful.
How is it out there?
There are a lot of excited policemen.
Don't worry. I have asked them
not to shoot their guns in the air
when you say "I do."
You know, mothers-in-law
aren't supposed to be so nice.
Monica...
I have something for you.
Suzanne, you shouldn't have.
My mother gave that to me
on my wedding day.
She told me someday
I'd give it to my daughter,
but since I had four boys...
here.
It's perfect.
You know,
Kevin's been coming to the church here
since he was about yea high.
When I first met you, Monica,
I was struck by your honesty
and devotion to Kevin.
And when I asked him
what he loved most about you,
he said,
"because what you see is what you get."
That being said,
we've got the rings,
you've vowed your vows,
and I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Watch the Step.
I'll give you two some privacy.
You okay?
Yeah. You?
Yeah, I'm...
I'm great.
Where are they keeping you?
Outside, in a cage.
Sawyer?
He's in a cage, too.
They're making us work.
Work? On what?
I don't know what it is,
but it's big.
We're hauling rocks and--
Did they hurt you?
Hey, it's gonna...
it's gonna be all right.
It's gonna--
Jack, you have to do it.
- What?
- This thing that they told you to do...
this operation.
She said that if you do it,
- then that they would...
- What did they do to you?
- Nothing.
How did they get you to ask me?
What did they offer you?
- Nothing.
- Then what are you doing here?
They're gonna kill Sawyer!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry,
but she said that if you do it,
and if you do it soon,
they'll let us go.
And you believe them?
I have to.
Please.
We're done here.
We're done in here!
Jack, I'm sorry.
You have to do this.
They said that they couldn't--
Get her out of there.
Jack, please!
Hey, you.
Hey, what's for dinner, gorgeous?
It's taco night.
You're making tacos?
Yes, and you better like 'em.
Or what?
Or no dessert.
I'm leaving now. I'll be home soon.
- Love you.
- I love you, too.
Agent Mars.
It's me.
Well, I'm glad.
I realized this morning
that it was the feast of
the ascension,
and I was feeling bad.
A lot of holy days
have come and gone
since you last called.
I thought you and I were friends.
I don't want to run anymore.
What's his name?
Does he know who you are?
Edward, please.
I know you don't want to spend
the rest of your life chasing me.
Please, I love this guy.
Just let me go.
I'll tell you what.
If you can really stay put,
you really settle down,
then I'll stop chasing you.
But you and I both know
that's not gonna happen.
Sawyer...
You really care about him, huh?
Where is he?
I'm sorry
you weren't able to help us, Kate.
Move it, Ford.
Danny.
Son of a bitch!
Right. Sorry, Jules.
You got anything
you wanna say to your girl,
you'd best say it tonight.
And how was your day, honey?
When the hatch exploded,
your prayer stick fell out of a tree
right on top of me.
So Sayid and I went out to get it,
because it didn't feel right
to bury you without it.
I'd like to think you died for a reason,
Mr. Eko.
Just hope it's not too long
before we find out
what the heck it might be.
Rest in peace, Mr. Eko.
Thank you for helping me find my...
I saw Jack.
They brought me in to see him.
They want him to do surgery on Ben.
Who the hell's Ben?
Henry, the guy who brought us in.
He's sick.
And they say that if he does it,
they're gonna let us all go.
And you and me are what,
- bait?
- Somethin' like that.
At least
the doc ain't dumb enough to do it.
I told him he had to.
Why the hell
would you do something so stupid?
To save your life.
My life don't need saving.
You wanna die?!
'Cause that's what's gonna happen.
Pickett is just waiting for his chance.
I've seen him look at you.
Damn it, Freckles, stay put.
And you know what he's gonna do.
So don't pretend
like you don't care.
Get down, Freckles!
We already been through this.
Shut up, James.
You don't want Jack to save your life?
Then you're gonna save your own.
We're getting outta here now.
Stop it! Damn it, Kate.
Go. Get outta here. Run!
You're out of your cage.
Why don't you run, Kate?
'Cause me...
I ain't running...
'cause there ain't no place to go.
What are you talking about?
We ain't on our island.
We're on another island, like Alcatraz,
couple miles offshore.
So unless you're a mermaid,
or you got a boat,
there ain't no point.
When were you planning
on telling me this?
- Never.
- Why not?!
Why wouldn't you?!
'cause I wanted you to believe
that we had a damn chance.
What was that for?
I don't know.
Very nice.
Okay, now it's your turn.
Look under your place mat.
- What did you do?
- Just look.
What is it?
You know that honeymoon
I've been promising you for six months?
You are holding in your hand
two tickets to Costa Rica.
So get your passport ready, baby.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just love you so much.
Come here.
Let me ask you something.
The day blockhead was beating on me,
and you said...
"I love you."
That was just...
to get him to stop, right?
I love you, too.
Who is this?
Hello?
Try it... the door.
If it helps, I was surprised, too.
If I were a betting man,
I would have picked
- her and you.
- Shut up!
Well,
I suppose this would be
the proverbial nail in my coffin,
wouldn't it?
Tomorrow.
Sorry?
Tomorrow morning, first thing.
Get everything I mentioned before,
the instruments,
the anesthesia, and someone
who can hold a damn clamp.
- Of course.
- I'll get it out...
your tumor,
and I'll keep you alive.
But I need your word.
I need what you promised me before.
I need to get the hell off this island.
Done.
What you working on?
Just finishing some I.R.S
on that fugitive recovery out of Tampa.
That's what being a cop is...
just endless paperwork.
Thank you, sweetie.
What if I told you I was a fugitive?
What if I told you I was on the run
for blowing up my father,
and it was only a matter of time
before you found out?
- This isn't funny.
- It's not a joke.
I almost had a baby, Kev.
Me. A baby.
I can't do this.
Taco night?
I don't do taco night!
Calm down, Monica.
My name's not Monica!
I love you...
but I can't stay.
Wait. Hang on.
- Kev...
- Something's wrong with me.
I drugged you.
- You what?
- I had to.
Otherwise, they would think you knew.
People are gonna be asking
a lot of questions,
and I didn't want you
to lose your job. Kev!
This is gonna be
a very tricky procedure.
If I tell you to do something,
I need you to do it then and there,
no questions asked.
Is that understood?
You may find this hard to believe,
but I've always been very good
at just following orders.
Is that a yes?
Yes.
Good.
Let's go.
Do you get nervous...
before you do surgery?
I used to,
but not anymore, no.
Whatever happens,
everything will be very different,
won't it?
No doubt about it.
Juliet...
did Alex ask about me?
We took her home last night.
I don't know where she is now.
Well, see you on the other side.
I'm ready.
I need you to count down from 20.
20...
19...
eight...
Scalpel.
Let's go.
Ben's just gone into surgery.
Ben just put his life
in the hands of one of them.
Shephard wasn't even on Jacob's list.
Well, well, well,
look who got out of her cage.
You two should've run
when you had the chance.
- Let's go, James.
- Don't. Please.
You don't have to do this.
He's coming with me,
and you can do anything about it!
Step away.
Give me another hemostat.
Swab again.
Clamp.
What happened? Is he okay?
His blood pressure's dropping.
- Should he be bleeding like that?
- No. No, he shouldn't.
Back away from the table.
Back away from the table now!
Can you hear me in there?
Good.
I just made a small incision
in Ben's kidney sack.
Now if I don't stitch
that back up in the next hour,
he's dead.
Now get in here
and bring that walkie-talkie!
Step away!
You let go, or I do her, too.
Let go!
Don't you let go!
Don't even think about it, Sawyer.
You fight!
Sawyer, please!
You get your hands off of him!
Down on your knees!
Please!
I'll do anything you want!
I want you to watch.
Close your eyes, Freckles.
Stand up.
Close your eyes!
Don't you give up!
This is for Colleen,
you son of a bitch!
Danny, are you there?
Pick it up. Pick it up, Danny.
Pick it up, damn it!
I'm here! What?!
You anywhere near the cages?
Yeah, you could say that.
Give your walkie to Kate.
Now why the hell would I do that?!
Because if you don't,
the doctor's gonna let Ben die.
What are you talking about?
What's that beeping?
Just hand her the damn walkie, Danny.
Do it! Just do it now!
Let go of her!
You have about an hour head start
before they come after you.
Jack, where are you?
You remember
what I told you on the beach?
The day of the crash?
Do you remember what story
I told you
when you were stitching me up?
- You remember it?
- Yes Jack, I remember.
When you get safe...
you radio me and you tell me that story.
Jack, please...
If don't get a call from you
in the next hour
I'm gonna know something went wrong,
and he dies!
I can't leave without you.
It's time, go.
- Jack, I can't...
- Go, now!
- I can't!
- Kate, damn-it, run!