Subtitles: swsub.com
You okay?
Yeah, I just...
got a rock in my shoe.
He didt mean it, you know.
What?
Sawyer.
When he said that he didn't want you
to go with him... he didn't mean it.
If he didn't mean it, why'd he say it?
He was trying to protect you.
That's why I asked you
not to come back for me.
Why are you sticking up for Sawyer?
He'd never do it for you.
Because I love you.
Can I help you?
Sorry. I...
Actually, I came...
Is the funeral over?
There was no funeral, sir.
Only a viewing.
Nobody showed up.
Nobody?
- You sure?
- Just you.
My deepest condolences.
Friend or family?
Neither.
Would you like me to open it up?
Take your time.
Damn it.
How much further?
About an hour.
The radio tower...
when was the last time you were there?
The day I recorded the message.
I'll take you to the tower,
but I'm not leaving the island.
What?
There's no place for me back there.
This is my home now.
We need to talk.
What did Ben say? Can we kill him?
Is it possible to turn
this equipment off?
What?
The equipment that's jamming
the island, can you turn it off?
Sure. Ben gave us the code.
You are the only ones who have it?
Yeah. Why?
What would happen
if the station were to be flooded?
Nothing. The casing for
the equipment is waterproof.
It'll keep going forever.
Then why do you need to be here?
Because Ben told us to.
We were following orders.
And you never asked why?
No, because I trust him,
and I trust Jacob,
and the minute I start
questioning orders, this whole thing...
everything that we're doing here...
falls apart.
She makes an excellent point.
Please...
I'm sorry, Bonnie.
I, too, am following orders.
We need her.
Hi. I'm Benjamin. I don't
believe we've had the pleasure...
Don't talk to him!
What do you want?
Just a moment of your time...
to talk, you and me, alone.
For what?
You've just killed seven of my people.
The least you can give me
is five minutes.
Is he alone?
There's only two sets
of tracks... his and hers.
Five minutes.
I'm sorry, sir there are no more
refills left on this prescription.
Well, that... That's a mistake.
I...
I only refilled it twice.
Could you check again?
I did check it again, Dr. Shephard,
and that was the third refill,
so there's nothing I can do.
Fine. I've got another prescription
right here.
Hey, I know you.
You're the hero.
I'm not a hero.
We saw it on tv.
Hey, lady, what's wrong with you?
Give this guy whatever he needs.
You know what he did?
Here, just... Here...
Oxycodone.
Dr. Shephard, you can't write
a prescription for yourself.
That's not me.
That's Dr. Christian Shephard.
I'm Dr. Jack Shephard.
He's my father.
I'm gonna call his office to confirm...
- He's out of town right now.
- I'm sure somebody in the office...
Don't bother.
Have a seat.
Not so long ago, Jack,
I made a decision
that took the lives
of over 40 people in a single day.
I'm telling you this because...
history is about
to repeat itself right here,
right now.
Let me guess. You've...
You've got us surrounded,
and if I don't do what you say,
you're gonna...
You're gonna kill all my people.
No, Jack. You are.
And how am I gonna do that?
The woman you're traveling with...
the one who parachuted onto
the island from a helicopter...
she's not who she says she is.
- She's not, huh?
- No, she's not.
Then who is she?
She's a representative of some people
who have been trying
to find this island.
She's one of the bad guys.
I almost forgot. You're the...
You're the good guys.
Jack, listen to me.
If you phone her boat,
every single living person
on this island
will be killed.
So here's what has to happen.
Get that device...
the phone she carries with her...
and give it to me.
I will turn around.
We'll go back to my people.
You will turn around,
go back to your people.
I'm not going anywhere.
May I have my walkie back?
- What?
- There's something you need to hear.
Please?
Thank you.
Tom, are you there?
Yeah, I'm here.
Your plan killed seven of my people,
but the ones that you failed to kill
are now holding your friends
Jin, Sayid, Bernard... at gunpoint.
Jack, don't give him any...
- Leave him alone!
- I said shut up!
And what's to stop me
from snapping your neck...
Tom, unless you hear my voice
in one minute, shoot all three of them.
Bring me the phone.
40 seconds.
No.
I'm getting them all off the island.
- All of 'em!
- Let me ask you something.
Why do you want to leave the island?
What is it you so desperately
wanna get back to?
You have no one.
Your father's dead. Your wife left you,
moved on with another man.
Can you just not wait
to get back to the hospital,
get back to fixing things?
It's 20 seconds now.
Just get me the phone.
Ten seconds.
Bring me the phone.
- I'm not bluffing.
- I won't do it!
Four... three...
I'm so sorry, Jack.
Tom, are you there?
Yeah, Jack, I hear you.
I'm gonna lead my people
up to the radio tower,
and I'm gonna make a call,
and I'm gonna get 'em all rescued.
Every one of 'em.
And then I'm gonna come find you...
and I'm gonna kill you.
- What's the code?
- Go away.
Let's just get this over with, okay?
- What's the code?
- She'll not tell you.
- Yeah, she'll tell me.
- What makes you say that?
'cause you said it's my destiny
to turn off that jammer.
We're both gonna die
down here, alright?
Let's be perfectly honest.
That one-eyed maniac
just killed your friend.
He shot you in the back.
It would appear
that your glorious leader, Ben,
put him up to it.
Are you a sodding idiot?
You have the opportunity
to make Ben very, very angry.
Why would you not take that?
- 5-4-5...
- What?
- 8-7-5-5...
- Is that a code?
- 4-3-7...
- Wait.
- Start again, start again.
- 6...
Start from the beginning!
- 1-3.
- Start from the beginning.
Start again.
Wake up, wake up.
Start again. Start again.
Good vibrations.
What?
Beach Boys.
Good vibrations.
On the keypad.
The numbers...
they're notes.
It was programmed by a musician.
Tie him up.
He's coming with us.
What?
This is your mother.
Will you help me tie him up?
What happened? What'd he say?
It's not important right now.
- Just get everybody together.
- Jack, your knuckles.
What happened?
He killed them.
All three of 'em. He...
He radioed the beach.
And I let it happen.
I had to let it happen.
We can't tell Rose...
or Sun, not yet.
We gotta keep moving. I promised Sayid
that we would keep moving.
So why did you bring him back?
Why didn't you just kill him?
Because I want him to see it.
I want him to experience the moment
that we get off this island,
and I want him to know...
That he failed.
And then I'll kill him.
It was an order, Tom.
We had to follow it.
Ben didn't know what the hell
he's talking about.
He's lost it.
I mean, look at what they did to us!
Instead of putting three bullets
in the damn sand,
we should've killed them for real.
All they got left is
three guys and four guns.
And all we've got, James,
are two people and no guns.
So we'll wait till night.
That isn't gonna change the fact
that we're unarmed.
If you wanna kill yourself, that's fine,
but before you go and try...
You hear that?
Stay in the bus, hero.
Stay right there, Tom.
I give up.
That's for taking the kid off the raft.
Dude, it was over. He surrendered.
I didn't believe him.
What are you doing, Dr. Shephard?
I was just...
I was just checking the...
The Arlen charts.
Just wanted to...
Wanted to see how the operation went.
I left three messages on your
voice mail. You didn't get them?
My phone's broken.
Let's go to my office.
For what?
We need to have a talk. Come on.
You know, I know that you're...
You're new around here,
so you don't know much about me...
I know enough.
So let's go to my office...
If you got something to say to me,
say it to me...
Right here.
Will you excuse us, please?
Mrs. Arlen, the woman you saved,
woke up in recovery about two hours ago.
She was in some pain
but highly responsive
to the reflex tests and entirely lucid.
Well, that's...
That's great.
But then she described
the series of events
that caused her accident.
She says she was driving over the bridge
when she saw a man
standing on top of the railing
about to jump off.
She was distracted
and lost control of her car.
She ran into the median,
rolled over
and was hit by the van behind her.
So the obvious question here...
it's how did you get
to that flaming car so fast?
What were you doing on that bridge?
Do you know how many years
I've worked at this hospital?
Do you know...
Anything about me?
Do you have any idea...
what I've been through?
How much have you had to drink today?
Okay, I'll tell you what. You do this...
You get my father down here.
Get him down here right now,
and if I'm drunker than he is,
you can fire me.
Don't you look at me like that.
Don't you... pity me.
- I'm trying to help you...
- You can't help me!
Attention, Others. Come in, Others.
If you're listening to this,
I want you to know
that we got you bastards,
and unless
the rest of you wanna be blown up,
you best stay away from our beach.
Where are you? What's going on?
Dude, I'm back at the beach.
What?
I went back to help Juliet and Sawyer.
I saved them.
You're...
They're okay? Juliet...
Everyone's fine.
Me, Sawyer, Juliet, Sayid, Jin, Bernard.
Wait.
Bernard and Jin and Sayid...
They're with you?
Yeah, dude, I told you.
I saved them all.
Stay where you are.
We're almost up to the tower.
- You'll be safer there.
- Yeah, I gotcha.
We'll stay put until you like,
you know, phone home.
What about Charlie?
Did he make it back yet?
Not yet, but they're probably
paddling home as we speak.
Don't worry. I'm sure he's fine.
There's diving gear
on those racks, yeah?
- Aye. It's plenty.
- Why don't you take care of that?
- I'll tap out Good Vibrations.
- Alright, mate.
You get any flashes?
No. Nothin'.
I'll meet you back here, then.
So much for fate.
"Incoming transmission"?
Can you hear me ?
Yes! Yes, I can hear you.
Who is this? Who am I speaking to?
Charlie Pace.
I'm a survivor of flight
8-1-5... Oceanic, flight 8-1-5.
Where are you?
We're on an island. We're alive.
An island? Well, where?
What's the location?
I don't know. Who's this?
This is Penelope.
Penelope Widmore.
How did you get this frequency?
Did you just say, "Desmond"?
Yeah, he's here. He's with me.
- Is he okay?
- He's brilliant!
Hey, are you on the boat?
- What boat?
- Your boat...
80 miles offshore.
Naomi, parachutist.
I'm not on a boat.
Who's Naomi?
Can you hear me?
Hey, Aaron, it's okay, sweetie.
What's the matter?
I don't know.
I think he's just a bit scared.
Hard to blame him.
- What is it?
- What's your boyfriend's name...
The rock star who goes to the station?
Charlie. Why?
Charlie just got us rescued.
He did it!
- Your friend bloody well did it.
- What?
The green light... it's on.
The jamming stopped.
Use it, then.
Alright.
4-2.
What's this?
It's Rousseau's message.
It's still blocking the signal.
It doesn't matter. We're here.
Iteration 1-7-5-0-4-5.
I recorded this 16 years ago.
Three days before you were born.
I guess we don't need it anymore.
All right. Do it.
I can't get a signal in here.
I'm getting something.
It's gonna work.
It's happening.
We're gonna get off of this island.
We'll celebrate when we're home.
I know you think
you're saving your people,
but you need to stop this.
It's a mistake.
The mistake was listening to you.
This will be your last chance.
I'm telling you, making that call
is the beginning of the end.
I've got it! I've got a signal!
Jack, please!
You don't know what you're doing!
I know exactly what I'm doing.
Step back, Jack.
What did you do?
What I had to. Now step back.
Stay away from the phone.
What are you doing?
I don't want to shoot you.
Do it, John! Shoot him!
Do what you need...
Please, put the phone down.
You're done keeping me on this island
I will...
kill you...
if I have to.
Then do it.
You're not supposed to do this.
Minkowski.
Who is this?
My name's Jack Shephard. Are you...
Are you on the boat... the freighter?
How'd you get this channel?
Naomi told us about your search team,
about the boat.
Naomi? You found her?
Where is she? Who are you?
I'm one of the survivors
of oceanic flight 815.
Can you get a fix on our location?
Hell, yeah, we can.
Sit tight. We'll be right there.
It's me.
Wait. Don't... Don't hang up, please.
I know what you said. I just...
I just need to see you.
Please.
Yeah, out at the airport.
You know where.
Thank you.
Saw you on the news.
Still pulling people
out of burning wreckage, huh?
Old habits.
You look terrible.
Thanks.
Why did you call me?
I was hoping that you'd heard,
that maybe you'd go to the funeral.
Why would I go to the funeral?
Been flying a lot.
What?
The golden pass that they gave us.
I've been using it.
Every friday night, I...
I fly from L.A. to Tokyo or...
Singapore or... Sydney.
And then I...
I get off, and I...
have a drink
and then I fly home.
Why?
Because I want it to crash.
I don't care
about anybody else on board.
Every little bump we hit or...
turbulence, I mean, like,
I actually close my eyes,
and I pray
that I can get back...
- This is not gonna change...
- No, I'm sick...
of lying.
We made a mistake.
I have to go.
He's gonna be wondering where I am...
We...
were not supposed to leave.
Yes, we were.
Good-bye, Jack.
We have to go back, Kate.
We have to go back!