Previously on "Battlestar Galactica":
Oh, no, look, l'm sorry,
l can't live like this.
So l won't divorce and you won't cheat.
- So where does that leave us?
- Trapped.
What's this?
The summary executions of all
the detainees listed on the next page.
It needs your signature.
(Gaeta) This is a death warrant.
Have you seen the names on this list?
Do you have any idea
what they're about to do out there?
(gunfire)
(Number Six) If you are a Cylon, these
feelings are part of your programming.
The final five revealed only to those who
enter the temple, only to the Chosen One.
Her destiny will part company from yours.
She's not the Chosen One, you are.
Dear God, tell me the truth before l die.
Am l a Cylon?
Welcome home, Mr President.
(Baltar and Number Six sing lullaby)
Sorry. Improvising.
You're doing the right thing, Gaius.
- Gaius...
- What?
Yes.
Wake up!
(both sing lullaby)
Wait.
Wait a minute.
l need some time to think this through.
Too late, Gaius.
It's time to learn the truth.
- Sergeant.
- Sorry, sir.
No one can speak to the prisoner
without presidential authorisation.
- l already have authorisation.
- Step back, sir.
That's it, Gaius.
Deep breaths.
The first time's the hardest.
You're doing wonderfully.
l'm alive.
Thank God! l'm alive!
l always told you to have faith.
Then no one was betrayed.
l was never one of them.
l am one of you.
Is that what you think, Gaius?
l knew it. l knew it.
l always knew l was different.
Special.
Maybe a little gifted.
Ow! That's a bit rough, actually.
That hurt.
- What's wrong?
- You're wrong, Gaius.
You're not Cylon, you're human.
And you're dead!
He's alive.
l'll get Cottle.
l'm just saying,
you're gonna be surprised.
- Yeah, well, Major...
- Right this way.
"Joe's"?
Well, l think l've seen a bar before.
(laid-back music plays)
- You've got to be frakking kidding me.
- Come on.
OK, this way.
Hey, Joe!
Chief Tyrol. Welcome.
Any friend of the major's a friend of mine,
which means you get the good stuff.
Thank you very much, don't mind if l do.
Not going home tonight, so...
Why, did you and Cally have a fight?
You didn't hear us?
l figured we could've sold tickets.
Uh...
To marriage: why we build bars.
Yeah.
Joe!
(Cottle) l warned about
the dangers of sleep deprivation.
Psychosis can make a man
do strange things.
And Baltar's little hunger strike
is not helping, either.
Bastard wants to die that bad,
l say let him.
Bottom line, we need Baltar to talk.
If the other Cylons saw
the same symbols that we saw,
they could be on their way to Earth
and setting up an ambush by now.
l bet after tonight
he'll be more willing.
Doc, wait an hour or two.
l want him cogent.
l also don't want him to starve.
- What do you expect me to do about it?
- l expect you to make sure he eats.
(clears throat)
l'll see about putting
security cameras in that cell.
Um, Mr Gaeta...
What exactly were you doing going to see
Dr Baltar in the middle of the night?
Um...
l couldn't sleep and l guess l thought
he might be willing to talk to me.
We understand.
Just leave his interrogation to us.
Of course.
You're up late.
- You know, the Chief says hi.
- He one of your new drinking buddies?
l would invite you, but you made it
very clear it's not your thing.
No, it's your thing,
and that's not what l was asking.
l got a briefing at 0500.
- Are we still on for dinner tomorrow?
- (sighs) Yeah.
- l already switched watches.
- Sure.
Just be nice for a husband and wife
to occasionally...
Forget it.
(Roslin) Thank you.
You can leave the door open.
Hi.
Touché, Madam President.
l have no wish to see you suffer.
Really?
l've just had the pleasure of having a tube
forced up my nose and down my throat.
Everybody's got to eat.
It's for your own good.
And it's nothing compared to what
many of our people were subjected to
in your jail cells on New Caprica.
Not my jails... the Cylons'.
It's an academic distinction
at this point, Doctor.
None of us are enjoying this, so why
don't you just tell me what l need to know
and your suffering will come to an end,
and l promise you this.
l know nothing about the Cylon plans
or their whereabouts.
l witnessed nothing in that temple.
My information on Cylon intelligence is...
is limited, to say the least.
Prior to the attack, did you have
high-level security clearance?
- Yes. So what?
- Did you tell anybody about it?
Did you let someone
into the defence mainframe?
- Careful, Gaius.
- The blonde woman l saw you with
on Caprica, just prior to the attack?
She'll flush you out of an airlock
without a moment's hesitation.
Unless, of course,
that prospect no longer frightens you.
(exhales)
Lies.
All lies.
A rehash of all the other old lies.
l did not collude
in the genocide of my own people.
Devlin and Maryanne McAIlister
and their son and daughter.
A family of four gunned down
in their own home
- on suspicion of insurgency.
- l am not responsible.
l just wondered if you recognised
even one of these faces.
Did any image get through to you on the
rare occasion when you ventured out...
- l am not responsible...
- ...from behind your sandbags to see...
- ...any more than l am for the genocide.
- ...what was happening to your people?
Your people! l need to know, now.
Colonel Tigh, get in here!
Get this man out of here.
This is not about uncovering a threat.
- Toss him out of the nearest airlock.
- This is about your pound of flesh!
- Get in here! Get rid of him!
- What about my fair trial?
- Take him out of here.
- Get your frakking hands off me!
l demand a fair trial! l am a citizen
of the Colonies and l demand a fair trial!
A fair trial!
Take a good look. Just a fraction
of the people you sent to their deaths.
Rather fitting they should see
you take your last breaths.
Stop! Stop, wait!
- Stop!
- What? What?
You asked if l know these people.
l know that man.
Show me, show me!
Let him go, let him go!
- Keep your guns on him!
- This man.
His name was Adrien Bauer,
my lab assistant on Caprica.
- So what?
- He was Gemonese. l got him a visa.
l introduced him to his wife.
l am godfather to their first child.
l wouldn't harm this man or his family.
Or anybody's family! l am not a murderer!
l am innocent! Why won't you believe me?
- Get him! Take him out of here!
- Is this what you call Colonial justice?
What did l ever do for you, huh?
Only save your bleeding life! Argh!
You gave it your best shot.
l understand.
Yeah, the bastard still wouldn't talk.
Either he's got more stones
than l gave him credit for, or...
Or he knew you were bluffing.
Well...
what do we do with him now?
There is one thing.
Admiral?
The military once ran an experimental
interrogation programme involving drugs.
Hallucinogens, specifically.
The goal of the programme was
to create a state of anxiety so intense
that the subject believed
that their very survival was at stake.
The interrogators exploit that,
become less an adversary and more
a lifeline - at least, that was the idea.
It might get Baltar to talk,
tell us what the Cylons know about Earth.
But it's dangerous, especially
for someone in Baltar's condition.
Are you telling me we have these drugs
aboard Galactica?
You're being awfully accommodating.
Is that how it looks to you?
Your estranged two-timing bitch of a wife
calls you up for a quickie
and you hop on the first shuttle?
l'd say yeah.
- l've been thinking about stuff, Kara.
- Yeah, like what?
Like...
what that crazy skin-job Leoben said
about you and your "special destiny".
What if there's something to that?
Kara Thrace and her special destiny?
That sounds more like
a bad cover band, Sam.
Think about it, though.
Why did l survive all those months
on Caprica, waiting for you to return,
if l was just gonna walk out on you?
And you... l mean,
did you go through that hell
locked in that fake house
with that fake husband
just so you could ditch me?
l don't think so.
Not when l think about it like that.
Do you love him?
What?
Lee, Kara. Do you love Lee?
Gods, Sam, I...
Maybe.
l don't know.
Then you gotta go to him.
- l thought you were off duty.
- l am, yeah.
l was just gonna
stop by the bar for a little while.
If you're gonna see Kara, just admit it.
- l told you, there's nothing going on.
- Yeah, you both told me.
"Lee won't cheat, he's too noble."
The problem is, it's all a crock.
You know what the only problem is?
That you don't trust me, that's it.
And this is just your own frakking
insecurities talking, same as always.
l mean, right from the get-go.
The very first morning that l proposed.
l mean... You know what? Forget it.
This is frakking pointless.
Maybe you're right.
l did see this coming.
And l was naive enough
to marry you anyway.
And you wanna know why, Lee?
Cos l loved you.
l loved you so frakking much.
l thought l was lucky.
That's right - lucky.
That l could have you for just as long
as you - or Kara - would let me.
Dee...
- Come on, come here.
- (sobs)
It's not a marriage, Lee.
This is a lie.
You wanna be with Kara?
Go ahead.
l won't stand in your way.
It's over.
Wait, where are you going?
(door closes)
No, Sam.
l gotta get going.
This was fun.
(Anders) l love you.
(Baltar) l'm a human being.
l'm a human being, l have rights.
l said, l have rights!
Please. Please help me.
l'm not sure l can, Gaius.
Pain is one thing, but this...
Without free will, what are you?
Can God even pity such a creature?
Why not just admit you're doing this
for your own satisfaction.
That's the truth.
Why not put the needle in yourself?
- (Cottle) Hold his head.
- Oh, no, no, no!
No! No! Oh, God!
He's under.
Try not to make any loud noise.
Put the head strap on.
Where am I?
My God, where am I?
(Apollo) What are you saying?
If l leave Sam, will you still leave Dee?
My gods, Kara.
How do l know that tomorrow
you're not gonna pull another 180?
These are our frakking marriages.
It's not some stupid dogfight
we can just jink our way out of.
Think about it, Lee.
It's what you're best at.
Where am I?
My God, where am I?
(Adama) Can you hear my voice?
Can you hear me, Doctor?
- Admiral, is that you?
- l'm looking for you, Doctor.
But l can't find you.
Can you tell us where you are?
It's water.
l'm in the water.
It's cold and it's dark.
l can't see anything!
Is there anything you can see
that can tell us where you are?
Look for the light.
Can you see it?
- Yes.
- Try to reach for the light.
(monitor bleeps rapidly then slows)
That's it.
- Yes.
- Follow the light.
(thunder)
(explosion)
Caprica.
Caprica Six!
She saved my life.
She shielded me from the explosion.
Doctor, did you conspire with her
to subvert our defence system?
Conspiracy requires intent.
l never intended...
But she said deep down
l'd always suspected.
But l didn't know.
How could l know?
Did l conspire? Did I?
No!
No! l don't know.
No.
It wasn't my fault.
It wasn't my fault!
l am not responsible!
(monitor bleeps rapidly)
She...
Caprica Six.
She chose me.
She chose me over all men.
Chosen to be seduced.
Taken by the hand.
Guided between the light and the dark.
But is she an angel or is she a demon?
ls she imaginary or is she real?
Is she my own voice or the voice of?
l can't stay afloat much longer!
Now give us details, Doctor.
Give us details about the Cylons,
or we'll let you drown.
Alone... in the dark.
No!
Hey, Chief.
Why is it so frakking hard?
Why can't we just... get back to normal?
Normal...
What is "normal", anyway?
Chief, you can tell me
if l'm out of line here,
but, um...
Do you ever think about Sharon?
No.
Come on.
You never wonder, "What if..."?
No.
No, don't leave me!
l know l'm flawed!
l never claimed to be...
Yeah, mistakes... mistakes were made,
terrible mistakes!
Were they mine?
Am l solely to blame?
l was a player, that's all! l was a player!
l was struggling to try
to find my place in God's plan!
God's resolve. I...
l never intended for certain things
to happen! Doesn't that matter?
You took the Cylons to the temple,
to the Eye of Jupiter. What did it tell them?
What did it tell them about Earth?
l was looking for...
What were you looking for, Doctor?
What were you looking for?
(spiritual chanting)
Their faces,
but they wouldn't show them to me.
Their faces. Whose faces?
The five.
The final five.
The final five? Cylons?
l thought l might be one of them.
l told them l wanted to be one of them.
A Cylon? Why?
All my sins forgiven.
A new beginning.
Are you a Cylon, Dr Baltar?
No.
That's not good enough, Doctor.
Tell me what you told the Cylons.
What do they know?
Tell me, or l'll have to let you go, Doctor.
l'll have to let you go.
Tell me, or l'll have to let you go.
Look where you're going.
My ring.
Has anybody seen my ring?
l lost it.
l want my ring!
- Admiral, we're losing him.
- (rapid bleeps)
That's enough. l'm putting an end
to this freak show right now.
(Roslin) No, listen to this.
Five final Cylon models.
Five pillars of the temple
for the five priests devoted
to the one whose name cannot be spoken.
- Come on, it's all just mumbo jumbo.
- He's holding a lot back, l'm sure of it.
Maybe we should resort
to more direct methods.
Direct methods?
Now you have my vote.
No.
We tried the stick -
it's time to try the carrot.
The thing he's most deeply afraid of
is, even if he talks, we'll kill him.
- Smart man.
- We have to ease his fear,
make him believe that if he collaborates,
at the very least he'll have his life.
He won't buy that, coming from us.
Of course not.
We have to find someone he trusts.
(Baltar) As perverse as it may seem,
l may actually owe these people
a debt of gratitude.
l realise there's probably nothing l can say
that can make this right.
But there's something you need to know.
l asked you to marry me
because l was in love with you.
Just like l'm in love with you now.
They forced me...
to admit my failings.
And now that l have,
l feel positively liberated.
You were right.
l loved Kara.
You know? And maybe
there's part of me that always will.
In my heart,
l know l have always done...
what l've had to do.
But l married you.
l married you.
And, you know,
when l look back at our marriage,
at the time that we have spent together,
you are good for me, Dee.
And l need you.
And l don't think l ever really realised that
till l knew that l was losing you.
(Gaeta) l can't promise you a trial, Doctor.
l'm sure that if you give them
something... anything...
But, please, just give me another chance -
that's all l'm asking.
Just give me the chance.
(Gaeta) These charts that l've been using
to plot our course to Earth...
l've never been confident
of my calculations.
That's lucky, because
the calculations are wrong.
l detect a number of inconsistencies
right off the bat.
- These figures here are wrong.
- That's exactly what l was afraid of.
Cylon navigation systems
are far more advanced than ours.
But l have managed to commit
many of the algorithms to memory.
If we can offer them this kind of help,
l'm certain, at the very least,
they'll spare your life.
Maybe we can even get you out of this cell
and offer you some proper quarters.
Creature comforts, that's the clincher?
Sorry?
Where is it?
- Um... where is what, Doctor?
- "Where is what?"
So much for that little stratagem.
Hello.
You all right?
Listen, we don't have to stay here
if you don't want to, OK?
Yeah.
Two whiskies, straight up.
l should have known that you'd betray me.
What did you tell them?
You stayed behind till the grisly end
on New Caprica so you could, what,
so you could feed information
to the Resistance?
Who do you think allowed you to do that?
- That's a lie.
- No, it's not a lie. You think l'm blind?
You see, l literally had a gun
pointed to my head.
But nobody forced you to play both sides.
So l'm asking you, Mr Gaeta...
who is the real traitor in this room?
To the first of many.
- Let's do another.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
- l'm not a traitor.
- Of course.
Because there are far worse things
than being a traitor, aren't there, Felix?
If your friends only knew the truth.
Don't worry. l can keep your little secret.
We gotta get in there.
Frak you!
(guard) Lieutenant Gaeta,
step away from the prisoner, now!
Step away from the prisoner.
l will not ask again.
- Stand down, Sergeant.
- Yes, sir.
- Step back, Mr Gaeta.
- No! No, sir.
l can't let him live,
not after what he's done.
Mr Gaeta? Mr Gaeta, wait, please.
Look at me.
- l understand what you're feeling.
- No, you don't.
Yes, l do. The other night, you didn't
come here to interrogate Dr Baltar.
You came here to kill him, didn't you?
l understand that, l do.
- What's his condition?
- He missed the artery. He'll live.
Gotta get him to sickbay.
Get a gurney in here right away.
(Roslin) Go easy on him.
(Number Six) All things considered, Gaius,
it could have been worse.
Much worse.
Well, you're not one of the five,
but you certainly have
the luck of the gods.
Well, l am the Chosen One.
You didn't tell them that, did you?
No.
Everybody's got to have a secret.
l told him l didn't take any satisfaction
in seeing his pain.
But the truth is, l was willing to see him
endure a great deal of suffering
in order to get what l wanted.
It wasn't some intelligence or some truth.
l wanted a genuine admission of guilt.
That's something you're not gonna get
from someone like Baltar.
He doesn't see himself that way.
It's not who he is.
In his eyes... he's the victim.
Not the criminal.
It's not too late for him
to just... disappear.
We can't do that.
For all his crimes, he's one of us.
So what happens next?
We give him his trial.
Back masking.
Turn me on, dead man.