(j.D.) sacred heart--
eight years of great memories.
This place will live forever.
They tore down
the old crappy hospital
And rebuilt it
on the med school campus.
I'm just back
to teach some classes.
First, though, I need to do
my morning good luck ritual.
And seven.
That's one good luck kiss
For every month
you've been in there.
Are you done yet?
Not yet.
And thank you for making
mommy's boobs so much bigger.
They're almost jugs.
Seriously, I think I can
probably rest 'em on your head.
Check it out.
Okay. Yeah.
Whoa! Talk about
a 10-gallon hat.
(chuckles) how cool is that?
Donny, no questions right now,
okay? This is private.
They're still looking.
I said this is private!
Turn around!
That was heavy.
Hey, do good today.
Bye.
I can still feel them
on my head.
How sweet is he?
Part of me hates
how familiar this seems.
I hope I can find a way
to make this all feel new.
(woman) oh, my god.
The first day of med school.
Everything is so new. I mean,
just look at all these people
Who don't know that I used to
wear a back brace.
I can look left.
Yep, new sights, new sounds,
even new smells.
Kiwi.
What?
I smell kiwi.
Yeah, it's my shampoo.
I love kiwis, okay?
I love them, too!
Actually, that's not true.
They're hairy.
They look like monkey nuts.
Don't smell people.
It's weird.
I'm lucy.
I don't care!
Regroup, lucy. Find an ally.
Hi. I'm lucy.
Cool. Hey, after class,
You want to go somewhere,
get weird with each other?
I feel like you skipped
a few steps.
Hey, come on. You already know
if you're in or out.
So what's the deal, girl?
Not interested.
Medicine is...
Well, it's a dead career.
Thanks to insurance companies
and malpractice lawyers,
You have absolutely no hope
Of finding a rewarding
or satisfying profession
In this once noble field.
The only exception to this very
true rule is the following--
If you are lucky enough to go
to a great medical school,
Then, my children,
you got a real shot.
Because to call this particular
school a "crap house"
Would be
an honest-to-god compliment.
Plus, m the only teacher here
worth a damn,
And I already hate
each and every one of you.
Would you like to know why?
Well, it turns out
You're not actually
medical studen at all.
You are all murderers
and assassins
That have been sent here
to try to kill my patients.
Here's the bottom line--
If you do get a good clean kill
on a patient,
Go ahead and take a pinkie
or an ear as a trophy.
I am ready for you,
have been for a while,
So watch your ass. Good day.
Okay. I hope everyone enjoyed
orientation with dr. Cox.
I'm dr. Mahoney,
your student advisor.
Here's some crappy pizza.
Joining us, gramps?
You know, 'cause you're old
for a med student.
They told me to give out
fun nicknames for team building.
It's working.
Look, uh, drew,
I don't like dealing with,
well, people.
And all these kids
obviously look up to you.
I've never spoken
to any of these people.
I can still feel a bond,
and I thought,
Why don't you deal with
the whiny, emotional stuff?
And in return,
I will let you do that.
Look, just, uh, let me fly
under the radar.
Please.
I guess I should answer any
annoying questions you all have.
Yeah, monkey nuts.
Uh, I just wanted to thank you,
on behalf of all of us,
For getting us pizza.
There. Smelling incident fixed.
Yeah, they gave me money
to do it,
Along with
free room and board
To attend
to your emotional needs.
Speaking of which,
little administrative thing--
If you're going to
kill yourself--
I'm looking at you,
sad eyes--
Do it off campus,
'cause it is a buttload
of paperwork.
All right, everyone,
pay attention,
Because my spleen is right here.
Whoops!
This feels more like
my private-time area.
Wouldn't it be easier if you
could see what you were doing?
This is the way I'm doing it,
cole!
Or maybe
you're just uncomfortable
Because it's a black man's head
on a fake white man's body.
That's right, people.
It just got real up in here.
In my class,
you will each be graded
By the color of your skin.
F's.
There he is.
Yes!
Dude!
What the hell are you doing?!
I thought
it'd be more dramatic
If we spotted each other
from afar
And then ran
to see each other!
But now if we meet
in the middle,
We'll wind up somewhere
inside the hospital,
And this really feels like
more of an outside thing!
If you count to ten
before you run,
I should be able to get
downstairs and over to you!
I'm already counting!
Three, four...
Hey, dr. Turk.
Not now, denise.
Turk!
I'm late. Gotta go.
Mm.
Mm. You smell like prison.
When was the last time
you guys saw each other?
This morning. We carpooled.
But we haven't worked together
in over a year.
You know
what I'd like to do now?
Is it go to vermont
anmake this thing legal?
Talk to the hand.
Remember that?
(high-pitched voice) eagle!
(normal voice)
oh, hey, perry.
I'm really looking forward
to teaching wi you.
Onward.
(high-pitched voice) eagle!
Oh, good god.
Sync By YesCool
www.addic7ed.com
"Scrubs", Episode 1
"First Day of School".
I'll have you know
this is the very jacket
Worn by michelle pfeiffer
in "dangerous minds."
All I had to do was sew
these elbow patches on
And take the shoulder pads out.
Hmm.
By the way, what ever
happened to the janitor?
Oh, dude. It was
the day after you left...
When's that little buddy
of yours coming back?
He's never coming back.
He's gone for good.
He's right here, isn't he?
Where would I be hiding him?
But he's coming back...
No.
After his vacation.
And no one ever
saw him again.
Dr. Kelso,
what are you doing her
I'm teaching
a couple of classes.
J.D.'s gonna teach here, too.
(chuckles) oh, turk,
sometimes I'll teach them.
Sometimes they'll teach me,
But we're always going to
inspire each other.
You're still
such an odd little fruit.
Is that woman's jacket?
No, it's a man's small.
Yes, it's actually the jacket
from "dangerous minds."
He doesn't need to know that.
Dr. Kelso, I heard about
enid's passing. I'm so sorry.
Well, you bottom out,
And then you persevere.
(wspers) yeah.
I feel like I can say
the worst is over.
How long ago did she pass?
About two days.
I'm a frequent flier.
Congrats, I guess.
No, no, no. That means I'm in
and out of the hospital a lot.
Oh.
Ben. Ischemic bowel disease.
Lucy. I'm a med student.
You look like
you could use a grape.
Thanks, ben. I really could.
No stealing food
from patients.
Gather 'round, murderers.
Gather 'round.
I saw that. Spit it out.
Now eat it again.
At least we know
you're a good listener.
Score!
You should all follow 19's lead,
And I call her "19," because
instead of using your names,
I'm going to go by where
you currently rank in my hd.
Now who can tell me what artery
Goes above the optic chiasm
to the cerebral hemispheres?
Supermodel in the back.
(australian accent)
I'm fairly certain
It's the anterior
cerebral artery.
What?
I'm not understanding a word
ththat she's saying,l artery.
And, people,
I can teach anyone.
You just gotta speak english.
I'm australian.
Still not getting it.
Everyone, leave. (whistles)
I'm sorry
about the grape thing.
Oh, don't sweat it, 42.
Is my number going down
because I'm talking to you?
Why was michael in my room?
His name isn't michael.
Well, he has a weird
serbian name that I can't say,
So I'm calling him michael.
He loves it.
I don't. My name is ilyevic.
Mike, just go.
Young michael informed me
that you told everyone
To come to me
with their personal problems.
Yeah, I did.
I checked on you.
You've already been
to med school
Once already
when you were 21.
And you didn't just flame out,
you, like, you went nuclear.
Seriously, how was prison?
It was cold.
You couldn't just let me be.
Well, I'm gonna take
The high road and not mention
your mannish voice
And all the pictures you have
in here of your friends.
Tell me,
which one's your b.F.F.?
You are a giant douche.
I know.
Want to take a shower
together?
Fine.
I know you think you're so hot,
but I'm not a fan.
Hey, I'm not happy about this
either, okay?
Welcome
to internal medicine, gang.
My name is dr. John dorian.
Hey,
should we be taking notes?
That's a good question, fellow.
What I'll tell you is
I don't like to really stop.
That ruins my flow.
So what I'm gonna do is give
a subtle nod like so...
As a signal, okay?
Now back to my name.
I prefer "dr. D.,"
or in a pinch, "dr. Dizzle."
But if you see me
out in the quad--
there is no quad.
I'm not a big fan of the t.A.S
doing a lot of speaking, denise.
Okay?
Oh, wait. Wait. That was
an accidental nod, you guys.
No note taking.
No note taking, okay?
Now if you see me
out in the quad...
I want you to think of me
as more than your teacher.
I'm also your friend, all right?
Okay, we're definitely
gonna need a new signal
For the note-taking thing.
This guy's trying
to die on me again.
Who wants to play
patient roulette?
Please not me. Please not me.
There ain't no use runnin',
little girl!
First one to bring me
a med student gets a juicy bone.
He gets a juicy bone.
You gotta yell!
91, here's how we play.
I'm not gonna do anything
to help this dying man
Until you answer these
three very simple questions--
At is it called
when a blood clot
Occludes a branch
of the pulmonary artery?
What is it called when
tuberculosis affects the spine?
And what was the name
of the african nba center
Who did this
whenever he blocked a shot?
Oh, I'd hurry.
His heart's slowing down.
And he's dead,
Not because of you.
I'm not insane.
He was dead
when we walked over here.
But just a stunningly
horrible job nonetheless.
All right. We finally found
a signal that works--jazz hands.
Love it.
Guys, tomorrow you'll be divided
into groups,
And you'll be given
your cadavers.
So great first day, everybody.
Who wants to keep this party
going?
If so,
meet me back here at 6:00.
I will have beers, on me.
Everyone take a mixed cd
on their way out.
For those of you who are fans
of a young miss miley cyrus,
I recommend the green ones.
She's heavily featured.
Dr. Cox?
Professor.
Professor cox?
Actually it's both.
Dr. Professor cox?
Yes?
Sometimes I feel like you're
not even trying to teach me.
I'm not.
I generally don't waste time
With people
who aren't gonna make it.
Oh. Thanks.
Thanks?
Hey. Can I talk to you
for a sec?
What do you want?
Well, um, I get the whole
trial-by-fire thing--
And you're wonderful at it,
really.
Don't ever touch me.
Sorry. Um, but you seem
to go out of your way
To pick on the weakest kids.
Ybe you could,
I don't know, not do that.
Thank you for the feedback.
It's invaluable.
You don't mean that, do you?
I don't.
And since you don't see yourself
as one of the weak ones,
Maybe a good solution
would be for me to unload
My years of rage and frustration
and pain onto your head
And your head alone.
Are--are we locked down to that,
or can we keep spitballing here?
Very locked in.
Looking forward to it.
Not you. Just something I say
whenever I'm pissed...
When I'm with a whore.
Whoa!
None of them showed up.
I got us all these
glow-in-the-dark necklaces
So we wouldn't lose each other
when we were out on the town.
It's their first day
of med school.
Come on.
You remember how we were.
Nerds!
Losers!
(bicycle bell tinkles)
I feel so alive.
Everybody at that party
had sex.
No.
(j.D.) we all go through life
Worrying about
what other people think of us.
Man, I must be
the worst teacher ever.
The truth ,
the harshest words
Are the ones we say
about ourselves.
You okay, sweetie?
No, ben.
I don't belong here.
(lucy)
I was so depressed yesterday.
To cheer myself up, I made what
I think is a great decision.
Sometimes one perfect night
Can change your whole outlook
on life.
(camera phone shutter clicks)
Yep. I've got a good feeling
about this guy.
Hey, darling. I'm dr. Cole.
I'll be your physician.
So... What are we dealing
with here?
Non-hodgkin's lymphoma.
Oh, giant drag.
Hey.
Come here.
Hope you enjoyed your last day
of med school.
Yeah, I don't see it.
I'm sorry. What?
You know that bust
you pass on your way
To pick up
your tiny paycheck?
Notice any resemblance?
Symmetric features, strong jaw.
Yeah, that's my pop-pop--
paid for this whole building.
So here's the skinny--
I'm teflon.
You can fire bullets at me
if you want, but be careful.
When they ricochet off me,
they sometimes hit other people.
Pa-chi. Pa-ching.
Don't pa-chi me.
Pa-ching.
Don't you pa-ching me!
My dad always says
every day is a new day.
So today I'm gonna
be confident, strong,
And nothing will knock me
off my game.
Oh, who am I kidding?
I'm doomed.
Has anyone seen
the crash cart?
Ah, it's, uh,
over by bed four.
Now can you make that out?
I think I heard the words
"bear fight,"
But that makes no sense.
You're right.
That's super fun.
I love doing things with you.
Thanks, perry. I needed that.
I'm having a little trouble
getting my teacher groove going.
Maybe you suck at it.
Why do you have to lash out,
perry?
Stay open for business
in here,
In your heart cage.
I guess I'm just tired
of weeding out the weak
To protect the rest of the herd,
like I always do.
Maybe you could mix it
up a little.
Try in-investing emotionally
in one of them.
A kid stood o me
just the other day,
And... I kind of felt
connected to him.
Good, good, good.
I'm--I'm sure
you probably knew him
For--for all of 30 seconds.
It's not like I tried
For--for eight years or anything
to get your love.
I thought we were over this.
I'm drowning here.
I wish there was just someone
Who could fly up
and rescue me from all this.
(j.D.) I feel like
I'd get back on track
If I could just find
one student to connect with--
One kid that really needs me.
I mean, that's what it's
all about, right? Reaching out.
What's your name?
Drew.
I'm taking an interest
in you.
Carry on.
That's not good for me,
is it?
Drew, you know I d care.
Come on. Grab me like a man.
Let's do this.
Ah, what up, dizzle?
You dropped something.
I got it.
I'm not always a believer
in serpity,
But sometimes the world
just brings things together.
I was chasing that,
so it's mine.
It's a naked picture of me.
It fell out
of that cole kid's notebook.
Oh, don't be sad.
It's just--oh, wow!
That is a very graphic
naked picture of you.
You know, we're gonna go over
a lot of that stuff in class,
So don't worry about it.
I shouldn't have looked.
I'm both a married man
and a beloved professor.
I know. You're dr. Dorian.
This area's
technically the quad,
So it's--it's j.D.
Lucy.
Nice to meet you, lucy.
(lucy) don't let him leave.
Say something, lucy.
J.D.?
Can I help you
with something?
Dr. Cox is all over me.
I can't take it.
Come with me.
Come on.
Lucy, to win
at the game of perry cox,
Yohave to stand up to him.
He just wants to kw
That you're strong enough
to survive here.
So you need to
go ahead and show him.
Dr. Co--dr. Professor cox?
I actually knew the answers
to all your questions.
Check it out--
Pulmonary embolism,
pott's disease
And dikembe mutombo.
That's fabulous.
I dot care.
It's just that
you kept yelling,
And you had that vein thing
Popping out the side
of your head... There it is.
And sometimes I get nervous
under pressure,
And I forget basic...
You know,
the things that you speak.
Words?
Yes! Words.
People speak words.
Look, when you have a patient
coding on the table,
What, are you gonna tell
the whole room to stop screaming
So that you don't get nervous?
No.
Oh, I know that face.
You're a crier.
You cry.
I have not cried once
in my entire adult life,
And I am not gonna start now
because of you.
We'll see.
And, dr. Cox?
If you do make me cry,
it won't be a big deal,
Because I lied.
I cry all the time.
Oh, good god.
(j.D.) little victories count
for a lot around here,
Even if you ner asked to win
in the first place.
(whistles) congrats.
I am now going to expect
more from you
Than I've expected
from a med student ever.
Whore.
And you have to enjoy those
nice moments while you can.
This is your group's cadaver
for the semester.
Because around here,
They never last very long.
Treat him well.
I wonder
what this guy's deal was.
Ben.
His name was ben.
why are we whispering?
And I threw a blanket over
his head and then sat on him.
He doesn't know it's me.
What's your exit strategy?
I haven't really thought
that far ahead.
I got a plan. Todd, can you
come here and sit on this?
Okay. (grunts)
Get him.
Sodude or chick?
I'm good either way.
Sync by YesCool
www.addic7ed.com