All right, Mrs. Cropper,
I think you'll gonna be fine without the antibiotics
And you don't think that I'll need a pelvic exam?
But not for the cold, no
Do it with the gloves off.
Ok. Either step a side, or I'm gonna go through you
Then you go through me...
you go through me hard.
Mrs. Cropper wasn't the only one showing agression
Every since Turk visited his bother last month,
he'd been more alpha-male than ever
All right,
we all know the rules of remote wrestling
last man standing decides what we watch.
Man rumble?
I've got next.
Right! Right!
No
I don't care that you've been waiting two hours to be helped.
Thank you for let me think about it.
Right here.
I can't believe I've never said this to you,
nobody cares whats you think.
Listen, guys.
It's come to my attention that nobody around here cares what we think.
Tell me about it.
But no!
Exactly.
Sort of.
I've figured a way to get our voices heard, ok?
It's a little news letter called...
Brace yourselves...
Seriously, brace yourselves.
The Janitorial
Todd has a question.
Yes, could I be the photographer,
so I have a value excuse for wearing this?
What I need, is an investigate of reporter.
Somebody, who is blend enough, insignificant enough
that he'll be listening in a private conversation
get the secrets, but nobody even know if he was there.
I'll do it!
Have you been sitting here all time?
No, first I was in your chair, but you sat on my lap,
remember?
I said "excuse me", and you said "get up and sit over there"
and I did.
Right?
And...
Hey, Janitor?
Oh, hey, Ted!
Rate Dr.Reid's butt?
Yes, 9.2!
Come down, Enid.
It's not my fault that I've been forced down out my job.
Now Enid...
I've got to go back to work...
Don't be too pleased with that 9.2, that's out 100.
Dr.Cox, can Sam watch West Side Story?
Helps him fall sleep.
And it makes my heart sing...
All right, I just do it in my head then.
Wow, we're watching the game
Put that remote down or be prepared to wrestle.
Who ordered to care whop ass? I think you did...
I want you to see this.
Do you see a TV from there, buddy?
Unfortunately, you're going to have to get used to events like this.
Don't... listen... to him... Sam...
Turk... stop... bouncing...
Timing, french subtitiles - Traxdater, Maître Kooms, Guronzan, Srabounette, Gotouille, Arbu, Arthax
English subtitles - PsixROs
Scrubs, season 7, episode 8
My Manhood
How you get it to spin so well?
Check it out! We made the front page!
I know, it's awesome. Now there is no doubt
who has the best butts in a whole hospital.
Tracy and Stacy can suck it!
Dude...
Oh, sorry, Tracy and Stacy.
See you, guys, are wearing each others oxygen mask(?).
That's cute.
All right, they win.
-Get two!
-I know.
It's great having a silver bullets like that on everyone in a hospital.
-You sure told him.
-Thanks, herpis.
I'm so sorry
Oh, sweetheart, you should. It's your fault.
Don't help me. And keep this to yourself.
That'll be our secret!
This is your new patient John, what's your secret?
I can't tell.
And besides, you are terrible in keeping secrets.
You know, my brothers are great in keeping secrets.
There was only for a second!
Still gay, though...
Told you!
It's official,
The Janitorial is a hit.
But no time to rest,
Doug, the Janitorial is a try daily.
I'm right here.
I bought you that scone.
I'm kidding, Ted.
Actually, I was't kidding.
Todd, how's the weather section shaping up?
You called me stupid?
Well, it's your stupid paper, right? So...
yeah, you're stupid.
And...
Done.
What did I miss?
Hey, dude...
I want you to let him go.
I don't have a problem with you, man.
I should warn you, I've killed the man.
-Sorry.
-That's why. Walk away!
Walk away!
We got him.
Well, that was a close one, wasn't it?
Thank godness, your big brave man friend was here.
Sam,
I wanna be real clear about this:
that's your daddy.
Not your mommy.
How you get Sam out of day care?
I'll be right here.
It's a nice guy, isn't he?
He's incredible, what's your secret?
Aah, are you pregnant?
-It's his baby.
-That was one dream, Carla!
Which have?
I'm kidding, Ted.
I don't wanna eat it again.
Ted.
Here's John's labwork.
If you tell me your secret, I won't tell anybody about the time you ate a cricket.
But dude, that's my job, remember?
When Sam gets older I'll teach him about sports and stuff,
Turk, we are not married.
Dude, we are little married.
I know, I love it.
You know?
That's it! I am a man,
Thank you.
I feel alone too...
Oh no...
Get up!
I knew I had two choices.
Apologize to Turk and admit it was an accident.
Or this...
Yeah, how you like me now, bitch!
So uncool.
I'm gonna kill him... where...
Why are you here?
Could question?
How can I possibly have breast cancer?
Anyone can get it, John.
What?
No, Dr.Kelso, my cousin didn,t hang himself, ok?
He did, but he lived.
That's a nice story.
Stop, stop,
stop it, please...
There is no touching.
No please, no touching me...
Ok, everyone! Can I get your attention?
That interview is a fake.
It never happens.
So,
there is no more touching me.
not now, not never!
Knock, knock, knock.
You've the interview too?
What interview?
Oh, thank God,
Turk will never beat me in front of Carla.
What is John's problem?
Yeah, Carla, what is his problem?
One testicle.
These conditions are perfect.
He's a beautiful.
Oh my God! It is totally awesome.
Stop, Turk, you're making him cry.
It's ok, plant Turk.
Friends.
See? He's learning.
We have to find your ball, Turk.
We have to find it and destroy it.
Look at him, he's dying in there.
Good, he's not dying.
Josh.
Fair enough.
I'm sorry.
Apologize accepted.
Occupied!
I know!
Stupid doctor-patient confident
It's like to be silenced.
It's like last month,
Oh my God.
Dr Kelso wants my help.
I swear, Elliot, if you don't tell me this secret,
So which one's you lose?
How did it happened?
That sucks.
I'm not really sure.
Turk, if you not being listening...
Sam.
Rule model.
I have to win.
So what's you wanna do?
And then we had it.
Check out the scar.
This is brilliant.
I've thought you'd like it.
It can even make so afraid to ask for a help, bur instead
we just quietly hope for someone to notice.
Dr.Kelso, I told Carla your secret
we'll gonna help you.
We're going to try to regroup all of the hospital
Are you in on this too, Perry?
Nope.
First time hearing it, and could careless.
He'll get there.