Hey, man.
I'm gonna hit the gym and sneak
in a quick workout. Wanna come?
Sweating it out in a steam room isn't
exercising, buddy.
No, it's sit-cercising.
Newbie, gandhi, come here.
great. Dr. Cox
and his golden boy med student.
I wanted you to witness this.
Number one, say good-bye
to the number one sign...
Aw, that's too bad.
Whoo-hoo! Arriba!
And say hello
to the number one shirt.
What?!
It's beautiful, honestly.
The nicest shirt
I've ever received
From a grown, married man.
Oh, go on.
Please leave me alone.
Put it on.
Hey, wow. That's--that's
some crazy ink you got there.
What the hell is that thing, anyway?
I don't know. I woke up after a 3-day bender
Driving a forklift and sporting this.
"my name's drew. I'm so cool
'cause I've been in prison
and I got a tattoo."
mock him,
and I'll eat your soul!
Tattoo spooked you
a little, huh?
His breath was so cold.
So cold.
flapjacks!
oh, thank god.
I thought I was late
for dr. Cox's class.
That would be the biggest
mistake I could make.
Damn, girl.
That was a workout.
Okay, second biggest.
You know, normally,
I like to sleep in,
But part of me is...
an early riser.
Wow. This should not
have happened... Again.
Not that it wasn't nice.
You have small
but surprisingly powerful hands
And almost no beard.
It's like you were created
in a lab for a woman's pleasure.
The thing about cole is that--
No, no.
No third person.
Let's begin
with some "q" and "a."
You, seat filler,
Tell me the thickest layers in the walls of veins.
Uh...
Thank you for getting us off
to that rousing start.
Who's next? Ah.
Pinup girl
avoiding eye contact?
Ugly don cheadle?
What about you, legacy?
Got anything?
Well, uh, you see...
No, curiously, I don't see.
when dr. Cox gets like this,
It feels a lot like second grade gym class.
all right, you hairless babies.
Show some sack and pick up a ball.
Who wants it? You? Huh?
You? You! You're out!
watch out!Watch out?
You!
Not in the face!
Sure, in the face!
Take it!
Anybody else?
Oh, thank you, muffin.
No!
The thickest layers
of the walls of the veins
Are the tunica externa.
Correct. Everyone else,
Stare into my eyes
so I can clock the very instant
When you first realized that
you're not going to make it.
Here we go.
Thank you. That was lovely.
Hey, congrats, bro.
You really brought it today.
Oh, but who's that
nippin' at your heels?
uh-oh. It's c-dog.
I'm sorry. I don't speak hipster gibberish.
Oh, I'm talking about this epic
battle you and I are locked in
For the number one spot.
Okay, I'm assuming you like to be called "dude."
Love it.
Dude, I don't like the spotlight.
I don't like
the extra attention.
I tried med school before,
and I crashed and burned, okay?
Oh, playing it humble. Nice angle.
But careful walking on the tracks
'cause there's
a coal train a-comin'.
choo-choo!
Sync by honeybunny/ReHelen
www.addic7ed.com
I'm always psyched
When dr. D. Asks me
to swing by for office hours.
So tell me,
how's school going?
Well, my hair is
falling out in clumps,
But that's not necessarily
stress. Um, I am get older.
That's what I wanted to
talk to you about, lucy.
You need to be prepared
for when I leave.
damn it! Why bring her
to the learning tree
If you're not gonna use it
in your inspiring talk?
My--my point is,
while I'm here, I'm yours,
But you also need to...
Branch out. nailed it!
I don't know if I can
get through med school alone.
Don't worry.
Before I, uh, leaf...you're on fire.
I'll make sure
that you have a mentor
You're as close to as I am to mine.
Speak of the devil!
Hey, perry, you wanna hang out later?
Sure. And if we can't find any more climbing trees,
We'll just head down to the old
swimmin' hole and skip stones
Until the fireflies tell us it's suppertime.
I assume that's a dis of some sort.
Ahh!
Oh, snap!
That hurt to watch.
Can't wait to see that
on the surveillance tape.
That's right.
We have cameras everywhere.
We're watching you.
Drive.
Copy that.
I need a new mentor--
Someone strong and not afraid
to express emotions.
Maybe a woman.
Give me my chips, you dirty bitch!
Or her.
Help me shake this machine.
Dr. Mahoney,
I was wondering if it would
be possible for me to, uh,
Shadow you in the hospital.
This is not over,
you filthy whore!
Shadow me? Sure.
No, wait.
I forgot you totally annoy me.
Is there any way you could
Instantly change your entire personality?
I guess I could try.
Even the way you said that
was irritating.
Look, I'm not
the mentoring type, okay?
Go ask turk.
I did, but he said, and I'm quoting now,
"I already have dr. Bradley
all up in my business."
Dr. Turk, thanks so much for
taking me under your wing.
It's such a privilege, I feel
like I should be paying you,
So...No,
I don't want your money.
Okay,tearing it up, sir.
No, don't--don't tear up your money.
My bad, sir. Taping it up.
Tom, you're ten years older than me
And you have a wife and kid.
Please, have some dignity.
Too late, sir.
I wish dr. Cox
had some time for me,
But I get it.
He's a busy man--
A very busy... Man?
Cheers.
"sy-hwa"?
it says, "why?"!
Cox and I were drinking beer
and watching sports--
Two things you hate.
First of all, turk, I've learned to pretend I enjoy beer.
And secondly, I love sports.
The opening ceremonies
for the winter olympics
Is not a sport,and you cried during it.
Oh, you want to talk about crying?
Let's talk about the end of "rudy."
hold on!
He got on the field at the end
of the movie with his dad in--
You know what? No. No, we're not going there.
Excuse me, dr. Dorian.
Sorry I missed your class. Can I get the notes?
No. Actually, drew, you can't.
And I'm gonna e-mail
the whole class and ask them
Not to share their notes
with you.
Then tomorrow,we'll have a quiz on it.
That seems excessive, but okay.
What was the lecture on?
I don't remember, drew.
It was 20 minutes ago.
What are you doing?
I know, I know.
It's just that cox is
draping himself over that kid
Like a cheap hussy, and then
I have to find you and perry
Canoodling in that sports-themed
tavern pretending you like beer.
Well, we're not pretending.
We actually like beer.
Oh, stop it, turk.
It's me.
I just feel like
I'm being replaced.
That'll never happen.Do you wanna know why?
Tell me this instant.
Because you're
john damn dorian.
You're right.
I am john damn dorian.
You john-damn right, you are!
Now gimme a chest bump.
Yeah, but don't flex 'cause
it'll knock the wind out of me.
see? Can't breathe.
I'm sorry, white bread.
I'm not currently looking for
A protégé/suck-up.
dr. Mahoney,
I am not sucking up.
If I were sucking up,
I would tell you
how much I like your shoes.
Which I do, by the way.
They're mannish, yet flirty,
Like, "hey, boys.
Come watch me build a deck."
Look, I just really, really want to shadow you. Please?
Gurney.
What?  oh!
Uh, I think I'm on your tube.
that's how I eat.
Sorry!
Uh, dr. Mahoney,
if you do let me shadow you--
For the last time, no.
How you feeling today?
Well, I have my up days and down days.
Some weeks I have more
up days than down days.
Like last week, I had
four up days, one down day.
I was like, "whoo-hoo!
Let's have a party!"
But today I think I could really use a hug.
Lucy!
I changed my mind.
You can start shadowing me
by hugging mrs. Maroney.
Okay, dr. Mahoney.
Wait a second...
Maroney, mahoney-- that is so funny!
Yeah,
not as I understand funny.
Take mrs. Maroney down
for her m.R.I.
Oh, can you keep an eye on my son?
Your what?
Excuse me.
Hey, watch a kid for me?
No, I'm afraid of kids.
He's 12.
I got shot by a 12-year-old
at a petting zoo.
Besides, I gotta change this
shirt. The neck's choking me.
we get it, drew.
You got a very muscular neck.
All right, team. This should be
fairly straightforward.
Scalpel.
Drew's rubbing this
t-shirt thing in my face.
J.D., what the hell? I'm in surgery.
It's not even the right color for him.
He's clearly an autumn.
You've lost it.
Dr. Turk is right.
You should be asleep.
She should be asleep!
That's my fault, sir.
If anyone gets sued for this,
it's gonna be me.
Look, you gotta remember,
you're john damn dorian.
So think about it.
What would john damn dorian do?
W.W.J.D.D.D.D.?
Was that too many d's?
Why are you awake?!
this thing is so complicated.
You're not that petty kid
anymore. Just let it go.
I could do that, or...
Okay, a patient has hypotension,
hyperpigmentation of skin
And hyponatremia. What
diagnostic test should we run?
Ooh! I know! I know!
Anyone but the board-certified doctor?
Good call. I'll observe.
We do an a.C.T.H.
Stimulation test to diagnose--
Addison's disease!
It's addison's disease!
I was gonna say that.
Well, we'll never know, will we, drew?
Walking tall, dorian.
Walking tall.
feeling tall, perry.
Okay, I'll admit it.
Kids are good for something.
I can get you the mints,
But if you want these chips,
I might dislocate my shoulder.
Chips
Fine. Ah, got 'em.
Nicely done.
with my mom
in the hospital all the time,
I just figured out how to do this.
Yeah, I never knew my mom.
You gonna cry about it?
No. Here you go.
Oh!
Mm, you gonna cry about it?
Excluding number one here,
today's assignment
Is for everyone
to drop out of medical school.
Your parents' money
would be better stuffed into
Garbage bags, packed io
a rocket and shot into the sun.
oh, my. This gentleman appears
to be coding. What a delight.
Who would like tdive in?
I'm on this.
Where the hell did you get a scalpel?
Uh, present from my unc.
Handle's made from elephant
tusk. It's mad illegal, yo.
Step off. Number one, jump in.
Excuse me?
do you know why
I call him number one?
It's because he is roger
and ready to do this stuff.
Drew, run the code. What's first?
I don't know.
I'm standing right here next
to you. Let's take his pulse.
Now tell me which nurse should
go get the crash cart?
Huh?
He who hesitates is lost.
Take a breath.
Make a decision.
Uh, her.
Tell her to do something.
Go get the crash cart.
Now we're cookin'.
Around here, you can be
thrown into the mix
At a moment's notice.
I'll be right back.
Um, I've got the results
of ryan's mom's m.R.I.
What's it say?
That she's dying.
Bring him back to her room.
You just have to hope
you're up to the task at hand.
You're doing really great.
Is this guy dying?
Probably.
But he's been circling the drain
for months, so it's no biggie.
Now he's unresponsive to c.P.R., what's next?
I don't know!
Sure you do. Think.
I don't!
Come on, drew, tell me.
This is insane! I'm not ready for this!
of course,
if you let someone down...
Newbie!
A little help here, please.
Thank you.
It can turn into
someone else's moment to shine.
there's no better way
to celebrate saving a life
Than pretending to like beer.
Ohh, sticky.
Yep, I'm sitting
between my best bud
And my abusive father figure,
watching my new favorite thing.
Footballing!
They're staring.
Quick, talk like a jock!
Sports grass is so lovely.
Here I thought we weren't
bringing our wives this evening.
Speaking of ich,
Carla can't make it to
the owlcats game this Friday.
We have an extra ticket.
I'm in! I'm in!
I gotta see this sports grass in person.
Excuse me, dr. Cox.
I don't mean to interrupt,
but, uh, I have to apologize.
I've made a lot of bad choices
in le. Quick example--
I accidentally, uh, set a shrimp
boat on fire once.
It was a long story.
Another time.
But, um, today was
one of those bad choices,
And if I had
the power to go back in time--
You know, drew, we all wish
we had superpowers, okay?
Do you know what the perfect
superhero power would be?
candy hands!
For me, it would be
the ability to get back
All the time I wasted on people
who eventually let me down.
Awesome.
Dude, think about it--
candy hands.
Everything you touch
turns to candy.
Whoop! Candy lamp.
Candy perry!
No candy perry.
I don't know
How I'll ever be ready
to give people news like that.
You all right?
I'm super.
Goway.
Hey.
I know the next couple months
are really gonna suck.
If I had any questions,
could I, like, call you?
Yeah, I dot know, ryan.
Well... Okay, cool.
Why is the college mascot
an owlcat?
I don't even know what an owlcat is.
I like to think it's what happens
When an owl and a cat
fall in love.
Hey, there's my kiss-ass
with some pizza.
I'll be back
with a couple of slices.
Dr. Dorian. Do you have a second?
No.
I mean, sure.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Ok at! Whoo-hoo!
Look at that right there.
Look.
Appreciate you.
Oh!
Dr. Mahoney.
Hey, I need to talk.
Oh, my god.
Were you raised by horses?
No.
I wish.
I was just studying.
What's up, shorty?
And fornicating.
Cole, get back under
the horse blanket, please.
I was thinking that maybe the three of us--
cole! Horse blanket.
Fine.
Maybe we should just go outside.
Great idea.
You want me to help ryan
through his mom's death?
It'll only be
a few months, a year, tops.
Come on. It'll be fun.
It'll be like having a really sad pen pal.
What are you doing? You should help him.
Listen up, seabiscuit.
Th isn't my wheelhouse, okay?
It's taken me a long time
to get to a point
That I can be there
emotionally for a patient.
You know how I do it?
Every second that they're here,
I remind myself that
once they leave this hospital,
Either on their own
or in a box,
They're no longer
my problem anymore.
Out the door,
out of my head.
It's the only way it works
for me.
I still think you should do it,
but I'll talk to ryan.
Good.
And another thing--
I do love horses.
They are
god's most majestic creatures.
If they could talk,
they would be so very wise.
I've been in a pretty deep hole
the past couple years--
A lot of
self-destructive stuff.
Honestly, the only thing
I've burnt more than
shrimp boats is bridges.
I need to change that.
What do you want from me?
I understand you and dr. Cox
have a special relationship.
He's kinda like my dad.
Well, I was hoping you could
help me fix this with him.
You know, dr-- It's drew, right?
Yeah.
Drew, I've known perry cox
a very long me,
And once he's made up his mind
about someone,
He's never gonna change it.
I wish I could help.
That's awesome.
You're not gonna
help him out, huh?
Kinda sucks. I thought you
wanted to be a good teacher.
During the day,
I'm a good teacher,
But right now
I'm ready for a little
"magnum p.I." crustache.
I'm gonna be magnum p.I.,
And you're gonna be
black higgins.
You should talk to dr. Cox.
I'm questioning
a lot of things today--
Like my choice in men...
hey, babe, check it out.
I'm dr. Wolverine.
And my choice in mentors.
I really don't want to do
Dr. Mahoney's
dirty work for her.
I got this.
Oh, I love that game.
If you want
to beat the level,
You gotta take that sniper out
in the church.
I know.
Hey, I know you guys
are going home today...
So I wanted to give you
My cell phone number
In case you
still want to talk ever.
Whatever.
Give me that.
You're horrible.
I'll get the sniper.
What the hell are you wearing?
I'm showing my owlcat spirit.
If it's not enough, I have
wings and talons in the car.
Is that glitter? Hell, no!
But it came with the makeup kit.
I don't have to use it. Today...
Oh, for the love of god,
francine!
I gotta go get
the tickets at will-call.
Please don't let him
put the glitter on.
I've never heard that sentence
uttered about another man.
Perry, uh, I want to talk to you
about drew for a second.
I-I really think you're
making a mistake with him.
Don't you have some gay dance
rehearsal you got to attend?
He has potential, and you know it.
He's too old.
He's experienced.
He quit.
But he came back.
What exactly
do you want from me?
I want you to realize
you set the bar too high.
The attention
that you're giving to drew--
I would've killed for that
eight years ago.
But you weren't ready yet.
I had to break you down.
I tamed you... Like a bull.
Excuse me, are we approaching
a point here, dorian?
Perry, you finally found
someone to believe in.
Don't ruin it by being you.
I think I just
mentored my mentor,
But maybe
that's how it always is.
Our roles
are always switching.
Sometimes you're a student,
And sometimes you're a teacher.
Lucy, you still wantto shadow me?
More than horses love rainbows!
Let's go. Too close.
And if you're smart enough,
everyone can learn something.
One more question,
and all you little assassins
Can get out of here.
Someone please tell me
Where the foramen ovale
in the fetal heart is located?
Drew, save us, please.
Uh, the interatrial septum.
Yes. Nicely done.
I'll expect you to be
wearing your shirt tomorrow.
Everyone leave now.
But whatever you do, don't wait
for that pat on the back.
Because, believe me,
it will never, ever--
Oh, come on!
Oh, I love you, sports grass.
It is pretty soft.
Pretty soft?
It's like lying on a cloud.
Why did they have to ruin you
By painting all
these numbers and lines?
Hey, captain. Looks like
we got some more turf freaks.
Found some what?
check this out.
That is disgusting.
Mm-hmm!
Unh-unh.
Warm up the golf cart and get the taser.
The mexican one?
El conquistador.
Let's do it.
Sync by honeybonny/ReHelen
www.addic7ed.com