- Third drowning this year.
- Anyone see it happen?
- Is that her little girl?
- Get her away from here.
- Don't let her see her mom like this.
- Mommy!
Are you Prue?
Your gram sent me to find you.
Why don't you come
back inside with me, okay?
Mommy!
- Hello?
- Prue? Are you still on the road?
Yeah, traffic's insane.
Some guy called from Buckland's
and thought you'd be back
from the estate sale already.
I was just calling to make sure
you and my car were okay.
- Yeah. We're fine.
- Oh, that's... That's probably Dan.
You know, he does live,
like, 20 feet away.
I mean, you guys could get
walkie-talkies, two cans, a string.
Point taken, Mom.
All right, look, go talk to your boy.
I'll see you later.
Help me!
Help!
No! It's too late.
It's already taken him.
Just call 911!
Yeah.
- Pouring.
- Chewing.
Can't believe you eat that stuff.
You guys are killing me
with cuteness over here.
Don't you have somewhere to be?
Somewhere very far away?
What do you say tomorrow,
when Jenny's at school,
- we have breakfast for real?
- I'll take what I can get.
Nausea?
What are you doing home? You said
you were heading to the office.
Yeah, things changed.
- Dan, I have to call you back, okay?
- Okay.
Okay, I saw something...
...or someone...
...drown. And it was
anything but natural.
On the freeway?
- No, up at the lake.
- Oh, wait a minute.
The lake as in the lake?
Where Mom was killed?
You said you were stuck in traffic.
Yeah, I was, after the lake.
I just go there sometimes to think.
You never told us that.
Because I didn't wanna make
a big deal out of it.
Anyway, this isn't about Mom,
all right?
I saw someone get pulled under.
I tried to help him,
but this man stopped me and said,
"It's already taken him."
Do you think he knows
what happened?
Could. Which means
I need to get to Buckland's
to drop stuff off
and get back up to that lake.
Wait a minute, Prue,
aren't you kind of missing the point?
How can you think
whatever you saw
didn't have something to do
with how Mom died?
Look, we need to stop
worrying about the past
and start dealing with the present.
They're reopening camp.
I thought they closed it
the summer that Mom...
Exactly. And no one has been
allowed in the lake since.
And if there's something in it killing,
then the last thing we need
is a lake full of kids.
Well, how do we find the guy
that stopped you?
What about the woman who used
to run the camp? Mrs Johnson?
If she's still up there,
she probably knows who he is.
She's still there, same cabin.
So I guess you go
up there to think a lot.
I'll meet you guys up at the lake.
I should be there in an hour.
Do you really think the thing she saw
has nothing to do with how Mom died?
- Nope. You?
- Not a chance.
- What are you doing here?
- Pondering the possibilities.
- Of?
- Redecoration.
Where's your flair in this place,
the panache?
- The Prue?
- Well,
I don't really think that's
any of your business, Jack.
Now, if you don't mind,
I have a lot of work to do,
so perhaps you could go annoy
somebody down the hall.
Actually, already did.
Signed the dotted line,
they sent me to my office.
- Your office?
- Well, it's only temporary, of course,
until mine is ready.
Wait, you think
that you're working here?
Well, you said we couldn't date
and work together,
so since you won't date me,
one out of the two will have to do.
And you consider that
proper work attire.
Hey, if you can get away
with wearing that,
I can certainly get away
with wearing this.
No wonder nobody gets any work
done around here. You look:
Flattery will get you nowhere.
Well, got me this job.
Okay, look, I have to go take care
of some personal things.
So until I get back, let's just employ
a hands-off policy, meaning,
don't touch anything.
Tell you what. Take your time. I'll sit
back here and make myself comfy.
It's really nice form, but the dismount
could use a little work.
Meant to do that.
Well, I'm finding it hard to believe
enough time's gone by
for you to have grown up
so much. Here.
Oh, look at little Prue.
- Nice pigtails, Piper.
- Not fair.
No, what's not fair is that I never
got to go to camp with you guys.
We heard you were thinking
of opening up the camp again.
Was. I thought it was over,
and then today, another drowning.
I can't ask the campers
to go swimming in the lake when...
We were wondering if you might
help us with something.
Prue was up here the other day,
and she mentioned a man.
Older, a bit off.
I think the word
that she used was "crazy."
We were wondering
if you might know who he is.
Oh, Sam. Only one it could be.
Man's not wired together properly.
He showed up
when the drownings started.
And then just stayed here.
No friends, no life of his own.
You know, somebody like that, you
have to wonder what he's capable of.
Mrs J., you remember my sister Prue?
Oh, Prue. Of course I do.
How good to see you.
Wow, you're looking more and more
like your mother every day.
Actually, it's Piper
who resembles her the most.
People see a little of her
in each of us, I think.
Of course. Well, will you come
see me again?
The old broad gets lonely up here.
- I love to see my campers.
- Sure.
- Bye-bye.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
She's not opening the camp, Prue.
Really? So that means
it's just between us
and whatever's hiding in that lake.
- Any word on the crazy guy?
- His name is Sam, and he lives right...
- Hello. This is Prue.
- Hey. How's my favourite auctionette?
- Fine. How's my favourite auction ass?
- Oh, nice one.
Hey, listen, I just wanted to let you
know that since you're not here,
I'm gonna take your 12:00 lunch
with Mr Fujimoto.
No. No, no, no, wait.
- Mr Fujimoto is very particular.
- Prue, would you relax?
I will take great care of your client,
okay? Later.
I just cannot figure out
what this guy's deal is.
That's funny, we were just gonna
ask you the same thing.
Excuse me?
Every time someone compares you
to Mom, you flinch.
- It's a compliment, not a curse.
- Is it?
Every single day, I feel like I'm
becoming more and more like her,
and every day, it terrifies me.
- Prue...
- I mean, don't you guys see it?
Look at what happened to her and
then look at what's happening to me.
No successful relationship with guys,
being responsible for a family
and now, because of this
being-charmed thing,
the very real possibility of dying young.
It's like history is repeating itself.
- Prue, that's all just...
- Coincidence?
I thought that we had figured out that
nothing is a coincidence in our lives.
Like me being here
when that thing attacked.
It's like I was meant to be here.
Well, you're not exactly
meant to be here
when you're here every week.
All right, look, I just wanna
find this Sam guy,
see what he knows about the demon,
vanquish it and get on with our lives.
Sam?
Be very, very quiet.
We're hunting demons.
I guess he's not home.
- Oh, my.
- What?
- What is it?
- Mom.
What is he doing
with a picture of her?
- Who is this guy?
- Or what?
Okay, he has articles
on every single drowning at the lake.
"New York teacher of the year,
Sam Wilder."
In 1872?
Okay, so this guy is
either 127 years old or...
A demon.
Named Sam? A demon
named Sam? I mean,
can't it just be
his grandfather's certificate?
After all, he did save me.
What are these? I found...
Leo? Hi. What are doing here?
We gotta get out of here.
Sam could be back any minute.
- Wait, you know Sam?
- Come on. We gotta...
We are not going anywhere until you
tell us what you know. Who is Sam?
Sam was...
...your mom's whitelighter.
Sam was Mom's whitelighter?
Emphasis on "was."
When your mom died,
Sam clipped his wings.
He's mortal now, but once,
yeah, he was...
He was a whitelighter.
He looked after your mother.
Then he lost our mom.
To the same demon
you're fighting now.
And you knew? This whole time,
he's been living up here while...?
I couldn't tell you.
And what would it change?
You know, it would only distract you.
Maybe even gotten you killed.
You guys were gonna have to face
this thing sooner or later.
I'm here to make sure that you do it
with a clear head.
Emotions will get the best of you
if you let them.
- Well, can you really blame us?
- Leo, he let our mother die.
Leo's right, this isn't about Mom.
And it's not about Sam,
for that matter.
It's about a demon who's waiting
till tomorrow for brunch to be served.
Mrs J. Is not opening the camp.
That doesn't end it, it just stalls it.
You guys are behind
and need to catch up.
Book of Shadows, get
a working knowledge of this demon
before you face him.
Said like an unfeeling professional.
This is personal for us, Leo.
Leo doesn't do personal anymore,
he just does his job.
Now that I've done it,
guess there's no other reason
for me to hang around.
Okay, he's gone.
Now you can explain.
- Explain what?
- Why you're acting like all of this
doesn't faze you, Prue.
We are talking about
how our mother was killed.
Help! Oh, please, somebody!
Help me!
Is that Mrs Johnson?
Please help me!
Please help!
Help me, please. Help!
Your hand! Give me your hand!
Prue, what are you doing?
We need you!
Mommy!
Get off the dock! It's her!
It's taken her over!
- Oh, my...
- God!
Damn it, get off the dock now!
Why didn't you listen to me?
I told you to stay away from the lake.
It only kills in the water.
Why didn't you listen to me?
Nobody ever listens!
We know who you are.
You shouldn't listen
to people in town.
They'll just tell you I'm crazy.
But I'm not.
We know you worked
with our mother.
And lost her.
I knew you'd come. I knew it.
And then when I saw you...
It's in your eyes. Your mother.
You have no right talking about her.
You lost that right when you lost her.
Why are we dealing with him?
Because we need to know
what he knows.
You have to tell us
about the demon.
No. No, you can't fight this thing.
It's made of water, but it has a...
It thinks.
You never know where it's gonna be,
who it's gonna be.
Sometimes it takes over its victims'
bodies to lure you to the water.
But sometimes it doesn't.
Leave now, please.
Forget you ever came here.
Forget you ever knew.
How can we do that?
I mean, it's out there killing.
We can't just walk away.
You really wanna know
what I know?
I know you're not strong enough
or well-versed enough in your powers
to take this thing on.
I know that you have the same power
as your mother, the power to freeze.
And you know what happened
when she tried to used it.
And I know you'll let your emotions
get in the way.
You'll lose focus, and you'll lose
your life. That's what I know.
Well, you obviously don't know us
that well, because we're not leaving.
Strong, wilful. Just like Patty.
I'm nothing like my mother.
But you're here.
- Just like she was.
- But we'll beat it.
Now you have one choice.
You can either get onboard
or get the hell out of the way.
The power of three. Okay, okay.
If you're gonna do this, then you're
gonna need me to help you.
All right, enough of this.
How do we kill it?
You don't.
Now, you're gonna go home,
and you're gonna go directly to bed.
And when you wake up tomorrow, you
will not remember coming to the lake
or discovering the demon
or meeting me.
Can't let it happen again.
I fell asleep, woke up,
and suddenly it's Thursday.
I don't feel so good.
- What is that?
- I don't know. I itch everywhere.
That looks like the time
Prue got poison ivy.
But Prue got poison ivy
at camp, and...
You don't look hungry.
You look confused.
And you're contagious.
- Dan, what are you doing...?
- Breakfast.
Me, you, here.
Remember?
Everything's a little hazy
this morning.
Well, is there anything I can do?
You could hold that thought.
- What are you doing here?
- What are you doing here? I live here.
What are you, checking up on me
and Dan? We talked about this.
It has nothing to do with him.
Why aren't you up at the lake?
What lake?
Look, nobody shut down the camp,
so the kids are on their way there now.
- He did it, didn't he?
- Did what?
Who did what? Who is he?
Sam used a powder,
sort of like a supernatural mickey.
- Must have got it from...
- Mom.
Good. It's fading. Now, concentrate.
It's kind of like
remembering a dream.
Okay, the lake, the kids,
the demon, Sam.
Sam? Why would he do this to us?
To keep history from repeating itself.
Oh, just a sec. You guys, scoot.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Dan, I know we were
supposed to do this this morning,
- but I'm really not feeling up to it.
- Well, I'll cook while you scratch.
I can't. There's just some stuff,
family stuff, going on.
Say no more.
I completely understand.
- I'd kiss you, but...
- But you're contagious. Tomorrow.
I'm just glad you can tell me things.
Well, I feel like
I can tell you anything.
- Except that there's a demon.
- And that you're a witch.
- Sorry, that was...
- The truth.
We should go get dressed.
The only place that you are going,
contagious girl,
- Why are you hitting me?
- Is back to bed.
- But...
- But nothing.
You just look in that Book of Shadows
for this thing's Achilles heel.
- But what if there isn't one?
- Then we're screwed.
Okay. How are we doing
in the plan department?
- I think I just got one.
- I love when you take charge.
Okay, you know that powder
that Sam used on us?
Maybe we should use it on the kids,
make them temporarily forget
that they wanna go in the water.
That will keep them safe until we figure
out a way to dehydrate this bastard.
- Perfect.
- Right.
- Prepubescent demon food.
- Okay, go.
Keep them out of the water.
Tell them anything. I'll deal with Sam.
I knew I should have given you
a stronger dose.
Not only did you put my sisters
and me in danger,
but you risked innocents' lives.
How could you?
I did what I had to
to protect you and your sisters.
Not that.
This.
All these years.
How could you just sit here
and watch them die?
People that you were meant
to protect.
Well, in case you didn't get the memo,
I'm not one of the good guys anymore.
Part of you is.
Part of you always will be.
I've done nothing but make your life
difficult. What makes you so sure?
Because you saved me.
You still have
whitelighter instincts, Sam.
You may have clipped your wings,
but this still gets you. It matters.
What matters most
was taken from me 20 years ago.
Then we have something in common.
You think I chose to stay here,
to watch?
That I get my kicks this way?
- I've been waiting for you.
- Why?
I knew you'd come.
And I had to be here to stop you.
To save you.
Because you couldn't save Mom?
Sam, I need the powder.
And then I'm gonna need
for you to tell me
how Mom was gonna
vanquish this thing.
If you're gonna defeat
your demons, Sam,
then you're gonna have to help us
defeat the one out there.
We need your help.
I'll try and face mine.
Question is, can you face yours?
Can't find anything.
Then you don't
have to stay with me.
Looks of sympathy are not
part of your job description.
I know.
And why didn't
your healing touch work?
I mean, you can save a life,
but you can't cure poison ivy?
It's not really up to me.
I can only heal when they allow me to,
when I'm meant to.
Well, why wouldn't you
be meant to help me?
Why wouldn't I be meant
to help my sisters?
There's always a reason.
Maybe you're meant to be here.
"Dear Sam..."
- Leo.
- What is it?
Letters that my mom wrote to Sam.
I must have forgotten about them
because of the powder.
"Dear Sam, where are you?
It's been two weeks since you
were last here, and I wonder,
are you all right? Do they have you
off guiding someone?
And I wonder when they will send you
back to San Francisco, to me."
Is this a...?
A love letter?
Okay. How about Red Rover?
All right, all right, how about
Thumbs Up, Seven Up?
Okay.
Lanyards.
This sucks.
We wanna go swimming.
Yeah!
Oh, you know, I could have done that.
- Did you get the powder?
- Oh, I got that and more.
- You didn't have to bring him.
- Yes, I did.
Okay, you go deal with that,
- I'll take care of this.
- Okay.
- Piper?
- Piper? I hardly know her.
Jack. Okay, well, I'm sort of
in the middle of something.
Yadda yadda yadda. Look,
I'm gonna conference Mr Fujimoto
about the carousel horse, okay?
Hold on.
- No, no, no, wait...
- Hello?
Mr Fujimoto, hi.
Miss Halliwell, have you seen it?
No, I'm looking at the object
- right now.
- How is it?
Well, yeah, you can tell
by the jewelled choker
that it's an original carousel horse
from the 1939 world fair
in New York City, and...
And, Mr Fujimoto,
there's another thing
you should probably know
about the piece.
This is a great piece,
and I really think you want to have
the first chance at it.
Okay, good. Good. Well, I'll have
the paperwork sent over today.
- Sounds like a good idea.
- All right. Bye, now.
So who are you crediting
as the sales agent, Jack?
Prue, do you not trust me?
Okay. Now, remember, kids,
on your way to bed, water bad.
Land good. Water bad. Land good.
"Sam, yes, you were clear.
My eyes are open to the difficulties,
the risks, but my answer is the same
as it was when you were
still here with me.
No one understands me
the way you do. No one can."
"What I wouldn't do for
what other people consider ordinary.
Conversation that gets finished,
a night spent uninterrupted,
a night with you."
It's like I could have written these.
I wish you had.
What would it have changed?
Looks like this one's
about our water demon.
"You can't be with me up at the lake.
This demon is too strong,
and I can't risk losing you,
not for myself
or the others you protect.
They must, as always, come first.
You know I'd never face this demon
if I didn't think
I'd be home in time for dinner
to see my girls,
to see you."
She never came home.
When did this happen?
Where was Dad?
Your sisters need to know
about Sam and your mom, Piper.
And if this demon is as strong
as she thought,
then they're going to need me. But
how can we get up there in time to...?
Can you? I mean,
is it breaking the rules?
What rules haven't we already broken?
I'll have to hold you.
It's time, Sam. We need to know.
How was Mom gonna vanquish it?
I don't know.
I failed, I lost her. Isn't that enough?
Whoa, that felt really...
All right, laying down now.
What are you guys doing here?
- He loved her.
- What?
Who loved who?
What is she talking about?
Sam.
Found the letters, Sam.
Patty and I...
Fell in love.
In her letter, she told you to stay away,
not to go to the lake.
But I did.
I wouldn't have for anyone else.
If I had just followed the rules,
not fallen in love,
I never would have been there,
I never would have distracted her,
and she never would have died.
You loved her,
and you blame yourself.
Well, don't you blame me?
Every day, I wake up,
and for just a second,
just a second, I think
maybe it didn't happen, maybe...
Yes, I blame myself.
We have to see past our emotions
to deal with this, Sam. So do you.
Even so, it doesn't change
the fact that I...
I didn't see what happened.
- I tried to warn her, and she froze me.
- Why?
Because she was
trying to protect him.
Protecting was
supposed to be my job.
I couldn't help her,
I don't know how I can help you.
I didn't see what happened.
I know somebody
who can see anything.
No. Wait a minute.
You tiptoe around the subject of Mom,
you deny looking like her.
You can't even go
to the end of that dock,
because you're afraid
to walk in her footsteps.
And now you want me
to relive her last moment?
- How is that fair?
- It's not.
None of this is,
Mom's death, Sam's guilt.
But I'm asking you to help me end it.
Hey, look out! Look out!
Did you see her?
Lt...
It entered her.
It drowned her from the inside.
Phoebe, in your vision,
what was Mom doing?
She was using something
on the dock, some...
- A wire?
- A power cable?
Makes sense. Electricity is the only
thing that separates water particles.
So...
...what do we do differently?
Maybe nothing. Sam,
would Mom's plan have worked
- if she had finished it?
- Absolutely.
But you said her power, my power,
it doesn't work against this demon.
So that's it.
We use Mom's plan
with one difference.
The witch at the end of the dock
is not gonna be the one
with the power to freeze.
It's gonna be me.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
- You don't have to do this.
- Yes, I do.
Just focus on the demon.
That's what this is about.
Right.
I forgot how good this feels.
Really?
How's it feel to be mortal?
Why would you wanna know?
Let's go face our demons.
Okay, you in the water...
...I know that you've been
waiting for this...
...for me.
Well, here I am,
so come and get me.
You took what mattered most to me.
And as long as I live,
you will never kill again.
- Look out!
- Prue, behind you!
Piper, wait!
No!
Not her! Take me!
Stay back!
Now!
No. Sam.
It's gone, it's gone.
Leo, do something.
What? Why isn't
anything happening?
Because it's not meant to.
- It's okay. It's time to go.
- No.
I did what I've been waiting to do.
I kept it from happening.
History won't repeat itself.
- But you're going.
- I'm gonna see Patty again.
Don't lose her.
Patty?
Say hi for me. For us.
Jack.
I have something to say, okay?
I have worked at Buckland's
for a year and a half.
And in that time, I've survived
takeovers, near-bankruptcy
and superiors from hell
who've tried to kill me.
So whatever it is
that you're planning to do
or have already done,
nothing, and I mean nothing,
will surprise me.
I just need you to sign this.
It's the confirmation sheet
on the Fujimoto sale.
You list me as the sales agent.
Yeah, well, it was your deal,
wasn't it?
You covered for me. I'm surprised.
So...
...what do you say, as a thank you...
...I take you to dinner?
But wouldn't that be breaking
one of Prue Halliwell's
rules of etiquette?
I've decided that even though
mixing business with pleasure
can have its very
nasty consequences...
...it can also bear
some fruitful rewards.
So...
...what's it gonna be?
Nasty or fruitful?
Well, that depends on
how you do at dinner.
At least fighting this demon
came with a consolation prize.
I mean, it didn't bring Mom back,
but these brought her closer.
It's a good idea, Pheebs,
making a journal out of Mom's letters.
Yeah, it's not as good
as the real thing, though.
Nothing is.
Tea. Want some tea?
I'm gonna go get some.
Sure.
I don't wanna interrupt.
I think I can steep and talk
at the same time. Do you want any?
It's just this...
This whole situation, you know?
Sam, your mom,
those letters.
He loved her.
Like...
Like I love you.
Leo, we've been through this before.
We both know how we feel, but there...
There are things...
...people involved now.
Can you tell Dan the truth, Piper?
That's between him and me.
You and I have a job to do.
And I thought we agreed
to try and put that first.
So did Sam and your mom.
Look at the outcome.
You're leaving, aren't you?
For good this time.
I don't know. But I do know
we have to stop
working together, because...
...I can't stop loving you.
Which means I can't do my job.
And I can't do mine.
I don't know how to say goodbye.
Don't.
Dan, what are you doing
at the back door?
Well, when I knock
on the front door,
I just never seem to make it
through the threshold.
You hungry?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm just...
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
I mean, you can tell me.
I know. I'm just not very hungry.
Come on.
Give it a try.
Okay, I'll give it a try.