- Oh, I am so glad to see you.
- Is that because I can work tonight?
Or is it because I am now
Phoebe Halliwell, college student?
Okay, neat, thin slices, please.
Wait, you enrolled?
Phoebe, this is huge.
Hugest thing I've done
since I came back home.
I mean, aside
from vanquishing demons
and saving the world from evil,
of course.
Okay, so I signed up
for two general courses.
And seven electives.
Seven, Phoebe?
All right, so I'm a little confused.
I could use some advice.
What do you think I should take?
- Honey, are you okay?
- Yeah, it's just a little cough.
I bet Prue made you have soup
at lunch today
- after she heard that little cough.
- I had to cancel, actually.
Last night's paperwork took
a lot longer than I expected.
So I guess you missed
your massage today also?
A reporter from
the San Francisco Weekly called
and had a ton of questions
about the club.
Piper, you have got
to take care of yourself.
You've been feeling funky
since yesterday.
- It's probably just a bug.
- Even more reason for you
- not to push it.
- I'm fine. Besides, it's all paying off.
The club is finally doing well,
and we're making money.
Now, would you slice?
What kind of fruit is this, anyway?
Kiwano. It's from South America.
It's great for Mai Tais.
Just got them in yesterday, actually.
The bartender has a connection
at the docks.
- Wait, you smuggled it in?
- Oh, it's fruit, Phoebe, not drugs.
You know, just because we're witches
does not mean that you're invincible.
Okay, you need to start
taking care of yourself.
Thank you, doctor.
Hey, Dr. Phoebe Halliwell.
I like it.
It's late. Let's just get this done.
Well, it certainly appears
to be a Monet.
Has the same style
that he enjoyed in Paris
after the Exposition Universelle.
The same delicate,
powdery interpretations
combined with great vigour
and expressiveness.
"Great vigour"?
Randy little painter, was he?
The brushstrokes
around the smokestack
are somewhat unusual for Monet.
They seem almost individual,
although beautifully rendered.
Well, no complaints
about my view either.
Okay, you know what?
Is everything with you sexual?
No.
Okay, you've never
thought about me?
Jack, come on.
We don't have very much time
- to authenticate this painting.
- Not even just a little?
Okay, fine. Maybe just a little.
And I was good, wasn't I?
Come on, Prue, I'm not pushing this.
I just... I know where you stand.
I just wanna know where I stand.
With you.
- How are you two doing?
- Oh, we're fine.
Exactly where we should be
at the moment.
As long as it's authenticated
by the auction.
I've got eight buyers on the block
interested in that piece.
You don't have to worry
about us, Mr. Caldwell.
Good.
Do I have to worry about us?
Piper, you need to go home.
You're sick.
I think we're over
our occupancy limit.
I don't want the fire marshal
to shut us down.
Piper, you need to go home.
Phoebe, I'm fine! I'm just...
- Maybe you're right.
- Oh, my God!
Call 911! Piper. Piper!
Hey.
Prue?
You're awake.
- What happened?
- You don't remember?
I remember being in the club
and talking to Phoebe.
And then, I gotta admit,
it's a little fuzzy.
You collapsed,
someone called an ambulance.
Oh, that must have been great
for business.
So, what's wrong with me?
They don't really know. We're just
sort of waiting for blood-test results.
I'm sure it's nothing too exciting.
It's probably something trendy like
mono or Epstein-Barr.
Yeah, well, whatever it is, you're
gonna take the time to get better.
Now you sound like Phoebe.
Where is she, anyway?
Hi.
Nurse person?
Hi. Can you tell me
where Dr. Wallace is?
He said that my sister's test results
should be in by 8,
and it's 20 past 8 now.
- What's your sister's name?
- Piper, Piper Halliwell. Thank you.
Piper Halliwell.
Piper Halliwell's been transferred
to Dr. Williamson's care.
If you have a seat in the waiting area,
- I'll page him.
- What happened to Dr. Wallace?
I'm sure that Dr. Williamson will be
able to answer all of your questions.
Please, have a seat
in the waiting room.
Okay.
- Are you sick too?
- No, I'm not sick.
Then why do you look so sad?
My sister's here and they don't know
what's wrong with her.
The doctors don't know
what's wrong with me either.
Maybe your sister and I
have the same thing.
- What is your name?
- Nathan.
Well, hello, Nathan. I'm Phoebe.
And who is that?
Ninja doll. Found him
in the children's ward.
You know,
I don't think that's just any ninja doll.
If I know my ninja dolls,
I think that one's really
a magical wi...
- zard. Wizard.
- Really? How can you tell?
- Well, let me see him.
I've seen what his type can do.
He's got powers. He can move things
and freeze things.
And he could kick-box too.
And the really cool thing about him
is he could do all this to the demon...
To the bad guys inside your body
without anyone even knowing about it.
Really? He can freeze the bad guys
and move them?
And kick-box them too, don't
forget that. Right out of your body.
All you have to do is,
when you feel bad,
you close your eyes and just
picture him fighting them for you.
- Do you think you can do that?
- Yeah.
- Phoebe Halliwell?
- Yes.
- I'm Dr. Williamson.
- Hi.
- Bye, it was nice to meet you, Nathan.
- See you.
And who are they?
Medical interns. They'll be
viewing my work with your sister.
Because...?
Because they're studying
the same field that I did.
I'm an infectious-disease specialist.
Specialist? Wait!
Miss Halliwell?
I'm Dr. Williamson.
He's a specialist.
- Where's Dr. Wallace?
- I'll be keeping him posted.
How are you feeling?
Okay. A little hot, tired.
Have you been out
of the country recently?
Africa, South America, Caribbean?
I wish. No, I haven't even been out
of the city. Why?
Well, apparently you've contracted
a blood disease
rarely seen in the United States.
Oroya fever.
- How is that possible?
- Well, Oroya fever is transmitted
through the bite of a sand fly
which dies right after the bite.
Have you had anything imported,
brought into your home recently?
- No.
- But you have in the club.
What was the name
of that weird fruit?
- Kiwano.
- That's a possible carrier.
Sometimes the fly has been known
to live in the crate
long enough to make the trip, but
rarely survives the quarantine period.
I think...
...I have a bite on my shoulder.
- When did you get this?
- Yesterday.
Just after I opened the fruit.
Tell a nurse I need 10 cc's
of Penilovin.
- Right away.
- It's an antibiotic
most effective when administered
through an IV.
It should bring your fever down.
I gotta run some more tests.
I'll be back shortly.
Excuse me.
She's gonna be okay, right?
I mean, it's not life-threatening?
Well, I'll know better after
I run more tests. Excuse me.
I'll be okay.
Yeah, I mean, he didn't seem too
worried. Just prescribed antibiotics.
The tests are just to confirm
his diagnosis, I'm sure.
Yeah. Don't you agree, Phoebe?
I think we should call Leo.
- Why?
- Why not? He can heal you.
No. He's out of our lives. He's
not even our whitelighter anymore.
Besides, with Dan in my life...
- But if Leo knew you were sick?
- No, and that's final.
No demon or warlock
did this to me.
Just let the doctors do their magic.
All right. Well, I just wanted you
to get well soon.
I know. And I will.
Now, you two guys get out of here.
Prue, go to Buckland's.
Phoebe, go to wherever it is
you go to.
And somebody please call
Dan so he doesn't worry.
Okay. Bye. Love you.
I'll call you as soon as I can.
- Okay, go. Go.
- I love you.
Hey, have you had
a chance to look
at the thread-density results
on the Monet?
Yeah, and you were right.
There are some
unexplained thread markings
in the area around the station,
as well as the signature area.
- Have you told Caldwell?
- Not yet.
I was hoping to talk you
into going home first.
Prue, you're exhausted.
Yeah, I know. But I just prefer
to stay here, you know, keep busy.
I mean, how long
can tests take, anyway?
Hey. Piper is going to be fine.
I know, it's just that...
...after everything
that I've seen in my life,
and believe me,
I've seen a lot of weird stuff,
it takes a lot to scare me.
But this time, I'm really scared.
Hey.
You know, I'm really not good
at this saying-the-right-thing stuff.
You know what?
Why don't you go back
to the hospital,
and I'll stay here
and handle everything, okay?
- Hello?
- This is Nurse Stone
calling for Prue Halliwell.
Is she gonna be okay?
You know,
that's what's so frustrating.
They won't tell us anything.
Damn doctors.
Can I see her?
I mean, where is she?
San Francisco Memorial.
Hey.
Nothing's gonna happen to her, okay?
Piper's strong and healthy.
And she's a fighter.
You noticed too, have you?
- Hello?
- Yeah, Pheebs,
the hospital just called.
They need for us to get
down there right away.
Why, what happened?
Seventy-six-year-old man suffering
from blunt-force trauma to the head.
We suspect a subdural haematoma.
Call for an MRI.
Prue? What's going on?
I don't know. All they said
is that her condition is worse.
What is that supposed to mean?
It means we're not gonna leave
the door until we find out.
Dr. Williamson?
Unfortunately, your sister's
immune system
isn't as strong
as we thought it would be.
And the antibiotic's having
no effect on the disease.
So, what do we...?
What do you do now?
Well, there's nothing more
we can do.
Wait, what do you mean by that?
What are you saying?
Well, either Piper pulls out of
the coma on her own,
or I'm afraid your sister's
not going to survive.
- Okay, we can't let Piper die.
- No, we can't.
But, Prue, this isn't a demon
or a warlock that we're up against.
If there are spells in here
to vanquish demons,
there's gotta be a spell
to vanquish a lousy bug.
Okay. But even if there is a spell,
how do we get past
the personal-gain issue?
- The consequences.
- What consequences?
The power of three remains
unbroken, innocents are saved.
I don't really see
a downside to that.
- Do you?
- Prue, if good witches
could really vanquish diseases,
do you think there'd be
one sick person in the world?
- Look, we have to save Piper.
- I agree.
All I am saying is, before
we resort to the Book of Shadows...
...maybe we should call Leo.
- No. She told us not to.
So? Let her be pissed at us.
At least she'll be alive.
We don't even know
how to contact him.
I mean, he's always
just sort of been around.
- Leo! Leo!
- It worked.
- All right, Leo, look, Piper is very...
Very sick, I know.
That's why I could hear you.
I've been nearby watching.
Wait, you've been
watching her this whole time,
- and you haven't healed her?
- I can't.
They know about Piper too,
and they won't let me interfere.
I'm not even supposed
to be here right now.
Leo, you can't just let Piper die.
Don't you think I would do
something about it if I could?
- But you love her.
- I know.
But I'm not her whitelighter anymore.
Besides, even if I could help her, my
powers probably wouldn't even work,
because she wasn't hurt fighting evil.
I have to go. They know I'm here.
I'm sorry.
Tell Piper I love her.
Screw the consequences.
You really think the awakening spell
is gonna work?
It better. All right, look,
I'll get Piper's blood.
Are you sure that you
can get a poppet?
- Positive. I'll meet you in her room.
- All right.
- How is she?
- No change.
She just looks like she's sleeping.
But I can't wake her up.
She'll wake up, I promise.
Hey, Nathan. Remember me?
Phoebe. I was hoping
you'd come back.
- Really, why?
- You were right, the wizard did it.
I feel great, just like I used to.
- The power of positive thinking.
- The power of magic.
The doctors are letting me
go home in a couple of days.
Oh, that's great, Nathan,
I'm so happy for you.
You know, I was wondering
if you would let me borrow
the wizard for a while.
My sister can use
a little magic right about now.
She can keep him.
- I don't need him anymore.
- Thank you.
Hey.
I was gonna bring us
back some sodas,
but the machine down the hall
is busted.
I didn't know where to find
another one.
- Oh, I'll find it.
- Really? You don't mind?
No, it's not any trouble.
- I'll be back in a minute.
- Thanks.
- I got him. Let's do this.
- All right.
Trouble blood with sleep's unease
Remove the cause of this disease
Prue!
- Hey!
- Sleep eternal nevermore
- And shift the source of illness borne
- Hey! Open the door!
To this poppet
Whom none shall mourn
What's going on in there?
- Prue, it's not working.
- Unlock this door!
Come on, open the door!
- Hi.
- Open the door!
Who was blocking the damn door?
What's up, doc?
When did this happen?
Miss Halliwell, are you feeling all right?
Look at me. Vitals are normal.
Pupils are normal...
- Halliwell pulled out of the coma.
- She stabilized.
- Piper.
- Are those for me?
- You're okay?
- Yes, I am okay.
This doesn't make any sense.
Fever's gone, vitals are normal.
I've never seen anything like it.
- Point of infection's gone too.
- So can I go home now?
Draw some blood.
I wanna run comparatives.
Then can I go home? Because
no offence, but I hate hospitals.
Get off me.
Cleanup in room 420, please.
Cleanup in room 420.
Turn it up! Up!
All right, Malik, you can go home.
I'll clean up.
Dance with me, Dan.
- It's almost 2 in the morning.
- So what? Come on, you're young!
No, stop the music.
Stop that music.
- Somebody need a nap?
- You know what, that's not fair.
You've been asleep
for almost 24 hours.
And I know you've been up
for almost 24 hours by my side.
I can't tell you how much
that means to me.
Being there for me. Hanging tough.
I wasn't that tough.
You're welcome.
Now, go home.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay, spill.
What are you talking about?
- You guys cast a spell, didn't you?
- Who, us?
Yeah, you. Not that I'm not grateful
to be cured, because I am.
But what about that
little personal-gain problem?
Don't you think we would've seen any
consequences by now?
- It's been hours.
- Yeah, maybe
saving a protector of the innocent
isn't really personal gain.
Maybe. Like I said,
I'm not complaining.
I'm just glad you didn't call Leo.
Strange though, with all the demons
we've faced,
this bug, this thing,
was the scariest one of all.
Yeah, you don't have to convince us.
- I love you guys.
- We love you too.
Hey, just don't ever scare us
like that again.
Don't worry.
Oh, my God, I almost forgot.
I have to get that Monet
authenticated by tomorrow.
- At this hour?
- Why not? I'm wide awake.
I guess I should clean up.
- Piper. Piper!
- What?
I think I found a consequence.
Get me Dr. Williamson.
Yeah?
Okay, put them both on Penilovin.
Though I doubt it'll do any good.
Call me if there's any changes. Right.
And what can the Centers
for Disease Control do for you
this fine middle of the night,
Dr. Williamson?
I've really got something
for you this time, Seigler.
I wouldn't have called you
if I didn't.
It's not ethical to get the
government to validate your findings
- just so you can get published.
- This will get me more than published.
I've got an outbreak
of Oroya fever at this hospital.
That's impossible.
Oroya fever isn't contagious.
It is now. I've got three patients
with the disease in isolation.
- How'd they get it?
- I don't know.
But however they did has something
to do with the first patient
that came down with it,
Piper Halliwell.
Morning.
Hey.
- So how's Piper doing?
- Fully recovered.
What? That's great!
Yeah. I just came in early
to confirm a few suspicions.
- Wait, back up, Piper's okay?
- Yes.
She's home, she's healthy,
everything's back to normal.
Jack, we've gotta talk seriously.
Okay, shoot.
We can't keep on fooling ourselves.
This thing isn't real.
I mean, I know that it looks perfect
from the outside,
and it makes sense
to just ignore the truth
and pretend that there's
nothing wrong, but I can't do that.
Look, Prue, come on,
I know we've had our difficulties.
And maybe our relationship isn't
everything you hoped for, but...
Jack.
I'm talking about the painting.
It's not real.
I mean, yeah, it's from his school,
but Monet didn't paint it,
- one of his students did.
- Are you sure?
Positive.
So what?
"So what"?
Prue, if someone wants
to believe in something
that may not be altogether true,
but it's true enough for them,
- then what's the harm in letting it be?
- Jack...
Prue, the world is made up
of almost perfect.
It's nothing but near misses
and necessary compromises.
Now, in this case,
I think we got a little bit of both.
But you know what, that's okay.
I know how you feel.
I'm just asking you
to not look so close.
Nothing bears up under
that kind of scrutiny.
Are you talking about the Monet?
Yeah, that too.
Just trust me, all right? Go with it.
Everything's gonna be fine.
- Piper Halliwell?
- What's going on?
I'm Dr. Seigler from the CDC.
We have a court order to take you
and your sister into custody.
And to quarantine your club
until further notice.
How many people have been...?
No, I would not classify this
as an epidemic at this stage.
Although that's for Dr. Seigler of
the CDC here to determine, not me.
All I can tell you is that an outbreak
has occurred in the hospital
and we've taken all the necessary
and responsible steps to contain it.
Dr. Williamson, how do you know
it's contained? How can you be sure?
Because we've identified
the initial carrier.
Who is it? What's his name?
Is it a patient?
We've identified the initial carrier
and we've brought her
and anyone she may have infected
down into the isolation ward.
Is it true that they've closed
down a nightclub called P3
because of the outbreak?
That is a question
best answered by Dr. Seigler.
If you'll excuse me.
Yes, I can confirm
that an establishment
by the name of P3
has been quarantined.
But only as
a precautionary measure.
Hello? Hello? Remember us?
I'm sorry, we can't hear you.
What is it you want?
We wanna get the hell out of here,
that's what we want.
Dr. Williamson will be right in
to discuss the situation with you.
Discuss what? I feel fine!
Dr. Williamson will be right in.
This is ridiculous!
Why won't they tell us anything?
They're lucky they're in the other room,
I'd freeze their butts.
Oh, Prue, thank God.
You're obviously not here
to get us out.
No, when I got home, someone
from CDC was waiting for me.
- And they took, like, a quart of blood.
- Ditto.
They might as well
have taken all of mine.
They shut down the club.
They'll ruin it. I'll lose everything.
No, you won't. Once this whole thing
gets straightened out...
I have a feeling
it's not gonna be that easy.
I overheard some doctors talking.
There's others here infected
with the disease.
- But I thought it wasn't contagious.
- Yeah, so did I.
- So can they hear us?
- No.
Did either of you sleep,
by any chance?
Sleep? Piper was bouncing off
the walls last night.
It's gotta be a consequence
of the awakening spell you guys cast.
I have a bad feeling
that's not the only consequence.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
- What, no mask?
- No, I don't need it. None of us do.
However the disease
is being spread, it's not airborne.
- I've just ruled that out.
- Great. Then we're free to go.
- Afraid not.
- You can't keep us here.
Actually, I can, by law.
And not just because your sister
circumvented it by opening
the uninspected fruit,
but because she's carrying
a rare disease
that has a possibility of spreading
to epidemic proportions.
I thought that you said
it wasn't contagious.
Oroya fever isn't
supposed to be contagious.
- Well, maybe you misdiagnosed it.
- I didn't.
Aside from the fact that I have no idea
how this disease is being spread,
there's another mystery
concerning me.
Your recovery makes no clinical sense.
Your blood has no antibodies,
which means the immune system
never fought it off.
By all medical standards,
you should be dead right now.
What's the matter, doctor,
you don't believe in miracles?
Not the kind
that don't leave traces, no.
I've got six people infected.
There's nothing I can do to save them
unless I figure out
how you survived.
I'm gonna run a series of tests on
all three of you. Even DNA sampling.
Maybe it's a genetic marker,
I don't know.
But I'm gonna find out. And
you're not gonna leave until I do.
Wow, his bedside manner
sure could use some work.
Six people?
How is that possible?
When we did the spell,
we must have awakened everything
in the room, including the disease.
Is there anything different about
our blood because we're witches?
I don't know, but our first priority is to
figure out how to save these people.
Yeah, but even if we can find
a spell to save them,
how do we prevent it from spreading
to other people?
You have to reverse the spell.
No, Piper, we can't reverse
the spell, because...
You would go back into a coma,
you could die.
I'm not gonna die.
Just reverse the spell
and call Leo so he can heal me.
Leo? I thought you didn't want us
to call Leo.
Well, yeah, that's when I thought
I was sick, not dying.
Piper...
...we already talked to Leo.
He's not allowed to help.
They won't let him.
Great.
Well, thanks for doing something
I specifically asked you not to do.
- Piper, you just said...
- Phoebe, just give it a rest.
Look, Piper, we don't know
the reversal spell anyway.
Yeah, and they won't let us out
of here to go get it.
Prue can get it.
No, I can't.
Okay, I cannot just astrally project
on command. I can't control it like that.
You can learn to control it just like you
learned to control your other power.
- Just concentrate.
- Piper, I can't and I won't.
Prue, you have to try.
We can't let anybody else die.
Take her blood pressure,
get her on FIO2. Let's go, let's go.
- What's wrong with her?
- Nothing, she's fine.
Hurry, Prue.
What was awakened from its sleep
Must once again slumber deep
Return the disease to whence it came
So life can ease back to the same
Did you see it?
Yeah, Piper, I don't...
Prue, we've already discussed this.
For some reason,
there's no magical out for me.
But there is for the others. Please.
What was awakened from its sleep
Must once again slumber deep
- Prue! Prue, get help!
- Help!
Piper! Piper!
- Help me get her on the bed.
- Let's go, pick her up.
You girls wanna tell me
what the hell is going on?
Get her on the monitor.
Miss Halliwell.
Miss Halliwell, can you hear me?
Assist in respiration.
Get me a crash cart.
- Starting CPR.
- Her heart rate's erratic.
Get a code team in here stat,
I'm losing her!
Where's the crash cart?
Piper Halliwell, what room is she in?
No, what room is she in, damn it!
I'm family!
Nothing. Draw blood gases,
I need an amp of epinephrine.
- Where's that crash cart?
- It's on its way.
She's not responding to the CPR.
Come on, Miss Halliwell.
Stay with us.
Fourteen gauge.
Leo?
Hurry, take my hands,
we don't have much time.
- Am I dead?
- No, not yet.
Not if you take my hand.
- I don't understand.
- It's the only way I can heal you.
The only chance I have
of them not finding out. Hurry.
- She's in V-fib. Give me the paddles.
- Charging.
- Two hundred joules.
- Two hundred.
On one. Clear. One.
No response.
I'm not getting anything.
- Again.
- Charging!
Clear!
I don't wanna lose you.
Call it.
Time of death, 9:40 a.m.
- Wait.
- EKG's responding.
There's a heartbeat.
Piper?
What the hell? This is incredible.
Leo.
You're all right.
Are you okay?
BP, 105/60, pulse is strong.
- I don't understand. What happened?
- I don't know.
But I'm gonna find out.
Hey, I just heard.
Are you out of your mind?
I don't know, maybe.
Come on, Prue, you can't be serious.
You can't just quit.
I already did. I turned in my
resignation and Caldwell accepted it.
Why? Just because he doesn't agree
with you about selling the Monet?
It's not authentic, Jack.
You know what?
Buyers think it is.
And they've been thinking that way
for over a hundred years.
So it's worth whatever someone's
willing to pay for it, right?
- Yeah, right.
- No, it's wrong.
At least, in my book it is. That's the way
it used to be here before the takeover.
Before everyone cared more about
the sell than what they're selling.
- Including me, right?
- Jack.
It's not just about the painting
or Buckland's new philosophy.
I've been thinking about this
for a while.
A lot has happened to me in the
past year and a half. I've seen...
I've seen things that
I never imagined existed.
And it's changed me.
It's made me wanna make changes.
So, what are you going to do?
I don't know.
Just take some time, figure it out.
Look, I had a little wake-up call,
and I realized that life
is way too short
to be wasting my time doing something
I really don't wanna be doing.
Or being with someone
you really don't wanna be with.
Jack, you have been great.
You've opened me up
to so many new things.
Made me feel wanted again.
But...
But I need to be alone for a while.
No strings.
These haven't been inspected yet.
Put them in the back,
we're returning them to the supplier.
Looks like someone
learned their lesson.
Yeah, the hard way, unfortunately.
Well, still, the club's doing okay.
Doesn't look like quarantine
hurt business much.
Yeah, thanks to no cover charge
and free drinks.
- Have you guys seen Dan around?
- No, why?
No reason, I guess.
I thought he might stop by.
You know, Piper, Dan heard
you call Leo's name
when you were coming around
in the hospital.
He did?
That wasn't me thinking about Leo,
that was just...
Him saving you, I know.
Still, how are you gonna
explain that to Dan?
Well, at least you're alive to try,
that's what's important.
Just because we're witches doesn't
mean we're above the laws of nature.
Or the Wiccan ones.
I know, you don't have
to tell me twice.
I'm not taking anything
for granted anymore.
- Ditto.
- Yeah, Prue,
welcome to the ranks
of the unemployed.
I'm proud of you.
I think what you did was very brave.
Thank you.
Piper.
Leo.
Tell him thanks for us too.
- Hey.
- How you feeling?
- Okay.
A little tired,
which is actually a good thing.
Leo, thank you for everything you...
- I couldn't let you die, Piper.
- I'm very glad you couldn't.
- Did you get in trouble?
- Yeah, actually, a lot.
They found out what I did.
- They clipped my wings.
- What?
It's not permanent,
it's more like a suspension. I hope.
Leo, I don't know what to say.
You don't have to say anything.
You didn't do anything, I did.
I guess in the back of my head I always
hoped, thought, that someday...
...somehow, you and I would get
a second chance.
- I'm with Dan now, and...
- I know.
And I also know
that now that I'm a mortal...
...l'm gonna fight for you.
May the best man win.