Legend holds that buried
somewhere in the Iraqi desert
is a fabled book penned
by ancient mystics
known as the Akashic Records,
believed to be a written account of all
significant events throughout time.
Powerful stuff.
If someone were to get their hands
on that, they could win the lottery.
Or at least get tenure.
To know the future brings,
obviously, ultimate power.
Which is why everyone from Herod to
Hitler has been looking for the records.
But to find them...
To find them, one needs a map.
This tablet, found
in the lvory Coast last year,
is believed to be the very map.
Although the engravings are of a lost
language so far indecipherable
to even scholars like myself.
But we're close.
Whoever can decipher them first will
know the exact latitude and longitude
- of the Akashic Records.
- My God, that's it.
- Excuse me?
- No, no. Excuse me.
If you'll follow me, I'll show you the
next exhibit, which is quite interesting.
I cracked it. Dad,
the rest of the map,
it was a transposition sequence,
just like you said.
And it's all in here. The location
of the Akashic Records.
Now, they're gonna come after me
just like they came after you.
But I'm gonna be ready
for them, Dad.
- Hey.
- How's he doing today?
- The same.
Thanks for always keeping his room
so cheerful. I really appreciate it.
Oh, don't mention it. I mean, for all
we know, he knows they're here too.
Isn't that why you keep
talking to him?
Eric, can I speak to you
alone, please?
Yeah. Outside.
- I'm not moving him, Dr Stone.
- Eric, it's been six weeks.
This facility is not designed
for long-term maintenance.
Maintenance? That's my father
you're talking about.
And he's gonna get better.
And he's gonna stay here.
Sorry.
Eric, wait!
- I think Jack's a warlock.
- Who?
Jack. Jack Sheridan, the
Internet-auction guy I met, remember?
I went to go get coffee,
he was standing in front of me,
and then I went straight
to the newsstand, and wham,
he was right there
reading a magazine.
He went from one place to another
in the blink of an eye.
- You think he blinked.
- Well, yeah.
I mean, that's what warlocks do,
right? Where's Phoebe?
She's volunteering
at the convalescent hospital.
Great.
Wait. You have to know
if there's a warlock test.
Me? Why would I know?
Well, l...
I mean, you are a warlock magnet.
Am I never going to
live Jeremy down?
You know, you had that
Rex-and-Hannah thing at work.
Okay, you've got them in your love life,
I've got them at the water cooler.
- What's up with the suitcase?
- A little overnighter.
Dan's friend is getting married
in Tahoe,
and Dan invited me to come along.
In-the-same-hotel
in-the-same-bed sort of thing?
That has yet to be decided.
Oh, so then this is just
tennis outfit, right?
Give it. Thank you.
I mean, you did test him, right?
You know that he's not a warlock?
He's not a warlock.
No cats have hissed at him,
he has not blinked, he has not
tried to kill me or my sisters
and steal our powers, which,
as you know, is a key indicator.
I need the Book of Shadows.
Oh, I'll get it.
- Hello, you.
- Hi.
I was wondering if maybe
we could get an earlier start.
You know, miss traffic,
get there quicker so we could
have enough time to...
- Relax?
- "Relax" is a good word.
Any chance you could be ready
in an hour?
Yes, every chance.
I wonder what her problem is.
I gotta go now.
Bye.
Prue! Did you find
that warlock test yet?
Nineteen warlock-specific
death spells and not one test.
What if it's a conspiracy?
Jack and Dan working together,
sweet-talking, and the whole time,
they're figuring out how to kill us.
- Okay, now you're getting paranoid.
- Well, how can we not,
with warlocks and demons coming
out of the woodwork all the time?
- It's a wonder we trust anybody.
- We don't.
- Here it is.
- "To hear secret thoughts"?
We can hear Jack and Dan's
thoughts just long enough
to confirm or deny our suspicions.
- No personal gain.
- Purely for protection.
Okay.
As flame lights shadow
And truth ends fear
Open locked thoughts
To my mind's willing ear
May the smoke from this candle
Into everywhere creep
Bringing innermost voices
To my mind in speech
- Hey, she's wearing my lipstick.
- What, I can't borrow your lipstick?
- I didn't say that Prue, I thought it.
- Whatever. Just learn to share.
I heard that.
- This could be very dangerous.
- Stay calm. Calm down.
Book of Shadows,
needles and warlocks.
And Eric's in trouble.
Find out who. Find out what.
The hospital hottie?
What?
How's Eric? Did you see him today?
Why is the Book of Shadows
down here, girls?
- Jack blinked.
- And Kit hissed at Dan.
Right. And we think that
they may be warlocks,
so we were looking for a test
so that we could test them.
- Hello, paranoid?
- We are not.
Able to find a spell
in the Book of Shadows.
Well, just prick him.
Warlocks don't bleed.
So if there's no blood,
you got your answer.
- Who knew?
- Phoebe did.
- The spell, don't tell her.
- Should we reverse it?
Not until we know if they're really...
- Are you two okay?
- So how's Eric?
- Has he asked you out yet?
- No, but he's in trouble.
I had a premonition today.
A demon, or a warlock, maybe,
with a needle thingy on his finger,
and he was sticking it
into Eric's head.
So I came home to see
what we're up against.
You guys go deal with Jack and Dan,
and I'll look on the Internet,
and I'll tell you if I find anything.
Great, we're surrounded
by warlocks.
Next time, get your own
damn lipstick.
- I heard that.
- I love you.
Bite me.
- Prue.
- Jack, you actually wear that to work?
Feisty, feisty.
Well, when work puts me
in front of an online server
handling 5 million online
auction hits a day, yeah, I do.
- So, what's the emergency?
- Verschwang.
My what?
Verschwang Publications,
the German conglomerate.
You handled their CEO's
bronze-miniature collection
for the Internet auction, right?
Be careful. She suspects.
Yeah, of course.
Well, I need some bronzes
checked out. Who did your validation?
Validation?
You do have people's collections
validated, don't you?
Mostly, I put people in graves,
or I incinerate them.
Oh, yeah.
It was Walt Potock at Berkeley
School of Design. He's the best.
If she finds out I'm lying,
she's gonna die.
Well, you know what,
I'm a little late. Gotta go.
Good to see you again.
You're dying first.
You ready?
Can you come in?
- Where's your suitcase?
- Upstairs.
I see.
Cold feet. She's backing out. It's okay.
Don't push it. Just don't push it.
Look, don't move.
Okay, this is gonna hurt me
a lot more than it's gonna hurt you.
Piper, we have to get to Eric.
What's the matter?
He didn't bleed. He's not bleeding.
There's no blood. There's nothing.
Yeah. Of course he's not bleeding.
He's frozen, his blood is frozen.
Yeah. Right.
- Okay, go back upstairs. Go.
- Yeah.
Okay.
- What the hell was that?
- You're bleeding.
It's... Just a little bit.
Love her touch.
If she doesn't wanna go,
it's okay. Don't force it.
- Dan, listen. I really want to go.
- But?
- He's bleeding.
- He's lucky.
Hi. Listen, Dan,
I have to borrow Piper
for just a little while,
but I'll have her back soon, okay?
- Nice butt.
- Hey!
Hey, you hang in there.
And I'll be back in time.
- Yeah, I hope so.
- Later.
That's what's scaring Kit.
It's... You got hornets.
- It's probably what stung me too.
- Yeah, probably.
Okay, gotta go.
Don't leave without me.
Okay, gotta go, gotta go.
They're called "collectors."
They're a warlock...
They're a warlock breed
that drains knowledge
out of people's brains
with that weird finger I saw.
The Book didn't say
how to vanquish them?
No, it just said, "Their hunger
for knowledge is your ally."
Okay, whatever that means.
Are you sure this is where he lives?
That's what the hospital record said.
5D, here it is.
Piper!
Okey-dokey.
Oh, my God. That is Dr Stone,
Eric's dad's doctor.
All right, let's get him out of here.
We'll figure out what they want later.
Okay, ready?
- You do a little thingy.
- Okay.
Get out of here! Get him out of here!
Get back.
Oh, my God.
Okay, let's go, let's go!
They put my father in the hospital.
They took his mind.
- Who do you think they are?
- NSA, CIA, who knows?
Somebody in bulletproof vests.
The question is, who are you?
Friends.
Yeah, right.
They're after the Akashic Records too.
- What are the Akashic Records?
- I knew it.
Wait, what did you just say?
The Akashic Records,
what are they?
- You tell me.
- I'll tell you.
They're a book of ancient prophecies.
The future of the world,
down to the smallest detail,
hidden away and lost for centuries.
- But it's just a legend. How did you...?
- You're well informed.
- I read a lot. How did you know that?
- I'll tell you later.
So they want those records.
And they want Eric
because he knows
how to find them, right?
- Who are you people?
- What if it's not a legend?
Say they're real. What happens
if the bad guys get these records?
And they use the future against us?
No more us, the bad guys win.
- I gotta get my father out of there.
- No, wait, Eric.
He's stuck in the hospital.
Dr Stone's in on it.
Eric, it is not about
your father anymore.
It's about you,
especially if they think you know
- how to find the Akashic Records.
- Try and stop me.
How?
- Entertaining guest, I see.
- Hi.
Piper? Could you help me out a little?
Who's the cute boy?
It's Eric, from the hospital.
Two warlocks called collectors
want what's in his brain:
The location of the Akashic Records.
A lost text that predicts
all future events.
Collectors get it, the world's a goner.
- It's a...
- It's a lost text
that predicts all future events.
The collectors get it,
the world's a goner, I know.
Okay, does someone wanna tell me
what's going on here?
Have to tell her now.
Okay. Phoebe, see,
Piper and I didn't really know
about the whole pricking thing
to expose a warlock.
So we sort of cast a little hearing-
thoughts spell just to find things out.
Oh, a hearing-thoughts spell.
- Dan's clean, by the way.
- Glad to hear it. Jack's not.
Wait, are you guys thinking
something about me right now?
No. Does Eric know
witches, warlocks?
No, he thinks it's
a government conspiracy.
How do you know Jack's a warlock?
I heard his thoughts,
and they are bad. Really bad.
You know, graves, dead people,
burnt bodies.
- Did you prick him?
- No, that's why I need Piper.
Freeze him, prick him and then
vanquish him if necessary.
Where did you get that?
Remember the troubled priest
with the warlock brothers?
Well, they left this behind,
and I've sort of hung on to it,
just in case we needed it
for future warlock use.
Wow, it's been a while,
but it seems like they're everywhere.
Okay, you two go to it. I'll stay here.
- What if the collectors show up?
- Well, just get back before they do.
And don't lose that dagger.
We have to go kill a warlock
while she sits on some guy's...
Hey, hey, hey!
You heard that?
Like I need a hearing-thoughts spell
to know what you're thinking.
Stop it.
Now, are you gonna behave?
Do I have a choice?
No.
- Did you find Eric?
- No.
Not good. He's being protected
by a time-freezing witch.
And Bruce Lee's little sister.
The Akashic Records
are within our reach.
It's going to be very difficult to drain
his brain if they know what we're after.
Not to worry.
We'll get into his mind
through his heart.
Very nice.
There she is, hard at work.
- I'm glad you called. Can I come in?
- Sure.
Stay focused. Get it over with.
Freeze him.
The dagger, his hand,
just kind of poke him.
- He's not bleeding.
- He's frozen.
Yeah. Okay, okay, okay.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Hey, any survivors?
- Okay, there's two of them.
- Twin warlocks?
Or maybe they're just twins.
Okay, you unfreeze them.
If that prick doesn't bleed,
- then that one's dead too.
- All right.
All right, let them go.
What? What's the matter,
she bite you?
You shouldn't be here.
Come on, man, I couldn't let you
take all the blame.
He's bleeding.
All right, this is my sister Piper.
Which one of you jerks is Jack?
I'm the jerk.
This is my twin brother, Jeff.
Hey. Nice to meet you. Look,
sorry for the little tap dance earlier.
So, what exactly was it that you guys
were trying to prove?
It's just a little something
we used to do growing up.
Yeah, so when one of us would
take an interest in someone...
Don't get the wrong idea.
So you'd send the other one
to check out the merchandise,
- sort of kick the tires?
- Crude, but accurate.
Still doesn't explain
why he wanted to kill me.
Good point.
So, Jeff, what is it
that you do for a living?
Oh, great, this should be
a conversation stopper.
I own a mortuary.
Actually, a whole chain of them.
- Mortuaries.
- Put them in graves, set them on fire.
You know, you two should be
ashamed of yourselves.
That's for thinking that you
could get away with it.
And that's for thinking
that you wouldn't get slapped.
Piper.
I approve.
How did you know to be there
to help me?
- That's a long story.
- Wait. Shorten it.
I have this gift.
I sort of know when things are gonna
happen, if there's gonna be trouble.
- How?
- Just something I was born with.
So you don't work
for some government agency?
No. I'm just a girl.
Now, let me ask you a question.
This thing that you did, translating
this ancient code or whatever...
...why did you do it?
- I did it for my father.
- To finish his work?
- People hurt him.
And I wanted to find out who,
and I wanna get even.
- Even at the risk of them hurting you?
- He's my dad.
I love him. And if I can't
have him back, I want justice.
- I envy you.
- You're not close to your folks?
My mom is dead.
- I'm sorry.
- And my dad is...
...gone.
You don't know where he is?
I'm not really that interested.
- I don't understand that.
- You don't know my dad.
Do you?
No, I never got the chance to,
unfortunately.
Okay. I'm a sucker for family.
Follow me.
- Jack's not a warlock.
- He's a jerk.
We're going to the hospital.
We gotta get Eric's dad out of there
and keep him someplace safe.
Come on.
Where is everybody?
- Did you bring that dagger?
- Yep.
- Dad!
- Eric, wait!
Dad, we gotta get you out of here.
- Eric.
- I'm getting him out of here, Phoebe.
- What's going on?
- Later.
Get him. We gotta get out of here.
Where did they go?
Looking for that?
He's got the dagger.
Piper!
Move, and she dies.
Dad?
Eric. Eric, we still wanna help you.
Nothing has changed.
No, everything has changed. Some
kind of monsters just took my dad.
- They're called warlocks.
- Warlocks?
What does that make
the three of you?
Witches.
Forgive me, but what
you're saying is insane.
Eric, you believe in
the Akashic Records
and all the power
that they represent, right?
- Yeah, I guess.
- Well, most people think that's a myth.
But you now know that it isn't.
So isn't it possible that other things like
witches and warlocks actually do exist?
Maybe, but why would warlocks
want my dad?
They're probably gonna offer you a
trade: Your dad for what's in your head.
And they can appear
any time, anyplace.
Which is why we need to get you
back to the manor.
You'll be safer there
than anywhere else.
Okay, look, Eric, I am the same girl
you met at the hospital
a few weeks ago.
The only thing that's changed is,
now you know our secret.
- It's one hell of a secret.
- Yeah, and I trust you with it.
So please trust me in return.
Look, if we're gonna save your father,
we have to keep you safe
until we figure out
what we're gonna do.
You do that. I have another idea.
Okay, I'm gonna go get him,
you two get home.
- Do we have to protect him?
- He is pissing me off.
- Eric, what are you doing?
- You'll see.
We shouldn't be out in the open
like this. It's not safe.
Then go. I have
something I have to do.
What? What do you have to do?
Get busted, Eric? That...
That's the map stone, isn't it?
Yeah. My father thought it would be
so wonderful translating it.
A gift of knowledge to usher the world
into the new millennium.
What are you doing?
If the Akashic Records are everything
you say they are, they're not a gift.
I mean, the warlocks shouldn't have
that knowledge.
Neither should the rest of us.
With all knowledge revealed,
we could have no free will.
And no world as we know it.
Maybe no world at all.
Oh, my God!
Now no one else will ever
be able to translate the map.
The only place the longitude exists
is in my head.
I'll get security.
- Poor Eric.
- He'll be okay. We'll figure this out.
Yeah. In the meantime,
warlocks have his father.
I can't imagine
how helpless he must feel.
I can.
Prue, a warlock
didn't take our father.
No, he left on his own.
- Do you miss him?
- I didn't say that.
- Do you think about him?
- Why?
Because I'm wondering
if I'm the only one who does.
- No, you're not.
- So you miss him.
I miss who he should have been,
and I miss who he never was,
but I don't miss him.
I do.
All right, can we get to work?
Okay, let's save
someone else's father instead.
All right, the only way to protect Eric
is to take the information
out of his brain forever.
The spell is right here.
But if we do that, Eric won't
have anything to offer the warlocks,
and they'll be furious.
And they'll kill his dad.
Well, Eric is our innocent.
Our priority is him.
Yeah, but they're both innocents.
Piper, I hope it doesn't come to this,
but we may have to make a choice.
Why? I mean, there's gotta be another
way, with all the hocus-pocus we have.
Still may not be enough.
I mean, we're talking about
the future, everyone's future.
So we have to sacrifice Eric's dad?
For the greater good.
Man, you can dress it up
any way you want, it still stinks.
You know what, it sucks.
Oh, that's Dan.
I gotta go deal with him.
You gotta figure out
what we're gonna say to Phoebe.
Hey. You ready to go?
Oh, man. She's not coming.
Dan...
Look, I wanna go, I really do.
I'm just not quite ready yet.
Piper. Any word from the...
...pizza guy? Hi, Dan. We ordered
pizza. Would you like to stay for pizza?
No, I wanna go. With her.
But what's the point?
Okay, okay,
I know what you're thinking...
Piper!
- But I can be ready on time.
- Okay.
Well, I have to leave in an hour,
I'm gonna be late
for this wedding rehearsal.
So car's gonna leave at 6.
I hope to see you in it.
Okay.
Someday, some way, somehow,
I'm gonna make it
through that damn door.
Have the warlocks
made contact yet?
No, not yet.
Where have you guys been?
Well, Eric destroyed the map stone,
so we're covered there.
Did you guys find
anything in the Book?
You tell her. I've broken
enough hearts this afternoon.
We'll both tell her.
Eric, why don't you go check
your messages at home.
- Maybe they tried to contact you there.
- Okay.
What's going on?
Can we talk?
You have no new messages.
Wait, you're willing
to let Eric's father die?
We can't risk losing Eric and allow
the warlocks to gain future knowledge.
But not at the expense of his father.
We have to save him.
Phoebe, we have to save
everyone's dad.
We have to protect the whole world
from these warlocks.
And we can't do it
if they have the Records.
So, what am I supposed to tell Eric,
that we might have to
sacrifice his father?
I can't do that. I promised him
that we would save him.
- Phoebe.
- You don't even care.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that. I don't know
why I even thought it.
- Do you want us to tell him?
- No, it's something that I have to do.
- Hello?
- Eric. I assume you know who this is.
- Where's my father?
- Oh, you do know. Good.
Say hello to Eric, Ben.
- Eric? Son?
- Dad?
I feel so odd.
Dad! Dad!
Oh, he's gone, Eric. But I can
bring him back and give him to you.
All I want in exchange is
what's in your head.
- Where can I find you?
- The oak grove, the west end
of Golden Gate Park. Half an hour.
Alone. Without the witches.
Eric?
- Any messages?
- No, not yet.
Eric...
Before you say another word,
I just wanna say thank you
for everything you've done
for my father.
I mean, everything you're trying to do.
You sure you're not an angel?
No, I'm no angel. I could probably
introduce you to one, though.
It's a shame your father's
not a part of your life.
He would be so proud of you.
Eric, I need to talk to you...
...about you and your dad.
Okay.
Maybe we should have
another cup of tea first.
- Okay, I'll go get it.
- Thanks.
Eric, where are you going?
I'm just gonna go out, get some air.
The oak grove, Golden Gate Park.
Phoebe!
Yeah?
- Where is he going?
- He was thinking Golden Gate Park.
Oh, my God, the warlocks
must have contacted him.
All right, there are
oak trees everywhere.
- What if we're too late?
- Phoebe, stop thinking that.
Would you get
out of my head, please?
The Book of Shadows
said that their hunger is our ally.
So there must be a way
to use the knowledge
that they've acquired against them.
Or use their greed to trap them.
Yeah, well, if all else fails,
then we'll freeze them and move them
long enough to get Eric away.
And save his father, right?
Look, it just seems to me we should do
everything we possibly can
to reunite Eric and his father.
I mean, imagine, a dad who actually
wants to be with his child.
Pheebs, we'll do our best.
Okay. Then we should split up.
The first one that sees him hollers.
- Dad!
- That's close enough, Eric.
I can restore him,
or I can kill him, Eric.
That choice is mine.
Restore him, or you don't get
what you want. That choice is mine.
No, no, no, no, no, you can't bargain,
Eric. We're in control here.
Let's check again.
Who's got the upper hand?
Haven't you been paying attention?
That gun won't do anything to us.
No, but it will blow my head off.
And if I do that, you don't get
the second half of the map.
Restore him. Now.
- Dad?
- Eric.
Son, what are you doing?
Dad!
You're mine now, Eric!
Like I said, we're in control.
Phoebe.
Prue, watch out!
That's right, witches.
Come and get me.
Don't blink.
Keep them focused on me.
Let him surprise them from behind.
- Wait, don't freeze him.
- Why not?
Didn't you hear his thoughts?
He's playing decoy.
Let him think that it's working.
You know, they really shouldn't have
given us the finger.
You read my mind.
Prue? Piper?
Are you okay?
I think so.
What are we doing in the park?
Who are those people?
- You don't recognize Eric?
- No. Why, should I? Should I?
What's the last thing you remember?
- The Halloween party.
- That was three weeks ago.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Just a little confused.
What am I doing here?
You don't recognize her?
No.
Wait, I think I've seen you
at the hospital.
Who's the cute guy?
- Dad?
- Eric.
Oh, my God! You're...
You're better!
- What's going on? What's happening?
- I don't know.
- Did we do something good?
- You did something incredible.
Okay, what am I thinking?
That Dan's gonna leave without me.
- Nope. Good, the spell is reversed.
- What a relief.
I think we've proven beyond
a shadow of a doubt that man
and, especially, woman aren't meant
to hear each other's thoughts.
Definitely. Too much knowledge,
whether it comes from the
Akashic Records or people's heads,
- is just dangerous stuff.
- So, what were you thinking?
I was thinking what it shame it was
that Phoebe finally met a nice guy,
and she's not even
gonna remember it.
- Hi.
- They're gorgeous.
They're for you. The florist left them
on the porch. But there's no card.
- They're huge.
- They're expensive.
They're ringing.
- Hello?
- Oh, no!
Dan! He's leaving. Without me.
- Don't just stand there, freeze him.
- Oh, right.
I gotta go.
It's such a nifty little power.
Honey... Open.
- Hello?
- At last.
I've been calling you every
20 minutes for the last hour.
- Did you like the flowers?
- Jack, what do you want?
You know, you are
a very suspicious woman.
No, I just like to think of it as careful.
Oh, come on, Prue, are you saying
you've been totally honest with me?
Jack, I can't hear you,
the phone's breaking up!
I just... I wanted to apologize.
Can l...? Can I take you for dinner?
- I don't think so.
- Come on. Let me buy you a drink.
- Can I at least get my phone back?
I don't think so.
- Oh, I like it.
- What are you doing?
I'm calling Tokyo.
Konnichiwa.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for a Dr Schlenzig. I need
him to sign some insurance papers.
I was told he'd be in here.
Yeah, he actually just took
Mrs Bruen to the sunroom.
- You could probably catch him there.
- Great. Thanks.
You're Phoebe, right?
I'm Eric Bragg. I think I saw you
the other day at the park.
Right. Right, how's your father?
Oh, he's better, thanks.
He's almost back to his old self.
I remember...
...you were really sweet to him
when he was in here.
Not many people
would have bothered.
- You must be an angel.
- No, I'm no angel.
But I could probably introduce you
to one if you'd like.
You know, I just realized, I have
no idea where the sunroom is.
It's kind of complicated.
Maybe I should draw you a map.