Piper?
- Expecting company?
- You think? What are you doing here?
I was supposed to have
the house to myself tonight.
God, I thought that that
was tomorrow night.
No, I put it on the kitchen calendar
way in advance.
That's why Phoebe's at the library,
and you're supposed to be
out on assignment.
Yeah, well, I was all day.
I was just downstairs in the basement
developing these shots that I took.
Actually, I was hoping
to get your opinion on them.
But I guess now wouldn't
be a good time, would it?
No.
- Although, Leo's not really here yet.
- All right, make it fast.
Okay.
All right, so the magazine asked me
to capture faces in the city.
So I went to the Haight
and I took these shots,
- but look at this man.
- Yeah, so?
So he is in every single one
of my pictures.
I mean, I didn't really focus on him.
I didn't even notice him
until I got home.
But, I mean, there he is
in all of them, just hanging out.
- Well, maybe he's homeless.
- Handing out flyers? I don't think so.
And look at his face.
I mean, he looks so sad
and determined.
Okay, bye-bye.
All right, so I'm gonna go now,
and I'll be downstairs
and work all night long.
And I'll be really quiet.
You don't have to worry about me.
- Okay.
- So no sex without safe sex.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
By the way,
on the kitchen counter,
there's a birthday card for Dad
if you wanna sign it.
I don't. Night, Leo.
Good night.
That's weird. I wonder why
she doesn't wanna sign...
Hi.
You wanna sit down?
Why don't we go upstairs,
since she's downstairs?
Okay. I know a faster way.
- You do?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
- I won't tell if you won't.
- Hey. Hi, I'm Phoebe.
- I'm Charlene.
Actually, we've met,
we even carpooled.
Metaphysics 301, remember?
That's right. And your dad
is the professor of that class, right?
Yeah, he's a dirty rat.
He gave me a C.
We don't get along, in anything,
even metaphysics.
But I'm hoping that will change.
I'm gonna finish my thesis,
get published.
He'll finally have to
take me seriously.
Run quick, before I start
telling you about my mother.
No, it's okay. I've been
studying here for so long,
it's nice to have someone to talk to.
So, what's your thesis about?
It's about the existence
of demons in our world.
- Demons?
- Yeah, I've been researching
for five years to prove they're not
just myths, like my dad thinks.
That they actually really exist.
I've got proof right here.
- That's very interesting.
- But you believe in them, don't you?
I mean, you seemed to in class.
Certainly knew a lot about them.
It's really late, and I really
gotta go. Okay.
It was really nice
talking to you, Charlene.
- Take care, okay?
- Okay, see you around.
- Bye.
- Bye-bye.
I'm sorry. You scared me.
Wait.
Hey, Piper.
Will you do me a favour
and feed the cat?
I wanna get down
to the Haight, you know.
I wanna see if that guy
is still on the bus bench.
You know, I just could not
stop thinking about him all night.
I mean, there's no guarantee
that he'll actually be there,
but if he is, I wanna
get a better shot.
Prue.
- What...? What are you doing in here?
- Piper, can you hand me a towel?
- Prue.
- Leo.
Nice orbs.
Okay, bye.
Bye. Out.
Let me help you,
let me help you. All right.
Go on, sicko.
Phoebe.
It's 8:00. It's 8:00.
I'm late for my finals.
Phoebe, relax.
It's Thursday.
Your finals are tomorrow.
- It's Thursday?
- Yes.
Today is Thursday. You sure?
Okay, that's really good news.
Please tell me you didn't do
another all-nighter.
- I can't.
- Phoebe.
What? Piper, what am I
supposed to do?
- Hi, Leo.
- Hey.
If I don't ace this final,
I'm gonna flunk out of school
because of all the
demon-hunting interruptions.
Still, Phoebe, you have to take care
of yourself. Get some rest.
After. Piper, I did not go back
to college to fail at it, okay?
So, what do I have to do?
Okay, I'm gonna go change,
and then I'm gonna go to the library.
Now, if any demon or warlock attacks,
please, just fend them off till Saturday.
I have a question for you.
Is it possible for someone to find proof
that demons really do exist?
I don't know, maybe.
But even if anybody did,
nobody would ever know about it.
- What do you mean?
- Evil doesn't want anybody to know.
It has a system for covering
its tracks, protecting its identity.
That's why demons disappear
when you guys vanquish them.
Why do you ask?
Just curious.
- Okay, adíos.
- Wait, Phoebe.
Don't you wanna sign
Dad's birthday card?
Why? He never sends me one.
She's right.
He doesn't to any of us.
So why do I keep trying?
- I'm just a sucker for punishment?
- No.
You keep trying
because you never give up hope.
That's one of the things
I love about you.
You never gave up on us.
Were you close to your dad?
Well, that was a long time ago.
Different lifetime.
I prefer to focus on the present.
So do I, which means I have to go.
I have a dentist appointment.
- How long can you stay?
- Till they call.
If they don't call before lunch,
why don't you meet me at the club?
- I'll buy.
- You'll have to.
Whitelighter pay sucks.
Hi.
My name's Prue Halliwell.
Cleavant Wilson.
I'm a photographer
with 415 magazine.
I'd like to know if it's okay
if I take your picture.
- Why?
- We're doing a feature
called "Faces in the City,"
and I would love to include yours.
I'm not interested.
Although, I would appreciate it
if you would include this one.
"Tyra L. Wilson."
My daughter.
She was murdered six and a half
months ago here waiting for the bus.
I'm looking for a witness.
That's why you were sitting here
all day yesterday.
That's why I'm here every day.
I have been since
the police quit on us.
I'm not leaving until I find somebody
who saw what happened.
How can you be sure that you will?
I will.
I have to be sure.
So are you gonna print that or not?
Actually, it's not really up to me.
I'm just looking for a witness.
Just looking for a witness.
Sir, I'm looking for a witness.
You don't have to be afraid
to come forward.
- What?
- You two must've been very close.
She was my daughter.
It doesn't get any closer.
You know, I have a friend,
a really good friend,
who's an inspector.
You know, maybe I can call them,
see if they have any ideas who did it.
I know who did it.
The punk that owns that pawnshop
across the street, Gibbs.
He killed my little girl.
- Why?
- Wrong place, wrong time.
Everybody knows he did it.
Problem is, he's got everyone
too afraid to talk.
Hey! Hey!
All right, you first.
What the hell is going on here?
Don't ask me,
he came in here punching.
Dan did?
Well, what did you do to him?
- What did I do? Nothing.
- Come on. He had to have a reason.
Like losing you isn't enough reason.
All right, back
to your position. Go on.
You kidding me?
He's about to clock me.
I'm sorry, I can't help you
with that. Let's go.
Let's go.
Piper, where did you come from?
I'll be asking the questions.
What the hell is going on?
- I don't know, why don't you ask him?
- I did... I mean, I will.
I'm asking you first.
- You know what? I just gotta go.
- Dan, wait.
Oh, no, you don't. They can wait.
- I'm sorry, I have to go.
- Leo.
Agent Cucushny, at this time, we need
you to return to homequarters.
Excuse me.
Excuse...
Darryl.
Don't tell me. Demons, right?
Or is it warlocks this time?
- What are you talking about, Darryl?
- You're not here because of this?
No, Darryl, contrary
to popular belief,
not every crime in the city
is demonically related.
Or Halliwell-related, for that matter.
I was on my way to the library.
- What happened?
- College student.
She was decapitated
and her body was dumped here.
College student. Any idea who?
Charlene Hughes.
Charlene.
You know her?
I saw her last night in the library.
Hey, Phoebe.
Do you have an aspirin?
I have a splitting headache.
Charlene.
You're supposed to be...
I'm supposed to be what?
Okay, just tell Dan
that I called again, okay?
No, believe me, he knows
what it's about. Thank you.
- They're both ducking me.
- Who both?
- What happened in here?
- Dan and Leo.
I found them in here
beating the crap out of each other
and neither one of them
will tell me why.
Well, I hate to top that,
but I am dealing with a ghost
who doesn't know she's a ghost.
She thinks she's still alive.
Charlene, she's a student
that I know, or knew.
The police found her body
behind the library,
about 20 feet away from her head.
So I went back to the library,
and I saw her ghost.
You know? And I tried to tell her,
but I just couldn't.
You're right. Yours tops mine.
I just don't get it. How could someone
not know that they're dead?
Well, it takes them a while to accept it,
to get over the shock.
Why today of all days?
I have got to study.
Hey, I know. Maybe you could
help me out with this one,
and then I could take
the next two ghosts, okay?
Nice try, Pheebs,
but you know how this works.
That ghost came to you
for a reason,
and more than likely it's to get justice
for her murder so she can move on.
The other thing, I think
a demon actually killed her.
Oh, and you were gonna
pawn this off on me.
Well, no, I was gonna tell you
about the demon part sooner or later.
But remember what Leo said
about evil covering up its tracks?
I think that's what happened
to Charlene.
She was convinced that she found
proof that demons really do exist.
Well, then you have to get her
to tell you what that proof was.
But first you're gonna
have to tell her that she's dead.
I know. That's the problem.
How do you tell someone
that their life is over?
Darryl.
See, I knew I was right the first time.
You guys don't give me
nearly enough credit.
Credit?
First Phoebe, now you.
I've learned by now that if it walks
like a duck and it quacks like a duck...
Okay, Darryl,
what are you talking about?
Demons. You're here to tell me
one got Charlene, right?
Okay, number one,
I have no idea who Charlene is.
Number two, I'm here to talk about
Cleavant Wilson's daughter, Tyra.
Tyra? She wasn't killed by demons.
No, but you guys have an idea
of who killed her, right?
Yeah, we got a pretty good idea.
- Just a pretty good idea?
- All right, a very good idea.
- Why are you so interested?
- Honestly, I'm not entirely sure.
I just... I'm drawn to him
for some reason
and usually that means to help.
Unless you can magically
turn up a witness,
I doubt there's anything you can do.
- You can't, right, magically?
- No, if I could do that, Darryl,
Cleavant wouldn't be out there
giving up his life trying to find one.
You really wanna help?
Convince him to give up trying.
Help him to move on. No one
is ever going to testify against Gibbs.
- We have been down that road.
- He is never gonna give up, Darryl.
His daughter was his entire life.
And why are you guys
so okay with giving up?
Look, Gibbs owns that street, okay?
Tyra was probably gunned down
because she saw something
he didn't want her to see.
And short of us finding a witness
or him walking up
on the street and confessing...
...there's nothing I can do.
Maybe there's something I can do.
I got your messages.
All eight of them.
So you wanna tell me
what the fight was about?
Actually, I was hoping Leo would,
but I gather he hasn't.
He's unreachable, apparently.
You know, this is very
awkward for me.
I don't wanna come across
as the jealous ex,
but that's not what this is about.
That's why I went to Leo first.
But, see, I started it.
I came at him very hard
with this, and...
With what?
Do you remember my brother-in-law
who works for the State Department?
When I asked him about Leo?
Well, he found something wasn't right
with Leo's Army records.
- Dan...
- I know. I asked him
not to go any deeper
about this, okay?
But he did.
And he sent me this anyway,
something very unusual.
Leo isn't who he says he is.
But what you do with this
is all up to you.
You know, I'm...
I'm still here for you.
I'm still your friend.
What? Leo's married?
Yeah, there's even a picture of her
in his Army file being presented
his Purple Heart after he died.
She's pretty. Her name is Lillian.
Prue, why didn't he tell me about her?
Why would he hide that from me?
I don't know. You have to ask him.
Well, I'd love to, but he's conveniently
out of the calling area at the moment.
Leave it to me to fall in love with
an angel who happens to be married.
Maybe he didn't tell me about her
because he's still in love with her.
No, come on.
How do you know
she's even still alive?
Well, I sort of did
a little Internet search.
I was thinking maybe I should
go have a chat with her.
No, Piper, I don't really think that
that's a very good idea.
But speaking of chats, I need to go
and talk to this pawnshop guy
before he closes, okay?
So we'll talk later?
Yeah. Okay.
We're closed.
- Well, it's only a quarter...
- I said, we're closed.
Get the hell out of here.
You know, you don't scare me.
Well, then you're stupid, lady.
And stupid people don't last long
in this neighbourhood.
Ask around.
Are you threatening me?
What, are you a reporter?
You work for the DA's office, what?
You know, I seen you over there
talking to that dead kid's old man.
- I know what you want.
- Is that right?
Yeah, and you ain't getting it.
Nobody's gonna mouth
on me. Nobody.
You're just wasting your time.
And you're trespassing.
You know, it must be something
living off of other people's pain.
I hope it doesn't
come back to haunt you.
If you saw anything, I'd appreciate it.
- Appreciate your help.
- All right.
Phoebe.
Sorry. I didn't mean to spook you.
So to speak. Charlene,
how are you feeling?
Do you feel any different?
My headache. I guess. Yeah.
I mean, I just feel
kind of weird in general.
I think that's to be expected.
I think she's mad at us.
Why don't we go over here so
we can talk and not disturb anybody.
Is something wrong, Phoebe?
Yes, Charlene, actually,
there is something wrong.
I think that the reason that you've
been feeling so weird lately
is because you're...
You're a ghost.
- Excuse me?
- Yeah, I know that this sounds crazy,
and it's probably really hard for you
to accept, but think about it, Charlene.
When was the last time
you ate something?
Or were hungry,
for that matter. Or slept.
I mean, are you tired
right now, Charlene?
- Are you even tired?
- What are you saying?
I'm saying that I think
a demon killed you last night.
That's what I am trying to say.
And the only reason I can see you
is because I'm a witch,
and I'm supposed to help you.
I think you're the one
who needs help, not me.
Look, you don't believe me?
Try picking something up.
Now, you know as well
as I do that neophyte ghosts
cannot channel their anger
into moving material objects.
Try picking up a book.
See for yourself.
This is ridiculous.
I am not dead.
I've got a full life ahead of me,
and I will finish my thesis,
and I will be published.
Charlene. Charlene, wait.
- Anybody here?
- In here.
Hey. Good, I was looking for that.
Wait, what are you doing
with the Book?
I'm looking for the demon
that's gonna kill me.
I just love getting
those premonitions.
Okay, what premonition? When?
About an hour ago, right after I was
trying to tell Charlene that she's dead.
I'm lost.
Oh, sorry. Wrong sister.
Okay, Cliffs Notes version:
She is a student
who found proof that demons
really do exist.
And this demon right here, Libris,
chopped off her head
and dumped her body behind
the library because of it.
There are a whole bunch
of Libris demons out there.
Wherever humans have the potential
to find unequivocal proof
of the existence of demons.
Yeah, talk about
your conspiracy theories.
Well, you just have to stop doing
whatever it is you're doing.
I can't. Charlene's spirit can't move on
unless I get justice for her murder.
So, what, by getting
murdered yourself?
Well, hopefully not.
On the bright side, I won't have
to suffer through flunking college.
- So how was your day?
- Not as bad as yours,
but it's gonna get a hell of a lot better
as soon as I find the truth spell.
What do you need that for?
To catch a murderer who thinks
he can get away with it.
So you're gonna use the truth spell
to make him confess?
- Exactly.
- Not exactly. Prue, you can't do that.
We can't use our powers
to punish the guilty.
We learned that lesson
the hard way, remember?
Yeah, but it's not
the same thing, Pheebs.
I mean, I'm helping a father
with his grieving.
I'm helping him to move on.
It's more like protecting
the innocent.
No, it's not, honey.
Phoebe, I see this man
on the bus bench every single day,
and he's just waiting there, hoping.
Why was I drawn to him if I can't
help him nail his daughter's killer?
- Why were you drawn to him?
- The look on his face, the pain.
The pain of a father's loss?
Maybe.
I mean, I can't help
thinking about Dad,
and wondering if it hurts him as much
not having his daughters in his life.
- I think it does.
- Yeah, I wish I thought so too,
but, you know, I keep on bumping up
against this whole theory
that if it hurt him so much,
where is he?
Phoebe.
- Charlene. That's Charlene.
- You were right about me.
I went home, saw the folks crying,
then I knew it was true.
I've never seen my dad cry before.
Not over me anyway.
Then I got pissed.
If a demon did this to me,
I wanna get him.
I wanna prove
he doesn't exist anymore.
- Your friend, obviously?
- Yeah, the dead one.
Leo's Purple Heart.
He was a special man.
He always went out of his way
to try and help somebody,
even before he shipped out.
He was studying to be
a doctor, you know.
- Yes, I know.
- He'd have been a great one too.
You know, he had
the most marvellous touch.
It was gentle, sensitive...
- Healing.
- Yes, exactly. A healing touch.
That was Leo. And they said
that he was doctoring
a wounded soldier
when it happened.
I'll never forget when they came
to give me that news.
It sounds like you still love him.
I'll always love Leo, in a certain way,
for so many things,
including helping me to move on.
Move on. How'd he do that?
Well, one night, not long after he died,
Leo came to me in a dream,
and he was bathed in the most brilliant
white light that you could ever imagine.
He said I was not to worry
about him,
that he was in a good place.
He also said that I was
to let him go,
that there was another love
out there for me to find.
- Another love?
- Yes.
Another doctor, as it turned out.
A wonderful man.
He gave me two wonderful children,
grandchildren, even a great-grandchild.
Leo was right.
Well, I think I've taken up
enough of your time.
But you haven't found
what you came for yet.
Actually, I think I have.
It was very nice to meet you, Lillian.
You too, Piper.
So I was walking down the aisle,
and I heard strange voices,
whispers, sounded like Latin.
And then I went
to pull out a book, and...
I don't know.
It all went dark,
until I was back in the library again
with that terrible headache.
You didn't get a chance
to see the demon?
- Don't remember.
- All right, well, if it was Libris,
he must've grabbed her in the aisle
and taken her somewhere to:
- Sorry.
- That's okay. I'm over the shock.
You know, the question is,
how did he grab her?
And this vanquishing spell
isn't gonna do us much good
if we can't catch him first.
Well, we're gonna
have to do it in the library
if we're gonna keep
that premonition from coming true.
Maybe I can retrace
Charlene's steps
and that'll bring him
out into the open.
- Phoebe.
- And just before he grabs me,
you and Piper can use
your powers to stop him,
and then we can
vanquish him, easy as that.
- No, that is way too risky.
- How is it risky
with two witches and a ghost
to back me up?
Prue, help me get my demon,
and I promise I'll do everything
I can to help you get yours.
- I'm home.
- Come on.
- Where are we going?
- We'll explain on the way.
- Who's that?
- Let's go. Let's go.
That's my dead friend.
Last thing I wrote
was under "Demonic Acts."
- There.
- You know, this is pretty accurate.
You were really
onto something here.
Obviously.
Sorry.
- Okay, what was next?
- I went to find the encyclopaedia.
This way.
There's the book.
I don't hear any voices.
Okay, here it goes.
Maybe demons can see ghosts.
Phoebe!
Where is she? Where did she go?
No!
- What, the basement?
- Worth a try.
Demon, hide your evil face
Libris die, and leave no trace
Thank God.
Okay. All right.
- That was close.
- Yeah.
Thank God you're a quick study.
At least justice was served.
So I guess that means
I'm moving on.
Bye, Phoebe.
Thank you for this.
Thank you for helping me.
You're welcome. Take care.
Why am I not moving on?
I have no idea.
I thought you said all we have to do
is get justice for Charlene's murder?
- I said, maybe that is all you had to do.
- You did not say maybe.
- Yes, I did. I absolutely did.
- I did not hear the word maybe.
Yes, I did.
You guys aren't helping.
Are you sure that
vanquishing spell really worked?
- Maybe Libris isn't really gone.
- You know, you're getting good at that.
I'm just frustrated, that's all.
I told you she was a quick study.
Maybe Charlene's right,
maybe you didn't vanquish him,
- like the Demon of Illusion.
- No, he is definitely gone.
I mean, the spell was
specifically written for Libris.
Yeah, and he wouldn't have left
his sickle behind if he were still alive.
But the question still remains:
If justice was served, then what
is she still doing here?
Damn it!
Sorry.
Wait a minute.
- That's it.
- What? What is it?
Maybe she has to get justice
for somebody else.
Who's there?
Gibbs.
You really think you're tough
with that gun, don't you?
"Tyra."
- What the hell's going on?
- You wanna know what's going on?
- Who are you?
- Who do you think I am?
So how does it feel
to be pushed around?
Murderer.
I'm the woman you murdered.
Leave me alone!
Admit it.
Admit you killed me,
or I will haunt every minute
of every day of the rest
of your miserable life.
Okay, okay!
Okay, I did it. I killed you.
- Say it. Say my name, damn it!
- Tyra Wilson! Tyra Wilson!
I killed Tyra Wilson, I admit it!
I've been waiting a long time
to hear you say that, Gibbs.
- Did you get that?
- I got every word.
- What the hell is this?
- Justice.
What's the matter, Gibbs,
you look like you've seen a ghost?
I hope you rot in hell.
How's this connected
to Charlene again?
It's a cosmic thing, Darryl.
Don't worry about it.
Are you okay, Mr. Wilson?
Yeah, I guess.
It's an empty feeling, though.
You know, it...
This doesn't bring her back,
it doesn't take away the hurt.
No, but at least you can
move on with your life.
Tyra would've wanted that.
I wish I could tell her how much
I love her just one more time.
I think she'll get the message.
Thank you...
...for however
you made this happen.
Thank you.
Well, even if I could never seem
to please my own father,
at least I could please
someone else's.
I know what you mean.
I think it's time.
Hey. Ask me how I did on my final.
- How did you do on your final?
- Oh, thank you for asking.
I aced it. They just
posted the grades.
- Good for you.
- Thanks.
Although, I did get
some perspective on the test.
After what happened to Charlene,
it just didn't seem important anymore.
Speaking of perspective,
I signed Dad's card.
- Really?
- Yes.
Just in case he thinks of us too.
No, I definitely
don't need to sign that.
I mean, I realize that Dad is never
gonna be the father that Cleavant is,
and I just need to accept that
and stop thinking that magically
he's somehow gonna change.
Excuse me.
How'd you get in?
I thought whitelighter pay sucked.
I sort of didn't tell the bouncer
I don't work here anymore.
Imagine that. Like you sort of
didn't tell me you were married?
Look, Piper, I didn't tell you,
because I didn't want you to get upset.
And it was literally
a different lifetime for me,
one that has nothing to do
with this one, with us.
I know that, and I'm not mad,
but you can't not tell me stuff
because you think it might hurt.
If we're gonna have
a normal relationship,
at least as normal as possible,
then you need to be honest with me.
You're right. I'm sorry.
- Forgive me?
- I'll think about it.
So how much do you think
Dan really knows?
I don't know.
We'll worry about it later.