www.ydy.com presents...
May 24, 2007
"Underdog" by Spoon
You get done cleaning up
that mess,
go tackle the john.
Stopped up again.
I look like a janitor,Tommy ?
Haven't taken my lunch yet.
You're spending too
much time on each job, Ed.
You gotta turn around six more cars
after you clean the can.
I'd eat first before I walked
in there, Ed.
Or call FEMA.
Hey, Channel 7,
what's she wearing ?
Welcome to Pennsylvania Power...
Wearing out
your bank account, buddy.
It's a sucker's dream.
Ed... can I talk to you ?
Yeah.
I just got the estimate
on my car.
I can't afford this.
Two grand,
ain't that beautiful.
Tommy ought to be ashamed
of himself.
Yeah, I just got my tuition bill,
but I need my car to get
from work to school...
Relax. Relax.
Most of these repairs
you don't even need.
And I got a rebuilt
water pump in the back.
I just need it to run.
Uh... what can you afford ?
Um... maybe 400.
400 ? Okay.
I'll fix all the stuff you need to have
done and drop it off your place tomorrow.
- Don't sweat it, Shelly.
- Thanks, Ed.
You're the best.
11...
Keep cutting folks a break like that,
boss'll take it out of your hide, Ed.
Yeah,he can kiss it.
20... 49...
Hey, what's it up to ?
Jackpot. What's the latest ?
I don't know. 7,8 mil ?
27...
Break's over, George.
Ed, you just tell that
customer we padded her bill ?
... and 55.
Thanks for playing
Pennsylvania Power Lotto today.
Talking to you, Ed.
You can stick it where the sun
don't shine,Tommy,
'cause I quit !
Look at this !
How long you playing
the lotto, Ed ?
Well, since my sister Pam was
old enough to buy me a ticket.
Hey, Ed! What are you planning
on doing with the 8 million ?
What do you think ?
I'm gonna spend it !
Well, Detective Strickland
just caught
that double over in Point Breeze.
I'll call you later.
Look like you could use
a few winks, Walt.
Too many open jobs, Lil.
Hoping you might be able
to take one off my plate.
Heard one might be thawing out ?
Auto mechanic named Ed Dubinski
got popped in Fishtown
on his way back
from the SwiftMart.
Way back to where ?
Working late in the garage.
Shooter took his wallet.
Robbery gone bad.
What we thought.
Thing is, Dubinski wasn't
just any grease monkey.
He won eight million in thelottery
six months before.
- Eight million ?
- Yeah.
I asked the bank to keep
Ed's account open
in case the doer tried to use
the stolen ATM card.
How much was in the account ?
Seven and change.
Seven mil ?
Seven dollars and thirty-nine cents.
Dubinski went through it all.
Lost eight million dollars ?
Yeah. Turns out a lot of these lottery
winners get in over their heads.
One third of them go
bankrupt in five years.
Ed was no different.
Something kicked up on the case ?
Someone used Dubinski's card yesterday
at a sandwich shop in Center City.
ATM camera working ?
There wasn't one. Doer attempted a
withdrawal, checked his bank balance.
Means the killer knew
his PIN number.
Someone who knew him ?
Or the stickup guy made him
give it up.
But why wait two years
to hit that account ?
Unless they think the
jackpot's still out there.
Cold Case
Season 6 Episode 12
Transcript VO : www.ydy.com
Lotto Fever
Ed Dubinski, thirty-four.
Moved back to
his old Fishtown apartment
a few days before his murder.
Talk about bottoming out.The guy
burned through eight mil in six months.
Wait, how's that even possible ?
What was he,smoking it?
Jackpot's up to 18 mil this week.
More people in the pool,
more tickets we can buy.
I don't know.
Seems like a chump's game.
Well, this chump's gonna be rich
when the money train comes in.
You in the lotto pool, Will ?
Nope. It's pointless.
Wrong.
Point is, dreaming about the
things you'd do if you won.
Dubinski went for a pack of smokes
at the SwiftMart around midnight.
Shot in an empty lot on his way
back to the auto repair shop.
Slug from a nine
recovered from the body.
Cashier, Shelly Reid,
last to see talking to Rush.
Any surviving next of kin ?
Uh, older sister Pam,
owns a hardware store in East Falls
with her husband Marty.
Took custody of Ed at age 18.
What happened to the parents ?
Lost mom to a car accident,
dad to prison.
What else we got
on Ed's finances ?
Money manager listed here as
a Roger Weaver, on the way in.
PIN number was 747539.
Figure the killer had to
know Ed to get that number?
What are the odds of
guessing a six-digit PIN ?
I'll bet I could guess yours.
Shut up.
50 bucks. Give me your ATM card.
Tell you right now,it ain't
my birthday or my address.
Machine eats it,
you owe me double.
We'll see.
I work part-time at the Swiftee.
Going to night school
to become a veterinarian.
Tough, though, you know ?
You knew Ed
from the store, Shelly ?
He worked up the street, used to
come in for coffee and smokes.
Seemed like a nice guy.
You said that he fixed
your car ?
It was always breaking down.
He knew I was on a tight budget,
so he'd cut me a break and
then I'd give him free refills.
Ed come in to use
the ATM a lot ?
Sometimes. Just coffee that night, though.
He'd just moved back to Fishtown.
He seem okay to you
when he left the store ?
I think he was a little embarrassed
about losing all that money.
Can't believe somebody
would shoot him.
Sweet guy, you know ?
I can only offer
financial advice, Detective.
Most of my clients take it.
Mr.Dubinski was an exception.
An $8 million exception.
5.2 after taking the lump sum.
3 million after taxes.
Another million down on a
house with property tax due.
And the rest went to whomever
had their hand out first.
How'd you get hooked up
with Ed, Mr.Weaver ?
Well, I get most of my clients
through referral,
but Mr.Dubinski found me
in theYellow Pages.
You draw up a will for him ?
Well,I set him up with an attorney
to handle it,
but he was killed before
the scheduled appointment.
So any money would've gone to... ?
His sister, now stuck with probate.
But I'd be surprised if there's
enough to cover his funeral expenses.
We'll need to take a look at
all of his financial records.
Look,Detective,I regret I
couldn't help him more than I did.
But a fool and his money
are easily parted.
My little brother practically
grew up in this store.
Always tinkering with something.
Marty taught him how to fix things.
How he got so good with cars.
Anyone you know had a problem
with Ed ?
No. Everybody loved him ;
he was like a big kid.
If anything killed Ed,
it was that damn lottery.
The lottery killed Ed ?
We never had any money
when we were growing up.
It was all just too much.
His face gets on TV,
and all of a sudden
he's surrounded by a bunch of phonies
taking advantage of him.
Any in particular you remember ?
I didn't know any of them.
Too many freeloaders to count.
Well, hard to believe how fast
he burned through all that cash.
I tried to get him to do something
constructive with it,
but it was like, like the money
wasn't real to him.
Cleaned out his apartment,
there was nothing but bills left.
And this probate thing
is still a mess.
I'd like to get copies of Ed's
probate papers if that's okay.
However I can help.
Is Ed the kind of guy that'd give
out his ATM card or PIN number ?
Maybe. Ed trusted everybody...
generous to a fault.
Problem was,he just... couldn't say no.
"Chelsea dagger"
by The Fratellis.
Hey,hey, you guys check
out the bathrooms ?
All-black porcelain and gold fixtures.
Plasma TVs in every one. Huh ?
Oh,it's,uh,it's really something,Ed.
Are those, uh, a pinball
machines over there ?
Yeah !
I used to get up everyday
to fix cars,
now I just play pinball all day.
Pammy, you remember when we were
kids when we went to Atlantic City ?
And then we just like
played all day.
Of course I remember,Ed.Yeah.
Do you know all these people ?
Sure,they're all my friends.
Just hope you're not spending
too much money.
Oh, hey, that reminds me.I got,I
got something special for you guys.
No, open it. Open it.
The Atlantic City boardwalk.
It's 50,000 !
I owe you,Pam.
Ed,you know you don't owe me a thing.
Thanks.
You're the best, bud. Thanks.
If you guys need anything else,
you just let me know,okay.
Smokey One-Niner,
this is Rubber Duck!
Your presence is requested
outside on the double.
Oh, dude. Sounds like
my ride just got here.
Hey, come on. Come on !
Yeah !
Oh, hello, pretty car.
This is awesome !
How much this car cost, Ed ?
Who cares ? Look at it !
Old Georgie wasn't laughing
too hard when his buzz wore off.
George Sweeney, from the garage ?
Yeah, the two of them were...
like kids in a candy store.
Used to be good friends.
Sounds like he handed
out a lot of checks.
We didn't need it,but
we put it to good use...
something I wish that
Ed would have done.
Now, George Sweeney filed a two
million-dollar lawsuit against Ed.
Hired that ambulance chaser
with those late-night TV ads.
The "King of Compensation."
Any record of a trial
or a settlement ?
Looks like it was dismissed.
George still works at
the auto shop in Fishtown.
Near where Ed was killed.
Yeah, maybe old George figured out
Ed's PIN number,
thought he was still due
a nice settlement.
What do you got ?
Figure out how the code's personal, we figure
out how the shooter could have known it.
Run Ed's personal info ?
Old phone numbers, addresses,
friends' birthdays, social numbers,
you name it.
- Nothing yet. / - We get any paperwork
from the money manager ?
Eight million dollars of it.
Saw the latest jackpot
just went up to $33 million.
Nick sucked you in on that pool ?
33 will pay for a lot
of old Blue Note vinyl.
How about you, boss ?
Got a better chance of
winning "American Idol".
First try, sucker.
Knew it had to be
either Flyers or boobies.
That's gonna leave a mark.
A little jumpy, George, or
you just naturally clumsy ?
What's this all about, guys ?
Ed Dubinski... you took a dive
on his property.
Ed was my friend.
Is that why you sued him ?
I had a lot of medical bills.
I just needed Ed's insurance
to pay up.
- It wasn't personal.
- Oh,sure it was.
You go back to rebuild
transmissions.
He goes off to spend his millions.
No, I was... I was happy for Ed.
Look, I... I was his friend
before he won that money,
and I was still his
friend after he lost it.
How did you know
he lost it all, George ?
Why else would you
move back to Fishtown ?
- You own a gun, George ?
- No, no, no.
I never asked Ed
for a thing, but,
I mean, you win a lotto
like that,
you never know who's gonna come
crawling out of the woodwork.
"Flashback"
by The Twilight Singers.
To the good life.
Listen, Ed...
I feel real bad about that
shark lawyer bugging you.
Yeah, I got to say I was kind of
surprised you didn't talk to me first.
- I mean, we go way back, right ?
- I know.
I had no idea that
he was gonna sue you.
Yeah.
I talked to my insurance people.
They said that ATV accidents
aren't covered under my policy, so...
here.
25 Grands ?
That's a lot of money, Ed.
I can't take this.
George, we're like family, man.
I don't want this to come
between us. Just... just take it.
Thanks. Thanks.
I best be going.
Some of us got to go back to work.
What, Tommy threatened
to fire you ?
Told me I got to do
three clutches tomorrow.
Hey, make sure you
resurface the flywheel.
Armchair mechanic.
What can I say ? I get bored.
All right.
First one with a head shot doesn't
have to make a run for beer.
I lose myself when the
real guns came out, you know,
I knew that it was time
to get back to reality.
The hell was this crazy old codger ?
- Ed said it was his father.
- His father ?
Thought he was long gone.
Yeah, he must have heard about
Ed hitting the big money.
Came to pick up a payday.
Didn't look like he came
back to have a catch.
Jack Dubinski, Philly PD.
Open up.
I'm entertaining a friend.
Do you mind ?
Not at all.
Open up, Jack.
Come back when you got
a warrant.
Gun !
What did you do that for ?
No, you don't.
Welcome back to Philly, Jack.
Watch the back...
not my back !
That gun's gonna land
you back in prison.
How long depends on what you tell us.
What did I do now ?
For starters, you're here...
in the same town your son
got capped.
The world's a rough place.
I don't recall your daughter
telling us you were at his funeral.
I got no relationship
with my daughter.
No, you just came out of your
rat hole to shake Ed down.
A month later, your boy's dead.
Just 'cause I'm a crappy dad
don't mean I'd hurt my own blood.
Ed's old bank card got
used a couple days ago.
We turn this place upside down,
we gonna find it ?
Don't know what
you're talking about.
Why did you go see Ed, Jack ?
It wasn't a shakedown. I just...
need a little help,
get back on my feet.
"Lived in bars"
by Cat Power.
Some place you got here, Ed.
Thanks.
We like it.
Want a drink ? We got a bar.
Uh,beer is fine.
Hey, can we get two beers, baby ?
You remember Nikki ?
Engaged, huh ?
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Might want to keep
an eye on her.
What do you mean ?
One thing I know about women
who've got one hand on your wallet
and one foot out the door.
No risk, no reward, right ?
I must have got that from you.
Why I kept playing the
numbers all these years.
Blew through my share of cash, too.
Wished I'd put some aside,
looked out more for you.
Pam took care of me.
And Marty.
How is your sister ?
She'd be surprised to see you.
- Yeah.
- I know I was.
I'm sorry I wasn't there
for you, kid.
But we have plenty of time
to catch up now, don't we ?
Sure.Yeah, I'd like that.
All right.
Hey,I got something for you.
It's a... it's a French circus
Nikki's been wanting to see.
We're driving over
to Atlantic City tonight.
Hoping you could join us.
It sounds like fun.
Yeah,I thought, like, afterwards,
we go to the boardwalk,
like when Pam and me were kids.
And then we could go play pinball
and go over to that museum,
you know,the one with the...
with the mermaid in it.
Yeah,sure, Ed, listen...
uh, about that thing...
What, Dad ?
We talked about it before.
Thanks, son.
Don't worry,
I promise to pay you back.
Ed didn't like what I said
about his lady,
but he sort of knew
I was right.
So, where were you
the night Ed got shot ?
St.Joe's. The hospital,
getting prepped for surgery.
Surgery ?
Fused vertebrae so I can work again.
Ed's money saved my life.
Finally able to hold down a job.
Another Hallmark moment
in the Dubinski clan.
Yeah, we talked about...
keeping in touch,
but it just wasn't gonna happen.
Maybe you could call your daughter,
see if she'll bail you out.
Upsy daisy.
"Riskey," with an E.
Why ? Guy's a mechanic, not a
spelling bee champ. Put it in.
Satisfied ?
Not until I get everybody in the pool.
Know what the jackpot's worth ?
Enough to get me a down
payment on a Main Line mansion.
Walk-in closet...
full of high-heel shoes.
More tickets we get,
the better our chances.
Mama could use a new pair
of shoes.
Going through the
probate papers, found this :
a Nikki Dubinski opened
a credit card
using Ed's name and social.
Week before he died.
Ed's fiancee...
they ever married ?
Well, looks like she was enjoying
an extended stay at the Four Seasons
when he found out
about the card.
Froze the account, and she was
arrested for credit card fraud.
Nikki Dubinski, Nicole Atkins,
Nikki von Haven. Quite a sheet.
Fraud charges were dropped
after Ed's murder.
Lucky lady. Know where she is ?
Faxed her photo to a few
of the high-end hotels
and just got a call back
from the Hardtmore.
The concierge recognized her
as one of the ladies on
the four-star lounge bar circuit.
Oh... happy hunting for
her next millionaire.
Macallan 18, neat.
Old school Scotch man.
I like that.
Nicole Gillette.
Pleased to meet you.
John Stillman...
the pleasure is mine.
I'm thinking finance or
pharmaceuticals.
Close ?
Not quite.
Try not to make a scene, Nikki.
Hate to snatch you up out of here in
front of all these nice, rich people.
Oh,my.
I see three different names, Nikki.
What's the matter, fellas,
slow night in Killadelphia ?
Ed Dubinski. Your late fiance ?
I'm aware.
Someone used his ATM
card looking for money.
A little pillow talk,
figured you knew his PIN.
I don't know anything
about that or Ed's murder.
Do I look like a killer ?
Takes all kinds... even pretty ones.
Look, Ed knew the deal.
He enjoyed my company,
but we both knew
it wasn't built to last.
Two guys out front just repoed
your little race car, Ed.
Really ?
What, you don't care ? You got
checks bouncing all over town.
Hell, the pool boy even quit.
Is that before or after
you slept with him ?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
I know how this works, Nikki.
It's been a good ride,
but it's time for me to get off.
No, it's time for you
to get off your duff, Ed.
Get it together and
figure out what you want.
You know what, you're right.
I want you to keep the ring.
So, that's it ?
It's time for me to
get my house in order.
Well, I'd start by paying
your property tax bill.
It's three months late.
I don't know which
was worse, Nikki...
winning the lotto or meeting you.
That was the beginning
of the end for Ed.
Went into a tailspin when he
couldn't buy his daddy's love.
Evidently yours, neither.
What happened to the rest
of Ed's money ?
He was all but broke by the time
he moved back to Fishtown
with his tail between his legs.
Where were you
the night Ed was shot ?
With a lawyer from Chestnut Hill.
I'd call him at work.
His wife's a real bitch
on wheels.
Found some big gaps
in Weaver's paperwork.
Yeah ? How so ?
For one thing, he charged
him 20% off the top.
20% ?! He should have just
hit the guy over the head.
And Weaver only put the minimum
down on all of Ed's hard assets.
His house, his car.
To put the cash into bonds ?
Or so he said,
but it looks like he was moving money
in and out of his accounts.
Using Ed's money as a float.
Maybe to shore up
other clients' accounts?
Robbing Peter to pay Paul.
I checked with the Board of Standards
for certified financial planners.
Ed filed a formal grievance against
Weaver just before his murder.
Could have taken away Weaver's license.
A/V unit found something else.
Check it out.
Also found him with three other
Powerball winners around the state.
Lottery millionaires were his racket.
Johnny on the spot.
Makes you wonder how
he keeps getting there first.
You know what I'd get ?
A new Bugatti.
It's mad torque, over 600 ponies.
Only built 300 of them.
Well, you ain't getting boo-gatti
'cause you didn't pony up for the pool.
What ? What ?
It's not too late, is it ?
Sorry, pal. Next time.
Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Hey, hey ,hey, here, come on.
Well...
Nice.
What the hell ?
Look at this.
Are you serious ?
Punkass bitch !
Punkass bitch ?
You do this to my car, pal ?
You the guy that been calling me ?
Oh, man, you guys are cops ?
Yeah, you got two seconds before you
catch the beating of your life, moron.
What is your problem, man ?
My problem ?
He slept with my wife.
- What ?
- Who's your wife ?
Frankie. She's my wife.
What a racket you get going, Roger.
We found the lottery official
who had been feeding you names
and addresses of the latest winners.
Gerald Malone.
Just lost his job.
But he is willing to testify that
you paid him for the referrals.
I don't believe this.
Working stiff like Ed never had a
chance with your paws on his money.
I have been a certified financial
planner for over 15 years.
Certified scam artist.
Securing bad loans,
making a mess of his money.
But no bailout for Ed.
He had to file a grievance
with the board.
You would have lost your license.
He was gonna have you prosecuted.
But a guy like you would
never let that happen.
What's, what's going on ?
You think that I had something
to do with Ed's murder ?
I'm sure the DA would find your attempt
to cover up fraud and larceny
pretty compelling motive, Roger.
This is ridiculous.I didn't kill Ed.
He almost killed me.
You got to take the long view, Ed.
Now, the market, it
took an unexpected turn.
Your investments are
down for the moment.
They're gonna rebound at some juncture.
- How long ?
- Hard to say.
Five, maybe ten years.
But...but I ... I still
got some money, right ?
Well, cash flow's a
little light right now.
No more toys for a while.
Uh, my house, my car...
is that some...
Well, the good news is that we can use
the equity left in your house
to pay off the rest of your debts.
And, uh, thanks to me, you
still have your old apartment.
- Thanks to you ?
- Yeah.
I held the lease termination,
just in case you needed
someplace to go back to.
Now, most people aren't as lucky.
Lucky ? You call this lucky ?
Back to square one is
what it's looking like.
Ah, come on, Ed. That's a
cynical way of looking at it...
Shut up !
I just,uh... I want to know... I
I want to know how much money I have
in the bank right now, this very second.
Around $100,000,
but I wouldn't recommend
touching that money right now, Ed.
I'm gonna fix this.
Come on, let's go. Now.
What ? Where ?
You're going downstairs with me
to the bank so I can get my money.
100 grand in cash ?
He put it in the briefcase.
Just walked right out of the bank.
Couple days later,
I heard he was shot.
Where were you that night ?
I had to meet a new client,
Suzanne McGee.
Lottery winner from Allentown.
Curious.You even feel anything
after hosing a guy like that ?
Let's be honest, Detective.
Wasn't like he earned it.
Called the IRS and the SEC.
They'd like to have
a little talk with you
about all the money
you earned, Roger.
Met a guy last night,
says he knows you.
- Guy who knows me ?
- Yeah. Your husband, Billy.
You're kidding me.
Wish I was.
We're separated.
We have been for a while.
Does he know that ?
What happened ?
He jumped me outside
of Jones, Frankie.
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
But you're okay ?
Did you hurt him ?
When were you planning
on telling me about this ?
I mean, that's why you're
staying at the hotel, ain't it ?
Look, it's over.
We're just working some stuff out.
Oh, this isn't gonna be a problem,
is it ?
I'm thinking, yeah.
So... So, we're off for tonight ?
No, Detective Jeffries is not here.
What time's the kid
getting arraigned ?
Valentine ? Got it.
I'll make sure he gets it.
Money goes to the schools, right ?
Sure, boss.
Could also buy a hell of a boat.
Aloha.
Where are we
on Ed's missing cash ?
Well, checked all bank accounts,
safety deposit boxes.
Even Ed's old locker at the auto garage.
No briefcase, no money.
Just got off the phone
with his landlord.
Said a woman was rooting
around Ed's storage unit
in the parking garage
the day of the shooting.
Get a description ?
Medium height, brown hair,
mid-twenties.
Wearing a SwiftMart uniform.
Thought you just knew
Ed from the store, Shelly.
Uh,well,yeah.
I mean, he used to come
in there all the time.
So what were you doing at his place,
rummaging around his storage unit ?
What ? I wasn't rummaging.
What were you looking for ?
I was just... nothing.
I was returning his bike.
He let me borrow it.
His bike ?
Yeah.He lent it to me
'cause my car broke down.
He gave me the key
to his storage unit.
- When was this ?
- The day before.
I had no way to get to class
after work.
Really ?
He lend you his bank card, too ?
What ? No.
I dropped my car off
at the shop,
and George told me that Ed
had just moved back.
I heard what happened to him,
so I stopped by to cheer him up.
"Two" by Ryan Adams.
Shelly.
Can I come in ?
Oh, yeah. Uh, come on in. Sorry.
Heard you were back.
Just wanted to stop by and say hello.
Brought you some cupcakes.
Cupcakes.
Hey, um, do you want a beer ?
Sure.
Figured you could use
some cheering up.
First, thought maybe I'd bring you
a dog from the animal shelter.
Yeah. I'll stick with the cupcakes.
Oh, you don't like animals ?
No, I... I, uh... I do.
I had a dog when I was a kid.
Oh, yeah ? What kind ?
Just a mutt.
We named him after that weird museum
on the Boardwalk in Atlantic City.
- Ripley ?
- Yeah.
Yeah, he was always happy
to see you.
Oh, yeah, mutts are the best.
Never let you down,
less disease.
But when he did get sick,
you know, we just...
we just didn't have the
money to take him to a vet.
That's what you want
to do, right, be a vet ?
Trying. It's hard. You know, going
to school and holding down a job.
Yeah.
How's your... How's your car ?
Worse.
It's making this horrible noise.
Right when you turn it on ?
Yeah, it's like it's screaming
in pain.
Yeah. Probably just a belt.
Drop it off at the shop ?
Oh, I did, but they said they
didn't know what was wrong with it.
It's just dying, but I
can't afford a new one.
I can fix it.
Oh, I thought you were done
with that place.
I'll just call Tommy.
I mean, he's always looking
for a good mechanic.
Yeah, me, too.
I mean, um... if that's
what you want to do.
Yeah.
I sure is.
Thanks,Shelly.
Why are you thanking me ?
Ed left me a message to pick up my car.
The garage said I owed
them two grand for the work.
Told them, no thanks.
I'll take the bus.
Ed happen to mention if
he had any money left ?
No, and I didn't ask him.
Honestly... I think he
was glad to be rid of it.
You see what I see ?
Ripley.
Man's best friend.
Ed's childhood dog.
Dear old sis figured out
his PIN number ?
That, or she knew it all along.
We hope you could enlightened us
on how Ed's probate works, Pam.
Wish I could. It's been such
a headache.
Been almost two years since Ed died,
and it still isn't closed ?
It's so frustrating, but first,
they have to close out all his accounts.
So it's possible that
there's an active account still out there
in Ed's name with money in it ?
I don't think so. I don't know.
You're not even curious ?
I mean,you've waited so long.
What are you talking about ?
You remember the name of the
dog you and Ed had as kids ?
Our dog ? You mean Ripley ?
Ripley. That's it.
Yeah. Great name.
Of course. I brought him home
for Ed after our dad took off.
Ed loved that dog.
Even used his name for a PIN number.
But you already knew that.
What ? Wait a minute.
I... I don't...
Looked into your hardware store.
The bank's got a lien on it.
Marty and I have had
some debt issues.
Say, your real estate venture.
Loft conversions, wasn't it ?
Yeah, that market went
south after Ed died.
You slog through two long years
waiting for Ed's probate
to close.
His debts get paid off,
and you're still left with nothing.
How's that happen ?
Eight million to zero in six months.
What is this ?
I mean, I'd be dying to check
the balance of that last
outstanding account, too.
Especially if I had Ed's bank card.
No.
I loved my brother.
We... argued over money,
but we were still family.
We're converting each
floor into a loft space.
The kitchen will go here.
And the living room...
will go here.
It looks really, really good, Pam.
Yeah.
Good luck.
Ran into a little bad luck, Ed.
That's why I asked you here.
Marty miscalculated a
couple things in the budget.
But with your help,we can still get
these lofts completed on schedule.
What happened to the check
I gave Marty three weeks ago ?
The other 50,000 ?
I didn't know about that.
I'm sorry, Pam. I just can't
invest any more money in this.
You spent $150,000 on a race car,
and you won't help us out
with a real investment ?
The car was stupid.
Blowing all that cash,
but so is trying to solve
erybody else's problems.
Everyone else ?
It just complicates things, Pam.
In a bad way.
You're right. I'm sorry.
- Don't worry about us.
- Yeah ?
You guys are going to be all right ?
Yeah. Of course.
- Okay.
- We have other options.
Business line of credit,
home equity line, yeah.
We'll be fine.
Question is,
are you going to be okay ?
Yeah.
I'm just trying to get
back to where I started.
Are you completely broke, Ed ?
Hey, I got my old job back.
I think everything's going
to work out all right.
I was so embarrassed.
It's hard enough to
ask someone for money.
It must've been even harder
for Ed to turn us down.
So your husband never told you
he had already hit Ed up
for $50,000 ?
Marty got in over his head.
He'd shut down whenever
I brought up money.
This is a consent form.
It allows us to search your store.
The store ? I don't understand.
Well,it would just help us to
clear both you and your husband.
Marty ?
But that's ridiculous.
You don't think for a minute
that Marty...
Do I need a lawyer ?
Only if you have something to hide.
That's a filthy habit, Marty.
I had a girlfriend,
chewed her nails.
It drove me crazy.
Yeah, I guess,you take
it all on yourself, huh ?
Running a business,
paying the bills...
Why am I here, Detective ?
I'm just saying, if I got
myself into money trouble,
I'd have a chat with the little lady.
You know, not be a coward
about it, that's all.
I know how to handle my
own business, thank you.
Is that why your wife had to go
beg her brother for more money ?
- After you ?
- Pam told you that ?
Also said you screwed up big
time on that loft project.
No, we just need enough to get started
with the construction, that's it.
He already gave you a hundred-K.
Hell, I'd have turned you down, too.
A hundred thousand was nothing !
He had eight million.
Did you even like your
brother-in-law, Marty ?
Yeah, I did.
I loved Ed.
I treated him like he was my own.
And he repaid you by saying
"no" when you needed him most.
- Are we finished here ?
- Sit down !
Where were you night
Ed got shot ?
Where I am every night.
Home with Pam.
Ask her.
He was with me, watching TV.
- Thank you.
- Watching what ?
I don't know, um...
Wheel of Fortune.
The rest of the night ?
And Marty never went out ?
I mean, um...
Sometimes he went back
to the store to close... to clean up;
you know, to make sure
it was locked up.
Oh, so he left to go back
to the store that night ?
I don't know. I don't know.
I can't remember.
You remember
what you were watching,
but you don't remember
if he went out ?
Where's, where is Marty ?
I need to talk to him.
How did he react when you told him that
Ed wasn't going to give you the money ?
He must've been angry,
wasn't he ?
What ? No. No, it wasn't like that.
Oh, everything you did for him,
raised him when your father
couldn't be bothered.
We did what was right.
What we had to do.
But Ed didn't. Did he ?
The fact that you had to,
you know, even ask for money ?
Marty had a right to be upset.
No. No, Marty loved Ed.
He was my brother.
Got it.
$8 million.
Oh, jeez. Marty, you scared me.
Wait, wait...
what are you doing here ?
Did you really tell Pam
you won't help us out, Ed ?
Come on, Marty, I'm done
talking about money.
Do you know how hard it
was to ask you for that ?
Marty, I'm sorry. I can't pay
for your business mistakes.
My mistakes ?
We had to delay construction, because
your sister didn't get the permits.
I don't know what to tell you.
We might lose the store.
- What ?
- The store, Ed !
Where you grew up !
Does that mean anything to you ?
Pam didn't say anything about that.
I just... I don't get it,man.
I mean, after all we did for you.
All the sacrifices we made for you.
Look, I'm sorry, Marty.
I can't give you the money.
I don't have it.
I don't believe you.
What are you doing ?
I'm sorry, Eddie. The money's coming
to us whether you're dead or alive.
No, it's not, 'cause it's all gone.
That's not true !
I gave to someone
who deserved it.
The only person who
didn't ask me for it...
Well, it turns out, there was
more money out there, Pam.
Shame you'll never see it.
Where did you get this ?
Your dresser drawer.
The search consent you
signed was also for your home.
- Marty...
- No.
Not Marty.
You.
You knew the PIN number.
The card's going to have
your prints all over it.
You waited so long,
you finally just had to check
that account, didn't you ?
I didn't shoot my brother.
No, you sent your husband
to do the dirty work,
then you tried to throw him
under the bus.
How dare you...
All you did for Ed,
all those years.
How could he just blow it all ?
Even gave some to your father.
- No, he didn't.
- Oh, yes he did, Pam.
Somehow he cared more
about Jack than you.
My father was a bum.
Without me, they would've
put Ed into the system.
He was eight years old.
And the one time you came to him,
he turned you down.
I was his sister.
And he owed me !
...to someone who deserved it.
The only person who
didn't ask me for it...
It's over.
I'm sorry
"On the way back home"
by Lucero
* So young and so hungry,
so unqualified *
* Don't want the jobs anyways
,no settled life *
* To get out of here,
two options, one chance *
* You joined the army
and I started a band *
* We'll meet at the bar,
we'll buy us a round *
* We'll toast that we're back home *
* We'll toast this damn town *
* Annie's still working behind the bar *
* You can buy her a drink,
I'll sleep in the car *
* Well, let's go *
* It's on the way back home *
* We'll be there soon
* We'll be there soon *
* One of two choices *
* I guess I've made mine *
* I drink in a different
town nearly every night *
* And now you don't drink
for months at a time *
....................
* I owe you a couple rounds,
we're back home tonight *
* We'll meet at the bar,
we'll drink to old times *
* We'll toast that we're back
home and those left behind *
* Annie's still working behind the bar *
* You can buy her a drink
and I'll sleep in the car *
* Let's go *
* It's on the way back home *
* It's on the way back home tonight *
* We'll be there soon *
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly
Presents