the following story is fictional
and does not depict any actual person or event
"Corduroy" by Pearl Jam
I can see from down there
that you have not shaved.
Why is that ?
Why are you staring at me ?
Do you think I am attractive ?
You better tuck in that bottom lip.
Double time and down to the quad.
Is that understand ?
Sir, yes, sir !
Go !
****************
Caretaker relocating graves
came across a bastard coffin.
No headstone.
Perfect place to bury a body.
CSU found a duffel bag
and personal items buried
underneath the box.
Idiot bag.
Bears a book of knowledge
to be worn by knobs at all times.
- Knobs ?
- First-year cadets,
military school.
Shave their heads to look like knobs.
Well, this knob got a name ?
ID says Kate Butler.
Parents reported her missing
three years ago from...
Pennsylvania Military Institute.
Oh, I remember this girl.
One of the first females
admitted to PMI.
It took a lot of guts.
PMI. That's in what,
Bucks County ?
How she wind up out here ?
Weekend leave in the city ?
Except this box is a
military footlocker.
Issued by the school.
Fractured skull,
possible blunt-force trauma.
Could be our murder weapon
right here...
seven-pound hand weight
with her initials on it.
Yeah, we'll have those
examined for blood or hair.
Corroded laptop, clothes.
Made it look like she ran away.
Got her in there without
cutting up the body.
Had to be before rigor set in.
So she's murdered on campus,
stuffed in a footlocker.
Driven all the way out here,
30 miles away ?
Hoping it would never
get tied back to the school.
Well, it just did.
Cold Case
Season 6 Episode 22
Transcript VO : www.ydy.com
The Long Blue Line
All-male for 162 years.
Well, mid -'90s,
Justice Department forced
almost every state military academy
to admit qualified female
applicants.
Even Valley Forge and
the Citadel are coed now.
PMI was one of the last holdouts
till four years ago.
Can't believethis is still an issue.
Male institutions dragging
their feet to admit women ?
Yeah, glad that's behind us.
Next thing you know, they'll
start letting 'em be detectives.
Kate Butler was
one of two female cadets
who entered PMI
in the fall of '05.
Missing clothes, laptop.
Assigned figured she ran away.
Well, the body changes all that.
What happened to the other girl ?
Courtney Gaines. Went into
the infirmary after the first day,
gone within a week.
Butler almost made it
to Thanksgiving.
School reported her missing
when she didn't show up
for chapel on Sunday morning.
Campus computer system
had her swiping out her ID card
at the front gate night before, 8:26 p.m.
Well, ID was found with the body.
Possible her killer swiped
her card on the way out ?
Used the footlocker to get
the body off campus,
but he still needed a car.
I'll look into parking permits.
Victim's father's downstairs,
just coming from the morgue.
Mother's on her way in now.
Separated when they lost their daughter.
Autopsy report.
ME confirmed blunt-force trauma.
Kate's hand weight
matched the contusion.
Could have been killed in her own room.
Had a stress fracture in her pelvis.
Undetermined cause.
Possible sexual assault ?
I'll check the PMI infirmary records.
Latest from the crime scene.
Thanks. How you doing ?
Billy moved out this morning.
Finally asked him for a divorce.
I didn't know
you were gonna do that.
Ah, I know, right ?
Time to move on.
Yeah.
- So, um, see you around ?
- Yeah, sure. Yeah.
Still have her room
the way it was.
Every time the phone rang,
a little part of me...
hoping it was her, you know ?
We're thinking she may have been
killed on campus, Mrs. Butler.
Have you informed her father yet ?
He's handling the identification.
Nothing he loved more
than that school.
Lot of folks have a problem
with her attending PMI ?
Including her own father.
He never wanted Kate to go
there in the first place.
His alma mater.
She was just as stubborn as he was.
Force of her own.
Never even told us
she was applying
till after she was accepted.
Mr. Butler was concerned
for her safety ?
Concern for his daughter ?
You'd have to ask him.
Graduated in '78
before I got my commission.
I went to PMI because
that's where my father went.
His father before him.
Footlocker we found her body in
was from PMI, Mr. Butler.
I think that's how the killer
got her body off campus.
I don't want Charlotte to
ever see those pictures.
So, how she holding up ?
Well, she said you never wanted
Kate to go to PMI,
that you had a difficult relationship
with your daughter.
I knew what she was gonna
be up against.
She did it to prove me wrong.
Her mother blamed me
for what happened.
Why would she blame you ?
She didn't tell you ?
Kate would have done anything
for her father,
but you don't defy Hank Butler.
She'd made up her mind.
I always sided with my husband,
but there comes a time when a child
needs more than just tough love.
"Come Back" by Pearl Jam
Hank ?
Your daughter's going off
to college.
Do you intend to say good-bye
to her ?
Dadd That I feel I know you
don't want me to do this.
I just want you to know...
I'm not gonna let you down.
Good-bye, Daddy.
If you can't hack it,
don't bother coming home.
Do you think that was...
an ultimatum or
a means of motivation ?
Either way,
I always thought it was the reason
my baby never came back.
Blamed your husband for that.
Kate didn't need any
more people against her.
This is all the hate mail she got
before she even set foot
on campus.
Did you show these
to the police before ?
They said they looked into it.
They told us that she ran away.
I guess that's not true now, is it ?
Did you talk
to Commandant Murillo ?
We will.
Thanks for coming in, M. Butler.
Sure.
You better find the son of a
bitch who did this before I do.
When Cadet Butler didn't return
to campus,
we assumed that she'd eventually
show up on her parents' doorstep.
Got new information indicates she
may have been killed on campus.
I find that hard to believe.
First year is difficult,
but we have standards of safety
for all cadets,
male or female.
But there are no female cadets
presently enrolled ?
Yes, well, it's a rather
limited applicant pool.
Maybe if you put a woman
on your brochure,
see what happens.
Gonna need access to
all school records and grounds.
I've been ordered to give
you whatever you need.
Cadet Gardner here
will show you to Moe.
He's my Operations Officer.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Attention on the quad !
All hail the Commandant.
Saw a bumper sticker on the lot.
God, country and PMI.
Gotta figure the Commandant's
next on that list.
Thought they were supposed
to look straight ahead.
Sir, not every day a pretty blonde
walks across campus, sir.
Of course I remember
Kate Butler.
It was my job to implement
the necessary changes
to accommodate female cadets
on campus.
I don't think these were the
accommodations she had in mind.
Got a way to track
that footlocker, Moe ?
Please.
Two in every room,
but we don't assign them
to any particular cadet.
One goes missing,
who requisitions a replacement ?
No inventory.
We just replace them as they fall apart
at the end of the year.
Must be thousands of them.
Sounds odd for a place that
keeps such meticulous records.
Like the computer log
you supplied back in '05.
Showed the exact time
Kate left campus.
It goes into a computer any time a cadet
swipes their ID at the front gate.
On or off campus.
We're gonna need
a list of registered cars
and parking permits that year.
Infirmary records,any injuries
Kate may have incurred.
Whatever you need.
- Lawrence.
- Yes, Major.
You know if Kate had any
problems with another cadet ?
Every fourth class cadet
has a rough go of it.
More a function of being a knob.
It's not personal.
What about the function
of being a girl ?
That get personal ?
Well, she never filed a complaint.
Look, I'd be lying to you to say
there wasn't resentment
among some of the cadets.
Why ? She get special consideration ?
It didn't matter much.
That girl was determined
to be one of the guys.
"Who You Are" by Pearl Jam
Major, it is still too long.
How short do you want it,
Commandant ?
I have no idea.
She still looks like a girl.
With all due respect, sir,
she is a girl.
And we don't have a female precedent.
Courtney. Don't.
Don't what ?
Well, keep cutting
till we find one.
I'm gonna be a knob,
I might as well look like one.
Still, cutting your hair doesn't mean
you can cut the mustard here at PMI.
This program is just too
demanding for most women.
- Kate have a boyfriend on campus ?
- No, ma'am.
We instituted a non-fraternization
policy
the year women were admitted.
Yeah, 'cause those always work.
Damned if you do,
damned if you don't, Detective.
We'd like to see her room.
- Lawrence, show them the barracks.
- Yes, sir.
"A cadet shall not lie, cheat, or steal,
nor shall he tolerate those who do."
Honor code. Noticed they
got one in every building.
Single sanction policy, ma'am.
One violation gets you drummed out.
Pretty strict code
for most mortals.
That's why on the eighth day,
God created PMI.
This the only dorm room
with a lock on the door ?
Yes, sir, first one
installed in school history.
Along with a special latrine
bathroom for women down the hall.
Room's been unoccupied
since Cadet Butler
and the other girl left.
The other girl ?
Courtney Gaines ?
Yes, ma'am, non-hacker.
Cadet Butler only shared
a room the first week.
Tell the commandant this
is now a crime scene.
Yes, sir.
I think it's time we
talk to Courtney Gaines.
I transferred to Bryn Mawr
my freshman year
to major in women's studies.
Quite a contrast, going from an all-male
military academy
to a women's college, Courtney.
I'm writing my senior thesis on
the merits of single-sex education.
Which one ?
Women's colleges only graduate 4%
of the country's female students
but they produce 25%
of the female board members
of Fortune 500 companies,
50% of the women in Congress.
I know where my daughter's going.
How did you get along with Kate ?
Oh, she was a great girl,
tried to help me.
I thought going to a school
like PMI would be empowering.
Instead I spent half my
time in the infirmary.
- What happened ?
- Hell Week.
Marching, pushups, more marching.
Suffered a stress fracture in my pelvis.
Kate had the same injury.
Women's legs are shorter
so, we have t take longer stride
to keep up,
but the physical abuse
was nothing
compared to
the psychological assault.
Maybe 'cause
Kate's father went there,
she was more prepared.
She knew how to survive.
Actually, neither one of you
survived the school.
But at least you're still
sitting here.
What do you mean ?
Kate's body just turned up
in a cemetery.
Oh, my God.
Anyone in particular you can remember
gunning for her, Courtney ?
Yeah, I do.
He hated both of us on sight.
I'll never forget his face.
In what year was my beloved
institution founded ?
Fatbody ?
Sir, Eighteen-forty...
something, sir.
Cadet "Chucklehead"
has just desecrated the very ground
upon which you worthless knobs stand.
For that, you owe me 20
more pushups.
Eat floor, knobs ! Exercise !
What we obtain too cheap,
we esteem too lightly.
Come on. Get up. You can do it.
You can hack it !
I can't... can't do it.
This ain't yoga class,
downward dog !
Get your ass out of the air
and do a man's pushup !
You gonna spend another night crying
in the infirmary, Cadet "Useless" ?
That's what I thought.
You all right ?
Shut up. Don't even look at me
before he comes over here and...
"Eight-Ball", did you just blow
chunks on my fine quadrangle ?
Sir, yes, sir ! Sorry, sir.
Are you suggesting
that my mess hall
doesn't quite measure up
to your mama's home cooking ?
Do you need a bib ?!
Sir, no, sir !
How about you, Sinead ?
You wanna gimme some tears ?
Make me feel sorry for you ?
Sir, no, sir !
You see this ring ?
You think I busted my ass
for three long years
just to see them give it away to a
bunch of sports bra-wearing pantywaists ?
Only way you're getting one
is through me,
and that ain't gonna happen.
Sergeant James Addison.
Still have nightmares about that guy.
Made it clear it was you or him.
The day I walked out,
every guy in the place cheered.
Kate stayed.
God knows why.
Did Addison threaten you
personally ?
Visited me in the infirmary.
Told me to leave now and walk
out through the front gates...
or be carried out in a box.
First Lieutenant James Addison ?
I help you ?
Detectives Rush, Valens.
Philly Homicide.
You're here about Cadet Butler.
Word travels fast.
Graduated two years ago.
Still hanging around ?
Grad program, engenering.
Finished my first tour in Afghanistan.
Get free room
as resident hall director.
How well did you know Kate ?
I was part of the Echo Company cadre.
Saw her every day during Hell Week.
Not much after that.
I heard you took special pride
in racking knobs,
especially the female kind.
Made it your mission to run them off.
Guess it worked.
I didn't treat the women
different than any other knob.
Courtney Gaines says otherwise.
Hell, yeah, I tried to run 'em out,
tried to run 'em all out.
It was my job.
Break down the individual,
build up the group ?
Whiny maggots call it hazing.
I call it natural selection.
But then, Courtney was no Kate Butler.
What was different about Cadet Butler ?
She understood what it took to
earn the respect of her peers.
How'd Butler rank first
in the two-mile run ?
She finished sixth.
Called gender-norming, "Chucklehead".
Women automatically get two
minutes shaved off their time.
What, one for each knocker ?
You're up first, you gaudy smack !
Get on that bar and
give me ten pull-ups.
Yes, sir !
You have got
to be kidding me, fish !
Only girls and gumps
do the flexed arm hang.
Hold it right there, Gomer.
Get up there, Butler.
Sir, yes, sir.
Let's see if you girls
can hang for a full minute.
Let the girl beat you ?!
Come on ! Pull it up !
You are a no-go at
this station, Stewart !
Get off my bar, you fat tub of goo !
- Get back in formation.
- Sir, yes, sir.
Butler knew that as long as
there was gender-norming,
she'd never be equal.
Had to respect the effort.
Even if "Rhianna" never lived it down.
"Rhianna" ?
That's what they called
Ryan after Kate smoked him.
Drove the kid nuts.
Where's this "Rhianna" now ?
First class cadet. Senior.
His folks live upstate.
Went home to visit.
Due back tomorrow before first call.
Is that a sign-out sheet ?
Yeah, cadets have to
sign in and out
of the barracks on weekends.
You know, I don't mind standing
the duty.
I basically get paid to study.
Different from the ID
swipe at the front gate ?
The ID swipe's to get on and off campus.
Barracks log is for curfew purposes.
School keep track of these ?
Collected every Sunday morning,
filed over in the main office.
Remember where you were the
Saturday night Kate disappeared ?
Saturday night ?
Would have been out drinking
with the guys in Echo.
It's mandatory around here.
Good. Then you'll remember
their names.
Hey, I have Kate's medical
records from the PMI infirmary.
Usual bruises and blisters
except the 18 stitches she needed
for a gash in her hand
two weeks before she disappeared.
Little rough for regular PT.
Told the doctor on
duty she broke a bottle.
I'm thinking possible defensive wounds.
It makes you wonder why the hell
she wanted to go to this school.
Get anything from the hate mail ?
Uh, yeah, a lot of folks
with serious issues.
Here's one blowhard...
threatened to have Kate
drawn and quartered
for taking the spot of
"more qualified young men".
Postmark's from one of those office
postage machines.
Worth tracking.
Nutjob #2 thinks
Kate going to PMI
is a breach of the garden of Eden.
"He placed on the east side of the
garden of Eden angels and a flaming sword
flashing back and forth to
guard the way to the tree of life."
Well, there's six of them
with the same sword business.
All sent out on a Saturday.
It could be a cadet
off-campus on open weekends ?
Hate mail on Saturday,
chapel on Sunday.
These guys are unbelievable.
I believe it.
You're tellin' me this kind of stuff
happened to you back in the day ?
First female in Homicide.
Remember Walter Harris ?
Detective retired in '02 ?
Sure, was the Walrus.
Legend with the practical jokes.
Oh, he was funny, all right.
Had a joke for me every day.
PMS, my social life,
my ass, you name it.
You're kidding.
No ,I rolled with it 'cause
that's what you do, right ?
Even rolled with it
when he put
a centerfold with my face on it
on the fridge.
Till this one night
I'm down in the Bottom
picking up a 6'4" meth-head.
I turn around,
I got no backup.
Walter hung you out to dry.
You report his ass ?
Figured it'd only get worse.
Least I was 29.
Kate was only 18.
I'll hit PMI in the morning,
talk to Ryan Stewart.
See if "Rhianna" ever lived
his nickname down.
- Night, dollface.
- Night.
Philly Homicide.
Rise and shine, "Rhianna".
What the hell is this ?
Know you got a busy schedule.
Figured we'd talk to you
before first call.
- Remember Kate Butler ?
- Kate's dead ?
Found her in a footlocker.
You reported yours missing knob year.
I reported all my furniture missing, sir.
They used to put it out on the quad while
I was asleep, sometimes with me in it.
Where were you the night
she disappeared ?
Don't know. My room ?
Where I always was.
"Rhianna". Pretty nickname.
Cadets still call u that ?
No, not if they want to keep
their teeth, ma'am.
Kate stuck you with that name.
Dusted you off good.
Lit a fire under my ass.
I bench over 300 pounds now.
Forgive and forget ?
How sweet.
I busted my hump to make it this far.
I'm gonna graduate on time
with a ring.
Congratulations.
Kate's pushing up daisies.
Look, it wasn't... it wasn't the students
that Kate Butler had to worry about.
Who was it ?
Kate was a member
of the "Color Guard".
Most cadets,
it was a time to shine.
But Kate dreaded it...
"Rear View Mirror" by Pearl Jam
Hell you think you are,
performing with the color guard ?
You aren't fit to touch that flag.
Just trying to do my job, sir.
Yeah, well, it's bad enough
a guy's denied a place
to let some bitch like you in.
You're a disgrace to the long blue
line of men who wear this ring !
You hear me ?
The guy did the same thing
to her every single game.
There was nothing she could do about it.
She'd get in trouble if
she fell out of formation.
- Yeah, no one had her back.
- No one knew what to do.
I mean, that type of thing
didn't happen with the guys.
Loudmouth with the ring,
he alumni ?
Yes, ma'am, Jeb something.
Drunk still comes to every game.
Jebediah Buford. PMI class of '82.
Works on the tenth floor.
Genius who sent the anonymous
hate mail letter
using his office postage machine.
Just talked to Moe.
Qualified young men he was ranting about?
He's talking about his own son.
Letter from PMI admissions.
Brandon Buford,
wait-listed the same year
Kate was accepted.
Kid never got in.
Legacy or not.
Check out the Bufords'
home address on the top.
19128 Roxborough.
Four blocks from the cemetery
where Kate's body was found.
How long you work at the
Army Corps of Engineers, Jeb ?
Been serving my nation and
the public my whole life.
When you're not getting loaded
at PMI football games,
threatening girls ?
"Better lock your door at night.
With 2,500 bloodhounds
and only one bitch,
you won't make it to Thanksgiving."
What the hell is all this about ?
Your meter number is the same
as your office mailing
machine, Einstein.
No other PMI grads in your department.
Certainly not your son Brandon.
Couldn't get anywhere near the place
with a 2.2 from Roman Catholic.
Brandon was a good kid.
PMI would have straightened him out.
Woulda, coulda, shoulda.
How many DUIs he got now ?
My son was a legacy.
That used to mean something there.
You wanted that girl gone.
Hate mail is state offense, Jeb.
So I wrote one stinking letter.
Big deal.
Why you hassling me over a girl
who dropped out three years ago ?
She popped back up.
Roxborough Cemetery,
few blocks from your house.
I want a lawyer.
Why ? Got something to hide ?
Class of '82 had a tailgating party
on campus
same day Kate disappeared,
November 15, 2005.
You were there.
We're gonna give the jury
opportunity and motive.
Look, I didn't hurt that girl,
all right ?
I don't know how she
wound up in that grave.
You want to find out,
you talk to her boyfriend.
I'm sure her multicultural boyfriend
knows what happened to her.
Multicultural boyfriend
got a name ?
Don't know.
Not a lot of 'em at PMI,
shouldn't be too hard to find out.
What did you do after
the class of '82 tailgate?
Cross burning ?
I went to dinner with the same
group of alumni that I always do.
You can check.
Count on it, Jebediah.
Keith Henderson, only black cadet
in Echo Company.
Kid never spoke to Plumstead
Township Police in '05.
Better have a good excuse
for not coming forward
when she went missing.
I'll get his records,
see what I can dig up.
Oh, did you check on
Jeb's alibi ?
Oh, be taking my time getting
to that.
Ever get an award
for penmanship ?
Guessing you think I should have ?
This "P" looks like an "R".
Could have unraveled
your PMI warrant big time.
Came all the way down here
to rail on my cursive ?
Actually, I was wondering what
you were up to Friday night.
I got tickets to
"The Heartless Bastards".
The who ?
Yeah, I wish it were The Who,
but venue's a little small for them.
Are... are you asking me out
on a date ?
So what do you say ?
You... gonna feed me first ?
I can do that.
Then I say yes.
I don't get it,Scotty.
I'm divorcing my husband.
That's not good news?
Maybe if you had told me six months ago.
Look,I don't know what to tell you...
You need time. Yeah, you told me.
All this back and forth,
seems like we could both use
a cooling off.
Is that what that was last month ?
Cooling off ?
Will got shot.
It was wrong, me coming to you.
So that's it ? Just like that ?
I don't know what you want
from me, Frankie.
For the record, I think
you're making a mistake.
A really bad one.
At ease, soldier.
- Can't leave my post, sir.
- Put down the weapon, Keith.
Making us nervous.
Talk about your relationship
with Kate Butler.
Knob year.
She was in Echo Company with me, ma'am.
That's about it.
See,now you're violating
our honor code.
Got an eyewitness puts
you and her
getting cozy at the
Danboro Grous Coffee Shop.
Have to stay at my post, sir.
Your post can wait.
Maybe your graduation next month, too.
Introduce you to another long
blue line down at the station.
They called us the Odd Squad.
Echo had me, the chick,
and a Jew.
No one could figure
out why we were here.
What's that got to do with you
giving Kate the high hard one ?
We weren't sleeping together, sir.
I needed a tutor,
and she needed a friend.
("In Hiding" by Pearl Jam playing)
I... I dunno, Kate.
I,infinite sequences
look like Chinese to me.
I'll take dim sum over
antiderivatives any day.
Oh, my God.
- What ?
- You just smiled.
What are you talking about ?
I smile all the time.
Not since I've known you.
Is your face gonna
fall off or something ?
Nope, still works.
Why you so serious, Kate ?
Why do you think ?
I gotta be a hundred times more
Teflon than the rest of the guys.
Put up a front, just like you.
Front.
I really thought you were that tough.
Well, if I let my guard down,
I'll be dead.
Why you doing this, Kate ?
What's matter,
your father wanted a boy ?
I were a boy, he'd be bragging
about me to everyone he knows.
Um... it's just...
we want to get that ring, we gotta
get back to this calculus, right ?
Chinese, you mean.
Kate was good people
once you got to know her.
Touching story,Keith.
- That your signature ?
- Yes, sir.
It's barracks sign-out log
from the day Kate went AWOL.
You signed out at 7:17.
Same time as her.
You came back.
She never did.
There's gotta be a mistake,
ma'am.
I was on tours every weekend
that month.
Tours. That's punishment, right ?
What was that for ?
Don't remember.
Something to do with that demerit you
got for getting caught in the ladies' room ?
November 1, 2005.
Two weeks before she's murdered.
That was a misunderstanding.
Same night Kate shows up in the
infirmary with her hand cut up like sushi.
She get that injury
from you, Keith ?
- What ? No,  / - What the hell were you doing,
skulking 'round that ladies' latrine ?
Right here, Keith.
Anytime.
I did go in that latrine.
'Cause I was trying to help.
"Indifference" by Pearl Jam.
Kate?
Wake up. Wake up.
Keith ?
You're bleeding.
Your hand is... Jeez.
Pressure on it.
Here.
What happened to you ?
Kate, who was it,
did this to you ?
Just get me back to my room.
- Kate...
- Please, Keith.
I knew the cadets hated her.
Just didn't know how much until then.
You ever find out who did it ?
She wouldn't tell me, ma'am.
And I never got a look at his face.
You take her to the infirmary ?
Yes, sir. Couldn't get
the bleeding to stop.
When I went back to get my calculus book,
that's when they caught me in the bathroom.
Reason you had to do tours.
Knew I should have kept my mouth shut.
All this time I thought
they just ran her out.
Who did you talk to, Keith ?
I was in the "Odd Squad",too.
I thought they were
gonna come after me next.
There's no incident report
filed with Echo Company.
I didn't go through
the chain of command.
The honor code is only as strong
as the cadets who uphold it.
I went straight to the top.
Commandant Murillo ?
Thanks for coming in, Mr.Murillo.
It's Colonel Murillo.
I think I've earned that.
You can have a seat.
You have a problem with Cadet
Butler enrolling at PMI, Colonel ?
What's this all about, Lieutenant ?
I believe the detective
asked you a question.
What I have a problem
with is irrelevant
in view of what the courts
have decided now, isn't it ?
It isn't when you allow a
student to be assaulted on campus.
That's a bit presumptuous.
Am I on the stand here ?
You knew Kate was attacked,you should
have stopped it from going further.
I knew no such thing.
We have a cadet who witnsed it.
Told you what he saw.
What Cadet Keith Henderson
told me was hearsay.
I chose to go directly
to the horse's mouth.
Sir,Cadet Butler
reporting as ordered,sir.
At ease.
I want to talk to you about an incident that may
have occurred in the women's latrine last night.
Sir ?
I've been told that there was an
altercation between you and another cadet.
Is that true ?
To my knowledge, sir,
there was no incident.
Cadet Butler, are you aware
of the honor code ?
Yes,sir.
"A cadet shall not lie, cheat, or steal,
nor shall he tolerate those who do."
Now, did anything occur in
the women's latrine last night ?
Nothing happened, sir.
- Dismissed.
- Sir, yes, sir.
That's it ?
You just let her go ?
What the hell
would you have me do ?
The honor code is the
backbone of the institute.
If she said it didn't happen,
it didn't.
She was trying to suck it up,
to fit in with the male cadets.
Well,then she made
her choice, didn't she ?
You were head of the school.
I still am.
That hasn't stopped you
from trying to tell me how to do my job.
Maybe if you did it better.
I don't care how many pull-ups
Kate Butler could do.
She was never gonna be one
of the boys.
Her anatomy prevented that.
Plain and simple.
You don't give a rat's ass
what happened to her, do you ?
Any help I would have given her directly
would have just made the situation worse.
What do you mean, directly ?
I assigned an upperclassman
to keep an eye on her,
the same as I'm sure there was somebody
who looked out for you during your training.
Woman with a badge
intimidate you ?
Who was the upperclassman
you asked to look after Kate ?
A first sergeant, Echo Company.
He would order her to his room
every Sunday for shine detail.
Cadet James Addison ?
Put the fox in the henhouse.
Are we through here ?
Lieutenant ?
I choose to spend my Saturday
evenings kicking back with a Cohiba.
I apologize if the phallic
implications of that offend you, officer.
It's Detective.
And I've absolutely earned it.
A lot of work goes into keeping
everything clean, polished.
How can I help you, Detective ?
Made it sound like you hardly
knew Kate last time we talked.
James Frederick Addison.
Commandant's list every semester.
I can see why he chose
you to watch over her.
Shine detail, right ?
Every Sunday when
she came to your room ?
Colonel Murillo told you
about that.
Wondering why you didn't.
Kate was attacked one of those Sundays,
two weeks before she disappeared.
Would have been after
she left your room.
That just a coincidence ?
You're right about
my perfect record.
I never failed at a thing in my life.
Until I met Kate.
You going to take all day
with that ?
Sir, I'll try to speed it up, sir.
Brasso.
Bring some back when you
go home for Thanksgiving.
Thank you,sir.
What's wrong ?
- Sir, nothing's wrong, sir.
- Look,enough with the "sir" sandwiches.
- What happened to your hand ?
- It's fine.
Let me see. Come here.
They stitch this up
at the infirmary ?
It's not a big deal. It's just,
some of the polish got in it...
How'd this happen to you ?
PT, I think. Not really sure.
Three years of PT,I never seen
someone's hand sliced like that.
Two parallel cuts, what's that ?
- It's a saber, isn't it ?
- I couldn't say, Mr.Addison.
Look,why do you think I make you
come to my room every damn Sunday?
So we can talk, so that you
have someone to turn to.
Look at me.
Now's the time, Kate.
I know.
Hello ?
Sir, request permission
to get a towel, sir !
Why do you need a towel,knob?
You ashamed of your nakedness ?
Answer me, knob !
You hiding from the sight of God ?!
Sir, yes, sir !
Who was it ?
Come on, Kate.
It was just racking.
Knobs are always getting
racked in the showers.
That wasn't racking.
That was assault.
Look, no guy would tolerate
what he did to you.
So you tell me who it was
so I can go kick his ass.
I got to fight my own battles.
Then take care of it yourself.
Or leave.
You're the first, Kate.
They're all going to be watching you.
I was supposed to protect her.
All cadets carry a saber ?
Only upperclassmen,
select members of the regimental honor
guard ; Operations should have a list.
What'd you think
when she disappeared ?
I wasn't surprised.
I thought she just finally
had enough and left.
Detective.
Find the person who hurt her.
"Yellow Ledbetter" par Pearl Jam
* Unsealed on a porch a
letter sat *
* Then you said,
I wanna leave it again *
* Once I saw her on a beach
of weathered sand *
* And on the sand I wanna
leave it again, yeah *
* On a weekend, I wanna
wish it all away, yeah *
* And they called and I said
that I want what I said *
* And I called out again *
* And the reason Ought
to leave her calm, *
I know I said,"I know what
I wear, not a box or a bag"
* Can't you see them ? *
And on the eighth day... God...
God created PMI.
* I see them Round
the front way, yeah... *
Come on, Scotty. Pick up.
**********