the following story is
fictional and does not depict actual person or event
june 8,1953
* She come true *
* Ah,look at that girl
Can blue eyes be so blue? *
* Look at the way she walks
Listen when she talks *
* With each word my heart just skips *
* Oh,if I could kiss those lips,mmm  *
* Look at that girl Do
you see what I see? *
* Ah,look at that girl She's
walking straight to me *
Look at me,Rita.
How about a little more
sunshine on the goodies,huh?
Zip!Men like to imagine,not see.
Not this man.
You ain't seeing nothing
tonight,you keep it up.
Oh...Betty,fix that sleeve.
There's nothing's wrong with it,Zip.
Just move it up an inch.
Yeah,like that.
Big difference.
Hey,hey,hey,every detail
matters in one of my pinups.
That's why Monty knows I'm the best.
Listen,this magazine is gonna be
a lights-out,call-the-doctor smash.
Cornucopias of cash,my friend.
Cornucopias.
Here's another fan
letter from Beanie,Ree.
"Dear Ms. Flynn,thanks
for writing me back.”
"I put your pinup in my locker today.
You are prettier than all
the stars" in the sky.”
Oh,he's so sweet.
Yeah,play with the straw,Ree.
- So,how was the picture show last night?
- Didn't go.
Well,I thought you had a date.
So did I.The rat didn't even call.
Oh,you should have come over.
Some of Zip's New York
friends were in town.
You party all night?
Danced with the sunrise,koo koo.
We're going national.
My new mag's a go.Rita,they
want you for the cover.
Zip,you're gonna take the picture.
To Rita...
the soda jerk who changed my life.
To everyone here.
The only family I ever had.
Let's paint the town red tonight!...
Jones?
We got to find another bar.
Got one in mind?
How about...
Jones?
Uh,Detective Rush?
- Yes?
- Yeah,Gus Medica.
I'm sorry; this is the
only time I could get here.
Uh,we spoke on the phone yesterday.
Rita Flynn?
Oh,right,the pinup girl.
It's a '53 homicide.
Detective Valens.You
a relative,Mr.Medica?
No,uh,just a fan.
Rita's pinup got me
through the Korean War.
My grandson was just
deployed to Afghanistan.
It has me thinking about Rita again.
Uh,this book came out a week ago.
She was a real bombshell.
Oh,she was more than a great figure.
Her smile gave me hope.
Now,the book says that this is the first time that
anything from Rita's crime scene has ever been published.
Some records clerk moron probably buddied up
to the media,let them have access to the box.
Mr. Medica,you said you had
new informatio on the case?
Uh,yeah.Turns out I've
had it for over 50 years.
I bought this in 1955 at an
estate sale of Rita's stuff.
It's not your usual cheesecake.
No... now,I'm a collector.
This is unique.
I've never,ever seen
another one like it.
Same clothes.
Same position of the glass on the table.
That's what I noticed:
same outfit,same everything.
Look at the ice.
Almost melted in the crime scene photo.
Papers back then had said it was
probably some creep,broke in...
So,who took this photo?
Photographer's stamp.
As good as a signature
if we could make it out.
May be a new witness.
Or the one who set Rita's final pose.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly
Presents
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET-几乎每周一都被老板迫害的邦德猪
COLD CASE
Season 6 Episode 09
Rita Marie Flynn.
Grew up poor in Tacony.
Mom died young.Drunk father walked out.
That's a good start in life.
Discovered by Monty Moran at the drugstore
where she worked with her best friend,
Betty Sue Baker.
Jeffries is trying to find her.
Betty Sue.Got to love the '50s.
Downstairs neighbor heard
a gunshot at 9:00,ran up,
found the chain on the front
door broken and Rita's body.
Looked like an attempted sexual assault.
No blood or semen,but
her clothes were torn.
Peeping Tom had been reported in the
neighborhood.Never caught the guy.
No record of this mystery photographer.
Wanted to take a picture Rita didn't.
She kicks his ass out.
He comes back without knocking.
An unregistered Webley .38 was found
outside in the rain near the building.
Matched the body bullet taken from Rita.
Webley's made in England.Maybe it
was registered there.Worth a look.
Rita was on the cover of
almost 30 pinup magazines.
Those come dog-eared?
Research.
Early '50s: last days of
selling sex with a G rating.
You have a pinup girl,boss?
Sophia Loren.
Had her picture taped
inside my algebra book.
That will get you through math class.
Check out these theme shoots.
- Circus Girl.
- Classy.
Rita Dresses for a Night on the Town.
"Planting a Garden.”
Gardening--
that's just hot.
Actually...
that is kind of hot.
Arthur "Zip" Fellig was
Rita's boyfriend.Last to see.
I'll try and track him down.
Check with the ID unit.See what else
they can get from Gus's photo of Rita.
You Francine Rafferty?
- Depends.
- On what?
On what you want.
I got a backlog of
surveillance videos to blow up.
One's from a triple.
- ****
- *****
**********
(scotty的新欢啊！！！！）
- ******
- *****
******Text a early '50s.
Professional print right
from the developing bath.
So,this wasn't mass-produced?
No,original.
Straight from a darkroom.
You missed first base,by the way.
Sorry?
Softball game last Saturday.
You missed it by a foot.
You were too busy
admiring your home run.
I played second base.
Oh,yeah.Yeah,that's right.
What about the,uh...
uh,rubber stamp?
Popped the ink and dirt traces.
Got this.
Stanley Nopell.
Great work,Frankie.Thanks.
You know,I touched that base.
The saddest lies are the
ones we tell ourselves.
Say cheese is right.
Welcome to Glamour World.
who wants to be a star?
Detectives Valens and
Miller-- Philly Homicide.
- We're here about Rita Flynn.
- Rita?
My God,after all these years.
Looks like you haven't forgotten.
She's more popular than ever.A whole
new generation is falling in love.
500 bones?Better hope so.
It's an original signature
there.It's very rare.
Check out my Web site.My prints
of her are selling like hotcakes.
Understand you worked with her.
We were a team.A good pinup
isn't just about the model.
We're tracking a
photographer Rita worked with.
Took this.
Stanley Nopell?
- You know him?
- No.
Wasn't even aware that she
worked with other photographers.
Seem surprised.
Well,Rita and I were both under
contract to Monty Moran,and...
no,Rita was faithful to me
on both sides of the camera.
Here you go,pops.
I'm yours exclusively.
You won't regret it.
We're like the immortal team
of Buonarroti and Cavalieri.
- Who are they?
- No idea.
I heard that line in a movie.
Look,Rita.
He asked me out.
He's got blue eyes to die for.
Isn't he a dish?
Supper and dessert.
- Who is he?
- He's a banker.
He's really sweet.
Oh,Betty.
This one feels lucky.
Um,are you Rita Flynn?
No,she's the Pope.
- Can I have your autograph?
- Sure thing,doll.
Oh,golly.
Drool is so charming.
I used to jerk soda for that fella.
Bet he didn't ask for
your autograph then.
Life's funny,ain't it,koo koo?
(The Four Lads' "Istanbul
(Not Constantinople)" playing)
Hey,Rita,it's your song.Do your thing.
- Aren't you tired of it?
- Come on,Ree.Do it.
Okay.
* Istanbul was Constantinople
Now it's Istanbul, *
* not Constantinople
Been a long time gone, *
* old Constantinople Still a *
* Turkish delight on a moonlit
night Every gal in Constantinople *
* Lives in Istanbul,not Constantinople *
* So if you've a date
in Constantinople *
* She'll be waiting in
Istanbul Even old New York *
* Was once New Amsterdam.. . *
Funny old geezer.
He's got a face like an angel.
You and me to the top of the top.
To the top of the top!
Rita was the life of the...
She was my life.
We were going to get married.
All that male attention
make any boyfriend jealous.
Ah,it's just part of the business.
Long as she went home with me.
Back in the day,you said you were
home the night Rita was killed.
Hit the sack early that night
for a big shoot in the morning.
What about Monty?
He could've hired this
Nopell guy for another shoot.
If he was a photographer,Monty would
have known him.He knew everyone.
But you never heard of him?
No.I told you I...I didn't.
Stay in town,Zip.
I might be back for a headshot.
Rita...
Yeah,she was a sweet kid.
She was like a daughter to me.
Yeah,to this day I blame myself.
Why's that,Monty?
Well,I made her famous.
And with fame came the
attention of men,good and bad.
In those days,any creep could
find her address in the phone book.
- You own a gun back in '53,Monty?
- No.Why?
Well,police never took a
statement from you back then.
Well,I thought she was
assaulted by some sick pervert.
Did Rita have her picture
taken by anyone besides Zip?
Oh,guys always wanted
to take her picture.
See,the thing about a good photo,you can
stare at it over and over and still find...
a new meaning in it.
We're looking for a photographer
named Stanley Nopell.
Took this picture of Rita.
You ever work with him,Monty?
Stanley Nopell?
Never heard of him.
Did Rita mention anyone in particular
might have been bothering her?
No,she never said anything.
But,well,there...
there was a fan.
Took things a little too far.
(Ruth Brown's "I'll Wait For You" plays)
Al,what part of "opportunity of Brobdingnagian
proportions" do you not understand?
Hey,what's the holdup?
Zip's running late.Keep
your hat on,koo koo.
So what are you gonna wear for
the big date with Blue Eyes?
I don't know.
I wish I could buy something new.
Borrow something from
wardrobe.No one'll notice.
- You think?
- Sure.
But I want you to report back to
me lickety-split after the date.
I want to hear everything.
Smile,you're on Candid Camera.
Mr.DeMille,I presume.
Sorry,boss.Traffic.
All right,hup two.Folks,break's over.
Oh,I forgot my lei!
Beanie Emerson,yeah.
He was the president of Rita's fan club.
Sounds like he took to the job.
The kid showed up everywhere we went.
She consider him a friend?
No,he was just a boy.
Back then,we thought
it was teenage hijinks.
Right.
Now we just call it "stalking.”
Up all night trying to track
this Stanley Nopell dude.
- Any luck?
- The guy's a ghost.
No driver's license,voter
registration-- like he don't exist.
Well,we found Beanie.
Got him in the box.
He still go by Beanie?
Research.
How're you doing,Ben?
Detectives Miller and Valens.
This really about Rita Flynn?
Really is.Understand you were
president of her fan club.
You bet.This was back in the '50s.
So it was you?
Snuck into Rita's
apartment night she died?
What?No.
You broke into her dressing
room.Figure apartment's a piece of cake.
Still got the panty collection,Beanie?
I was out of town with
my parents when Rita died.
Florida.
That wasn't the question,Ben.
Look,I was...I was 15.
You know what those pictures
do to a kid that age?
Got an eyewitness saw you
breaking and entering,Beanie.
You were stalking her.
Look,maybe I was a little
bit too,you know,zealous.
I admit,I did follow her around a lot.
But it wasn't me she had to fear.
(seducve bigand music plays)
Betty?
Betty,wait.
Wait!
What are you doing here?
I came to show you something.
Your dad said this was a restaurant.
I told my dad I'm waiting tables.
- Please,Rita,just go.
- You need money?
I could lend you some.
- You got $500 for all of last years' rent?
- Doesn't your dad pay for...
My dad drinks away every
penny I make from photo shoots.
You were wrong,Rita.
Men do like to see.
And they pay for it.
But,Betty,this isn't you.
What if Blue Eyes finds out?
How would he find out?
- Oh,no,Betty,I'd...
- Go to hell!
Yeah,I thought they were friends.
But that girl...
she was angry.
Ashamed or something.
Shame.
Guess that's something a panty
sniffer like you don't suffer much,huh?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Such a big fan of Rita,
why didn't you tell somebody about this?
I was a minor.
I wasn't even supposed
to be in that club.
Well,thanks for your time...
Beanie.
Thank you.
Hello.
Are you here about the
Bangladesh recovery?
I'm Detective Rush,Betty.
- Philly Homicide.
- Homicide?I don't understand.
It's about Rita Flynn.
Rita?For heaven's sake.
You told the police back then
the two of you were good friends.
The best of friends.
You two ever get into a spat?
No.
She made a lot more
money than you as a model.
Now,how about you?You get
paid enough to make ends meet?
I suppose.
You remember a club
called The Red Curtain?
Ms.Rush,that was a long time ago.
My father was an alcoholic
who needed my help.
I'm not proud,but...
I did what I had to do.
Desperate people do desperate things.
If you're implying I had anything
to do with Rita's death...
You lied about the fight,Betty.
I was upset.
Rita calmed me down.We
had a heart-to-heart.
- When was this?
- At the club.
Only Rita could find humanity
in such a depressing place.
(sultry jazz music plays)
I'm so sorry.
I just lost my temper.I'm
under such pressure.
You don't have to apologize,Betty.
- I just want to help you.
- I know.
So what was that surprise
that you came to show me?
Remember when I was taking pictures?
Ta-da!
There's a great one of you.
But these aren't glamorous.
Ordinary life can be beautiful,too.
Ordinary life?What
are you talking about?
I don't know.Real stuff.
Remember when we were jerking soda,all
the crazy characters who would come in?
You mean like
Half-a-scoop Lou?
Yeah!
"A full scoop's bad for the joints.”
See,I miss people like that.
Oh,yeah...See him?
That's a face with a thousand stories.
Get that camera out of here!
Lady,you better destroy that picture,or
so help me,I'll do it for you myself!
Get off me!
You know that guy?
Regular.
Named Reg Donaldson.
Came back from the front
with a few screws loose.
World War II vet?
Everyone walked around him on eggshells.
The scariest guy in a scary place.
You know if he carried a gun?
I saw him pull it one night on a
drunk who took his seat by mistake.
So you saw this man pull a gun
on someone; Rita's shot to death;
and you never went to the police?
Detective...I saw this when
I was working as a dancer.
Good to see you turned
your life around,Betty.
Think of anything else,give me a call.
- Found something?
- Maybe.
Here.
At first,I thought this
was a lighter.You see that?
Yeah,what is it?
Here,look closer.
Camera that took this was a Leica 3A.
It's unique for the time.That's
actually the self-timer switch.
Are you listening?
The Leica 3A,self-timer.
Saying Rita took that photo herself.
Exactly.
Turns out that American shell-shocked
war vet from the strip club
spent time in a psych ward in England.
Along with our gun.Check this out.
ID unit says the photo Gus
brought in was a self-rtrait.
But the stamp says Stanley.
It's that song she used to sing.
"Istanbul was Constantinople.
Now it's Istanbul...
""Not Constantinople.
Istanbul was Constantinople.”
"Now it's... Istanbul.”
Rita... was Stanley Nopell.
Saying she was a photographer?
Trying to be,at least.
Not a lot of female photographers
back then,so she makes up a man's name.
Snaps a shot of Reg
Donaldson with a stripper.
Yeah,married guy,caught red-handed.
Guy's half off his nut already.
Not a photo you want
coming home to the missus.
So this guy wasn't going
after Rita the pinup girl.
He was after Rita the photographer.
Ever spend time in
the UK,Mr.Donanaldson?
I thought this was about Rita Flynn.
Well,if you could answer the question...
I was in England after the war.
Pick up a gun while you were there?
- No.
- But you owned a rearm?
A Browning .22.I worked
nights in a bad neighborhood.
Understand you spent some time
under a doctor's psychiatric care.
What is this?
We've got witnesses saying
you threatened Rita Flynn.
What?You think I shot her?
She had a photo that could
have broken up your marriage.
My marriage was already broken.
I overreacted.
I-I just wanted to be anonymous.
Anonymous?
I was pretty messed up after the
war.Couldn't relate to people.
Just a...
bottle in a bar.
Did you see Rita again,Reg?
Yeah,she found me and apologized.
Asked me to help her out,take
her around the old neighborhood.
- Where's that?
- Tacony.She wanted to take pictures.
She pulled me out of the dark.
She said she was going to show me the
pictures,but then I read in the paper that...
What a world.
Where were you that night,Reg?
Same place I was every night:
The Red Curtain,trying to forget.
Rita mention anyone she
was having problems with?
No,she was in a good mood.She...
said she was thinking
about quitting modeling.
Quick follow-up.
Think Rita got that photo developed somewhere
or could she have done it on her own?
Lots of photography clubs back then.
- Home darkrooms were pretty common.
- Right.
So...who are these people?
Your great-grandfather
in there or something?
No,I-I found it inside a used book.
Every time I look at it,I
see something new.You know?
That guy's derby hat
there,that woman's smile.
I wonder what made her smile.
Yeah.I love the mystery
of old photographs.
- We'll never know.
- Well,maybe we do.
You see that guy?He's
knocking boots with her.
Just whispered in her ear,"My
compartment,five minutes.”
No.
She just slipped a slow-acting
poison in that guy's drink.
- Why?
- Well,it's her husband.
She's gonna inherit a million bucks.
Wicked imagination,Frankie.
Is your cell phone dead?
My phone?No.
Quick follow-ups are phone calls.
Unless there's another
reason you stopped by.
Yeah.I got reservations.
- You and me.
- Dinner?
- No.
- What did you have in mind?
That a yes?
Yes.
Hey,Miller got a hit on the
gun.Registered to a Philip Moran in London.
Moran?Related to Monty Moran?
His unRe.
Couldn't be our doer because
he died in January '53,
ve months before Rita was murdered.
Uncle could have given it to Monty.
And Monty started a British
version of See Magazine in 1950.
Traveled back and forth all the time.
Got a little gun problem,Monty.
Haven't we already gone over this?
Yeah,which means either
you're lying or...
you're starting to slip.
Wasn't your magazine
that got Rita killed.
It was your gun.
I never fired a gun in my life.
Except the one that killed Rita.
This was registered to your dead uncle.
My God,I'd forgotten
all about the damn thing.
My uncle gave it to me for a gift.
A Webley .38. Bullet from
that gun ended up in Rita.
That gun was stolen two
months before Rita died.
- You never reported it.
- Look,this is ludicrous.
I had no reason to kill Rita.
She tell you she was
going to quit modeling?
Eh,she told me about
it,but I wasn't upset.
You invested a lot of money in her.
Would have taken a big
hit of your circulation.
Yeah,but I was not about to let an
asset like that walk out the door.
Are you decent?
- I used to be.
- You should lock your door,cupcake.
What have we got here?
These are fantastic.
Who took 'em?
Me.
Come on.Don't kid a kidder.
No kidding,koo koo.
You got more tricks up your
sleeve than Harry Houdini.
- I'm through with pinups,Monty.
- Thought you were having fun.
I'm bored of making other people smile.
When I take these pictures,I smile.
So you want to ba photographer?
I don't know.Maybe.
These are like the ones
they got in Life Magazine.
You could be a photojournalist,take
serious pictures.
You think?
Oh,no,n-no,Rita.
Uh-uh,I didn't sign you to a pinup contract
'cause I wanted your autograph,so...
But can't we work something out?
Tell you what.How'd
you like 'em published?
Come on.Hey,don't kid a kidder.
You got a real way of
understanding people.
I can see it in those pictures,too.
Now you're just trying
to sweet-talk me.
Hey,if I can't have you as a pinup girl,I
sure as hell want you as a photographer.
As talented as Rita was in front of the
camera,she was even more talented behind it.
Hell,I was even going to
make more money that way.
What a sell: "queen of the lens.”
Still got some of her old negatives,too.
I never could bring
myself to print them.
Who else had access to that gun,Monty?
I kept it locked up in a
small safe in the studio.
Anyone else have a key to that safe?
No,just Zip.Kept his
expensive lenses in there.
Did Zip know Rita
wanted to leave modeling?
I don't know,but I'll tell you one
thing-- I was-- I wasn't sad to see him go.
Package deal like that,I
was better off without.
Talking about Zip with Rita?
All that time,I thought that blowhard made her look
good till I realized it was the other way around.
Yes,ma'am,uh,the pictures are ready.
Are you aware of our two-
for-one special on 8x10s?
Special can wait,Zippy.
You remember the safe
Monty had in his studio?
Safe?No.
You should.He gave you a key to it.
- That's where you kept your lenses,right?
- I guess.
Oh,yeah,come to think of it,uh,I
stored a few of 'em in ther
Along with his gun.Come
to think of that?
No,I don't remember any gun.
Well,how about Rita telling
you she wanted to quit modeling?
- Well,that was just something she said.
- Said she wanted to become a photographer.
Please.
Taking a few snapshots and doing what
I do are two different things entirely.
I checked your rsum,Zip.
- You had a hard time getting work after Rita died.
- I loved Ree.
It took me a while before I
could photograph a woman again.
Yeah,especially since no
other magazine would hire you.
Barely lasted another year
as a pinup photographer.
- That's 'cause you were a hack.
- You don't know what you're talking about.
- I created Rita.
- She outgrew you,Zip.
No,it was a
relationship.She...she needed me.
She needed you to let her
go,but you just couldn't do that.
No.I was the photographer.
I mean,we had a good
thing going,the two of us.
Till she had to go and
turn everything upside down.
("Somewhere Along the Way"
by Nat King Cole playing)
These are interesting.
Who'd you say did this?
Me.
What do you think?
You want to quit modeling for this?
They're ugly.
Well,I'm...I'm just getting started.
- I'll get better.
- Stick to smiling pretty,baby.
Don't ruin a good thing.
Don't you believe in me,Zip?
And what about "you and me all
the way to the top of the top"?
We can both do it as photographers.
Look,I'm the photographer.
You're a pinup girl.
That's the way it is.
I want to take different
kinds of pictures.
- Like a journalist.
- Journalism takes brains.
Dedication.
No more sing-alongs in
bars behaving like a tramp.
My mother taught me to
sing along like that.
I told you that.
She used to dance around the
kitchen when I was a little girl,
singing goofy songs to me.
I was gonna teach our daughter
the same thing one day.
I don't think we want the
same things anymore,do we,Zip?
I think you should go.
I knew as soon as I saw
those photos.She was good.
I just couldn't admit to it at the time.
You couldn't handle that she
was more talented than you.
Instead,I was cruel.
And that was the last time I saw her.
I went to Monty's studio that
night to get my prints of Rita.
I knew they'd be valuable someday.
Took me all night to pack 'em up.
Anyone to back that up?
Betty Sue was there.Trying on some
of Rita's wardrobe for her date.
Betty Sue borrowed Rita's clothes?
Well,the kid didn't have any money.
- Do you remember if she took a purse?
- A purse?
For her date.Did she borrow a purse?
I don't know.
She was awful excited,though.She,uh,made
me take a picture of her.
You still have that picture?
I'm a photographer.Got a negative
of every picture I ever took.
Dig it up and print it.
Betty Sue dresses for
a night on the town.
You remember when that photo was taken?
I don't know.
It's at the studio.
Must have been a photo shoot.
- Oh,Zip said he took it the night Rita was killed.
- He did?
You were at the studio getting
ready for your big date.
Oh,well,I'll be.I'd forgotten.
You forgot a lot,Betty.
I been going over these pinup magazines
You chose Seems like a time capsule.
Rita's "night on the town" outfit
for your date with "Blue Eyes.”
Quite a trip down memory lane.
But what does that have
to do with Rita's murder?
Everything.
You see that purse?
You had it with you on your date.
So how does it end up
in Rita's apartment?
I just figured Rita
borrowed it from wardrobe.
- Maybe she did.
- No.No.
The only way that purse gets to this
crime scene is if you brought it.
I did stop by.
But I didn't hurt Rita.
I ran your fingerprints,Betty.
Matches the gun.
How did you get my fingerprints?
A report from the crime lab.
And your prints are all over
your office at St.Mary's.
Patriot Act.Special subpoena.We
dusted that place two nights ago.
I didn't have a gun.
You were Monty's assistant.
You had copies of all his keys.
The strip club was a dangerous place.
You took Monty's gun for protection.
Oh,that gun.Yes,I had it.
I don't know how it
got to Rita's apartment.
Well,your date ended early,so you
went to Rita's to talk about it.
Just like she made you promise.
Your date was at 8:00.
The gunshot was heard at 9:00.
Your date didn't go well,did it?
A couple drinks to numb the pain?
Two best friends,both
working the soda shop.
Years pass and everything goes
right for one,but the other one...
She's stuck taking care
of a drunken old man.
And Rita plays and dances.
Everything was easy for her.
I just wanted one day of her luck.
One day when it was easy.
What happened that night,Betty?
I've devoted my life to helping others.
Helping others or seeking atonement?
Someone once told me God shines his
light on those who ask for forgiveness.
I hope so.
Rita!
Betty?What's wrong?
You told me to come by after the date.
Here I am.
Sit down,Bets.You don't look too good.
What's that?
Nothing.
It's just another picture I took.
- It's of you.-
Self-portrait.
Monty found another magazine
that wants to publish me.
I had to come up with a fake name.
Stanley Nopell.Get it?
From your song.
Good one.
What's a girl gotta do to
get a drink around here?
Hey,hey,haven't you had enough?
Betty,what happened?
My date went real swell.
Sat down for drinks.
He was excited...
a little nervous.
Then you know happened?
He gave me something.
He did?
- Well what did he give you?
- This.
He wanted your autograph.
He only asked me out
so he could meet you.
No.No,that can't be true.
He came to you that night.
Because he was too nervous to go to you.
He laughed at me when he realized
I thought we were on a date.
Oh,Betty.
What's it like...
...to always be lucky?
Betty,I'm not lucky.
Harder I work,luckier I get.
The men at the club--
they stare,stare.
They never ask me for my autograph.
They ask me for other things.
Betty,you don't have to do that.
Come stay here with me.
Your dad'll be fine.
If I can't make old Blue
Eyes happy,then you should.
You make everyone happy!
Life's funny.
Ain't it,koo koo?
Go ahead.Sign it!
Betty,don't do this.
Sign it!
Betty...
Betty,it's me.
It's Ree.I'm your friend.
Things can change for you.
I started right where you did.
That's what hurts the most.
("Can't I" by Nat King Cole playing)
* Can't I Will I Ever love you again *
* Tell me Why then can't I *
* Maybe others *
* Want you just like I do Tell me *
* Why then can't I  *
* You might have known others *
* So have I Who would
hurt you And desert you? *
* That's why I only want To hold you *
* Always Never to let you go *
* Tell me Why then can't I *
* You might have known others *
* So have I Who would
hurt you And desert you? *
* That's why I only want To hold you *
* Always Never to let you go *
* Tell me Why then can't I. *
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly
Presents
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET-很困很瞌睡的邦德猪