Detective Sheppard?
Come on, John.
I'm breaking this with or without you.
- What's she doing here?
- Is this victim related to the others?
If we have a serial killer on our hands,
people have the right to know.
Victim was most likely a white male.
"Most likely?"
No clothes, no ID.
Wasn't killed here.
Got tire tracks
leading from the road.
Based on size, and spread,
it's probably an older-model pick-up.
We've got radiator fluid down here.
Looks like the vehicle has a leak.
Pretty much as the other.
- Same chest wound?
- Yeah.
I thought I'd seen everything.
Yeah. Me too.
One day, we'll learn.
Season 5 Episode 19
Vegas (v. 1.00)
The Projet-SG & SG-66 Teams
www.projet-sg.net
www.seriestele.net
Thomas Crane.
Reported missing three days ago.
39 years old.
- You think this guy was 39?
- Check the dental records.
- It wasn't natural causes.
- Nope.
It looks like some sort
of rapid cellular breakdown.
The other victims...
had the same chest wound,
the same bizarre aging.
I read the other autopsies.
The cause was undetermined.
All I know is
we're not dealing with a contagion.
No chemical residue?
Detective,
you'll get a copy of my report.
The previous victims all had
radioactive residue
around their wounds.
When I'm done.
What'd you say your name was again?
I've got eight bodies
in three months,
and I don't like it
when the lead coroner on my case
gets replaced by somebody who doesn't
look old enough to be in medical school.
Maybe someone feels a need
for some fresh eyes on the case.
They should have just replaced me.
Do you have any leads?
Got a bunch of bodies being dumped
in the desert and it looks like...
- the life's been sucked out of them.
- You really think that's possible?
I don't know where you're from,
but out here, anything's possible.
Anyone treated with symptoms related
to radiation poisoning,
go back a month.
No, it's not gonna come back to you,
I promise.
I don't know.
I told you,
they said it was a virus or something.
Probably food poisoning.
You should see the place
they've got me at.
Not exactly Bellagio.
Whole trip's been
a useless waste of time, too.
My nose is bleeding again!
I better go.
Yeah, I will.
Love you too.
Turn it down, will you?
Son of a bitch.
- Sheppard, this is Agent Woolsey, FBI.
- Nice to meet you.
- What the hell happened to your eye?
- This case move jurisdiction?
Not yet.
I'm not at liberty to discuss
our interest at this time,
but I'd appreciate your cooperation.
- Well... I got nothing.
- I'm surprised at that, detective.
The victims are turning up faster.
This is obviously a progression.
The first few bodies were buried.
We only found them because coyotes
dragged one onto the 564.
Now they're just being dumped out
in the open for the vultures.
So is that more careless,
or more bold?
Tell me why the coroner's report
on the latest victim
shows no signs of radioactive...
what do you call it?
Isotopes.
I assume because
there weren't any found.
Well...
There were on the first seven.
- Where are you going?
- I gotta go see a nurse.
This guy was seen yesterday.
- Where is he?
- He's an out-of-towner at a motel.
- The chart should say.
- And you just let him go?
He was seen by a doctor.
We get people
with flu-like symptoms all the time.
All right, well,
what made it stand out?
He was also having nosebleeds.
It could have been unrelated.
Also common because of the dry air,
but then you mentioned
radiation poisoning...
- Thanks.
- Hey, look.
If he really was exposed,
it could be serious.
I'll track him down.
You want me to take a look
at that eye, John?
No, I'm... I'm fine.
- Are you gonna call me?
- Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Do you know that guy?
He checked out yesterday.
That a medical report?
If he had something, I gotta know.
Have that room cleaned up properly.
Wash the sheets, you know?
Wash those sheets. In the meantime,
let me look at your register.
They were fighting.
She tried to break it up.
You know, it was an accident.
- You couldn't find the finger?
- We were up all night looking for it.
Yeah, but you found it?
Out on the lawn,
when the sun came up.
I got it in the fridge.
- And where's the housekeeper?
- At the hospital.
- She lost a ton of blood.
- Really?
- Don't they need the finger?
- No, it's too late to reattach it.
She'll be all right.
- Which finger was it?
- Pinky.
- And you still got it?
- What are you supposed to do with it?
Besides, I thought maybe
she'd still want it. You know?
- And what about the dogs?
- Well, what about 'em?
- You're gonna get rid of them, no?
- What do you mean? I love those dogs.
I know.
I'll see 'em.
Nice hand.
Got me again.
Almost like you can read minds.
Only yours.
Look at this guy.
He won't even look at me!
You've been taking my money all night,
you won't even look at me?
Leave it alone.
He's a freakin' wacko.
Aren't you a little out
of your league here?
What are you, my mother?
Go ahead. I'll ante.
22,000 to call.
He doesn't have it.
Shut up.
He didn't have it!
No way.
Wait, where are you going?
You can't leave now!
Look at this guy.
Aw, geez.
You don't think
that's contagious, do you?
You said the guy next door
checked out yesterday?
I never saw him.
He used the tv.
Don't touch anything.
Sure.
What is it?
It's a crime scene.
Get lost.
Detective.
We got another body here.
I was just about to call it in.
I heard about
what happened at the casino.
You following me?
There's a satellite locator
on your car.
If you don't mind, we'd like you
to come for a little drive.
Do I have a choice?
Right.
- He won't sign it.
- Well, we should tell him anyway.
We can't trust him.
He might be able to help us.
Let me at least try.
Detective.
I'm Dr. Rodney McKay.
I realize you have
no way of grasping what's going on here.
There's really only one thing
you need to understand...
If you fail to co-operate,
I have the power to ruin your life.
Well, then you don't realize
how little I have to lose.
I know everything about you.
You've never been married.
The only thing you own is a car.
You have $2,363 in the bank
and are $13,000 in debt,
not counting
off-the-books gambling losses
to a guy named Mikey.
What else?
You finally passed
your detective exam
after four years
and two failed attempts,
and now barely scrape by
on quarterly performance reviews.
Am I getting this right?
I also like spearmint gum.
Have some.
- I was joking.
- No, you weren't.
Let's go back further, shall we?
You were a helicopter
pilot in Afghanistan,
but were dishonorably discharged
for disobeying orders
and trying to rescue a field medic
trapped behind enemy lines.
You were shot down,
obviously survived,
but, unfortunately, the crash killed
four american soldiers
along with eight civilians.
You avoided jail time.
The record was sealed
for various political reasons.
These things happen, right?
Somehow you've managed
to live with yourself since then...
But I'm not sure other people would
if they knew the truth.
I don't really care.
Yeah.
That's too bad.
You know...
I once met another version of you.
He was very different.
- What?
- Nothing...
is what you think it is.
That really doesn't come
as a surprise to me.
Look...
We're not bad guys.
We just wanna keep the planet safe.
I doubt that very much.
I don't expect
you'll believe me at first.
I'm about to tell you
some incredible things.
Wormhole travel
through a device called a Stargate,
ancient races of humans
on other planets,
other dimensions in space and time,
even infinite variations
of our known reality,
where alternate versions of you and I
play out events in ways you can't...
possibly imagine.
Space aliens?
It was found under a mile
of ice in Antarctica
five years ago
and later moved here.
It runs on a power source
that extracts energy
from vacuum space.
We call it a Zed-PM.
Well, a Zee-PM.
Sorry. I'm Canadian.
With the right genetic code,
you can control
some pretty cool weaponry,
remotely, with your mind.
It's how we were able to defeat
the Wraith hive ship
that attacked Earth
three months ago.
Are there more?
- What, chairs?
- No, aliens.
Oh, yeah. Lots more.
Fortunately,
they're in another galaxy...
And, for now,
they don't know where Earth is.
Detective?
They're called "Darts".
Small, fast,
single-pilot attack ships.
Luckily we took out the Hive
quickly.
Each one can carry
hundreds of these things.
And the guy dumping bodies
in the desert...
He's an alien.
A Wraith.
A genetic hybrid
between human beings
and something called an Iratus bug.
Feeds on human energy,
literally saps the life
out of people
using their sucker on their hands.
I suppose it all sounds
like science fiction to you.
I'm not really a fan.
My team and I usually operate
out of Atlantis, in the Pegasus galaxy,
but we were called back to Earth
to deal with this situation
because of our expertise
with the Wraith.
Now, the one that you've encountered
has obviously been doing
a fairly good job of blending in.
- What, disguising himself as human?
- Based on your description
and the video surveillance
from the casino.
What do they normally look like?
Normally...
they look like that.
- Why do they do it?
- Feed on humans?
Well, that's just what they are.
We're just cattle to them.
Fish in a pond!
Busy, busy, lots to do,
here and there...
This one fancies himself
a bit of a poet.
Not good.
Dry as a desert outside.
No place to go.
He's also delirious from starvation.
Eat up!
Get stronger.
Think and hope.
Think... and hope...
Don't look now!
Ohh...
Keep dreaming.
There must be some other reason
for your existence.
Did you get anything from him?
Nothing.
Believe me, we've tried...
everything.
Defiance tastes like life itself.
No river.
No water.
Dry as a desert!
Darkness all around.
The harvest moon is rising.
Wraith are never-ending.
I know the future.
Come inside.
I'll show you...
your destiny...
John Sheppard.
They can get in your head.
You okay?
People ever gonna know the truth?
Not my decision.
I think people choose to live
in their own happy little delusions.
They don't really
want to know the truth.
The other victims
had radioactive residue on 'em.
They all did. Once we got wind of it
and our suspicions were confirmed,
the whole thing was ultimately
going to be covered up,
but you tracked down the target
before that could happen.
Well, with serial cases,
you're supposed to look
for any victims who got away.
Which is how you found the motel
and the man who reported
radiation sickness.
He was most likely exposed because he
was in the room next door to the Wraith.
See, we didn't think
to look for bystanders
that could have been accidentally
exposed due to proximity.
To the alien?
No. No.
However, we do believe
that the radioactive
material in this case
is being transferred from the target
to the victims.
But the source is being shielded
from our scanning capabilities.
What is it?
Look, we know that the Wraith don't need
to feed as often as the target does.
I mean, they feed for pleasure,
but not if it means leaving a trail.
Some other reason?
If they're sick or injured,
they can regenerate,
but it requires energy.
The target must expose himself
to high doses of radiation
and has to eat
to counteract the effects.
What's the source?
He's building a device.
We're not sure of its
intended function,
but we know that he was able to salvage
certain parts from his crashed Dart
before we could get to it.
- Well, what about the rest?
- The Wraith are smart.
It wouldn't take them long to learn
the ins and outs of the way things work.
He's already acquired
some of the necessary materials
but he needs more.
He also needs untraceable currency,
or we would have found him by now.
So he makes money by playing poker?
There's got to be a better way.
I guess he could rob a bank,
but that's risky
and it draws a lot of attention.
No, the Wraith love games,
and with their mental abilities,
they are very good at them.
The following
is a worst-case scenario
should the device be detonated.
Excuse me.
Wait here.
- There's a very strong likelihood...
- It's not a bomb.
We need to be prepared
for every possibility.
What would be the point
of overcooking half the United States?
- Revenge?
- Not his first choice.
He wants to send up a flare
signaling the location of Earth
to the rest of the Wraith.
Excuse me.
He would not need that kind of power
to activate a Wraith communicator.
He does if he wants to send a message to
Pegasus and be rescued in his lifetime.
That would require a massive boost.
It would require
more energy than he has now.
- Not even a ZPM...
- I know!
- That kind of burst is uncontrollable.
- I never said it wasn't dangerous.
It could open up
any number of anomalies.
- Like the inter-dimensional rift?
- Would you stop bringing that up?
Why do you have to constantly
remind me?
- You are such a child.
- And yet I am still smarter than you.
Don't worry.
Everything's under control.
Thank you for your co-operation,
Detective.
If you think of anything else,
call me at this number.
If he's not finished yet,
why did he stop hiding bodies?
I don't know. Over-confidence
that he can't be caught?
He left money behind.
How much?
A few thousand.
Not enough to worry about, I guess.
That's it?
You're just going to let me go?
That field medic.
The one you defied orders
to go back and try and rescue?
You knew her personally.
You were...
involved.
Yeah, you know everything.
It was a hard choice.
Certainly you didn't intend things
to go as badly as they did.
Things just...
don't always go the way we plan.
We know where to find you.
Detective.
Remember when I told you
I once met another version of you?
Yeah.
I know you'll probably think
this sounds ridiculous,
but a little while ago, we accidentally
opened a rift in space/time...
Went through to an alternate
version of reality.
Very similar to ours in many ways.
I met a team,
much like the one I work with,
only you were the leader.
You were a hero...
- Saved the world several times over.
- Doesn't sound much like me.
I don't think there's much
difference between you
and the other John Sheppard I met.
It's amazing how one incident
can entirely alter
the course of your life.
Still...
I'd like to believe you have
the same strength of character.
That's why I told you the truth.
What do you want me to say?
For now?
Nothing.
What's going on?
They feed on human energy.
Literally sap the life out of people
using the sucker on their hand.
Dry as a desert outside.
No place to go.
He wants to send up a flare
signaling the location of Earth
to the rest of the Wraith.
Wraith are never-ending.
I know the future.
That would require a massive boost.
He needs more power than he has!
I'll show you your destiny...
John Sheppard.
Recalibrating the scanners to look for
similar isotopes at maximum sensitivity
just shows us huge patches
of radioactive desert.
From 40-year-old nuclear testing.
We're talking
hundreds of square miles.
It's like a needle in a haystack.
Or, he could've abandoned the resources
he had and just gone into hiding.
Yes, he probably got a job as a Klingon
at Star Trek: The Experience.
- That shut down.
- Really? Damn. I wanted to see that.
Dr. McKay, there's a call for you.
John Sheppard.
- Hello?
- I found him.
He thinks he's found him!
How?
I remembered the trailer
from the motel.
One of those old silver bullets.
Just a hunch. You said he needed
more power, so I drove along
some of the more remote
power lines into the city.
Harriman!
He's going to tap into the grid.
We should have
John Sheppard's coordinates.
Listen to me.
I know what I said,
but do not engage.
Do you hear me?
Crap.
ETA to target...
Three minutes.
We have widespread power outages
being reported across the state.
Daedalus is transmitting
new sensor data.
Got it! A massive subspace event.
Ten times the power of an active
Stargate, and getting stronger.
Its scope increases
the longer it stays active.
- What is it?
- It's a transmission.
Coded in Wraith.
I'm working on it.
Target has been acquired, sir.
Take it out.
We have a direct hit!
Target has been neutralized.
The transmission has ceased.
It contained the location of Earth.
Is there a chance
it reached Pegasus?
No.
I've seen
this energy signature before.
I know.
It looks like the device tore a small
hole in the space-time continuum.
- Do you think that was intended?
- No.
Most of the energy meant to carry the
Wraith transmission went thru the rift.
- To where?
- Well, there's no way to know for sure.
Other realities.
I'm sorry,
but I only care about us right now.
If John Sheppard hadn't found
that Wraith when he did,
that transmission definitely would
have made it through to Pegasus.
He saved our asses.
But that transmission
would have been stronger
in any other reality
exposed to the rift.
They could be
in a lot of trouble right now.