Previously on
Stargate Atlantis.
You're both familiar
with the ancient named Janus.
I have information that could lead us
to his secret lab.
- We were attacked.
- By who?
I was hoping you could tell me.
Get the device operational
within one hour
or I will kill him.
Do you understand?
Somehow,
you've found the attero device.
What?
We're locked in.
Wait, there's a very dangerous,
serious problem with the device,
- and we need to talk...
- if the power continues to build,
the gate will reach critical overload
and explode.
Everyone that doesn't need to be here,
get to the edge of the City.
It's not enough.
Move quickly. We have to get everyone
to the lower levels of the tower
to make sure
that everyone will be...
Colonel Sheppard, are you all right?
- How many were up there?
- Two.
I'll go get my people.
They were right here
when I left them.
If the explosion was hot enough,
there might not be anything left
for us to find.
Did you hear that?
We didn't take cover.
Are you all right?
- Are you all right?
- My ears...
I think I've got a some glass
in my back.
We lost the Stargate,
we lost the control room. That's bad.
But we did not lose you.
That's good.
All the troops you've requested
have beamed onboard.
Have them round up the rest
of the humans and confine them
to one of the hangar bays.
Inform our Hive to wait for us here,
and under no circumstances
are they to activate their hyperdrive.
Is that understood?
Yes.
Where are we going?
Atlantis.
Season 5 Episode 11
The Lost Tribe (v. 1.00)
The Projet-SG & SG-66 Teams
www.projet-sg.net
www.seriestele.net
I need you to get Banks
and her team to set up
an auxiliary control room
below the damaged areas.
They've already begun.
How are you?
I'm alive. That's good for now.
I still do not understand
what happened.
The Gate blew up.
That much I surmised.
But why?
I don't know. Where the hell's McKay
when you need him?
All right, so the device creates
a very specific subspace "turbulence"
that makes it impossible
to operate the Wraith hyperdrive.
- I know.
- But there's a side effect.
- The "unforeseen" mentioned.
- It's certainly not seen here
- because there's no Stargate.
- What's the point, Rodney?
Although the subspace turbulence
only affects
the Wraith's hyperdrive systems,
it creates a very dangerous
type of radiation that...
messes with the basic operation
of the Stargates.
Stargates?
What, as in all of them?
All of the Stargates in Pegasus, yes.
And when you say: "messes with,"
you mean what?
Look, when dialed, power will build up
inside the Gate until it overloads.
So you're saying that as long
as this Janus device is running,
every time someone dials a Gate
in the entire galaxy...
It'll explode.
Millions of people will die
if we don't shut that thing down.
Good timing, Mr. Woolsey.
Look,
I don't know what it is
you think we've done,
- but I assure you...
- Take us out of hyperspace.
We haven't arrived at Atlantis yet.
- Atlantis?
- We're within communications range.
We don't want to get too close.
Take us out.
I was hoping you'd be awake
for this.
Well, are we up and running?
Yes, sir. We've routed all the City's
main controls into this room.
- At least we're not blind anymore.
- No, but we're severely crippled.
Without the Gate or the Daedalus,
we have no way of getting to M6H-987
or rescuing Rodney and Dr. Jackson.
What should we do?
5 bucks to anybody who can figure
out how to contact the Daedalus.
Colonel Sheppard?
You got an idea?
No, but I am being hailed
by the Daedalus on subspace.
Does that count?
Technically that's not your idea,
but good enough. Put 'em on screen.
I'll pay you later.
- Daedalus, it's good to...
- Colonel Sheppard.
What the hell's going on?
Where's Caldwell?
I'm afraid I had to relieve him
and his crew of duty.
- How close are they?
- Not close enough to go by Jumper.
Don't worry, I'm more than willing
to return this ship and its crew
- to you.
- In exchange for what?
You've activated the attero device.
I need you to shut it down
and give me its location
immediately.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
It was very clever of you,
luring me
and my ship out into the open
so you could see for yourself
if it worked.
- If what worked?
- I have to admit,
in a way I'm impressed.
I was there 10,000 years ago
when the Ancients
first tried to use it,
but they didn't have
the stomach to leave it on
once they realized how many
of their precious Stargates
it would destroy...
how many humans it would kill.
Sounds like Janus work's.
Give me the location
of the attero device, and once
I have destroyed it,
I will return this crew to you.
Look, it's not what you think.
We have nothing to do with this.
Every minute that goes by
without you telling me
where this device is,
I will kill
a member of your expedition.
Your time starts now.
Give us a second.
I don't think this should count
toward the minute.
I mean, he didn't say no...
Yet.
What are the odds that...
What's this thing called?
Attero device.
What are the odds that this thing was
at the subspace link that Rodney opened?
M6H-987?
I'd say it's very likely.
It's also very likely
that's where they were taken.
It must be a weapon that Janus developed
during the Wraith war.
A weapon to blow up Stargates?
I doubt that was its original design.
Doesn't seem like an effective strategy.
So, a nasty side effect. That's probably
why they stopped production.
Whatever the aliens took from the lab
allowed them to reactivate it again.
Whatever it is,
Todd seems pretty keen to stop it,
enough to risk taking the Daedalus.
But we can't give him the address.
He'll destroy everything in his path,
including Rodney and Dr. Jackson.
John, we don't have a choice.
Our shield was able
to take the explosion,
but if this is happening
on other worlds,
it could kill millions.
Put 'em back on.
Thank God.
We're not the ones behind this.
Very well.
Wait! Wait! I said,
we're not the ones behind this,
but we may have what you need.
Atlantis was attacked yesterday, by
a race we have not encountered before.
They stole a piece
of Ancient technology.
We believe this could be a component
to this attero device.
We managed to track them.
You swing by here, pick me up,
I will take you there myself.
And give you the chance
to take out my hyperdrive
with one of your drones?
I think not.
Why would I do that?
You're one of the few people
in the galaxy
with a ship capable
of dealing with this problem.
And I intend to keep it that way.
Transmit the coordinates
or I will feed
on Mr. Woolsey before your eyes!
Do it.
We have it.
We'll be in touch.
- You really think that's gonna work?
- You got a better idea?
We're on a space ship.
Those doors are designed
to be airtight.
That means something as tiny as air
can't even get through.
- How do you think you will?
- I'm a lot bigger than air.
Yeah... that's kind of my point.
See?
You okay?
- All right. Come on.
- Wait.
What's our plan?
Where are we going?
Get to an access ladder,
head down two floors
to the engineering rooms.
Then we cripple the ship.
You... know how to do all that?
Yeah. Don't you?
Not really.
Watch and learn.
Hyperspace window opening.
Think Todd changed his mind?
He might have realized
how crippled we are.
- We're being hailed.
- Put it up.
My name is Katana Labrea.
I'm a traveler.
Larrin sent me.
Well, is everything all right?
No, as a matter of fact, it's not.
Larrin was hoping you could tell us
why the Stargates are blowing up.
You. Come with me.
Me? Why?
- We'll both go. No need for that.
- No.
I guess it just must be your turn
to use the fitness room.
Right.
Good luck.
You too.
It was the first colony we'd built
on the surface of a planet
in a hundred generations,
and it was leveled in an instant.
I was in orbit when it happened.
We could see the explosion
from space.
I've never witnessed anything
that powerful.
The Gates are made of naquadah.
When they become unstable, the size
of the explosion is unimaginable.
We lost 3,000 people
and two ships,
including our Ancient vessel.
- Larrin would have come herself, but...
- No, I'm sure she's got her hands full.
Look, these aliens
or whoever they are,
they have two of our people hostage.
They need to be stopped.
We have coordinates,
but... we have no ship.
- Then I guess I got here just in time.
- That's what I wanted to hear.
Zelenka, you're with me.
Teyla, I need you to stay here,
all right? The second Todd's done,
there's nothing stopping him
from making a run at Atlantis.
I need somebody I can trust
to stay in charge here.
Good luck.
I locked the door.
- This won't take long.
- So what do we do?
Bring up the main control systems
and disable them one by one?
That's one way to go.
You'd have to lock them out.
Or they could turn them back on again.
Do you have some sort of a passcode
to make sure they're locked out
once and for all?
Nope.
Well, then, what are you thinking?
- We just dropped out of hyperspace.
- I see that, yes.
- Why?
- I'm not sure.
The computer seems to think
it's due to battle damage.
Get our troops
down to the engineering room.
Someone's sabotaging this ship.
What are you doing?
Disabling the ship.
You can't just blast away
at vital systems like that!
What if you take out
the life support system?
Don't worry.
The life support system is that tray.
At least, I'm pretty sure it is.
Okay, we're out of hyperspace.
That's enough. Come on.
You wish to speak to me?
You're the leader?
You need to shut this device down
immediately.
No, I do not.
Okay, look, I understand
wanting to destroy the Wraith.
I do.
But this isn't the way.
I disagree.
I don't know
if you're aware of this or not,
but this device
has a serious side effect.
It makes Stargates explode
when they're activated.
We do not use the Stargates.
Okay.
But lots of other people do.
They are of no concern to us.
So you're just gonna let them die,
millions of people, across the galaxy?
- You're no better than the Wraith.
- Perhaps. But we have little choice.
Why?
Our planet is dying.
It can no longer sustain us.
For the first time
in countless generations,
we must venture out
into this galaxy again,
a galaxy controlled by the Wraith.
If we do not destroy them,
they will destroy us.
This is the way it must be.
They're ahead. When they get to that
planet, they'll open up with everything.
Trust me, they ain't gonna be worried
about collateral damage.
The only chance we have to save
our friends is to get there first.
You want speed?
You've come to the right place.
This is your engineering ?
That's right.
It may not look like much,
but trust me,
we can outrun most anything
in the traveler fleet.
Mila?
Hey.
This is Colonel Sheppard
and Dr. Zelenka.
They're from Atlantis.
Mila's our chief engineer.
- She can't be more than 16 years old.
- 15, actually.
She's been working on ships
since she was four.
We need to get where we're going
as fast as possible.
I want you to do whatever you can
to maximize hyperdrive output.
No problem.
You know, Zelenka knows a thing or two
about hyperdrives himself.
I'm sure he'd be happy
to give you a hand.
Who knows,
maybe you'll learn a thing or two.
The damage is significant.
Begin repairs.
Every second
the attero device is active,
we risk losing more and more
of our alliance.
It has come to my attention that someone
from the crew has eluded capture.
Your freedom has become a nuisance.
Turn yourself in immediately or
we will begin killing off your friends
one by one.
- You have three minutes to comply.
- He's bluffing.
- No, he's not.
- Where are you going?
- I'm turning myself in.
- No, you're not.
- He's gonna start killing people.
- He's gonna kill you.
Well, I hope not.
We need to get armed, free these people,
take this ship back.
Exactly. I turn myself in,
and he'll think he's got us all.
It buys you the time you need
to do what you've gotta do.
- No. I'm not letting you do it.
- Ronon, listen to me...
Jennifer,
no.
Okay.
You're right.
Come on.
We're almost there anyways.
We're talking about the deaths
of millions of people.
How can you be so callous?
And what is it you're so afraid of?
Why are you still in your battle armor?
I can't hurt you.
- I know you're not human.
- You're definitely not Wraith.
And if you were an Ancient, you wouldn't
need our help to activate the device.
What are you?
You're Asgard.
You've encountered our kind before?
No, not just encountered.
I've worked with them,
even called a few of them
my friends.
Indeed.
Of course, the Asgard I knew
were a noble race
who actually helped
the human population in my galaxy.
And where are they now?
Dead.
- But that had nothing to do with us.
- Are you certain?
They were clones...
Copies of copies of copies,
going back generations,
and they suffered irreversible
genetic degradation as a result.
- But you probably already know that.
- Of course,
because we are clones as well,
subject to the same law
of diminishing returns.
And yet,
we are still very much alive.
- So, what, you solved the problem?
- Not entirely.
But once we were able to conduct
our research without interference,
we made significant progress.
Research on humans...
Because our physiology is similar
to what yours used to be.
Precisely.
I take that back.
I have met an Asgard like you before.
His name was Loki,
and he was experimenting
on humans too,
until he was caught
and brought to justice
by the Asgard High Council.
Because they did not believe
the ends justified the means.
That's right.
And look where it got them.
- Well, how's it coming?
- Well...
It does that sometimes.
Don't let it bother you.
- What we are doing here is not safe.
- What else is new?
She is pushing this ship
well past its boundaries.
That's kind
of what we asked for, no?
If we don't get Rodney and Danny back
before Todd gets there, they're goners.
This is the crudest hyperdrive system
I've ever encountered.
It is cobbled together
from mismatching components.
She's gotta be smart
to put a hyperdrive together
- with mismatched parts.
- She's going to burn it up.
Once out of hyperspace,
there's a high possibility
we won't be able
to engage the drive again.
Let's worry about that
when we get there.
What was that?
Just a radiation warning.
The detector's
a little over-sensitive.
I wouldn't worry about it.
I gotta get back to the bridge.
I'll leave you to it.
We came to this galaxy
during the war.
With both of them occupied,
we were free to conduct our experiments.
Unfortunately, the hostilities
came to an end sooner than we thought,
and with an unexpected result.
You were betting on the Ancients.
They may have tried to shut you down,
but at least they wouldn't
exterminate you.
The Wraith do not tolerate
the presence of advanced technologies
other than their own.
Before we knew what was happening,
we were under attack.
We lost our intergalactic ships
in the first battle,
and we did not have the resources
to build more.
So how did you survive?
We had no choice
but to abandon our settlements
and retreat to a place
where the Wraith could not look for us,
a planet with a toxic atmosphere.
That... sounds nice.
It was tolerable at first.
We were able to survive
using simple breathing apparatus.
But over the eons,
the environment has grown so harsh
that not even our armored exoskeletons
can protect us now.
So you ventured back into the galaxy,
that's when you came across this place.
We knew it was built
by the Ancients, and why,
but we were unable to activate it
until you came along.
Look, I... I'm sorry
that you were trapped on a poisonous
planet for the last 10,000 years.
I really am.
I'm sure it was awful.
But that doesn't justify
what you're doing.
My people are dying.
The fact that, as you tell us,
our brothers are already gone,
only reinforces the need.
If we do not do this,
our whole civilization,
a hundred thousand years of history,
will be wiped out forever.
I cannot allow that to happen.
Dr. Keller.
You're the saboteur?
That's right.
Where's your weapon?
- My weapon?
- Yes.
The one you used
to destroy the crystal trays.
I ditched it.
You really think I'd want it
ending up in your hands?
Oh, it's foolish of you
to see me as the enemy.
Really? Why's that?
I'm on a mission
from your Colonel Sheppard.
I seriously doubt that.
It is a long story,
but he has requested
that we neutralize
a very dangerous target.
Then why did you take over the ship?
Why did you attack our crew?
As I said, it is a long story.
The mission, however,
is time-sensitive,
and you have handed us
a major setback.
Hyperdrive, weapons, shields...
they are all down.
- That's a real shame.
- It is,
considering that hundreds
of thousands of humans
could die because of it.
I would think that will weigh heavily
on you in the future.
What are you talking about?
Hyperdrive's coming back up.
And weapons?
Irreparably damaged.
They're no good to us anymore.
I guess you won't be able
to finish the mission, then.
We'll find a way.
Get us back into hyperspace
and get her down with the others.
You okay?
- I thought you were a goner.
- I'm all right.
They need me.
You're kind of expendable.
- I just figured...
- Yeah, I got what you meant by "goner".
- What did they want?
- To talk, actually.
- Oh. How did that go?
- They're Asgard.
- For real?
- Yeah,
a faction that broke off from the guys
we knew thousands of years ago.
- They're the ones inside the suits.
- I did not see that one coming.
- Apparently no fans of the Wraith.
- Are they gonna shut off the device?
- No.
- Then I don't care.
As long as that thing is on,
then millions of people could die.
Besides, I think
I've figured a way out of here.
Really?
This is an Ancient facility,
and Rodney McKay knows a thing or two
about Ancient facilities.
It's been proven,
referring to yourself
in the third person
is a sign of mental instability.
Mentally unstable like a fox!
Okay, so, here's the plan.
I blow the fire-monitoring fuse.
The system suddenly goes dead,
it assumes there could be a fire,
detects lifesigns inside the room,
it unlocks the doors for safety.
Good job.
Good thing they brought you back,
assumed you were dead, was gonna leave.
- Lucky me.
- Yeah, you're welcome.
- So, what do we do now?
- We've got to shut down the device.
- How do we do that?
- We'll just... We'll improvise.
Right.
Todd didn't kill you.
No, but you almost got me killed.
I've never fired one of these
outside of the range before.
You did great.
- Ronon. Good work.
- It's not over yet.
There's an armory down the hall.
We need everyone we can.
We're taking this ship back.
Okay. We need to get
to the device control room.
- It'll be crawling with soldiers.
- A diversion.
- I'm all ears.
- We go to the power relay station,
- we create a massive explosion.
- I never got
- how that made a good diversion.
- What?
You want to clear the device
control room of bad guys, right?
Why would assume if there was a massive
explosion, people would run towards it?
- I would.
- I rest my case.
I'm sorry.
I'm a good person.
I'd want to save people from the fire,
figure out what's going on.
I'd order more guards to protect
the room whoever wants to get to.
Explosion diversions
are the very cornerstone of diversions.
- You don't have any better ideas?
- I don't have any better ideas, yes.
Oh, my God. Please don't kill me.
You need me. Us, us. You need us.
Look, the device needs constant care.
I'm the only one who can work it...
What am I talking about killing for?
You ain't violent. You may've stunned...
- more than we'd have liked, but...
- They're suits.
Suits that house
one of the smartest races ever.
I've always been
a big fan of the Asgards.
- Some of my best friends are Asgards...
- They're empty suits.
See?
- Yeah. I know. I was...
- You were...
Yeah, it's not important.
You know, from what I could tell,
the inside of the suits form
around whoever's in them.
One size fits all...
You sure you have all that
figured out?
I've flown birds a lot harder to manage
than this one.
I'm surprised Larrin
didn't say anything.
Larrin's never brought you up
before today.
Really?
Never, huh?
Nope.
We're about to come out of hyperspace.
Everyone, get ready.
See, I knew this would happen.
- We burned it out.
- We got here, though, didn't we?
Any sign of the Daedalus?
No. Looks like we beat them.
That's the first good news
I've had all day.
Wait,
I've got two ships closing in.
Shields up.
Fire at will.
- Evasive maneuvers might be good.
- I'm on it.
Clear! How come
we haven't run into any of them yet?
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Do a lifesigns scan,
find out where they are.
I have a mass of lifesigns
in the second 302 bay.
They fell back to their ship.
It's still in the bay.
Why?
They saw we'd armed up?
Didn't want to risk a fight?
That doesn't sound like Todd.
I'm gonna check it out.
Take us out of hyperspace.
What?
- They locked us out of flight controls.
- Can you get us back in?
Not quickly.
What's he got planned?
Okay, how long
to get the device shut down?
Five minutes.
All right, look.
You watch the...
- Oh, come on!
- What? What now?
- Something must have spooked them.
- Why?
Aside from encrypting
the access to this...
- But you can break that.
- In a heartbeat,
but you can't operate this machine
without the control key.
Look... the thing they stole
from Janus' lab to begin with.
They've taken it.
One down, one to go.
I'm picking up a third ship.
Wonderful.
That was close.
It flew into hyperspace.
- What?
- Hold on,
- I've got another window opening.
- They're coming right back at us.
What kind of messed-up
battle technique is that?
It's quite a bit out,
nowhere near the planet yet.
Wait... it's the Daedalus.
Contact them.
We're gonna need the help.
- Colonel Sheppard?
- Surprised to see all of you guys.
Same here.
Look, I'm on a Travelers...
I'm on a travelers ship.
We've engaged the enemy.
Have you gotten the Daedalus back?
Because we're gonna need the help.
Todd let us take her back
without so much as a fight.
But he's locked us out of the controls
and retreated to one of the 302 bays.
Why the hell would he do that?
He needs that place destroyed.
- Mr. Woolsey, sir?
- What is it, Marks?
The second we came out of hyperspace,
a pre-programmed sub-routine kicked in.
- Meaning...
- Our main scanners located a facility
and immediately locked
the guidance system into it.
It's taking us to the Attero device.
In a way...
Sir, it's programmed
a collision course.
That's how he's gonna destroy it,
by ramming us into the facility.
Can't we just power down
the facility?
Can't do more than turn the lights off
without the component thing.
We have to do something.
Wait a second.
These suits were designed to protect
from harsh environments?
Technically, yes.
Then I have a really terrible idea.
You're not thinking
what I think you're thinking.
The radiation
would be pretty extreme.
Not to mention electrical discharges
look pretty unfriendly, but...
The antenna has a control crystal.
If we could pull it manually...
It's 50-50 we even get that far.
I'd go 30-70,
but I don't have a better idea,
and the suits,
they should protect us.
We disabled the ship weapons.
- You did?
- Ronon did, yeah.
They didn't have any other choice.
Ramming the facility with the ship
is the only way to take it out.
- Killing all of us in the process.
- I don't think he's worried about us.
They just depressurized the 302 bay.
- You ready?
- Let's just get this over with.
You know we both
don't have to go in there.
When you get killed
by one of those discharges,
someone's gonna have
to finish the job, so...
Great pep talk.
Thanks.
I'm pretty sure
we wanna avoid those touching us.
Thanks, coach.
What are you waiting for?
I have to pull the right one
or the antenna explodes.
Hurry up.
But get it right.
How long before the Daedalus
hits the surface?
A minute, tops.
How many people on board?
Couple hundred.
Look, I've got an idea,
but you're gonna have to trust me.
All right.
Open up the hyperdrive in 30 seconds.
We're gonna have to make a short jump.
- Impossible.
- Not a problem.
You can do this, Marks.
We're all counting on you.
I've almost got it.
We're entering the atmosphere.
Here goes nothing.
What just happened?
- You're welcome.
- What did you do?
I just opened up a hyperspace window
big enough for the both of us.
We just traveled through the planet.
I got it!
I'm back in.
We've got control of the ship.
And not a moment too late.
- They found us again.
- Give them everything you've got.
You're okay, you're okay.
Wrong again.
Did you turn it off?
I did... we did... you did.
Look, where does it hurt?
Everywhere.
I don't suppose
there's a hospital nearby?
I'm pretty sure we're on our own.
Good.
Look, on the bright side,
we'll be dead of dehydration in 5 days,
so you won't have to put up with me
for much longer.
I'm pretty busted up, Rodney.
I don't think
I'm gonna make it that long.
I know it may not seem like it,
but I want you to know
I really res...
- Oh, thank God.
- I sure am glad to see you two.
He's badly hurt.
That's a new look for you.
You know me,
it's function over fashion.
- Is the device still active?
- Not without this.
It's the facility's
main control crystal.
That's not good enough for me.
We have Drs. McKay and Jackson.
Our weapons are not operational.
Please see to it that we never have
to deal with the Attero device again?
- I'm locked on to its coordinates.
- Opening fire.
Leveled.
Good.
- Let's go home.
- Well, you want to... unzip me?
I'll look for a can opener.
Zelenka has helped with ship repairs.
It should be ready to fly in no time.
Then what?
Start a new settlement, I guess.
Good to hear.
You tell Larrin I'll help you
with whatever you need.
Thank you.
We'll be in touch.
Yeah.
I'm sure you will be.
Tell Larrin she doesn't need to wait for
the next galactic emergency to drop by.
I'm a lot more charming
when my friends aren't about to die.
That's not what Larrin said.
See, she does talk about me!
Every now and again.
What does she say?
What, not even a hint?
You all done for the day?
Dr. Cole's taking my shift.
Yeah.
Wanna get something to eat?
Listen,
I'm really glad
you came on the mission.
I mean, without you there, we'd...
probably all be dead.
But...
I just want to be clear,
because,
I just want you to know,
that I'm kind of...
interested in somebody else.
So?
I just didn't wanna give you
the wrong...
Didn't.
I just wanted to get something to eat.
Okay, because I thought...
Yeah, well, you're wrong.
Do you still wanna go...
No. I should probably...
I should go.
How are you?
- It hurts to eat this fruit cup.
- Don't eat the fruit cup, then.
Thank you, Groucho.
Not that I don't appreciate the visits,
but shouldn't you be figuring out a way
to keep the Asgards out of the shield?
One step ahead of you.
Won't happen again.
Oh. Good.
You don't think
they'd make a run at us again?
Well, I'm not sure,
but we did ruin the one plan they had.
They might hold a grudge.
Well, let's hope not.
- I won't be around to find out.
- I heard they're sending you back.
Yeah, I guess I need
some major patching up and recovery.
Landry prefers I do that
there instead of here, so...
The Daedalus already picked up
a Gate left over from the Gate bridge,
and my team is installing it,
so we should have you home in no time.
That's good.
That is good.
Yes. So...
Well, it's been...
- unique.
- Yes, it has. It sure has.
But I do want to say thank you for...
saying that you respected me
when you thought I was about to die.
- Excuse me? I said no such thing.
- Yeah, you did. You were, like...
"I know it may not seem like it,
but I really respect you.",
and that means a great deal to me.
I don't believe I ever finished
that sentence.
- How else would you have finished?
- I would have said "regret."
I would have said
I really regret you being here
because none of this
would have happened...
Otherwise.
So you can only
give compliments to the dying?
It's something I'm working on.
Do you wanna try any of this?
Fries.
Dive right in, take the...
Take the deal there.