Previously on Stargate Atlantis...
So,
I understand you have a proposal.
We've come up with a gene therapy
that alters Wraith DNA.
We think we can make it so that you
will never need to feed
on humans again.
Here. Try this.
His name was Janus.
Causality
is not to be treated so lightly.
- No one's treating it lightly.
- You are,
with your insistence
on continuing these experiments.
We ordered you
to cease these activities
I don't know why all the fuss.
If we do this every time someone comes,
we'll never get any work done.
- We're just meeting him at the Gate.
- We're not just meeting him.
I've been pulled from my regular duties
to help him with his database research.
I've got stuff on the go, you know.
Important, vital projects
for the betterment of the human race.
Apparently there are other people
doing equally important work, Rodney,
as hard as that is to believe.
- An exciting day.
- Absolutely.
- He's ready to beam.
- Very well.
Dr. Jackson, welcome to Atlantis.
Thank you, Mr. Woolsey.
It's great to be back.
Season 5 Episode 10
First Contact (v. 1.00)
The Projet-SG & SG-66 Teams
www.projet-sg.net
www.seriestele.net
I'll have Rodney here
show you to your quarters...
I'd like to get started right away,
if that's okay with you, Rodney?
Sure, sure. What have you got planned?
An exploration of insignificant events?
- Not quite. You're familiar with Janus?
- The inventor?
Yes, he was the lead scientist
and apparently a renegade.
And I've been over all his logs.
Look, this is work we've done already.
I'm sure I have information
that could lead us to his secret lab.
Secret lab?
A place where he conducted and hid
a portion of his unauthorized research.
And if I'm correct,
it's right here...
On Atlantis.
I've been over Janus' database entries
with a fine-tooth comb.
- I never saw any mention of a lab.
- Janus was doing a lot of work
that wasn't exactly approved
by the Ancient council,
so he wouldn't include a full accounting
in this very public database.
Do you include your research
in your reports?
Just get to the point.
He never talked about it in his entries,
but Janus' peers suspected he had
a "bastion of unfettered thought
and experimentation,"
- or as one of his lovers put it...
- He had lovers?
"An isle of solitude
within the City walls."
He was hard to talk to.
People say things like that about me.
They had no idea where the lab could be,
but one assistant recalls a day where
- he turned a corner down a hallway.
- "Today I saw Janus in the hallway... "
- there's a real page-turner.
- But when he rounded the corner,
Janus was gone.
The hallway was a dead end.
He had seemingly disappeared,
I think, into his secret lab.
- Did he happen to mention...
- Which hallway? Yes. He does.
As soon as the Daedalus
unloads its supplies,
we'll be heading off to meet
up with Todd and one of his hives.
You really think
he's going to show up?
And let you guys try out Dr. Keller's
gene therapy on a few of his guys?
Well, we held up
our end of the deal.
We let him use Teyla to take control
of an alliance of Wraith hives.
He's got what he wants.
I should go with you,
I have a relationship with Todd...
That is precisely
why I don't want you there.
This mission is basically going to be
a negotiation, and Todd has...
less baggage with me
than he does with you.
I'm not saying you shouldn't take
the lead on this.
You're second in command here,
Colonel.
My predecessors played fast and loose
with the rules set forth by the IOA,
but protocol plainly states
that in the rare instance
where I am required to leave Atlantis,
you stay put.
You're in command here until I get back.
Understood?
- Try not to blow her up while I'm gone.
- No promises.
Yeah, I think this should be
the last of it.
I was just leaving.
Yeah, I know.
- Here, let me get that.
- Thanks.
So you're going
on this Daedalus thing?
Thank you.
I kind of have to. I'm the one
that'll be administering the treatment.
If, you know,
we ever get to that point.
Right.
I think I should
come with you on this.
Really? Why?
I don't really trust these guys.
You don't trust Todd and his Wraith
or the entire crew
of the Daedalus to protect me
if something goes wrong?
I don't know.
Both, I guess.
- What?
- Nothing.
- Nothing, nothing.
It'd be great to have the company.
- Bye, Rodney. Wish us luck.
- Good luck.
What do you mean, "us"?
Is that a water line up there?
This section of the City flooded
the first year.
Anything salvageable
got moved to the main tower.
It's remote.
That's promising.
He wouldn't want anyone around
when he came in and out of his lab.
Like the bat cave.
Yes... Just like the bat cave.
I'm not picking up
anything unusual...
Something used to be attached here.
And here...
And another one.
Any idea what they are?
- Run-of-the-mill sconce interface.
- Right. Well,
- where are the sconces?
- I don't know.
Maybe the decorator
changed his mind.
You said anything worth salvaging
was moved to the main tower.
Now, tell me you kept detailed records
of what was found and where.
Did we keep detailed records?
Who are you talking to here?
There. That's the hallway.
Can you zoom in there?
There.
There are your light fixtures.
- Must have been knocked loose.
- Possibly.
- But you salvaged them, right?
- They're lights that fell...
Just humor me, okay?
I think we're onto something.
All right.
Here they are.
I've got'em.
That's odd.
Each of these lights
made a different tone.
Does that usually happen
around here?
Not usually, no.
They've been underwater a few days.
Maybe they're just broken.
No, it's a puzzle.
I think we need to activate these
in a specific order.
A 3-digit code?
You know how easy that'd be to break?
There's only 6 variations.
Maybe activate them a number
of times in a specific order.
I don't suppose you recognize
these three notes?
Does it remind me of Janus' favorite
Brian Eno track?
No. No such luck.
Janus' assistant said
he disappeared pretty quickly,
so it can't be a long code.
Maybe it's as simple
as 3 tones in a row.
Go for it.
- Hold on for a second.
- What is it?
- Come here and push against this wall.
- Why?
Please. Just humor me.
I think I'm on to something.
Okay, on the count of three,
push against the wall
as hard as you can, okay?
Okay. One...
Two...
Three...
Son of a bitch.
Controlled magnetic
harmonic resonance.
What?
Tesla was close to something like this
before Edison trashed his lab.
- What are you talking about?
- That wall was specially designed
to de-stabliize when bombarded
with a very specific harmonic resonance.
That's what the tones were.
And the strong magnetic property
of the particles
keeps the door
from crumbling into dust.
It's a great way to hide a door,
if you're looking for a door to open,
it's never going to be found.
It's like a hologram, only better,
because it's solid mass
until the tones are playing.
So you could have just told me
to walk through the door.
- I could have, yes.
- Yes, yes.
Where the hell are we?
Janus' secret lab.
Alert the others.
The device has been activated.
Where is your burly protector?
It's odd to see you
without him nowadays.
He's in the lab.
What are you working on?
- A speech.
- What for?
Well, this is a fairly
momentous occasion.
The Wraith will take a step forward,
not only for their own benefit,
but for that of the entire galaxy.
It's a historic day.
I just think
it deserves some recognition.
What have you got so far?
"Today is an historic day."
It's a good place to start.
Well, it's a work in progress.
That's pretty cool.
- Harmonic resonance.
- Yeah, I was told.
But what happens
if the sound goes off
- and you're in the middle of the wall?
- The wall would break apart your body.
Maybe we should...
I've set up a sub-sonic
tone generator outside.
The wall is now permanently open.
Don't worry.
Good.
So, what have we got?
The good news is
it's definitely his secret lab.
The bad news is
getting in was the easy part.
There are levels of encryption
on all data here
that even the most paranoid
NSA agent wouldn't use.
I mean, it is deep.
Some are straight-up math ciphers,
while others are Ancient puzzles.
And until we start deciphering,
no way to tell what of this stuff does.
Sounds like you guys
make a good team, though.
Well, I guess I'll go back
to being the boss.
- How's that going?
- Pretty boring, actually.
You're more than welcome
to help us crack this first cipher.
You know,
he could have been in Mensa.
Why don't you contact me when
you two geniuses have a breakthrough.
Will do.
Sir, we're being hailed.
Open a channel.
This is Colonel Caldwell
of the Daedalus.
We're ready
to receive your delegation.
The delegation is on their way.
Marks, you have the bridge.
I'm going to meet our guests.
- Thank you for coming.
- Thank you for having us.
Today is an historic day.
Robert Grosseteste once said...
I would like to get started
as soon as possible.
Yes, of course.
But I wanted to recognize...
I have my doubts
that your plan will be effective.
So shall we drop these unfounded
pleasantries and get to work?
Very well.
Dr. Keller, lead the way.
Please, come with me.
- Robert who?
- Never mind.
You know, it's almost dawn.
If you want to call it a night...
What? No, no, no, I'm fine, fine.
But if you need to rest,
I'll completely understand.
Seriously, is everything
a competition with you?
I'm not sure
what you're talking about.
I just found you a secret lab
full of really cool Ancient stuff.
That should score me
some points here.
Okay, I will admit that I may
have been a little brusque with you.
- Just a little.
- The truth is,
I really didn't think
you would have found anything.
Well, that much
I actually understand.
- You do?
- Yeah.
I've spent the majority
of my professional life
being ridiculed for my theories,
most of which turned out to be correct,
by the way.
I'm kind of used to it, Rodney.
Doesn't that bother you?
I mean, no vindication,
no recognition, no credit...
I could say the same thing
about you.
The discoveries you've made,
you probably could've won
the Nobel Prize five times over by now.
Too true.
So, I guess none of us signed up
to get famous, huh?
No, we did it for the money.
Good one.
Wait a minute... You don't get paid
more than I do, do you?
Do you?
Hyperspace window just opened.
Daedalus isn't due back yet.
Get Sheppard.
Colonel Sheppard, sir?
Yeah, just resting my eyes.
Who said that?
I patched into the PA
in your room, sir.
You're gonna want to get up here.
What's going on?
We're tracking a small ship,
in atmosphere. It's coming right for us.
- Get the Jumpers in the air.
- It's closing fast, sir.
It'll be here
in less than 10 seconds.
Shields up.
I still want the Jumpers ready.
Here it comes...
That's impossible.
- What did it just do?
- It passed through the shield.
Yeah, but how did it do that?
I'm not sure, sir.
Ancient ships can do it.
All right, tell Teyla and a team
of marines to meet me at that pier.
They should be
right in front of you.
Don't move!
- What's at the bottom of this tower?
- Rodney.
Rodney, this is Sheppard.
Come in.
- Rodney!
- What's up?
Get out of there right now.
Why?
Control room, what's the status
of that ship?
I'm sorry, Colonel.
They're gone.
- Is it alive?
- You tell me.
I'm not getting
any coherent readings.
Perhaps we should put it
under a medical scanner.
- Okay, do it.
- Go get a gurney.
So is it true
they took Rodney and Dr. Jackson?
Yeah.
- What the hell happened?
- We were attacked.
That much I got, thanks.
- By who?
- I was hoping you could tell me.
Okay, there is no way
this is a coincidence.
We discover Janus' super-secret lab,
and less than 24 hours later, a bunch
of aliens show up, all guns blazing?
Don't think that's a little odd?
Now that you mention it...
They knew exactly
what they were looking for.
Didn't waste any time,
went straight for the lab.
When they came out,
one of them was carrying a device.
Unfortunately,
we haven't had nearly enough time
to go through everything
we found in here,
so there's no way of knowing
exactly what they took.
All this stuff came on when
Rodney and Dr. Jackson came in here.
Pretty much.
It activated probably in response
to Rodney's ATA gene. Why?
What if something in here
has been broadcasting?
A subspace signal...
The only possible answer.
- What?
- We've come across them before.
They're a real-time, instantaneous link
between two Ancient devices.
They can be separated
by half a galaxy.
There's a bunch of aliens out there.
They stumble upon an Ancient lab,
probably built by Janus himself.
It's dormant.
It's not working.
Then one day, out of the blue,
it activates.
So they're standing around.
No idea what's going on.
They discover the subspace link.
They decide to follow it,
they trace it back to us.
And then attack us
and take two of our people hostage?
Rodney and Dr. Jackson
were not the targets.
The wrong place,
the wrong time.
Whatever that device was,
that's what they were after.
All right, good theory.
So what do we do?
We've gotta get out of here.
We're traveling through hyperspace.
Where do we go?
- I'll think of something.
- Really?
Always do.
I tried that.
They zap you when you touch them.
You could told me that
before I touched it.
I could have, yes.
They stripped us of everything but
the clothing, surrounded us with lasers.
- I'm not sure how much play we have.
- We've got one thing going for us.
- What's that?
- We're not dead yet.
Good point.
It's no good.
I'm still not getting
any useful readings.
The suit is emitting
some sort of EM field
that's disrupting the scanner.
I have no idea how to shut it off.
No way to penetrate the shield
and see what's under?
I'm afraid not.
Do you think there's a human
underneath all that armor?
Impossible to say.
Could be a robot.
One thing's for sure... It's not
like anything we've ever seen before.
Dr. Weir did say that there were
other technologically advanced societies
- that we have yet to encounter.
- We've just made first contact.
What do you want me to do?
Cut it open.
Ah, it's no good.
I just dulled the blade.
The neck.
- What?
- Looks like the softest part.
Try the neck.
- It's already dead, Radek.
- We think.
Just do it.
It's working!
Get out. Everyone, get out!
Everyone okay?
Yes.
Somebody really wants to keep secret
whatever's inside that suit.
We've run close to a hundred
simulations based on full medical scans
of the Wraith
we've had in captivity.
- They've all been successful.
- We both know very well
that computer simulations
and live trials are very different.
I don't think
we're doing this cavalierly.
I stand by the data.
It will work.
Perhaps it will.
The question is, do you want it to?
I do see the benefits.
Even if we only used the therapy
on some of my troops...
Say, those whose lives, thanks
to this war, are expected to be short.
Why waste perfectly
good resources on them, yes?
But it will be very difficult for me
to ask those around me
to give themselves over
for the good of the human race.
But it's for your benefit too.
If you don't have to rely
on human feeding,
the war would be over.
Perhaps...
But then what would we do?
Who would we be?
Can we talk to somebody in charge?
I think there's been a misunderstanding.
There's no need
to treat us this way...
- Get the device operational.
- I don't even know what it is!
Oh, great.
It's sealed shut, and they've removed
the door controls from this side.
Where they hell are we?
Judging by the lantian architecture,
I'd guess, you know,
secret Janus facility.
Which is probably bad for us, because
it probably means it's hard to find.
So I guess that means
no rescue any time soon.
Does that look familiar to you?
Yeah, it's the device
from the Atlantis lab.
At least we know
why they brought us.
They need us to get the device
operational. Caught that.
Right, and I don't think we'll get info
from talky McSays-a-lot out there,
so fire up these consoles,
see what we're dealing with.
Not like that.
Let's see.
Yeah, like that.
And then I need to be
right there, yep.
Thanks. There.
We've got five Jumpers in the air flying
a defensive formation around the City
and have the Chair fired up
and ready for you at a moment's notice.
I want marine details every five levels,
locked and loaded,
- ready for my go-ahead, just in case.
- Absolutely.
Colonel, I think
I may have something.
I've been working
under the assumption
that the device they took broadcasted
some subspace communication.
You can trace it?
Yeah, if it was broadcasting
from Atlantis, yes.
But obviously
it's not doing that anymore.
- So...
I'm using the work of Laszlo Babai
as a stepping stone.
You know, combinatorics and...
No offense, but the math I'm using
is so complicated
I don't know if I can
dumb it enough for it to make sense.
Try.
I've been going over
our recorded subspace logs
and I'm trying to extrapolate
the single thread
that will lead us to the area of space
associated with the device.
- Well, I understand that.
- Doesn't accurately represent what...
I get it.
What you're doing is difficult.
Just tell me when you get a hit.
This facility is tapped into
some pretty serious power generation.
- Never seen anything like it before.
- You'd need a lot of power...
What?
I think I know what this thing does.
- What?
- It's an endgame machine.
- How so?
- If it works the way I think it does,
it would mean the end of the Wraith
once and for all.
So how do you destroy the Wraith
once and for all?
I never said "destroy."
It would lead to that, I suppose,
but this device
would stop them dead in their tracks.
How?
It creates a very specific
subspace static...
Turbulence is a better way
of looking at it.
- Which...
- Okay, look.
Although they're all based on
a fairly similar technological premise,
each race has
a slightly different type of hyperdrive.
Ours are based on the Asgard drives.
The Ancients had their own,
the Wraith have their own technology.
- All right.
- So at its base level,
a hyperdrive allows you to travel
by entering and exiting subspace.
- Okay, this much I already know, yes.
- Okay, so, if this machine
is capable of actually
functioning safely,
it disrupts the very specific
subspace frequencies the Wraith use.
So they couldn't use hyperdrives.
That's the genius...
They would be able to.
It's just that their particular channel
of subspace would be destabilized
and the ship would be ripped.
Every time a Wraith ship
enters hyperspace, it self-destructs?
- Yeah.
- Pretty effective.
Because even if word got back
that they should stop using hyperdrives,
they'd be stuck where they were.
They could only travel using sublight.
Because Ancient ships' hyperdrives
operated on a different frequency,
the Ancients could
pick them off one by one.
Yeah, or just leave them to die
in the vastness of space.
So, what's the catch?
The catch is that Janus ran
a three-day test about 10,000 years ago
and then shut the whole project down
because of "unforeseen side effects".
Right, which were?
Well, it's not clear.
But that's the key to the whole shebang.
Janus brought that back to Atlantis
but kept it connected here.
- One won't work without the other.
- They think we can make it operational.
Cause we can. We've everything we need.
The question is whether we should.
The last time I went down this road,
I kinda destroyed a solar system.
And I'm not too keen about experiencing
those "unforeseen side effects".
- So what do we do?
- It's simple.
We reason with them?
Obviously you're excited about ending
the Wraith's reign once and for all.
But the reality is
this device and this facility
were abandoned by their creator
for a very good reason.
See... it doesn't work...
At least not safely.
That's from what my friend can tell.
Look, we share the same goal.
Perhaps we have many things in common.
Look, given the right amount of time,
we could get the device to function,
but we'd have to contact our people
and bring in a much larger science team.
See, I'm not that kinda scientist,
and my friend here...
Get the device operational
within one hour
or I will kill him.
Do you understand?
I understand. Yes.
Great plan, Danny.
Great plan.
Why the suits?
Well, they're not in battle anymore.
I thought it was their SWAT gear,
but they still have it on.
Maybe they're more than just armor.
Some sort of protective suit.
Maybe they can't function
in our livable atmosphere.
We should add it to the list of things
that have nothing to do with the task.
Those suits might be the key to
figuring out who these guys really are.
Well, you work on understanding them.
I work on trying not to get us killed.
- You got something for me?
- Yes. There.
M6H-987.
That's my best guess.
- Are you sure?
- Well, about 80% sure.
All right, it's our only lead.
I'll have to do.
- Doesn't have a Gate on it, does it?
- No.
Of course not.
- Daedalus still out of range?
- Yeah, I'm afraid so.
Their rendezvous point with Todd
isn't even near a Stargate.
Get to the Jumper bay, boost its
communications range as much as you can.
- What are you planning?
- We've got to get to that planet.
We'll gate as near as we can
to the Daedalus with a Jumper,
have them pick us up en route
to the planet.
- Give me half an hour.
- I'm gonna get the team ready.
That main chamber
houses the subspace antenna.
- It harnesses the static into subspace.
- It will once I light it up.
- What? You're already ready?
- Well, it wasn't broken.
He just shut it down.
All you need is that,
a basic understanding
of Janus' coding style,
and here's where I come in again,
the Ancient gene. We're ready to roll.
Rodney, you don't have to do this.
What?
If turning this on means a solar system
is gonna explode, then let's not.
- They'll kill you. We have no choice.
- Yes, we do.
I do nothing, they come, they kill you.
Who gets killed next ? Me.
To tell you the truth, I'm fond of me,
so might as well do it, you know, now
while you're still alive
as opposed to, you know, then.
All right.
You still alive?
I think so.
I'd hate to think
Heaven looks like this.
Who says we went to Heaven?
It's operational.
Anything out of the ordinary?
No. Everything is in the green.
I mean, it's working great.
What about those
"unforeseen side effects"?
They're still unforeseen.
It's working, and we're still alive.
Okay, so, what now?
Maybe... a nice pat on the back and an
all-expense-paid trip back to Atlantis?
You have an urgent message
from your hive.
I assumed you'd want
to take it privately.
Go ahead.
Very well.
Permission granted.
I shall remain here.
Is everything okay?
One of our facilities is under attack
by a rival hive.
Our two support ships
must depart for battle.
My hive will remain here,
continue the work with Dr. Keller.
I'm glad to hear that.
Oh, not the under attack part,
that's unfortunate, of course.
I just meant...
Never mind.
- Marks, what the hell just happened?
- How did you do that?
How did we... Surely you don't think
we had anything to do with that.
- You've tricked me.
- What?
This was your plan all along.
Somehow, you've found
the attero device.
The what? We have no idea
what you...
Commander,
we've been trying to contact you.
- The other cruisers were destroyed.
- I know.
We've been betrayed.
What should we do?
I have control
of the humans' transport system.
I'll begin beaming in our troops
immediately.
We're taking this ship.
Come on.
- What?
- We're under attack.
We got to get to the armory
and get you a gun. Come on.
Locked.
Ronon!
We're locked in.
That should limit their movements.
Continue beaming in our troops.
10 minutes and counting.
Still no problem.
- Oh, boy...
- What? What is it?
I think I just found a log entry
that tells what the side effect is.
It's not harmful radiation, is it?
We're safe. It's the rest of the galaxy
that's gonna have problems,
including Atlantis.
I've got to shut this thing down.
Step away from the device.
Okay, wait.
There's a very dangerous,
very serious problem with the device,
and we need to talk to your boss...
Okay, all set.
I'll have Chuck dial M5R-179.
You should be able to contact
the Daedalus once you get there.
- Nice work.
- Thanks. Good luck.
Thanks, we're gonna need it.
All right, dial up.
What's that?
We've got a power spike
at the event horizon.
What? Power is building within the Gate?
No, no, no. That can't happen.
Colonel, do not lower the Jumper
into the Gate room.
- Why not?
- For some reason,
there's an unprecedented
power build-up within the Gate.
Power build-up from where?
It's coming from within
the event horizon. Oh, no.
- This is very, very bad for us.
- Just shut it down.
It's probably a faulty Gate
at the other end.
I'm... I'm trying.
It won't let me.
All right, I'm coming down.
What do we do,
wait 38 minutes and ride the puddle out?
I wish. If the power continues
to build like this,
the Gate will reach critical overload
and explode.
- Explode?!
- I told you it was very bad for us.
- How does something like this happen?
- I don't know.
- How long do we have?
- Not long at all. About 90 seconds.
- 90 seconds?!
- I would say closer to 60.
We've got to evacuate
everyone in the tower.
The Gate exploding is equivalent
to 12 nuclear explosions.
There's nowhere we could evacuate
quickly enough to a safe distance.
- The shield.
- What?
Collapse the City's shield
around the Gate, contain the explosion.
Yes, yes, that might just work.
The Gate will reach
a critical limit in five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
one.
- Don't look at the blast!
- Might have mentioned that before!
I'll see if I can divert
more power to the shield,
see if I can block more
of the radiation...
And now what?
The shield continues to diffuse
the energy of the blast.
Every second it's contained within
the shield, the explosion gets weaker.
How long does it take?
- Oh, no.
- What?
The shield needs another minute
to contain the full brunt of the blast,
but we're frying out the emitters. Don't
know how much longer I can hold this.
- Shut down, transfer all the power.
- Yes, I'm trying.
Everyone that doesn't need to be here,
get to the edge of the City.
Move! Everybody!
You're gonna want to get out of here.
Teyla, please.
Come on, you can do it, Radek.
It's going down.
We're gonna make it.
No...
It's not enough.