Previously on Knight Rider...
Olara Kumali... she's the best hope
to end the civil war in central Africa.
I'm going to give you an ambassador,
but you're gonna have to do a little something for me.
They're going to give you a box.
The material in the box is hafnium.
You're having me build a bomb?
No, I'm having you collect pieces
so I can build a bomb.
Get into this car now and gun it to 100 miles per hour.
And then you stay on that road.
If you dip from 100 miles per hour,
the bomb will just explode automatically.
I'll find you.
You, too.
I got something. No!
Carrie?
Oh, my god.
Guys, what do we know?
All communications are down.
I can't get a visual on any of our people,
including Carrie.
Open a line to Mike.
Mike. what's happening?
Warehouse where they were holding the ambassador
has been blown.
I think Carrie and her people are down.
Any idea what your destination is?
No, Stevens told me
to travel North and stay above 100.
We're on it, Mike.
Zoe, go to the warehouse
and find out what happened to Carrie and our team.
I should go, too.
No, Sarah, I need you and your father
to figure out how to defuse a bomb
without dropping below 100 miles an hour
or veering off course.
Come on, dad.
Billy, we have to find Stevens.
Okay.
Carrie's a survivor.
She'll be all right.
Put her out of your head.
Let's get this done.
Michael, satellite imagery
is showing a blockage in the road ahead.
Are you serious?
We've been on the road for, like, five minutes.
You put up everything
on the touch screen except for my speed.
Would you like me to drive?
Sorry, Kitt.
You're programmed with too many safety protocols.
You slow down to avoid a pedestrian,
and that bomb will blow.
But go to attack mode.
And can you get me lights and sirens?
Will this suffice?
Kitt,
This is awesome.
A good idea, but I'm afraid the bottleneck ahead
is the result of a construction zone
merged to a single lane.
Cars have nowhere to go.
And neither will we.
Where were you on that one, super car?
Sorry, Michael. He was hidden quite well.
Well, I hope this guy can drive,
Because this is about to get gnarly.
Sorry!
Bomb in my trunk!
pull over!
I always wanted to elude the cops in a high-speed chase.
Just not quite like this.
I do not understand your enjoyment in breaking the law.
Eh, speeding is fun.
Is it fun that there's
an impassable obstruction ahead?
Binocular enhance.
You know what this calls for.
- I do.  - Will the cop be okay?
He should be fine.
I guess that'll have to do. Turbo boost.
Remember, you must stay above 100 miles per hour.
Yeah, you honestly think I've forgotten?
Any more obstacles coming up?
Funeral processions, circus trains?
Duck crossings?
Not immediately.
But there will be numerous obstacles
in the next 50 miles.
Kitt, we are gonna ditch this bomb,
find Stevens, and get Olara back.
You with that?
Yes, I'm with it.
Kitt, contact the S.S.C.
Tell them it's Stevens. Patch it through.
You didn't have to blow the warehouse.
And you didn't have to tell you friends where I was.
And now your friends are dead. Lesson learned.
Is Olara okay?
You know, I don't want you to take this personally.
Michael, it just doesn't do me any good
to talk to you anymore.
So will your boss please speak up? Uh, yoo-hoo?
Mike's boss? I know you're there.
Alex Torres,
of knight research and development.
Well, pleasure to meet you,
Alex Torres of knight research and development.
I have a question for you.
Do you have access to funds?
What kind of funds are we talking about?
A billion dollars.
You have less than two hours.
My boy Michael'll tell you what happens
if you don't deliver.
I don't doubt your resolve,
but a billion's gonna take some time.
Spare me.
Play around, I will kill the ambassador
And I will make 30 miles of this country glow.
Have a nice day!
Billy.
What do we have?
I found satellite imagery
of Stevens fleeing the mill property in a helicopter,
but the flight patterns are too erratic to track.
I pulled the call numbers,
distributed them to every air field within 200 miles.
That's a good idea.
I have another idea. Pay Stevens his money.
But we'll never
get a billion approved so quickly.
Besides, if we pay him,
he could still blow the bomb and kill the ambassador.
GPS is on a closed circuit.
Kitt can't hack it.
Then we transfer the bomb into another car.
That won't solve the problem.
Only delay it.
At least we save Mike and Kitt.
Mike and Kitt are the only ones
capable of keeping this thing from blowing.
Well, what if Mike bails out?
And we detonate the bomb inside Kitt?
Kitt can't contain this blast.
How do you know?
Beause I built it.
Just got off the phone with Washington.
We have 45 minutes
to present a viable solution.
Inbound planes on screen?
Right away, Mr. Torres.
Are you crazy?
Kitt's headed toward a highly populated area.
It doesn't matter.
Kitt can survive a missile hit.
Unless we order him not to.
45 minutes, they'll launch their missiles,
unless you can figure out
how to defuse that bomb.
Dad,
you wanna weigh in on this?
I got it.
And I thought I was crazy.
We're making the necessary arrangements.
We'll be there within 40 minutes.
Kitt, given your current velocity and trajectory,
compile a list of possible targets
where Stevens might detonate the bomb.
- Compiling now.  - Any luck tracking Stevens?
The helicopter seems like a dead end.
We're digging into his personal history
to see if we can figure out where he might be hiding.
We are running out of time
to get the ambassador to the negotiations,
so dig faster.
She's been unconscious since we found her.
B.P. Is 90 over 50.
She's got a few broken ribs,
and her left lung may be collapsed.
Thank you. We'll take it from here.
Let's get her intubated and in for a C.T.
We need to see what kind of damage
is under these broken ribs.
Yeah, yeah, I hear ya.
I've calculated the possible targets
based on our current course and speed.
And?
In 56 minutes,
We will arrive at a government disposal facility.
Disposal for what?
Nuclear waste.
And detonating a nuclear bomb
in a nuclear waste dump?
- Would be catastrophic.  - Get Sarah.
Our target is the nuclear waste dump
about 40 miles away.
How far out are you guys?
You should be seeing us now.
Mike, two minutes till the F-15s get here.
What F-15s?
You didn't tell him about the F-fif...
Nothing to worry about, Mike.
We got the road blocked off,
but there's an overpass up ahead.
We need to do this now.
Ready when you are.
Kitt, normal mode.
Initiating transformation.
See, Kitt? Fun, right?
A riot.
It's in! Lift off!
Copy that.
Lifting off.
Glad someone's calm.
Gus?
Yeah, we might be in a bit of a pickle.
Oh, god.
Folks,
We may have us a little contact.
I suggest you go ahead
and maybe get in those crash positions
we all love so much.
- We're not gonna make it.  - Sure we are.
No, you're right. We're not.
Kitt, what's the probability we hit the overpass?
Calculating collision probability.
This is gonna be really bad.
Collision probability...
100%.
Please brace yourselves for impact.
Kitt, speed and course.
Speed is holding at 134 miles per hour,
But we're veering off course.
Gus, we don't get back on that line,
This bomb's gonna blow!
Back on track.
Easing off.
You okay?
That was not fun.
You said it, Kitt.
Kitt, hook up to the plane's computer.
Run a diagnostic.
We maintain this speed and heading,
Stevens will never know we're 10, 000 feet up.
Avionics at 73%.
Hydraulics at 47%.
Structural integrity, 61%.
Landing gear is non-operational.
What do you mean, "non-operational"?
To use the technical term,
it's gone.
Kitt, transfer the call to the monitor
and make sure Stevens can't see us.
Hey, sorry about the detour,
but we're back on track now.
Oh, really? Be sorry again and you'll explode.
And why can't I see you?
I don't know.
Maybe the radiation
from the hafnium you stuck in my trunk
is messing with your signal.
Oh, but Mike, I love seeing you.
You're so pretty.
Well, why don't you come and say hi?
I'd love a little one-on-one time.
Oh, Mike.
I'm sure gonna miss you
when you're in a thousand little pieces.
Now put your manager on. I have to lodge a complaint.
I'm here. I don't see my money yet.
I'm working on it.
Okay, Alex Torres.
I have someone here who wants to say hello.
Olara.
Do you have anything to say
to the guys who are gonna let you die?
Do not give him anything.
You so crazy.
You have a half hour.
Guys, where are we on that bomb?
We'll get back to you.
I've never seen anything like it.
Great. Kitt, what do you think?
It's makeup doesn't match anything in my database.
Given stevens' penchant for trickery,
I'd strongly advise against attempting to disarm it.
I count five different triggers.
Yeah.
In theory, we could detonate the bomb
at an altitude which would render its fallout ineffective.
Explain.
If we jettison the bomb into the stratosphere,
its radiation will be carried by the jet stream
to the atlantic ocean
where it will disperse, doing minimal damage.
What altitude?
Taking into account current weather patterns,
the bomb's size,
the atmospheric conditions
relative to our global position...
51, 255 feet.
No way.
We could probably do it.
Gus, this plane has a ceiling
of 32, 000 feet, okay?
At 50, 000 feet,
the pressure could rip our fuselage,
which is already hurting from the collision.
Can we do it or not?
Yeah, she can do it.
Start climbing. Stay on course.
But don't crank it too far above 160 miles an hour
or stevens might get suspicious.
You have 27 minutes.
Roger-dodger.
Stevens' history drops off a cliff
after he left the pentagon.
Scattered financial records,
no discernible place of residence.
Reports claim he approached a few companies
about private funding for his satellite.
The only interesting lead I turned up
was his name
on a number of flight manifests to Phoenix.
Does he have any family there?
No obvious connection I can find.
Keep on it.
They're closing her up now.
So the next 24 hours...
Dial 118.
Is this her colleague?
Yeah. I'll let her know.
Sure. Okay.
Doctor says you came in with Carrie.
That's right.
- She's your colleague?  - And my friend.
Mmm. Well, she's in surgery.
There's no damage to the spine,
but the C.T. shows that one of her broken ribs
pierced her pulmonary artery.
That's what they're trying to repair now.
Are you a doctor?
No.
Company notified me.
- What company?  - Knight research?
C.I.A.
I don't understand.
Why did the C.I.A. notify you
about an injured F.B.I. agent?
Because I'm her father.
Lawrence Rivai.
Okay. Let's go, hank.
There we go.
Slow. Slow, slow, slow.
Kitt.
How long till we're over the target?
1 minute, 43 seconds.
How long till we hit altitude?
1 minute, 39 seconds.
Go... ho ho ho ho.
Why do we always have to cut these things so close?
Great.
Good job.
Okay. This is liquid plastic.
It'll mold itself around any object
and form a protective layer.
It'll ensure that the bomb
doesn't get jostled and blow,
and Hank tosses it out.
Wait, why can't we toss it out ourselves?
At that altitude,
if you are not inside my cabin
when we open the back door,
you will either freeze
or asphyxiate within seconds.
All right. Got it.
Yeah, got it.
Kitt, transfer the call to the S.S.C.
All right, Alex Torres.
It's the end of the road.
Bottom of the ninth.
The last hurrah.
The money should be in your account any minute.
Ah, now, see... you gotta remember,
I used to work for the government.
I know you're all liars and crooks.
so if you're planning to stall,
the man who has his finger on the trigger
is gonna be very upset.
We all want this situation
resolved quickly and peacefully.
Really? I don't. You have one minute.
We're over the target!
Into Kitt now. Come on!
Hank, hang on to the bomb
till I tell you to let go.
Come on, doc.
Pressurizing cabin now.
Kitt, open the cargo door.
Plane's structural integrity
is at maximum stress levels.
We're past the location.
- Release the bomb.  - Not yet.
This plane can't take much more of this.
Just hold on.
Okay, we're at altitude.
Hank, release the bomb now!
Still nothing, Alex.
You know, I hate to say this,
but I just don't believe ya.
I don't control the treasury, Stevens.
A lot of people have to sign off on this.
Please tell that to someone who cares.
You do this,
and it's on your conscience
for the rest of your life.
Oh, no. It's on yours.
Guys, hold on!
Billy! Get that feed back up!
I've got no signals.
Kitt, what's happening?
We have lost power.
We're back on line.
She's coming on up.
Lost the navigation computer!
Auxiliary power has been restored.
Our rate of descent is decreasing.
God, I hate flying.
Equalizing pressure and de-icing windows now.
You guys okay?
Yeah.
Kitt, I thought you said
the bomb had a blast radius of 30 miles.
No, I said its radius would be
10 miles for each gram of hafnium,
and we provided Stevens three grams.
If that's true, we should all be dead.
By my calculations,
the radius of the blast was 6.2 miles,
which would imply that Stevens
used approximately 1/5 of the hafnium.
Stevens has another bomb?
Why would he put a bomb inside Kitt
if he had another bomb?
Because he knew we'd devote all our resources
to help Mike.
He was right.
He has another target.
And by now,
he's probably already there.
Alex, how's Carrie?
We don't know anything yet.
Here's, um... for your coffee.*
Mmm. Thank you.
You must be proud of her...
following in your footsteps.
Carrie had been accepted to Columbia Law
just like her mother.
Instead, she goes to Quantico.
You didn't want her to?
Horrible hours,
lousy pay,
risking one's life for an ungrateful employer?
She's good at her job, Mr. Rivai.
She would have been good at anything.
What we do is necessary,
And she knows it.
I have been doing this for 30 years,
young lady,
and I understand what is necessary.
Then you of all people should understand
that the sacrifices are worth it.
My only daughter will probably die
on that operating table.
Still think it's worth it?
Okay.
We'll set a course for the pacific,
get everybody off the plane and then scuttle it.
Mike, I need you and Sarah to drop inside KITT
When we get a location on Stevens.
- Copy.  - No.
Sarah.
No, if Josh and Gus wanna jump, that's fine.
But you're coming with Mike and me and KITT.
I can safely accommodate up to four passengers
during a drop.
Okay, all right.
When the time comes, I'll drop inside KITT
with the two of you.
We managed to repair the damage,
and for the moment, she's stable.
But the problem is we can't put her on a respirator
because the forced breathing
could tear the stitches in her artery.
So now we wait and hope that she
can continue to breathe on her own.
Can I see her?
Take your time.
You dumb kid.
Dumb, stupid kid.
Come on, Stevens.
What the hell were you doing in Phoenix?
Speak of the devil. On screen.
Maybe... maybe you can help me with something.
According to the bomb's GPS,
The bomb exploded over the target.
And yet, it didn't explode over...
The GPS doesn't measure altitude.
Well played, Alex Torres.
No more games, Stevens.
What do you really want?
Oh, something that money cannot buy.
That last bomb...
Yeah, that was just window dressing.
The next one will unleash horrors
that you cannot bear to imagine.
What does that mean?
"something money cannot buy."
It means he's a true believer.
But if we can figure out what he does want,
then we'll be able to stop him.
We're right here.
You're in the hospital.
Stevens rigged the warehouse, and it exploded.
Pen?
"Valdor."
Valdor.
That's what she wrote down.
Uh, John Valdor pitches for Boston.
Val-d'or... a city in Quebec.
Valdor Chemical.
Bring that up.
They produce chemicals
for household products, cleaning supplies.
Cross-check it against Stevens.
Nothing.
Try again with the Pentagon.
There's something here.
It's encrypted but I can get through it.
Mike, are you getting this?
Yeah. KITT gave us some broad strokes.
The files detail a government contract
for Valdor to synthesize compounds for chemical weapons.
That's impossible.
There aren't supposed to be
any chemical weapons plants in the US
These documents indicate otherwise.
Stevens is gonna blow the plant.
That's what he wants.
Destruction on a massive scale
to prove to the Pentagon
that they were wrong for not building his weapon.
The guy wants revenge.
KITT, do the documents say where the plant is located?
No, but I am currently accessing
the location of Valdor's production plants.
It could be any of them.
What about that one?
It's in Phoenix.
That's it!
Mike, that's your target.
KITT, can you access security cameras
for that Valdor plant?
I'm already attempting to do so.
Maybe they're not there yet.
Or maybe it's the wrong location.
There we go.
And there they are.
Olara's with them.
Have gus set a course?
KITT, what's our ETA?
The plant is 142 miles from our current location.
We can be at an optimal drop point
in 34 minutes.
KITT, how many people are in that plant?
It appears very few at this hour of the night.
I'll alert the local authorities.
Call this in and 50 black and whites will show up.
Spook Stevens, and he'll blow that thing sky-high.
We can handle this.
All right, Mike.
You finish it.
Why are you doing this?
The country is incapable of taking care of itself.
They just don't know it yet.
So you're going to prove it by blowing up a building?
I handed them a weapon that could've stopped all of this.
They just didn't wanna make it.
But after today, they will.
I have spent many years of my life
trying to protect my country
from self-important children like you.
Hey, you know what?
During this whole time,
I just didn't feel bad once about killing you,
And I still don't.
All right.
I want you to lower the gate,
Then I want you to wait a half an hour.
Then I want you to get them in,
And then I want you to take the $1 million ransom
We got paid for that one and go.
Got it? Go.
Who is your mother?
We will reach our drop zone
In 32 seconds.
Thanks for everything, Hank.
Good-bye, Hank.
Couldn't have done it without you.
Dad, come on.
Let's go.
Kitt, protocol theta 7-3.
Dad!
Kitt, open the door!
I'm sorry. Per dr. Graiman's programming,
I cannot.
Dad, what are you doing?
Sarah, I can't leave these guys right now.
I'm fine. Just do your job.
Find Stevens and stop him.
Dad!
I love you.
Are you sure about this, Doc?
If I can help, I'm staying.
Drop 'em.
I must commence the drop or we will miss our window.
Kitt, commence the drop.
Sarah, strap in now.
Ooh!
Kitt is away.
You're quite a ride, kitt.
Glad you're enjoying it.
We will have ground impact in 38 seconds.
Gus, you won't be held responsible
If we've got to scuttle.
Sir, I'm not gonna put her on a possible collision course
with a hawaiian island peak.
I never jumped ship before, don't intend to start now.
Come on, Gus cut the cowboy crap
and let's ditch this bird. Tell you what.
You run the calculations, get me that landing zone,
I can set her down.
You got it. Let's do it.
You guys are crazy.
I'm jumping, no doubt about it.
I understand, son.
Permission granted.
Sorry, Gus, Dr. Graiman.
How long?
Six minutes, 12 seconds.
Stevens appears to be arming the bomb.
I hope six minutes is enough time.
I've been running the numbers.
If the bomb explodes in that plant,
The chemical reaction alone...
I know, billy.
We're talking an immediate death toll of six figures.
The worst disaster ever on American soil.
Get respiratory in here stat!
She's not breathing.
What happened?
I got no pulse!
Get me a crash cart now!
Can somebody turn off that alarm?
And get them out of here!
Charge 200.
Clear!
Charge 300.
Okay, I've got a pulse.
Let's get an update and some vitals.
Tell radiology we need a stat ct chest.
Make sure those stitches are holding.
Landing zone is confirmed.
Dropping down to 7, 000 feet.
We're 81.3 miles from the landing zone.
Currently traveling at 178 miles per hour.
Head winds at 53 miles per hour.
The C-130 is attempting to land.
Shall I patch the audio through?
I thought they were bailing out?
Kitt, get dad on chat line.
Dad, I thought you jumped?
Gus needed my help.
We're gonna land this. Don't worry, I've done the math.
We're in good shape.
You just concentrate on what you're doing,
And we'll see you shortly.
Okay. Be careful.
You, too.
There's no one better than Gus.
He'll be fine.
Stevens is streaming
A live video message from the plant.
I will put it on-screen.
Video message? To who?
Everyone.
The pentagon refused to build my design,
They called it excessive and unnecessary.
This is a weapon that would eliminate war.
If you wanted Bin Laden dead,
Just push in the coordinates and it was done.
But you see nobody listens
Unless something horrible happens.
And now, once again,
It will.
In exactly five minutes,
I will detonate a hafnium bomb
In the valdor chemical plant.
Now, if you had my weapon,
You could position it in time to stop me,
But you don't.
Good luck.
It's disrbing that Stevens truly believes
he's acting in the best interest of mankind.
I know, Kitt. That's why he's a crazy person.
Mike, did you see that?
Yup, that's guy's really lost it.
Don't worry. We're almost there.
We are approaching the barricade.
Put all available camera angles on the screen and enhance.
Kitt, go stealth attack mode.
Initiating transformation.
Stealth attack mode achieved.
Kitt, I need you to disable their radio frequencies.
Accessing and corrupting now.
We will encounter resistance in 14 seconds.
Kitt, what kind of weapon does he have?
Glock nine millimeter, extended clip.
How many rounds?
Twenty rounds.
That means you should be done right about... now.
Ooh, that's such a turn-on.
I'll go in alone.
You tell me where they are, I'll take them out.
I need you to back me up, can you handle it?
Yeah.
Michael, these men are armed and very dangerous.
Are you still having fun?
This part I don't like so much.
Enemy at your one o'clock high.
Another approaching three o'clock low.
10 yards down the right corridor
There is another target.
Stevens is in the second room on your left.
Olara and another employee are with him.
Perfect.
Do you have a plan?
I'm gonna walk in and shoot them.
Subtle.
I thought so.
Mike, he is holding the trigger!
Mike.
How are you? I am...
I am so impressed, man. Really, I...
How did you find us?
Let her walk and I'll tell you.
Oh, no, no, no. Mike, I'm sorry.
Sincerely I'm sorry.
Nobody's walking out of here,
Including me.
Stevens, disarm the bomb.
Mike, why do you do this job?
Because they let me shoot bad guys.
Mike, you are fighting for people
Who do not have the mettle to do what's necessary.
See, I disagree with you there, Stevens.
How's that? Well, I'm here, aren't I?
Yes, you are.
And that's exactly my point.
One man.
They send one man
to stop this.
And you can't.
You know what, stevens?
For the first time all day, you're probably right.
Sarah, trigger!
Nice grab.
Oh, my god.
Thanks.
It's all right. It's all right.
You're safe. You're okay.
Oh.
Come on, ambassador. We got a chopper inbound.
If you leave now,
You can make it to the negotiations.
But I've already missed the negotiations.
We made a few calls. You can still make it.
You good?
Oh, yes, mike. I'm good.
Good.
Hey.
Still holding a trigger.
Just hold on, bomb squad will be here any second.
You can't leave me here.
You'll be fine. Just...
Don't let go.
Thank you very much. Nice to meet you.
Mike.
Mike!
Fuel is dumped. Approach looks good.
Thanks for the help, Doc.
Any time, gus. Let's get this sucker
On the ground.
Sounds good to me.
Sorry, doc.
Remember, boys,
Don't shoot the girl holding the trigger.
This is your ride.
Mike, I owe you everything,
And my country owes you as well.
It is so good to know there are people
Who understand what is right
And are willing to fight for it.
Thank you, Mike
Good luck, olara. We'll be watching.
Okay.
Michael, may I speak with you please?
You are speaking with me, kitt.
I have something we need to discuss.
It's important.
Dude, it's been a really long day.
And if you're secretly falling in love with me,
I'm gonna be awfully upset.
So, how do you feel?
Not great.
Zoe told me to tell you that they caught stevens
And stopped the bomb.
Did the doctor...
Do you have any idea when I'm gonna get out of here?
Carrie, Carrie,
Your rib pierced what may be
The most important artery in your body.
It's a miracle that you're alive.
Just say it.
It's gonna be months and months before you're fully recovered.
You're never gonna work in the field again.
You don't know that.
I'm sorry. It's over.
This... this life is over.
Thanks a lot, douche-nozzle.
Next time you leave me holding the trigger
to a live bomb,
We're gonna have a problem.
Sarah, we got word from the ssc
About the plane.
Did it make it back okay?
No, it didn't.
When they were coming in for a landing,
There was an explosion.
I don't know,
The fuel line maybe.
Sarah, no one survived.
I'm so sorry.
Mike...
Sarah,
Our father is dead.