Can I get another?
You're a great dancer.
A professional?
I am a professional.
How did you know?
Really?
Well, that might be the best thing i've heard all day.
Well, it's gonna be the last thing you hear from me.
So why don't you pick up your knuckles
And go drool somewhere else?
Attitude.
I love it.
You know, you and I could really
do some damage together, sweetheart.
Yeah?
Well, you're half right.
Hey, I'm gonna need two bouncers
and could you call a cab and have it ready
to go to the hospital?
Oh! I'm in love.
And would you mind throwing some ice
into a plastic bag for me?
- No problem.  - Thanks.
I'm gonna ask you to leave one more time.
Come on.
You know you want it.
Come on, baby. Let's get outta here.
- You ice.  - Thanks.
He's gonna need this.
I see you're dealing with things in a healthy fashion.
Is there a bar you haven't gotten into a fight in?
You just can't take no for an answer, can you?
Good to see you too.
Don't start with me, Mike.
You shouldn't even be here.
That went will.
Hey, detente, okay?
Can we start over?
Why are you here?
Well, you just kinda disappeared after your father's service.
Excuse me for being a little worried about you.
Really?
Worried about me in Hawaii? In my father's beach house?
He's really gone.
I miss him too, Sarah.
It's okay to let go.
But this isn't gonna help anything.
Don't tell me what to do.
Sarah.
Please, Mike.
I don't wanna be alone tonight.
How we doing with the chip?
Relax.
We're almost there.
Mr. Torres, you cannot do this.
Dr. Graiman would never approve.
Graiman's not here anymore, Kitt.
If you remove my chip, there is no
guarantee I can be reactivated.
Pull it.
Please, Mr. Torres.
There it is.
All of Kitt's personality.
His memories.
The most advanced artificial intelligence program
In the world.
With that in Karr...
It might well be the future.
Yes, it might.
Get it out of here.
Come on, Mike. Pick up.
Where the hell are you?
I can't believe this. I can't believe this.
Just calm down and tell us what happened.
They took Kitt, okay?
Who did, Billy?
It was Torres
And a ton of NSA guys.
He totally betrayed us.
And he was talking about the Karr project.
As in knight automated roving robot.
I mean, I didn't even know that project was real.
Are you sure he said, "Karr"?
He shut us down, Mike.
The SSC is over. History.
They took the A.I. chip out of Kitt
And scrapped the program.
I mean, they took my cell phone, for god's sake.
My father was the program.
Of course they shut it down.
Don't listen to her, Billy.
She hasn't had her morning pitcher
of mojitos yet.
Also, I found a package in Graiman's office
Addressed to the both of you.
I managed to get it out before the NSA
had their garage sale.
I sent it overnight.
Yeah, it's here.
We'll take a look and get back to you.
You ready to look at this?
I'm getting dressed.
Hello, Mike.
If you're looking at this,
It means I'm gone and there are some things
you need to know.
First of all, your past.
You were used as an experiment.
You were the original driver for the Karr project.
Now there was a fatal flaw in Karr's A.I.
Which made him uncontrollable and extremely aggressive.
He reprogrammed himself. People died.
After the program was scrapped,
it was decided that your memory be wiped.
They said it was for your own protection
that you must never know.
But still, I should have told you the truth, Mike.
You're like a son to me.
And I hope someday you'll find a way to forgive me.
Kitt was developed in the wake of the Karr failure.
It was a means of perfecting the A.I.
With the ultimate goal of re-launching the Karr project.
I was the only one that stood in the way and that I'm gone,
I'm sure they'll be moving ahead very quickly.
This must never be allowed to happen.
Karr is a devastating weapon and only the beginning
they believe that Kitt's A.I. can override the flaws
in Karr's programming, but they're wrong.
This is a disaster waiting to happen.
Now you must protect Kitt's A.I. and stop Karr.
This is vital, Mike.
I just hope I'm not too late.
They're going to re-launch the Karr program.
That's why they took Kitt. I'm going back.
I'm going to the beach.
Sarah, we have to stop this.
- Good luck with that.  - Sarah!
Mike, it is not my fight anymore.
When you're done feeling sorry for yourself,
You let me know.
I'm coming back, Billy.
Get Zoe and I'll meet you someplace safe.
We got work to do.
This whole thing is totally out of control.
They've been through our apartments, okay?
I'm afraid to even go home.
I've hacked into the old sat streams.
Everything's already been re-coded.
Slow down. What does that mean?
It means we have no idea where they've taken Kitt
or how to find him.
All right, let's think about it.
- What would he do?  - Kitt?
He's a conscious being.
He would know he's getting shutdown, right?
Yeah.
Okay, then what would he do? How would he help us?
I don't know. It happened so fast.
They walked in.
He had maybe a minute before he went dark.
He would tried to get us a message.
Now I checked my email accounts. There was nothing there.
What about you guys?
The government can access our email.
That wouldn't be secure. Kitt would know that.
Okay, then what wouldn't they
be able to access?
How could he get us a message
that they wouldn't know about?
- Come on, think!  - I don't know.
- I don't know.  - I know Kitt.
He wouldn't go down without a fight.
He gets that from me.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
The Jam Haus.
The what house?
It's where Kitt and I would share music files.
It's online.
I was using music to help Kitt
develop his A.I. Personality protocols.
Graiman loved the idea
Because Kitt was learning about human behavior
from the perspective of musical narrative.
There it is.
A file sent from Kitt late yesterday,
Literally seconds before he was shut down.
Read it.
It's a... it's a song.
Absurd, by Fluke.
Musical narrative, huh?
I thought you were talking about Mozart.
You know, the classics?
No.
Kitt likes classical,
But deep down he's into trip-hop and rave.
What can I say?
The car's a groove machine.
Cool song, but where's the message?
Well, maybe play it backwards?
It's not zeppelin.
Binary.
- What?  - Binary.
Zeros and ones. Kitt's first language.
If there's a message in there, it's in the code.
Break it down.
Check it out.
I did a comparison of Kitt's version of the song
and the original, and look.
There are anomalous sections of code, they don't fit.
They're out of sync with the song.
If we calculate a numerical value
- for the anomalous sections  - Exactly.
- Okay, what the hell are you guys talking about?  - Ba-Ba-Ba-Ba-Ba.
- A yield in numerical value of 2-3-2-3-2-3.  - Well, that's not so helpful.
Wait, it's a pattern.
Try it this way. 23-23-23, as three numbers.
Try it as a letter.
The 23rd letter of the alphabet is...
W.
Damn!
Bush stole Kitt!
No.
It's three W's.
W-W-W.
The world wide web.
Kitt's on the net.
- Is that possible?  - It is.
And considering he only had a few seconds,
and the sheer volume of data that he had to dump,
it would've been the only option he would've had.
How would that work?
He would've had to use data packets.
Millions of tiny bits of data
that he could scatter and embed in various websites.
Like cookies... you'd never know they were there,
unless you were looking for them.
And we can retrieve them?
- If we can find them.  - I've got it.
www.michaelknight.org.
Hey, Kitt.
I knew you were out there somewhere.
Damn.
What's the matter?
It's like I thought, the files are ginormous.
I can't do this on my laptop.
I couldn't do this on a hundred laptops.
We're going to need some major computing power.
I know a place.
No way! No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, yeah.
Hello, Sarah.
I love you, my girl.
And I know you're grieving, but there's work to be done.
Now the two greatest creations
in my life are you and Kitt.
And now they're going to use Kitt for destructive ends.
And the thought that my legacy has come to this,
that my life's work will bring about the devastation,
that I'm sure will come if they're not stopped.
It's unbearable for me  to even contemplate.
But you, Sarah...  You're my legacy, too.
I need you to help me.
You must stop this evil.
Stop Karr.
Now Mike has information about this,
Which I'm sure has made him very angry.
You need to help him, Sarah.
Look out for him.
I have every confidence in you.
Some of my greatest memories
are working hard at my desk,
while you would play in the office.
And to think that that little girl
has grown into the one woman that I would trust
to carry on my work.
The answers that I've found at that desk
are there for you now, Sarah.
I know you'll use them wisely.
The answers that I've found at that desk,
Are there for you now, Sarah.
Oh...
Won't we be under surveillance?
The SCC was the surveillance,
Lucky for us, they shut the SCC down.
Fire in the hole.
Give me a hand with this.
- Holy...  - Crap.
Can't pull power off the grid, or they'll know we're here.
Let's get a back up,
Genny going to see what we have to work with.
You got it.
Where are we on funding?
Spoke to our guys in Alexandria.
Their putting in an allocation through channels.
Channels?
The usual channels.
But DOD won't commit without a hard look.
We can do that.
How long?
Kitt's A.I is not plug and play.
We need to conform Kitt's applications with Karr's.
So we test in a week? A month?
Give me 24 hours.
Beginning of eternity?
I set up a wicked encryption program.
No one's going to know we're here.
Computers are rebooted.
We can start whenever Billy's ready.
How you doing on Kitt's new A.I chip?
It's one of the most sophisticated data chips
in the world.
And considering I'm working with radio shack leftovers,
We're doing fine.
But it's going to work, right?
Yeah, I mean... It'll do something.
Something?
We're flying by the seat of our pants here, man.
What does that mean?
We'll find out in a minute.
Ready to be reloaded.
Hopefully.
Not going to give me anymore than that?
Nope. Awesome.
All right...
Let's do it.
Begin download.
Wow.
It's Kitt's life.
Flashing before our eyes.
His memories...
His personality...
Mike, it's Sarah.
When I say, "the beginning of eternity, "
does that mean anything to you?
In what context?
My father.
Doesn't mean anything.
Wait, isn't that a riddle?
Of course, he always to used ask me riddles
when I was a kid.
But how did it go?
Um... "I am the beginning of eternity,
the end of every rhyme,
the beginning of the end,
and the end of every rhyme.
who am I?"
That's it. But what's the answer?
The beginning of eternity, the end of space and time,
- The begin...  - I got it.
It's E. The letter e.
I got to go.
W-wait, where are you?
Hello?
Something's not right.
There's so very much here that's not right.
That might be the understatement of the century.
No!
I did a cross reference. We're missing a packet.
Okay, where is it?
I'm working on it.
You have got to be freaking kidding me!
- What?  - Not good.
Kitt's learned behavior
integrative algorithms packet has been downloaded
onto an XBOX Console Somewhere in Portland.
You're saying some kid in Oregon's got Kitt on his xbox?
That's what I'm saying.
His name is Cody Lundstrom. He's 11 years old.
Well, find him. Get it back.
I think you can handle an 11-year-old kid.
You can handle an 11-yeaold kid, can't you?
Accessing Sarah Graiman number current.
Transferring funds from Knight industries accounts.
Transferring funds from Flag accounts.
Transferring funds from Knight function accounts.
Uh, you're not gonna blow us up, are you?
When the agents raided the place,
they took all our surveillance files.
But Graiman built in a fail-safe.
In case of attack or natural disaster,
all data's backed up to the mainframe.
However, we no longer have the access code,
So we'll have to get at it the old-fashioned way.
Hacker style.
Hi.
I'm from gamer freak magazine.
I'm doing a story on xbox enthusiasts.
Your son's name was Randomly Drawn
From our xbox 360 live site
To be featured in an article.
These are all beta versions,
Won't drop until Christmas.
They're all yours.
Free stuff?
Excellent.
We've been looking at footage
three days back from the raid,
and I haven't seen anything.
You?
Wait a minute. Look.
Let me see if I can get another angle.
Well, that's kinda suspicious.
What's Torres doing holding a meeting in there?
He's being smart.
There's no audio in there.
Can we get audio in an adjacent area?
Maybe another mike picked him up.
If we got anything, maybe we can enhance it.
Program.
Charles Graiman is dead.
This is your call.
Wait, go back.
See what you can do with it.
I think it's time we shut down the Kitt program.
And move forward with Karr.
Graiman didn't think
the technology was ready.
Charles Graiman never supported the Karr program.
This is your call now.
We've waited long enough.
Shut it down.
Let's move on to the next phase.
Torres totally sold us out.
Can't say I'm surprised.
Run a facial recognition on the other guy.
We need to know who he is.
Don't bother.
His name is Jack Hurst,
NSA.
Yeah, well, he's the guy
Torres told to shut us down.
Then he's the guy we need to talk to.
He can tell us what happened to Kitt.
It's good to have you back.
How'd you get in here anyway?
There's a secret emergency entrance.
You guys coulda called me, but I'm sure whatever you did
was just as easy.
So Kitt was developed
after the failure of the Karr project?
Kitt was designed to be a more compliant personality.
They'd perfect the AI in Kitt
and then apply it to Karr.
That's been the plan all along.
My father was trying to stop it all this time.
Something went very wrong with Karr.
He was uncontrollable.
And people were killed.
Oh, my god.
I was Karr's original driver, Sarah.
That's why I can't remember
they took my memory.
Mike.
And I'm not gonna let it happen again.
Zoe, what do you got?
I tapped into Hurst's secretary's iphone
and recovered his schedule.
He's having dinner tonight
at IL Padrone in Georgetown.
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
Jack.
- Sarah.  - Hi.
What brings you to D.C.?
I'm meeting a friend. How are you?
Great. Thank you.
I'm so sorry hear about your father.
It was quite a tragedy.
He was a good man.
Yes, he was.
This nation has lost one of its brightest minds.
He'll be sorely missed.
I counted him as a good friend, you know?
He's always spoke about you with such great affection, Jack.
- It was good seeing you.  - Good to see you too, Sarah.
Yeah.
Again, my condolences. Thank you.
Take care.
Yes!
Totally smoked you!
I've got homework and stuff, you know.
We have to keep going.
We've got to retrieve the orb.
That's the coolest part.
Hey, I thought you were gonna interview me.
Oh, uh, no, this is it.
Your game play style
is the focus of my story,
and I must say, very impressive.
Whatever.
Hey, can't we at least play madden or something?
I'm not really into this stuff.
It's so lame.
What are you, nuts?
The graphics are stellar,
and the narrative complexity.
It's a totally immersive experience.
You need to get a life, dude.
You need to get a life.
There it is.
Yes!
Ahh!
That's it?
Yeah. Pretty cool, huh?
Not really.
Yeah, well, I should get going.
Great hanging with you, pal.
You're a beastly player. Bump it.
Whatever.
What a douche.
She shows up at a restaurant where I'm having dinner, huh?
Just days after this whole thing goes down.
Do you think she knows anything?
That's Torres.
I don't know.
I just don't feel comfortable assuming it's a coincidence.
There's too many loose ends we've left out there.
That doesn't matter.
Even if she does know something,
what could she do?
Still, it'd be safer
if we just tied them up.
How close are we?
Hours away.
Well, Michael Knight.
This is nice and tidy,
home invasion gone bad.
Lower your gun.
Have a seat.
You're in way over your heads.
This is bigger than both of you.
Your opinion on our chances
really doesn't interest me.
We want to know where Kitt is.
You're never going to get Kitt back.
That's a big problem for you.
You can't stop this.
My father's dead.
Everything he's worked for you've stolen.
Now, you will tell us where kitt is
or I'll put a hole in your chest.
Okay.
It doesn't matter anyway.
Where is he?
If you had a top secret weapons program
that no one could know about,
that you had to be able to deny even existed.
Where would you keep it?
DARPA?
Skunk works?
Black box?
Any bells ringing?
Area 51.
No one calls it that anymore.
Nevada.
You know you're dead,
Don't you?
Both of you.
You're dead.
Graiman put together
a pretty comprehensive collection of weaponry.
He used them in live-fire testing of Kitt's defenses.
This goes back to the early days of development.
I don't even think Torres knows this place exists.
I'm going up against US Soldiers.
I need non-lethal options, Billy.
I think we got some toys you're gonna like.
What do you think?
Looks like Christmas morning.
Oh, yeah.
Military-grade taser, rapid recharge.
Flash grenades, temporarily blinds the enemy.
30-mil grenade launcher.
Modified munitions disperse hard rubber pellets.
Ouch.
And my personal favorite,
Single-barrel 12 gauge shotgun,
Non-lethal beanbag rounds.
Packs one hell of a punch.
Nice, Billy.
Really nice.
It might take a while
for Kitt to integrate the data
after the chip has been reinserted.
But it should all be there.
What do you mean "should"?
You're still not sure.
Of course he's not sure. It's not that simple, Rambo.
We think we got it.
But without the original to compare it to,
there's no way we can be certain
we got the sequencing exactly right.
And what happens if you didn't get it exactly right?
Then it's just a bunch
of ones and zeros.
Not Kitt.
It's time.
Are you sure about this?
Going in alone?
They taught me everything I know.
They used me.
It's time I got a little payback.
Sarah, can you hear me?
We've got you, Mike.
I've got the compound in sight.
How you doing with eyes in the sky?
We're kinda slumming it here
without government satellite access.
I'm trying to page back on commercial systems.
It might be a little hit-and-miss,
but we'll do our best.
I know you can do it, Billy,
if anyone can.
I'll contact you when I'm in position.
He's got faith in you, Billy.
That's so sweet.
It was. You just ruined it.
I've got him, he's in.
Dammit. We lost the signal.
What else do we got up there? We gotta find another bird now.
Wow, the take charge attitude. I like it.
- Zoe.  - I'm on it.
Mike, we got him.
We were able to pick up the radiation signature
from Kitt's nano skin.
Point the way, Billy. You have a fix on me?
Yeah.
Kitt's in a warehouse building
about 600 yards due east of your position.
It's showtime.
Little help, Billy.
Keep heading back.
- Up ahead on the left you'll see a large crate.  - Got it
System reboot commencing.
Sir, the Knight Industry vehicle has just been taken.
We must stop them.
Karr, stop!
Kitt must be stopped.
No. Kitt is no longer important. You have everything you need.
Let him go.
My analysis indicates that Kitt is a potential threat.
I will not allow
for the possibility of being shut down again.
I'm giving you a direct order. Stand down.
I take orders from my creator, Dr. Charles Graiman.
Graiman is dead. I'm next in command.
You take orders from me.
Your reasoning is correct.
You are, in fact, next in command.
I do take orders from you.
Karr!
Now, we are one. And I give the orders.
System reboot complete.
Kitt, is that you?
Yes, Michael. I knew you'd come after me.
Save the sentiment for later, buddy.
Michael, I will be unable
to access my weapons or transformation protocols
until the download of my data is complete.
How long will that take?
I am unable to calculate,
as that application has not yet been restored.
Ask a stupid question.
Mike, you've gotta get outta there.
Why? What's going on?
Karr's coming after you.
Look, just try to outrun him and get home.
We'll figure out what to do about Karr later.
No.
They'll move him. Hide him.
This could be our last chance, I'm finishing this now.
How ya doing, buddy?
My advanced functions are still mostly inoperative.
Well, suck it up. I'm putting you in the game.
You're playing hurt.
I am Karr.
I must merge with you, Michael Knight!
Kitt must die!
Then you and I will become one!
- It is our destiny!  - Well, I have a different destiny for you.
You are my original driver!
We must be one!
- It is time to achieve our destiny, Michael Knight!  - Not today.
Michael, my nano skin is not responding.
I do not believe I can withstand much more.
All right. We're not gonna out-muscle this thing.
We gotta think of something.
What about your mechanical functions?
- You still got those?  - Yes, Michael.
Turbo boost?
I believe turbo boost is operational.
Good. I'll bring the rest.
Kitt must die!
Ski mode.
Then you and I will become one.
Grappling hook!
- Fire.  - It is our destiny.  - It isn't gonna be happen.
Let's do this.
Kitt, turbo boost now.
Mike.
Sarah, get an ambulance.
I'm so sorry.
I was doing what I thought I had to do.
I thought we could control it.
I thought we could save soldiers' lives.
Charles was right.
Shut up, man.
Just hang in there. Help's coming.
I didn't mean to put you in danger.
Or Sarah.
Or anyone.
Please...
Tell them I'm sorry.
Hey. Hey, just hold on.
I'm sorry...
It's just antiseptic, tough guy.
Yeah. It stings.
Baby.
Hey.
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
Little bit.
Your nano repair mods are hot again.
All right.
Kitt...
Go for it.
That's what I'm talking about.
How do you feel, buddy?
I feel excellent, Michael.
Well, we're glad to hear it, Kitt.
There is one thing.
I have scanned my memory files, and there seem to be gaps.
I don't know what it is I can no longer remember,
but I can sense something is missing.
Like a piece of me is gone.
You're not gone, Kitt.
You're all right here.
Sarah, I seem to have detected
a message file in my database.
It is from your father.
I would say that congratulations are in order,
as this message is programmed
to play only in success.
So, job well done. All of you.
I imagine you're now asking yourselves, what next?
Well, it is my hope that you will continue.
How do we do that?
I don't believe you know this,
but the SSC is the property of Knight Industries.
The government leased this facility
from us, and now it belongs to you.
Yes!
As far as funding goes,
Sarah, I assume you remember "the beginning of eternity"?
Yeah, what did that mean, anyway?
It means we're good.
You can now be
the Knight Industries
that Wilton Knight always envisioned.
You can reinstitute flag...
Foundation for law and government.
Completely autonomous.
No more hidden agendas, no more interference.
Just what you think is right.
You can make a difference, but you must decide.
So what do you say?
Are you kidding? Of course.
You know it.
One question.
Do I get to keep the car?
Sarah, your father is my father.
I will do anything to help honor his memory.
I won't let you down, dad.
I know you'll make me proud. All of you.
Well, god bless.
Carry on.