Previously on "Grey's Anatomy"...
I was dead. Now I'm not.
Anybody come looking for me yet?
No hits from missing persons, plus--
My face is hard to identify.
Anyone know who
the new chief candidate is?
- Colin Marlowe.
- The one and only.
- He...
- Yes.
- With...
Your best friend violently disses
our marriage every chance she gets...
She has feelings for you!
Is she crazy?
Surgeons always have a plan...
Where to cut, where to clamp,
where to stitch.
But even with the best plans...
Complications can arise,
things can go wrong...
And suddenly you're caught
with your pants down.
Wow. You and George
were really going at it last night.
- What?
- Oh, the laughing,
the drinking, the music--
Okay, you know what?
Nobody, meaning me,
needs to hear
George's rendition of "Sexy Back"
at 3:00 in the morning.
Yeah.
You shoulda-- You shoulda just,
you know, said something or-- or...
Banged on the wall.
It's like living in a youth hostel.
Well, the important thing is,
is that she and George made up.
You did, right?
I need to use your bathroom.
- Why?
- Because O'Malley is puking in mine.
- Okay, youth hostel.
- George is still here?
Yes.
Yes, but only because he was
too drunk to drive home.
You know, just totally impaired,
like no-heavy-machinery drunk.
What's her problem?
Still drunk.
What's she doing here?
She's afraid she's ruining
her engagement to Burke,
so she's hiding from him.
Not anymore. I have a plan.
Burke doesn't want me
to marry him just to appease him--
- Which you are--
- So...
we don't get married.
Simple.
We go back to the way it was.
"Be kind. Rewind."
My plan has a name.
I gotta go.
Gotta get to work.
I'll see you guys there.
Is that George?
You said he was upstairs puking.
So now he's downstairs puking.
What the hell happened last night?
Callie is gonna kill me.
Did I at least call her before
I passed out?
You don't...
You don't remember?
I remember the bourbon...
And, uh...
I don't...
Where did you sleep?
- Big day.
- Yeah.
What time's your interview
with the board?
3:00.
Well, if you have any questions,
please--
Yes, thank you.
I think I have everything well in hand.
That's a big folder.
It's, uh, it's nothing.
It's, uh, just a few ideas
I have for Seattle Grace.
A 10-year plan,
which, uh, really is just a few...
tweaks.
What did, uh, Einstein say?
"Newton did the work,
"I'm merely standing on his shoulders."
And in this scenario, I'm Newton.
- Hey.
- You look nice.
- I look insane.
I'm-- I'm wearing pearls.
- Listen--
- Listen, about, uh, last night--
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I had--
we're gonna have to put a pin in that
for now, because as of this moment,
You and I are the perfect couple. Okay?
We are the perfect,
happily married couple who are perfect
and-- And never fight,
because, uh,
because my dad's in town.
- What?
- Yeah.
My dad is in town, and, uh,
he wants to meet my husband.
Oh, hey.
The O'Malleys.
Carry on. Do your stuff, your...
married stuff.
Yay!
You told her about our fight?
Just when exactly is he coming?
Today. Lunch. Cafeteria.
You know what,
I think I'm gonna change it to Joe's
so he might not be able to tell
that stink's coming from you.
No, it's-- It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Uh, I'm good with parents.
Parents love me.
Funny, funny, funny little man.
Funny little smelly little man.
Get in the shower, OK?
- It's gonna be OK.
- Get in the shower.
I know. You'll see.
He's gonna love me.
Oh! No.
What's this?
We bring each other coffee.
This is what we do.
No, it's what we used to do,
before you moved in.
We started making coffee at home.
You know, I'm not really interested
in going back to the way it used to be.
So unless you have something else
to say to me...
I've already had my coffee.
Good morning, Doctors.
Good morning.
Big day today, huh?
Good luck to all and sundry, hey?
He has a 10-year plan.
- What?
- He's presenting the board
with a 10-year plan
for the surgical wing.
He's only been here a day.
Did you see that folder?
It's full of plans,
"tweaks" for my hospital...
This is our computer-generated
approximation
of your original facial structure
based on the 3-D C.T. scans we did.
It's what you could look like after
reconstructive surgery.
Or you could look like this.
Or this.
You don't like them?
No, it's not that. It's...
How does this work exactly?
He'll make an incision
along your hairline, and then...
It's okay. I can take it.
He'll literally pull your face off.
It sounds a lot worse than it is.
Your face is extremely elastic,
and pulling it down allows me
to repair the bone fractures
underneath without
causing any scaring.
And once you've healed, no one
will ever know you had the surgery.
I'm that good.
He is. It's annoying.
The surgery won't affect my baby?
I'll be monitoring the baby throughout.
So...
Then I-I just have to pick one?
Do I have to pick one now?
Um, take a couple hours
and think about it.
Couple hours... yeah.
- Dr. Bailey.
- Chief,
our Jane Doe is getting
a new face today.
Well, that's exciting.
How are you doing, Meredith?
You didn't take
too much time off after--
I'm fine. Really, sir. I, uh,
I think working is
the best thing I can do.
Like mother, like daughter?
Dr. Grey, what can you tell me
about reconstructing
the orbital floor?
Uh, you can create
a new base for the eye socket
by harvesting bone from the skull.
Dr. Bailey,
Dr. Grey will be scrubbing in
on the Jane Doe surgery. Come on.
I'll show you how to do it
without breaking the bone graft
into a million pieces.
Congratulations, Dr. Grey.
Okay, let's go, people.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I need to talk to you.
Why?
To prepare you guys
for what you're about to see.
You meant--
You meant "you" like "us",
not like "me".
You don't want to talk to me,
you want to talk to us
about a p-- About a patient.
That's what I just said.
Uh, this patient has a disease so rare
that you'll probably
never see it again--
- F.O.P.
- Oh, uh, fibrodysplasia
ossificans progressiva?
Yeah. It's a congenital disease
which turns muscle into bone.
You become a human statue.
So just, uh, try to learn.
Try not to stare, okay?
If you people are interns,
you need to stand back.
Nina, please don't be rude.
My mother still has movement in her...
face and hands. I would like to keep it
that way, so please be careful...
If you press too hard during an exam
or bump into her accidentally,
it causes a bone to grow
where a bone shouldn't grow.
So there can be no accidents.
Remember that
when you're dealing with her today...
It's just a stomach virus or a flu.
I'm sure it's nothing.
Nina insisted
- that I come in.
- She was vomiting blood
and going through her pain meds
like they were candy.
And she has new growths on her back,
no doubt caused
by some clumsy interns
on her last hospital stay.
Well, obviously you're having
a flare-up of the F.O.P.,
but what really concerns me
is the vomiting.
So I'm gonna need a C.T.,
see what's going on.
Wow. Did you build that?
- My mom did.
- No, Nina did it.
I used to do, I-I'm not able to.
It keeps her active.
When she's active,
she has fewer flare-ups.
Plus it makes her happy...
And relaxed.
Good. Okay.
Can I work in the clinic today?
You don't want the F.O.P. case?
Clinic, why?
What's going on in the clinic?
Nothing. I just feel clinic-y.
That's not a word. I'll take the clinic.
You both can go to the clinic.
The board is interviewing
the chief candidates all day today,
so we're light on surgeries.
Yes?
You're with Dr. O'Malley.
What am I supposed to do?
Find Dr. Montgomery.
See if you can help with Jane Doe.
I showered twice.
It's coming out of your pores, George.
You reek, you're trembling,
there's no way I'm letting
you near my patient right now.
- Dr. Bailey.
- Don't tell Bailey.
Bailey,
with Mrs. Rogerson's limited mobility,
I'm gonna, uh, need
an extra set of hands.
Fine.
Yang will handle the clinic.
You'll be with the O'Malleys today.
It's my foot.
It hurts like crazy.
I'm gonna need a painkiller.
Can't spend the whole day
propped on an ice pack.
Uh, you're gonna need
to take off your shoe.
No, no, no, no.
I've been down this route before.
Just slip me a couple painkillers,
and I'll be on my way.
Sir, uh, did you go to medicalchool?
I did. Take off your shoe.
You have type 2 diabetes.
Ten years now.
You inspect your feet every day.
Have you noticed anything?
I notice it hurts.
Look, I got 30 guys
sitting on their ass
waiting for me to show up.
Sir, I get it. You're in a hurry.
That makes the two of us.
Sock.
You need to call your guys
and tell them you're not coming in.
Did you choose a face?
Not yet.
I was hoping I'd see one of 'em,
and, I don't know,
recognize myself or something, but...
I don't recognize any of these women.
What if I choose the wrong one?
What if my husband or boyfriend
or whoever's...
baby this is shows up tomorrow with a--
With a picture of what
I'm supposed to look like,
but it's too late, and I'm stuck with
the wrong face for the rest of my life?
Okay, that would suck,
but if you don't pick one...
This is gonna be your face
the rest of your life.
Shouldn't you be preparing
for your board interview?
I am.
You're hovering.
No, I'm breathing you in.
Fine. I'm hovering.
If Cristina would sleep in her own bed,
I wouldn't have to hover at work.
I could hover in bed.
A different type of hovering perhaps.
How bad is it today,
on a scale of one to ten?
- Seven. Maybe a six.
- Good.
You know what's gonna make it
even better than that?
- What?
- The calvarial
bone harvest I get to do
on Sloan's Jane Doe later.
Sloan's gonna let you do a harvest..
- By yourself?
- By myself.
Which makes me very cool in the eyes
of my dead mother, by the way.
Okay, then.
Well, I better let you study.
Better stop distracting me.
I will not be cool
in the eyes of my dead mother
if I maim Jane Doe.
We're gonna need you to lie very still,
Mrs. Rogerson.
I think I can do that, Dr. O'Malley.
Sorry about that, Mrs. Rogerson.
I'm never gonna drink again.
I can't believe I have to be
presentable for Callie's dad at lunch.
Oh, god.
Hours--
Hours of our lives--
Many hours that are
all I can think about,
and you seriously don't remember?
How can you not remember those many,
many hours?
Let-- Izzie, if...
Whatever I did, whatever I said,
I was drunk. I'm sure I didn't mean it.
George, I promise you, you meant it.
You meant it a lot.
You meant it more than once.
Do you see that?
Gotta page Callie.
You'll be pleased to hear
I'm proposing an expansion
to the hospital board this afternoon.
Give you quite
a few more places to hide.
I'm not going to hide.
I'm just trying to find my resident.
I come here to Seattle to see you,
and you don't even give me a moment?
You didn't come to see me.
You came to get a job.
- I came here for both.
- Well, you made a mistake.
Are you going to invite me?
- Where?
- To the wedding.
Will you stop talking about the wedding?
Most blushing brides to be love
to talk about the wedding.
What the matter?
Are we getting cold feet?
Please leave.
If he's rushing you,
you should tell him.
When you marry, you want to be ready.
He should understand that.
Good afternoon, board.
Good afternoon,
ladies and gentlemen...
of the board.
I am so grateful for this opportunity.
Don't wear the glasses.
You fiddle with 'em.
It makes you look indecisive.
And stop stressing.
It'll be like any other job interview.
"What do you consider your strengths?
What do you consider your weaknesses?"
What do you consider your weaknesses?
I don't have any.
I'm that good.
What are yours?
I'm an easy Mark for evil redheads.
Trust me, you have other weaknesses.
Obviously...
you are a man-whore.
Correction. I was a man-whore.
Yeah, while you're bragging
about that to the board,
Colin Marlowe is pitching
his 10-year plan.
10-year plan?
Was that a requirement?
It is now.
Mrs. Rogerson, according to your C.T.,
you have severe internal bleeding.
It was probably caused by
your anti-inflammatory medication.
Does that require surgery?
Because she can't have any--
Obviously any surgical procedure
could cause more bone growth
or do more damage than good.
That's why Dr. Burke's here.
What we can do is insert
a line into your groin
and then float a catheter up
and embolize the area.
That's minimally invasive?
As minimally invasive as possible.
But with your condition,
even this is risky.
I'm 41 years old.
Most F.O.P. patients don't live to 45.
I'm down to the use
of my face and hands.
Pretty soon I won't have anything.
So what would happen...
If I refuse the surgery?
You will bleed to death...
Within a day or two.
Is that painful?
- Mom, stop, okay?
- Nina, please.
- Let me think.
- The reason you've gotten this far--
Our treatment plan works.
It will work.
Burke is using powerpoint.
He's doing a powerpoint presentation
for the board, which is...
cool if it's, like, 1998.
There's no swag, is there?
We're not allowed to give gifts?
Why did you ask Meredith
to do a bone graft on your Jane Doe?
Because I'm her teacher,
and that's my job.
You're doing it to impress the chief.
You're setting her up,
and she can't fail right now.
Why don't you let your girlfriend decide
what she can or can't do?
I will hurt you
if this goes wrong for her.
Is that a... dollhouse?
Yeah. The lights work and everything.
It's the perfect little home.
Did you have a dollhouse growing up?
I had sex last night...
with the wrong person.
But the thing is,
it didn't feel wrong at the time.
It felt like...
Something's falling into place.
So what do I do?
What am I,
the go-to person for adultery?
I just...
I just don't know what to do.
You stop.
That's what you do.
Are you sure?
I mean, how do you know
that it didn't feel so right because...
it's god's plan?
God wants you to be an adulter?
God got a virgin pregnant by magic.
God is not playing by the rules.
Uh, talk to paul.
Mr. Kendry.
No, Paul will get you drywall numbers.
- Mr. Kendry.
- Okay.
Let me just write
a couple notes about that call.
Mr. Kendry, we're gonna have
to amputate your foot.
- What?
- The infection is in the bone.
If we don't remove the foot,
it will travel to your blood,
and that will cause sepsis
and possible death. I'm sorry.
How can you be so...
I mean, I-I can't get around a...
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no. You're not cutting off my foot.
Sir, diabetes is a manageable disease.
If you had been here even a month ago,
- maybe we--
- Okay, so I screwed up.
But you're telling me
that this is my only option
because I'm late getting in here?
- That there is no way--
- Mr. Kendry--
Please.
There's gotta be a way for me
to get that month back.
Tell me what to do.
I'll do it. I'll do every line
of every plan you give me.
I'll do it.
Please.
You gotta find a way to save my foot.
What do you think of a robotics lab
as a goal for the hospital?
- Derek...
- You're harvesting.
I'm trying to be supportive
but this graft, it's really tricky.
You don't have to do it, you know.
I talked to Mark, and, uh--
You what?
I talked to Mark.
I mean, Meredith, this is a--
- It's a complex procedure.
- You don't think I can do it?
When has Mark Sloan,
allowed his interns to do anything,
let alone harvest a bone graft?
He's in the race for chief.
- He's trying to prove he can teach.
- By teaching you..
Your mother died, the chief
is gonna be watching you very closely.
And Mark is trying to gain points by--
Using me.
If it goes well, he gets the credit.
If it goes poorly,
he gets the save.
So this is about you onupping Mark.
He's using you.
I'm just trying to protect you.
You don't need to.
Close the door on your way out...
- Can I help you with those, Dr. Bailey?
- What do you want?
See, that's what I like about you.
You always get right to the point.
Make it quick.
I'm headed over to the clinic.
All right.
What would you change
about this hospital if you could?
Is this for your board interview?
You want me to do
your homework for you
because I'm not busy enough,
is that it?
All the other attendings are putting
together 10-year plans. I was...
just looking for some input.
Input? You want--
I have patients
in need of medical attention right now.
This guy here is about
to have one less appendage.
I don't have a 10-year plan for him.
I have a "right now" plan for him--
Cut off his foot to save his life.
So you need to get out of my way
right now so I can do my job.
- Right now?
- Right now.
Talk to me about blackouts.
Are they real?
Do you really not remember
anything afterwards?
Iz, I'm fine. Not drinking.
I'm not drowning my sorrows.
Fine.
Everybody needs to stop trying
to protect me.
Um, this isn't... really about you.
I'm asking, back when you had
a best friend named tequila, did you...
actually ever blackout?
Once. No, twice.
But the stuff
you don't remember is usually
the stuff you don't wanna remember.
Right.
Great. Thanks.
Hey, I have type 2 diabetes.
Patient let it go,
and the infection is in the bone.
I have to find a fix
or cut off the foot.
Anyone? Anybody?
You get to cut off his foot? Cool.
You think-- No, not cool.
The patient was neglectful.
He made a couple of bad calls.
Does that mean he has no hope?
Does that mean he can't have a do over?
But you get to cut
through bone and stuff.
We're talking about Burke now.
We are?
Operation "Be kind. Rewind."
not going so well?
You need to fix it.
Cause it seems like you guys
have a pretty good thing,
and pretty good things are rare,
and hard to come by,
unlike really screwed up,
complicated things, which...
seem to be freakin' everywhere.
You know what? Things are great.
I'm gonna get things back
to the way we were.
Watch me.
Has Jane Doe picked a face?
No, not yet.
How cool would that be,
to get to pick your own face, just...
disappear and start all over?
How you doing?
How am I doing?
I'm freaking out, Alex...
That's how I'm doing.
I can't do this.
I can't pick.
I can't.
All right.
Well, let's, uh...
Let's meet the contenders, all right?
Let's see. This...
This is... Maggie.
Married her high school sweetheart,
has two kids--
Boy and girl...
Loves being a mom,
coaches her daughter's
basketball team and...
makes an insane bana cream pie.
Bana cream pie?
It's my favorite, so shut up.
And this is... um... Elizabeth.
Graduated from Northwestern.
Met her husband
at a political rally where they...
got arrested and fell in love.
She's all angry and fired up,
but everyone forgives her
because she means well.
This one...
This one's Ava.
She's funny, she's tough.
You know, little neurotic sometimes,
but you get used to it.
You can tell she's-- She's been
through a lot in her life, but...
It's only made her stronger, you know?
It's just, your daughter, the way she...
You know, she's sort of undeniable.
And, uh, after I lost my father, I...
realized, you know, that life is short.
And it's-- It's long, too....
Short and long...
Life....
He talks a lot.
No, no. He-- He-- He talks.
Like a-- Like a--
Like a person who talks, dad.
- Please.
- Do you have any idea
what you've done to your mother?
You make this decision,
the most important day of your life...
We didn't even know she was seeing
someone... Are you pregnant?
- Did you get my daughter pregnant?
- No. Daddy.
No, it is not--
No. This is George, okay?
He's not like the other guys
I've been with.
Clean as a whistle,
and a mathlete.
He has no money.
- You have money.
- Oh, come on...
I didn't know that Callie was well-off.
- She just told me.
- Really?
Really? Well, then,
you won't mind if the house,
the car and everything else
we'll provide
will be in Calliope's name.
- Uh, what house?
- You're a married woman now.
I'll find something suitable. It's all
here in the postnuptial i've drawn up.
- Dad!
- Sorry.
I've got it. It's all right. It's okay.
You know what? You--
You are not drawing up any...
- ...you can raise a family.
- No!
- What?
- No, that's not gonna happen.
There's no way I'm gonna
let you pay for anything. I can't--
We can't, uh... Callie, I'm so sorry.
Mr. Torres, I'm sorry,
but the answer is no.
You remembered.
That's really coming along.
It looks great.
Thanks.
We've been working on it for months.
But when I say "we", I mean "she".
I just hold things and look pretty.
That can be hard work, too.
I'm gonna need to draw
some blood for, uh, your surgery.
Be careful.
You can only use one specific vein.
In this area here.
- I said be careful.
- I'm so sorry.
That's okay.
I's not. If she gonna be that clumsy,
she's not drawing your blood.
Nina, she's just doing her job.
Not very well. I'm going to get a nurse,
a senior nurse.
- Oh, Nina, stop.
- No, mom.
Do not let her touch you.
We can't be too careful.
You're not taking her blood.
She's not even a person anymore.
You know what I mean?
- Mrs. Rogerson--
- I know I'm gonna die.
You know, maybe not today, but soon..
I just need to talk, you know?
Nina won't let me talk.
I just need to talk.
No coffee.
One more thing for marlowe to tweak...
Please tell me you're not coming up
with a 10-year plan for this hospital.
You can me up with all the plans
you want, but in the end, it just...
Doesn't make one bit of difference.
- Things happen. People just--
- Drown?
You know, when I pulled her
out of the water, it was...
She was like ice.
She can swim.
Richard, she's...
She gave up.
I close my eyes for a moment,
it's like she's back in the water.
I'm up, and I just listen
to her breathe, you know? Just...
In case she stops.
So I can come up with plans
for the hospital, but...
But if they ask me where
I'm gonna be in ten years...
George.
Mr. Torres.
You want to take care of her
in your own way.
I understand that.
I respect it.
But you have to understand,
she's my only little girl, George.
And you need to promise me
that you will love her and protect her,
because the minute that you hurt her...
You understand?
Good. Then I'll tell Callie's mother
she can plan the party.
What pa-- What?
- Your wedding party.
- Oh, dad.
Oh, no, please, mija.
For my sanity, mija,
just let her plan a party.
All right, all right. Okay.
All right.
I have a plane to catch.
Come here.
George.
Bye, dad.
You stood up to him.
Nobody does that.
I was all proud.
So listen...
About last night,
I don't know about you,
but personally,
I'd like to take back about 90% of it.
Me, too.
Good.
Good. Okay. Then go--
Go find Izzie
and help her prep Mrs. Rogerson.
I'll see you in surgery.
You here to keep my baby alive?
I am.
Good.
So?
So...
Call me Ava.
You been practicing? You know
the chief will be watching today.
The chief. Right. Of course.
"Of course" what?
Derek was right about you.
You're using the memory
of my dead mother
to win points with the chief.
It's despicable,
and I'm not gonna play.
The chief--
The way he was looking
at you this morning--
Was like you were
some beaten down puppy
he picked up off
the side of the road.
You do this procedure
and you do it well,
he'll start looking at you
like a surgeon again.
But, you know...
You wanna think of me as despicable,
you wanna pass up this shot,
that's up to you.
They're doing a-amazing things
with prosthetics these days.
This doesn't mean your life is over.
Uh, take him up to the O.R.
I'll meet you there.
You've got your board thing now?
The chief picked you...
Originally. You were always
supposed to be the next chief.
That was the plan.
That was a long time ago.
A lot has happened since then.
But you're still that guy.
You're the guy the chief chose.
No, I'm not.
I'm not that guy, Cristina,
and I wouldn't want to be.
I want to be better than that.
I'd like to believe that I've grown.
I want to move forward.
I'm not interested in going back.
Dr. Burke.
You ready?
Osteotome and hammer.
All right, use the curved osteotome
to elevate the external table.
Gently.
- How's it looking?
- Still see bleeding.
The platinum microcoils--
They aren't holding.
What about using a gelatin sponge?
I've already tried polyvinyl alcohol,
glue, microcoils-- Nothing's working.
B.P.'s dropping to 62 systolic.
We'll have to open her up.
If you open her up, she's dead.
If we don't, she's dead.
Beginning amputation.
Fine amputation, Yang.
Beautiful.
Wait.
- Now they're laughing.
- Laughing?
They're laughing.
They can't be laughing with him.
They have to be laughing at him.
I'm surprised
you don't have a shot glass
pressed up against that window.
- We weren't listening.
- Just listening.
Let me show you the new clinic.
Chief.
So?
If you ask me, you all could stand
to borrow a page from Dr. Sloan's book.
Sloan? You're kidding right?
That's a joke?
He didn't get caught up in
this whole 10-year plan foolishness.
He said he had a "right now" plan
for Seattle Grace.
A right now plan?
Is that right?
The board ate it up.
To tell you the truth, so did I.
I should've brought her in sooner...
The first time she threw up.
I knew better.
- There was nothing any of us could--
- No.
It was a mistake.
Your mother...
talked to me.
She wasn't ready to leave you,
but she was ready to leave her body.
Please.
I don't need you to explain the relative
comforts of death for my mother.
What she was afraid of...
was that you had taken
on so much of her disease
that you were freezing up, too.
You've spent so much time
planning and...
Helping her avoid risk--
God knows,
that's what you should've been doing--
But...
She was worried.
You have a healthy body, Nina.
If you fall down,
you won't turn to stone.
And your mom so wanted you
to just let yourself fall.
Messing up...
It's what makes a person.
It's how we learn...
Where we find joy--
In the things you don't plan for,
the things you never see coming.
It happened.
It was a mistake, and it happened.
People make mistakes.
We need to figure out
where we go from here.
how to tell Callie.
I'm not gonna tell Callie.
Do you know how much
this would hurt her?
I'm not gonna clear
my conscience at her expense.
She has done nothing but...
support me, encourage me
and believe in me,
and this is how I pay her back?
I have to live with what I did.
This is our secret, okay?
The thing about plans is,
they don't take into account
the unexpected.
So when we're thrown a curveball,
whether it's in the O.R. or in life....
How are you feeling?
We have to improvise.
I'm a guy without a foot.
What do I do now?
You move forward, you...
You follow the plan and...
you try and keep your other foot.
My other foot.
Right.
Of course,
some of us are better at it than others.
I'm impressed, Karev.
You spent the whole day
watching a fetal monitor
and never complained.
Well, I, uh, I do what I'm told.
Since when?
Depends on who's doing the telling.
Good night, Dr. Karev.
What was that?
How's... Ava?
I don't think I'm gonna know
the answer to that for a little while.
What do you say we talk about you
and the redhead instead?
Well, the redhead's my boss, so...
- So?
- So, it's complicated.
- And?
- And...
Some of us just have
to move on to plan B...
And make the best of it.
It has to be small--
Just you and me...
And Meredith..
And-- And Shepherd, too, if you want.
But that's it.
And a justice of the peace.
I know you're...
spiritual and stuff, but...
I-I don't want any rabbis or ministers,
nothing religious.
We'll just...
Make an appointment at city hall, and...
that'll be that.
And no veil.
Okay? I don't want
to get married with...
mosquito net all over my face.
I let Mark use
the memory of my mother
to win points with the chief.
You were right.
I'm sorry.
- You know what's weird?
- What's weird?
It's exactly
what she would have wanted.
Dead mommy's proud?
Dead mommy's proud.
How was your interview?
Not great.
It wasn't great.
I was distracted.
By what?
Nothing.
I don't know.
On a scale of one to ten,
how bad is it?
Eight.
How about, now?
Seven.
And sometimes...
How about, now?
Six.
- What we want...
- Five.
- is exactly what we need.
- Four, three.
But sometimes...
I can smell your clothes
through the closet door.
Did you tie them up
in a plastic laundry bag?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm-- I'm so sorry.
Well, I guess I can...
live with it.
Sometimes what we need...
is a new plan.
Transcript : swsub.com - Synchro : Benj!
~ www.seriessub.com ~