previously on  "grey's anatomy"
when I told you I was done trying to compete?
That was me breaking up with you
I broke up with finn
Yeah
The patient died last month from complications
following a heart transplant
Denny
Are there any questions for me?
I got shot
I'm not fine  You're not fine
You quit being a surgeon
You'll stand on my right side,
I'll look at you,
and you'll know to slide in
to do the sutures we've practiced
Nobody has to know
to make it
really make it
as a surgeon
it takes major commitment
We have to be willing
to pick up that scalpel
and make a cut  that may or may not
do more damage than good
It's all about  being committed
because if we're not
we have no business
picking up that scalpel  in the first place
Put burke in O R 2 tomorrow at 10:00 A M
The usual scrub team
And get rid of his valve replacement at 20
That's no--
that's no good
Yang,brought you a latte
You're not scrubbing in
But burke always let's me scrub in
Hey,yang,
can i get in on burke's--
no,no,okay?
No residents
Burke says you crowd him,
so just go away
Make sure you put the instrument t
ray on his left-hand side
He needs the extra elbow room
And remember,O R Two No gallery
Burke was specific
Dr Burke's become very specific
since coming back to work,hasn't he?
Do you want me to tell him you said that?
Burke's back,
and suddenly cristina's running his board?
Who does she think she is--
bailey?
She's helping him
Bull
She's taking advantage
She gets out of rounds,
she scrubs in on every surgery burke does,
she's ordering around third-year residents
You guys are overreacting
I'm so sorry
It's completely illegible
She is writing on the O R Board
Maybe I should sleep with burke
you've been busy
Yeah
Derek hasn't called yet
I told him I broke up with finn a week ago
He still hasn't called
Hey,do you want to go grab a drink,
catch up?
no,I can'T I have to study up
for burke's surgeries tomorrow
She's busy
Callie
Hey,
talk to me
Hey,how about talking
to me instead of ignoring me?
- Callie
- George!
Well,that's talking
That's a good start
Oh! Oh,god
Hey,
stranger
Oh,
nancy
You don't call first?
hi
I know I
meredith
Oh,
wait
Let me explain Meredith
I take it that was the slutty
intern you cheated on addison with?
She's not slutty
What are you doing here?
You bailed on thanksgiving and christmas,
and you live in a trailer,
and you're getting a divorce
And then there's the slutty intern
I really don't like you
You love me
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-cflily
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
GARYS ANATOMY
Season 03 Episode 06
Feeling good
Really good
- Good
Yeah,first day back
It's big
kinda nervous But feeling good
Do I look okay?
- Great
I want to get off on the right foot
Gotta get my I D Renewed,new time card,
sign some papers with legal,
and then I'm back  I'm really back
- Yeah
This is me-- human resources
See you guys on the floor
Yeah
Okay,I'll be cristina for you
if you'll be izzie for me
Deal
derek had a woman in his trailer last night
She was ugly,very ugly
Except she was tall and beautiful
And he was naked
mcdreamy was doing the mcnasty with a mchottie?
That mcbastard
- How-- how was that?
- That was good
- Cristina enough? Really?
- Yeah
- Yeah?
- Yeah,'cause--
- channeling izzie
- Go
- Okay,
uh,
callie
she won't forgive me
she won't talk to me
She dumped me
Which is,I don't care about,
you know,at all
Good,
because you deserve better
You do
You are george
I mean,seriously Seriously Seriously
- Was that izzie-optimistic?
- That's very izzie
what the hell has happened to us?
We are now the people that the people
we want to be with avoid
We have careers to think about
We don't need attention from men with perfect hair
You know,
we should make a pact
There's no more dating
No more derek
No more callie
Just 100% focus on our work
- They're dead to us
- They are freakin' corpses to us
Preston burke What a pleasure
I have read so much about you
Well,
thank you
Pruitt byrd
Medivac brought him inhis morning
He presents with a primary cardiac tumor
We've been told pruitt needs
a "cardiac autotransplantation
" A cardiac autotransplantation?
A humpty dumpty surgery
Yes,
I know what it is
Mrs Byrd,
this is a very complicated surgery
You'll need thorough testing
already done
Mr Byrd is a perfect candidate
You understand what this surgery entails?
We have to--
we have to remove his heart,
cut it open,
scrape out all the tumor
and then put his heart back together again
Which is risky
But possible
which is why we're here
I want the very best for my pruitt
The best
- She means you
- I know that,
however-- I've scheduled
mr Byrd for surgery this afternoon
Just trying to be as efficient as possible
Legal cleared stevens
Explain her parameters
and make sure she understands
What,
stevens is being assigned to me again?
- She's your intern
- But I-I didn't think that--
wouldn'tt be better for her
to start fresh with another resident?
U don't want her,
I
want her to succeed
There's still a good deal
of fallout after the duquette m&M
There's been talk
Look,I don't need to tell you
that there are doctors  That there are doctors
who have concerns about your judgment
Concerns about my judgment?
Stevens was your mistake
Do you,
sir?
Do you have concerns about my judgment?
do you?
You're not gonna put those concerns
to rest by avoiding
taking responsibility for dr Stevens
She's your intern
again
Transfer from mercy west
Noelle labatt,
32 weeks along,
pregnant with twins
One appears to be developing
more slowly than the other
Hello Hi,there
Greg stanton
This is my fiancée,
the future mrs Stanton-- noelle
Greg,I promise you,you're the only person
who cares if we're married or not
They said at mercy that we had  to come
here because her condition could be serious
I-is it serious?
I've got to say,
at first glance,
you don't seem emergent enough
for mercy to send you over here in an ambulance
You're not in labor,you're not bleeding,
your vitals are fine
They said I need a specialist because of my thing
- Your thing?
- Two uteruses?
Ms  Labatt,
noelle was born with two uteruses
- uteri?
- Uteruses
Uteruses
That's very rare
I'm here
Hi Hello
That paperwork took--
well,forever
But I'm all do with it now,
and can I just say how
really grateful I am to be back?
You understand there are rules to your probation,
a protocol to follow?
yeah,
I know
Legal already took me through lots of that stuff--
the mandatory counseling,
the extra lab hours,
the volunteer work with transplant patients
That's the stuff you're doing for the chief
I'm talking about what you're doing for me
Okay,
what am I doing for you?
let's start with what you don't get to do
You will not interact with any patients
You will not be alone with any patients
You will be seen and not heard
You will perform no procedures
The O R
Is off limits
No pre-op,no post-op,
no anything have to do with an "op
" You have no authority,
you have no opinions
and you have no choice in this matter
Am I understood?
Is there anything I can do?
I want to be useful
Well
I can't use you
You've got to earn back the right
for any of us to trust you again
Until then,
you will be shadowing a different doctor each day
Okay,well,who am I with today,
dr Montgomery,you?
Dr Bailey,
you paged
Dr Grey
Meredith?
You're to make sure that stevens observes only
You want me to
wait,
meredith
meredith is the boss of me?
Y about this
It's not your fault
Hey,you want me to fetch you some coffee,
rub your feet maybe?
I did not ask for this assignment
I'm fine with it
Really,it's fine
- I'm so sorry
- Dr Stevens--
- hey,dr Shepherd
-  Welcome back
Okay
Uh,
meredith,
meredith--
sorry,it's not like I can leave
I gotta stay by my boss' side
Okay,the trailer sucks,
but in the light of day,
the land's nice
Seattle's pretty in the daylight,
plus you have your thing for ferries,
- so
- ferry boats
Right
Whatever
Dr Stevens,
meredith,this is my sister nancy
hi
Sister?
Yeah
you're one of derek's sisters
Yeah,I knew you didn't think I was
the wife seeing as you already ran her F
Nancy is visiting from connecticut
She's on her way home now,
straight back home
Well,
it was nice to meet you
Okay
Mcdreamy's sister's mcbitchy
you put me in charge of your schedule
To make sure that i didn't
get a surgery like this one
Only a handful of people do humpties,
burke,
and you're the best one on the west coast
Well,
he can go to houston
You want to tell that to the chief?
Pruitt needs this surgery
He'll die without it
You didn't tell me
You told the patient we were doing the surgery,
but you didn't tell me
I have been doing that all week
Are you up on the humpty?
Do you realize what this entails?
I have done my research
Stop worrying
We are a well-oiled machine
- dr Burke
- Yeah
I understand there are some doctors
in this hospital
who have concerns about my judgment since denny
Well,
everybody loves a scandal
So you think it's just gossip,
not actual concern about me as a doctor?
Sure
Iz,
set me up for debridement and dressing
It was stupid
I know better
When I'm studying for the bar,
I'm a mess
I can't focus on anything for weeks
but torts and real property and constitutional law
- the biosynthetic ones
- We never use those
We do now
Sloan changed the burn protocol last week
I was about to start a practice test,
and I wanted some tea,
so I put on a pot of water
and hit the timer and just forgot
Half an hour into my section on contracts,
the smoke alarm was blaring,
and well,you know the rest
So you're gonna be a lawyer?
All I have to do is pass the bar exam
I failed before,
but this time I'm ready
- I'm gonna pass
- Good for you
That was just mean
Kathleen called and told me to find out
why the slutty intern's panties were hanging
on the hospital bulletin board
Four sisters--
four sisters and not one brother,
and you wonder why I don't call more
Feel free to explain about the panties at any time
Nance,you know what?
It's great to see you
Really great to have you here
But I have a job,
you know?
I have patients
I have a mother at 35 weeks with twins
Where is her O B ?
Well,her O B Should be on a plane back
to connecticut where she belongs
Okay,so we've covered the trailer
We still need to cover the slutty intern
and the divorce
You know what?
You sound more and more like mom every day
Take it back
So two uteruses
that's pretty cool
And you're engaged
That's also cool
Well,
greg talked me into it
Oh,man,from the first moment I saw noelle,
I was ham
Did you just say "ham"?
- You're either ham or eggs
- Here we go
You gotta ask yourself in every situation,
are you the chicken or are you the pig?
Sorry,
pig or chicken?
Look,you got a plate of ham and eggs,
all right?
Now--
now the chicken is involved in the meal,
but the pig--
now the pig is committed
So the question is--
are you involved or are you committed?
Ham or eggs
karev,
you free?
Absolutely,
sir
Great,take this
I'm on hold with the D M V
Some mix-up about switching my license
and registration to seattle
Take care of that for me?
Thanks for thinking of me,
sir
O'malley,
how's it feel to be the new gynie grunt?
I got a patient who was born with
and is pregnant in two uteruses
Two uteruses
- Jealous?
- No
No,I'm-- I'm--
I'm busy I'm on hold
- important business
- Right
For sloan
Right,it's super important,
I'm sure
Noelle labatt,
room 2314
Two,two,two,two,
two,two
hang on
Can I see that for a sec?
Did I just hear him say "two uteruses"?
I'm sorry
You-- you must be
nancy-pants?
Hey,
loser
I wish derek had told me you were coming to visit
like he tells you anything these days?
Yeah,well,
I'm working on that
What are you doing here,mark?
Are you trying to torture him?
He's my family,nancy
Plus,I needed a change of pace
Plus,
I slept with my tennis partner's wife,
and he went out and bought a gun
There it is
my god
Nancy!
let me guess
Did mom send you out?
I hear derek's trying to ban you from seattle
Did he also tell you
that he's living in a trailer?
yeah
Derek
derek
I want to see the two uteruses
Yeah,
find me later
- I miss her
- Yeah
me,too
The diesel pushes past cornerback don mcneal
He's at the 30 He's at the 20
He's at the 10
Touchdown,
washingtoredskins
I'm sorry
One of the twins gets rowdy,and greg gets
carried  away when talking to the baby
He's decided that the baby is into sports,
of all things
Well,
she's daddy's little girl
I can tell,see,
because when I talk to her--
yeah,the rhythm in your voice,
it helps calm her
Sure I read a couple of articles
on that recently,actually
Dr Karev,
I knew you secretly missed my service
Right
Greg,noelle,
I have very good news for you
According to our tests,
the babies are both perfectly healthy
But they are substantially different sizes
for a very unique reason
The test indicate that the babies
have two different due dates
according to our calculations,
the larger baby,
your son,was conceived a full
six weeks before your daughter
- I
- oh,god
I-I don't--
I-I don't understand
That-- that can't be right
That's impossible
No,actually,
it's quite possible
Our tests are extremely accurate
in predicting due dates
But we broke up
Yeah,see,she,
she got pregnant
I wanted to get married She didn'T
I gave her an ultimatum,and she left me
Greg,I am so sorry
I am so,so sorry
I mean,we were barely speaking six weeks
after the conception,
let alone having sex
Or at least I wasn't having sex
It was one night,greg
It was one night
I-I didn't think that this could happen
It was nothing
I can't believe you did this
I can't believe you didn't tell me
god,
I can't believe this
He's not the father of both babies
**************************
I hear you burned your hand
because you were studying?
I can't even be allowed to warm soup
within five days of taking the bar
So you burned your hand while you were--
- burning my soup
- And when you grabbed the pot--
dropped it,obviously
I mean,it was literally red hot
You must have held on to it for a little while,
though
This burn's extremely deep
Oh,yeah No,that's right
I held on,and then I dropped it
There are some deep partial thickness burns here
Give her a gram of cefazolin and a tetanus
It's too bad,really,
that I did this to my hand
I'm supposed to be taking the bar again friday
This burn is bad,
but we'll get you fixed up
You'll be fine to take the test on friday
I will?
she's lying
Something's off about gretchen's story
Izzie,
you're only supposed to be observing
I am observing
I'm observing closely
And I'm telling you something is off
Did you see her reaction when sloan
told her she'd be okay to take the test again?
That was not relief
That was panic
It's okay to be nervous
about being back here at work,
bout failing,
but you haven't even been back a full day yet,
and already you're pushing to bend the rules
Meredith,
this is so not about me
This is about our patient
I am worried about our patient,
and get off your high freakin' horse
This is my patient
Try to remember that
Fine
Whatever
Iz
A humpty dumpty surgery?
B-burke's doing a humpty dumpty today?
yes
Well,
I've never seen a humpty firsthand before
Yeah,
me neither
what are you doing?
Scrubbing in
You'll let burke know?
Sure
I know you're not talking to me anymore,
and that's okay,
but there's something I'd like to explain
All you have to do is listen
You and me,
we're like ham and eggs
I was the chicken
I just want you to know
that I know that I was the chicken
You put yourself out there
and you were committed,
and I was just putting the eggs on the plate
Not the ham,
because you were the p
I was involved,
but now I'm committed
- Did you just call me a pig?
- No,it's a metaphor
Calling me a pig?
The point is,
you're not the pig anymore
What I'm trying to say is I'm the pig
Now I am the pig
I am the pig
I've been waiting for you guys
for a half an hour in the cafeteria
Since when do we eat in a patient room?
Izzie,
meet really old guy
We found him a couple of days ago
he sleeps all the time
It's quiet in here
Nobody bothers us
No,what are you doing?
It turns out I'm not doing anything
I'm literally not allowed to do anything
I knew coming back was gonna be an adjustment,
but this is just--
no
What are you doing right now?
Eating my lunch
Okay,if you want to socialize or talk
about your day or get in a quick therapy session,
you know,
go do it over there
- Seriously?
- Good-bye,izzie
Okay,
fine
So,o'malley,
your chick with the two uteruses?
You're on scut--
glorified plastics scut
You are in no position to mock me or my uteruses
Any cervical changes on the ultrasound?
- Why do you care?
- I don'T
I'm so glad to be back
Yay!
I'm not complaining about you
You and I are fine,boss
this is weird
- I called callie a pig
- to her face?
what happened to the whole she's a corpse thing?
I just can't get over how much
everything around here has changed
- How many times?
- Just one time
- I get one,too,then
- Deal
Gin
what was,
with that,with meredith?
We have a thing
Wait,you have a thing with meredith
and I don't know about it?
I live with you
I see you every day
It's a work thing
Okay,
you know,
the whole point of hanging out
with really old guy is that he doesn't talk
The man is sedated
This is supposed to be a quiet place
See?
Changed
She's changed
Everything's changed
I gave the other nurse a list
of his medications this morning
My husband needs his pills
He needed them hours ago!
okay
Why don't you check on the meds again?
- I have checked on them
- No,meds,pharmacy,now
I'm sorry
I am sorry
It's fine
I was never a yeller before
I'm becoming this horrible person
who yells at people who are just trying
to do their job
You are just looking out for your husband
You do exactly what it takes to protect him,
and that does not make you horrible
It makes you smart
He said he was leaving
He said he wasn't coming back
She's hyperventilating,
and the baby's had some bradycardia
noelle,
I ed you to get back into bed now
Is greg out there?
Did he leave? Like really leave?
Just take deep breaths
I always give him such a hard time,
you know,about everything
Like he likes weddings I hate them
He loves kids,and me,they scare me to death
Noelle,
have you had any cramping,
any contractions,
any pressure at all?
But I can't do this without him
We'll get past this,right?
We have to get past this
Damn it
All right,noelle,
I need you to get into bed,okay?
Why,
what's happening?
Stay on your left side,
and whatever you do,do not push,okay?
okay,I need slow,
deep breaths
So tell me about the slutty girl
Fine,
the slutty intern
It was the slutty part I had a problem with
Kathleen says she's not even single
She is single She's wonderful
She's smart
She's a lot of things
And she's none of your business,nancy
I've never seen you  like this over a girl,
even addison
I've never been like this over a girl,
especially addison
don't be bitter I mean,
shame on addison and all that,
but he's mark,derek
What did you expect?
He's just
mark
And who hasn't gone there once or twice,
right?
- What'd you say?
- Oh,come on
Everybody sleeps with mark
It's practically a rite of passage
Derek,
I get it,okay?
I get that they made a terrible mistake
It wasn't a mistake
Nancy,it wasn't a mistake
It wasn't just one night
It was months
They were together for months
Didn't you know that?
No,I had no idea
Then shut up about it and eat your lunch
STAFF:BURKE   LES :
Derek's sister is in town
Cristina,
are you mad at me or something?
Because I have been trying to talk to you all week
Everything is not about you,
meredith
Okay,what is going on?
Because george and alex are saying--
- I-I don't care
- What is your problem?
I just
I have bigger things in my life right now
What?
Nothing
10 blade
Hey Hey,dr O'malley Can you,
can you tell me what's happening in there?
I thought you left
She thinks you left her
Look,man,
this is all a lot to digest
I mean,
our daughter,
my--
my little girl isn't even my little girl anymore
Noelle is in there freaking out because you left
Just tell me if she is okay,
please
She's gone into premature labor
Dr Montgomery-shepherd--
dr
Montgomery is about to do an emergency c-section
on one of the babies to try
to stop the labor on the other
Wait,
so you're delivering one of the babies right now,
today?
In just a few minutes
The boy or the girl?
Greg
ham or eggs?
You say you want a career in plastics,
anyet you can't tear yourself away
from the baby catchers long
enough to actually show me you want it
Being on hold with the D M V Has nothing to do
with a career in plastics,dr Sloan
Only it does,because being on hold
with the D M V Has to do with me,
and I have everything to do
with your career in plastics
Tyler
addison montgomery needs two units
of b-positive blood in l&dstat
I'm on it
So the biosynthetic dressing should ensure
that you won't need skin grafts,
and that's good news
If I did need grafts,
would that take long?
I mean,
like how long would something like that take if--
if I had needed them?
that would just depend
on the severity of the burn,really
so more severe than this one?
It would have to be more severe?
just to make sure I have everything accurate,
you burned your hand
we've been over this,
haven't we?
I'm sorry
I--
look,I have a test on friday,
and I have work to do
So I have to--
I-I want to go home
I'm really ready to get out of here now,
okay?
I'm sorry
I didn't mean to--
gretchen,
did you burn your hand on purpose?
Izzie,
you heard what dr Bailey said
It's okay if you did
It's just,did you burn your hand
to get out of taking your test?
I can't fail that damn test one more time
I just
can'T
It's all anyone in my family,
in my life--
it's all they talk about
It's all I'm known for
"Oh,gretchen,the failure
" Can you imagine failing the bar exam five times?
Five times
I mean,
that's absurd
I mean
that's just,
that's pathetic
I cannot sit for two
and a half solid days of testing again
just to prove to everyone
again
how pathetic I am
Not
when
you feel that pathetic all by yourself
okay,
I've completed the incision
I'm going to ask you to move the top uterus
to the side so I can reach the one underneath
got it
Now I don't want to alarm you
or make you nervous in any way,
o'malley,
because you seem like a decent person,
but I've got about 120 seconds to get baby one out
of uterus one while you're holding uterus two,
and if you so much as hiccup,
you could tear the uterine wall
and kill this woman's child
So do what you can to be careful,
okay?
Okay
Look at that
Amazing,
applying the final hemostasis suture
Great
Don't be afraid to--
grab a bigger piece?
Got it
Good Very nice,
dr Yang
Applying pressure
Gently
It was attached to the interventricular septum
Are you gonna use a graft to repair?
Somebody's been doing their homework
4-0 prolene,please
Thank you very much,
Ready to perforate uterus two
Scalpel
Wait Wait,
dr Montgomery
My baby's moving It's really moving
I can't hold it
George,I need you to hold her
still if I'm gonna do this c-section
I'm trying
I mean it,
o'malley
What should I do?
It's really moving I can't hold it
I need you to keep her still,george
You're sending her into distress
You have to get that baby to stop moving
- How do I do that?
- Talk,o'malley
Alex
Karev,
back away from the table
Talk to it,to the baby,
to calm it down
- Karev
- Talk about what?
October 30,
1974--
it's the fight known as "rumble in the ngle
" World heavyweight champ george foreman
is pitted against muhammad ali
in his first major fight
after three and a half years out of the ring
- It's working
- Foreman is favored to win
He's younger,
he's stronger
scalpel
But he's not prepared for what
ali would later call the rope-a-dope
It all started in the second round
Foreman comes out swinging
Ali's backed up against the ropes
that's not gonna stay on
You're giving it too much slack
You're blocking my light
Think of it as a basic corner stitch
I can figure out how to sew on my own buttons,
thank you I am surgeon Right
for god's sakes
You sew this on for me,
and I'll get rid of addison and sloan
- Really?
- No
fine
I'll do it anyway
So I heard you've got a sister wandering the halls
She planning on moving here,
too?
God,
I hope not
Derek,
I know it's been hard on you
He was like my brother
I have four sisters
four very annoying sisters
Mark was my brother
It's--
it's hard
Divorce isn't all it's cracked up to be,
huh?
I just want it to be easy
I want it to be over and move on
But
but you're in a surprising amount of pain
You and adele?
I'm sewing on a button
for the first time in my life
What does that tell you?
technically,
I'm sewing
I'm just saying
Dr Sloan
So we're clear,
you knew when you stepped into that surgery,
you were forfeiting your future in plastics,
right?
- But,dr Sloan--
- I need my phone back
Well done
You really prepared
Yes,
I'm always prepared
Couldn't do it without you
- Thank you
- Dr Burke,
could we have a moment alone?
I just--
I didn't realize that you were one of them,
one of the doctors around here
with doubts about me or my abilities
Miranda,
I'm not
My name was erased from the board
I have to assume that was you
- Dr Bailey--
- I just-- I just--
I just need to know why
I need you to tell me why you didn't w
ant me in on your surgery
I'm afraid I just couldn't use you
I understand
you should've seen that
Two uteruses So unbelievably cool
And a cute baby to boot
Well,
I'm glad you're enjoying your trip
Relax,derek
I'm going
I'm on a plane in two hours
So
you're gonna report back to mom that?
That you're you
Still running in circles
around all the women in your life,
but that's to be expected
with four sisters and a dead dad
I'm not running around in circles
Derek,
can y even remember the last time you were alone?
You've never been single,
ever
I mean,you're fine,
but you're not happy
And you're not gonna get happy
until you get some space
Just get away from addie,
away from the intern,
just away
Figure out what you want
Kathleen's the shrink,
nancy,not you
I gotta go
Nancy
Thanks for flying out here
It was,
thanks
- where are we going again?
- We need to go upstairs
Okay
wait Wait
Where are we?
We're on the psychiatric floor,
gretchen
We need to place you on a 72-hour hold
No,I'm not crazy You can't--
no I'm going home
- Gretchen
- No,you have to let me go home
Please I'll just--
I need to go back home Please
If you go home,
you're just gonna hurt yourself again Right?
Isn't that your plan,
so that you won't have to take the bar exam?
You need some help,
gretchen
If the idea of taking an exam makes you
hold your palm to a burner,
you need some help
Everyone needs help from time to time,
someone to look out for them,
make sure they're okay,
make sure they're ready
I have that
And you need that right now
- I'm not crazy
- I know
I st
didn't want to fail
I know
What happened?
Are my babies okay?
The surgery went very well
You have a healthy baby boy
And the labor stopped on your little girl
She's gonna be just fine
And greg?
Has greg come back yet?
No,noelle,
I'm sorry
Greg isn't here
I want an update every half-hour,
and--
what happened?
- My babies?
- They're just fine
You're just coming out of anesthesia,
noelle
Everything went very well
Is greg back yet?
I'm so sorry,
noelle He's not here
And be sure to alert me to any fetal distress
What happened?
Your babies are healthy,noelle
Everything's okay
Is greg back yet?
I'm right here
Hi
I,
I saw our son
He's amazing
But how's our little girl?
You look like you could use a little cheering up
Not from you
if I recall,
I was pretty good at cheering you up
one,t wo yep,
three very cheerful times
Dirty It was not "cheerful
" It was dirty
And like I said,
no
So your sister really doesn't like me,
huh?
Sorry
It's just,she'S
from the east coast
Well,
I-- I-- you know what?
I shoulda called
But you didn'T
I want us to work,
it's just--
it's complicated
I think I need a little time to
take some space
Yeah
To clear my head
I okay
Okay
There are times  when even the best of us
have trouble with commitment
Dr Stevens
I was just looking at dr
Grey's evaluation on your first day back to work
I get daily report cards now?
She had a lot to say
Yes,
sir
It was a difficult catch
Nicely handled
Good work
Welcome back,
dr Stevens
I was rude to you before
I'm sorry
I understand what you're trying to say
You're the
pig
You are committed
Only we broke up
And I've been wanting to hear
this from you for how long?
And-- and you wait until now to say it
to me after we've broken up?
I'm out of my element here
I break bones for a living
I-I used to live in the basement
Most days I wear last night's eyeliner to work
I don't give a crap
what other people think about me
because I am a happily independent,
successful woman,
and I like it that way
Only when you say stuff like this,
it just
it makes things too hard So please
don't chase me anymore
unless you're ready to catch me
And we may be surprised  by the commitments
we're willing  to let slip out of our grasp
Commitments are complicated
I'm here for you,
whatever it is
Whenever you're ready,
I'm here
Thank you
We may surprise ourselves
by the commitmen  we're willing to make
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-cflily
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
GARYS ANATOMY
Season 03 Episode 06
True commitment takes effort
and sacrifice
Which is why sometimes
we have to learn the hard way
to choose our commitments
very carefully