Previously on Grey's Anatomy...
I have sex last night
with the wrong person.
This is our secret, okay?
Go 60 days with no sex,
no other women.
If I'm not having sex,
neither are you.
- Chief resident?
- The one fifth year resident
that rules all residents.
I went to the board this morning
and told 'em I was retiring.
I came out here to be chief,
- and Meredith complicates that.
- So I just have to pick one?
If you don't pick one,
this is gonna be your face
the rest of your life.
My name is not Ava!
You made it up!
It's not me!
What percentage of americans
will get an acute appy?
As interns, we know what we want...
to become surgeons...
And we'll do anything to get there.
7.
What are the signs
of residual eye infections?
Uh, pus, uh, redness and, uh, fever.
Suffer through killer exams,
endure 100-hour weeks,
stand for hours on end
in operating rooms...
- You name it, we'll do it.
- What's conn's syndrome?
- Uh, w-wait, wait, I know this.
- Oh, tick tock, dude.
Cracking under the pressure.
No. Um...
Hypercortolis... Cortisolism!
Unh-unh. Unh-unh. Uh,
primary hyperaldosteronism.
Yes! Out of the seat.
My turn.
- No, it's my turn.
- No, it is not.
- Um, try this one.
- You know, I...
White sponge with vanilla buttercream.
Yeah, I'm trying to study for the most
important test of my intern career.
- I don't have time for wedding cake.
- Well, just try it.
Go! Go!
Uh, what is the strongest
layer of the small bowel?
Fine. Yummy. Go.
Damn it,
damn it, damn it.
It is not snot.
- Submucosa!
- Yes.
Wait, wait, wait.
How do you know that?
- Are you studying with the wife's cards
- What cards?
Callie was ranked number one
in her year after this test.
She has legendary flash cards.
We don't need the flash cards.
We are independently brilliant.
- Dream team.
- Yeah, I'm gonna hurl. Outta the seat.
No, my turn.
I'm gonna kick all your asses.
This is the lemon.
Might be a little tart.
What is actinic keratosis?
Uh... actinic keratosis is,
uh, a premalignant lesion.
- In old people.
- In anyone.
Too tart?
I don't care.
I mean, is Alex right or am I?
Learn to care,
or I'll get another bride.
I love it. I love all cakes.
Now break the tie.
Karev's right.
The tough part, though,
is reconciling
this huge thing we want:
to be surgeons...
with everything else we want.
I haven't seen you
in a few days.
- I left messages.
- Yeah, I know.
- I was just trying to--
- I know I told you to stop hovering
and you did,
and I appreciate that.
But now stop with the stopping.
No, you're right. It's ridiculous for me
to worry about you all the time.
It's sweet that you worry.
It is. I should communicate more.
- Right.
- You don't think I can do it.
- I can do it
- Really?
In a few seconds, I'll be
getting on that elevator.
And then I'll be going
on rounds.
See, uh, I'm, uh,
getting on the elevator.
Communicating.
28 more days and...
Then it's you and me
in a locked room
for a record-breaking,
earth-shattering,
- mind-blowing...
- Okay! I get it.
- Thank you.
- That was less than enthusiastic.
I'm gonna be
more enthusiastic when we...
cross the finish line.
Okay.
Just making sure you haven't
lost interest in the project.
Not at all.
Good.
What are you doing?
The bakery wants me to make
a decision by tomorrow.
So if you can tell me
your favorite by then,
that would be great.
Cakes and little place cards?
Okay, he's turning into a girl.
I think it's sweet. He obviously
cares about this stuff.
This white one
taste's pretty good.
I should bring a piece
to Derek, right?
That's what good girlfriend's do,
bring their boyfriend's cake
and communicate?
No. The best ones just keep
all that stuff to themselves.
- Did you bring Callie's cards?
- Uh, no.
- Oh, well, no cake for you.
- Dr. Bailey,
I saw a hemiglossectomy
on the board. Can I scrub in?
No, no. You're not
doing surgeries today.
- What?
- Your intern exams are in two weeks.
You need to spend every available
minute studying for them.
Oh, believe me,
when you won't have to repeat
your year as interns,
you'll be thanking me
for this opportunity.
So, Grey and Yang,
you're... doing scut.
O'Malley, Stevens,
you'll be joing me
in the clinic.
Karev, you're with Ava.
Um, I don't always
have to be on her case.
Someone else can have her.
Or not.
So...
Last night we studied together.
Today we're, uh,
treating patients together.
And we're fine.
We're not tortured,
it's not weird.
We made a mistake
and we've moved on.
If anything, I think it brings
us closer together as friends.
- We're very impressive.
- I think we are.
Larry Jennings just checked in
to the hospital.
- What's the matter with him?
- I have no idea.
His assistant said it was
a matter of the utmost discretion.
Oh, that's never good.
Yeah, whatever it is,
it was important enough
for him to cut short
his vacation and fly home.
I want you
on point on this one.
- No clinic today.
- Oh, I can do both.
Miranda, we are talking
the chairman of the board
of Seattle Grace hospital.
The clinic will survive
without you for a day.
- Learn to delegate.
- Who am I supposed to delegate to?
Chief Webber,
you paged me?
Sydney Heron
reporting for duty.
I was wondering if I was
gonna see you today.
- Where you been?
- Just getting my assignments.
Yeah, anything good?
Anything as good as a crazily
hormonal pregnant amnesiac
with a tendency to yell
at the wrong people?
Your blood pressure's higher
than it should be.
So what,
we're not friends anymore?
Fine.
Then I won't tell you about
Dr. Montgomery's sex bet...
with the overly hot Dr. Sloan.
Yeah.
If he can go 60 days without sex,
they're getting back together.
Apparently they used to be a thing
back when she was married
to Dr. Mcdreamy.
The question is, how do you
know all that?
I'm on bed rest 5 feet
from the nurses' station,
and I have excellent hearing.
I know everything.
It's like...
It's like watching a soap.
Do you know how many doctors in this
hospital nurse Olivia has slept with?
Wait. Who am I talking to?
You're one of 'em.
Anyway, I'd strongly advise you
to move on Dr. Montgomery
before you lose your shot,
or I would if we were friends.
- So if she wants to be with Sloan...
- Dude...
if she wanted to be with Sloan,
she'd be with Sloan.
The other board members have
a say in who gets to be chief,
but Larry... he's the one
who really decides, okay?
He knows it,
and they know it.
So if the attendings
find out he's here...
The man won't get
a moment's peace.
You have to leave now. I want
you all out of here, okay?
Look, go, go, go. Out.
All right. But you know
where to find me.
Celeste. Larry's assistant.
- He's in here.
- Okay.
- Go away.
- But we can help.
- We can help?
- What is that supposed to mean?
He doesn't have any woman parts.
It's not like we don't know
where he is.
- Right. We'd just come back anyway.
- Right.
Richard. Finally.
Oh, for God Sake. What are
the four musketeers doing here?
What happened
to "I'll be discreet"?
Larry, they're here
for the same reason I am,
to see if they can help.
Right.
Bunch of ghouls.
All right, one of you
wants to be the new chief...
Fix this...
and you got my vote.
And, no,
those are not grapefruits.
Well... looks as though you won't be
needing my services after all.
And suprapubic tenderness.
That's because I haven't
taken a leak in three days.
- Three days.
- Could be a hernia.
A hernia wouldn't do that.
Was there trauma?
Testicular torsion,
uh, you know...
- twisting?
- Twisting.
You'd have to tie him
in a triple knot
to get that kind of
fluid buildup.
Am I wrong?
I was taking a 2-week raft ride
down the Amazon.
Maybe it's a tropical disease.
Schistosomiasis?
Filariasis?
Well, now they're just guessing.
Richard!
Dr. Bailey, call Dr. Fischer
in urology
to do a suprapubic cath
an order an ultrasound
and K.U.B.
Larry, have you called Nancy?
I don't want to worry my wife
unless I have to.
She wasn't on the trip
with you?
White chocolate with...
hmmm, buttercream.
Dr. Montgomery.
I can't decide.
Triple berry at least has fruit,
so I could pretend it's healthy.
Yeah, Ava's B.P. is 171 over 118.
- She's preeclamptic.
- I ordered blood tests
and a biophysical profile
on the baby.
It was fine, but, uh,
Ava's got edema.
- Get her on mag and hydralazine.
- What about an epidural,
to get her blood pressure down?
- I mean, am I going overboard or...
- Believe me,
I wish I had someone
who cared that much
about my blood pressure.
Yeah, well, from what I hear,
in 28 days you will.
I've had a cold,
like forever.
And I've been here
three times,
and they keep telling me
it's gonna go away,
but my nose
just won't stop running.
I'm like the most disgusting
fountain in the world.
Sometimes these things
just drag on.
- You might have to wait it out.
- No, I can't wait anymore.
See, there's, uh,
there's a girl, and...
we've been out a few times,
and now it's gotten to the point
where we're supposed to,
you know, seal the deal.
But the nose thing is so gross,
I can't get anywhere near her.
Well, I'm sure if she's really
into you, she'll hang in there.
No, no, no. You don't understand.
Have you ever met someone
where the attraction was so intense,
you thought it may just kill you?
Like you're in the same room,
and your skin is on fire.
You want to touch 'em so bad...
Yeah, okay, we get it.
We're...
- on the case.
- Yes, I will do an E.N.T.,
and you will listen to his, uh...
- Chest.
- Yes.
I'm on it.
Which fluid resuscitation
technique
is used in acute burns?
The parkland formula.
Come on, Mer. Step it up.
What is virchow's triad?
Oh, I hate George.
He married into the cards.
You think he knew? You think
that's why he married her?
Yeah, that's why
he married her.
We need those cards.
We don't need the cards.
- What is virchow's triad?
- Dr. Torres.
Um, Dr. Burke and I are trying
to choose a wedding cake,
and there are some samples
in the conference room.
If you have a moment, I would
really love your opinion,
because, you've got such great taste.
You're not getting my cards, Yang.
Dr. Bailey...
need an intern?
Uh, yeah. How's it going
in the clinic, O'Malley?
How's Sydney doing?
Oh, that's w-why
you wanted to see me,
to find out how things
were going? I...
- Dr. Bailey, um can I...
- Well...
- talk to you for a second?
- Oh, of course, Ms. Newman.
What can I do for you?
This is embarrassing.
Um, mortifying, actually...
I think I need to be tested.
Larry and I...
Whatever Larry has,
I probably have it as well.
Uh, O'Malley.
- Yeah.
- Page Dr. Montgomery.
How's it going, buddy bud?
I'm getting a strep culture on bed 9
and discharging Mr. Benton.
The gentleman with the sinus issues?
It's a runny nose,
and I have a test to study for,
- and Bailey doesn't like us...
- Bailey's not here today, okay? I am.
And it's all well and good
to open a clinic
as some kind of power play
for chief resident,
but chief resident isn't really
about big think.
It's about patient care, okay?
So let's see what we can do
to improve
Mr. Benton's experience.
It's just a cold.
Nasal lavage.
- Because we care.
- Nasal lavage?
Get yourself a bulb syringe,
squeeze an isotonic solution
into one of Mr. Benton's nostrils.
It'll squirt right out the other
side. Incredibly restorative.
Rinse and repeat.
It's not what you think.
I-I mean, it is. It's, uh...
It's just not an affair.
Though, I guess technically
it is.
But we're in love.
The, uh, the kind of love you
think you're never gonna find,
and then you do and...
the fact that he's married
seems a small price to pay
for being happy, you know?
At least, most of the time.
But then five years go by,
and he still hasn't left
his wife, and...
you must think
I'm a terrible person.
- No, no. No judgment whatsoever.
- I mean,
I know I should
leave him, it's just...
Do you have any idea
how rare it is
to find someone you can work
and play with?
And we love each other.
How wrong can it be?
Richard, this thing
still hurts like hell,
and my boys here
are not getting any smaller.
I want to know
what you're doing about it.
Well, the urologist
just drained your bladder.
Next step is an ultrasound
and an X-ray.
The interns will be
taking you up quickly.
No, no, I mean,
what are you doing for me?
Getting some of the best surgeons
in the world to help you.
I came here for you.
You.
You're the best surgeon
in this place,
at least you used to be.
What's the problem, Larry?
Am I not taking
good enough care of you?
How does a man lose his...
desire at 53, 54,
however old you are?
How does that happen?
I haven't, okay?
There are other things in life.
Like what,
Adele leaving you?
Even more reason to keep the job.
You're a surgeon, man.
I have to go skinny-dipping in the
Amazon to get that kind of a thrill.
I'm not gonna let you browbeat
me into keeping this job.
Like I'd even want to
at this point.
When I appointed you
chief of surgery,
you were hungry,
you were the man.
Now you're a politician,
giving me excuses,
handing things off.
I hate to think that's the kind
of doctor that you've become,
but if it is...
maybe it is best
that you're stepping down.
I know I said you could use
the day to study,
but we've got
an all-hands-on-deck situation.
- A bad car accident?
- Multiple gunshot wounds?
A penis. The chairman
of the board's penis.
What's wrong with it?
His testicles have swollen,
which is the understatement
of the year.
Fantastic. How much?
No, you know, don't tell me.
Let it be a surprise.
Look, you and Grey can
take him for his ultrasound
- and his X-ray.
- The V.I. penis.
Just go.
Elephantiasis?
No way Jennings has that.
Did you check for brucellosis?
It could be
Fournier's gangrene.
I don't know.
I'd go to gonorrhea
before I went there.
Then again, I'll be there
at the finish line
to make him pretty,
which is what he'll remember.
Oh, uh, Derek.
Grey wanted me to tell you
that she's still working
on Jennings' X-ray,
and that she'll be in the, uh,
X-ray viewing room.
Good to know.
She's communicating.
Just when I need time to think,
she suddenly starts communicating.
Time to think about what?
All of it... the relationship,
the chief thing...
how to juggle both
without getting distracted.
With Cristina,
I have to be explicit.
There would be no wedding
if I wasn't.
- Oh, it's that easy, huh?
- Oh, no.
I never said it was easy.
Right.
- Hey
- Hey. How's it going?
I, uh...
caught George in a lie
the other day.
He said he spent
the day in the clinic
when he spent it doing god knows
what with Izzie Stevens.
- It's probably nothing, right?
- Right.
Right.
So how's your man-whore?
Miraculously reformed?
For now.
That's never gonna
turn him into...
- what I want.
- Which is?
The whole thing.
I want someone stable
who barbecues
and teaches little kids
how to play catch.
That's not Mark Sloan.
Which doesn't explain why
I spent the entire day
looking at Alex Karev
like a puppy at a chew toy.
Why don't you just
go there already?
Because he doesn't
barbecue either.
Plus, he's like 12 years old.
Could fit all of
his belongings in a milk crate.
I don't know.
Guys like Karev...
Look, at least you know
he'll never lie to you.
Guys like him, they...
They mess around in their 20s,
but, then they, you know...
pack it in and...
and teach their kids
to play catch.
Maybe.
I need to stop thinking
about both of them.
And I have to stop thinking
about Izzie Stevens.
Hey, Callie...
Here's the thing,
when you're obsessing
about something like that,
there's generally a reason.
What the hell are you doing?
Nasal lavage.
Why?
Because she's trying
to kill me.
Sydney.
Dr. Bailey, we've really
turned this place around today.
- Nasal lavage?
- Four visits in one month?
Oh, are you questioning
my patient care?
Miranda, I get it, okay?
You're protecting your turf.
Very mama bear.
Very chief resident.
But this is not about
hospital politics, okay?
This is about the patient.
The patient can go home.
Get that stuff out of his nose.
No, I'm not comfortable
discharging him
until we've addressed
his problem.
The 16 patients
in the waiting room
aren't comfortable either.
Sir, I...
I-I don't think there's
anything else we can do.
You know, colds drag on.
Yeah. Yeah, I hear you.
- Oh, hell.
- What?
That come out of his nose?
See? This is why I'm never
gonna have sex again.
Uh, wait right here.
Um, order a head C.T.
Why? It's not a cold?
No, Dr. Stevens.
It's definitely not a cold.
Hey, just so you know,
I'll be over here
while you're over there, okay?
Cute.
Easy to locate, right?
Girlfriend comes with a G.P.S.
Looks like some kind
of foreign object.
- Ouch.
- That almost looks like...
A skeleton.
It's skeleton-like.
Definitely skeletony.
- Are those barbs?
- No.
- Can't be.
- Well, it could be.
It looks like a teeny,
tiny catfish.
That's close.
You see there?
Those are spines.
This is a candiru fish.
The penis fish?
This guy has the penis fish...
In his... in his...
What the hell
did you do to me?
You know, most pregnant
laboring women
- love their epidurals.
- I'm not in labor.
I'm trying to keep it that way.
By paralyzing me
from the waist down?
I can't even sit up
in the bed.
I'm missing the show...
the Seattle Grace show.
I can help with that.
So I guess you're
talking to me again.
Well, I can't stay mad at you.
I tried. But I couldn't do it.
You make your move
on the redhead?
I thought you already knew everything
that went on in this hospital.
As a matter of fact,
I have an update.
I saw her talking to
the ortho resident.
Yeah, and?
She's seizing.
She's seizing!
Somebody page Dr. Montgomery!
Somebody page
Dr. Montgomery, now!
It's the candiru.
It's a freshwater fish
that lives in the Amazon.
It's a parasite.
I'm not an idiot.
I didn't drink from the Amazon.
- Did you urinate in it?
- No, I... What?
The candiru is attracted
to blood and urine.
It's been known to swim
up the stream of urine
and lodge itself
in a man's urethra.
You mean a fish swam up...
It's rare, but there are
documented cases.
One man actually saw it go in
and tried to grab it.
- It was too slippery.
- Yang.
- It's in the literature.
- So this thing is in my...
Is now in your bladder.
Well, right next to it.
It's stuck in your, uh,
prostatic urethra,
which is causing
the obstruction.
We need to get it quickly
before it causes sepsis.
Sepsis?
You mean I could die?
B.P. shot up to 202 over 134.
There's fetal distress.
The epidural didn't help.
- It'll help during delivery.
- What's going on? Alex?
Your blood pressure spiked.
You had a seizure.
The only way we can reduce
your blood pressure
and the swelling in your brain
is if we deliver the baby right now.
No. She's only 30 weeks.
I'm not in labor.
We're gonna do a c-section.
Don't worry.
The survival rate for preemies
at 30 weeks is extremely high.
Alex, tell her no.
- I'm not ready.
- You're ready.
But I can't do this
by myself.
Then it's a good thing
you're not by yourself.
I was on a consult
on the chairman of the board.
This better be good.
- What do we have?
- We had a patient in the clinic...
Chronic runny nose,
a halo sign on the pillow.
The fluids are still in the lab,
but as far as I can tell...
He's leaking spinal fluid
through his nose.
Thought you might like
this one.
Oh, okay. Look at that.
It's a brain herniation.
His brain is literally sinking
into his skull base.
And all along,
I thought it was a cold.
- Book an O.R.
- Dr. Bailey?
You're still studying.
You can watch from the gallery.
- I'll scrub in with you.
- Thought you're doing Jennings.
No, um, I'll do both. I sent
this guy home three times.
I can't not scrub in.
Your daughter is beautiful, Ava.
- She is?
- She is.
- Get her over to the warmer right away.
- I'll work on her.
Hand her off to peds.
I need an extra set of hands.
- We need to hang some blood.
- Why?
Why do we need blood?
Want me to get
the uterine arteries?
- Yeah.
- Clamp.
Uh, Alex, what's going on?
- Alex.
- If the bleeding vessels are deep...
- You what?
- Ligate around the hemostats.
- Got it.
- Oh my god.
I'm gonna die.
Oh, my god. I'm gonna die.
- Can I?
- Go ahead.
...and my baby's gonna be
all alone. Oh, my god.
Ava.
Ava, look at me, okay?
Look at me.
You're not gonna die.
You're doing great.
You're gonna be fine.
The baby's gonna be fine.
I just need you to breathe
for me, all right?
Nice slow, deep breaths.
That's it.
Just breathe. That's it.
Keep breathing.
Celeste.
Good news.
No chances of an S.T.D.
Now Larry's condition...
He's having surgery,
but you are fine.
You did hear the part
about being fine, right?
That's what
I keep telling myself,
that I'm fine with things
they way they are, but...
I probably won't be really fine
until...
I don't care
if he's fine anymore.
Celeste?
I got here as soon as...
Is he in surgery yet?
Um, no. They're taking him soon.
This is Dr. O'Malley.
Dr. O'Malley...
This is Mr. Jennings' wife Nancy.
- Hi.
- It's a pleasure. He's just in there.
- They're prepping him for surgery.
- Thank you.
I left my car in front
in a no parking zone.
Could you move it?
What are you going to do?
Move her car.
- Talk about divine retribution.
- What?
He sleeps with his assistant
and a carnivorous fish
lodges itself in his penis.
That's instant karma
if I've ever seen it.
Well, Derek wasn't
struck by lightning,
- and neither were you.
- Addison showed up.
I had months of pain
and self-loathing,
a crazy, ranting mother
and a near drowning
off the side of a dock.
I mean, it's no fish
in my hoo-hoo,
but it's certainly not
an easy ride.
Well, I've cheated
on my boyfriends, and I'm fine.
I mean, am I the only one?
Which cake is your favorite,
or have you chosen one yet?
Okay, clearly,
you're not getting the point.
I don't have favorite cakes.
That's why you're involved.
We gotta go.
If you see my boyfriend,
tell him I had some tuna salad
and a yogurt,
and now I'm off to the O.R.
Okay, this is not eating
for pleasure.
I really need a choice,
so mark down your favorite.
Sorry I froze there
for a little bit.
That's okay.
I... I'm not... I'm not...
I'm not getting weird.
- You know, it was a weird question.
- Shut up and eat some cake.
- Good?
- Disgusting.
- Karev.
- Hey.
I was just checking up on Ava.
Do I have another Denny Duquette
situation on my hands?
What? Are you serious?
I have never seen you
so attentive with a patient.
You're always there...
Checking her stats,
running tests, doing research.
- That's my job.
- No, it's my job.
I'm her doctor.
You're my intern.
Which is why I have to know
her stats at all times.
Because I'm not about to stand
next to you in your O.R.
And be anything less
than overprepared.
Okay? There's no way I'm gonna
go to work every day
with a surgeon like you and not
be at the top of my game.
So if you want to yell at me...
Uh, I know you have
to give him the cards
'cause you're married to him.
I respect that.
But there is an argument
to be made for female surgeons
- sticking together.
- You're relentless.
- "Sisterhood" and all that, you know?
- Scary, inhuman relentless.
You are like a role model
to me or... something.
Okay, you know what? Stop.
Okay?
This is just getting sad.
I will give the cards to George.
- I am sure he will share.
- No, he won't, with me anyway.
He'll just share them with Izzie.
They're like an exclusive
little unit. Whatever.
Yang.
Uh... my, uh...
My locker
is on the right side,
third one from the door.
The cards are on the top shelf.
- Really? You...
- They're all yours.
Oh, god. Um...
- Sorry.
- It's okay. Me, too.
- I was, uh...
- Yeah, I...
- So we're good?
- Yes, good.
Good. Okay, then.
Don't talk.
I know it's not fair,
and I know it's not your fault,
I know there's nothing
between you and George.
I know that.
Except there is.
You're his best friend.
He loves you.
He gets you. He needs you.
And I'm just...
I'm just... I'm his wife.
And I know, I know
I get the sex
and the commitment
and the life with him...
But I-I want him to get me
and to need me.
And I can't compete with you.
So I'm asking you...
to please stop.
Just stop.
Find another friend.
Or whatever you do,
just give me my husband back.
What about the forked stone grasper?
It can lead to urethral injury.
Well, the forceps aren't working.
At this point,
I'm willing to try anything.
All right. Stone grasper.
- Coming in.
- Did we miss anything good?
Hello? You okay?
I've had better days.
Where's Dr. Bailey?
Page her.
V-tach.
Does he have a pulse with that?
- Oh, he's going down.
- Yes.
He needs 150 of amiodarone.
How much longer
you think it'll take?
You worry about getting
his arrhythmias down.
We're gonna have to change
our game plan.
The scope isn't working.
Excuse me, Dr. Fischer.
We're gonna have to
open him up.
I don't know how I missed it.
It presented as a cold, Miranda.
This sort of thing, at some point,
ou think it's gonna get better.
You don't figure it's something
that could ruin your whole life.
- The chief.
- The candiru?
- Go ahead. We're almost done here.
- Okay.
- Doctor.
- Thank you.
You want to quiz me
on the G.I. stuff?
No, I'm still trying to get
through my cardio notes.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
I should've snuck in
to the candiru surgery
- with Mer and Cristina.
- You still can...
George, can you maybe
stop talking
so I could concentrate?
What's your problem?
My problem... is you.
You're my penis fish.
Your what?
You've crawled in,
and latched on,
and now I can't move
or talk or think or even pee
without the nagging feeling
that something is eating
through my organs.
You don't
even have a penis.
- How am I the fish?
- It's a metaphor, George.
What happened to us being fine?
I don't know.
Maybe we're not.
A little more suction
there, please.
Those barbs won't let go.
Dr. Bailey,
glad you could join us.
Oh, this is useless.
We're gonna have to
cut it out, Dr. Fischer.
- I'll repair the bladder.
- Okay, let's do it.
How's his heart holding up?
Occasional runs of V-tach.
He can't take much more.
Forceps.
Okay. Almost there.
Come on, you.
Almost there.
Got it.
Oh, man. Unbelievable.
You see that thing?
Remind me never
to pee the Amazon.
What?
What do you say we have a real
meeting of the dirty mistresses club?
Like what it should've been
from the beginning.
- What are you doing?
- Once.
20 minutes in the on call room.
Nobody ever finds out.
- Mark.
- What you're telling me
everything's great
between you and Derek?
What makes you think
there is something wrong
between me and Derek?
Something's always wrong
between you and Derek.
Enough.
What is wrong with you?
Nothing. I'm... I'm...
Addison and I were gonna
try and make a go of it.
Things are not
gonna work out.
So you make a pass at me?
Like that'll help.
She doesn't want me.
Something's gotta help.
Revenge sex is not the answer.
If you're letting her go,
let her go.
Be an adult.
Thanks... for the baby
and for me not dying
and stuff.
Well, it's always a nice bonus
when a patient doesn't die.
You and red
make a pretty good team.
Don't tell Sloan.
Oh, she and Sloan
aren't happening.
She wants you.
- How do you know that?
- I know everything, remember?
I heard her talking
to the ortho doc
about how she wants someone
who barbecues and plays catch.
She wants someone
who's committed.
Yeah. Well, that's not me.
I hate to tell you this,
but it is.
You may talk tough,
but you're a decent guy, Alex.
Whether you want
to admit it or not,
you're actually
one of the good ones.
Mrs. Jennings.
Your husband's out of surgery.
Everything went very well.
Oh. Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
That's... That's wonderful.
Dr. Webber will be down
to fill you in soon.
Uh, Dr. O'Malley,
um, do me a favor.
Could you go tell Celeste?
She's a basket case,
and I just don't have it in me
to take care of my husband's
girlfriend right now.
Of course I know.
The wife always knows.
- Dr. O'Malley.
- Yes.
Mr. Jennings', uh,
personal physician
would like a copy
of his medic records.
Um, here's the number.
Mr. Jennings, I've canceled
your appointments for next week.
There's just a conference call
that's proving a little bit
difficult to reschedule.
But I'm sure Danny
can handle it.
Wait, what's...
What's Danny got to do with it?
I've asked him to step in,
temporarily,
until you find someone else.
Now, w-wait, Celeste...
What the hell was that all about?
Well, I think she just left you.
Good-bye, Larry.
What...
What the hell's going on here?
I think I'm done here.
Can you be a vault?
I think I need a vault
'cause I've eaten like
a cake and a half,
and it's just not cutting it.
- And you don't gossip.
- Because...
nobody tells me anything.
I was with a married man.
- It was...
- I don't mind
that nobody tells me anything.
It was George.
I was with George.
It should be firm inside,
not spongy.
The frosting,
like meringue...
Light and not too sweet.
I always thought
chocolate inside,
but, um, well,
I'm leaning away from that.
You've thought a lot
about this cake.
This cake...
for this day...
with this woman.
The red velvet's your winner,
by the way.
What are you doing here?
I wanted you to know
where I was,
so I thought I'd come
and tell you.
Oh, you're mocking me.
I'm apologizing to you.
You're making light
of things.
I'm running my fingers
through your hair.
I'm standing in your bedroom,
unbuttoning my shirt.
And now I'm taking off my pants.
And now...
I'm getting in your bed naked.
Mark...
we need to, um...
We should go get a drink,
um, and maybe talk.
Do you have some time?
Uh, I mean...
just something's always wrong
with you and me...
You don't want to have
a drink with me.
I'm not what you're looking for.
What are you talking about?
I slept with someone.
Couldn't hold out.
Once a man-whore,
always a man-whore, right?
Miranda, go home.
I'm almost done.
Go home. See your family.
You have to accept there are
days where you can't do it all.
- You have to delegate.
- I did.
And then you do
all the work anyway.
And you're still doing it.
You didn't have
better things to do today
than to ride herd
on that V.I.P. case?
There was a fish
in a man's penis.
There's always gonna be
a fish in a man's penis, chief.
You can say you movin' on
all you want,
but are you really?
If you don't slow down,
you might end up without
a family to go home to.
Good night, Miranda.
Now see,
you can't do that.
Do what?
Not look happy after sex.
It's bad for the ego.
I'm fine.
- Are we fine?
- Sure.
Not so convincing.
I shouldn't have
accused you of hovering.
It wasn't nice.
You were just trying
to be there for me.
But...
now I'm being available,
communicating
and getting naked
and doing all of your
favorite things.
Mm. Good things.
Then why are you
still staring at the ceiling?
I-I don't know.
I just... I...
That day...
You came out of the water...
I spent the scariest hour
of my life
trying to breathe for you.
I love you and I want you,
but I don't know what to...
You didn't swim.
You didn't swim,
and you know how to.
And I don't know if I can...
I don't know if I wanna...
keep trying to breathe for you.
I should go.
I'll go.
Too often,
the thing you want most
is the one thing
you can't have.
What acid-based finding
do you classically get
with significant vomiting?
Hypokalemic hypochloremic
metabolic alkalosis.
Unbelievable.
Did you pick a cake?
Uh... I like the red one.
The red velvet?
That's the girl?
Runny nose guy's big love.
I don't know
how we do this.
how we work together
and be friends
and act like it's all okay.
I, um...
There's a spot available
at Mercy West.
I called them.
You're gonna transfer
to Mercy West?
I have to.
Desire leaves us heartbroken...
It wears us out.
Desire can wreck your life.
I was gonna go get a drink.
You want to, uh...
head over to Joe's?
Yeah. Well, I'm kinda under it
with this test.
You know, um...
I, uh, took that test
once upon a time.
We could, um...
go back to my hotel.
I could quiz you.
Look, uh, this...
This isn't, uh...
You're not my girlfriend.
Okay?
What?
I mean, no offense.
Today was awesome.
It's just...
I'm... I'm really busy.
I have a lot of work to do.
I don't have time for...
No, of course.
Uh... study.
That's what you're here for,
right?
But as tough as wanting
something can be...
The people who suffer
the most...
are those who don't know
what they want.
Transcript: swsub.com - Sync: Benj!
~ www.seriessub.com ~