Previously  on "Grey's Anatomy"...
You're gonna transfer to Mercy West?
- I have to.
- Give me my husband back.
- Chief resident?
- The one 5th year resident
that rules all residents.
Your intern exams are in two weeks.
You need to spend every available
minute studying for them.
What happened
to our small ceremony?
What happened to
you and me at city hall?
There's no guarantee the surgery's
gonna bring back your memory.
- Is there a man in my house?
- I'm so sorry, Richard.
And I'm finally ready to have a baby,
and I can't.
We're losing her pulse.
She's coding!
We did everything we could.
A surgeon's education never ends.
Every patient, every symptom,
every operation...
is a test.
A chance for us to demonstrate
how much we know...
And how much more
we have to learn.
How do you treat pancreatic divisum?
Izzie?
Oh, Cristina.
If you're not gonna let us sleep,
you at least have to let me
put coffee in my cup.
- Okay, so go. No one's stopping you.
- I'm too tired to go.
- Pancreatic divisum.
- Dorsal duct sphincterotomy.
Not your turn, but correct.
You do me.
Can't believe O'Malley's missing this.
- How's he gonna be ready?
- You're kidding, right?
- We have Callie's cards but George has-
- George has Callie.
What's the most frequent cause
of diarrhea in hospitalized patients?
Is she coming to
this bachelorette thing tonight?
Rotavirus. Yes.
No, no, no. Uh, salmonella.
Diarrhea in hospitalized patients.
The most frequent cause of diarrhea
in hospitalized patients is C. diff.
Which can lead to toxic megacolon,
perforation, sepsis and death.
That's what killed Susan.
- Is she okay?
- Oh, she's fine.
- Dude, she's messed up.
- Of course she's messed up.
Susan was basically
her surrogate mother.
Yeah, her fake mom
was better than her real mom.
Is she going to the hospital first
or the funeral?
First to the hospital,
then to the funeral,
then to the test this afternoon.
- Has she even studied?
- Yeah, she studied. She's fine.
She just needs
to be left alone, okay? So...
what's inside the carotid sheath?
Izzie?
The internal carotid artery,
the internal jugular vein
and the vagus nerve.
Ah, that was too easy.
Let's find you a hard one.
Uh, what is this?
Uh, what is what?
Yeah.
That just came this morning.
You got a spot at Mercy West!
Why didn't you tell me?
Because it's pending the results
of the intern exam.
Oh, you know what this means,
don't you?
You, you got,
you got into Mercy West...
I haven't told the chief yet.
You'll tell him today.
He'll understand.
It's a smaller program,
fewer residents,
fewer distractions,
more surgeries.
And when I come home
and ask you how your day went,
you can actually tell me
because I won't already know.
- Hi.
Look, I...
I know this is a...
an impossible day for you.
So...
I'm just want to say one thing.
I brought a black suit, just in case.
Thank you.
But I think this is something
I need to do by myself.
If you need me, just...
let me know.
- Oh, Cristina.
- What is M.E.N. syndrome?
Don't answer that.
The minister needs to see a copy
of your vows before the wedding.
Multiple endocrine neoplasia. Yes.
Look, I know it's test day,
and I'm not supposed to be
talking about the wedding
on test day.
- But since tomorrow's our wedding day--
- You have five seconds. Go.
Bill Adams can't make it.
I have no best man.
Oh, no. Baby, I'm so sorry.
- And I need your vows by--
- Okay, time's up.
Test day.
What am I supposed
to tell the minister?
Test day.
They paged you guys, too?
- Well, I think they paged all of us.
- That can't be good.
Sure it can. He could be letting us
know I won the race for chief.
Not today, he isn't.
He's making his recommendation
to the board tomorrow
for chief of surgery
and chief resident.
Why were we all paged?
Oh, because search and rescue
found those lost
climbers who were up
on Mount Rainier.
- People, the climbers are on their way.
- Any specifics?
They found only 3 so far.
One's still missing.
They're reporting
severe dehydration
with traumatic head
and chest injuries.
Dr. Bailey, Dr. Torres,
you'll be my trauma team.
- Bad day not to have interns.
- What?
Today's the intern exam.
You'll all have to do your
own heavy lifting today.
And if you see an intern,
which you will,
because they can't help themselves,
turn them away
until after the exam.
The ambulances
are 5 minutes away.
It's time to do what we do best,
people. Let's roll.
What is a gerota's fascia?
Uh, the fascia surrounding the kidney.
Which is longer, the left...
- or the right renal vein?
- That's right. The left one.
- Looks and smarts-- Not bad.
- You think?
She's got my dad's nose, though.
Girl's gotta have a big personality
to pull off that nose.
What?
You-- You remember your dad?
No. I don't-- No.
- You just said--
- I know, but I...
I have no idea
where that came from.
That was a memory.
That's what it's like sometimes.
It doesn't always come back all at once.
It can happen in bits and pieces.
- Don't-- Don't get all--
- Dude, your memory's coming back.
How you feelin', Preston?
You ready?
I'm always ready for surgery.
I think he's talking
about the wedding.
Yeah, tomorrow's the big day.
And apart from the fact that
Cristina hasn't written her vows,
my best man just canceled,
- and it's still raining...
- He's not ready.
You're never ready.
I certainly wasn't.
But then... the minute I saw
Adele coming down that aisle...
Well... have you picked
your best man?
- Actually, chief, I--
- You can't be his best man.
- Why not?
- Because it's unethical.
It's a conflict of interest.
The man wants to be chief of surgery.
- Actually, Derek--
- Not that that's why you're asking.
- I was... going to ask you.
- Ask me what?
- Really?
- We have been through a lot this year.
And everybody else turned you down.
Oh, what do I have to do?
Well, traditionally the best man
plans the bachelor party.
- Drinks at Joe's after work?
- Yeah.
I knew you were
the man for the job.
Dale winick, 32.
B.P. 90 over 50, tachy to 110.
Severe frostbite,
but no obvious internal injuries.
Got it.
My god.
Yeah, those aren't gloves.
Please someone tell me
if they heard the others guys are okay.
They're right behind you.
We'll let you know.
Get him a tet-tox
and push a gram of cefazolin I.V.
And let's get some warm, circulating
water to start thawing his hands.
I'll get someone on it.
Callie.
We're supposed to be studying.
If Bailey finds out we're down--
We are studying.
How do you treat frostbite?
Rewarm, avoid early surgery unless
there's a deep infection
due to autoamputation.
See? Studying.
Okay, okay,
Mr. Meltzer, Mr. Meltzer,
I'm gonna need you
to save your breath, okay?
We're gonna give you
some pain meds.
You have several broken ribs,
which are compromising your breathing.
You understand?
- Did you see that?
- That is freaky.
I think that was a flail chest.
I've never seen one before.
Come on. Come on.
Why, oh, why does today
have to be test day?
Oh, I know.
Look... I bet you
if you talk to the chief,
he'll let you take the test later
with the funeral and everything.
I don't need to take the test later.
- Can I get a little help here?
- I can't feel my legs!
Sir, you have a spinal injury.
You need to stop fighting me
and stay calm, okay?
You're only making it worse.
Where we going?
- You guys are going to trauma 3.
- All right. Trauma 3.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
I got accepted at Mercy West.
Wow that's...
Are you gonna go?
Well, I kinda have to now, right?
What are you fools doing here?
In a few hours,
you people are taking a test
that will determine the course
of your entire medical careers
because the five interns
with the lowest test scores
will be cut from the program.
But are you studying for this test?
No, you're not.
Are you helping out in the E.R.?
You are most certainly not!
Are you getting the hell out of here
before I throw you out?
I think you are.
- Whoa, Dr. Shepherd.
- Aren't you supposed to be studying?
- Yeah, I just have a quick question.
- Yeah.
Could the craniotomy you performed
on Ava-- On Jane Doe-- Could--
- Could that have affected her memory?
- Uh, it's doubtful.
I was mostly working
in the speech center of her brain.
- But you never know. Why?
- I think she remembered something.
Can we test her to see
if anything's changed?
Yeah, you can run another W.M.S.R.
But we're gonna have to wait,
see if she remembers anything else.
- It's a good sign, though.
- Thanks.
- Nice work, Dr. Montgomery.
- Oh, thanks.
- I was just directing traffic.
- I was being sarcastic.
Oh, like brain surgery
is so impressive.
- It is, actually.
- Addison.
Yes? Oh, Joe, Walter.
What are you guys doing here?
Everything okay?
Yeah, we came to see you, actually.
- We need a consult.
- Don't tell me you're pregnant.
- Uh, no, but--
- Our birth mom is.
The potential birth mom.
She hasn't actually picked us yet.
You're adopting?
Well, we filed an application,
but we never thought we'd get picked.
You know, bar-owning gays
don't get picked very often.
I guess having a baby
is easier than we thought.
Yes, I guess so.
So I was hoping
you could take a look at her?
You know, kicking the tires,
checking underneath the hood?
Car metaphors? No.
I'd be happy to.
Just, uh, give me a call
and we'll set up an appointment.
Well, see, that's the thing, uh...
She lives in Portland,
and she's only gonna be
in Seattle for one day, so...
She's kind of here now.
Now, as in...
now.
- George, wait. Wait a minute.
- Yeah?
You don't have to do this.
You don't have to transfer
to Mercy West.
- Yeah, I do.
- No.
Just forget about you and me
for a second, OK?
What about Meredith?
What about Alex and Cristina?
Who's gonna hold us together
if you're not here?
You're the glue. You're George.
- I can't stay here. I can't...
- No one's making you go.
stay here
and see you every day...
and not...
I can't keep kissing you
in elevators.
I know. I know that.
I'm married.
I'm a married man.
- You busy?
- Cute. What are you doing here?
- Isn't the exam in like--
- I know, I know.
I just want to run
a quick neuro-psych test on you.
No. No! Go take your test.
I-I have a baby to feed.
- What the hell is wrong with you?
- Nothing.
You've been sitting in this bed
for weeks wishing
you could remember who you were
now suddenly you can.
I can't. It was something I said.
Well, you remember
your father's face.
Why are you acting like
it's no big deal,
- like it happens all the time?
- Alex, come on. I-I--
It-- That's not...
Unless it does happen all the time.
Tell me the truth.
Do you remember?
Do you know who you are?
- What is biloma?
- Cristina, I really don't have time.
A biloma is an intraperitoneal
bile fluid collection.
- Excellent.
- Okay? I'll be fine.
- George, I gotta go.
- Your dad.
Hey.
I was just on my way to--
No, I-I came here to tell you,
you're not wanted.
I don't want you at any funeral,
Meredith.
- Thatcher, why don't you come--
- She trusted you!
She came to you for help,
and you killed her.
You did. You killed my wife.
You took her from me.
Dad!
So I don't--
I don't want to see you.
I don't want to hear from you,
and I do not want you
anywhere near her funeral.
- Do you understand me?
- Dad, dad, come on.
This-- Lexie's waiting in the car.
We have to go, dad.
She was everything to me,
all I had.
She was all I had.
I can sit here all day.
I'll miss my test,
but I will sit here all day.
I don't-- I...
It happened a few days ago,
and I-I just...
I just woke up, and...
- it was all there again.
- And you didn't tell me?
Becau-- Because there's...
There's nothing to tell.
Why don't I believe that?
I was a pregnant woman,
in a lousy marriage,
to the nicest guy
anyone's ever met.
End of story.
Who-- who is he?
What does he do?
Wh-where--
Where did you meet him?
College.
We got married the year
after we graduated.
He...
I wanted--
I wanted to move to New York,
and he wanted to live
on the side of a mountain
and take over his dad's shop.
And he's a woodworker.
He makes beautiful furniture.
It's-- It's-- It's...
quiet, and he's quiet and...
- I was going out of my mind.
- So you just...
- took off?
- No, I...
No, I need-- I need-- I need--
I needed to think
and to be around other people.
So I came to Seattle, and I...
Thought I'd see the sights,
ride the ferry.
- Have you even called him?
- No.
- Why not?
- I left him, Alex.
So? He's your husband.
You should call him.
You want me to call him?
I mean, what's his name?
What's your name?
I'm not telling you that.
- We've got everything taken care of.
- You don't have to worry about a thing.
I've got number 2 pencils
and bottled water.
Oh, and-- And powerbars.
And you know the material.
You're gonna get a high score--
Not as high as mine--
But everything's gonna be fine.
What are you guys
all standing around for?
Don't we have a test to--
What happened?
You people need to head upstairs.
Dr. Grey will join you in a minute.
You're not to blame for Susan Grey's
death, and you know it,
and your father knows it, too.
He's just...
Well, he's never been
the best communicator,
and he just lost his wife.
Stop acting
like my surrogate father.
- Meredith, I've...
- Just Because you slept with my mother,
that does not make you my father.
Follow my finger. Up.
Okay. Good.
Let me know
if you can feel this, okay?
Yeah, I'm not enjoying that.
Good. That's a good sign.
It means I'm not paralyzed?
Well, the M.R.I. will show us
the full extent of the injuries.
But, uh...
can we ask you
what happened up there?
It was my fault.
- Dale--
- It wasn't your fault.
60 ways to get up Mount Rainier,
and I had to pick Liberty Ridge.
It wasn't the route.
It was the storm.
On a clear day,
you don't think about storms.
A minute later, the wind's pasting you
to the side of the mountain,
and you can't see your hand
in front of your face.
Is that why you fell,
because of the storm?
All I know is I felt the rope tug,
and...
- I was in midair.
- We all were.
We were tied together.
Must have been a 100-foot drop.
And when we came to,
Lonnie wasn't moving.
Lonnie?
He's your friend who's still missing?
Well, this Lonnie,
is that why he didn't make it back,
because he was hurt?
Because he was dead.
I'm sorry.
We had to leave him.
We had to get to the other side of
the mountain, or we'd be dead, too.
We had no choice.
You always have a choice.
You never leave a man behind.
Please take your seats,
doctors,
and put all study materials away.
Okay, if you don't know the answer,
choose "B." It's always "B."
And write your name in the upper
right-hand corner of your answer sheets.
You may open your test booklets...
Now.
W-we don't have to be here
if you're uncomfortable.
Oh, no, it's fine.
Unless you're uncomfortable.
- Actually, uh, I-I--
- He's fine.
So, Rina, how are you feeling?
Any problems?
Just the fact that I'm huge,
and I have, like, the worst heartburn
I've ever had in my life.
I can prescribe an antacid for that.
The first thing we're gonna do
is take a look at the baby.
This might be a little cold.
This baby deserves parents
who are gonna make it
their whole world, you know?
You know we're gay, right?
I figured, with you both
being boys and everything.
The other couple I'm considering,
they're, like, oh, 40.
She's been trying
to get pregnant for ten years.
It's so sad.
There's the heartbeat.
Oh, my god.
There's, like,
a person inside of me.
Actually... there are two people.
Twins.
- Oh, my god.
Oh, my god.
I think I'm gonna pass out.
Doctors, we are halfway
through our allotted time.
You only have 60 minutes left
to complete the exam.
She didn't write anything on the test.
She didn't answer a single question.
She just sat there.
Wait, George, just--
Just give her a second.
I've got an extensive
antero-lateral flail chest.
He'll need surgical stabilization.
Dr. Torres, if you're available--
She's not.
My guy has bone fragments
in his spinal cord,
internal fixation.
Dr. Torres is gonna scrub in
with me.
Uh, we have more than one
orthopedic surgeon in this hospital.
And you'll need 'em,
because Dr. Torres and I are looking
at possible multiple amputations.
Guys, I can be there for all of you.
We just have to figure it out.
Dr. Burke asked first.
- Well, I mean, with all due respect--
- okay, you all want Torres. Fine.
Rock, paper, scissors.
One, two, three.
All rocks. Very typical.
Ready?
And...
Rock smashes scissors.
- See you in the O.R.
- Best two out of three.
Dr. Burke!
What?
I just wanted to know
how it feels...
to not have to spend
the next 24 hours
wondering if Richard picked you
to be chief resident.
How's it feel to be the chosen one?
Feels just fine.
How'd it go?
Meredith.
Don't worry. I've got it.
It's not like
she actually flunked.
She-- She just
didn't write anything.
It's kinda like
she actually flunked.
One guy two years ago,
he was on call three nights
before his test.
He slept through the whole thing.
He had to repeat his intern year.
She can't repeat her intern year.
It's pathetic.
We have to do something.
Cristina.
What? Okay, I don't know.
Mredith and I don't fail things.
This is not in my book.
It's Bailey. We gotta go.
We gotta go.
- We can't just leave her here.
- You got a better idea?
Okay, it's showtime, people.
Yang,
you're scrubbing in with Dr. Burke.
Karev, you're with Dr. Montgomery.
Stevens, find Dr. Sloan.
- You paged me, too.
- Mercy West.
Callie told you.
You're in the best surgical program
in the country,
the toughest, most competitive
most respected.
You want to leave
this for Mercy West?
- Mercy west--
- Is not Seattle Grace.
Are you trying to...
After all the work
that we've put into you,
are you trying to throw
your career away?
I'm trying to...
do what's best for me right now.
I've had some personal issues.
I-I don't know what your personal
problems are, and I don't care.
I do care about your career,
so let me make myself clear.
This is a mistake.
It's like we're on a train
that's going 200 miles an hour,
and it would just be
so nice to get off,
and just...
stand on the platform
just for a minute.
Looks like I'm off the train.
Our parents died.
When a parent dies,
it doesn't make any sense.
So you make...
a lot of really terrible decisions...
that you're gonna end up having
to live with for a long time.
You should go.
You are still on the train.
It's okay.
You have to go.
Go.
Go. Go, go.
Addison.
Adele.
What are you doing here?
What happened?
A fender bender. I'm fine.
I told the E.R. resident I'm fine,
but...
All right, I'm gonna page Richard.
I'll let him know you're here.
Oh, you will do no such thing,
Addison.
Richard cannot know I'm here.
We're separated.
My life is none of his business.
I'm serious.
Uh, all right. Well...
let's get you checked out.
Do you have any, um,
any pain, any...
anything?
Well...
there's one thing
I should probably mention.
I'm pregnant.
The baby looks fine on the ultrasound
but you are spotting a little.
It's nothing severe,
but I would like to hold you
overnight for observation.
Overnight? Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
- But--
- For just a couple of hours at least.
Look, it could be nothing.
But a pregnancy at your age is--
Terrifying? Embarrassing?
I was going to say a miracle.
I don't know. I resigned myself
to the fact a long time ago
that I would never have kids,
and...
here I am, 52,
about to be divorced and...
pregnant.
May I ask who... the father is?
You may ask.
Look, all I'm saying...
is that if Richard finds out that
you're walking around this hospital
carrying another man's baby...
Richard is not going to find out
because neither one of us
are going to tell him.
- Chief.
- Addison.
I just heard the news.
You-- You heard?
Who told you?
What-- What did you hear?
That Joe and Walter are adopting.
Is the birth mom here?
I'd love to put in a good word.
Chief, you don't want to go in there.
It's a young girl...
in the stirrups, you know,
her equipment exposed, right?
You don't want to see that.
No, I-I don't want to see that.
Are you going to give me
an inspirational speech, too?
I can't talk.
I have a patient to prep.
This isn't about you and me.
This is about Meredith.
- What are we gonna do?
- There's nothing to do.
What?
I'm not even gonna be
here in a week, so...
So your transferring
to another hospital
means we're not gonna be
friends anymore?
Why are you doing this, George?
Didn't you hear a word
of what Bailey said?
What were we supposed to do,
carry him down the mountain?
He was our friend,
and we left him there.
If we hadn't, we'd be dead, too.
You know that.
Dale was right.
You don't--
You don't do that.
You don't...
climb all the way up there together
just to leave a man behind.
I am being stalked by pregnant women.
You're an obstetrician.
And barren.
You know, apparently as a healthy,
successful woman in her 30s,
I don't deserve to have a baby.
Maybe I'd have a fighting chance
if were gay,
or a teenager
or a member of the A.A.R.P.
Oh, that sucks.
It really...
No, no, not you, too.
Oh, no, no, I'm not. I'm just--
I'm thinking about it.
That's all.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't even know.
It's just that with George...
- going to Mercy West next year...
- He is?
Yeah, they have a spot for him,
and we need a fresh start.
We need to get away
from all this crap.
It might be a good time.
It's a great time.
Don't let me and my fossilized eggs
discourage you.
Are we gonna be friends still
if I get pregnant?
Absolutely not.
- Hi, chief.
- O'Malley.
Finally coming to see me
about that letter from Mercy West?
No, sir.
I'm here about Meredith.
I have to say, I don't get it.
Why would anybody
waste their time freezing
and climbing up
the side of a glacier?
It's a way to test yourself, you know,
your strength and endurance.
You put yourself through
a situation like that,
and you know exactly
who you are,
what you made of.
Have you done it before,
Dr. Burke?
No. You?
I used to, all the time,
in college.
- Really?
Yeah, it's, intense.
I mean, it's painful and hellish,
and you think your lungs
are shredding, but...
Man, when you get to the top,
there is nothing like it.
Makes the whole climb worth it.
How's it going?
Worse than I thought.
There's nothing here.
We're gonna amputate both?
You can't amputate
both of his hands.
I-Isn't the left hand less damaged?
I don't want to take
the man's hands, Dr. Stevens.
Once the infection gets that deep,
the only way to save his life
is to make the cut.
The patient's laminotomy happens
at what level, Dr. O'malley?
The level of maximal neural
compressions between
the pedicles
of the fractured vertebrae.
Very good.
You must have aced
your exam today.
I don't know about aced.
How did Meredith do?
Yeah, she was kinda...
Don't worry, though.
I talked to the chief.
About what?
She didn't tell you?
All right, here's the thing--
The Seattle police department's
been on this for weeks.
They've been in contact with
missing persons from all 50 states...
Canada, the FBI--
You know how many people
are trying to find you?
- Yeah, yes.
- That's right. You do know.
You know exactly
how many relatives you have.
You know if your parents
are dead or alive.
You know if you've got a sister
somewhere who cries every day because
- she has no idea what happened to you.
- Stop it!
What do you think
it's like for your husband?
He didn't come looking for me, okay?
He obviously
doesn't want to find me.
- Besides,it's my life.
- No, not just yours.
What about your daughter?
I'm sorry,
but I'm not gonna lie for you.
If you're not gonna tell anybody,
I will.
What are you gonna say?
You don't know my real name.
You don't know anything about me.
It'll be my word against yours.
You're right. I have absolutely
no idea who you are.
- You paged me?
- Yeah.
I think I figured out
a way to help Meredith.
But I've got shepherd's post-op,
and...
I can't do it without your help.
And I won't leave
the program without...
knowing that she's still in it.
You're not leaving the program.
Listen... we made a mistake.
We had sex.
But that's all it was.
I think we both wanted it
to mean something because...
you didn't want to have to feel like
that guy that cheats on his wife,
I didn't want to have
to feel like that girl
who put you in that position
in the first place.
But the truth is...
It didn't mean anything.
I know you think
I have feelings for you,
but I don't.
So you can stay.
You're not leaving the program.
Nice work today Torres...
Three surgeries at the same time.
I performed four osteosyntheses,
amputated two hands
and stabilized
one spine in two hours.
Impressive.
Looks like Bailey's not
a shoo-in for chief resident after all.
Uh, you're in the running
for chief resident, too?
Why wouldn't I be?
No. Uh, it makes sense.
I just... I hadn't thought about it.
That's all.
I'm good at what I do, Bailey.
I'm focused,
I'm disciplined, I'm--
I'm more than qualified
to be chief resident.
Look, we all know
that you're the chief's favorite,
but that doesn't mean
I can't take a shot.
Here she is.
Thank you, Stevens.
You can go now.
We'll be waiting right outside.
- You don't have to.
- Shut up.
If you called me here
to lecture me--
There's a copy of
the intern's exam on the table,
some number 2 pencils,
a bottle of water
and a sandwich if you get hungry.
I'll send a proctor in,
and I'll come back
in a few hours and check on you.
You are not my father.
I know that.
I know.
Well, at least test day
is almost over.
Speak for yourself.
I'm getting married tomorrow.
This is what you invited me to?
This is your big bachelor party?
It was last-minute.
I needed some warm bodies.
Which would explain
why I'm here.
Why am I the only girl,
by the way?
What am I, the entertainment?
I am not stripping.
That's okay.
We've seen it already.
- True.
- I haven't.
Yeah, well, why don't I buy you
a drink instead?
First round's on me.
I'll give you a hand with those.
Cristina write her vows?
I guess I'll find out tomorrow.
How's Meredith doing?
I have no idea.
Shouldn't be this difficult,
should it?
Probably not.
Then again...
when I see Cristina walking down
that aisle tomorrow...
It'll all be worth it?
So how was L.A.?
L.A. was... different.
Look, Mark...
Things don't have to be
awkward between us.
We tried.
We tried, and we did our best
and just because we failed
as a couple, it doesn't mean--
I know.
So we're still friends?
With benefits?
Don't push it.
Thanks, Joe.
So hey, how'd it go with Rina?
Oh, well... Walter took her
to the bus station,
and I'm pretty sure he was wishing
it was me he was dropping off.
That bad, huh?
If I can't even make it
through an ultrasound
without breathing
into a paper bag,
how am I gonna handle a kid?
Forget about twins.
You two are gonna make
great parents, okay?
Whenever that happens.
You... ever think
about having kids?
All the time.
Adele?
Oh, come on.
I know you saw me.
Now this is just silly.
You don't have to hide.
I've moved on.
I'm dating now.
Okay, I'm not actually dating,
but I intend to...
at some point.
What the hell am I supposed to do
about the stupid vows?
You still haven't written anything?
- Well, it's stupid crap.
- No, it isn't.
Well, what am I supposed to say?
I swear to love and cherish you every
moment of every day of my life?
I mean, that's not real.
That's not how it works, right?
It does, at first...
- but then it...
- It passes.
No, it doesn't.
You guys are just used to it.
That's all. You already have it.
You have that thing
everybody else wants.
You can take it for granted.
But let me tell you,
if you didn't, if you couldn't...
be with the person
that you love,
I guarantee that...
hearing him promise
to love you and...
honor you and cherish you,
no matter what, it would be
pretty much all you could think about.
Wait, can you say that again,
just slowly?
You're talking about Denny,
right?
Yeah.
Hi.
Can I buy you a drink?
Wow, you're forward.
Bad day.
I get to be forward today.
Yeah, I had a bad day, too.
So what do you say, one drink?
I'm with some friends.
It's a bachelor party. So...
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna say no.
That's too bad.
Maybe you're right.
Rebecca Pope.
That's my name.
Adele, come on.
Now you've got me
in this ladies' room.
The least you could do is an--
Oh, my god. Adele.
- What are you doing here?
- Sweetie, get Rina some water.
I thought you guys were
going to the bus station.
- We were.
- It's this heartburn.
It's like it's--
It's ripping through...
Call an ambulance.
Tucker, uh, since he's awake,
can you put him on?
Let me call you back.
Nicole, what have you got?
We got the fourth climber.
Pressure's 70s, last pulse 135.
Severely hypothermic.
Started two large-bore I.V.S.
Oh, and, uh, obvious head trauma.
Is that an ax in his head?
What the hell happened up
on that mountain?
Let's go!
Somebody help me!
Please!
Somebody help!
Please, somebody help me!
Transcript: swsub.com - Sync: Benj!
~ www.seriessub.com ~