Previously, on Grey's Anatomy
You and Burke, are you OK ?
We're existing in total silence.
That hand is worth two millions dollars.
I want it fixed.
Mark and I--it wasn't
a one-night stand.
I was in love with him.
At least, I thought it was.
your sister molly's
just been admitted
for an emergency c-section.
Molly's not my sister.
She is. You have the same father.
Why didn't you stay
and fight for us ?
I did. I-I tried.
Why didn't you try harder ?
You are officially
off my service.
But for what it's worth,
I think you're gonna miss me.
(Cristina)
Harold O'Malley, 63,
diagnosed with esophageal cancer
and severe aortic regurge.
You think I want to die
and leave my boy in charge ?
You are not gonna die.
Www. 1000Fr. Com present
capture:frm@fadeout
sync:frm@lepetitprince
Good morning.
Are you watching me sleep ?
Maybe.
Are you
some kind of weirdo
who watches women sleep ?
Maybe.
Izzie.
What ?
I just dropped $8.7 million
on the floor.
And ?
I shouldn't be able to drop
$8.7 million on the floor.
You need to deposit
that check.
George. . .
Your father's surgery
is tomorrow.
Any chance you're misplacing
your anxiety
on me and my check ?
No, there is no chance.
That check ruins my morning
every morning.
It belongs in the bank.
Would you just please--
as a favor to me--
Would you just. . .
put it in the bank ?
Please.
Mm. No.
But. . . If you're nice to me
for the next seven minutes,
I will
give you a ride to work.
You don't deserve
$8.7 million !
Mm. So true.
So true.
What's Burke doing ?
I don't know.
She doesn't know.
He just had surgery
yesterday,
and you don't know
how he's doing ?
They're not speaking.
I thought they made up.
They did, sort of.
But she's still
not speaking to him ?
He's not speaking to me.
They're not speaking
to each other.
Okay.
Did you ask Derek
about Burke's hand ?
I don't want to get
in the middle of it.
Derek and I are happy.
Could we just keep it
that way for while ?
You know, u could always
swallow your pride
and just ask him yourself.
Her gut's not big enough
for that.
Oh, Alex,
you hurt me.
Oh, georgie.
(harold) Quiet down !
Everyone, quiet down !
Good morning, everybody.
Good morning.
Uh, who's presenting ?
Oh, can Georgie do it ?
He's real good.
Come on, Georgie. Yeah !
Come on.
Um. . . Harold O'Malley, 63,
status--
post-aortic valve replacement.
Morning chest x-ray showed
no atelectasis
after aggressive C.P.T.
for the last two days.
Um, scheduled for
a transhiatal esophagectomy
tomorrow morning at 9:00.
That's it.
Um, for the next few minutes,
I think it would be best
if the extended family could
wait out in the waiting area.
Just a few minutes, guys,
and then you can come back.
How are you feeling,
Mr. O'Malley ?
He's feeling great.
"better than ever, "
he said.
Which is why we had everybody
come out today,
because we figured
after today,
he maybe won't be feeling
so great for a while.
Uh, after the surgery,
uh, then when do we start
chemo and stuff ?
That protocol depends on
what we find
when we open you up, Harold.
What do you mean,
what you find ?
Uh, Grey.
There's only so much
they can tell
from labs and scans,
so they really need to get
a good look inside
to see if the cancer
has spread.
If it's spread, that changes
how much chemo he needs ?
That changes a lot
of things.
Like what ?
I'll let the oncologist
explain that to you
later today, Harold.
And Dr. Grey will be
taking you through
a final battery of
preoperative tests before we go.
So, um--
so it would be best
if the party went home.
Mm.
Dr. Shepherd.
Uh, Dr. Burke's hand--
has he had any tremors ?
That's confidential.
Uh, but I'm--I'm
one of his doctors.
You're also his girlfriend.
Ask him yourself.
Good morning, everyone.
Who's presenting ? Good morning.
Preston Burke, post-op day one
from I and d
of a compressive hematoma
to the brachial exus.
He is afebrile, and vital signs
were stable overnight.
Incisions are clean
with no signs of infection.
Last morphine was given
at 2:00 this morning.
Ask about the hand.
You ask.
No, it's just one question.
(whispers) Be a friend.
Dr. Yang. . .
Something you want to share
with the rest of us ?
No, ma'am. Sorry.
Look good, Preston.
Take it easy on the nurses.
I'll do my best.
O'malley.
Your father's surgery
is today ?
Tomorrow.
(woman) You okay, honey ?
Yeah.
Can you just help me. . .
Mm-hmm.
Scoliosis ?
Looks like
a birth defect.
Looks like hell.
What are you all staring at ?
Really, if you're expecting me
to be the brave and heartwarming
differently-disabled girl,
that isn't gonna happen,
so go ahead and do your thing.
Yeah.
(Miranda) Okay. Stevens.
Heather douglas, 17,
past medical history
of vater syndrome.
Which is ?
Vater syndrome
is a genetic condition
that affects the vertebrae,
anus, trachea,
esophagus
and renal system.
Wow. Give this girl a medal.
She memorized the whole acronym.
Which I assure you
is a hell of a lot easier
than living with it.
Stevens.
Right. Um, heather is--
is in today for a lithotripsy
to remove kidney stones
and a thoracoplasty
to alleviate pressure
on her lungs.
Can I ask--
I-I know I'm just supposed to
be here to remove a few ribs,
but I'm wondering if you've ever
tried anything more radical
to treat the spinal curvature ?
Let's se
if by "more radical, "
you mean having a steel rod
inserted into my spine,
then, yeah, we've tried.
The rod just bent.
Removing the kidney stones
may seem minor,
but it will really improve
your quality of life.
Really ? So this surgery
is gonna get me laid ?
Heather, stop it.
Mom, I'm sorry,
but she's talking about
improving my quality of life,
and I don't think doctors
should make promises
they can't keep.
Laura Grey-thompson,
born four days ago
with jejunal atresia.
Corrected surgically.
Uh, post-op course--
oh, I'm--I'm sorry.
Am I interrupting ?
Her mom and grandma
ha-have the flu,
and they asked me
to get an update.
Oh, she's doing
very well, mr. Grey.
We'll be out of here
in just a minute.
Dr. Grey,
you were saying ?
Um. . .
Excuse me, uh. . .
I'll just come back
a little later.
Grey ?
Um. . .
Uh, laura Grey-thompson, um,
had some dilation of the bowels
on x-ray this morning.
We need to do a barium enema
to make sure there's
no intestinal stricture.
Grey's Anatomy S03E11
Dr. Grey, I'd like you to stick
with Mr. O'Malley this week.
Yang, pit. Karev, Sloan.
Stevens, prep heather douglas
for surgery.
O'malley.
Yes.
You're taking the rest
of this week off ?
Yes, ma'am.
May as well take today, too,
spend some time
with your family.
Thank you.
Uh, dr. Bailey, as things
progress with my dad uh. . .
You know, sometimes we--
with families--
we coddle them,
sugarcoat things.
It would help me
if you were straight with me
as things progress.
Okay.
Thank you.
Uh, dr. Bailey.
D-Dr. Bailey.
I know that I'm supposed
to prep her only,
but any chance I can
scrub in on Heather Douglas ?
I mean, a vater patient isn't
something you see very often.
No.
But I'm ready.
I am ready.
Your psychiatrist has not
given you an all clear.
He's. . . I have done everything
he has asked me to do,
everything,
except deposit
my inheritance check, which--
wait, you have not deposited
a nearly $9-million check yet ?
It--it's. . .
Being unreasonable.
That check has nothing to do
with any--
what's unreasonable
is that you're losing
thousands of dollars day
in interest.
That's unreasonable.
You clearly
are not reasonable yet,
which, I think,
is the point your psychiatrist
is trying to make.
Hey, I need c. B. C.
And a chem-7 on harold O'Malley.
I need these labs asap.
Everybody needs everything
"asap. "
Oh, yes.
And all throughout
this hospital,
people are dying while you
give me crap about "asap. "
Hey, are you okay ?
Why wouldn't I be ?
Your father ?
Freezing up on rounds--
oh, god.
That was mortifying.
Thank you. Thanks.
Oh, okay.
It wasn't mortifying ?
I just wish the baby
would get well and go home
and Thatcher
would go with her.
Is that wrong ?
Oh, wrong would be, uh,
if you wished
the baby wouldn't get well.
Okay, good. Thanks.
You know, if you want
to thank me,
um, you could ask Derek
if Burke has had any tremors.
Talk to him.
No.
'Cause then he wins.
Wins what ?
Forget it.
Do you have a father ?
I have a stepfather.
He's nice.
I see him for yom kippur.
Karev, what did I tell you
about how I like my charts ?
I like to round on pre-op
before post-op.
Do you like wasting my time ?
Is it fun for you ?
No, sir.
Then get it right.
You like abusing the interns ?
Is it fun for you ?
Yes, it is,
and in case you've forgotten,
you don't get the high horse
this week, Addison.
Not this week.
He's an ass.
You know Shepherd
pretty well, yeah ?
Lots of hair,
too many women,
likes elevators
and long walks on the beach.
So, um, what's the best way
to get him to do something ?
What kind of something ?
A consult that
the patient hasn't requested
but that the friendly
neighborhood ortho resident
thinks is worth pursuing.
Shepherd thinks he's busier
and maybe a little bit more
important than everyone else.
Standard neurosurgeon
breed.
Exactly.
Okay, so ?
So he'll say no
until you stare him down.
"Stare him down" ?
Stare him down.
You're way too hot
to be a doctor.
Okay.
I mean, aren't people
who look like you
supposed to be dumb ?
I'm just saying, you're not
gonna be in my surgery, are you ?
'Cause I'm a little
too young to die.
I will not be in
on your surgery.
See ? I knew it.
You're not even a doctor.
I am a doctor.
It's just that when my,
uh, fiancee dropped dead
not too long ago,
I went a little nuts,
and, uh, no surgeries
for me for a while.
Well, so much for my theory
that life doesn't suck
for pretty people.
I'm sorry
I was such a bitch to you.
Well. . . You're in pain.
Sometimes I'm a bitch
for no good reason at all.
Oh, um. . .
Dr. Shepherd.
Yes.
I am so sorry
to bother you.
I know you're very, very busy,
but there's a girl here.
She'17 years old with severe
scoliosis from vater syndrome.
She's here for thoracoplasty
because her ribs are pressing
against her lungs, and she's
already had two spinal fusions
and a segmental
spinal instrumentation
that didn't work.
She's bent over at 9degrees,
which clearly sucks.
"Clearly sucks, " is that
your professional assessment ?
My professional assessment
is that we can help her.
My day is impossible.
I'll come by for a consult
in the morning.
I'm a good starer.
Doctors,
could I get a word ?
Oh, how are you feeling,
harold ?
Feelin' great.
Feelin' fine.
It's just that
the oncologist. . .
He said that, uh,
if the cancer
is in other organs,
he said that maybe you wouldn't
proceed with the surgery.
That's right, harold.
If the cancer's spread
to your other organs,
it would compromise your ability
to recover from the surgery.
So if you close me up
and then send me home,
I get, what,
a couple of weeks to live ?
You'd have. . .
Weeks or months, yes.
No. No, you gotta take
the tumor out,
'cause I can survive this.
I know I can.
O'malleys, we're fighters.
Mr. O'malley,
it--it's just not
a good idea to--
you know, my wife. . .
We've been married
40 years.
I make her crazy,
but. . . 40 years.
She needs me.
My family needs me.
I can't let you close me up
and then tell them
that there's nothing
that can be done
when I know I can fight it.
So I. . . I'm asking
for your word.
I want you to take
the tumor out.
Mr O'Malley
My job is to do the best I can
for you medically.
After--
well, closing me up
and sending me home to die
isn't best for me,
not medically
or any other way.
Please. . .
Take the tumor out.
All right.
All right ?
Thanks.
This falls under
confidentiality ?
If you ask if you can tell this to his son, the response is no.
You're watching me
sleep again ?
You're cute when you sleep.
What can I say ?
Yeah, but don't you sleep ?
Why are you always up
before the alarm ?
(yawns) I'm a light sleeper.
It's no big deal
so something woke you up.
It's no big deal.
It's just that. . .
You snore a little.
What ? I do not.
Yes, you do.
I-I love it.
I find it charming
that such a big noise
can come from
such a little person.
Do you know
what's not charming ?
What ?
Your morning breath.
I'm sorry. What ?
I'm just saying,
seeing how you're always up
before me,
you might consider
brushing your teeth.
I don't--
okay, this is me
brushing my teeth.
Thank you.
Surgery's today ?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Yeah. I-I have
a really good feeling.
Yeah ?
Yeah.
I didn't even bake anything
for you.
Thank you.
Aha. Bone dry Cappuccino.
At least something's dry
around here.
Does it ever stop raining
in this hellhole ?
Not really.
Great. Good to know.
What the hell is this, Karev,
vanilla ?
Are you trying to poison me
or are you just trying to make my day a little worse
Mark.
Coffee cart must have
screwed up.
You know,
if you can't handle coffee, you can't handle plastics.
Maybe you oughta head back
to the gynie squad
where life was all squishy
and pink.
Squishy and pink
though it may be,
I have an amazing surgery
today, Karev, if you want in.
Yeah.
(olivia) Good morning,
dr. Burke.
Yes, it is.
Beautiful morning.
I love watching the rain.
Feeling good ?
Not too much pain ?
Feeling great.
And. . . Your hand--
your right hand--
feelin' good today ?
I'm sorry, olivia,
you're just--
you're gonna have to tell
dr. Yang
that I'm not ready
to give her that information.
Right.
Okay, then. Sorry.
(whispers) George,
ask him--
uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Ask him--
you know Cristina's
stalking your room ?
I do.
Your father ?
Yeah. Um. . . The surgery
my dad's having. . .
Has a 50% morbidity rate.
Oh, O'Malley. . .
That statistic,
it means 50% of the people
who undergo the surgery
survive.
If you're gonna hang
your hat on statistics,
then you have to look at them
from both sides.
(Derek) Heather, I've looked
at your case history,
and I know you've been through
a lot of very painful
and very unsuccessful
surgeries,
but if you're up for it, I think
I could significantly help
with the spinal curvature.
By "help, "
you mean what, exactly ?
I mean, I think I can get you
standing up straight.
Are you messing with me ?
'Cause it's not nice
to mock crippled kids.
You see this--
this curved part here ?
I'd remove it.
You--you want to remove
a portion
of my daughter's spine ?
Mm-hmm. And I would replace it
with a titanium mesh cage
that would fill in the space
between the vertebra.
I've seen case studies. There
have been quite a few successes.
And--and the ones that aren't successful
they result in paralysis
or death.
But dr. Shepherd
is the best there is.
She's 17.
Mom, I know you still think
death is the worst thing
that can happen
to a person.
Death is not
the worst thing.
I'm in.
They're gonna cut out
a piece of her spine--
heather douglas.
Doctors Shepherd
and Torres, they're--
they're gonna straighten
her spine.
And ?
And. . . It's
a once-in-a-lifetime surgery.
Please.
She's my patient.
I've gotten to know her.
I would really like
to scrub in.
Did you deposit the check ?
It's my money.
I should get to do
what I want with it.
Uh, you get a 5% return
on 6-month cd ?
In the time we've been
standing here,
you could've
just made $400.
Dr. Bailey.
It's not reasonable,
Stevens.
Dad, it's you to discard.
I'm sorry about
running over bucky.
What ?
Your dog.
That happy dog bucky.
When you were a kid,
I ran over him,
and I told you he ran away.
I'm sorry about that.
You ran over my dog
on purpose ?
Of course not. He was chasing
after the truck like always
and he got caught up
under the tire.
You were so sensitive.
You were such a soft kid,
I couldn't bear to tell ya.
I wasn't soft.
I mean it good, georgie.
You know, you were kind
and you loved animals.
You were always looking
to help people.
And I couldn't face you
and tell you
that I killed your dog
so I told you a lie.
I'm saying I'm sorry.
Okay.
You're a good kid, georgie.
Always been
such a good kid.
I want to tell you--
dad, stop acting like
you're dying.
You're not dying, okay ?
I want to tell you
that I think you're crazy
if you let that Callie
get away.
Dad, please !
No, she gets you.
She gets you in a way
that your family never has.
I'm sorry about that,
that you grew up feeling
so different all the time.
That's another thing
I'm sorry about.
Dad, stop it.
Stop apologizing,
stop saying good-bye.
You can't. . .
That's no way
to go into surgery.
I'm gonna die someday,
georgie.
We're all gonna die,
and lying here in this bed
gives me time to think
about all the things
I haven't said is all. Okay.
Well, just discard.
Anything you want
to say to me ?
Dad !
All right.
I'm discarding.
Dog murderer
Tell me what I want to hear.
If I die, you'll kill me.
He's a quick study.
Meredith.
Hello.
I'm. . .
Uh, how are you ?
Good. Uh, busy with work.
We have a patient.
Hello.
Hi.
Uh, all right, then.
Oh, I'm so--
uh, nice seeing you.
Okay.
That's your ex-boyfriend.
No, that's my ex-father.
You see, Grey ?
Good exposure
to the esopheal hiatus.
Yes, sir.
Now we will inspect
and palpate
the abdominal cavity.
Oh. . .
Those are the mets,
right ?
Throughout the stomach,
the celiac lymph nodes,
the liver.
It's everywhere.
So that's it ?
We're closing him back up ?
No.
We will proceed.
But I thought--
the patient asked us
to proceed.
What does that mean exactly ?
This man asked
for a chance to fight.
What it means is. . .
He's gonna have to fight
like hell.
But he can recover ?
There's a chance ?
There's a chance.
Dr. Grey, the request
from the patient. . .
It was private.
Yes.
Okay.
Preston.
Oh, Addison.
How you feeling ?
Better.
Looking forward
to going home.
Well, I'm sure dr. Yang
is looking forward
to having you back there
as well.
Uh, maybe.
I wouldn't know.
Why wouldn't you know ?
What. . .
Is. . .
Is that over ?
No, it's not over.
It's just. . . Silent.
Si--oh, yeah, yes.
I heard something about this.
Um, one of the nurses
was talking.
I just thought it was gossip.
It's not.
So you're not talking to her.
Why not ?
Did you ever play
say "uncle" ?
Say "uncle" ?
Someone bends your arm
behind your back
harder and harder
until you say "uncle. "
And then what happens ?
Then they have all the power.
I see.
So you
are not saying "uncle. "
Yes.
And neither is she.
It seems that way.
That's pathetic.
Well, you may be right.
I am right.
If you did something wrong,
then you apologize.
Well, I didn't do
anything wrong.
Did she ?
She doesn't seem
to think so.
That's pathetic.
Hey.
You're all alone.
Where's your family ?
Eating. They like to eat.
Mm. You're pacing.
Yeah.
It's just, he's been
in surgery for a while.
That's good. It means
they're being thorough.
Or it means
there are complications.
Somebody would've told you
if there were complications.
Right.
It's okay to be scared.
I'm not scared.
I'm just sayin',
if you are. . .
I'm not scared.
You can talk to me.
You're sure about that ?
Okay, now I'm scared of you.
Damn it.
I was staring you down.
Staring me down ?
Yeah, it worked on Shepherd.
Seriously ?
Wait, wait.
Let me try it again.
No, it's not. . .
No ?
I'm still scared.
Hold on.
I'll be right back.
Uh, you should
prepare yourself,
because this is
a much more extensive surgery
than the heart valve.
There's probably still
a tube in his throat
helping him breathe,
and half his stomach
was cut out
and part of his esophagus,
so there's gonna be a big scar.
Okay.
Just. . . Be prepared.
Welcome back, sweetheart.
Dad looks like something
out of the butcher shop.
That's a cool scar.
You need to breathe.
He's my dad.
I know.
Oh, you have got
to be kidding me.
Where is George ?
He spent the night
at the hospital.
And you slept in his bed.
Mm-hmm.
All night ?
No. Just after
you fell asleep.
So you're telling me
that my snoring is so bad--
how did you deal with it
for all those nights
before I found out
about your wife ?
He usually sleeps on the couch,
sets an alarm,
gets back in bed
before you wake up.
(Derek) Yeah, I didn't want
to hurt your feelings.
Mmm. Oh.
Well, I'm gonna do more
than hurt your feelings.
What are you doing ?
Oh. Stop it.
Aah !
I'm gonna hurt your feelings
'cause. . .
Can I. . . Help you ?
(sobs) I, um. . .
I-I inherited
$8 million.
I'm sorry ?
Almost 9, actually.
Sorry. Oh, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'm sorry. Did you say--
here, just take it.
Just take it, please.
Is that. . .
It's covered in food.
Is this some kind
of joke ?
It is kind of a joke. . .
A really cruel joke.
I'm sorry.
You want to deposit this ?
If I wanted to deposit it,
do you think that
I would look like this ?
I don't understand.
I'm. . . I'm supposed to do
something good.
I'm supposed
to do something good,
and--and I didn't. . .
Can--can you just deposit
the damn thing already ? !
I'm surprised they proceeded
with the surgery.
Me, too. I guess
they think
he has a strong enough constitution
to fight the cancer.
Is he conscious ?
Still intubated,
so they have him sedated.
The main concern
for the next few days
will be multisystem
organ failure.
That is that the surgery
was too intense
for his weakened organs
to support.
You want to watch
the kidneys
because if the kidneys fail,
that's a sign
that everything else
is starting to go.
So we're watching
the kidneys.
You're watching the kidneys.
Thank you.
Oh, do you mind me asking,
uh, how's your hand ?
I don't mind if you ask.
I will mind
if you tell Cristina.
You two have
a strange relationship.
Yes, we do.
Yeah.
And when you go home,
you're gonna have
your very own room.
Yes, you do.
And your mom, she got
one of those, um,
you know, uh, those stencils.
Mm-hmm.
And she made
little butterflies
and flowers.
You need something ?
No, I'm fine.
Oh, it gets quiet
in here.
You're the one
who paged me ?
I started my shift
ten minutes ago,
noticed her stomach looked
a little distended.
Her stomach's distended ?
I-I didn't notice that.
It's hard to see.
Page dr. Montgomery, stat.
Is everything okay ?
Is this bad ?
Well, let's just wait
for dr. Montgomery.
What's the matter ?
My father's here.
Your father ?
The one I don't talk to
and barely know, he's here.
What, is he here to see you ?
No. He's here
with his other family.
Oh, sorry.
Where do you sleep
at the trailer ?
What ?
When we sleep at the trailer,
where do you sleep ?
You know
the hammack outside ?
Sorry.
I'm a girl
with abandonment issues.
You have to sleep
with me from now on.
Okay.
A note from my hack
of a shrink.
I get to scrub in.
Not till I say so.
I deposited
the damn check.
You cheap
son of a bitch bastards
are going straight to hell--
straight to hell !
Ms. Douglas ?
Insurance bastards.
They say the surgery's
too experimental.
They won't pay.
It's a $200,000 surgery,
plus a hospital stay,
plus rehab.
Even if I get three jobs. . .
Son of a bitch bastards.
Looks like there won't be
a surgery to scrub in on.
Sorry, Stevens.
Talk to me.
Her abdomen was distended
and she needed increased
ventilatory support,
so I ordered some x-rays.
I'm sorry. I was talking
to her. I didn't notice.
She's got massive free air
trapped beneath her diaphragm.
Mr. Grey, we need to get
laura into surgery.
What ? Another surgery ?
Why ?
Her x-rays indicate there's ? ? ? ? ? ? ? ? ? ?
We need to get in there
right away.
Here's a consent form you need to sign.
I don't--I--
I don't know. . .
Her--her mother
has the flu.
At, you're not
authorized to sign ?
I am.
But I--I'd like to
fill her in--
we don't have time
for you to not know, mr. Grey.
Your granddaughter
doesn't have time.
All right, all right.
Take out more of the bowel.
I need better visualization.
It's so tiny, I'm afraid
I might crush it.
Oh, it's tougher
than you think.
Go ahead and give it
a little squeeze.
Cool. Thanks. Hmm.
Look at that.
The n. G. Tube has eroded
right through the stomach wall.
I may have to resect
an entire portion
of the stomach.
She's hypotensive.
Push 30 ccs of albumin.
Got it.
Whew.
Scary.
You're telling me.
This is
Meredith's Grey's niece.
If I lost her, people might
think I did it on purpose.
How's it going ?
Okay. They had a scare
a minute ago,
but she stabilized.
Your, uh, father is pacing
up and down the halls.
He's worried.
Maybe you can give him
an update.
*Maybe you can give him
an update. *
He's not a big fan
of mine.
of mine either.
Oh, I can't imagine
that's true.
Your mother was a force
to be reckoned with.
If she wanted things
a certain way, I. . .
I'm saying your father
was a good man when I knew him.
He may have a side in this that
you don't know anything about.
What, you think he tried
to send me a card every year
and my mother
has a whole drawer
full of unopened cards ?
Because it's not often
that my life
turns out that way.
I don't know.
You don't know either
until you ask him.
Hey.
How's he doing ?
Uh, georgie is obsessed
with our dad's pee.
Yeah, this is weird,
even for georgie.
Boys, be nice.
It's his kidney function.
I'm obsessed with his
kidney function, not his pee.
And I'm not obsessed.
I'm excited.
You're not gonna drink that,
are you, georgie ?
130 ccs !
130 ccs of shiny,
yellow urine !
130 ccs in how long ?
Four hours.
No way !
That is fantastic !
Yeah ! Yeah !
Thank you !
Mm.
Thank you.
Mark.
I'm sorry you're hurting.
You're sorry I'm hurting
or you're sorry ?
(Addison) Karev.
Oh. Hey.
I was, uh, just checking
the baby's capillary refills--
no, it's good,
it's good.
We all need
a little human contact
from time to time.
It sucks.
It's like she hasn't had
a chance to deserve this,
you know ?
Is that why you want
to go into plastics,
'cause people sign up
for the pain they get ?
Yeah.
For the most part,
they do, yeah.
You're right.
It does suck
watching them struggle.
And that part
never stops sucking.
But. . . Then when you get
to see a baby heal
and, um. . .
They get to go home
and. . . You just imagine
this whole life
that they're gonna live,
there's nothing better
than that.
And that part
never changes.
But. . . If you want
to go back to plastics. . .
Nah.
The vanilla latte ?
I did that on purpose.
Why ?
'Cause he was rude
to you.
Oh.
I'm, uh, sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Gosh, I'm. . . Really sorry.
No, I'm okay.
I'm, uh, I'm just, um. . .
I'm gonna--
yeah, okay. Yeah yeah.
Oh, hey.
You need some help ?
I can walk
to the bathroom myself.
I've been doing it
my whole life,
and nothing's changing
any time soon,
so just get out
of my way, okay ?
* And I can't live alone
in this lie *
* so look up
* take it away
* don't look da-da-da down. . .
Meredith.
* The mountain
* if the world isn't turning
* your heart won't return
* anyone, anything, anyhow
* so take me
* don't leave me
* take me
* baby
* love will come through
* it's just waiting for you
* well, I stand
at the crossroads *
* of high roads
and low roads
*nd I got a feeling
it's right *
* if it's real,
what I'm feeling *
* there's no make believing
* the sound of the wings
of the flight *
* of a dove
* take it away
* don't look da-da-da down
* the mountain
* if the world isn't turning
* your heart won't return
* anyone, anything, anyhow
* so take me
* don't leave me
* take me
* baby
* love will come through
* it's just waiting
for you *
* love will come through
* yeah
welcome to www. 1000Fr. Com