[Phone Beeping]
- [Ringing]
- [Miss Parker] What?
- [Jarod] Always the workaholic.
- Jarod-
Tormenting hours are from 9:00 to 5:00.
Call back tomorrow.
Who said I was calling to torment you?
Maybe I was just feeling nostalgic.
If you're feeling homesick, come visit.
I have a room all ready for you.
Generous offer,
but I will regretfully decline.
So. What is it, Jarod?
I was hoping you'd give my best
to the rest of our dysfunctional family.
Particularly Mr. Raines.
Oh, I'll be sure to say hey,
next time I see him.
When was the last time you saw him?
He hasn't been around
much lately, has he?
I count Raines's absence as a blessing.
I don't question it.
If you don't question...
- you don't learn.
- [Beeps]
I brought the Triumvirate
phone logs you requested.
Back burner, Broots.
I have a holier crusade for you.
Find out where Raines
has been lately.
[Ringing]
[Ringing Continues]
- [Beeps]
- Hello?
Well, it's about damn time.
Tell me you found him.
Look, I'm paying you
all this money...
'cause you're supposed
to be on the inside.
This boy should be dead by now.
Bolton, Minnesota must
be a podunk, nothing town.
How hard can it be to find him?
Well, he goes to school, doesn't he?
The clock is ticking.
My new trial is in five days...
and this boy's testimony is the
only thing that they've got on me.
I want you to find him.
I want you to kill him.
Otherwise, you're dead.
Got me? Don't let me down.
What's the problem, buddy?
You in some kind of hurry?
Yeah.
As a matter offact, I am.
[Bell Ringing]
[Chattering]
- [Claps]
- Good morning, class.
My name is Mr. Brodie.
I'm your substitute teacher.
[Man Narrating]
There are Pretenders among us.
[Jarod]
I was taken from my family.
Thirty-six hours and he's already demonstrating
more talent than any of our others.
How many people died
because of what I thought up?
Since I broke out, I've spent
every moment searching for my past.
[Miss Parker]
He's a Pretender-
A genius who can become
anyone that he wants to be.
- The Centre wants him alive.
- Preferably.
- [Miss Parker] He defends the weak and abused.
- [Jarod] Life's a gift.
- You a doctor?
- I am today.
Mr. Conklin, your regular teacher...
is on vacation, so before we get started...
I'd like to get to know
all of you a little bit better.
- Do you know about sex?
- [Laughter]
Mr. Conklin said we're gonna
start our sex education this week.
- My mom signed a permission slip.
- Kevin-
Interested in biology. Good.
[Boy]
I already know about sex.
- My dad has the Internet.
- Joel- Likes computers.
Mr. Brodie?
Are you married?
Uh, no, uh, Gemma.
- I'm not.
- Do you have a girlfriend?
- Yeah. Does she know about sex?
- [Laughter]
I'm the one that's supposed
to be asking the questions, remember?
What about you, uh, Matthew?
- What are you interested in?
- Uh-
I like to read, I guess.
You like to read.
That's a good thing.
And you, uh, Eric.
What are your interests?
Cool stuff. Espionage.
Counterintelligence.
You know, I could tell you more,
but, uh, I'd have to kill you.
[Laughter]
Eric's a freak!
He can't even write.
- It's all gibberish.
- It's not gibberish, Joel.
It's asecret code,
so knuckle-dragging mopes...
- like you can't read it.
- Oh, yeah?
It's probably a love letter
to your girlfriend Molly over there.
[Laughter]
All right. Can we, uh,
get back on track here?
- [Laughing, Chattering]
- Uh, class.
- Class.
- [Laughing, Chattering Continue]
Enough!
[Whistles]
Could you cut me
a little slack here?
It's not easy being
the new kid in school.
I'll bet some of you know about that.
Tell me something.
How many of you were born here?
How many of you spent
your whole life in Bolton?
Mr. Brodie? I was born here,
but my brother wasn't.
Okay. And how many of you
have brothers and sisters?
- Does this mean we're not
gonna learn about sex?
- [Laughter]
[Woman]
It was a child's eyewitness testimony...
that sealed Esposito's fate
to a life in prison.
However, just last month
the court granted Esposito a new trial...
based on a procedural technicality.
The charges against Esposito
stem from the brutal murder...
of a Brooklyn shop owner.
According to police, Esposito bludgeoned
and then buried the victim's body...
unaware the crime was being
witnessed by a fifth grader...
on a field trip from nearby
Woodbury Elementary School.
What's our rule
about other people's things?
- Excuse me.
- Those aren't your files, are they?
Uh, no, but there was
nobody in the office so I just-
Our rule about other people's things
is, "we don't touch them."
- I understand, but there was-
- Butts belong in ashtrays, mister.
It's all right, Mrs. Warner.
Jarod's our new sixth grade teacher.
I'll expect those back, young man.
Don't worry about
Mrs. Warner. She's a lifer.
- A lifer?
- Been here 32 years.
Teaching a 10-year-old
is the only language she knows.
Kind of scary, isn't it? Just like
being in grade school all over again.
Or for the very first time. Hi.
- Hi.
- Jarod, Rachel Daly, our student counselor.
Jarod's taking over the sixth graders
while Mr. Conklin's in Hawaii.
You believe Conklin's luck?
He's always been talking about Hawaii...
and out of nowhere he wins a trip.
Said he didn't even
remember entering the contest.
- Hmm. Unbelievable.
- Well, if you'll excuse me...
I've got a fourth grader
who is habitually pulling fire alarms.
- Nice to meet you, Jarod.
- Nice to meet you.
Principal Bauer, while I've got you here-
I have a student in my class-
Uh, Matthew Reese.
His records only go back 11 months,
and before that...
- it's like he doesn't exist.
- Matthew only moved here last year.
But even still, wouldn't
his old school transfer the records over?
Normally, but according to his mom,
his last school had a fire.
All the files were destroyed.
Well.
I guess that explains it.
[Miss Parker]
Raines has been going to an insane asylum?
Uh, the Pratt Institute.
It's about an hour south of here.
He's been going a couple of times a day.
Look. There he is.
- Cue men with big butterfly nets.
- No, no. He's not a patient.
He's visiting someone.
There's a woman.
A woman who means something to Jarod.
- The question is, who is she?
- [Sydney] My God.
Sydney?
- [Sydney] It's Edna Raines.
- Raines's wife?
- It's impossible.
- Kick the rock over, Syd.
What am I not seeing?
Edna Raines committed suicide
more than 20 years ago.
Or so you were told.
- Broots, get a town car.
- No, it's too late.
The guy at the hospital
told me she escaped last night.
[Children Laughing, Chattering]
Okay, a teacher's pay
is one thing, Jarod...
[Laughing]
but eating the school lunch-
- What, do you have a death wish?
- I was intrigued.
A tube of processed meat
covered by a deep-fried carbohydrate...
and skewered with a stick
so that it's fully portable.
- Sort of a meat Popsicle.
- Is that your first corn dog?
- Mmm. Good.
- [Laughs]
You're much braver than I am.
I've noticed that Matthew
doesn't socialize much...
with the other children.
Are there any issues
about him I should know about?
Matthew's been a little slow
assimilating since he transferred here...
but some kids are just like that.
- Why the interest?
- I just figure the more I know
about my kids...
the more I can help them.
[Esposito]
Three days and counting.
I don't want to hear
you're getting close.
I want to hear that this kid is dead.
If you can't figure out which boy
it is and get this job done...
then I'm gonna come do it myself.
You better worry that I just
don't bury you with him.
[Doorbell Rings]
- Hello.
- Hi.
My son said that there was
a new teacher in town...
so I wanted to bring you
a little something to say welcome.
- That's very nice. Thank you.
- Oh!
It's hot. I'd probably better do this.
I know what it's like
to be new in town.
Matthew and I just
moved here ourselves last year.
You said, uh, Matthew.
Matthew Reese?
Oh! I'm his mom.
I didn't say that, did I?
- No.
- No. [Laughs]
Where did you two move here from?
From back East.
[Doorbell Rings]
Excuse me.
- Hello.
- Uh, hello.
- Hello, Justine.
- Hello, Gail.
- You two know each other?
- Yeah.
We're in the same single moms'
cooking group here in town.
Oh, uh- Mmm.
[Doorbell Rings]
[Jarod]
It's pretty cool, huh?
You can see a whole world of things that
are too small to see with your human eye.
Hey, maybe we can use it
to see Eric's tiny little brain.
- [Laughter]
- Mr. Brodie, how do they
swim around like that?
That's a very good question.
Why don't you all read
chapter four and find out?
- [Students Groaning]
- I lost that book.
[Chuckles]
Get to work.
- It's pretty neat, huh?
- Yeah.
But I've seen protozoans
and stuff before.
We had microscopes in
the science room at my old school.
- Did you like your old school?
- I guess.
Must have been pretty tough-
leaving your old friends like that.
Mom said we didn't have a choice.
We had to move.
- I'm not really supposed to talk about it.
- [Bell Ringing]
Come on, Joel.
That's for my eyes only.
Oh.
I'm sorry, dude. Here.
[Laughs]
- This is sweet.
- It's way over your head.
Oh, yeah? Let's find out.
Hi. I'm Eric Gantry,
and I'm a scrawny little freak...
and I'm so madly in love with Molly.
[Joel On Recorder] Hi. I'm Eric Gantry,
and I'm a scrawny little freak...
and I'm so madly in love with Molly.
What's our rule about
other people's things, Joel?
- What?
- We do not touch them.
Pretty manly, freak-
Always having a teacher rescue you.
It seems he has it in for you.
It's no big deal.
What's a secret agent
without an archenemy, right?
Just forget about it.
- Hey!
- [CarStarts]
- [Tires Screeching]
- Hey!
[Sydney]
I still can't believe Edna's alive.
[Miss Parker]
You sound as if you liked her, Syd.
Very much so. You see, Edna was
not like so many company wives.
There was something
more alive about her.
There's also something
familiar about her.
She was working as a physician,
right here at the Centre...
- in the staff dispensary.
- Right.
In fact, I think she saw me
when I had the mumps.
- Your mother trusted her completely.
- She did?
Edna, you see, had
many admirable qualities.
She was as vocal
in community politics...
as she was at Centre cocktail parties.
How did she end up marrying Raines?
After the murder of their daughter,
Edna fell apart.
I was told she took
an overdose of barbiturates.
I was at the funeral, Parker.
I wonder what's really buried
out there in the Centre cemetery.
I've got Broots out hunting for Edna.
[Sydney]
Raines must be doing the same.
I think it's testing
his new-found innerpeace.
- [Knocking]
- Not a word to anyone, Sydney. Good night.
Broots, tell me something good.
Oh, it's so good to see you again,
Catherine.
- [Bell Ringing]
- Great little town like Bolton-
Never thought we'd have
sickos hanging around our school.
Did you get a good look at him?
- No, and he didn't stick around for questions.
- Reminds me.
Kids are having a big dance
on Friday- Sadie Hawkins-
in light of yesterday, I'd feel better
if we had another chaperone there.
Oh. I look forward to it.
And I can't wait to meet this Miss Hawkins.
Wait, honey. Forgot your lunch.
Remember, I'm working late, okay?
So leftovers for dinner.
- Bye.
- Excuse me, Mrs. Gantry.
My name is Jarod Brodie.
I'm Eric's new teacher.
I was wondering if I could talk to you
about some trouble he's having.
Oh, you mean Joel? Yeah, Eric
told me about what happened yesterday.
Joel is a bit of a problem.
But you think Eric's all right otherwise?
- "Otherwise"?
- Oh, you know, I just worry, that's all.
You know, with this whole
"secret agent"...
spy game of his.
Pretending isn't so bad.
Yeah, as long as
he's not hiding in it.
But it is the sixth grade.
I'm probably just being silly.
Hey, it's not silly
to care about your son.
I'll have a talk with him.
- [Bell Ringing]
- Thank you.
Excuse me, Mrs. Warner.
The parking sticker you gave me-
I can't find it anywhere.
I must have lost it.
Boys- They'd lose their heads
if they weren't attached.
Well, technically,
lack of cranial attachment...
would nullify all other
motor skills, therefore the notion-
Uh, if it helps, I believe
it was sticker number 48.
No, Mr. Brodie, you had 55.
Number 48 belongs
to Larry Grasso, our janitor.
Thank you.
Mr. Brodie! Hi.
Matthew forgot his lunch.
So, I have just been dying to know...
what you thought of my risotto.
Actually, I was- I was going to call you.
Really?
The other evening, when
I was asking you the questions...
about where you used to live-
I know why you were dodging them.
Did- Did I give you that impression?
Gail, I know why you and Matthew
had to move here.
You can trust me.
Really.
You have no idea how hard it's been...
keeping this a secret
and living this lie.
I mean, I-I thought
that he was a nice guy.
You know, I had no idea
about the hidden camera.
I guess everyone's
got the Internet these days.
- And- And before you knew it-
- You never lived in Woodbury?
There was no testimony, no trial?
Trial?
[Sydney]
How is Edna?
As vacant as the Bates Motel.
Edna? Do you remember me?
We were colleagues at the Centre...
- many, many years ago.
- Sydney.
That's right.
You do remember.
Edna? Edna, can you hear me?
Forget it, Syd. She's been clap-on,
clap-off all afternoon.
Twenty years of sedation must have
taken a damaging toll on her brain.
But something brought her here-
Something brought her here
looking for my mother.
- What?
- Let's try and find out.
Well, there's only one reason
the Centre would have gone to...
such lengths to keep her quiet.
She knows their
dirty little secrets.
I want to know them too.
Even if Edna were lucid...
she may not have
the capacity to tell you.
Well, this dig isn't over.
Takes one to know one, right?
Maybe we should
pass the shovel to Angelo...
and see what he can find in there.
[Eric]
Tough day, huh?
- I'm afraid so, Eric.
- Did you just get some bad news?
Yeah.
Wow.
That's some pretty sophisticated
spy equipment you got there.
What's that thing?
Hey, look at this-
An operative's communicator.
- You know, so my superiors can contact me.
- When you're on a mission.
Eric, Joel was kind
of a jerk yesterday...
the way he was making fun of you
in front of everybody like that.
I try not to let him get to me.
I don't really care what he or
any of the other non-operatives think.
Except for Molly, right?
I see the way you look at her.
That's supposed to be top secret.
Again, stupid Joel compromised everything.
Check this out.
I keep all my secrets in here.
You don't exactly have
the proper clearance...
but, uh, I'll make an exception.
Whoa.
- A surveillance photo. Nice going.
- She probably hates me.
Nah. No, you got that
dashing spy-thing going on.
Girls love that.
- Still, what do I do?
- Well, if I were you, I would just...
face it head on and tell her how you feel.
Noway. Suicide mission.
When you care about somebody,
you've gotta tell them...
while you've got the chance.
I wouldn't know what to say.
Here.
Practice into this thing,
and when you get it right...
tell her.
[Bell Ringing]
Mr. Brodie?
Thanks.
You're the first friend
I've made since I came here.
[Eric's Voice] You're the first friend
I made since I came here.
[Jarod's Voice] How many of you
spent your whole life in Bolton?
[Eric]
I keep all my secrets in here.
[Thinking]
Woodbury.
Eric is the witness.
Mrs. Warner, have you seen Eric Gantry?
He was talking to the janitor a few minutes
ago. Then I saw him walking home.
- Damn it.
- Mr. Brodie!
This is Agent X-4 checking in.
Eric! Eric!
[Tires Screeching]
What happened?
Where's Eric?
I was trying to help the kid.
- You're a U.S. marshal.
- There's a leak inside Witness Protection.
I was just about to pull Eric in.
- They're gonna kill him
if you don't stop them.
- Who?
- Who shot you?
- Didn't see him.
Gotta be Esposito's inside man.
You hang on.
I'm going to get some help.
Save Eric. The killer knows where he lives.
Don't let him go home, Jarod.
Don't let him go home.
- Operative's communicator.
- So my superiors can contact me.
[Beeping]
- [Muffled Cries]
- Shh, shh. It's me. Come on.
Back to my house.
Let's get your mom.
When I heard that animal
got out, I was, uh- I was so scared.
But then Witness Protection called
and they said not to worry...
that they were sending someone
out to keep an eye on us.
The janitor. Esposito's man
already got to him.
My God.
They gave me a number to call
in case of an emergency.
You can't. There's a leak
inside the agency.
It's not safe.
Okay. Okay, so what do we do?
We call the police?
My gut says that we stay
under everybody's radar-
at least for tonight.
Sit down and try to relax.
Mr. Brodie, I am so, so sorry...
that I lied in class when you asked
who's lived here a long time.
I mean, they told me
that sometimes I had to lie.
- It's not like I wanted to.
- Eric-
You did the right thing.
- Mom, I'm done.
- Okay, honey.
Hey. There's eight cartons
of ice cream in the freezer.
After your homework.
- He's a terrific kid.
- Yeah.
You two have been through a lot.
Yeah, but he's just a boy,
and he deserves a childhood...
surrounded by family and friends...
and instead he was hustled away
in the middle of the night...
taken away from everything.
It's not fair.
I know.
At least he has his mother
to take care of him.
My little man. I don't deserve him.
I really don't.
Saw the murder-
His class was going on a field trip...
and Eric woke up with some sniffles
and a fever coming on...
and I really should have
kept him home...
but I didn't.
- See, I had made plans that day.
- What happened wasn't your fault.
I am his mother.
I'm supposed to keep him
safe and happy, and he's neither.
And the worst part is...
that once the new trial starts,
it's gonna start all over again.
[Sydney]
Quietly, Angelo.
I'm taking you to see
a friend of mine- Edna.
- Sydney's friend dead.
- No, she's very much alive.
No. Dead inside.
That is why I need your help, Angelo.
Got it?
- Working late, Sydney?
- Isn't it past Bonzo's bedtime?
I have this idea...
that Angelo might
be able to empath...
- Jarod's next move.
- Your idea will have to wait.
Angelo's skills are required
in another pursuit at the moment.
That a problem?
No, of course not.
Come on, monkey boy.
[Eric]
Mom, what's gonna happen to us?
I don't know, kiddo. We may have
to play it fast and loose again.
Mom, I can't leave. Not yet.
Honey, I don't know
that we have a choice.
- Mom, please. There's something I have to do.
- Baby, I'm so sorry.
This never should have
happened to you.
Now try and get some sleep. Okay?
So what now?
The marshal said that Esposito's man
is someone inside the school.
I find him before he finds us.
[Beeping]
Mrs. Raines, that monster...
you're married to has kept you
doped up for the last 20 years.
Why? What did you know?
So good to see you again, Catherine.
That's right. I'm Catherine, your friend.
I'm here to help you,
but you need to help me too.
So good to see you again, Catherine.
And I know you came here
to see me for a reason.
Please... tell me what it is.
So good to see you again, Catherine.
Look. I'm not Catherine.
All right?
Catherine's been dead
a very long time.
Do you hear me?
[Groans]
I'm not my mother.
How are your mumps, little Miss Parker?
You remember.
Edna, please-
Tell me why you came here to see me.
- Mirage.
- "Mirage." What is mirage?
What your mother started.
Work she hoped you'd finish.
What kind of work?
Edna? Edna?
Edna, stay with me.
Rachel.
"Rachel Daly.
Chicago field office.
"Federal marshal,
Witness Protection Division.
- Current assignment: On leave."
- [Beeping]
Rachel Daly.
Rachel Daly, the school counselor?
She's a Witness Protection
agent from out of state.
- But why would she do that?
- Money. Eric's testimony...
is the only thing that could
put Esposito back in prison.
- Where is he?
- Uh, he's still sleeping.
I didn't want to wake him till I had to.
We have to get you two out of town.
I'll deal with Rachel later.
Oh, my God, they got him. Eric!
- Eric!
- No. This wasn't forced open.
It was unlocked from the inside.
But why? Where would he go?
- [School Bell Ringing]
- [Chattering]
# [Pop On P.A.]
Hey. Hi. Uh, Molly...
can I talk to you for a sec?
There's somewhere I have to go.
You know, it's a secret mission...
but I didn't want to leave
before I told you something.
Yeah? What?
All year long, I-
No. No, I'm sorry.
That's not what I meant.
Here.
Uh, can you just listen to this?
- Please?
- Sure.
Sorry to interrupt
your love connection...
but you already got a date-with my fist.
Eric.
Just the young man I was looking for.
Why don't you come with me?
There's someone here to see you.
Hey there, buddy.
Remember me?
Eric! Eric!
[Jarod]
Molly.
- Have you seen Eric Gantry?
- That jerk Joel chased him that way.
Eric! Eric!
Oh, my God. She has him.
Jarod, what are we gonna do?
- Where could they have taken him?
- Wait a minute.
- Smart boy, Eric.
- [Tape Rewinding]
- [Eric On Tape] Leave me alone.
- [Esposito] Shut up.
My God.
- Where are you taking me?
- Don't worry, kid. It's a short walk.
- Sorry I didn't bring a hard hat.
- [Daly] Come on, Eric.
- Let me go!
- Call the police.
[Eric]
Come on!
I swear to God,
I will not testify against you.
- Please let me go!
- Sorry, kid, but as long as you're alive...
you stand to seriously
foul up my life.
- Get in the hole.
- No!
Be a good boy, Eric, and do as he says.
Both of you.
Why don't you fill it yourself?
Thank God, Jarod.
- I saw him dragging Eric here and I didn't-
- I know, I know.
You know something?
I don't think this hole is full enough.
Oh!
- You okay?
- Uh, yeah.
- Good. You go take care of your mom now. Go.
- Okay.
It's kind of fitting, don't you think?
You've gotten yourselves into a hole...
you can't get out of.
- Jarod, come on.
- Come on. We were just talking to that kid.
Oh, yes, like the way
she was just talking...
to that federal marshal-
when she murdered him...
or the way you were just
talking to the shop owner...
two years ago when he was
bludgeoned to death.
Oh. Whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
Jarod?
- Jarod, what are you doing?
- He's crazy.
Eric was just a boy.
All he wanted was his childhood-
to be with his family,
to play with his friends.
But you took all that away from him.
In an instant, everything
he knew was just taken away.
Well, now it's your turn to disappear...
and no one will ever miss you.
Okay, I did sell Eric out...
and I did shoot the marshal,
but I can help you out.
- I can testify against Esposito.
- Shut up!
I don't know. Why don't you offer her
some more money, Esposito?
- You're insane. You can't do this.
- Who the hell are you?
I'm just a guy who's digging your grave.
Oh, that's right-You two already dug it.
I'm just filling it in.
You better talk quick.
This stuff dries fast.
All right! All right, I did it!
I said I did it.
- Come again?
- I killed the shop owner.
I hired her to kill the kid.
Is that what you want to hear?
- Yes. As a matter of fact, it is.
- [Tape Rewinding]
[Esposito On Tape] I killed the shop
owner and I hired her to kill the kid.
Is that what you want to hear?
You're still going to disappear-
Both of you.
- [Daly] What are you doing?
- [Esposito] I gave you what you wanted.
[Daly, Esposito Shouting]
- Jarod! You can't just leave us in here.
- Wait! Wait!
Jarod!
What about Mirage?
Anything yet?
Uh-
[Clears Throat]
Well, I've, uh- I've scanned
the D.S.A. file directory, and-
The headlines, Broots.
Not the fine print.
No. Nothing on Mirage.
Maybe it's just nonsense. I mean,
this lady is a little whacked-out.
Most of the time, yeah,
but not when she said Mirage.
I know it.
- So-
- It's back to the salt mines for me.
[Bell Ringing]
Come on, Joel.
What did you bring for me today, freak?
What's this? Brownies?
Oh.
Don't, Joel. You'll be sorry.
Oh, I haven't been sorry yet.
[Snickers]
Mmm!
Mmm! That's good.
Too bad your mother
didn't make you any, freak.
Patience.
It won't be long, with the amount...
of prune extract we put in 'em.
I would say right... about...
now.
[Rumbling]
I wonder what came over him.
Something he ate, maybe?
Hmm.
[Laughing, Chattering]
No!
Well, Agent Gantry,
mission accomplished.
Mission accomplished.
[Bell Ringing]
Excuse me.
Seen the paper this morning?
Now, I can't understand...
how they got the story, and yet
there's not one mention about the guy...
- who made it all happen.
- Teaching can be such a thankless profession.
Not entirely.
- Thank you,Jarod.
- Thanks, Mr. Brodie.
Eric, can I talk to you for a sec?
I listened to your tape.
It was sweet.
I'm really glad you gave it to me.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
So I was wondering-
Do you want to go to the Sadie Hawkins
dance with me tomorrow night?
Yeah! I-I mean-
- Of course I do.
- Good.
I'll... see you in class.
Mom, we don't have
to leave tonight, do we?
Does a certain secret agent
have one last rendezvous?
Yeah.
[Miss Parker]
She okay, Sam?
She went and laid down.
I haven't heard a word from her.
Mrs. Raines? Edna?
[Whispering]
Oh, man.
Now we're left empty-handed.
Not exactly.
I still have Mirage.
# Kri kra toad's foot #
# Geese walk barefoot #
[Vehicle Approaching]
# Kri kra toad's foot- #
[Edna]
# Kri kra toad's foot#
# Geese walk barefoot##
www.tvsubtitles.net