Fletcher Ridge, Illinois. Large
enough to have a U.P.S. office...
and a driver named Jarod Harper.
Very good, Broots.
Any physical description?
Size, weight and color
all match Jarod perfectly.
And he got the job at almost
exactly the same time that...
- I calculated his position.
- Call Lyle.
- I already have. He's on his way.
- Great. Let's go.
[Cell Phone Rings, Beeps]
- What?
- [Mr. Parker] Angel.
- Angel, I have to see you.
- [Whispering] Daddy?
The junkyard near the Quentin Street
Overpass, and hurry.
- Daddy!
- [Dial Tone]
You look bothered, Miss Parker.
Don't you have
a bake sale to organize?
I know these are
stressful times for you.
That's why I want you to have this.
It's a prayer card.
I slept with it under my pillow.
- That explains the grease stains.
- I asked for it to be filled...
with the answers you need.
- God bless.
- You too.
Parker?
Are you coming?
I'll be back.
- What about Jarod?
- What about Lyle?
Um, buy me some time.
A few hours.
[Siren Wails]
[Second Siren Wailing]
Ouch!
Sorry, mister.
It got away from me.
- Wow. This is a great car.
- Thanks.
- I bought it with my tooth fairy money.
- "Tooth fairy"?
You know, where you put
your tooth under your pillow...
the tooth fairy takes it
and leaves you money.
Didn't you ever get that
when you were a kid?
I wasn't really a kid
when I was a kid.
Thanks, mister.
[Bell Tolling]
[Woman] Would you just shut up?
I don't want to talk about this anymore.
Damn it, Sarah,
we don't have a choice.
Cam, we don't need to be
making these arrangements.
The hell we don't! These people
at the hospital already showed...
they don't care whether us Larsens
live or die- Billy, come on.
- Cam, the doctors said-
- I know what the doctors said.
I know what needs to be done.
- Why do you have guns?
- [Engine Revs]
Cam! What are you planning to do?
- I didn't start this, Sarah.
- Cameron!
- Go home!
- [Screams]
Come on, damn it!
[Crying]
Damn it!
Here you go.
Use mine.
[Beeps, Dials]
- [Line Ringing]
- [Woman] 9-1-1. Can I help you?
Yes, ma'am. My name is Sarah Larsen.
My brothers are on the way
to the hospital. They have guns.
I don't know! Look, you just
gotta do something...
before somebody gets hurt, okay?
- [Sobs]
- [Beeps]
I appreciate- Mister?
[Woman On Police Radio] All units,
hostage situation at Saint Mary's Hospital.
- Men considered armed and dangerous.
- [Sirens Wailing]
[People Clamoring]
[Cam] Billy, hurry up
and get those windows painted.
Nobody moves and nobody gets hurt!
We're all gonna be here awhile,
so just get comfortable.
[Woman On P.A.]
All medical personnel.
Prepare to evacuate all non critical
patients from the first floor.
- How you doin', Pop?
- [Machine Beeping]
[Man]
Keep evacuating!
Everybody sit tight
and wait for my command.
If there's a clear shot,
you let me know.
Well, that's an interesting philosophy.
Shoot first, ask questions later.
- Who are you?
- Special Agent Jarod Jackson, Chicago F.B.I.
I'm the hostage negotiator.
- This is my show now.
- Damn!
[Man Narrating]
There are Pretenders among us.
[Jarod]
I was taken from my family.
36 hours and he's already demonstrating
more talent than any of our others.
How many people died
because of what I thought up?
Since I broke out, I've spent
every moment searching for my past.
[Miss Parker]
He's a Pretender-
A genius who can become
anyone that he wants to be.
- The Centre wants him alive.
- Preferably.
[Miss Parker]
He defends the weak and abused.
Life's a gift.
- You a doctor?
- I am today.
Best we can figure, there's
a half a dozen people being held.
Including three patients in
the seized wing that could die...
in the next few hours
without treatment.
- Kill that alarm!
- The hostage-takers?
Billy Larsen. He's 21.
Good kid, with no priors.
Big brother Cam's 28.
He's a hothead...
with a sheet that goes
all the way back to high school.
- Weapons?
- Rifle and shotgun,
according to their sister.
- I'll need her brought here
as soon as possible.
- Yes, sir.
- They make any demands?
- Nothing yet.
- What's your read on the situation?
- You're the big badge.
- You tell me.
- They've isolated the situation...
to a specific area of the hospital
where their father is a patient.
My guess, it's some sort of grievance
against the hospital.
- How do you figure that?
- Like you said, I'm the big badge.
Let's go to work.
This is F.B.I. Special Agent
Jarod Jackson.
I want to talk to you
about your demands.
If you've got something on your minds...
now might be a good time
to discuss it.
This is between us and the hospital.
You've got your father in there.
Innocent people who
need medical attention.
Neither one of us want
anyone to die here today.
So why don't you
tell me what you want...
- and we can end this thing.
- [Cam] I want you to write this down.
$41,342.17.
Not a penny more, not a penny less.
Over and out.
All right.
I'll see what I can do.
Need to establish a direct
phone line into that room.
- Yes, sir.
- What if they don't answer?
Hell, they could have already killed
somebody, and we'd never know it.
Where can I get blueprints
of this building?
- I can get 'em here 10 ten minutes.
- All right.
I need a fiber-optics video camera, with
a transmitter and microwave intercept.
Hold on, Einstein.
This town has two red lights,
three hardware stores.
- Meaning?
- Meaning, if you want a hammer,
I can help you out.
You want to build a nuclear reactor,
you're outta luck.
- This town have an electronics store?
- That we got.
I'm going to make a list
of things I need.
Get these to me, A.S.A.P.
[Engine Revving]
[Beeping]
[BabyCrying]
[Crying Continues]
Angel.
- Ugh.
- You weren't followed?
- Daddy, you look-
- Oh, I'm sorry to scare you.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
- Daddy, what the hell is going on?
- Come on, come on.
Come on back here.
Sit down.
- [Panting]
- Where have you been?
Underground. This is the last place
they'd look. [Panting]
Now, look.
There's a strongbox in SL-22.
- In a panel behind the fire hose.
- Strongbox?
Yeah. It's filled with cash.
Bring it to me.
But don't tell anybody.
Life and death, understand?
- No, I don't.
- Brigitte and I had to leave
our hiding place.
I need the money to last us a few weeks.
- Daddy, if I knew why you were running-
- [Cell Phone Rings]
- [Beeps]
- What?
Bad news. Jarod never showed up
for his shift at the U.P.S. job.
- We missed him!
- Lyle?
He's looking for you,
and he is peeved.
What else is new? I want you
to keep searching for Jarod.
- I'll be back as soon as I can.
- [Kissing Sound]
Daddy?
[Woman] This whole thing is gonna
turn into a nightmare.
Nobody's gonna want to
get treated at the O.K. Corral.
- Who are you?
- Rebecca Simons, hospital administrator.
Dr. Stephen Franklin,
chief cardiologist.
They spoke to the Larsen boys
before they pulled their guns.
- I'm listening.
- Family brought their father.
- Jake Larsen.
- He was complaining of chest pains.
- Family thought it might be a heart attack.
- He was admitted to C.C.U.?
Yes, yes. I diagnosed him with a type of
arrhythmia known as atrial fibrillation.
It's painful, but it's
not life-threatening.
- Apparently, his sons had a different opinion.
- Maybe I should have kept...
Mr. Larsen one more night
to ease their minds.
Does this figure mean
anything to you, Doctor?
$41,342.17?
- Not in particular. What is it?
- [Sighs] That's a good question.
Agent Jackson,
there are patients in there...
who will die in the next few hours
if left untreated.
[Sighs]
Excuse me.
Sarah, my name is Jarod.
- The man with the telephone.
- I'm with the F.B.I.
I think it's safe to say that neither one of us
woke up this morning expecting to be here.
- [Sighs]
- I realize that you're going through...
a very difficult time right now.
But I have to understand:
Why are your brothers doing this?
Look, I want to end this thing
without anybody getting hurt.
But the truth is, I can only hold
those men off for so long.
Move over there.
Get that door.
Everything was always
pretty crazy in our family.
But things seemed to really
come undone after Mom died.
- Especially for Cam.
- Your mom was here, at this hospital.
Same room where Daddy is.
[Sighs] She was so sick
when they sent her home...
and... she died a few days later.
And now your father's here.
Look, my brothers may be
doing the wrong thing...
but they must be doing it
for the right reason-
and I am not gonna help you
kill them for it.
Agent Jackson.
Got the equipment you wanted.
All right. Let's see
what's going on in there.
- [Heart Monitor Beeping]
- [Moaning]
- What are we gonna do, Cam?
- I'm thinking!
[Softly]
I'm thinking.
[Billy] I hope you know
what you're doin', big brother.
- I don't get it.
- Sometimes it helps to be a fly on the wall.
Or in this case, the airvent.
Grab those blueprints.
This will give us a better sense of the space
where the hostages are being held...
windows, exits-
[Deputy]
I'll be damned.
I could use this to get a clean shot. I have
men on the roof, next to the seized wing.
Isn't it your job to consider
everybody's safety?
My job is to save the lives
of those civilians inside!
If I hesitate, and one innocent person
dies, it's my fault.
I won't make that mistake.
The sheriff seems a little on edge.
[Deputy]
He has his reasons.
[Jake] Cam! What the hell
do you think you're doin'?
- [Cam] I know what I'm doin', Pop.
- You wouldn't be here...
if your mama was still alive.
Well, she's not, and I am.
Stop talkin'.
Just get some rest.
Man, there are guns and badges
all over the place down there.
[Sighs] Well, what the hell did
you think was gonna happen?
Come in here with guns, they'd leave
a parking ticket on our car?
Just keep lookout.
Sheriff says,
kill the air and the lights.
[Motors Decelerating]
You two get down!
- [Jake Gasping]
- What now?
[Phone Ringing]
- Yeah.
- Cam. This is Agent Jackson.
Turn the lights and air back on!
All right, I'll give you what you want,
and you give me a couple of hostages.
- Why should I trust you?
- You have my word.
No harm will come to you or your brother,
as long as we keep talking.
It's going to get really warm in there.
Now, do we have a deal?
Cam. You can trust me.
- Cam? Talk to me.
- [Gunshot]
Get down!
Everybody get down!
[Screaming]
[Gunshots Continue]
I had Cam's trust until
your sniper got trigger-happy.
Hey! Cam Larsen isn't
a man who can be trusted.
He incited a riot while he was in prison.
Did you know that?
The guards were beating the prisoners, and
they were convicted on brutality charges.
Did you know that?
I got Cam on the line.
- Cam.
- Are you guys crazy?
I had nothing to do with that
shooting, I swear to you.
Look, i-it's important that I come
in there and speak to you face-to-face.
I'm not here to talk!
I'm here to save my dad's life.
Understand? It's too hot in here.
Turn on the air, now.
Yes. Yes, I will turn the air conditioning
back on, I promise.
- Now, can I come in there?
- [Sighs Deeply]
Okay. But just you.
Unarmed. Ten minutes.
- All right. Ten minutes.
- [Line Clicks]
- Those are Cam's kids.
- I had them brought in.
- To get under his skin?
- To get into his heart.
- [Cell Phone Ringing]
- What?
- Where are you?
- Never mind. Did you find Jarod?
I was scanning police chatter
in Fletcher Ridge...
and I came across a hostage negotiation
situation there at a hospital.
- F.B.I. involvement.
- And?
It sounded like something
that Jarod would be drawn to...
- so I-I contacted the Chicago office
of the F.B.I.-
- Let me guess.
- No F.B.I. involvement.
- If there were any agents on the job there...
they would have come from the Chicago
office, and they hadn't sent anybody.
[Groans] He never left town. Get the jet
ready, and I'll be back as soon as I can.
- [Softly] What about Lyle?
- Lyle who?
[Hangs Up Receiver, Beeps]
Hmm.
I love ice cream.
[Smacking Lips]
I want to help your dad, but I'm going
to need your help to do it.
[Siren Wailing]
Last night, Daddy was
yelling at Billy and Sarah.
- He was angry?
- He said the hospital was gonna
send Grandpa Jake home to die.
Just like they did Grandma.
He said they were murderers.
- Murderers.
- [Sighs]
- Looks like you just lost a tooth.
- It fell out.
Are you going to put it under your pillow?
For the tooth fairy?
- Tonight.
- Wow.
- How much you figure you're gonna get?
- Mm-
- Maybe a dollar.
- A dollar.
How would you...
- [Helicopter Whirring]
- like to make five?
[Helicopter Passing By]
It's Agent Jackson.
I'm coming in, and I'm unarmed.
[Heart Monitor Beeping]
Check him out.
He's clean.
Could have got somebody killed,
shootin' in here like that.
That was a mistake. That officer
has been removed from the line.
We're not exactly talking about
an elite police force out there.
- [Cam] Tell me about it.
- So, are you ready to end this thing, Cam?
Get your father taken care of?
I know you care about him.
That's why you're doing this.
- You don't know nothin'.
- Why don't you explain it to me?
$41,342.17.
- That's an odd price to place on somebody's life.
- It's not my price. It's theirs.
- [Moaning]
- Oh, she's gettin' worse.
- Hey-hey!
- So, what are you gonna do?
You gonna keep her here and let her die?
Her life for your father's, is that it?
- Cam, maybe we should let her go, huh?
- Billy, shut up!
- [Gasps]
- You're not a killer, Cam.
You let this woman die, and you're going
to spend the rest of your life in prison.
You and Billy, here.
- Think about your children.
- My kids.
- They won't understand this.
- Can't believe how much
your little boy looks like you.
- You talked to my boy?
- It'sprocedure. Oh, Cody.
He asked me to give you this.
[Helicopter Whirring]
- So, how much do you want me
to leave for him?
- How much?
Money. From the tooth fairy.
Right. Tooth fairy.
You got a dollar?
- All I got's a five.
- Give it here.
- You're gonna give him five bucks
for a baby tooth?
- Just give me the money.
You walk outta here now, you can still put
this money under your son's pillow yourself.
I can't leave him.
[Sighs]
Man, you don't get it, do you?
This isn't just about my father. It's about
every person out there who is sick...
and deserves to be treated with dignity.
They're gonna send this man home. Does
he look like he should go home to you?
- [Gasping]
- At least, give me a hostage.
- [Scoffs]
- You gotta work with me here, Cam.
There are a lot of people out there
looking for any reason to shoot you...
and your little brother over here.
[Woman Breathing With
Diffilculty, Coughing]
All right. Take that lady.
Take her. Help him.
Unhook her, and get her out of here.
- What about the others?
- One at a time.
Allright, allright, allright.
One at a time.
You're doing a good thing here, Cam.
[Chattering On Police Radio]
If some of those patients don't get treatment
real soon, we could have a disaster here.
- Meaning?
- Maneuver Cam to a window.
One shot, and it's over.
Why is it that you feel that
bullets are the only option?
One shot.
Deputy, may I have a word with you?
[Heart Monitor Beeping]
[Spitting]
- What's your name?
- Lindsay.
L-Lindsay Tyler.
Shouldn't bite your nails,
Lindsay. It's a bad habit.
- I know.
- Y-You don't remember me, do you?
- Should I?
- Cindy Perkins?
Junior high school,
Sadie Hawkins dance-
I asked you to dance once,
and you said yes?
- [Sighs]
- I had stringy hair, braces-
Yeah, yeah.
You chased me around the gym all night.
What was that, 10, 15 years ago?
You kept asking the band
to play your favorite song.
- "Dream Weaver." [Chuckles]
- That's a damn fine song.
[Helicopter Passing Overhead]
You know, my dad
died of heart problems.
Th-That's why I went into nursing.
Your father sort of
reminds me of my dad.
[Jake Coughing]
Look, Cindy-
[Sighs Deeply]
I'm sorry about all this.
I never meant to-
- Cam?
- [Alarm Beeping]
- Cam, come here.
- Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
He's not breathing!
- [Ringing]
- I need a doctor in here now! Now!
All right, Cam. I'll send one in.
Get your gear.
- [Doctor] No.
- What did you say?
Those men are heavily armed, and they've
threatened the lives of innocent people.
Unless you can assure me
of my safety, I'm not going anywhere.
- Get the lights back on in that room.
- What are you gonna do?
Agent Jackson.
Agent Jackson!
Cam, it's Agent Jackson.
I'm coming in.
- I asked for a doctor!
- Cam, he's going into cardiac arrest!
- Let him in, Cam.
- [Alarm Buzzing]
- We didn't come here to kill our own father.
- [Alarm Continues]
- [Assisted Breathing]
- Come in!
- Easy, easy!
- Where is the doctor?
[Jarod] There isn't a doctor available.
I can handle this.
- [Exhales]
- [Huffs]
I hope you can handle this.
'Cause if my old man dies, so do you.
[One Long Beep]
- [Cindy] He's been flat for 15 seconds.
- [Electrical Whining]
- Paddles charged?
- Clear.
- [Electrical Thumping]
- [Cindy] Nothing. 25 seconds.
- Talk to him.
- What?
I need him to fight.
Tell him a story from your past.
Something you did together.
Talk to him. Clear.
- [Thumps]
- Nothing.
- We're running out of time. Talk to him.
- [Cindy] 40 seconds.
Dad, remember when I was
five years old...
how you used to take me
hunting up near Patchett Lake?
I'm going to 360 joules.
Keep talking.
- [Paddles Charging]
- Used to wake me up early,
while it was still dark out.
I used to hate gettin'up so early,
but you said it was important...
- to get out before the sun.
- [Jarod] Clear!
You told me that a sunrise in the woods was
as close to God as a breathin' man could get.
- [Paddles Whining]
- Remember when you said that?
Remember that, Dad?
- [Cindy] One minute.
- Clear.
- [Thumping]
- [Gasping]
- Come on, old man. Fight! Don't give up! Fight.
- [Cindy] 70 seconds.
- Don't leave us, please.
- [Paddles Charging]
- We need you.
- I'm gonna hit him again. Clear!
Come on, you can fight this!
Come on, Pop.
We need you.
Cody and Kerry need their grandpa.
If we don't get him back quick,
there could be permanent damage.
Don't die on me, Dad. Hang in there.
Come on. Don't die on me, Dad.
- Come on, pop!
- I'm getting a pulse.
[Steady Beeping]
They really train 'em
up there at the F.B.I. Academy.
[Police Chattering On Radio]
Let's get a closer look.
[Whirring, Banging]
- What the hell was that?
- What the hell happened?
- I don't know. The signal went dead.
- [Panting] Look, Cam.
You've made all the right choices up till now.
Let me take another hostage out of here.
- Okay. Yeah. You, Cindy. Go home.
- No.
- What?
- I don't leave until you do.
For my father.
I-I'll go.
- I've got to get that picture back.
- [Jarod, Indistinct]
- [Deputy] We've still got sound, Sheriff.
- [Whirring, Banging]
What the hell is this?
You've been watchin' us
the whole time!
I should blow you away right now!
I knew I couldn't trust you people!
- [Moaning]
- No, no!
No. Cam. Not like this.
[Helicopter Whirring]
All right. Get out.
Take her with you.
No more talking! Just get out!
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Please take care of her.
- Are you out of your mind?
- Hey, it was an accident!
You could have gotten all of us killed
in there. We can't keep pushing him.
- Why can't you get that through your head?
- I've had a bellyful of you.
- Oh, yeah? And what is that supposed to mean?
- You're the big badge.
You figure it out.
[Keypad Beeping]
- [Line Ringing, Clicking]
- Alice? Get me the number
for the F.B.I. office in Chicago.
[Sighs]
[Sydney] I doubt you'll find Miss Parker
searching through her desk.
[Broots] We saw her this morning.
I think she had some errands to run.
She didn't say where she was going?
You know your sister. You know she dances
to the beat of a different drummer.
- [Slams Book Closed]
- So I've noticed.
You two wouldn't lie to me, would you?
So, a-anybody see the, uh,
Redskins game this weekend?
Agent Jackson. Any idea when
I might be allowed back in my office?
- No idea.
- Oh. [Sighs]
That's very impressive, the way
you handled that code situation.
I didn't have much of a choice, did I?
Tell me something.
How are insurance claims
processed at this hospital?
In the middle of a hostage situation, and
you're wondering about billing procedure?
I'm just curious.
For instance, an H.M.O. claim.
H.M.O.'s rely on the information
provided by the attending physician.
So a particular medical procedure
would be approved or denied...
- based upon your recommendation.
- Yeah, that.
And the recommendation of
the facilities administrator.
- Rebecca Simons.
- In the case of this hospital, yes.
What percentage of major surgeries
have been denied at this hospital?
- [Sighs] Oh, I-I don't know.
- Take a guess.
[Stammering]
I-I don't know. Fifty percent?
Sixty-eight percent: 11 percentage points
higher than the national average.
- Why do you think that is?
- Maybe there are just a lot
of healthy people in this town.
- Maybe.
- [Helicopter Whirring]
[Dialing Phone]
- [Line Clicking]
- Uh, we need to talk.
[Siren Wailing]
[Scoffs]
You look like hell.
[Chuckling]
That's the way it is when you're dyin'.
Got yourself in a real mess here, boy.
Like everything else in my life.
Look, maybe I didn't do the things
I should have when you were small.
Hell, I- I was makin' it up as I went.
But I taught you kids
right from wrong. I did that.
- I'm tryin' to save you, Dad.
- Why?
Because we're a family.
I never knew my own old man.
Not more than a smack in the head
now and then.
I just did the best that I could, and-
[Sobs]
When your mama died-
I think a little bit of me went too.
Guess we've been fightin'
the same pain.
[Sobbing]
I miss her. Every day.
Me too, Pop.
[Exhales]
[Jarod]
$41,342.17.
This is the exact amount this hospital
charges for heart bypass surgery.
- What are you talkin' about?
- Jake Larsen has sky-high levels
of creatine kinase enzyme...
- in his blood.
- So?
- His fingertips are blue from lack of oxygen.
- I still don't follow.
He has heart disease.
He's headed for a massive heart attack.
His only chance of survival
is heart bypass surgery.
The same surgery
this hospital denied him. [Sighs]
- Who the hell are you?
- Excuse me?
I called the F.B.I. Nobody's ever heard
of an Agent Jarod Jackson.
Well, it's a big agency.
Maybe you talked to the wrong person.
If any of those people in there die,
it's on your head.
You understand what that means, to have
somebody's blood on your hands?
As a matter of fact, I do.
And so do you.
Your deputy told me about that hostage
situation a year ago at the grocery store.
The way you lured that
perpetrator into the doorway...
and hesitated to take the kill shot.
Did he tell you how that same
hostage-taker took his gun...
and shot to death
a 15-year-old stock boy?
Did he describe the sick feeling
I get every time I see
that boy's parents on the street?
- You did what you thought
was the right thing to do.
- And an innocent boy...
lost his life.
That's the blood I have on my hands...
Agent Jackson.
[Siren Wailing]
Certainly has been
a long day, hasn't it?
- Agent Jackson.
- I was wondering if you and I
could have a little talk.
Oh, well, the truth is,
I'm late for a meeting. Perhaps later.
I know about the cover-up concerning
Jake Larsen's coronary disease.
But what could an H.M.O. possibly
have to gain by such a cover-up?
I saw you and Dr. Franklin arguing in
the parking lot. I know what's going on.
We could talk about it here in private,
or we could go downtown...
and talk under the glare
of the television cameras.
It's up to you.
Is it just for the money?
Or is it something more personal?
I see the way you and
Dr. Franklin are together.
My girlfriends and I...
used to dream about meeting a doctor.
Falling in love,
and living happily ever after.
I actually believed that's the way
it would be for Stephen and me.
Your signature is on the release forms
for all the patients in question.
I made my decisions based on
Franklin's recommendations.
I looked the other way in one case,
next thing I knew, I was-
All for money.
Franklin was getting kickbacks from
the H.M.O.'s for not doing expensive surgeries.
By denying certain procedures
to critically ill patients...
he saves the H.M.O.
hundreds of thousands of dollars.
- And makes a nice percentage.
- I swear to you...
I didn't know about Jake Larsen
until his sons took over the hospital.
Franklin said that you questioned him,
and he threatened to expose me...
if I said anything, and-
I was afraid.
Not half as afraid as those patients
who were sent home to die.
- The key you gave me doesn't work.
- Really? Huh.
Must have given you the wrong one.
Here, let me try this one.
- [Key Turning Lock]
- Yep. That works. [Chuckling]
Angel, I'm sorry I had
to drag you into this.
"Baby Parker."
Wh-What was that?
Oh, it's nothing.
- It looked like a medical record.
- It's ancient history.
- It is mine, or Lyle's?
- It doesn't matter!
Trust me. Some day, when I have more time,
I'll explain everything to you.
- But right now, I need your gun.
- My gun?
This is about that hit out on you.
Yeah, the bastards are closin' in.
- Who ordered it?
- I don't know. I don't know.
I do know... this...
is the only thing that really matters.
It's the future of our family.
It's the heir to the Parker name,
and it's growing inside Brigitte.
The baby'll be here soon.
- What else can I do?
- Well, the key is still Jarod.
Bring him back, and
it'll be just like it was.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
[Ringing]
- [Beeping]
- I'm on my way.
[No Audible Dialogue]
[Phone Ringing]
- Yeah?
- Dr. Franklin?
Agent Jackson. Cam and Billy Larsen
have tapped into hospital records...
and are trying to find information
about patients who were denied care.
- Can you cut them off?
- We tried.
I suggest I download everything. I wouldn't
want you to lose any patient records.
No! No, I'll, uh-
I'll handle that.
I-I know which files are important.
Can I get back in my office yet?
I don't think that's a good idea.
Things are still pretty dangerous up here.
I couldn't assure your safety.
Dr. Franklin?
- Dr. Franklin.
- I'm on my way up.
If you think that's best.
[Coughs]
- [Gunshots]
- [Glass Breaking]
- What happened?
- I was shot! The Larsen boys.
They're crazy!
They're coming down the hallway.
They say they know who's responsible
for trying to kill their father.
I've gotta get out of here.
[Grunts]
- Doctor?
- I can't breathe! [Panting]
My heart!
[Groans]
[Panting]
What's happening to me?
The same thing that you
let happen to Jake Larsen.
You're having a massive heart attack.
[Gasping] Wha-
What have you done to me?
I laced your keyboard with
a tricyclic antidepressant.
It's absorbed through the fingertips.
Speeds up the heart's rhythm.
That's why I faked getting shot...
told you that the Larsen boys
were coming down the hallway-
I wanted to scare you. You see, adrenaline,
it really increases the effects of the drug.
- [Gasping] Why?
- Because of what you did to Jake Larsen.
Because of the drugs you gave him to cover
up the symptoms of his coronary disease.
- [Groaning] Who are you?
- I'm everyone.
I'm no one.
If you tell me the truth...
I can bring your heart
back to normal.
Look, we're all on the same
side here- [Grunting]
There's no reason
to let this become a problem.
Oh, it became a problem when
you aligned yourself with an H.M.O....
that cared more about profits
than taking care of patients.
God, Larsen wouldn't have survived
another year no matter what we did.
That is not the point!
You're a doctor!
Your job is to give care,
not take it away!
- [Groans In Pain]
- That cyanosis must really
be setting in right now.
You should really seek treatment.
Or you can die within minutes.
- Please! Please!
- How many people?
How many people did you let die
so you could stuff your pockets?
[Grunts] All right,
I took kickbacks from the H.M.O.'s...
to send patients home-
now please, help me!
- Please!
- Sorry, Doc.
But your claim has been denied.
No! No.
[Sobbing, Groaning]
[Chattering On Police Radio]
- Is he really gonna die?
- I just laced his keyboard with trigoxin.
He has nothing more than
a really bad case of heartburn.
And he'll probably lose
bladder control for a couple of days.
[Chattering On Police Radio]
[Grunting]
- [Sighs]
- [Siren Wailing]
I'm gonna drop some of the charges
against the brothers.
Let the judge deal with the rest.
Considering the circumstances, I think
they've suffered enough for one family.
I think you're right.
Thank you for keeping me
from doing something stupid.
I guess we can't let the mistakes
of our past ruin our future.
Will you excuse me, Sheriff?
Excuse me. Are you
from the Chicago office?
- Are you a reporter?
- Blue Cove Gazette.
Have you been involved
during the entire crisis?
No, I just arrived on the scene.
There was another negotiator involved.
Our source from your Chicago office...
- tells us he was an impostor.
- That's what we've been told.
- And where is he?
- No idea.
I don't know how he did it, but witnesses
say he really knew what he was doing.
Excuse me.
It's your fault we missed him.
[Mr. Parker]
Now don't tell anybody.
Life and death, understand? Someday, when I
have more time, I'll explain everything to you.
Well, the key is still Jarod.
Bring him back,
and it'll be just like it was.
You're gonna be held
accountable for this, Parker.
I know. Let's go home.
www.tvsubtitles.net