I hope recovering this knick-knack of yours
is worth all this waiting.
-A first century Roman glass bowl is hardly a...
Knick-knack.
If it's so priceless why would you ??? with
this Benoit without see any money
I've done what I ever done times before
using ??? with that money
And he was always paid,
he's always paid on time.
Well, if the ??? you
riconsider your businness practices.
What is he look like?
Oh, he's businness *****he's late forties.
Kinda ???
You haven't even met him?
Let's just get this bowl
and get out of here, shall we?
Wow, somebody's cranky.
I came as soon
as you called me.
If I'd known this was a simple
recovery case, I would have...
stopped for a bite first.
-Oh.
-Henry, what is it?
-There's something here.
It's pain and fear and hate.
Suffering.
We're in a no-tell motel.
Worst thing going on is some guy getting busy with
Mary from accounts payable.
There's presences.
Scores of them.
Henry?
Frigobar.
You certainly have the most unconventional methods
I've ever seen.
Your friend is like a bloodhound.
You got the blood part right.
OH!
Okay,
your half hour's up.
Are you okay?
No.
I had, um...
a dream or something.
Looks more like a nightmare.
Yeah, I was....I was with Henry.
I, uh...
We were in a building,
but it was a hotel.
We were walking and
something came towards us.
It was like an energy
or something.
And...?
And I died.
-Cool dream.
-No.
No, it wasn't cool.
And whatever it was,
it tore right through me.
I felt every part of it.
Okay...definitely no more
frozen burritos for lunch.
I need the Ackerman file.
Right.
Oh!
-The goblet!
-Oh, it was an accident.
-I'm sorry.
-I knew you hated it.
-No, I like it fine.
-Ahem, Vickie Nelson?
-We've met.
-I don't think so.
My name is Jacob Keller.
I'm in need of your help.
Stagione 2 Episodio 03
- "5:55" -
Traduzione italiana: Sharkypan87,  Icegirl e AlexandraD.
Revisione: AlexandraD.
www.subsfactory.it
I'm an antiquities dealer,
and I'm looking for a business associate of mine,
Benoit Fournier.
Benoit Fournier...
You know him?
I don't think so.
Well, he's hired me to
track down a piece for him.
It's a Roman glass bowl.
Now I shipped it to him over a month ago
and I haven't received any payment yet.
His phone number's not listed
and I can't seem to find him.
I'm beginning to fear that
I'm a victim of fraud here.
Well, where did you send it?
Well, I use a bonded courier,
and all they'll give me is the billing address,
which happens to be a mailbox at the photocopy shop.
Do you often do business with
people you know nothing about?
Yes.
Well, he's a very wealthy man
and, well, you could say,
an offbeat individual.
He doesn't like people
knowing where he lives.
He really sounds
on the up and up.
My business caters
to a lot of eccentric people.
I've learned not to ask
any questions.
When you're poor,
you're crazy.
When you're rich,
you're eccentric, right?
I can't tell you the resources
I've used to find this bowl.
But, if I don't find him,
and get paid,my business won't survive.
I'll look into it.
Okay, well...
here's my card.
Please call me anytime,day or night,
as soon as you find anything.
All right.
All righty, then.
Oh, hey there.
This is Emmy Lou from Union Courier.
To whom am I speaking with?
Oh hi, Gary.
Listen, I'm in a bit of a pickle
and I'm wondering
if you could do me a bitty bit of a favour?
Aren't you precious.
Oh, I bet you're just as cute
as a specked pup in a red wagon.
It's a shame you
live so far away.
Well, listen Gary,
we have a package here addressed to box number 413 at your address.
And we have a strict policy of
not delivering to mailboxes.
So, I was fixing to see
if you'd be able to give me the registrant's address
so we can deliver this package properly.
Oh, now come on, Gary.
This ain't my first rodeo.
I know you all
got that address.
A numbered company, huh?
22 Corrigan.
Oh, Gary, you are just sweeter
than a Tennessee...
Williams.
Don't!
Do one thing for me.
Tell me you've always depended
on the kindness of strangers.
Well, if that don't put
the pepper in the gumbo,
I don't know what would.
I have to get in there!
My piece!
Stop!
Just keep him here.
Hey, John
M.E. says he couldn't
have been dead more than a hour.
And the guy next door?
Says he only ever talked to him once,
but he thought he was a bit of a nut job.
I noticed a bloody
shoeprint by the bookcase.
Yes, I already have
F.I.S. on it.
They'll have a brand
in an hour or two.
Nice work, Kate.
Is that Benoit Fournier?
-Oh, this can't be good.
-Thanks for the warm welcome.
Any other time but
a homicide, right?
So...
what?
You're going to tell me
that he was killed by the bog monster or a basilisk?
No, actually I'm just here
to retrieve a piece of Roman glass.
I can't believe this.
The first normal case I get and the guy I need to talk to turns up dead.
What happened?
Well, we got a single
stab wound to the abdomen.
The place was obviously torn apart.
Looks like a struggle.
Yeah, he's got defensive wounds on his hands.
Is that your lucky tie?
No, it's just a tie.
It's just your lucky tie.
Who were you hoping
to get lucky with?
Look, it's not
just lucky like that.
Look, this is the same tie that
you gave me after we solved the Aries murders, right?
For me, it's just work related.
Okay, yes.
When we got the call Kate
and I were out celebrating the Nicholls cold case.
Yeah, I heard about that.
Congratulations.
Who would have thought
it was the old man, huh?
Oh, clearly not me.
We worked that case for, what?
Six months solid?
Kate opens it up last week.
She said she had a hunch about the scratches
on the old man's wheel well.
That's quite a hunch.
I'm sure we would have solved it
if we'd had enough time, okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
So, who's this
client of yours?
A guy named Jacob Keller.
He's been with me for
the last hour and a half,
so don't get your hopes up.
Okay, just covering the bases.
Every one.
So you went out celebrating
wearing your lucky tie...
with her.
Yeah.
Entirely professional.
It's just a tie, Vicki.
-He'd dead.
-What do you mean he's dead?
Looks like he was robbed.
We have to get it back.
They must have some idea who killed him.
Excuse me! A man is dead!
But I still owe money to the
people who sold me that piece!
I have to get it back.
Are you going to help me or not?
I may know where your
package is going to be tonight.
Okay, I think it's time you
told me what's going on here.
How do you know the bowl
wasn't in Benoit's office?
The police believe the killer
robbed him and got away.
I know.
Benoit had an appointment to buy the bowl jotted down
on a note pad in his office.
That could have been
last week, last night.
It could have been
a business lunch.
Did you ever have the feeling,
like you've been somewhere before?
Like ??, paramnesia?
Kinda, only this is like
more than that.
This isn't exactly
a place I'd visit twice,
even in a deja vù.
A guy and a girl
go out for a drink.
Is that a date?
-What is that about?
I was just wondering.
I mean, is a drink an implied sexual advance?
Other than our strange,sexless relationship we seem to share,
I don't have much experience in the world
of 'dating'.
Really?
So you don't get your groove on before you put the bite on?
My relationships are usually intense and passionate
from the first glance.
I don't need to make
a sexual advance.
I am one.
-I hate it when you do that.
-I know.
What is all this
line of questioning?
Oh, I was just wondering
why a guy would wear his lucky tie to work.
I mean, especially when he was going out
with a strange woman later on.
This hypothetical guy
we're talking about,
what would be so wrong if he was wearing his special tie
he believed would help him get lucky?
Well, because maybe the person who gave it to him would be hurt
if she saw him wearing it with some bimbo.
Okay, now I'm starting to sense that this guy
and this bimbo might actually be people we know.
The tie donor, too,for that matter.
Look, if it's any consolation,
I believe it takes much more than silk accessory to win a woman over.
Oh, come on, don't you have
some kind of lucky shirt
or, I don't know,
socks or something?
Well, I do have a bonnet Anne Boleyn gave to me right
before she tried to poison me.
And I am still here,
so I guess that's lucky.
Forget I asked.
-Uh...excuse me.
-Keller?
Any idea of where
my package is?
Yeah, I do, um...
but I think we have to hurry.
I hope recovering this knick-knack of yours
is worth all this waiting.
-A first century Roman glass bowl is hardly a...
-Knick-knack.
-You're hungry, aren't you?
-I could eat.
-You haven't eaten all day.
-How did you know that?
-She did it again.
-What do you mean, again?
I told you.
I've been here before.
Well, that should make
the rest of this case exceedingly simple.
Where do we go from here?
I don't know.
We'd just started looking for the thing
and then something happened.
-Something like...?
-Like we kinda died.
Excuse me, what are
you two talking about?
-You feel it, don't you?
-The energy?
How did you know that?
It's hate and fear
and pain and suffering.
Him!
I think that's the guy.
OH!
Ugh...
Is that it?
That's it!
-Keller! No!
-No! Keller!
HENRY!
Arrggghhh...!
Okay,
your half hour's up.
Are you okay?
-Where's Keller?
-Who's Keller?
A twitchy guy
wearing glasses.
Came in looking
for a Benoit Fournier.
I know.
Can you believe it?
-Thirty years.
-Is this yesterday's?
No, today's.
OH!
The goblet!
-I knew you never...
-I liked it fine.
Forget about the goblet.
Coreen, it's the same day!
-Keller!
-Do I know you?
-You lied to me!
-I haven't even said anything yet.
What is it?
What's in the box?
-How could you know about the box?
-Never mind, you just tell me the truth this time.
This time?
I know what it can do.
The box you want me to look for, what is it?
It's a piece...it's something that I recovered.
I'm an antiques dealer.
Yeah, you're Jacob Keller.
You're an antiquities dealer,
and you're looking
for Benoit Fournier.
You're about to tell me that
it's a Roman glass bowl,
and you sold it to him.
But what you're really looking for is some kind of box.
And I think you're looking for it the same way
that he is.
How could you possibly know that?
Just tell me what's in the box!
I don't know what's inside the box.
Wrong answer!
It has mystical powers
that's associated with it.
Some say it can prolong life,
give you supernatural powers.
I think it does a whole
hell of a lot more than that.
Let's go save your
friend Benoit.
-You know where he is?
-Yeah, I do,
and in about 15 minutes
he's going to be dead.
What's the rush?
We gotta go see a man about a box.
Okay.
I don't understand.
Who would want to kill Benoit?
Well, if you weren't with us,
you'd be my first suspect.
So you're saying
he actually has the box?
No, I think he's going
to buy it tonight at the Empire Hotel.
Wait a second.
How do you know that?
-Call it a hunch.
-A hunch is when you think it's going to rain tomorrow.
This is play by play.
Just trust me, okay?
Henry!
Janitor!
-Vick?
-I don't care what you say,
a lucky tie means a date.
Where the hell did that come from?
I know...two cops out for a beer after work.
Isn't that how we started?
Well, yeah, that and a 10-37.
Yeah, we'll always
have aggravated assault.
Okay, look,
did I miss something here?
I feel like I've walked into the middle of a fight
that we haven't even had yet.
What the hell are you doing here anyway?
Do you want to hear a theory?
The assailant came in dressed as a janitor looking for something,
which we now know he didn't find.
In the course of looking he got into an altercation
with Benoit Fournier and stabbed him.
-Questions?
-One.
Who's Benoit Fournier?
Oh.
Okay, I mean, is that a date?
A guy and a girl can go out
for a drink without it being a date?
Even if he is wearing his lucky tie?
I wouldn't know.
-Aside from our strange...
-I know, we have a strange relationship and you've never been much for dating.
Why do I feel like I don't
have to be in this conversation?
It makes sense, doesn't it?
Them?
-Absolutely.
-What?
Well, it's not like
you've snapped him up.
And with him seeing someone,
you might want to take this opportunity to move on as well.
To someone special.
Someone who deserves you.
Right.
Someone who'll be snacking on a different girl in his bed every night of the week.
Everybody has their flaws.
Speaking of which...
I know, I called
before you had time to.
What about her?
She looks like your type.
Keller?
What are you doing here?
Well, you said they were
going to make the exchange.
-I can help.
-Of course you can.
He came from this direction.
All right, we're going
to end this right here.
He's going to be coming through
that door right about...
now.
Ooomph!
Okay, you are going to tell
us what the hell is going on.
Stop it!
??
NO!
Okay, your half hour's up.
Okay, Keller's going to
be coming in here looking for me again,
and I want you to
hold him here until I get back.
What do you mean again?
Who's Keller?
Hey, it's me.
I'll be downstairs so stay in the car.
Wait!
I need the Ackerman file.
It's on my desk.
-Where are you going?
-Later.
OH! The goblet!
Okay, so you had a client come in today
looking for a business associate of his, Benoit.
But what he's really looking for is
a box Benoit is on his way to buy.
Yeah, it's a box.
It's an ancient box,
and the's something inside,
some kind of mystical energy.
And it is evil,
more evil than you could imagine.
You died.
I died.
-Everyone died.
-If I might say so,
you're looking awfully appealing
for someone who's dead.
Henry, listen,
my marks glowed.
Something kept me alive.
You think because Astaroth has marked you
that other evil can't touch you?
Maybe, I don't know.
Maybe he's saving me for something,
and if that's the case,
I'm going to use it.
Don't!
Do not begin to think that you're on the right side of evil,
that you can beat it.
That's part of its seduction.
I watched us die
three times tonight.
And if I have a chance to stop it,
I'm going to take it.
-Vicki, please.
-Henry, I may have been marked by that thing,
but I am not going to be fate's bitch.
Benoit Fournier?
Who are you?
And what are you
doing in my office?
My name is Vicki Nelson.
I'm a private investigator.
I was hired by Jacob Keller.
I'm sure I don't know
anybody by that name.
Please, Mr. Fournier,
I need you to come with me.
You're in danger.
Madam, with
all due respect...
It's about the box.
I don't know anything about any boxes.
Henry?
You're coming with us.
Come on.
You have no idea what you're
getting yourself into with that box.
Nonsense.
How could something so beautiful be dangerous?
Trust me.
I've seen it, up close and personal.
Twenty-five years. It's taken me 25 years
to locate that box and
I'll be damned if I'm going to let you stop me now.
Like, I got here too soon.
- But Vicki said...
- I don't care what she said,
- I have to be on my way.
- But Mr. Keller, please!
I can't let you go yet.
She'll be here any minute and she really wants
to talk to you.
Why would she want to talk
to me? I don't even know her!
I have no idea.
She was a little weird this morning.
She gets like that sometimes.
But you have to trust her,
because it's when she's
the craziest that she's most right.
I don't care. If you don't let me out
that door right this second, I'm going to have to...
What what?
- You!
- Hello, Keller.
Your goons may have brought me here,
but that won't get you the box.
Be careful who you call a goon.
How dare you put a price on it, like it's one
of your little trinkets.
That is a priceless
artifact, my friend.
I'm sorry if myove of beauty offends your
holarly sensibilities.
Enough!
Hey, whatever either of you
think you know about this box,
it doesn't matter.
It is about to fall into the wrong hands
and we have to stop it.
- Keep them here.
-  Wait...!
No one leaves.
Sit down!
But you don't understand!
I have to get out of here.
SIT DOWN NOW!
Okay.
I will never get tired
of the way that you do that.
It's awesome.
Hey, Mike, it's me.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
I know you're out celebrating
that cold case.
No, I am not following you.
Listen, Mike, I need you to meet
me at the Empire Hotel tonight.
I'll explain everything there.
It's urgent.
Yeah, it's one of those cases.
But I gotta tell you, this one is stnge,
even for me.
Thank you.
A magic box?
And you're re-living
the same day over and over?
I told you it was
strange, even for me.
Actually, the only thing
that would be strange is
if there was nothing strange.
Look at you.
You're learning.
Vicki, I went to bed last
night, I woke up this morning.
Today is today.
- Yeah, for the fourth time.
- It can't be.
>> How do you know?
>> Because.
How do you know
it's not four times?
it's not a hundred?
How do you know that it doesn't
keep happening until fate
gets everything straight?
Mike, he's the guy
who had the box!
He's dead.
Darryl Forman.
You know him?
Sort of.
I mean, he's the guy
who's supposed
to be selling the box.
Well, if he's selling it and
the two buyers are corralled back at your office,
- who the hell has it?
- I don't know.
Oh, wait...
There was another guy
back at Benoit's office.
He was dressed
in a janitor's uniform.
Henry and I saw him before
we stopped the other murder.
another murder?
- We already stopped it.
- You stopped a murder?t.
- Mike, stay with me.
- Hey, I have to call this in.
Come on!
Vicki!
- That's him!
- Police!
Hold it right there!
Drop the briefcase!
What are you doing?
I didn't do anything.
Well, you've got nothing
to worry about then.
Vicki...
DON'T DO IT!
DON'T OPEN IT!
Vick?
- DON'T LOOK AT IT!
- Vicki?
Okay, your half hour's...up?
Have you ever seen this symbol?
Maybe... I can't place it, though.
Okay, I need you
to do some research.
Find out whatever connection it
might have to some kind of box.
A guy named Jacob Keller
is going to come in here
looking for me.
Don't worry, Henry's on his way.
He will help.
Phone...
My goblet! I knew you hated it.
You know what?I don't hate it.
Okay, I'm sorry I broke the goblet.
But listen, fate is not going to beat us.
We are going to live our day the way we want it to.
Am I right?
- Yes?
- Right! Good!
Nonsense. How could something
so beautiful be dangerous?
You have no idea what
you're getting yourself into.
How could you
possibly know this?
- Where is it?
- I don't have it!
- I don't have it.
- Where is it?
- Drop the knife!
- No, no, no.
- You don't even understand.
- No, you don't understand.
Drop it!
It's the bloody janitor!
And don't think I'm not
going to press charges.
- Vicki said...
- I don't care what she said!
I have to be on my way.
- You're not going anywhere.
- She'll be here any minute
and I know she really wants to talk to you.
Why would she want to talk to me?
I don't even know her.
Sit... down!
Okay, so Vicki woke up babbling
about a broken goblet, fate,
and told you to keep him
here, and then ran out.
I think she's finally snapped.
Vicki Nelson Investigations.
Hey Coreen, it's me.
I need you to get Henry
toring Keller down to the station.
Okay.Is everything all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Did you find anything
about that symbol?
Oh, yeah.
It's a symbol for a secret
society called the Knights of Babylon.
The Knights of Babylon?
One of your lesser
known secret societies.
They're not sure exactly when
they were started,
but a lot of the legends say it was
in the 15th century when they came into possession of -
listen to this -
Pandora's Box.
Pandora's Box?
As in...Pandora's Box?
- The one and only.
- The one Zeus gave her and told her never to open.
But she did and released all
the misfortunes of mankind.
Just once...once...
couldn't a myth be a myth?
I've been reading up on it.
A lot of scholars say it
wasn't Pandora's fault.
They say there's no living
creature that can handle the box
without giving in to the
temptation to open it.
I think we can prove them
wrong on that one, though,
I mean, who would be dumb
enough to unleash a tidal wave of evil into the world?
Yeah...who'd do that?
- How do you know Benoit?
- Who's Benoit?
How about the guy you
were planning to kill?
I wasn't going
to hurt anybody.
Right.
You were just coming for
a visit and forgot you happened
to have a knife in your hand.
Is that it?
What were you doing
in his office?
What office?
You do realize we're just
going to keep doing this
over and over until you
give me some answers.
How do you know Benoit?
Get anything on
that name I gave you?
Yeah, Darryl Forman.
He graduated top of his class,
did some military service in
Europe, and then disappeared off the books.
There are records of border
crossings here and there,
but for the most part, he's an enigma.
Just like this one.
Vicki, I don't
know how you...
I don't care if you
and Mike go out for drinks.
But...
you just....
Thanks.
Was Mike going to
ask me out?
I don't know.
What Mike does is
his business, right?
I'm charging him
with assault, but I have
no proof of attempted murder.
You have proof.
You have me.
I saw him die...
twice.
Right, because...
Because you're re-living
the same day.
You really think that's
going to hold up, do you?
Where are Fournier
and Keller?
They're being
released right now.
Mike, you can't do that!
I told you what they did.
Vicki, what am I supposed
to do?
Hold him overnight?
At least until I get the box.
The laws haven't changed
since you left the job, okay?
I need to be able to
charge him with something, and buying antiques
isn't a crime.
Well, it didn't use to be.
this has all gone wrong.
Look, if you need me,
I will be at the Empire Hotel.
It's going to hit the fan at
midnight and I need to be there.
Okay, hold up.
I'm coming with you.
I don't know why.
Okay, so everything else
you've called has come true.
The woman dropping the tray, the
guy whistling at the front desk.
Even finding a free parking
space in this part of town.
Now that's eerie.
So basically we can expect
to see this Forman guy walk
through that door any minute now.
No, not any minute.
This minute.
Okay, hey, hey, hey!
That's far enough.
- Drop the briefcase.
- Carefully.
Mike!
Mike?
MIKE!
Mike!
Mike?
Come on, you're getting blood
all over your lucky tie.
Yeah...
Mike...
Hey...
Hey...Mike...
Mike! Mike!
Mike...!
Bring me the box!
- What?
- I can go back!
I can change this!
Who's to say the same thing
won't happen over again?
Because, I won't let it!
If it weren't for me,
he'd...he'd be alive!
He'd have gone out with Kate.
He would have had a chance to be happy.
There are some things
you can't change, Vicki.
There's not!
- Nothing is preordained.
- What do you want to do?
You want to keep opening the
box until everything is okay?
I have the box.
We've won.
No, we haven't.
Not like this.
Please, please...
Please.
You'd die for him,
wouldn't you?
Please.
- Okay, your ...
- ...half hour's up.
I know.
Here's the Ackerman file.
- Yeah, Cellucci.
- Mike?
Hey, Vick.
Vicki, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, you wearing that tie?
The one I gave you the night we
cracked that triple homicide in Cabbagetown?
Yeah, I am.
The one after the
triple homicide.
What's going on?
Nothing I just
... I gotta go.
I'll call you soon, okay?
No, Vicki, wait.
Hey, have a good time tonight ok?
Vick!
Hey Mike, what do you
say we head to Lavey's for a few drinks after work?
Celebrate breaking the Nicholls homicide?
Yeah, sure, why not.
Nice tie.
Thanks.
Coreen, I'm giving you the
rest of the day off, okay?
Go home.
Get out of here as soon as
you can and don't come back.
But I was just about to...
Do it at home.
Cool.
And I'm taking your
meeting at the Empire Hotel.
He's going to keep you safe.
What do you
mean, 'keep me safe'?
Well....
Gotcha.
Board Room.
Here we go.
Hi. Sorry, I just got to drop
these off for the conference tomorrow.
Put it down and get out.
Sure.
- Where is it?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
The box!
Enough people have died.
I don't mind making it one more.
You have no idea
what you've done.
- How many people you've hurt.
- Put the box down.
This has nothing to do with you.
It sure does.
You're one of them.
You both are.
I know all about it.
I know all about Pandora's Box
and the Knights of Babylon.
Then you know that it has
go back to where it belongs.
Our Order has been protecting
it for hundreds of years.
And what's a few dead
bodies along the way, huh?
To save it from
the rest of the world,
I'd say one or two
bodies are worth it.
Why does he have it?
He professed to have
a vocation and was brought
into the fold.
But all he was doing was biding
his time until he got close
enough to the box to steal it.
He betrayed a sacred trust.
Don't do it!
Put the gun down!
I told you, this has
nothing to do with you.
It does, all right?
I've opened it.
I saw myself and
everyone I know, die.
Then what's coming next
won't be a huge shock to you.
I'd never open it!
I've been trained!
Just the same...
I really don't care.
It goes where I know
it will be safe.
- How can he do that?
- He's not opening it.
No living person
can resist it.
He falls into an entirely
different category.
I'll be happy when this
is sealed up in the wall of my apartment.
- It's been a long day.
- I know.
- And I haven't ...
- ...even fed yet.
I know.
I wanted to thank you for
everything you did today.
Everything you did in the
last few hours...
days...
day.
tell you the truth,
I don't have experience of anything except this last time.
You ended the world for me.
Because you believed
I could bring it back.
You trusted me.
Trust can be
extremely stimulating.
It can at that.
Do you mind?
- What time is it?
- Five to six.
I know...
you've been sleeping all day,
but I didn't want to wake you.
It looks like you had
a late one last night.
Yeah.
Is that today's paper?
Yeah?
Finally.
Vick?
- Um...I'm going ...
- Yeah.
Vick?
Hey, you okay?
You sounded a little
frazzled on the phone there
when we spoke.
Did you ever have one
of those days that you wish
you could just reset
and start over?
All the time.
Well, I had one of those.
Well, I'm glad
that you're okay now.
You kind of had
me worried there.
How was your date?
- My date?
- With Kate.
Oh, we just...had some drinks
to celebrate solving the case.
I mean, it wasn't a date,
it was just ...
...two cops having a drink.
Exactly.
What?
I just came by to tell you
that I'm happy you're okay.
Thanks.
You know, it's good seeing
you around here.
It's like nothing
ever changes, huh?
Almost nothing.
welcome to www.1000fr.com