Deeds.
Nelson.
Wow! Undercover does
not agree with you.
You look like hell.
You've had better days
yourself, babe.
Thanks, so to what
do I owe the pleasure?
I heard you were
in the crazy business.
Yeah, you know if I wanted
to be insulted before my first
coffee, I would have continued
working with Cellucci.
I came to you because I may
need your help with a homicide.
You're a cop.
You know how to work a case.
This one's a little
different.
Why?
Who died?
Me.
Okay, why don't we start
at your place?
I went to my apartment first.
Everything's just like I left
it - no sign of a break-in.
No sign of your...body?
It sounds worse when you
actually say it.
What do you mean apartment?
Didn't you have a house
in the Beaches?
Divorce cleaned me out.
You blew another marriage?
We're trying to find
my lifeless body
and you're busting my balls
over my marital problems?
One divorce is a problem.
Four is a one-man
catastrophe zone.
About the death thing?
Right. Sorry.
I mean, I've been living
on the edge a long time...
dying I can handle.
The question is,
why am I a ghost?
>> Hm.
You see that?
If I can't pick something up,
how come I can sit down?
Well, my guess is, that if
you think about it too much
you can't do it.
But when you're not trying
so hard, you can.
You see?
Maybe I came to the
right place after all.
All right.
So where else...where else
could your body be?
>> I've been working undercover,
riding with a bike gang.
Chances are we're not talking
about a tidy
little aneurysm here.
Okay, so who was
your supervisor?
Fry.
You remember him?
Yup. All right.
When was your last check-in?
I talked to Fry...
I can't remember.
I mean, I probably report
to the guy every day, but...
Maybe it's some trauma
related to the death,
that's why you can't remember.
Remember what?
What death?
Coreen, this is Paul Deeds,
we used to work together.
Is Paul invisible?
No, he's a ghost.
You don't have to whisper,
Nelson, I know I'm a ghost.
I can't believe it.
He's right there.
He passes through doorways.
He can't pick anything up.
I could give her a try.
I mean I can't believe
there's a ghost in the room
and you're the one who
gets to see him.
Red thong.
Are you wearing a red thong?
Cool.
And observant.
Classy.
Vicki >> I would have gone
to Paul's supervisor myself,
but you know, he's never
going to be straight with me.
Mike >> Oh, I know.
Undercover is so unfair.
They won't tell
civilians anything.
Ah, yes, but you,
oh distinguished officer
of the law,
you could ask him.
And why the sudden
interest in Paul Deeds?
He's a client.
Sort of.
Oh, wow.
There's a whole world
of intrigue in that 'sort of'.
I don't even know
why I hesitate anymore.
He's a ghost.
A ghost.
>> A ghost.
>> So did he just come
rattling his chains to you,
moaning that he had a case?
No, no chains, just
leather and denim.
Essentially yeah, that's i
All right.
Look, if he's a ghost,
then that means that he's dead.
And if he's dead,
then there will be a hundred
cops all over this case.
Well, you see, that's
where he has a problem.
There's no body,
not yet.
Paul 'Dirty' Deeds -
make the bust no matter what.
>> He sure closed
a lot of cases.
Yeah, he just didn't
care how he made that close.
You gotta figure that has
something to do
with why he's dead.
>> What are you saying?
I'm saying that
I never trusted the guy.
So it doesn't matter then
that somebody offed a cop?
>> No, I'm just saying
that even then,
he probably had
some kind of angle.
He's not here now, is he?
>> No.
Oh, apparently I'm the only
person who can see him.
Of course you are.
So are you going
to ask Fry or what?
Yeah, but I think
I'll skip the ghost part.
Good call.
>> Okay.
Stripes and checks,
it's interesting.
>> Bye.
Henry >> I have very little
experience with ghosts,
and this one I don't see.
>> Ummmm...
oh.
Paul >> What the hell is this?
Ah! He's in your bedroom.
>> What's he doing there?
Um...cops have a natural
curiosity.
Remind him that
curiosity killed the cat.
Right.
Hey, Paul, you want
to get out of there?
My friend may have
some skeletons in his closet.
Whoa!
Tell me about it!
Do you see him now?
>> I'm glad I don't.
What does he remember
of his demise?
Nothing much so far.
So you have a dead client
who doesn't know how he died.
Vicki, I don't like this.
Mmm...is there a...
It just hit me.
Are you guys...?
>> No.
Oh, so you and Mike
are still getting it...?
No, no, no, no.
>> Then maybe I got a shot?
Do you remember
anything or not?
>> Vicki...
>> Standard.
He says he was
at the Standard.
It's a biker bar.
It's kind of a....
I know it.
I don't always hunt
in the opera circuit.
One has to vary one's diet.
Everybody enjoys a little
fast food now and again.
Paul >> Girl.
He says that he was there.
He met a girl.
He didn't know her previously.
How do you know he
is who he says he is?
Look, I know him, okay?
And no one's going to
investigate his death
without a body.
How did he get to you?
Same reason as everything
else gets to me these days.
Apparently
I'm a ghost beacon, too.
Cowley >> Detective Deeds
has been riding undercover
with the Wolverines for
over two years as Paul Pevere.
His cover has him
as an ex-con with experience
in international drug shipments.
Wolverines have had a run of
tough luck lately, haven't they?
One of their members was
killed recently, right?
And a drug shipment stolen,
and a club house fire-bombed.
Well, if they're feeling
targeted, that's just going to
make them even more dangerous.
>> There's a lot of pressure
on organized crimes to use
Deeds' Intel soon,
to make a trafficking case.
>> What? Just trafficking?
>> That's all I'm supposed
to know.
And it is certainly all
I am telling you
without more information.
At this point
I don't have much.
I just got a tip that Deeds
might be in a little trouble.
You do realize they made us
out for cops the moment
we walked in here, right?
>> So?
t means they're paying
attention to the cops
on the outside and not
the one on the inside.
Works for everyone.
You worked under Deeds.
Yeah, yeah, good cop,
lousy person.
Yeah, he was a good cop.
> Was?
>> Is.
Maybe 'was'.
Internal Affairs
is taking a look at him.
They think he'sent?
I'm telling you because
I trust you, Cellucci,
but it goes no further
than this table.
Not your partner,
not your shrink, nobody.
Understood.
In the last couple of months,
he hasn't produced
anything we can use.
We were counting on Intel
to put a lot of Wolverines away.
There is some concern that he
might be a little crooked.
That's like being
a little pregnant, isn't it?
I guess we'll know
soon enough.
When you called, I wondered
if you might know something.
It doesn't fit with the
general picture I have.
I just spoke with an outside
source that said, um...
Said that Deeds might
be in a little trouble.
He knows how
to play the part.
Yeah, the question is,
who is he playing it for?
Coreen >> If you ever want to be
convinced about the one world
concept, every culture's
got vampires, ghosts,
body snatchers, werewolves.
We're all afraid
of the same things.
Henry >> Um-hum.
In most countries ghosts
remain behind because of
unfinished business
or dissatisfaction.
If Paul was murdered I suppose
that meets both requirements,
right?
You're a vampire
reading about vampirism.
Like you've never
read a self-help book?
What are you looking for?
This situation reminds
me of a myth I heard.
Early vampires who would
visit the living.
At first they'd seem benign,
but then they would strip
a person's life force.
>> Paul came to Vicki for help.
Not knowing how
or when he died.
Not knowing where his body is.
Dragging Vicki into who knows
what kind of situation.
You don't think
he is who he says he is?
Ever since Vicki and I met,
supernatural things
have been drawn to her.
This very well could be
the ghost of Paul Deeds.
But it also might be
something very different.
Astaroth?
Or something he sent
to do his dirty work.
If you'd excuse me.
You take all the fun out
of supernatural sometimes.
You rang?
Paul?
Oh, Vicki!
You're a sight for sore eyes.
What are you doing here?
Ask Serpico.
Giving organized crime an
assist with a Wolverine murder
I thought that Paul here,
might be able to help.
Threw me over the car,
cuffed me.
I thought he was going to
take me down to Cherry Beach
and beat me.
>> Well, we had to make
it look good, didn't we?
>> Mmmmm.
You look yummy.
You don't.
You're burning up.
That's because I'm lovesick.
Why don't we spend a dirty
weekend in the Bahamas
together, baby?
>> Yeah, you bring me back
that snowball from hell
and we'll talk.
Same old Vicki.
Same old Paul.
>> Yeah.
Are you sure you're okay?
>> What?
Why this sudden concern
with my health?
I don't know.
Does the cow know
it's misng that?
>> You want a bite?
No, thanks.
>> A little red meat
never hurt anybody.
Unlike the swill they call
coffee around here,
but I love it, love it.
The Paul I met, he couldn't
pick up a sandwich,
let alone hug me.
>> Yeah, mostly what I noticed
was Paul walking around.
That fever,
did you feel that?
Vicki, the man is alive.
Yeah, apparently so.
Did you find out
what he was up to?
Is up to.
>> What's a verb tense
between friends?
>> Okay look, you know how
I'm supposed to trust you
on this Paul-is-dead-thing?
Well, I'm following up on
something, and if and when
it pans out,
I'll let you know.
Will you call me later?
>> Yeah.
Ew!
> I hear Vicki's walking
on the wild side.
You know - werewolf ate my baby,
vampire killed my boyfriend,
that sort of thing.
We're not really that close.
So this 'Spanky' Edwards
murder...
Who do the Wolverines
think did it?
Bartender >> I don't remember.
Henry >> Take a closer look.
My eyesight's not so good.
>> He may have met a woman.
Lucky man.
> Tell me if you saw
him two nights ago.
> Yeah, this guy, he was
here when that girl came in.
Seemed like the sort who knew
what she was looking for.
> Just happened to be him.
Yeah, I guess, but I don't
think they knew each other.
What happened?
They started talking,
talking led to dancing, close.
Next time I looked back
they were disappearing
into the washroom.
I was just hoping they
remembered to lock the door.
A few minutes later,
the guy comes out
and books out the door.
>> And the girl?
She came back in here,
and sat right there.
Seemed kind of funny...
I figured maybe she was stoned.
Then she just keeled over.
Fainted?
Died.
Mike >> You busy?
I had a pretty interesting
conversation with Paul Deeds.
I heard. Bringing him in
was not a good idea.
He's a Wolverine.
We talked about
the Wolverine murder.
I don't think he suspects
anything deeper to it.
>> Maybe.
So, what was so interesting?
I asked him who he thought
was targeting the Wolverines.
He likes the Only Ones for it.
>> Could be.
They're ambitious.
O.C. has a detective
inside the Only Ones.
He said they didn't do it.
Maybe Deeds isn't as good
at his job as he thinks he is.
Or maybe he's got reasons of
his own to hide information.
>> Or maybe Deed's isn't
stealing from the Wolverines.
Maybe he's selling them out.
To who?
>> I don't know,
maybe another gang,
maybe another agency.
I think it's worth
following up on.
Give it another day.
Yeah, you got it.
Paul >> Are you telling me
I'm not dead?
>> No, I'm telling you that your
body is still walking around.
I don't know, it might be some
kind of demonic possession.
You know, your spirit's being
ousted to make room
for something else.
Like some kind of
spiritual squatter?
Coreen's at some underground
library researching it
right now.
It's just that a sudden
penchant for red meat
isn't much of a clue.
The guy's killing
my health regime.
You're taking
this awfully well.
You figure out how I can
hit something and I will.
Well, your body is still
hanging out with the Wolverines
so that kind of rules
them out as suspects.
Who else would want you dead?
Seriously dead or
just a little dead?
Two lists?
What is wrong with you?
> You don't take on
undercover to make friends.
What, like you don't have lists?
See, I knew you and I weren't
that different, Nelson.
You catch a case, you
don't stop until it's done.
You don't care who or what
gets in your way.
No, no, there's
always a line.
Oh, yeah?
Mrs. Donovan...
the firebug's wife.
You gave te t interview.
Talked about
how he killed that kid.
You did everything you could
to get him set up
as a dangerous offender.
He pulls life, and three days
later she comes after you
with a butcher knife.
Yeah, with a crazy ass
gleam in her eye.
See?
Everybody's got lists.
It's just, I think I would
handle that differently now.
That's where we part ways,
Nelson.
You see mistakes and think
you can learn from them.
Are you saying
you can't learn?
I don't see mistakes.
Vicki >> This is the girl
Paul met at the bar?
Henry >> She dropped dead
right after he left.
Mohadevan >> How old
do you think she is?
Vicki >> Early twenties?
>> Precisely, on the outside.
But on the inside she has
the cellular structure
of a seventy-year-old woman.
Her liver is darker
and smaller.
She has advanced
arteriosclerosis of the heart.
I found atrophy
in all the tissue.
It'sascinating.
>> Isn't there that aging
disease?
>> Progeria, but she's
too old for that.
>> Correct, and progeria
is genetic.
This girl is normal
in every respect.
It's just like she's burned out.
What do you think caused it?
>> I haven't the slightest idea.
Is there anything else
besides the aging?
>> Her diet was terrible
but hardly terminal -
a stomach full of raw meat.
[pager beeps]
Excuse me.
Paul's body was chowing
down on raw steak today.
>> This girl was his last
memory, or at least
the last memory he told
you about, anyway.
Paul >> Wow! Vicki!
Oh, we meet again.
I must be living right.
Though, I have to wonder,
what are you doing here?
>> She's a friend of a friend.
>> Hm.
>> Do you know her?
>> Me? No, no friend.
Just in the neighborhood.
>> I'll tell you,
for someone who's undercover,
you're awfully visible.
>> Who's he?
>> My chiropractor.
Henry >> You never know when
something needs to be cracked.
Yeah, I guess you have time
now to take care of your health.
Tough break, though, having to
leave the job you love.
This one has its benefits.
You haven't changed.
You're one of those cops
who are going to die
with their boots on.
>> Yeah, just like you, right?
>> Yeah. We've got that
in common all right.
Too bad.
She's pretty.
You never know what's
coming for you, right?
>> Okay, now I know you don't
know him, but that man
is not right.
>> That doesn't mean
the thing that contacted you
is Paul.
When you're a cop you have
to learn to trust your gut.
And I'm telling you,
that was not Paul Deeds.
My client is.
>> Okay, fine.
you want me to kill him now?
It's lovely to know that's
an option, but perhaps
we'll save that for later.
Later.
Mike >> Hey, Dave, it's me.
He
I'm outside the
Alleycats Body Rub.
It's an Asian gang, right?
Dragons, right.
Do you know if there's
a turf war going on
between the Dragons
and the Wolverines?
That's what I thought.
Listen, see if you can
find out any info
on an attractive Dragon girl,
late twenties, she's driving
a black porche, can't make
out the plates just yet.
Yeah, thanks.
Paul >> Hello, beautiful.
Anyone can see
us here, idiot!
>> Idiot, ha! It turns me on
when you call me idiot.
You're the one
who's committing suicide.
Your boys just took over
another Wolverine operation.
I am here for my thank you.
Your thank you was
already delivered.
>> Cash? That isn't the
thank you I'm looking for.
Forget it.
Don't say no right away,
baby, I brought you a gift.
Your active file with th
cops just got a little lighter.
>> Sweet little Wolverine,
I might just keep you.
>> I think you can
do better than that.
I don't fraternize
with employees.
Well, think of
us as partners.
>> Can't get a promotion
in your own bike gang?
>> They don't wear
tights like you.
>> This is good,
but I want you to
really impress me.
>> Don't tease me, Lady Fang.
>> I'm not.
>> Impressed, coming up.
I can't wait.
You're going to be yummy.
Vicki >> Interesting girl, she
took a left turn after college
ended up dealing drugs.
>> What kind?
Small time dime bags mostly.
She's got a few charges,
but no convictions.
>> I talked to Tessa's mom.
She says her daughter had
cleaned up over the last
few months.
Got straight in N.A.
Was working full time.
Just one small wrinkle.
>> Oh, the kind of wrinkle
we like?
>> A boyfriend who was still
in the life.
Probably still an addict.
Mom says Tessa was
trying to save him.
Did you get the
boyfriend's name?
>> Derek Pheasant.
I don't know how much good
it will do us, though,
because he's dead, too.
When did he die?
>> Four days before Tessa.
Bouncer >> What the hell
are you doing in here?
Mike >> Chuntao Fang.
You got a minute?
Unless you got a warrant,
cop, get out!
>> Oh, come onon.
Tell me is it that obvious?
Hey, is it the tie?
It's the tie, isn't it?
You guys all
have the same smell.
Well, you know, we do
get a volume discount.
I don't talk to cops.
>> Oh, you don't, huh?
Well, you certainly seem
to talk to Wolverines,
or at least one of them.
So it looks like the Dragons
are moving into Wolverine
territory, doesn't it?
Three deaths so far.
>> Since when do cops
care about bikers dying?
>> Well you see, Chuntao,
homicide is homicide.
I'm after the killers,
or killer.
I think you've come
to the wrong place.
You know, Chuntao, I'm
really starting to doubt that.
Well, you look kind of
busy here, so...
you have a nice day,
Miss Fang.
Fang.
You know, that would make
a nice alias for a Wolverine,
wouldn't it?
We'll be in touch.
Nice.
> Okay, what are the chances
that Derek Pheasant
just dropped dead?
Henry >> He was a junkie.
So we'll look at
the coroner's report.
Come on, two deaths, one
after the other like that.
>> And then your client was
evicted from his body
right after being with her.
It may well be jumping
from body to body.
Aha!
See, you can admit it,
any time now.
>> All right, the spirit
you've been seeing probably
is that of Paul Deeds.
> Seriously, you're
becoming a fine detective.
And I'm not telling you to
give up your critical mind.
I mean, you get cocky,
you get sloppy.
A fine detective,
you really think so?
I'd make a good partner then?
>> Oh, you jostling for
space on the letterhead?
>> For starters.
i tell you, after the last
few months, with everything
that's happened, I couldn't
have done it without you.
I mean I wouldn't
have wanted to.
>> That means more than
a mountain of letterhead.
Coreen >> You wanted
the mocha, right?
>> Yeah, exactly what I wanted.
Crueler?
Biker >> Hey, Paul!
>> Hey, I got something for you!
>> What?
It's hot!
[gunfire!]
Vicki >> Nothing like Homicide
the morning of a fresh murder.
Yeah, and I've got
a feeling you know
what we're dealing with.
Come on, let's go to my desk.
Vicki >> So, Tessa's boyfriend,
Derek, was pre-deceased
by a hooker named Mary Wallace.
They all died of the same
mysterious cause of death,
burning out from the inside.
Now, Mary Wallace had a john
named Bert Winters,
this is according to the
girls on the stroll.
Also dead.
>> Yup. So, Tessa Bradley,
Paul Deeds, Bert Winters,
Derek Pheasant, Mary Wallace,
All dead.
And they all knew each other,
okay, however superficially.
And they've all died
from the same cause.
>> Yeah, except that Deeds
isn't dead.
>> Well, not yet.
Okay, so what is killing
all of these people?
I don't know.
Coreen's looking into it.
Did you find anything out?
I'm not sure.
Oh.
You can't tell me.
Which means Internal Affairs
is looking into it.
I didn't tell you that.
Look Vicki, be careful
with Paul, okay?
And I don't just mean the guy
who's walking around.
You're going to blame a guy
who's dead for something
his body is doing?
>> There's more to it than that.
I know he played fast
and loose, believe me,
but he was always straight up.
>> Yeah, maybe he was
straight up, but that's
a slippery slope and you
and I both know that, Vicki.
Okay, you cut a few corners
here and there and before
you know it, you can start
justifying anything to yourself.
I'm pretty sure that
Paul wasn't clean.
Vicki, I know you like the guy.
Just ask him, will you?
Sure.
Vicki >> Bert begat Mary, Mary
begat Derek, Derek begat Tessa
and Tessa begat...
Paul >> And Tessa begat me.
It moves quick.
Yeah, it's gone anywhere
from three-and-a-half weeks
to as short as six days.
Guess I should
treasure every moment.
Well, we have to get this
thing out of you before
it does too much damage.
Your body's in good shape, so...
Thanks for noticing.
> What I mean is that maybe
we can get this thing out
before it does too much damage.
Look Paul, there's something
I have to ask you about,
and I need you
to be straight with me.
Are you saying
I haven't been?
I just found out that IA
has been investigating you.
Why would they be doing that?
Did you get in too
deep with the bikers?
Did you take a payoff
you shouldn't have?
You got the wrong guy.
Paul, this thing is jumping
from low-life criminal
to low-life criminal.
What did it want with you?
Maybe it thought I had
a bright future in the gang.
No, I talked to
your boss downtown.
He says you haven't delivered
any Intel on the Wolverines.
You couldn't have been
that connected then.
Are you saying I can't
do my job or that I'm dirty?
What I'm saying is that this
thing isn't attracted to looks.
It's attracted to a certain
kind of essence.
So something was going on with
you and you better tell me
what it was or I stop looking.
Wow, you give 17 years
to this job.
four lost marriages, no kids,
and now I'm dead, and the
only person who knows it is you.
You're my only ally and
now you want to smear me?
Thanks for nothing, Nelson.
Paul...
Henry >> What was that?
You felt that?
Man, I'm busting your chops for
not trusting my instincts,
and then this guy goes
and plays me.
He was a good cop in his time
and he was also your client.
You can't blame yourself.
You found another one?
> Yeah, died in a flop house
a couple of weeks ago.
> Humble beginnings
for the chain.
Maybe they're
>> Mcareer opportunities.ls.
He goes from this low-life
and its unemployed john
to biker in six weeks flat.
The Ekimmu moves
in and gets a twofer.
The Ekimmu?
Coreen and I found a
description of an ancient
Babylonian entity.
It moves from one body
to the next.
Its whole raison d'etre
is to create violence and chaos.
The Ekimmu, you're sure?
>> Well, the raw meat
was the real clue.
It lives in a perpetual state
of hunger and anger.
Raw meat being its
poison of choice.
Now, according to the book,
it jumps from one gender
to the next.
But it has to touch
Its victim to make the move.
By touch I'm assuming
you don't mean a handshake.
I'd imagine something
a little more intimate.
You would.
>> So as it moves, I mean that
would be the moment that Paul
would be able to jump
back into his body.
> Right, and it hasn't
been in there that long,
so maybe the cellular damage
isn't that far advanced.
Now all we have to do is find
Paul and find a way to trap
the Ekimmu between bodies.
Yeah, that might be a little
difficult because I think
he just fired me.
You can pick a fight
in two dimensions?
You know, that's incredible,
Vicki.
Look, Henry, I heard
a rumour that he was dirty.
I don't know if he's
planting lies, stealing secrets
or destroying evidence,
but I had to ask.
Something's going on.
>> When we were at the morgue,
there was a sheaf of papers
in his jacket.
I didn't think anything
of it at the time.
Records is down there.
>> Would he have access?
He'd find a way.
If we could just figure out
what he was up to, then maybe
we can figure out what's coming.
Or who's next.
Will you drop
me at the station?
Yeah, and while you're there?
Well, maybe you can't
see a ghost, but perhaps
you can shadow an Ekimmu.
Henry >> What was the
name of the massage place?
Alleycats.
You're there, aren't you?
If you are there, there's always
a way to make things right.
Paul >> A vampire lecturing me.
I took something for
myself, no one got hurt.
I know that some of my
greatest joys have occurred
only because of what some
people called my curse.
So being a ghost will
actually solve my issues.
You're classic.
I may be becoming
a detective after all.
I think we just figured out
where it's going to strike next.
ght, October 3,
Wolverines, surveillance photo.
Mike >> Yeah, still here.
October 8, Wolverines,
micro cassette recorder?
Still here.
>> So how many 'still here's'
is that?
Okay, try looking
up the Dragons.
Because...?
Because he's involved
with them somehow.
What do you mean?
Playing one gang against
the other?
>> I saw him having a real close
confab with their leader.
>> Define close.
Sharing the
same breath, close.
Okay, November 5, Chuntao
Fang surveillance photo.
Did you say November 5?
>> Yeah.
>> Gone.
Right, there was also
surveillance on Chuntao Fang
from December 7th, 13th
and 20th.
You mean there was.
In fact this whole file
seems a little slim.
These dates, they're from
months before that thing
took over Paul's body.
So what are you saying?
Paul was working
for the Dragons?
> Give me a better theory.
> All right, see
what you can find.
Can't find.
>> I'm going to have
a conversation with Crowley.
See if she can authorize
a wiretap of the
Alleycat's Massage.
>> The what?
>> Seems to be Fang's
headquarters.
>> Of course it is.
>> Okay, I'll be
back in a minute.
All right, November 12,
micro cassette recording.
That Dragon's missing, too.
Everybody knows that
dragons don't exist.
Not in here they don't.
See, what I'm trying to
figure out is how much trouble
you and I can get into.
Well, that would
depend on who's asking.
You think you know who I am?
Yeah, you couldn't get into
the underworld, so you're here
acting like a tourist at
an all-you-can-eat buffet.
A bit self-righteous, but
I think you could be some fun.
>> You ask around.
Everybody says I'm no fun.
> I'm willing to give it a try.
Stupid creature!
Don't try to hold on to
your miserable existence!
>> I've worked very hard to
be this miserable.
Paul >> Vicki.
You're back.
> You don't sound
too happy about that.
You should have told
me what you were up to.
Chuntao Fang?
You stole police records.
It wasn't me.
Right.
And what about the files
bo that went missing
six months ago?
>> Nothing I did
compromised my job as a cop.
All right, so I gave some
information about the Wolverines
to another gang.
Telling one group of bad guys
about another group of bad guys,
letting them take a bite
out of each other,
I don't see that as a crime.
>> No, especially not when
you're getting paid for it.
Oh...there's that sanctimony
I missed and loved
about everybody in this job.
You know what?
I thought you were different.
I thought that you
would understand.
>> Understand what?
How to get people killed
by remote while you make
money off of it?
>> I was getting results,
bikers off the street!
More than I would've done
in ten years if I was
doing it straight!
Oh, the end justifies
the means.
It was just a perk that a big
wad of money fell into your
pocket while you were doing it.
I didn't do wrong.
You don't see mistakes.
> Oh, wow, okay.
I took some cash.
I gave myself to this job and
it took everything so big deal.
Big deal.
I thought you were
one of the good guys.
I stuck my neck out for you.
I told people that despite all
the bravado and all the bluster
That you were a good cop.
Man, what a mistake that was.
I come bearing gifts.
Cedar.
A cedar dagger?
The Ekimmu
is a Babylonian spirit.
This is a Babylonian solution.
Coreen says the moment
to strike is very precise.
The Ekimmu has to
be between bodies.
I think we all
know who that body is.
Let's go.
>> Lady Fang, did you like that
love letter I sent you, baby?
Two dead Wolverines,
I'm impressed.
>> You're impressed.
Want to have some fun now?
What's you're idea of fun
my sweet carnivore?
The usual - destruction,
chaos, death.
>> That better not be what's
on the menu for tonight.
>> You're on the menu tonight.
Henry >> VICKI, NOW!
Oh god, is he dead?
>> Where's the ghost?
i don't know.
Paul!
Tell you what, Nelson,
I'll take fighting
the bad guys we used to,
over this crap any day.
Hey, that's my livelihood
you're talking about.
> You're welcome to it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I lied to you,
I'm sorry for everything.
> That's okay, it happens.
>> No, it's not
supposed to happen.
It's not supposed to
happen to people like us.
We're the good guys, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, we're the good guys.
>> Man, I'm beat.
You know?
>> Hey, hey, hey!
>> Get if off of me!
Calm down, calm down!
>> Get it off! Keep it off!
Let's go.
>> I'm sorry.
That's a first.
Did something
crawl into you, too?
I was mad at you for not
believing I was talking
to Paul's ghost.
I was wrong, too.
I took everything
he said at face value.
It never occurred to me
that he lied about it all.
Well, except for the ghost part.
We all need to
believe in something.
Mike >> Hey.
>> Hey.
Internal's investigation
will get filed away.
Yeah, but it won't matter.
When people remember Paul Deeds,
all they're going to
remember is a dirty cop.
They didn't see what we saw.
In the end he came clean.
>> No fun in remembering that.
We'll remember.
Night.
>> Mike's going to be one
of those guys who dies
with his boots on, too,
isn't he?
We all will.
We?
Yeah, we!