Hi, Mom.
Yeah, my date ended early so
I thought I'd give you a call.
Mom, with you if it ends too late,
I'm going too fast.
If it ends too early,
I've driven him away.
You know what?
We just didn't fit, okay?
No, I did not hit him.
He was one of those guys, you know?
He held the door
and he pulled out the chair.
Mom, he tried to read me the menu.
You know what? I don't need help.
I'm not blind.
Yet.
You know my desire...
and you may have your price.
Was that a 'yes'?
I don't know.
Savage Garden? Fun House?
The Bovine?
Yeah, we'll do the Bovine.
Okay, you choose then.
What?
Sorry, I thought I heard something.
There's some guy.
He's wearing
a black cape or something.
Cool. He looks like the freakin'
Prince of Darkness.
Mom, something's come up.
I gotta go.
Yeah, I love you too.
Mom, I gotta go!
Season 1 Episodes 01-02
Blood Price
Transcript: swsub.com
Synchro: Benj! / Loky
www.seriessub.com
It'll just be a few more minutes, ma'am.
Detectives are on their way and...
want to ask you a few questions.
All right.
Who's catching tonight?
Detectives Celluci and Graham.
Had to be Celluci, huh?
Vicki!
What the hell are you doing here?
Uh, almost getting myself killed
trying to stop a homicide.
Hi to you, too.
Dave Graham, Vicki Nelson.
Hi. You're a legend.
I mean, he's burned through
a lot of partners.
Yeah, how much longer
are you going to last?
Listen, why don't you see if they've
been able to lift any prints, will you?
You look nice.
You dress for work these days?
I just came from a wedding.
Don't start with me, okay?
Well, if you can't close cases
you might as well look good.
Well, thank you.
You look good, too.
So, what did you see?
I saw someone big, and dark.
It looked like
he was wearing a cape.
Tossed the kid around like a doll
and then disappeared
into that alcove there.
What do you mean 'disappeared'?
What, do you need a Websters?
I mean he went in and didn't come out.
I...I saw from across the street,
came over to try and stop it.
So, let me get this straight.
no weapon,
no backup, no idea
really what's going on.
Plus you can hardly see. So...
What, you turn PI and
forgot everything you ever knew?
No, I did forget
how ignorant you can sound.
What would you have done?
Well, I certainly wouldn't
have got myself almost killed
trying to prove
I'm some kind of superhero.
Oh, That's good, Mike.
You know what?
You should go into psychoanalysis.
Oh, well, shoot me for caring, Vicki.
Okay, I'm good. All right?
Settled?
I'm all good.
You're not going to
shoot him again, are you?
That was an accident.
Mike?
It doesn't look like a robbery.
The money and wallet are still there.
The wounds on his neck make it look like
somebody came after him with a chainsaw.
- It also looks like he's been bled out.
- Bled out where?
Well, a few drops
leading down the alley...
A couple more down the alcove.
It's a dead end from there.
Yeah, it's just like the other one.
What other one?
The other one
that's also police business.
Well, I'm the primary witness.
I think I deserve a little information.
Just like you went out of your way
to inform your witnesses
when you were on the job, right?
I cannot believe
you are shutting me out.
I can't believe
you walked away from the job
and expect to be treated like a cop.
Then I guess I'll just leave
this up to the um...
- professionals.
- Yeah, you do that.
Well, it was nice meeting you.
What?
Hi, Mr. Chan?
Hi, my name is Vicki Nelson.
I'm an investigator working
for a lawyer in Hongkong.
Yes, I was wondering, do you remember
an uncle named Chi Fung Chan?
Okay. Sorry to bother you.
Can I help you?
The papers say you
were there last night.
You saw Ian's murder.
You know what? If you're some kind
of graveyard groupie...
My name is Coreen Fennel.
Ian was my boyfriend.
I was on the phone
with him when it happened.
I'm sorry.
What can I do for you?
He saw something.
He saw who killed him?
You should be telling
this to the police.
I did.
They won't believe me.
I need somebody who will.
Well, what exactly
do you need people to believe?
Ian was killed
by a Walker of the Night,
a vampire.
Coreen, I understand...
Don't patronize me.
They're real.
Out there.
Walking the night.
Looking to slake
their unquenchable thirst.
Feeding on us the way
we feed on cows or chickens.
Chickens?
Ian told me what he saw.
He said it was
a guy wearing a black cape.
The police tried to hide it from me,
but it was in the
paper this morning.
Whatever killed him,
took all of his blood.
You know what? I'm sure
when they find who did this
there will be
a reasonable explanation...
They won't find him because they're not
looking for what really killed him.
It was a vampire.
I know it.
I can pay you.
I've got a job at the University Pub.
It wasn't a human
that killed Ian, Miss Nelson.
You were there. You must know that.
You know what? All I know is
that whoever did it,
was big and they wore black.
If it's not a vampire, fine.
I just need somebody
to investigate it.
Please.
I don't want to waste
your time or your money,
so I'll put a few days into it.
That's it.
Okay, it's, um...
500 per day, plus expenses.
Just don't put too much hope
into this, okay?
It may not turn out
to be what you think.
That...was...
delicious.
You have no idea.
From your graphic novels
I thought you'd be dark and...
angry.
I never figured you for a lover.
Passion is at the centre of my work.
There's nothing else worth living for.
Ah, you're smooth.
I bet you'll even say you'll call me.
You know it's sad to see someone
so young be so...
cynical.
Yeah.
Like you're all of 23.
Looks can be deceiving.
Hey, what are you doing?
I thought we could play some more.
It's late.
You should go home.
Well, I could... just sleep here.
You have a very busy day tomorrow.
You should go.
Man. What was I thinking?
Tomorrow's crazy. I should...
I should go home.
Good night, Sandra.
Good evening, Mr. Fitzroy.
You been following
the excitement in the news?
I avoid it whenever possible.
It's all about the vampire.
Two killings already
Not a drop of blood
left in either of them.
- Just like in the movies, huh?
- Just like in the movies.
Vampires are a myth!
The people who write this
and the people
who read this are idiots!
Yeah. I guess.
They play on people's fears.
You'd think
reporters would stick to the facts.
You can keep that.
Do you believe this?
No.
Good.
Hey!
Hey, excuse me!
Can I ask you a couple of questions?
You understand I wouldn't normally
share this kind of information
outside the police force,
but there are times when
we must rise above the rigidities
of conventional ethics.
Solving this young fellow's
murder is all that's important now.
Amen to that.
Whoever did this did not care
about the extra marks for neatness.
Please. Not in front of the client.
- I don't think he'll mind.
- Just because he's dead
doesn't mean he doesn't have feelings.
Most are more sensitive than the living.
What do you think caused
these marks on his neck?
Frankly, I haven't a clue.
Celluci said there was another
victim killed the same way.
Yes.
With both, the wounds
are jagged and uneven.
Like from teeth.
But whatever did
the cutting was razor sharp.
It cut right through skin,
muscle and cartilage in one fell swoop.
No animal can do that.
- What about the blood?
- Exactly.
What about the blood?
Both victims were drained nearly dry.
That's unnatural.
And what do you think this is?
I found it in a crack in the wall,
near where I lost sight of the killer.
I know what I think it is
but I need confirmation.
Blood.
Most certainly blood.
Ah, yes.
Now whether or not
it's from my young friend
I can't say until I do more testing.
Maybe I should ask him.
I'm kidding.
Just let me know.
Look familiar?
Hey, Norman.
You said you were gonna show up
at the Everquest Tournament last night.
We had eight computers
networked at once.
It was freakin' awesome.
I was busy.
I have better things to do
than hang out with undergrads.
Right,
'cause your social
life is such a whirl.
Something like that, yeah.
What? You got a date?
I might have.
Doing math tutoring for girl
in the cheerleading squad
is not considered a date, all right?
I'm doing some stuff,
some serious stuff, all right?
- I'm making some changes.
- Oh, where to start?
Wardrobe? Bank account card?
Personality?
We got another game Tuesday
night if you're inter--
Screw that.
I'm not like you guys, all right?
I'm going to get the clothes.
I'm going to get the money.
And I'm going to get the hot car, okay?
And I'll tell you another thing.
I'm going to get a girlfriend.
A hot one, all right?
You'll see.
You're going to see, all right.
Oh. Hi...
How's the orange pop?
Do you want another one?
No. Uh...
I'm done.
Say...
Here,
take that.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
Dude, where'd you get all that money?
Like I said, boys,
things are changing.
Nelson Investigations.
I heard you spoke with the coroner.
Oh, news travels fast
Well, it's a small world.
Did you call to trade clichés
or is there something
you have to say to me?
What the hell are you doing
sniffing around this case?
You know,
that information is confidential.
That means it's between me
and my client.
What client?
Your inquisitive mind,
that's what I always loved about you.
Oh, why don't you tell me
some of the rest then.
No. I don't think so.
You're too obnoxious already.
Uh... you know though,
if you're willing to share information
this case could be solved a lot faster.
Oh, I'm sorry. My ears must be
playing tricks on me.
Vicki Nelson asking for help?
That's not what I said.
I said 'share information'.
Well, that's an interesting idea.
Why don't we discuss it over Chinese?
You buying?
I figured you could write it off
as a business expense.
You know, consulting
with the city's finest and all.
You surprise me, my son,
calling me up so soon.
And after all those lovely toys
I got for you.
This isn't like I thought.
I want more.
Of course you do.
And I'm here to provide.
Good.
Good. Okay.
Cause I want more money.
I want some new clothes.
I want a car, okay? A nice car.
- Get me a Porsche.
- You know the price.
Blood,
and souls.
Blood and souls.
Fine, fine, whatever.
Take what you need, okay?
But do... just do what I say.
Your wish... is my command, sport.
Cool.
Okay, here's mine.
"It is easy to suggest solutions
when you know nothing
about the problem."
That's the story of your career.
No, that is the job description,
baby, and you know it.
about the problem."
"The night will be filled with
mystery and budding romance."
I could help with part of that.
You going to fill me
on the murders or what?
Oh, Vick, come on.
This is a hot case.
None of it's supposed
to leave the department. You know that.
- Mike, come on.
How many cases have we solved over
beer and bad Chinese?
Oh, I get it.
You're doing Chinese with
somebody else, aren't you?
It Dave, isn't it?
Yes, it's good old Dave.
You found me out.
God, I miss this.
Ever think about coming back
to the force?
Yeah, sure, just as soon as
a miracle happens
and somebody
gives me my eyes back.
Aw, come on, Vick.
It can get better. You know that.
They say that...
megadoses of Vitamin A and E
can make a difference.
No, seriously. It can...
increase your visual field,
help with the dark adaptation, right?
Sounds like you're reciting this crap.
I googled it.
You googled it?
Yeah, I wanted to know. Why?
All the better to pity you, my dear?
Now, you see,
that's your problem right there.
You never knew
the difference between pity
and somebody
actually caring about you?
Oh, is that what this is?
Yeah, and if you weren't so damn
angry all the time you'd know it.
So I have anger issues, too?
All I'm saying is that you never
need to leave the force, all right?
With a few simple adjustments you could
have lived a perfectly normal life.
I am!
Okay? And one of those 'adjustments',
it would have meant me riding
a desk for the rest of my career
watching third-rate detectives
fumble their way
through homicide cases.
Am I supposed to resent that remark?
What's that about?
You know what?
You can take that however you want.
You started it.
All right.
Rather than have this whole
evening go off the rails,
I'll make a deal with you, okay?
You tell me why you're poking around
in this and I will share some,
some, of what I know.
Fine.
You show me yours first, though.
Always was that way
with you, wasn't it?
Okay. Fine.
I figure from the way Reddick
was beat up before he was killed
that the killer had to be on something.
Yeah, maybe crystal meth, PCP.
That would give him
that kind of crazy energy.
Exactly. The wounds,
they could have been caused by a,
glove with razors or knives on it.
- Like Freddy Kruger?
- Yeah.
- Something like that.
- What about the blood?
Well, it could be
a ritual thing, you know?
Oh, for the occult, maybe.
Yeah. Could be.
Why, you got a better theory?
Okay, um... my client
is Ian Reddick's girlfriend.
She believes a vampire killed him
A vampire.
Come on, Vick,
going private is no excuse
to take money from somebody
who's not playing with a full deck.
Listen,
from what I've seen
this is as good a theory as any,
Okay? There was something
about the killer.
The way he moved.
His strength, you know? I mean,
how about the fact that
he took every drop of blood.
- Come on.
- Maybe he had something with him.
- I don't know.
- Like what?
A portable blood-sucking machine?
Mike, I went back to the alcove
where the killer disappeared
and I found blood
four inches into a crack in the wall.
Oh, well, that's a hell of
an escape route.
I mean, Vicki come on.
You're talking about real life murders
being committed by some character
out of a monster movie
It's ridiculous.
What are you doing?
Why are you...?
You know what?
I'm sorry.
You know I was just about to tear
your head off for something
I don't even believe. This is crazy.
Well, maybe I am losing it.
Here, eat your fortune cookie.
Get some Vitamin A.
- Nice catch.
- Clearly I need more beer.
Yeah, I just got out of a meeting
with Cindy and Rob.
Network is screaming
about the violence in the show.
Well, I told him this isn't the '50s.
There's more violence
in your kids' nursery schools.
Well, they started with
the whole chicken and egg thing,
and that's when I lost it.
Gerry?
Uh... no.
No, it was nothing.
Where was I?
Yeah, so I said, you know,
it's just a TV show.
What does one more lousy
murder at an act end matter?
Sorry love,
you just got cancelled.
Well, that was fun.
Kinda like old times, huh?
The talking or the fighting?
I was thinking both, actually.
Bye.
I've got some work to do still.
It's ten o'clock.
I've got to check out
that bar that Ian worked at.
Vicki, I already checked out that bar.
It is a dead end, all right?
Well, maybe it needs
a better investigator.
Just like old times!
The city's finally world class, eh?
- What?
- The vampire.
I mean you always imagine them in like,
New Orleans or London.
Now we've got our own.
Who knows?
They might have always been here.
Oh, people would have known.
I mean, hideous blood-sucking
freaks running around
kind of make an impression.
They might at that.
I knew that guy, Ian,
the one who was killed.
He lived across the street.
- Really?
- He worked at the Nervosa Club
Nice guy.
He used to let people in the
service biz in for free.
I'll have to check it out sometime.
You need someone to go with,
I get off at ten.
I'm glad I kind of made an impression.
You're new here.
Not new to that line.
What are you doing here?
You wanna take that hand off my arm
before I snap it off at the wrist.
I need to know about Ian Reddick.
What do you think people
have been talking about?
Last night was a perfectly normal night.
You don't wind up being killed
on a perfectly normal night.
Trust me on that one.
He had a problem with a couple guys,
- had to cut them off.
- What guys?
They're in here every night.
Thanks.
Good evening, gentlemen.
We're busy.
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
Why didn't you say so.
Love meetin' new people.
Step into our office.
Hey, can I talk to you a minute?
Escuse me!
So this is better.
So what do you want to know?
They say the waiter
who was killed the other night
had a problem with you guys.
That's a lot more expensive question.
He said we were bothering the girls,
he got us kicked out.
That might make
some people angry at him.
Yeah, try pissed.
But you didn't kill him.
You're unpleasant,
but you're not involved
in the kind of evil that killed him.
How do you know
what the hell we are?
We're done here.
You know we've done
a lot of talking for you, pretty boy.
I think we deserve a bonus.
I'll give you something
you don't deserve,
and that's a warning.
Ian worked a normal shift,
picked up his check
and headed home.
Is that the best you can give me?
There were some guys
here he had a problem with.
Hey, are those freaks who
Ian threw out, around tonight?
They went outside with that guy.
What guy?
Pale, black suit.
That sure narrows it down.
Pretty boy. Long brown hair.
Where's outside?
Stop.
You don't want to go out there,
beautiful.
Yeah, actually I'm pretty sure I do.
Aw... maybe we should dance instead.
You picked the wrong dance-partner.
You will not remember
what happened tonight,
but you will remember there are bigger
predators than you out there.
You will not do this again.
Who did this to you?
I don't know.
You all right, Mr. Fitzroy?
Cooking accident.
Making dinner at a friend's.
It looks bad. You want me
to call somebody to take a look at it?
I'm sorry. I'm fine. Thank you.
Look, if it was up to me,
I wouldn't have said
nothing to nobody.
But my wife,
she said it might be important
to stopping this guy.
Yeah, well, anything helps, right?
So you say you saw somebody?
Man, I'm not sure what I saw.
I was working the block
next to the park and I seen
something drop out of the sky.
What something?
Okay, this is where
it starts to get messed up.
It started out as birds or bats and then
when it gets close to the ground
it kinda came together.
They sort of took a shape
as they dropped over the treetop.
- Yeah? What kind of shape?
- I don't know, like a guy.
Like a guy.
He was all flappy.
Like he was wearing a long coat...
made a noise in the wind.
You see, this is why
I didn't want to say nothing.
So what happened next?
It was just after that
I heard the screams,
then the cops show up.
All right, well, thank you.
Thank you for your time.
You've been a great help.
If this thing is a vampire,
you need holy water.
- Holy water?
- Yeah, that's what the wife says.
That's what the wife says,
don't you know that?
- I'm Norman.
- Good for you.
Hey, this is, uh... my new ride.
Pretty cool, huh?
You want to go for a cruise?
Why would I want to do that?
Oh, because I did it, right?
I got the car.
I got the fancy clothes.
Really.
Are you going to let me pass
or do I have to scream for help.
Like screaming's going to help.
Where did you go?
Wild guess, but I don't think
they go anywhere.
You'd be surprised.
Now, where were we?
Blood, we were talking about blood.
Yes, yes, blood.
Well, it was blood.
And it was Ian Reddick's blood.
How it got there I can't say.
There really is
no reasonable explanation.
You're going to think
I'm crazy for mentioning this,
but the woman that hired me believes
it was a vampire that killed him.
Well, that would explain
certain other findings.
Well, there was a substance on Ian's
throat and that of the other victims
which was something like saliva.
Like saliva?
I'd be more precise if I could,
but it doesn't match
any animal or human species.
And there's something else.
I found this under the nails
of the woman that was killed
in the parking garage last night.
It's very similar in structure
to a bat's wing but...
But it doesn't match
any human or animal species.
Exactly.
Intriguing, isn't it?
So... so what are we talking
about then?
We've got Count Dracula
out there on a bender?
We must keep an open mind.
There are more things in heaven
and earth than are dreamt of in the...
police officers' training manual.
I'm starting to believe that.
Now,
Mary Baum.
Where would Mary Baum be hiding?
I seen the way
you looked at her, man.
You were gone.
No, no, you were way past gone.
Now we were talking about the case.
How the hell do you get that?
Look man, I got eyes.
Let me think.
Last time you got out with
all your parts intact.
Next time you might not
be so lucky.
Who are you to talk, Dave?
Your third marriage is on its last legs.
My girlfriend's not too happy either.
You know, I think
this kinda qualifies me
as having a certain amount of...
experience, dealing
with difficult women.
Gee, I would think it might not be them.
You see what I'm talking about
dealing with difficult women?
So Vicki has a strong
personality. So does Mike.
Maybe they're made for each other.
Yeah, like, um...
gasoline and a match.
My bet is? He gets whupped.
I'm so thrilled to have been
a part of this conversation.
Honestly.
Don't listen to him, Mike.
She got away once.
If there's even a chance
it could work, you have to take it.
Well, I do appreciate that.
Thank you for your concern.
Anybody do any work around here?
I'm going to go talk to...
I'll talk to you later.
Man, somebody get that girl a doughnut.
You are here for a reason, right?
Just checked in with the M.E.
Did you read that report?
That report is for me only.
what do you think of it, though?
I mean, the batwing
that's not from a bat.
The saliva
- that's not human or animal.
- It's so obviously a vampire, right?
Look, I'm just trying
to make sense of this.
Vicki, I'm not going
to start hunting vampires.
I don't need you running
around scaring people, OK?
The papers are already having
a field day with this thing.
I am a concerned citizen, all right?
I'm trying to help
with an investigation.
If you don't want my help...
Look, I'm cool with that.
Vickiii...
Great. Great.
Finish the ritual, Nightwalker.
The power will be yours.
Saw something on the monitor?
Probably somebody's
dog got loose.
There. You see?
Nothing.
Vicki Nelson.
Ms. Nelson, it's Coreen.
Hi, Coreen
Have you found out anything
about Ian's killer yet?
You know, I told you
this would take a little time.
We might not have time.
How many peopleis this undead creep
gonna kill before somebody stops it?
Coreen...
Okay, say this is something
supernatural.
You're all over
this occult stuff, right?
Like ectoplasm on a poltergeist.
What's the significance of a pentagram?
It's a power symbol.
They're used to focus power in rituals.
Like, to call spirits,
that kind of thing.
Why? What did you find?
It may be nothing.
If I find anything
I'll get back to you, though.
You know something.
Tell me.
Look, if I find anything
I will call you back, okay? Bye.
This is Celluci.
Leave a message.
Hey, Mike, it's Vicki.
This is going to sound crazy, but
I plotted the locations
of the three murders
and they make up the first three
points of a pentagram.
I think I know where the
fourth is going to be
and I think it's going to be tonight.
Call me back, please.
You thought I wanted you?
Stupid.
It's her I'm doing this for.
You seemed disturbed.
- What do you want?
- Tell me what I want.
The girl who ate this?
She's yours.
all right?
I offer her to you.
But there's another girl.
Her name is Coreen.
She works at the University Pub. I...
want her... to love me.
Can you do that?
Stealing trinkets is one thing.
But to steal a heart...
that's a tall order.
You have to understand, see?
I...don't have the power of love.
For that you need someone
much more powerful than I.
Great. Yeah, fine
- How do we call him up?
- First,
let me finish marking
the doorway in blood on the city.
Then, one more sacrifice,
here, in the centre,
and he'll arrive
and he'll be ready
and willing to serve you.
I don't care
how much blood has to be spilled.
I want her.
I... I'm tired
of playing the nice guy, okay?
Make it happen.
- You'll find her in Parkdale.
- Yes, master.
That's why I dropped physics
in the first place.
...for shopping.
You're right.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
- I'll scream.
- I'd appreciate it if you would.
You're not like them.
My master knows you.
He's coming for you!
Stop right there!
Make another move and
you're going to lose that
fancy dental work.
Hold it right there!
Victoria Nelson, PI.
Cute.
You son of a bitch!
Easy, easy, easy.
I was just trying to protect myself.
Perhaps a bit too forcefully.
You think?
I didn't have time
to pick up your glasses.
I see you carry an extra pair.
Thank you.
Now, I know you won't believe me,
but I don't want to hurt you.
Yeah? You've got
a funny way of showing it.
I wasn't the one threatening
the other's dental work.
My smile is my best feature.
I've never met
a vain serial killer.
I didn't kill that woman.
I was trying to stop it.
And why would I believe that?
You were there.
You must have seen it.
I saw something.
I don't know... what I saw.
The problem with your eyes...
it's more than just bad vision.
Yeah, it's called
Retinitis Pigmentosa.
It's a progressive loss
of visual function.
It starts with night blindness.
Then your vision tunnels
so that it feels like you're
looking through a straw.
Next stop, blindness, and to...
top it off, I'm near-sighted.
People with that condition
might want to stay away
from night-time stakeouts.
Yeah, are we gonna talk about
my vision or are you gonna...
tell me what it was
I'm supposed to have seen.
It was a demon.
A demon? Sure.
Why not?
You're taking this rather calmly.
Well, I'd be more concerned
if I actually believed it.
I suppose I wouldn't either.
So, how did you wind up there?
I'm busting your chops
for talking about demons,
and I was out hunting a vampire.
Yeah, I know.
I'm going to let you in
on a little secret, okay?
You believe in vampires.
I am a vampire.
- You didn't try and kill me.
- Was I supposed to?
Isn't that what vampires do?
Unless of course, you also
thought that garlic and
silver crosses would hurt them.
Call me old-fashioned,
but, I'm pretty religious.
Okay, say you are...
a vampire, Mr...?
Henry Fitzroy.
Fitzroy.
Why would you be trying to
stop another blood sucker?
That's hardly professional
courtesy, is it?
I couldn't have something
like that running around town
terrifying the
masses, now could I?
The next thing you know,
the villagers are out
with their stakes and their torches.
That happen much?
- Often enough.
- Really? - Really.
I've lived a long time...
almost 500 years.
Yeah, I wouldn't have pegged
you for a day over 450.
I use a great moisturizer.
You know, it's a shame you're not
the more trusting type, Vicki.
That's a nice trick.
It's not a trick, Victoria.
I'm telling the truth.
That's what I'm afraid of.
The wounds are
exactly the same but...
she hasn't lost the
same amount of blood.
Whoever killed her
didn't have time to take it.
Right.
The radio car was
on the scene about a...
minute after they
heard the screams.
Yeah?
They get a look at the guy?
Well, uniform thought
he saw something
before he flipped the light on.
What makes me think
I'm not gonna like this?
Well,
he thought it looked
like a man in black,
carrying a woman.
There's another thing.
- They found these.
- God dammit.
This is Vicki, leave a message.
Vicki, it's me.
Where the hell are you?
Call me as soon
as you get this.
Why did you bring me here?
If you had a more
compliant personality,
I could have made you
forget what you saw.
- But considering you're so...
- Strong-willed?
Try 'hard-headed'.
I had two options, I could...
elimate you...
or I could trust you.
Trusting's good.
If I sense I can't trust you,
I can still eliminate you
before you do me any harm.
Just 'cause you got in
a lucky shot,
doesn't mean
that I'm easy to kill.
Everybody's easy to kill.
- Why me?
- You're a private investigator,
and you were good enough
to find him the same time I did.
The demon hunts nights,
as do I.
But if there's a human who's calling
him up, and chances are,
he's living his life by day.
You want to team up?
Until the demon's stopped.
I gotta think about this.
Come to me tomorrow
night with your answer.
And Vicki...
I may be the only one
who can stop this demon.
Don't even think of
giving up my secret.
Who'd believe me?
Should I call the cops, or
do you just want to arrest yourself?
Hey, I've been up
all night looking for you.
God, you sound like my mother.
How the hell
did you get in here?
I showed the Super my badge.
It works wonders.
You gonna use that, or what?
You know what?
I haven't decided yet.
So, why... why were
you looking for me?
A uniform saw a woman
being taken from the scene of
a homicide last night.
You were there.
You are messing around
with my investigation.
It's my investigation, too.
No, Vicki, you're wandering
around half-blind,
looking for somebody who's
already killed four people.
That's a good way of
becoming number five.
Aw, you know what?
I'm, uh...
I'm just happy that
you're alive, all right?
Talk to you later.
You said you had this covered.
- We're on it, okay?
- And the Chief is on me,
the Mayor is on him,
and the paper's are on all of us.
All right, look. We found
a pattern to the crimes.
It looks like there's some
kind of Satanist agenda here.
Great. Even if we break it,
it's going to make news
for the next ten years.
I want this freak taken down,
and fast.
We done?
One more thing.
I heard Vicki Nelson's
got her nose in this.
No, she's working
a separate investigation.
That's not what I heard.
We can't afford her
anywhere near this.
She's a wild card.
Vicki cleared just about
every homicide she ever pulled.
We'd be lucky to
have her on this.
You do not want to
stake your career
on that statement, Celluci.
I guess we're working together.
History buff?
Family photo.
- Right.
- You believe I'm a vampire,
but you don't believe
I had a father?
And he just happened to be one
of the most famous figures in history.
But that would make you
Henry, Duke of Richmond.
You surprise me again.
How did you know that?
I have a minor in history.
I learned mine the hard way.
I lived through it.
So how did you end up
drawing comic books?
Graphic novels.
Art and literature have
always been my passions.
I finally found a medium where
I can fully realize the both of them.
This is going to take
some getting used to.
Okay, partner.
Why don't we start by you telling me
how you know so much about demons.
London in the 1890s.
They called themselves
the Hellfire Club.
Rich men and women who went
to any length to relieve
the boredom of their
pampered lives.
Mr. Fitzroy,
I've heard so much about you.
The club gave them the sense
they were being wicked.
They had no idea.
Welcome.
And that's when the evil,
at the center of it,
all came out to play.
O'Mara was performing a ritual.
I didn't know if
it was real or not.
I knew he was trifling with
something better left alone.
- Why?
- I demand your service!
- What do you demand?
- Eternal life!
And what do you
offer in return?
Blood and a soul.
A Nightwalker in our midst!
Take him and
give me his power!
Oh, yes.
You shall have your power,
and I shall be free.
Finish the ritual, Nightwalker.
Use his blood to
bring me through.
The power will be yours.
Anything you want!
All I want right now,
is for you to go to hell!
We will meet again, Nightwalker.
I took the grimoire
so that none of O'Mara's
followers would use it again.
It was the smell at one of
the crime scenes that gave it away,
the worst kind of
corruption imaginable.
I guess demonology's not for
people with sensitive noses.
Once the demon touches them,
their minds are so broken,
they don't even know the difference.
Whoever's called this demon
still thinks he's in control.
Well,
if this guy's
not calling the shots,
what does the demon want?
The thing I saw last
night was a minor demon.
His job is to open a door
to bring a much more powerful
demon through.
Once the pentagram is complete,
all it takes is one more sacrifice
to open that door.
- You sure about this?
- His master is Astaroth,
the same demon
I fought 100 years ago.
Great.
And what, pray tell, happens
at Astaroth's coming-out party?
That's when all
hell breaks loose.
So, for those of us who
skipped Demonology 101,
define 'All hell breaks loose'.
Pure evil unleashed on Earth.
- Like what? Wars?
- Of Biblical proportions.
Death, pestilence and despair
ruling for 1000 years.
Most will become corrupt and
fall sway to the dark forces.
Those who don't,
will die horribly.
You know, don't go painting it all
rosy-coloured for my benefit.
Demons have escaped in the past.
- Why haven't I heard of this?
- You've heard of their work.
The slave trade, the Black Death,
Stalin's atrocities in Russia.
So if we stop the one
who's calling the demons,
- do we stop the demon?
- If we get to it in time.
- The trick is finding him.
- Where do we start?
Well, the demon
from last night
can only offer
material goods.
Well, we can't just go
looking at every newly
rich person in town.
Well, the demon
can't create the goods.
He has to steal them,
from somewhere close to where
he's going to deliver them.
Well, I guess we
know what I'm doing.
- How about you?
- Now it's time for me to take a nap.
Victoria...
Vicki. Victoria was
an overweight Queen.
She wore it well, though.
Trust me.
I wanted to thank you
for your help.
I haven't met anyone quite
like you in over a lifetime.
Well, you know,
500 years old or not,
you and I start
hanging out together,
people will say
I'm robbing the cradle.
I'm willing to take that
chance if you are.
It must be that vampire
magnetism I find so tempting.
My powers of persuasion
don't work on you.
Then I guess it's just you.
Past you're bedtime, isn't it?
So you found the vampire?
Know what? I can honestly
tell you it's not a vampire.
You're as bad as the police.
Look, I threw the I-Ching,
consulted my spiritualist.
How much more
proof do you need?
I know a vampire did it.
And so do you.
If you won't help me prove it,
I'll do it myself.
Seen any vampires lately, Coreen?
I don't have time for this.
Maybe it was
a giant mosquito.
Hey, it was her boyfriend, man,
give her a break.
It was a vampire,
and I'm going to prove it.
Coreen...
Get yourself some help.
That's the theft reports
from the last week.
More in the last couple weeks
than the whole month before.
Keep that stuff in order or you're
gonna have some filing to do, too.
It's like I never left.
It's good to see you
around again, Vick.
Yeah, you too.
Still searching
for your vampire?
Not a vampire.
It's definitely not a vampire.
Since when?
I was just messing with you.
Come on,
who believes in vampires?
Well, you were all over
me about it yesterday, weren't you?
Mike, you're out of practice.
You don't even know when
I'm playing you any more?
So what's this?
Uh... I've walked away
from the homicide. I've...
got to trace a stolen Mercedes
for a bail bondsman.
Really?
Vicki Nelson walking away
from a case, just like that?
Yup. Other paying clients
waiting for service.
Well...
Good luck to you then.
Thanks.
Nice tie.
Look, if you didn't
get the blood you need,
that's your problem!
You're supposed
to be so powerful!
You let him stop you.
Unforeseen circumstances.
It won't happen again.
Not when the one after me arrives.
And you are sure
he will serve me?
Every wish, every whim,
every dream, every desire.
You're the master.
That's right.
Go, go run off and
do what you gotta do.
I just want her to be mine!
I've ID'd a number of thefts
that seem kind a hinky.
Stuff stolen from
a locked room.
A Porsche taken from a
showroom full of people.
Cash taken from a bank vault
that had a time lock.
Child's play for a demon.
All of them are around
the University Annex.
Chances are good that
our target is right in the center.
I mean, our demon caller
may even be a student.
That's still too big an area.
Well, unless you have a demon GPS
around here somewhere,
this is all we have.
I was hoping not to have to do this.
What do you mean?
You actually have a demon GPS?
I have always
avoided contact
with the Dark Arts.
Although what I'm going to do
isn't much more than
a parlour trick,
is still repugnant.
Do you want to leave?
I'm always up for a good trick.
Hey, I can see you.
Man, another vampire myth
blown to bits!
That's not what
we needed to show.
I took this from
the demon in the park.
This is the one we seek.
We need to know
where it will strike next.
I know where that is.
It looks like a city park.
There could be 20 places like that.
Demons aren't the
only ones who hunt
lonely
places at night.
I know this city.
It's by Queen's Park.
All right then, let's go.
Too bad that spell
didn't tell us
when he was
going to strike.
He won't waste any time.
He'll take his last
sacrifice tonight.
You love it, don't you?
The night.
All of this.
It's what I am.
It's what I've been
for a long time.
Speaking of which,
how exactly does one...
become a vampire?
Vacation in Transylvania.
Come on, I'm serious.
It was a woman, Christina.
We met at my father's court.
She was only there
during the evenings
and she wouldn't let me
see her during the day.
Suppose you love
someone so much
you just shut off
your rational mind.
Yeah, I'm familiar
with the phenomenon.
So she... she fed on you?
That's one reason
to take a mortal lover.
Didn't you notice
the marks on your neck?
My neck wasn't the only place
she put her mouth.
Then, after about a year,
she finally confessed
to me what she was.
People in the court
had become suspicious,
and she had to move on.
I begged her to turn me.
Wait. You wanted
to become a vampire?
I wanted to be like her.
I wanted to be...
I wanted to be with her, forever.
Forever's a long time.
She warned me that two vampires
couldn't share the same hunting grounds,
but I didn't believe her.
I told her that
true love would prevail.
She drank my blood
and I drank hers. I died, and...
returned from death.
She showed me
the ways of the night.
Our lovemaking was like
we were on fire.
You should work in recruitment.
Then shortly after a year,
I was feeding on a woman
I'd met at a tavern.
Christina was suddenly there,
angry, vicious.
Jealous.
It was the territorial instinct
she had warned me about.
We almost killed each other,
then she was gone.
- I'm sorry.
- I should have listened to her.
I'd have lost her anyway,
but still...
You never saw her again?
If you live long enough,
everything comes around again.
I needed your friend's blood.
But I've never been able
to refuse a second round.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
What the hell are those things?
You know what?
You really don't want to know.
But you might want to get out
of here! Now! Come on, go!
See? We're stronger.
When the master arrives,
you'll suffer.
Henry! Henry?
Are you okay?
You're okay, right?
Come on, you just heal, right?
You just heal!
You can do it.
Come on, you okay?
I need...
I need to feed.
Enough!
I gotta go home!
I need to go.
Take me home.
Mr. Fitzroy?
Come on...
Are you okay? What...?
So we're skatin' nation
on that, right?
Back some sweet backside air.
And we're thrashed,
I mean stoked, but thrashed.
So then we come
walking back through the park.
All of a sudden, Bam!
This thing jumps on my buddy, Chad,
and then hits my head
busting a south shore birthday.
- What the hell did you just say?
- Man... English!
Dude, look, I don't know
who this guy was, all right?
He was just scary and strong.
I mean, check it,
seven ply maple hardwood
sliced through it
like it was cheese.
And then he just let you go?
Nah, that's when
the other dude came.
Oh yeah, another guy with like, uh...
big teeth and leather wings.
This was just a dude.
He went all B. Lee on this thing, man.
I mean, you should've just seen it,
like faster than you could see.
Brother, and the chick!
Wait a minute.
Don't tell me.
Glasses, blonde, good looking.
Oh yeah, hot!
The first guy laid
a smackdown on her, too.
Wait a second.
Is she all right?
I don't know, man.
First chance I saw, I was outta there.
I'll tell you what. Make sure
that this officer has your information.
We'll be in touch with
you soon, all right?
My buddy, Chad, is he...?
We'll be in touch
with you, thank you.
Best bet at finding this guy and
the poor guy's a space case.
Another murder last evening
by Metro's vampire killer
brings the death toll to five.
Now few details
are available at this time,
but sources suggest that,
although he did escape,
the killer may have been
injured in the encounter.
Keep it here on your local news
for complete coverage of this developing
story and we'll continue to bring you...
Vicki, it's me.
I've left messages at your office,
your home and your cell.
Call me as soon as
you get this!
Mr. Fitzroy?
Oh, crap!
Can I help you?
Oh, I was just... just...
I was just checking in.
I was worried about Mr. Fitzroy.
Oh, that's so sweet of you.
Henry's, um...
Henry's fine.
Hey, babe,
it's just the doorman.
Henry's a little bit...
tied up, right now.
I'm sorry, I...
absolutely, I didn't want
to disturb anything... anyone.
- That's okay.
- Sorry.
But, you have yourself
a good night, all right?
- Thank you, you too.
- Thanks.
What am I? An idiot?
How long have you been awake?
- Long enough.
- Yeah, well...
Get dressed. We've got
a lot of work to do.
You're beautiful.
Chop, chop, mister.
So I guess it shouldn't
really be a surprise
that a professor
of the occult works late.
She's a bit of a
nighthawk herself.
I've consulted for her
on various matters over the years.
Does she know what you are?
She's been a good friend.
We've missed you.
So this is your new friend.
Hi, Vicki Nelson,
Private Investigator.
We're working
together on something.
Sorry to keep you late,
but we need some information
about a student.
Anything, Henry.
You know that.
We believe a student
at the university
might have taken
an interest in demonology.
A more than academic interest.
Every year, there's a few.
They play one too many games
of Dungeons and Dragons
and then they start looking into
places they have no business.
Can you get us names?
Uh... current students?
Anyone, perhaps,
from previous years?
If you give me an hour,
I could fax you
seven or eight names
you might want to check out.
All right.
Here's my card, fax number.
I hope nobody's gotten into trouble
because of this stuff.
- Vicki Nelson.
- Vick, it's me.
Hey, Mike, how's it going?
I've got a body
at the skate park.
Skate park?
Yeah, no, I have no idea.
This kid says you were there.
You want to come in for a line-up?
Oh... well, that sounds like a...
like a really good time, but um...
I'm kind of busy tonight.
Come on, Vicki, talk to me.
Tell me what the hell is going on.
Let me help you.
Listen, I'm getting a list of names
that I have to run and uh...
I think one of them
might be our killer.
All right, don't tell me.
One of them's a vampire.
Uh... it's actually
worse than that.
Mike, listen.
I don't expect you to believe me,
but you asked me to keep you in the loop
on this and that's what I'm doing.
All right?
I'm not going crazy.
At least I don't think I am.
All right.
Fax it over and I'll see
what I can do.
Okay, I appreciate it.
Thank you.
This cop, Mike,
there's a story there.
- A long and twisted one.
- You still care about him?
- Professional curiosity as a writer?
- You could say that.
I don't know what's
between me and him anymore.
Speaking professionally,
that's pretty common.
I've got to go.
If you find our man
before tomorrow night,
don't try to take him yourself.
Wait for me.
And what should I tell him?
Just to...
stop killing for a little while?
Bravery...
is a powerfully
attractive trait in a woman.
Stupidity is not.
I'll call you.
Travis Macdonald, 30 Edith St.
Got it.
You know what?
As you go through the list,
be on the lookout for anyone
with a fancy red Porsche, okay?
"... do anything stupid."
Mike! Come on!
You know me better than that.
All right, talk to you. Bye.
You're Coreen, right?
Yeah, I'm, uh... Norman.
From the... pub?
Big tipper? Remember?
Hey, what's up?
Well, I heard you talking to
those people the other day
about how you were looking
for that vampire.
You know what?
I don't need anybody else
to make fun of me right now.
I don't want to make fun of you.
No, no, no, I believe you.
There are supernatural forces
at play here.
You're serious?
I can prove it to you.
Hey, you're the only person
who'll believe me, Coreen.
You know who killed him?
What proof do you have?
I'll answer all your
questions but, uh...
I can't do it here.
All the proof is back at my place.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, that's cool.
You don't want
to come, that's fine.
I called the police.
They didn't want to listen.
- I thought you'd understand.
- All right, just...
Give me a minute, okay?
This is Vicki, beep's coming,
leave a message.
Vicki, it's Coreen.
I met this guy named Norman.
He says he knows about Ian's
murder and the vampire.
I'm going to his place.
I'll call you if I get anything.
You all set?
You know, Coreen,
I've waited for somebody
like you for a long time.
Somebody who
I could really talk to.
Somebody who cared
about the same things I do,
like vintage computers,
Medieval fairs...
You know what, Norman?
Can we make this quick?
I mean, I have to meet somebody.
Don't worry.
I'm the only friend
you're ever going to need, Coreen.
Thank you.
So these are the candidates
for our serial killer?
Half these kids haven't left
their bedroom this month.
Somebody on this list
is our guy, Dave.
Mike, this last guy's mom
still cuts his crusts off.
And I know Vicki.
If somebody on that list
isn't our guy, then he's a witness.
So who's next?
Nobody believed me.
But that's all
changing now, isn't it?
And soon, you're going
to see for yourself.
See what?
The demon!
Not just a demon!
This time, I'm gonna
call a Demon Lord.
- What are you gonna do?
- Well...
It's a ritual.
And you know how it is.
You call up a demon,
something's gonna die, right?
Not you!
Not you. Hell you know,
some of those people had to die.
They had it coming.
But when I chose your boyfriend,
what was his name?
- Ian.
- Yeah, whatever.
- You killed Ian?
- Well,
I did it so
we could be together.
I did. I did it so we
could be together.
And when I call that Demon Lord
and he serves me,
you're gonna be my Queen.
All right.
Ready?
Let's get this show on the road.
Vicki, it's Coreen.
I met this guy named Norman.
He says he knows about Ian's
murder and the vampire.
I'm going to his place.
I'll call you if I get anything.
Oh, shoot!
Henry, it's me.
I've got our guy.
His name is Norman Bridewell,
52 Lunnigan Ave.
I'm on my way.
Get there as soon as you wake up.
52 Lunnigan.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
I think we found
our final sacrifice.
Henry, it's me.
I've got our guy.
His name is Norman Bridewell,
52 Lunnigan Ave.
I'm on my way.
Get there as soon as you wake up.
See, I need another life,
to bring the Demon Lord.
I was gonna order a pizza delivery guy,
but you're so much better.
You know, she's like
part of the family.
Yeah, well, next time,
leave me off the list for the reunion.
Took you long enough to get here.
Sorry.
See? You couldn't even
find a proper sacrifice, so I...
I had to find my own.
Lord Astaroth will be pleased.
Don't listen to him!
He's using you!
Trying to mess with your head.
What are you talking about?
You don't even know him.
For all you know, he's a nice guy.
Look at him, right?
All right, so tell me.
What do I got to say
to get him here?
He's here...
Finally.
Finally is right.
I've been waiting a long time.
You were the one
who called me?
Quickly perform the sacrifice
so I can fully enter this plane,
and then you will have
what you wish.
That's what
I'm talking about, man!
Norman! He's lying!
He's not going to give
you anything!
He's going to kill you!
He's going to kill all of us!
Shut up!
Does this happen
much in sacrifices?
'Cause I think she could be
a little bit more cooperative.
Kill her!
Ah, crap!
Eternity is long.
I will be back for you.
My hands.
It won't come off.
We can't worry about that now.
You're okay. Let's get out of here.
Vicki, what the hell
did I just see?
It's a really long story.
But I'm sure glad
I'm not the one writing the report.
Vicki, I can't thank you enough.
Not just for finding Ian's killer,
but for proving to me
there really are vampires.
Who said there
really are vampires?
Henry. I saw him, remember?
The eyes, the teeth, all the rest.
Well, I think it would be better
for all concerned if you...
never mentioned that ever again.
I agree.
Nobody would believe me.
But now that I know,
I will be a great assistant for you.
What?
Look, I haven't been
to class in two months,
so school's not an issue.
I can help you.
Plus, it'll help keep me
quiet about what I've seen.
Five hundred a week.
No benefits unless
you count bad coffee.
Thank you!
- Thank you.
- Don't ever do that again.
I wanted to thank you
for your help, Vicki.
You're a great detective.
Thanks, though it was weird
working with you.
But, I enjoyed it.
Good.
This won't be the end for us.
- No?
- You gave me your blood.
You're part of me now.
You know, feel free to...
call me if you need to...
hunt down any demons,
or anything.
Vicki, speaking of demons...
These, right?
I don't know what they mean,
if they mean anything at all.
But you're worried.
That I may have just agreed
to go steady with a demon.
All I know is Astaroth
is an enemy of both of us now.
Then I ask
we'd better stay in touch.
You'd better...
Talking to yourself again?
- You know me.
- Yeah.
I was just enjoying the night air.
Oh, you're shivery.
It's not that cold.
Maybe it's not the cold.
Well, come on.
- What's with the arm?
- Sorry, it's just me.