Previously on The 4400...
All right, listen up, everyone.
We're at DEFCON One.
A comet cannot change course.
This one has.
Then it's not a comet.
We're not sure what's just happened.
The light is gone
and thousands of people
have just suddenly appeared...
A lekinetic insurance salesman,
a clairvoyant eight-year
old, and now some kind
of sad sack super vigilante.
They can't hurt me.
No one can.
And those are only
the ones we know about.
Unless you can think
of anyone else.
There's nothing to tell.
I just want to know what's
going on between you two.
Yore my brother.
She's your girlfriend.
It's all good.
No. Wee not actually a couple.
So, it's just you and the baby?
No. It'll be the three of us.
What the hell
did you do to Kyle?
I didn't do anythingo him!
Then can I go home?
Home?
With you.
I don't like being here alone.
You don't like being alone either.
They said draining the fluid
might not be enough--
That more might build up,
and if it does...
then Kyle will suffer
permanent brain damage.
The time I lost is gone.
I'll never get it back.
But my years in the dark
didn't kill me
and my work remains.
And even though
I might not understand
what's happening to me,
I have faith in the final outcome.
After all...
I'm doing what I was intended to do,
becoming what I was meant to be.
I look forward to corresponding
with you again.
I know it's been a long time.
I tell you this as a courtesy.
You can observe my work,
but there's no point
triyng to interfere with it.
I'm now in full command
of my talents.
I hope the world is ready.
Despite nationwide protests,
Homeland Security reses
to divulge the names
or the whereabouts
of the 4400 living here
in the United States.
Confirmed reports of unusual abilities
have the public panicked,
and yet this man sitting beside me
says we have nothing
to worry about.
I'm sure most of you
still recognize him,
even though he's been away
for the past 28 months.
I'm talking about Mr. Jordan Collier,
who recently breached
the government's wall of silence
and chose to out himself
as one of the notorious 4,400.
Jordan...
why?
Why now, why here?
What's your agenda?
I have no agenda.
But someone had to put
a human face on the 4,400.
We have been demonized
enough by people like you.
Well, if you're implying
this is a witch hunt,
I disagree.
You're not the one
being burned at the stake.
Breakfast is ready.
Shouldn't I be saying that to you?
Maia, thank you very much.
This beats a can of Coke
and slice of cold pizza.
And I promise, I will get better
at being the grownup
in this relationship.
It's okay.
I like bei the grownup.
You know, I think
you're going to have a good time
with Mrs. Banky
'cause I hear
she's a very cool baby-sitter.
Oh, and I talked to Mr. Ryland
about getting permission
to get you enrolled in school
because that would be nice, right?
Yeah.
School might be fun.
Diana...
you're not going
to like what's in there.
Oliver Knox disappeared
August 22, 1983,
five nights after the last
of the eight bodies turned up
And he moved back
to Friday Harbor when?
About three weeks ago.
19 days before
the latest body turned up.
You know, it could be coincidence.
And the letter the guy
sent appears genuine,
but this latest victim
wasn't a prostitute.
The eight original ones were.
Coincidence.
That's the kind of positive thinking
we like to encourage
in this department.
Because if it is Knox,
then it means we've got
a 4400 serial killer on our hands,
and if that's not
a worst-case scenario,
it'll sure as hell do for one.
It's the kind of hot button issue
that Barbara Yates lives for.
So I guess wre taking
a trip up to Friday Harbor.
Bring me back a T-shirt.
Alex...
National Threat Assessment Command
NTAC. Are you here about Knox?
Got it in one.
It's a small town.
Oliver reappeared
after 21 years in the wind
and he dsn't look a day older.
We connected the dots.
So you two going to take over
my investigation?
Let's just say we'll be
cooperating with your department
until we've established
Knox's guilt or innocence.
I could use some fresh air...
and some cooperation.
His alibi's airtight.
Alibi or not, we're still going
to want to talk to him.
Anything else you can tell us?
You want to know about Knox?
When he was 15, he was
bow hunting with his cousin.
There was an accident.
Knox ended up with
an arrow in his chest.
His cousin panicked and ran.
Knox woke up lying
in a pool of blood
with this arrow sticking
out of his chest.
So l me guess.
He pulled it out,
and he cauterized the wound?
Even better.
He stood up
and walked four miles into town.
Strolled into the emergency room
and checked himself
in at the front desk.
All this with an arrow in his chest.
Years later,
I asked him if it
really happened that way.
He said every word was true.
I told him that must
have been the walk from hell.
"Not at all," he said.
"It was exhilarating."
He felt like he could
have walked forever.
That's Oliver Knox.
* So long ago *
* Another life *
* I can feel your heartbeat *
* It's not a dream *
* Remember us *
* I can see it in your eyes *
* We'll find our place in time *
* Our place in time beyond the sun *
* Our place in time to call our own *
Mr. Knox?
Mr. Knox.
We have a few questions to ask you
about the death of Theresa Baron.
Sheriff Conrad call you
or did you jump
to the same conclusion he did?
Not exactly a big jump.
You were on the police
roll out back in '83.
Along with a number of other people.
Did you know Ms. Baron?
No.
She was born after I was abducted.
Look, I know how tempting
the math is on this murder.
I disappear in '83, the killings stop.
Here I am and the poor girl is dead.
We noticed.
And if were in your shoes,
you know, I'd probably
want me to be guilty too.
It would be so convenient.
But I almost feel bad
I can't oblige you.
I did not kill that woman.
Listen, can I get you
some water or something?
I mean, if we're going to talk,
we might as well be civilized
about it, right?
No. No.
We've taken up enough of your time.
Thanks.
Conrad told me the story
about how you got shot
in the chest that day.
Jim does love to talk.
Would you like to see the arrow?
I have it inside.
Th won't be necessary.
How's Kyle?
We don't know yet.
Um, about last night.
The kiss.
That...
and other things.
We've kind of got a lot to talk about.
No, we don't.
Shawn.
You have a gift.
Nikki.
When did you get here?
How's Kyle?
He's still in intensive care,
but Uncle Tommy says he's stable.
I guess whatever they're doing
to him this whole time worked.
For now, anyway.
Listen, I'm starving.
Yowant to come with us
to the cafeteria?
Yeah, I'll bring you a burrito.
Why don't you start
with something easy.
Tell me about your relationship
with your parents.
My parents?
They used to argue about money a lot.
That was before they split up.
They divorced?
Yeah, I was 14.
Do you remember how
that made you feel?
Depressed.
I don't know. Angry, maybe.
Why don't you tell me
about the rest of your family.
They're gone.
I've got a few cousins
outside of Saint Lis
who remember me as a picture
in an old photo album.
Well, my husband
married another woman.
My brother hates that I'm back.
What's the point of this?
Look... you want to help me
Help me find a job.
Tell me what to say
when they ask me how old I am...
or about my work experience,
or-or tell me how to explain
that 50-year gap in my resume.
Everyone says that the world
has-has-has changed for the better,
that people don't judge you
by the color of your skin.
Well, let me tell you something:
I'm still being judged,
and you're sitng there asking me
about my-my relationship
with my parents?
Let's talk about this hostility
that you're manifesting towards me.
Danny, you wanted to see me?
Thanks, Peter.
So, this is where you work, huh?
Yeah. What's up?
Uh, I wanted to talk to you
about something, Uncle Tommy.
Is this about Shawn?
How'd you know?
I'm listening.
He, uh... he had a fight at school
a few weeks ago.
He might've killed the guy if
I didn't step in.
What'd he do to him?
Well, it sounds crazy,
but... I don't know.
It was like Shawn was draining the life
out of him somehow...
and I'm not the only one who saw it.
What made you decide to tell me now?
Just thought you should know.
Beautiful, aren't they?
I wonder if that's
where we were.
What's everybody doing here?
What are you doing here?
I don't know. I wanted to see it--
where we came back.
I figured it'd be a good place
to come and think,
you know, clear my head.
Most people come for the conversation.
Well, there's not
a lot of that going on.
Oh, give it time.
Around 11:00, this place becomes
one big group therapy session.
I'm sorry to interrupt...
but I just had to see this myself.
My name's Jordan Collier.
Some of you may recognize me,
and if you do, you know
I'm one of the 4400 just like you.
I'm impressed that you found each other,
and I'm glad that you've come
in support of each other.
And, uh... I'm cold,
and I have to guess that you guys
are cold, too...
...so I want to suggest that we continue
these get-togethers indoors.
I have a place nearby.
It's warm, it's spacious...
and I want to invite all of you
to meet me there
next Thursday afternoon.
You listen to the news.
You read the paper. You hear the talk.
Seems like the entire world
is turning against us.
Well, what are we going to do about it?
We going to give up?
We going to run and hide?
Maybe.
Or maybe... just maybe,
we build a world of our own.
This is the spot where we found
Theresa Baron's body.
We went over everything pretty good.
Yeah, well, we have the toys.
We like to take 'em out of
the box every once in a while.
The killer posed her after
she was dead, right?
There should've been
blood, handprints all over the place.
It rained the day we found the body.
The whole scene was washed clean.
Yeah, but if he dragged her
over here, he had
to grab onto something.
Tom.
I'll be damned.
His name is Philip Lopez.
He did 18 years on an aggravated
rape conviction.
He was paroled six months ago.
We just got confirmation.
His prints were found at the scene
of Theresa Baron's murder.
All right.
Everyone set?
Go.
Lopez!
Tom.
The suicide note says
he killed all nine women.
He wrote that only his "time away"
kept him from doing more.
Do the dates make sense?
Lopez was up here
working as seasonal labor
during the first round of killings.
Guess we owe Oliver Knox an apology.
Excuse me.
Can I get a cranberry juice and seltzer?
And, uh... give me another of
what he's having.
Vengo subito.
Vuolo giaccho con quello?
Excuse me?
Sorry, I, uh...
I'm going to Florence in four days,
and I didn't want to seem like a tourist
when I get there
Oh.
Ice?
Yeah, a little.
I studd, uh, Italian in college.
Really?
Tu sci bella...
come il tramanto di Duomo.
"Beautiful as a sunset over Duomo."
That is very good.
You get an A-plus.
And you get a free round.
Grazie. Hey, Felicia,
can I get a beer?
Need a refill, friend?
Thanks.
Listen, I, uh...
I know we don't know each other,
but I have something
I want to show you.
So, what's her name?
I don't know, but...
I can tell you something about her.
Hello? I'm so sorry I'm late.
Oh, hey, Iris. How did we do today?
I can't come back here.
What? Why?
That child.
I'm sorry. You'll find someone.
I told her that we wouldn't
be seeing each other
for a couple of weeks.
Why... why did
you tell her that?
'Cause she was going to be called
for jury duty.
She thought I was kidding.
A few hours later, her husband called.
And she got a summons for jury duty?
Wellhey, come here.
It's okay, all right?
It's okay.
What are you doing
here so late?
Well, mom said
he was getting worse.
Thã fluid's building
inside his skull again.
Why did they take me
and leave him like this?
We were both on the beach that night.
I don't understand.
I wish I could remember something,
'cause I keep thinking...
think it would help.
Tom said that you were here the night
that Kyle had that jump
in his brain activity.
And he was getting better,
and now he's dying.
Shawn, did you do something to him?
Shawn, tell me.
Just talk to me and tell me...
Aunt Linda, no, I didn't do anything.
Please...
I told Uncle Tommy, and
I'm telling you, oy?
I got to go.
I wish we could talk
to a doctor about it.
And say what? "My baby
may be some kind of alien,
and by the way,
I know what it's thinking"?
Yeah, all that'll do
is get me thrown
right back into quarantine.
I was there today
to register our new address.
Oh, thank you for doing that.
I can't stand going back there.
I ran into Gary Branskul.
He had the bed next to mine.
He told me about some get-together
Jordan Collier's throwing.
Hey, Jordan Collier.
He's the-the hotel guy.
Yeah. Turns out he's one of us.
Yeah, we should go.
Richard, come on.
You can't tell me teenagers didn't
make out in 1951.
Yeah, in a parked car by the lake.
Ohin a parked car by the lake.
That's very cute.
Let me tell you something...
What the hell is wrong with you?!
Are you crazy?
Get out of the road!
I killed them.
I killed them all.
Hands... hands up.
Keep your hands up.
Her name was Gayle Keating.
She worked at a local video store.
They found her body in
Frick Park this morning.
Her blood was all over him.
He spoke for five minutes straight
when we first brought him in.
Confessed to Gayle's death
and the other nine murders.
Hasn't said a word since.
Philip Lopez killed Theresa Baron.
He said so in his suicide note.
We found her shirt
in his apartment, his prints...
I know, but this morning,
Charlie Staley confessed
to the same murder.
And they both claim to be behind
the original round of killings?
Yeah, only Charlie's 39.
He was five years old
when the first death happened.
And we can eliminate Lopez
as a suspect in the original
murders as well.
How do you figure that?
checked Lopez's prison records.
He's left-handed.
According to the autopsy reports
in the '80s,
the Friday Harbor killer
was right-handed.
So, Lopez kills one girl,
Staley kills the other,
and neither one of them
committed the original crimes?
Why would they confess to murders
they couldn't possibly have committed?
Pieces don't quite fit together, do they?
Until you add Knox into the puzzle.
He disappears, the killings stop.
He came back, they started again.
So, let's say
Knox is involved somehow.
That means what, he's...
he's forcing these men
to do his murders for him?
Could be.
The question is how.
I mean, why would he want
more than one person
to admit to the original crimes?
One confession, we might stop digging,
but two - it just gets our attention.
Well, maybe he can't control
everything they do.
What if Knox can force
people to kill?
But only by convincing them
that they really are
the Friday Harbor killers.
In for one murder, in for them all.
Good, good.
Hi. Welcome.
1969, huh?
Well, the good news
is your bell bottoms are back in yle.
Hi.
So, there's this one guy--
I was just talking to him--
and he was gone for 40 years,
and he came back
and picked everything up
without missing a beat.
And then there's me.
I'm gone for three years,
and I come back,
and it's like my whole life
has fallen apart,
everything's different...
I know Shawn, look, the thing to remember
is that most of us feel
the same way you do.
Well, some of us are
more different than others,
if you know what I mean.
I'm not sure I do.
Okay, I had this fight
with a guy at school,
and I know it's going
to sound crazy...
I really can't hear
the specifics right now.
Not yet, anyway.
I have a lot of interviews
over the next few weeks,
and I have to be able to deny
what I need to.
Look, I, I know you're feeling
confused right now,
and I can't blame you.
But it sounds to me
like you've been given a gift.
That's, uh, that's what Nikki called it.
Well, Nikki's right, whoever she is.
And about this gift--
don't let scare you.
You will find the right way to use it.
Okay.
Well, what can I do for you
this afternoon...Lily, '93?
Don't worry, it's not a line.
Though I do have to say
you're the most attractive abductee
I've met all afternoon.
I'm Jordan Collier.
I'm throwing this party.
Oh. Nice to meet you.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Do I detect a little romance brewing
among the 4400?
You have a good eye.
Well, I'm just happy you two
are getting something
positive out of all this.
You're Jordan Collier?
Yes. See, he's not afraid of me.
I, I'm a little lightheaded.
It's hot.
Yeah, I should sit down.
Uh, why don't I find you a seat, huh?
I'll get you some water.
Thank you.
You want me
to, uh, call a doctor or...?
No, I'm not sick.
It'll pass.
Here you go.
Well, that good.
If you're not sick, then what's, uh...?
It's just morning sickness.
You're pregnant.
Uh... first trimester.
Well, that explains it
Congratulations to both of you.
Did I say
something wrong?
I-It's a little
more complicated than that.
Richard's not the father.
I-I wasn't pregnant
when I was abducted,
but I was when I got back.
Strange, huh?
Well, interesting is more like it. Uh...
Kind of makes you wonder
what the hell they have in mind--
whoever took us, I mean.
You haven't told your counselor
about this, have you?
We haven't told anyone.
Well, I'd keep it that way for now.
Look, how are you guys managing?
You have everything you need?
Yeah, everything except a job.
I was a pilot in the Air Force.
Supposed to be drawing a pension, but...
that hasn't come through yet.
I've applied for flight instructor jobs.
I even filed a application
with Seattle P.D.
But every time they find out
I'm one of the 4400...
the job suddenly goes away.
Well, look, I may have something
you'd be interested in.
Doesn't involve flying,
but given ur background
in the military, uh...
My foundation has an opening
in the security department.
Foundation?
For the 4400.
Anyway, if you're interested,
why don't you come by
tomorrow and see me?
I'll be there.
Good.
The rash of violence
involving the 4400 continues,
with sources telling us tonight
that Homeland Security
is investigating a possible connection
between the Friday Harbor murders
and an undisclosed returnee.
That hypocritical, self-righteous,
irresponsible bitch.
Oh, I-I take it he doesn't like her show.
He doesn't like her.
When we were with the FBI,
she disclosed the name of a
juror in a RICO prosecution.
Judge declared a mistrial.
Three years of work down the drain.
You know, she blindsided me once.
That is not going to happen again.
Tom Baldwin.
Yeah, sure.
I see.
We'll be there.
That was Conrad.
He got another letter.
"I decide who lives and who dies.
My judgment is final,
and more verdicts are coming."
The date's clipped from
this morning's paper.
It couldn't have been composed
by Charlie Staley--
not from jail.
You telling us this letter's
from the Friday Harbor killer?
It's genuine.
He describes wound patterns
on the original victims.
We kept that private.
If you really believe
Knox is involved in this,
why the hell is he out
there walking around?
Let's pick him up right now.
We can't do that.
The bottom line is
we need to know exactly
how he's connected to these murders
before we can bring him in.
So, what do we do--
wait for another girl
to turn up dead?
I think we can do better than that.
That's $27.75 - your change.
Thank you.
Who's this?
Let me tell you
something about her.
Her name's Felicia
and she works over at the bar...
W or maybe a tax audit,lling
but I didn't think I'd merit
an invitation into the belly of the beast.
Consider it a tribute to
the size of your bully pulpit.
I'm flattered.
Don't be.
DC is calling for your head.
I want you to dial back on the 4400.
Not going to happen.
I'm a journalist;
I answer only to my viewers.
Don't you hide behind
freedom of the press.
What you do isn't journalism;
it's shouting "fire" in a crowded theater,
and you're going to stop
before the stampede begins.
Yeah.
You have a really strong face.
Seriously, Dennis,
you should come on my show.
You're getting in the way
of my job, Barbara.
And if you're going to continue
interfering
with Department of Homeland Security,
I'd advise you to tread lightly.
And what are you going to do,
disappear me?
I asked for your cooperation.
And I've chosen not to give it.
Fair enough.
Don't forget to get your parking
validated on the way out.
This healthcare plan is incredible.
Yeah, well, the maternity coverage
should provide for all yo doctors' visits
and hospital care once the baby's born.
Mr. Collier, I don't...
I don't know what to say.
Say you'll take the job?
I'm sorry, one moment;
I have to take this.
Yeah, Len.
Oh, good, good.
The whole property?
Excellent. 26 million.
Yes, I want you to lose.
Well, don't worry about
the board of directors, Len.
They voted me back in as CEO
when I returned, didn't they?
I will handle them.
Call me when it's done. Okay.
Real estate deals-- they're
never over till they're over.
So are you going to come
to work for me or not?
I can start tomorrow.
Mr. Ryland - Phil Gibson.
This is an honor.
Uh, Barbara will be very disappointed
she wasn't able to meet with you herself.
Actually, I prefer to speak to you.
Great. First, just let me
say right off the top, sir,
that any information that
you give us about the 4400
will never be traced back to you.
I'm glad to hear that
because I have something
very important to pass on.
Great. Do you mind if I tape this, sir?
Quick and simple.
I want Barbara Yates's
coverage of the 4400 to stop.
What do you mean "stop"?
I mean it ends.
She stops covering the story, period.
Uh, listen, uh, Mr. Ryland,
Barbara has sole ahority
over her editorial content.
It's Barbara. Barbara says what Barbara wants.
There's nothing I can do about it.
You're her producer - produce.
I don't think you know what it's like
to work in this business these days.
We're not Walter Cronkite here.
You want to talk about the old days?
In the old days, I would need a warrant
to tap all your phones,
to freeze all your assets,
and to prevent you
from ever being a passenger
on any airline in the world.
But like you say,
it's not the old days anymore.
Now you've worked for Barbara Yates
for a long time, since the beginning,
and I'm guessing that you know
where the bodies are buried.
Draw me a map.
You're just afraid
my dad will kick your ass
if I come home smelling like beer.
Evil cousin Shawn.
Corrupter of the innocent.
Help!
Help me, Shawn! Shawn, help me!
Oh, my God.
Excuse me.
I-I lost my dog.
Could you help me find him?
I haven't seen him.
He's a-a wirehaired terrier.
His name's Boss.
I haven't seen him.
Could you let me by?
This isn't funny.
I'll scream.
Yes, you will.
Don't move!
Felicia has to die!
She has to!
This man, what did he say
to you, Mr. Mitchell?
You've been following me?
No. Actually, we were following Knox.
You know, I really like
the composition of this shot.
It's nice cozy symmetry.
Now, what did he say to you?
You keep at him.
We'll bring in Knox,
sit him down next to his friend.
See what they have
to say to each other.
Knox! Open up!
Tom!
Knox!
Tell me the police have someone
at the girl's house.
She refused an escort.
She's leaving for Italy
in the morning.
Hello?
Excuse me.
I-I lost my dog.
Can you help me find him?
He's a wirehaired terrier.
His name's Boss.
Somebody, help me!
Stay back!
Let her go! Let her go, Knox!
Knox, get away from her,
or I'll shoot!
I think you break my nose.
Stay down!
Hey, you got me all wrong.
Let me tell you a story...
Not a word. Not a word.
Not a word.
...damn serial killer.
This guy murders eight people
before he's abducted.
They send him back,
and he picks up right where he left off.
In '83, Knox was your
garden-variety psychopath.
They sent him back enhanced.
Big difference.
Well, it makes whoever took
him sound pretty nasty.
They also sent back Shawn.
And Maia.
Yes, I know, Tom.
And for that, I'd like to thank them.
But it all seems so random.
Maybe.
Until you start to look
at the bigger picture.
Orson Bailey kills Adam Kensington.
Revenge murder - open-and-shut.
Carl Morrisey is a well-intentioned,
but hapless vigilante
o ends up dead.
Like I said, random.
Yeah, but we know that
Adam Kensington's company
was perpetrating a massive
fraud on the public.
And now we've learned,
since Carl Morrisey's death,
his neighbors have formed a watch committee
that's helping to protect Bradley Park.
Anyone starting to see a pattern?
What, you're talking about
some kind of ripple effect?
Diana Skouris to the head of the class.
The incidents themselves
are just catalysts for change.
But positive change
in these two cases.
Wait a minute. What?!
Who-whoever sent them back,
you're saying they planned
for these changes to take place?
What about the Knox killings?
There's nothing positive there.
Or maybe we have seen the ripples yet.
Excuse me.
Hey, I have something
I want to tell you.
I want to tell you!
Police aren't saying
who is behind the release
of this closely guarded secret.
A document containing the names
and the current addresses of all the 4400
has appeared on the Internet,
and is now posted on more than 20 sites.
Authorities aren't confirming the leak,
but their efforts to shut down the sites
with an emergency injunction
suggest the list is genuine.
We will have more on this
breaking story as it develops.
What are you doing here, Shawn?
Kyle?
How long...
...have I been in the dark?