All right, listen up, everyone.
We're at DEFCON 1.
It's a comet.
It's not a flyby anymore.
A comet cannot change course.
This one has.
Then it's not a comet.
We're not sure what's happened.
There appears
to be something out there.
The light is gone,
and-and thousands of people
have just suddenly appeared.
Finding Shawn and figuring out
what happened to our son-
that is my job.
Diana Skouris,
Tom Baldwin.
You two will be
one of the teams
that's responsible
for investigating
what happened to the returnees.
And what about my parents?
They're dead, aren't they?
This is Maia Rutledge.
She's eight years old,
only she was born
in 1938.
No time has ssed.
Returnee 2117: Shawn Frell.
Uncle mmy.
Hi.
He's all yours.
Hey, what about Kyle?
Kyle's in a coma, Shawn.
We're letting them go.
We're letting them go?
We don't have
a legal right to hold them.
Hey, Mom, Dad!
Shawn!
Hey, buddy.
Remember me?
Nikki?
I'm Richard.
Lily.
Lily Bonham from St. Louis?
You knew my granother.
Some of these people
have no place to go,
no families left. What the
hell are you looking at?
I used to live here.
Heidi?
Yeah?
Heidi, it's Mommy.
It's, uh... it's okay,
sweetie, I got it.
Brian.
Lily.
But there's no mistake.
You're definitely pregnant.
It's a temporary
restraining order.
You can't stop me
from seeing her.
If Orson can do those things,
who knows
where all this is going.
So far we've got one case,
and maybe that's all
we'll ever have.
You haven't noticed
anything unusual with Shawn?
'Cause I just need
to know-
if you had, you'd tell me.
What looks good
today, Carl?
I have a whitefish
with your name on it,
Mrs. Martino.
Oh.
When you were gone,
in 18 month,
I haven't got a decent piece
of fish.
You...
You take care of me.
You are such a sweetheart.
Aw, it's easy
being nice to you.
Tell me,
how does it feel
to be back?
It's okay.
It's good.
Carl.
It's like I never left.
What do you think
you're doing out there?
I was helping a customer.
Rosie
can help a customer.
Derek can help a customer.
I told you to stock
the display cases.
BuI-I...
I've known Mrs. Martino
since I was a kid.
And I'm supposed to care?
Now get that
flounder on ice.
Grace!
So how'd it go today?
It was slow, as usual.
It's the neighborhood.
It's not like it used to be.
It's not that bad.
Ug It's gotten
a lot worse
since you were away.
I don't see it.
You don't want
see it.
Okay.
I admit it, it's not like
when we were kids.
Yeah, no one cares
about the place anymore.
There's no pride.
There's no sense
of community.
I didn't know
you were so unhappy.
I'm not unhappy.
Hey, I got you
back, didn't I?
I gonothing to
complain about.
Yeah.
Oh...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Fish smell.
I don't mind.
I'll hop in the shower
as soon as we get back.
Hey, let's cut across the park.
The park?
Nobody goes into
Bradley Park anymore.
No.
Yeah? Sure they do.
How do you think I got here?
It's not safe.
There's nothing
but lowlifes
and junkies in there.
Grace, 15 years ago,
I proposed to you
in this park.
Aw...
15 years ago?
Yeah.
I was a size 2,
and you had your hair down
to your shoulders.
Things change.
From now on,
you take the long way around
You know, Grace, I just wish
that you'd, you know...
...stop worrying.
Marry me, Gracie.
Of course I will.
Yo, what are you doing
in our park, man?
Your park?
Ju give up your wallet.
You're mugging me?
Now you're
catching on.
Seven bucks?
It's all I have.
* So long ago *
* Another life *
* I can feel your heartbeat *
* It's not a dream *
* Remember us *
* I can see it inour eyes *
* We'll find our place in time *
* Our place in time
beyond the sun *
* We'll find our place in time *
* Our place in time
to call our own *
So the complaints started
right after her foster parents
brought her back
to quarantine last week.
Well, what kind of complaints?
Well, for instance,
yesterday, Maia was talking
to an employee in the cafeteria.
She told her
her daughter would be
in the hospital soon,
but that she'd be okay.
The next day, the little girl
was in a car accident.
So you're saying what?
She-She's got some kind
of second sight?
I'm saying I have five stories
just like that one.
Why disappear
a little girl
from the 1940s,
hold her for 60 years,
and then send her back
with the ability to
predict the future?
I mean, what were
they thinking?
"They"? We don't even know
if there is a "they."
He, she, it-
take your pick.
Somebody's behind this.
You know, let's leave that
for the team
in the theory room, huh?
Yeah, when they're not
playing video games.
Oh, that's why they're
intimidated by you, Tom.
They feel your hostility.
Good.
I wouldn't worry too much
about the big brains.
Just talk to that girl.
Thanks.
I never meant
to scare anymore.
We know that, sweeti
But why did
you say those things
to Mrs. Krause
about her daughter?
Because they're true.
But how did you know?
I just do.
If I asked you
whether it was going
to rain next Sunday,
would you know the answer?
Maybe.
I don't know.
What's going
to happen to me now?
The doctors here are going
to take another look at you.
Oh, don't worry.
It won't hurt.
I don't believe you.
It's going to hurt, isn't it?
You might be uncomfortable
some of the time,
but mostly, oh,
it's just going to be boring.
Will you look in on me
every now and then?
Me?
To see that I'm all right?
Sure.
It's expensive, though.
The rental vouchers
will cover it.
So... do you
have any questions?
Um,
the small bedroom-
do you think
it'll get too much light
for a nursery, I mean?
It's a northern exposure,
so you should be all right.
So, what do you think?
I like it.
Me, too.
Is this your first baby?
Oh, we're not actually
a couple.
Oh, uh, so, it's just you
and the baby?
No, it'll be the three of us.
Why not?
You can't stay
in that hotel forever.
We can share this place.
Unless you don't want to.
No.
No, I'd like that.
Great.
I'll go do the paperwork.
I hope I didn't barrass you.
No, it's... it's not that.
It's, uh...
It's just, I figure
he wouldn't rentou the place
if I was part the deal.
I know, I know.
It's not 1951 anymore.
Times have changed, but...
Sometimes I'm just surprised
at how much.
Good.
It's settled then?
Oh, God.
Lily? Lily, what is it?
No.
Oh.
Lily.
No, I... I don't feel so good.
You need to sit down.
Should I call a doctor?
No, no.
No, I... I just have to leave.
And go where?
Anywhere but here.
Carl, where have you been?
I got mugged.
Oh, God, are you all right?
Did they hurt you?
No, I didn't get hurt.
They got hurt.
Who did?
Grace, I learned
something tonight,
something important.
I'm a different man.
Those aliens-
or whoever took me-
they did something.
They took me;
they changed me.
They made me better.
I think first thing
in the morning
you should call the counselor
and make an appointment.
What? No.
I don't have time for that.
I got things to do.
What kind of things?
The park, Gracie.
I want to make it
like it was before.
People will bring
their kids there again.
You and me-
we can have our picnics
at the old spot.
Carl, you're scaring me.
There's nothing to be scared of,
not anymore.
Linda, any idea
why Dr. Mayhew wants to see us?
He didn't say.
So how have you been?
Good.
My lawyer was asking if you'd
signed those divorce papers yet.
I thought maybe if
we had dinner some night,
you know, we could...
sign them together.
Oh, you mean make plans
that you'd cancel
at the last minute?
I'll bring the papers,
we'll have a good meal,
a couple glasses of wine...
And a good cry?
That, too.
Stefano's?
Where else?
Tom, Linda-
thanks for coming in.
I was reviewing
Carl's EEG readout,
and I noticed
something peculiar.
What now?
Well, it seems
last Thursday night
he had a momentary burst
of increased brain activity.
It was brief- no more
than a few seconds.
That's good, isn't it?
Technically, yes.
Let's not get ahead
of ourselves.
I'm going to run some tests,
see if I can find
out what happened.
Tests- we've had
three years of tests.
I understand your frustration,
Linda,
but we really need
to look into this.
It's a roller coaster,
isn't it?
It never ends.
Linda...
So, Stefano's, right?
How does Thursday
night sound? 70?
I'll be there.
Dorothy...
Yeah?
Did anyone visit my son
last Thursday night
besides his mother
and me?
Let me check.
Yes, he had one
other visitor:
Your nephew Shawn.
Shawn!
Yeah, I went and s Kyle
on Thursday night.
He's my cousin.
I wanted to see him.
What about it?
And nothing happened
while you were there?
Well, I was ly there
for a couple minutes.
So, you saw nothing,
did nothing?
What could I have done?
The day of your welcome home
party, a bird
smacked into the window,
remember?
Yeah, it was stunned.
at about it?
No, it wasore than that.
And then... you picked it up
and suddenly,
it was alive and well.
What the hell did you do
to Kyle?
I didn't do anything to him!
Look, look, I really like
these little chats we have,
Uncle Tommy,
but I got to go to class.
Shawn.
We'll talk again.
Oh, I can't wait.
A bunch of us are going to see
Fountains of Wayne
this weekend.
Have fun.
You know, um, this whole
loner thing is so tired.
Well, it works for me.
Fountains of Wayne!
Friday night!
What is with you?
Why do you keep
pushing him like that?
Someone has to.
I don't see you
doing anything.
Well, I'm giving him his space.
Let him figure things
out for himself.
You should try it sometime.
Oh...!
Marco.
Skouris- good.
I checked out your idea.
What idea?
So, am I a genius, or am I crazy?
We don't make that distinction
in here.
of disappearance sites on the
West Coast, like you suggested.
Turns out you were right.
The avity at those
sites is weaker.
But according to
the interferometer,
only by five parts per billion.
That's barely measurable.
Not to mention
barely understandable.
English, please.
The gravity is changed
at some of the places
where people disappeared.
The question is
did it change naturally,
or was it articially manipulated.
Now, if the gravity
was manipulated,
the question then becomes by who.
So we're back to
the possibility
of alien abductions.
I wouldn't rule out
little green men,
but obviously I'm going to need
to take more measurements.
So, in other words,
you've made no progress.
Uh, you explain it to him.
Oh, hold on.
You remember Adam Kensington?
The, uh, insurance guy
Orson Bailey killed?
Yeah, what about him?
Not one of the good guys,
as it turns out.
He was point man
in a huge insurance scheme
to defraud tens of thousands
of policyholders.
Orson Bailey
saved the State of Washington
like, a billion-dollar buyout.
Could've been Enron
all over again.
God, that's interesting,
'cause that brings up
all kinds of possibilities.
Well, uh, don't be a stranger.
Oh...
So, this thing about Bailey.
Are you trying to say
whoever sent him back
meant him to go
after Kensington?
It's a theory.
That's why they call it
"the theory room."
That's tight.
Oh, no, I suck.
Hey, if this is about
the, uh, concert thing...
No, no, no, it's got nothing
to do about that.
I just want to know
what's going on
with you and Nikki.
Me and Nikki what?
I just want to know
what's going on between you two.
Well,
what do you think's going on?
Something.
She's always talking about you.
Can't go anywhere or do anything
without her wanting
to bring you along.
How is that my problem, Danny?
Just do me a favor.
Leave her alone, okay?
Oh...
I thought
that's what I've been doing.
Look, Danny, you got a problem
with your girlfriend,
go talk to her about it, okay?
Hey, uh...
we're the same age.
I'm not your little brother
anymore.
Then stop ting
like a two-year-old.
You're my brother.
She's your girlfriend.
It's all good...
right?
Yeah, right.
Oh, Richard, I am so glad
we found this place.
And now that we got an apartment,
we can get you a computer.
Forget abouthe computer.
I still think we need
to get you to a doctor.
I'm fine.
I know this is going
to sound strange,
but that other place
we looked at-
the baby didn't like it.
Marnal instinct's
kicking in already, huh?
No, it's not that.
It's that somehow...
I know what the baby's thinking.
Lily, the baby's
barely two months along.
It's not thinking anything.
Look, I can't explain it
any more than you can explain...
where you've been
for the past 50 years
or, or what's happened
to any of us
during the time we've been gone.
I don't sound too strange, do I?
Of course not.
Lily?
I used to rock Heidi like that
when she was a baby.
It feels like yesterday,
but it wasn't, was it?
No.
It was... what, 11 years ago?
I want to see Heidi.
I miss her.
Lily, give it some time.
Once Brian
is used to you being back,
he'll drop
the restraining order.
Shut up.
Just shut up!
Stop it! Cut it out!
It isn't funny!
Shut up! Just shut up!
Grab her legs, man.
Hey, guys.
Why don't you leave her alone?
Get lost!
No.
You get lost.
Go get him, man. Come on.
Hey, Maia.
How long have they
left you like this?
A while.
I think they all wt
on their coffee break.
Well, you know...
that's pretty dumb
of them, isn't it?
Will you stay
until they come back?
Of course.
And when they show up,
your doctors and I,
we're going to have
a little talk.
And then can I go home?
Home?
With you.
I don't like being here alone.
You want to come and stay with me?
You don't like
being alone, either.
I can always come back
for my checkups.
Please.
Look, Maia...
I'm not even sure
I'm the kind of person
I want to live with.
No, I-I eat cold pizza
for breakfast and...
That sounds all right to me.
Yeah, you know, Maia...
Just let me think
about it, okay?
Where have you been?
I was looking in on Maia.
Really.
Well, I promised her,
didn't I?
So, what do you got?
Sid e-mailed the latest
rearch clippings to us.
I think I found something
worth checking out.
One guy taking on three attackers
doesn't sound that farfetched.
I know, but if you saw him
you'd think it was impossible.
He was, uh, 35, 40.
Maybe 5'6".
Wehed 150 pounds.
So not exactly The Rock, huh?
But it was the way
that he moved.
Could he have been on
some kind of drug, maybe PCP?
He didn't act
like he was on drugs.
You know,
most guys would have walked away,
or, uh, maybe called the cops,
later, after it was
too late, but, uh...
this guy- he saved me.
I'm sorry.
Baldwin.
Linda.
Dinner, yeah. No.
Linda, I'm so...
Don't hang up, Linda.
Just, just...
Is there anything else
you can remember?
There is one thing.
This guy,
I don't mean
to be rude or anything,
but, uh, he smelled funny.
Like day-old fish.
So that was your
wife on the phone?
Excuse me... I don't
want to talk about it.
Fair enough.
So what, are we
in Orson Bailey territory here?
Well, I wouldn't rule it out.
Which would give us what?
A telekinetic insurance salesman,
a clairvoyant eight-year-old
and now some kind of
sad-sack super-vigilante.
Hell of a trio.
And those are only
the ones we know about.
Unless you can think
of anyone else.
Just take it one case at a time.
Heidi, do you remember
the formula
for an isosceles triangle?
Hey, buddy.
I saw that.
Richard...
Lily- Thank God.
Are you all right?
I been worried sick.
Where are you?
I've been arrested.
Carl...
I have my grandchildren
coming for dinner.
Uh, how 'bout
some nice swordfish?
You can't go wrong
with swordfish.
Carl!
Uh, give me a second, Burt.
You got, like...
What did I tell you about
chatting with customers
when there's work to be done?
Stop with the finger.
Stop...
I asked you
not to do that.
Let go.
I mean it.
I show up on time.
I do my work.
Now just leave me alone, okay?
Okay, okay.
So, how much swordsh
are we talking here?
I'm telling you, Tom,
there's a lot of chatter in DC
about putting the 4400
back in quarantine.
Not that I agree.
I mean, if they're
so dangerous,
how is cramming th
all into one space
going to make us
any safer?
So I took my pistol
and I shot her in the forehead.
Shot who?
Do us a favor, Tom.
Sign the divorce papers.
Do me a far, Dennis.
Stay out of it.
I spoke to her.
What are you doing
talking to Linda?
I've known her for 20 years.
I danced with her at your wedding.
Now I'm not supposed
to talk to her.
I was in the middle
of an investigation.
Tom, you asked her for dinner,
and you stood her up.
It slipped my mind.
Maybe.
Maybe you just don't want to
admit the truth to yourself.
Brian Moore?
Yeah.
I'm Richard Tyler,
a friend of Lily's.
Are you another one
of those 4400?
Is that a problem?
Look,
I warned her;
I told her to stay away,
but she wouldn't listen.
I understand you're set,
but Lily's in jail.
You don't want that.
What I want is a normal life
for my daughter, for my family.
She made a mistake.
It won't happen again.
I'm just supposed to take
your word for it?
I promise, you drop the charges...
she'll never bother you
or Heidi ever again.
You used to love her once,
remember?
Yeah, I remember.
I want you to stop.
I can't.
What do you mean, "can't"?
What you're doing
is dangerous,
not to mention illegal.
You can't just
go around beating people up.
I've been given an oppornity
here, Gracie,
and I'm going to take it.
I'm going to clean up that park,
and when I'm finished,
I'm going to clean up
the whole neighborhood.
Oh, God.
You sound like a crazy man.
You promised me you'd
call your counselor.
I never said that.
You said that.
Come tomorrow, I'm
going to call him.
You'd call Homeland Security on me?
If that's what it takes.
The way you're acting,
can you blame me?
What I'm doing here
I'm doing for us, Grace.
This is where we live.
I just want us to be happy
and to not be afraid anymore,
and it starts with Bradley Park.
And I don't want it to end there.
It won't. I won't let it.
They can't hurt me.
No one can.
Oh...
You're just one man.
I lost you once,
and I don't want
to lose you again.
I can do it.
I can make this neighborhood
safe again.
For you, for Mrs. Martino...
even Burt.
So please, stop worrying.
This is what I was meant to do.
This is my destiny.
*...or is this your way *
* To hide a broken heart? *
* Many dreams *
* Have been brought
to your doorstep *
* They just lie there *
* And they die there *
* Are you warm, are you real *
* Mona Lisa... *
This was brand-new
when I disappeared.
And it's a...
What'd you call it, a...?
Golden oldie.
Oh.
I guess I'm a golden oldie, too.
No, not to me.
Lily, we have to talk about
what happened last night.
No, there's nothing
to talk about.
Do you know what I saw
when I looked
through Brian's window?
A happy family.
I realized Heidi doesn't need me.
Well, maybe one day she...
Yeah, I'll be there
r her, if she does.
But until then, I...
I'll stay away.
This is where I want to be now.
Here with you.
Where I'm happy,
and the baby's happy.
Well, that makes three
happy people then.
All you've done for me...
it's not because I remind you
of the other Lily, is it?
Maybe at first.
But now all I see is you.
* Mona Lisa *
* Mona Lisa. *
Danny's inside.
I'm not here
to see Danny.
Cute. Could you turn it
back on, please?
Did Danny say something to you?
Is that why you're acting
like this?
Because our friendship
has nothing to do with him.
Nikki...
we don't have a friendship, okay?
Shawn, listen to me...
Hey, hey, hey, come here.
Let me see. Let me see.
Let me see what's going on.
It's okay. It's okay.
Let me see.
It's gone.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Must not have been
that bad of a burn.
Yes, it was.
You did something
to it, didn't you?
*...And be the one who
catches all your tears *
* That's why I need you to hear *
* I've found out a reason for me *
* To change who I used to be *
* A reason to start over new *
* And the reason is you. *
Tom.
See, the thing about vigilantes
is that they're not very common,
except in Charles Bronson movies,
so I had to create my own profile.
Now, we know he's
a white male, slender,
somewhere between 30 and 50.
He probably works a blue-collar job,
suffers from low self-esteem,
lives in a high-crime area.
I'm with you so far.
Right. So I cross-
checked my profile
with the members of the 4400
in and around the Seattle area,
and I came up with 37 names.
You're not going to take me
through all 37, are you?
Of those 37, I was able
to eliminate 24-
I'm sure you don't care how-
and that left me with 13.
I'm on the edge of my seat.
Here are my o favorites.
Robert Laurenzano
and Carl Morrissey.
They both fit the profile,
but Carl- he's our guy.
Check out his occupation.
Supermarket employee.
Yeah. I called the store.
Carl works in the seafood section.
And our guy smelled
like day-old fish.
Oh, yeah. I'm good.
Hey!
What the hell you doing?
I just cleaned that.
What?
Do you know
where your husband is?
We'd like to talk to him.
Why?
Any idea where he
was Tuesday night?
He was here.
You sure about that?
I just told you.
Have you heard of the Bradley
Park Vigilante?
Wh-What does that have to do
with Carl?
You tell us, Mrs. Morrissey.
You're not going to throw him
back into quarantine, are you?
We want to help him.
That's funny. That's all Carl
wants to do is help.
People grumble. They complain.
Nobody does anything.
Nobody tries to make
anything better except Carl.
Where is he, Mrs. Morrissey?
Carl.
Grace, I got rid
of all the graffiti.
Oh, my... oh, my God, Carl.
Oh, you should've seen it.
They, uh...
they were falling like bowling pins.
I didn't see the knife.
I don't know why
Get an ambulance!
It's a nice night.
No, no, no, stay here.
Just sit with me.
No...
I thought I could clean it up.
I thought I could clean the
whole neighborhood up myself.
I thought that's why
they sent me back here,
but I guess I was wrong, huh?
No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah.
No, don't leave me,
Carl, please.
No, no!
No! I just want you.
I just... I just want you.
No, no!
No!
No...
Why take this guy,
give him enough extra juice
to think he can make
a difference, send him back...
Only to get himself killed.
What's the point?
I wish to hell I knew.
Grace Morrissey,
wife of slain Bradley Park
Vigilante Carl Morrissey,
revealed today that her
late husband was one of
the controversial 4400.
Mrs. Morrissey went on to state
that her husband was a true
neighborhood hero,
a sentiment echoed
by many area residents.
Local law enforcement officials,
as well as a spokesperson for
the National Threat
Assessment Command,
refused to confirm or deny
Mrs. Morrissey's statement.
Okay, I got the paperwork.
Okay, I need you to sign there...
and there...
and initial here...
Mm-hmm.
and sign there.
So that's it?
You got Mr. Ryland's
signed approval.
That simplifies things.
I thought you were
one of the doctors.
Yeah. I thought you were asleep...
so you sure fooled me.
How would you like
to get out of here?
Now?
Right now.
Look out, look out,
look out. Thanks.
Where'Kyle?
Surgery.
Dr. Mayhew said he's got
some kind of fluid
building up in his skull,
and they're going to try and
relieve some of the pressure.
What do they mean, try?
They said
the draining fluid
might not be enough,
that... that-that more
might build up,
and if it does, then Kyle
could suffer permanent
brain damage within a week.
Uncle Tommy...
Mom's on the way.