In a land of myth
and a time of magic,
the destiny of a great kingdom rests
on the shoulders of a young boy.
Merlin! Spear.
Do you have any
natural gifts, Merlin? No.
Let me think...
I'm not naturally rude
or insensitive.
Just naturally irritating.
It's probably more scared of you
than you are of it.
Have we lost it? Who's missing?
Where's Sir Bedivere?
Aaaaagh!
The creature you describe
has all the characteristics
of the Questing Beast.
Surely that's a myth.
The appearance of the Questing Beast
is supposed to foreshadow
a time of great upheaval.
Gaius, that's an old wives' tale.
Look, whatever it is,
it is spreading panic.
The people fear
it will enter the city.
Then we must kill it. Arthur, gather
the guard together. We ride at dawn.
I beg you, Sire - do not
dismiss this. The beast is an omen.
I have seen it come before - the
night your wife Ygraine passed away.
I've told you not to speak
of that night again.
I have conquered the Old Religion.
Its warnings mean nothing to me now.
Arthur will destroy the beast
and we no longer suffer at its hand.
This is no ordinary beast, Merlin.
Don't worry. No, listen to me.
You don't understand.
Uther may not respect the Old
Religion, but it is very real.
To face a beast such as this, you
must understand where it came from.
What do you mean? At the very heart
of the Old Religion
lies the magic
of life and death itself.
The Questing Beast
carries that power.
One bite, you die.
And there is no cure.
Morgana! Morgana!
Wake up! No! No!
It's me, it's Gwen! Stop it.
It was just another dream.
It was terrifying. It's all right.
You've seen the foe we face.
It's a creature of nightmare.
But you are the best knights
in the realm.
We can and will kill it, before it
harms another citizen of our kingdom.
For the love of Camelot!
Arthur!
Morgana, what are you doing?
You cannot face it!
Morgana, go back to bed.
There is nothing to be afraid of.
Please, Arthur. I have seen
terrible things.
You cannot go. She's probably had
a bad dream, Sire.
I'll take her to see Gaius.
No, I will not let you go!
Please, Merlin, get her inside. No!
I will make sure he is safe,
my lady. I promise. No! No!
Let's follow the trail.
Keep close.
What is it?
Shh!
Hey!
Aaagh!
Fleoge. Bregdan anwiele gefeluec!
It didn't bite you, did it?
Arthur!
Somebody help me!
What's happened?
He's been bitten!
I tried to save him.
We must tell the King.
There must be something you can do.
I wish there was. I'll find a cure.
Merlin! Trust me.
Can you hear me, Sire?
Here.
The King will be here any moment.
He can't die.
It is my destiny to protect him.
We haven't done all the things
we're meant to do!
That is the lament of all men.
Gaius, he's my friend.
Then save him.
Gethlio!
Thurhaele!
Maybe the spells need time
to take effect.
The bite of the Questing Beast
is a death sentence
that no magic can overturn.
Where is my son? Arthur!
Do something, Gaius!
I am trying, Your Majesty.
Gaius will find a cure.
He will not let him die.
I will do everything in my power.
I will bear him to his chamber.
I have failed Arthur,
failed in my destiny.
And yet, you would not be here
if that were true.
He was bitten by the Questing Beast.
He's going to die.
Does he still breathe?
Only just.
Then there is still time to heal him.
I've tried, I cannot save him.
You do not know how to save him.
But you can tell me how?
Perhaps.
It will not be easy.
I will do anything. Anything?
Please. Just tell me
what I have to do! Very well.
The Questing Beast is a creature
conjured by the powers
of the Old Religion.
You must use the same
ancient magic to save him.
The Old Religion died out
centuries ago.
The Old Religion is the magic
of the earth itself.
It is the essence which binds
all things together.
It will last long beyond
the time of men.
But how can that help me
save Arthur?
You must find those
who still serve it.
Those who hold dominion
over life and death.
Go to the place that men call
the Isle of the Blessed,
where the power of the ancients
can still be felt.
There you will discover
Arthur's salvation.
Thank you.
Thank you. And Merlin -
the young Pendragon must live,
no matter what the cost.
Merlin, you're back.
I need your help. We must get this
to Arthur to ease his passing.
No. We have to save him.
We've already tried.
The Beast comes from
the Old Religion - the cure
must come from there as well.
There are few left with such an art.
There is an island beyond
the white mountains... No!
The Isle of the Blessed -
you know it?
It was said to be the centre
of the Old Religion,
the focus of its power.
Why did you keep this
from me? Because it was
too dangerous, Merlin.
It's our only chance!
I have to find it.
And once you are there, what will
you ask? For Arthur to be saved.
The Questing Beast chose Arthur.
That means the Old Religion
has decided his fate.
Then I will convince them to change
their minds. It is not that simple!
The high priests have the power
to mirror life and death.
But there will be a price to pay.
Merlin, please, I beg of you...
I'm sorry, Gaius.
But whatever the price is,
I will pay it gladly.
Here. You'll need a map.
And I'm going to give you this.
My mother gave it to me.
It's a rabbit's foot.
To keep you safe? It was said
to protect you from evil spirits.
It's rubbish.
I don't believe the superstition.
I don't know why I gave it to you.
No.
I want it.
Thank you.
You've got to keep Arthur alive
until I get back.
HE MOANS IN PAIN
Sleep, Arthur.
'You must travel to the place that
men call the Isle of the Blessed,
'beyond the white mountains, through
the Valley of the Fallen Kings.
'To the north of the Great Seas
of Meredor, you will find a lake.'
Gaius.
You should get some rest.
He must not be left alone.
I will nurse him.
You're not going to die, Arthur.
I'm telling you.
Because I know that one day,
you will be King,
a greater king than your father
could ever be.
It's what keeps me going.
You are going to live to be the man
I've seen inside you, Arthur.
I can see a Camelot
that is fair and just.
I can see a king that the people
will love and be proud to call
their sovereign.
For the love of Camelot...
you have to live.
Is there anything
I can get Your Majesty?
The people have begun
to say goodbye.
He is not yet gone, Sire.
But he will not recover.
Not without a miracle.
I don't believe in miracles.
Astyre!
Hello?
Hello, Merlin.
You?
Do you know who I am? Nimueh.
You can't be who the Dragon meant.
And why is that?
You tried to kill me.
Before I understood your importance.
And Arthur... Arthur was never
destined to die at my hand.
And now, it seems I will be
his salvation.
So you know what I've come to ask?
Yes. Will you do it?
I do not have the power
to mirror life itself
and yet give nothing in return.
I know a price will be asked. To
save a life, there must be a death.
The balance of the world
must be restored.
I willingly give my life
for Arthur's.
How brave you are, Merlin.
If only it were that simple.
What do you mean?
Once you enter into this bargain,
it cannot be undone.
Whatever I have to do, I will do.
His life is worth a hundred of mine.
The Cup of Life,
blessed by centuries of powerful
sorcery so that it contains
the very secret of life itself.
If Arthur drinks water from
the cup...he will live.
Tidrenas!
The bargain is struck.
I hope it pleases you.
Merlin!
We need to give this to Arthur.
What is it?
Water, drawn from the Cup of Life.
If Arthur drinks from it,
he will recover. Please hurry!
What are you waiting for?
What price did you pay
to redeem his life?
Whose life did you bargain?
We don't have time. Merlin!
Don't worry, Gaius,
everything's going to be all right.
What are you doing, physician?
What are you giving him?
It's, er...
It's a tincture,
made from the lobelia plant.
An ancient remedy
for poisonous bites.
A cure?
We hope.
Do you really think
it will have some effect?
It's our last resort, Sire.
Perhaps you should allow him
to rest. I will not leave him.
Please, Merlin, you must beware.
This is only the beginning.
Arthur!
The Prince lives.
I thought we'd lost you.
Don't worry, Father,
I'm not going to die.
I think there's someone watching
Maybe you're right.
On your long journey to become King,
you'll need a guardian angel.
I shall inform the court
that their Prince lives.
I knew it.
I said you'd be all right.
I can remember you talking to me.
You can? You stroked my forehead.
I was tending to your fever.
Never lost faith.
I was just talking.
Tell me again what you said.
I don't remember.
Yes, you do.
No, I don't. Come on.
Something about
the man I am inside.
No, I never said that. Guinevere!
I have to get these washed, Sire.
THUNDER RUMBLES
Aagh!
Gaius!
I'm alive! What is it?
What's happened? Merlin, stay there.
What's wrong?
No, don't.
Mother?
Merlin...
What's happened to her?
She's gravely ill.
Do something!
If I could... Please, Gaius.
Merlin, this is no ordinary illness.
This cannot happen! Who did you meet
at the Isle of the Blessed? Nimueh.
Nimueh?! It was as you said.
She demanded a price. But I
bargained my life, not my mother's!
Merlin, I wish there
was something I could do.
I will make you better. I will.
You knew this would happen!
You had me trade
my mother's life for Arthur's!
You said you would do anything.
Did you know my mother would die?
I knew the price would be
a heavy one. But you sent me anyway.
We need Arthur to live.
I'm not one of you!
We are both creatures
of the Old Religion.
It is the source of your power.
What's that supposed to mean?
Your destiny is to protect the young
Pendragon until he claims his crown.
And when he does,
magic can be returned to the realm.
Only then will I be free.
So that's all you cared about?
I thought you were my friend.
I am more than that, Merlin.
I am your kin.
No, the only family I have is my
mother, and you had me murder her.
Her life has not been taken in vain.
We will achieve great things
together, you and I.
For what you've done, I'll make sure
you never see the light.
Merlin!
You...won't see me...again.
Where is she?
She's sleeping.
I have to save her. You cannot.
If the balance of the world needs
a life, then Nimueh must take mine.
No, Merlin.
Yes. I will return to the island.
You are young.
Your gifts, your destiny,
are far too precious to sacrifice.
My destiny? This is my mother.
My powers mean nothing
if I cannot save her.
You have taught me so much.
You taught me who I am,
taught me the purpose for my skills,
taught me that magic should only
be used for great deeds.
But most of all, you have always
taught me...to do what is right.
Merlin...
I need to say goodbye to Arthur.
Ah, Merlin. How are you?
Good.
I'm pleased.
Yes.
I owe it all to Gaius.
I need to talk to you.
You still haven't
got it yet, have you?
I decide when we need to talk.
Not today.
I sometimes wonder
if you know who I am.
Oh, I know who you are.
Good. You're a prat.
And a royal one.
Are you ever going to change, Merlin?
No. You'd get bored.
Promise me this, if you get another
servant, don't get a bootlicker.
If this is you trying
to leave your job... No.
I'm happy to be your servant,
till the day I die.
Sometimes I think I know you, Merlin.
Other times... Well, I know you.
And you're a great warrior.
One day you will be a great king.
That's very kind of you.
But you must learn to listen as well
as you fight. Any other pointers?
No.
That's it.
Just...
don't be a prat.
Gaius had to go
and get some supplies.
He asked me to keep an eye on her
until you got back. Thank you.
I'm sorry. No, she'll get better.
I've tried to make her
feel comfortable.
You've such a good heart, Gwen.
Don't ever lose that.
I'm gonna make you well again.
I promise.
You'll see.
You're such a good son.
But I don't want you
to worry about me.
I know that the Gods
will look after me
and that one day,
I will see you again.
I will miss you.
I'll miss you, too.
Gaius?
'Dear Merlin,
'my life is already near to its end.
'There has, for the most part,
been very little purpose to it.
'Very little
that will be remembered.
'In contrast, Merlin, your life
is destined for greatness.
'Live by the tenets
I have taught you,
'and I believe you will, in time,
become the greatest warlock ever.
'To have known you has been
my greatest pleasure,
'and to sacrifice myself for you
is but an honour.
'You are, and will always be,
the son I never had.'
No!
I never thought
I'd see you here again.
My Lady.
It is a long time since you called me
that. I've come to ask for your help.
As you once did before, for Uther.
You did not like the outcome.
I offer a chance for you to atone
for the death of his wife.
I have saved the life of her son.
What more do you ask for?
That this time, you take
a just price.
Merlin intends to offer
his life for his mother's.
I want you to take mine
in his place.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
With all my powers of prediction,
I could never have foretold this.
Gaius the hero!
Why should I grant your wish?
You stood and watched as our friends
burned in the Great Purge.
Merlin is the one man who can bring
magic back to this land.
At Arthur's side, he can help
forge a new kingdom.
A world of peace and beauty
that we can only dream of.
And you're willing
to give your life, Gaius,
for the future they will bring?
I'm waiting.
Are you ready to die, Gaius?
Gaius?
For Merlin, I will give my life.
Ic, seo heahsacerd, the acwelle
strengthe ealdan aewfaestnesse!
Stop!
Back again so soon, warlock?
What have you done?
Your mother is safe.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Have you killed him?
It was his wish.
I bid my life for Arthur's,
not my mother's, not Gaius'!
The Old Religion does not care
who lives or dies.
Only that the balance
of the world is restored.
To save a life, a life must be taken.
Gaius knew this.
It is not the Old Religion
that has done this. It is you.
Come, now.
We are too valuable
to each other to be enemies.
No! I share nothing with you.
With my help,
Arthur will become King.
I will make Arthur King.
But you will never see that day.
Astrice!
Your childish tricks
are useless against me, Merlin.
I am a priestess of the Old Religion.
Forbearne!
You too are a creature
of the Old Religion.
You should join me.
You think I would join forces
with such a selfish and cruel magic?
Never.
So be it. Akwele!
Pity.
Together, we could
have ruled the world.
You should not have killed
my friend.
Gaius!
No-o-o! No-o-o!
Merlin... Merlin...
Gaius!
Gaius, you're alive!
What did you do?
Nimueh's dead. The balance
of the world has been restored.
You amaze me.
You've mastered the power
of life and death itself.
We'll make a great warlock
of you yet!
So you believe in me now?
Well, I would do...if...
if you could...
stop this blasted rain!
Merlin!
No! Aaagh!
transcript:chocolate
sync:innuit
www.tvsubtitles.net