Subtitles:
Put the gun down Team
www.sub-way.fr (1.00)
Sir, it's Senator Mayer.
- He's dead.
- Are you telling me that Jack Bauer
just killed a United States senator?
- How could you have let this happen?
- You wont lay this one at my feet.
What is it, Ethan, what's wrong?
I'm afraid I have no choice
but to resign as your chief of staff.
You're taking this too far.
- Where's Jack?
- We don't have him.
The man who framed Jack
for Burnett's murder was John Quinn,
a Starkwood contractor.
Jack went to Mayer
to prove it.
Starkwood was involved
with what's happened today.
They helped Juma bring down those planes
and attack the White House.
In exchange, they were allowed
to develop and manufacture
a WMD in Sangala.
The text message I got
off their agent's cell phone said
"Port of Alexandria,
lot C, 10:15 p.m."
Go red, go red!
Engage, engage.
Get that truck out of here now!
Tony! The truck, I'm going after it!
Cover me now!
I'm in possession of a biological weapon
interdicted at the Port of Alexandria.
- What's your status?
- Package is secure, we're inbound.
- What about Bauer?
- He's at the scene, sir,
he sought cover nearby.
We have to assume
that he contacted the authorities,
so we'd better be
on an accelerated timetable.
Get over here.
Starkwood reacquired the bioweapon.
They airlifted it right out of here.
They're headed due west
from my position.
I can't assault a private compound
without a proof that a weapon exists.
- Okay, where is the CDC?
- They're scrambling a team right now.
Send them to me.
You'll have all the proof you need.
- Jack, what happened?
- I was exposed.
We're ready for you, sir,
come with me.
Mr. Bauer. Dr. Macer, CDC.
We need you to get undressed.
You're the one that talked to Moss?
He brought me up to speed, said you had
some information about the bioweapon.
All I know
is that it was developed in Sangala,
According to rumors
from the village it was tested on,
all the victims suffered
from dementia and paralysis.
Check neurological vectors
and pathogens.
How much was released?
I'm not exactly sure.
The weapon was stored
in a pressurized canister.
It was breached for maybe two minutes
before I could seal it off.
This is not a reaction.
I've had these scars.
This is a full spectrum antibiotic.
It should counteract
a wide range of known pathogens.
Step inside, sir.
Raise your arms and close your eyes.
- Janis, where are we?
- Metro closed down Highway 236.
The CDC first responders are on-site.
What the hell's going on?
One of the bioweapon canisters
was breached.
- Jack may have been exposed.
- Oh, my God.
Starkwood took the canisters.
They probably fly it back
to their compound in Virginia,
- along with Tony Almeida.
- Almeida?
We think he might
have been taken captive.
Hang on one second.
Put together a briefing packet
on Starkwood.
I want every division caught up to speed
on what we might be dealing with.
You move on Starkwood?
That place is enormous.
- It's a military base.
- We'll do nothing
till we have concrete evidence
on the bioweapon from CDC.
Then I'll inform the president.
She'll decide how to proceed.
Almeida's not going to talk.
He's not the type,
he's the brave type.
Know the psychology of your subject.
That's in our manual.
Here we go.
Mr. Hodges,
we isolated the damaged canister.
We got lucky.
They know we have the weapons.
That's not so lucky.
How fast can you have them ready?
- It'll take me at least two hours.
- Too long, Tom.
We don't know
what the government knows.
They're coming, and they'll be coming
with everything they've got.
The only thing that's going to stop them
is getting this weapon ready to deploy.
Yes, sir, I'll do my best.
I know you will.
Okay, let's go!
What does the FBI know?
I'm not gonna ask you again.
Okay.
You're a good man, Tony.
I know your profile.
You've had some hard breaks.
I don't want to see you hurt,
so you just tell me
what the FBI knows
about what we're doing here,
and I can't say
you'll walk away smiling,
that would be unrealistic,
but you'll be alive.
You hear me?
I don't know anything,
Mr. Hodges.
I'm giving you a way out, Tony.
Sir,
may I speak to you for a moment?
- Not now, Greg.
- Please, sir, just for a moment.
What is it?
This was supposed to be
a covert operation.
That is not the case anymore.
The government knows
we have these weapons.
They're not going to sit
on that information.
What are you suggesting, Greg?
Maybe
we should destroy the evidence
while we still have some time.
I can't believe
that I'm hearing this from you.
I'm just trying to help, sir. I care
about this company as much as you do.
Oh, I doubt that.
We've invested
a lot of blood and treasure
to get these weapons.
I'm not going to give them up.
Think about
what you're risking, sir,
everything, everything you've built.
You say you're trying to help.
You know what I think? I think
you're worried about your own ass.
Get him out of here
and do what you have to do.
Think about what I said, young man.
You're a little nervous, Greg.
Well, I've got a news flash:
we're all nervous.
Keep your doubts to yourself.
I'm not going to tell you again.
We need to take more blood
and saliva samples,
and to collect
a spinal fluid specimen.
Until we know what it is,
we need to keep you under quarantine.
How long is it gonna be
till you know if I've been infected?
We should have the preliminary results
in the next 15 minutes.
- Dr. Macer.
- Yeah.
We've detected a trace amount
of pathogen concentrated near the truck.
We're picking it up in the surrounding
environments at lower concentrations.
- Can you identify it?
- No, but we're analyzing a sample now.
These levels shouldn't present
any danger to the nearby population,
but I still want
atmospheric monitors set up.
It's a good thing you sealed off
the canister. You saved a lot of lives.
You're going to have
to transport me back to FBI.
I'm still material evidence
in an ongoing terrorist threat.
Those were our orders.
We can run our tests from there.
Bob Justman's been associate counsel
for the past three years.
He and Ethan
worked very closely together.
He is certainly qualified
to be chief of staff.
But...
After what's happened today,
I think you should be looking
outside your administration.
An insider has a leg up.
Chief of staff has
a steep learning curve.
I think you're underestimating
the value of a fresh perspective.
You have someone in mind.
I do.
Rick Berman.
Would Rick even consider
leaving the private sector?
He's made his fortune. I think he'd jump
at the chance to serve his country.
- Let's sit down with him.
- Great.
But keep Bob on the list.
I still have a good feeling about him.
I'll start to set up meetings
tomorrow.
Livy, it could take weeks
to find Ethan's replacement.
In the meantime,
I'm going to need
a provisional chief of staff.
I'd like that to be you.
Madam President?
Tim Woods is here to see you.
Just give me a minute, please,
and then send him in.
Yes, Ma'am.
Livy, I need someone I can trust.
Especially after everything
that's happened today.
You're not going to say "no"
to your mother, are you?
Of course not.
Good.
Madam President, I have Larry Moss
at FBI calling for you.
- What's this about?
- I don't know the specifics,
but he says it involves
an imminent homeland threat.
Put him through.
It's all right, Tim.
I've made Olivia Acting Chief of Staff.
Agent Moss, you're on
with the president.
Madam President,
we have a situation developing.
First of all, you need to know
that Jack Bauer did not kill
Ryan Burnett nor Senator Blaine Mayer.
He was framed for their murders.
I knew it. Who framed him?
Our operational theory
is that he was set up by Starkwood.
I don't understand.
Why would Starkwood frame Jack?
To cover up the fact that they helped
Juma stage the terrorist attacks today.
What?
Ma'am, we have evidence
that Starkwood provided Juma
with technological support
and intelligence. And in return,
Juma allowed Starkwood to use Sangala
as a base to operate without having
- to worry about any oversight.
- A base for what?
To manufacture
weapons of mass destruction.
Specifically,
biological weapons.
What kind of bioweapons
are you talking about?
We're not sure, but it could be
some kind of neurological pathogen.
CDC has obtained a sample
and they're analyzing it now.
Agent Moss, you said
there was an imminent threat.
Yes, a large shipment of bioweapons
was delivered to Starkwood.
We believe
they're in possession of them.
These weapons are on U.S. soil?
We suspect they're at the Starkwood
headquarters in Virginia.
You're not suggesting
that Starkwood intends
to use those weapons
to attack this country?
We don't know, but,
given their actions today,
we need to move on Starkwood
immediately.
Madam President?
Assemble the Cabinet
and the Joint Chiefs.
Yes, ma'am.
Jack was right about Starkwood.
You found evidence
that they've been supporting Juma.
Did you find out why? What could
Starkwood possibly get from Juma?
The infrastructure to develop and test
biological weapons.
We think they're holding them
somewhere on the Starkwood compound.
Where's Jack?
He's on his way over here.
What, Larry?
He managed to secure the weapons,
but then...
Starkwood got them back.
And when that happened...
Jack was exposed.
He may have been infected.
He's being placed under quarantine.
He's on his way here
and we need to find out
everything that he learned
about these weapons.
And I think you should be
the one who debriefs him.
And I owe you an apology.
I was wrong not to trust you,
and I let my prejudice about Bauer
get in the way.
But...
Renee,
you should've kept me in the loop.
You should've trusted me.
I know.
I should have.
When are we moving on Starkwood?
Aaron?
I'll check in with you guys later, okay?
Thank you.
- May I speak with you for a moment?
- Of course.
I heard you finished your debrief
and were on your way out.
Yes, ma'am.
Well, I need you to stay.
Ma'am?
I've been appointed
Acting Chief of Staff.
Secret Service is going to assign
an agent to handle my security detail.
I'd like that to be you.
Well, I'm truly flattered, ma'am,
but as you know, I'm retired.
I can have you reinstated.
There are plenty of fine agents
on the roster.
But I don't want them.
I want you.
I can't go into the details now,
but the threat to this country
isn't over.
We're in the middle of a crisis,
and I need people around me I can trust.
I trust you, Aaron.
I can't say that
about a lot of people.
I'm running
into a meeting with the president.
I'll assume your answer is "yes."
Gentlemen, ladies,
please take your seats.
Those of you who haven't had a chance
to finish your briefing packets,
please keep reading.
As we've all just learned,
this day is not over.
Our national security
is still being threatened,
and we are here
to consider our options.
Mr. Woods.
Your briefing materials include
FBI intelligence
about a cache of biological weapons
on Starkwood's main compound
in Northern Virginia.
This is a recent satellite view
of the compound.
Over 3 square miles,
259 structures...
the weapons could be hidden
anywhere on the facility.
What kind of bioweapons
are we talking about?
This is Ben Landry,
he's director of CDC.
He's here to answer any questions
you may have in regards to the pathogen.
I've just received a preliminary report
from our agents in the field.
They've identified the pathogen
as a prion variant
indigenous to the East Congo.
It's a form
of Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease.
It attacks the brain
and the nervous system,
causes dementia,
physical deterioration,
ultimately death.
Standard CJD kills
within several months,
but this strain kills more quickly.
- How long?
- A day, maybe two.
There's no treatment.
There's no cure.
If dispersed over a populated area,
the results would be catastrophic.
But it goes without saying we cannot
allow a private military force,
these killers, to possess
weapons of mass destruction.
We need to find these weapons,
and arrest
those bastards in Starkwood
who are responsible
for bringing them here.
Madam President.
Given the size of the compound,
it would take a considerable force
to locate these weapons.
Not to mention the fact
that there are 1,500 highly-trained
mercenaries on that base.
God forbid they decide to resist.
We could have a small war
in our own backyard.
I share those concerns,
Madam President.
We also have to consider
the possibility
that Starkwood might use
these biological weapons
against our own forces.
What about an air strike?
A facility that large would require
multiple bombing runs.
We'd be looking at massive casualties
on the Starkwood base,
with no guarantee
of destroying the bioweapons.
For all we know, they've been buried
underground or in fortified facilities.
There's also a risk that hitting
these weapons with insufficient force
could release the bio-agent
into the atmosphere.
We can't just ignore the law here.
All these scenarios would be
in violation of the Posse Comitatus Act.
We can't deploy military personnel
in a law enforcement capacity.
Not without congressional approval.
What I'm hearing
is that there are no good options.
I don't accept that.
Until we find a way
to contain this threat,
we are risking another attack
on this country.
And that is an option
I won't consider.
Mr. Hodges wants to know if you've given
any thought to his offer.
Why this loyalty
to a government that screwed you over?
I don't get it.
Just tell us what the FBI knows
and you can walk.
For the record,
I bet Mr. Hodges a pair
of Redskins tickets you wouldn't talk.
Looks like I'm going to be sitting
on the 50 yard line.
Hey, what the hell's going on?
I need your help.
My help?
We need to stop this.
It's gone too far.
I'm not going anywhere
until you tell me why you're doing this.
I'm not spending
the rest of my life in prison
because Jonas Hodges
has lost his mind.
- You know where the weapons are?
- Yes.
Then you better tell me right now.
- I want immunity.
- Look, I can't promise you anything.
We can call the FBI
and negotiate a deal,
immunity in exchange for your help,
that's the best I can do.
I can set up
a secure landline in my office.
Good, let's go.
We're pulling up to FBI.
We have to put you in an isolation suit
to transfer you to the quarantine area.
I understand.
How are you feeling?
No different.
- We have the results of the blood work.
- Thank you.
Open it.
Thank you.
Excuse me. Larry wanted me to tell you
that CDC arrived with Jack Bauer.
- I'll meet them down in quarantine.
- He's not in quarantine.
- I don't understand.
- That's all I know.
They just cleared security.
He's on his way up.
Are you okay?
My blood work came back positive.
I'm infected.
Mr. Bauer, there's a room
for you to change in.
Thank you.
It's fine.
- But he's not in quarantine.
- The disease isn't contagious.
It was engineered that way to prevent
blowback on the people deploying it.
OK, but there has to be something
that you can do to help him.
There's no cure.
But he's patient zero.
Whatever we learn from the pathogen
will come from the tests we'll run.
Excuse me.
This is Macer.
He's stable for the moment.
Jack,
I don't know what to say.
Then tell me that Agent Moss
followed up on Starkwood.
Sorry.
Larry debriefed the White House
and we're waiting on the President
to decide on a course of action.
Good.
Any word on Tony?
Sorry, we don't know anything yet.
I need to debrief you
on the canisters that you saw.
- You okay with that?
- Yeah.
I read the statement
from the Port Authority cop.
He said that you risked the mission
to save his life.
You did the right thing.
Thanks.
It's the lab.
It's probably Hodges.
We should talk to him.
Put it on speaker.
- Seaton.
- Where the hell have you been?
I've been trying to reach you.
I was checking on Almeida.
- Did Stokes get him to talk?
- He's still working on that, sir.
I told him to put Almeida down
if he didn't start talking.
I think we should give him
a few more minutes, sir.
We're busting our asses
to get these weapons ready
before the government
makes their move,
I want all hands on deck.
We'll be there soon.
See that you are, Greg.
Call FBI.
I need to set up the secure landline.
Make sure nobody's listening.
All right, well, do it.
I never thought Jonas
would take it this far.
I mean, the man's a patriot.
He founded Starkwood
to protect this country.
- Yeah, well, why is he attacking it?
- It's complicated.
I don't understand it myself.
I should've done more to stop this.
I should've called FBI months ago.
You're doing the right thing now.
I've pulled together
everything we have on Starkwood.
Structural specs, aerial maps,
topography, company roster,
the whole works.
Upload it onto the interagency servers.
Let's get everybody on the same page.
That's good work.
I heard about Jack.
I'm sorry.
I'm still debriefing him but I brought
a full description of the canisters.
All right.
Get this out to the field agents.
How's he doing?
Hard to tell.
So many people have died today.
We cannot let their deaths
be for nothing.
We won't.
I've got Tony Almeida on the phone.
Almeida?
He says he's calling from Starkwood.
Put him through.
Go ahead, Tony.
- Who am I talking to?
- It's Larry Moss. What's going on?
I'm on the Starkwood compound.
I was being held by a man
named Jonas Hodges,
but I was released by one
of his executives. A man named...
Greg Seaton.
Now he wants to cut a deal.
He wants immunity.
What's he offering in return?
He knows where the weapons are.
Tony, I got to run this
by the President.
Wait, Larry.
Do you know what happened to Jack?
He's here.
He's in medical.
- Was he hit?
- No.
One of the canisters was breached.
He's been infected.
Tony, I got to call the White House.
Stand by.
Set up a secure connection with Almeida
and the White House for this signature.
And get the President on the phone.
What is this?
Footage recovered from Sangala.
It was smuggled out of the remains
of a biological weapons lab
about 45 minutes ago.
It's a confirmation
that Juma was experimenting
with biological weapons
on the local population.
These poor people were suffering
from the effects
of the weaponized prion variant.
And that's what we allowed Starkwood
to bring into this country.
We didn't allow this.
Starkwood is a monster
we created, Olivia.
We have been feeding it for years.
We gave them military contracts.
We relied on their paid mercenaries
instead of our own soldiers,
outsourced intelligence
gathering operations.
My God, we even passed a law
so that they could build a military base
13 miles from the nation's capitol.
You fought against all that.
You've been trying to limit Starkwood's
power ever since you took office.
I didn't do enough...
fast enough.
And now it may be too late.
Madam President, Tim Woods
and Admiral Smith are here to see you.
- Send them in.
- Yes, madam.
Madam President, Larry Moss at FBI
is calling in. He says it's urgent.
Put him through.
Agent Moss, the president's here.
Go ahead.
Madam President, we've been contacted
by someone inside Starkwood.
- Ma'am, it's Tony Almeida.
- Almeida?
He was working with Bauer
to recover these weapons.
He was taken captive
but then released
by someone on the inside.
His name is Greg Seaton.
He's part of Jonas Hodges' inner circle.
Ma'am, he says he's willing
to tell us where the weapons are
in exchange for immunity.
I've already started mobilizing
for a targeted raid.
We can catch 'em by surprise
and lock down these weapons.
But I'm going to need you to sign
an immunity agreement for this man.
How confident are you
of Seaton's intel?
We believe it's genuine, ma'am.
Madam, we may not
get a chance like this again.
- Admiral Smith?
- I concur,
but I would suggest we supplement
the FBI with a SEAL squad.
They're ready to move on my order.
The attorney general will raise hell
about us involving the military
- in this operation.
- We'll deal with him later.
Agent Moss, you have
my direct authorization
to move on Starkwood.
How soon can you be ready?
We've already drafted an executive
pardon, and set it up via WebEx.
You'll be able to give a secure
digital signature and we're good to go.
We have the document set up
at your assistant's computer.
- The President is prepared to sign.
- Go ahead, ma'am.
Alright, it's done.
- You get the signature?
- Yeah, we're good.
When can you be at Starkwood?
We can be there in 10 minutes.
Agent Moss, thank you.
- And good luck.
- Thank you.
Let's go.
Madam President,
we may have just caught a lucky break.
Until this plays out, I want everyone
to keep looking for other options.
All right, Mr. Seaton. Go ahead.
The weapons are in a warehouse
on the northeast quadrant
of the compound.
32° 44.23' north...
117° 10,42' west.
It would help to have someone
on the ground doing recon.
Can you get Tony to that warehouse?
I think so.
See if you can find a hand radio.
We'll be on 480 kilohertz.
We'll be there.
If we land here, we'll be
within 50 yards of the warehouse.
Yeah, support teams here and here.
Shore us up. Coordinate with the Navy.
- Get moving. I'll meet you upstairs.
- Let's move!
- You're mobilizing. What's going on?
- We got a call from Tony.
He's working with an informant
inside Starkwood.
We got a location on the weapon,
we're staging a raid on the compound.
- I want to go.
- I can understand why, but I'm sorry.
- No.
- I can help you.
I've seen the canisters,
I know exactly what we're looking for.
I read your debrief.
You gave us all the details we need.
Larry, please, I've earned this.
I know what you've done today,
the sacrifice you've made.
Under any other circumstances,
I'd want you out there with us,
but you're sick,
and we have no idea when you're
going to start showing symptoms.
I cannot risk that
happening out in the field.
I need my best men
for this operation.
I hope you can understand that.
You're right.
I always knew eventually
we'd agree on something.
I'm so sorry, Jack.
- Mr. Seaton?
- I need to check the personnel that...
That's it.
The weapons are inside there.
How many men inside?
Hodges, munitions team, security.
I'm guessing a dozen or more.
Wolves are at the door, Tommy.
How much longer?
We're still an hour away
from being armed.
We just intercepted
a government transmission.
FBI is on the way.
Sir, we haven't even run
the sequence checks yet.
Let's do it!
Damn it.
What's our ETA?
Two minutes, sir.
Tony, it's Larry Moss.
Are you in position?
Affirmative.
We're about 50 yards north
of the warehouse.
- What can you tell me?
- Got two entrances, north and south.
Heavy steel doors.
Two guards
armed with automatic weapons.
There's probably about a dozen inside.
We have to assume they're armed as well.
We're almost there.
I'm gonna need your eyes on the ground
in case there's any resistance.
Copy that.
Aerial One to home base.
Target has been confirmed.
We are go for Tac plan Alpha.
Copy that, A-1. All feeds are live.
We're monitoring your approach.
Sir, we're being signaled
by Starkwood's air tower.
Let me talk to them.
- You're on.
- This is Special Agent Larry Moss, FBI.
We have an executive order
from the president of the United States
to search one of your buildings.
FBI? I'll need to get authorization
from my superior.
We have sent you a digital copy
of the executive order.
Check your wireless frequency.
That is all the authorization
you will need.
Make no attempt to interfere,
or you will be arrested.
Do you understand?
Understood, FBI.
Take us in.
Aerial One to home base.
We're good to go.
Copy that, Aerial One. Looks like you've
a clean approach. No hostiles in sight.
You all right?
We have a medic.
I'm fine.
I need you to stay behind us.
Let's go.
Stand down!
You were told to stand down!
Lower your weapons
and get on the ground now!
Lock them down!
- It's locked, sir.
- Blow it.
Blasting! Three. Two. One!
Go. Go!
Where are the weapons?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean, you don't know?
Almeida was threatening to kill me.
I told him what he wanted to hear.
You lying son of a bitch!
You came to me!
Now, where are the weapons?!
- Where are they?
- Tell him to take his hands off of me.
I need you to stand down now!
- You're not getting away with this.
- Secure him!
He's lying, Larry.
He played me.
Yeah, I know. It looks that way.
Well, what do you know?
Little old Seaton
bought us some time.
They're on the other side
of the compound.
We just have to keep them there.
There's nothing here, sir.
The warehouse is empty. Tony's informant
sent us to the wrong location.
This whole thing was a diversion.
They couldn't have gotten them out that
fast. The weapons are there somewhere.
The weapons have to be inside
of Starkwood. Tell them to keep looking.
Stand by.
All right, everyone outside now.
All right, listen up.
We're going to do a point-by-point
search of this entire compound.
Good.
I want four teams sweeping
every structure on this property.
Hold your fire!
Hold your fire.
Stay in position.
Tell Larry to have his men
stand down.
They just drew on federal forces.
If you don't want to lose your men,
you'll get them to stand down now. Now!
Hold your fire!
That's far enough.
We cooperated with your demand
to search this building.
We're asking you to leave.
There are biological weapons
on this facility.
We're not going anywhere without them.
Now, tell your men to stand down.
Those charges are absurd, and we're not
going to let you keep searching.
You're on private property,
and we're prepared
to defend it if necessary.
You are threatening federal agents.
Stand down! Now!
We're protecting our rights
against a hostile government
that's using false charges
to try to shut us down.
We don't want any bloodshed.
But if you try to advance
any farther,
you will be fired upon.