Previously on "One Tree Hill"...
Haley, marry me again in front of our all friends and our family.
It's hurt me to see what's happened with your relationship with Dan.
Uncle Cooper, what are you doing here, man?
I met this smoking-hot girl.
- I'm 17.
- You got to go.
You know you still want me, Cooper.
The guy shot up a school.
Yo, Marcus, would you shut up, man?
I hope they fry his ass.
Promise me that when you pick the boy you're really gonna be with
that he'll be someone who you love.
Use your head and follow your heart.
"Once upon a time, there was a beautiful princess
who lived in a kingdom far, far away.
And in that kingdom, there also lived a boy,
and the princess loved that boy."
Unbelievable.
"And so the two decided to marry."
Did you just say you wanted to get married?
Yeah. Crazy, right?
- It's a little nuts, yeah.
- Okay, but maybe not.
It worked for Nathan and Haley. Look how happy they are.
Brooke, let me in!
No, it's not ready. Go away.
It's my apartment, and it's my wedding dress, for that matter.
No, it will be. But for now, it is my wedding dress, and it is not ready.
Does it look like my dream dress, Vera Wang meets Snow White?
It's better.
Yay.
This is so exciting.
So, how did Nathan ask you to marry him the first time?
Um, well, it was raining, and we just had that argument, the, um...
one that I told you about.
Oh, the one about the internet porn.
Yes. Thank you for reminding me.
Anyway, we made up in the rain,
and we were laying in bed the next day, and, uh,
he just looked over at me and said,
"you're my family now."
And he said that he could love me forever.
Then he asked me to marry him.
- That's so sweet.
- Yeah.
But the dress still isn't ready, so you need to find something else to do with yourself. Chop-chop.
You're such a grouch when Lucas isn't around.
How long until he gets back?
A couple of hours. Just in time for your rehearsal party,
which, like your dress, is a total surprise.
I hate surprises.
Not these you won't. I promise.
Get out of here.
Hi.
Oh, hi.
You're Deb, right?
Yeah.
I was wondering if you could tell me how to get in touch with Cooper. I'm--
No, I'm sorry. He's out of town. Can I give him a message?
Just tell him his girlfriend stopped by.
Rachel...
Look, um, I know you've called the house,
and I'm sure you've tried his cell, but...
I think you know this is not going to work out.
Well, maybe I'll just wait and hear that from him.
You're not going to, okay?
And I know that must hurt, but you're in high school, and he's nearly 30.
What's next? He takes you to the prom?
If you thought this could work, you wouldn't have lied in the first place.
Did he tell you that he slept with me after he knew how old I was?
Yes, he did.
He also told me that it was a terrible mistake...
...one he regrets.
Just tell him I stopped by.
Okay, this is weird.
Normally it's the groom that can't see the dress before the wedding, not the bride.
Quit whining. Are you ready?
Yes, please!
All right, Haley James Scott, I now pronounce you...
fabulous.
Do you love it?
You're speechless!
I knew you would be. Hold on. There's one more thing.
Do you get it -- halo?
Wow, wow. Brooke, this is, um...
You're  welcome.
Thank you so much for asking me to be your maid of honor. I love weddings.
"Now, in this kingdom, all was not well."
I love you, Jake.
I do.
And you know that I love Jenny.
So maybe that's enough.
I think only in fairy tales that's enough, Peyton.
You know what?
Someone told me once that there's nothing wrong with fairy tales.
Everybody lives happily ever after.
Okay, listen to me.
You can't just fly into Savannah and then get in my head all over again,
tell me you want to stay, and then ask me to marry you.
- Why not?
- Because...
I might just say, "yes."
"So the princess and the boy were set to be wed.
And because she was a princess, the call went out for a beautiful gown."
Whoa.
Sorry, I'm not supposed to see you in your wedding dress, right?
It's okay. This is not my wedding dress.
It's not?
No, it's supposed to be, but there is no way that I am getting married in this frock.
I asked Brooke to make me something simple and elegant,
and, instead, she makes me something that's so...
Brooke!
Maybe you should wear it, anyway.
Brooke's your maid of honor, and you did ask her to make the dress, right?
So?
So she'd be crushed if you didn't wear it.
Anyway, it doesn't matter what you wear.
My girl's gonna look beautiful...
Thank you.
- Except maybe in this thing.
- Oh, shut up!
Hello?
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I know where it is. All right. I'll be there.
All right, bye.
Peyton's car broke down. You want to come with me?
Um... yeah, actually. Let me just go change.
You  can drop me at the cafe. I'm gonna need money for a new wedding dress.
What's on your mind, kiddo?
B rooke.
You know, it was nice to get away, but I'm glad we're gonna be home soon.
Did you like any of the colleges we looked at?
Yeah, but, you know, I figure I'll just go to somewhere we can afford.
I mean, thanks to my heart condition, I won't be getting a basketball scholarship.
You know, this trip wasn't just about finding you a school.
It was also about finding a way back.
To what?
To a place where it's okay to dream again.
You walked away from basketball so that you could live a long life.
What are you gonna do with that life?
What's your next dream, Lucas?
Hey.
Sorry about this.
No problem. What did it do -- overheat?
Yeah. I'm not really sure why, though.
So, how's your leg doing?
Oh, um... it's okay.
It's just kind of weird everybody knowing about it.
I was in the tutor center that day.
Well, I guess you know my friend Haley then?
Not really.
But I think that was kind of the point.
You got a hole in your radiator.
I'm gonna have to tow you in. I can drop you off somewhere if you want.
No, it's okay. I called someone.
Hey, you okay?
- How's it going, Nate?
- Hey, Marcus.
So, I guess you guys have met.
Yeah.
How you been?
Could be better.
You mind giving me a hand?
Sure.
I'm gonna go clear my head.
Okay.
So, uh, I haven't seen you around much.
It's 'cause you don't hang out with any cool people.
Good.
Nah, the truth is, that day in the tutor center kind of screwed me up.
Yeah, I think it kind of screwed all of us up, man.
Yeah, I guess, but...
I just made it worse.
Sometimes I wish I could talk to the kid in that room and try to help him.
Edwards, you mean?
And me too...
the me I was then.
So, you're working a part-time job now, huh?
No, full-time.
You dropped out of school?
Yeah.
It was hard walking past that room,
so I just quit going.
Thought it might help, but...
I guess we're all gonna have that day with us forever.
You know I love you, Sawyer, but, uh,
isn't this the kind of thing you usually call Lucas for?
He's out of town.
What about Brooke?
Jake, you okay?
You know you talk in your sleep?
Uh, yeah, I'm sorry.
I've been sitting awake, wrestling with the feeling that...
you need to go back to Tree Hill.
You shouldn't stay here.
You can't.
Why? What happened?
You talk in your sleep, Peyton.
Okay, so -- so what? I don't -- I don't understand.
So, what, I mumble a few words in my sleep?
I mean, what did I say? Was it really that bad?
Did I say I wanted to kill you or something?
No.
You said, "I love you."
Okay, well, normally, that's a good thing.
You said, "I love you, Lucas."
Now, as the wedding day approached,
the princess worried about the evil king.
Because, although he had not always been this way,
his heart had turn dark and his kingdom had grown to fear and despise him.
Okay, Mr. Scott you gotta go home because you've been out here all morning,
and you're kinda creeping some of the customers out,
and Deb's not working today, okay?
How's Nathan doing ? I mean since he lost Keith ?
He's a mess, especially since he lost his father long before that.
Haley.
I hear the two of you plan on renewing your vows.
I'm happy for you.
You're the best thing that's happened in his life in a long time.
Would you tell him I send my best?
I understand he wants to keep his distance with this restraining order. I respect that.
Mr. Scott, I'm not buying it...
This...
You.
I guess I can respect that, too.
I'm glad that you're protective over him, Haley.
I suppose if he reaches his potential, it doesn't matter who got him there,
you or me.
It's just that he gets there that's important.
Have a nice wedding day.
Hey, this is Cooper. You know the drill.
Hey, Cooper. I was just thinking about you and thought I'd try you again.
Give me a call, okay?
It's kind of starting to feel like you're trying to avoid me.
Okay, bye.
Hey, buddy. Okay, I know I said I was done with the dress, but I came up with a fantastic idea.
It involves feathers but tasteful feathers, so don't freak out.
Okay, um... I-I need to talk to you about the dress.
Okay.
I know that you've worked really hard on this, and I just love you for it.
Um, I just don't know if it's me.
You don't like it?
No, it's not that I don't like it. It's just a little...
Maybe we can just take it down a little, you know?
I worked really hard on this.
- I know you did, like I said --
- And you hate it.
I don't hate it. I just want something simple.
This is simple.
Brooke, you're -- you're putting feathers on it.
Fine.
You know what? Why don't you wear that stupid hat and poncho of yours for all I care?
Brooke, there's no need to get nasty.
No? You can insult my fashion sense, but I can't insult yours?
Brooke, all I'm saying is I want something closer to the picture.
Right, closer to the picture.
Okay, so if you want to go shopping and buy a new wedding dress, why don't you go to Slut Barn?
I'm sure they're having a sale.
Oh. Well, you would know, wouldn't you?
You told Lucas that you loved him?
It was the school shooting, okay, and I was bleeding.
And I thought I was gonna die. I didn't mean it like that!
Jake, I love you.
I know that you do.
Well, then why are you making such a big deal about this?
When you decided that you weren't gonna go back to Tree hill,
do you remember what you told me?
Yeah.
You said that your father's not around,
that Haley has Nathan,
and that Brooke has Lucas.
Okay, you know what? Haley and Brooke are my best friends,
and they spend a lot of time with their boyfriends. That's all I meant by that.
Let me ask you a question.
What if Brooke didn't have Lucas?
"In the days before the wedding, the king surprised the princess
and gave his blessing to the marriage,
but the princess was still torn
for, even though she had found her true love,
it meant she would have to leave her faithful handmaiden behind forever."
Hi, only friend I can trust.
Whoa,  what's wrong?
Did you break up with Pete?
I didn't go to see Pete.
When I left this weekend, I went to go see Jake.
Oh... my... god.
But that's a good thing, right?
Don't you see, Peyton?
You asked me to marry you after Jenny called you mama...
Yeah.
After you lost your mom again.
- And your dad's not around.
- Oh, you know what? Don't.
You're alone, Peyton. I get it.
It makes all the sense in the world that you want a family.
No, I want this family.
Do you?
Okay, you know what? Just don't...
I don't understand this, okay? 'Cause it seems like you're working really hard to push me away.
So if you're not into me, just say so.
No, that is not it. I love you, Peyton, okay?
I don't want to believe there's another guy in your heart,
but I think that there is.
I think that you're afraid.
Yeah,  you know what? I am afraid.
It hurt like hell the last time I lost you, and I --
I-I don't want to do that again.
Then don't.
L ook.
Marriages fall apart all the time because people, they get caught up with the romance,
and they're not honest with themselves.
Well, I have to be twice as honest --
once for me, once for Jenny.
Whoa! Anyone I know?
Mostly me. I talked to Brooke today.
Oh, boy.
I have never seen someone go from so thrilled to so hurt
to really mean so quickly, and that was just me.
I'm sorry, Hales.
Well, hey. You'll never guess who I ran into today -- Marcus.
Marcus-from-the-tutor-center Marcus?
Yeah. You know he dropped out of school?
I ran into Dan today. Who do you think is a bigger ass?
Actually, he seemed like he was really affected by the whole thing,
like maybe he was trying to change because of it.
Actually, I was gonna say the same thing about Dan, believe it or not.
Not.
But I was thinking about inviting him to the wedding and to the dinner tonight.
- Dan?!
- No -- Marcus.
I mean, I'd love to include my dad, but I know he'd just screw it up.
There's still hope for Marcus.
Oh, and just a reminder. You still got to pick out our first-dance song.
I know. I have it narrowed down to three.
Oh, cool.
I'll tell you what. Give me those songs, I'll surprise you on the day.
- Okay, it sounds fun.
- All right.
Now what are you going to do about Brooke?
I mean, besides pretending that she's a speed bag and wailing on her?
I am going to apologize and hope she forgives me.
That's my girl.
Literature.
You asked me about my future.
And if I could go to any college, it would be U.N.C. to study literature.
My son, the next great american author.
I don't know about that, ma.
And U.N.C. would be your dream school?
Yeah, sure, if we had the money.
Okay, listen to me.
Before we left, the lawyer who drew up the adoption papers called.
He told me that ever since you were born,
Keith has been saving a fund for you for college.
I didn't know about it myself.
He dreamed your dream with you, Lucas.
And if this is something that you really want, and you have the grades, then...
you can have it...
because Keith left it for you.
God, I miss him so much.
He's always with you.
Always.
You make him proud.
I will.
I totally lost my mind and went off on Haley.
- I called her a slut.
- Ow.
You know what? I'm proud of you, B. Davis.
Helping Haley find another dress is --
Oh, no. We're not shopping for her.
We're shopping because I feel miserable, and this is therapy.
Brooke...
Oh, see? All better. Be right back.
Rachel?
He said he liked me.
I need him to like me.
"On the eve of the princess' wedding, a lavish feast was arranged.
Friends and royalty were summoned from lands far away
to join the happy couple for a night of laughter and magic."
Well, well. As usual, Brooke Davis shows up when all the work is done.
Sorry, I had some things I had to deal with.
Speaking of, you never told me how everything ended up with Jake.
Uh, just not what I wanted it to be, um...
I think I'm gonna go hide the knives.
- Hey.
Um...
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I was being selfish, and I wasn't listening to you.
I was so wrapped up in what I wanted that dress to be, that I freaked out a little bit.
I would love to wear your dress.
That's really nice, but I think you might want to save the love until after dinner tonight.
You know all those questions I've been asking you about the early days of Naley?
Yeah.
You didn't think I really wanted to know all that, did you?
Yes.
No. I was just gathering material.
See you tonight.
It's really filling up out there.
Really?
Thank god. I was worried.
Apparently, there's a flu going around, and everybody's dropping like flies.
Lucas should be back any second.
Are you excited?
Yeah, I am.
But I don't know. It's -- it's kind of strange.
I realized since he's been gone that I'm not as dependent on him as I thought.
You know, I have my clothing line, and I have my friends, and I have me,
and I'm not such bad company.
Who knew?
Peyton. Naley's here.
Okay.
Brooke...
you're the best company.
Believe that.
...a time, there was a girl and boy.
No. Once upon a time, in a land far, far away, a girl and a boy...
Hey, pretty girl.
Hi, boyfriend. Oh, I missed you.
I missed you.
This place looks great.
- You did good, Brooke.
- Yeah, I know I did.
Peyton and some other people helped, but it was mostly me.
Small problem.
Skills is sick, and he's supposed to be in that first scene with me.
Fergie said he'd stand in for him, but I don't think
anybody's gonna buy him as Nathan 'cause, you know...
...his hair.
Um, you know what? I think it's gonna be fine. Just give him a set of lines.
Lucas, here's yours. It's -- it's showtime.
Once upon a time, in a kingdom far, far away, a girl and a boy fell in love.
And then another girl, supposedly a friend,
secretly taped how they fell in love and decided to use it against them.
So tonight I give you an authentic and very unauthorized re-enactment
of "Nathan and Haley, a fairy tale."
Look at that blond girl! Look at her wig!
Oh, my god.
So you're Nathan Scott, Mr. big-shot basketball player.
I don't trust you, and I'm totally not into you,
and I'm just tutoring you so that you'll leave my best friend Lucas alone.
Damn, baby. That is one ugly-ass poncho.
Yo, check it out.
Don't say I never gave you no bling.
Listen, Nathan. I know you collapsed on the basketball court tonight,
so I was thinking maybe you wanted to stay the night and get a little freaky.
How about this?
Okay.
- This is not how it happened.
- Yes, it did.
No! It's not!
What's wrong, Haley?
I just want to go home to my own room.
I'm not a wife.
I'm not even a senior.
I'll always be there for you, Mrs. Scott --
I mean, um, Haley -- always and forever.
Um, it seems that there's a bit of a bug going around, and we've lost a few performers.
So I was wondering if, in this next scene, Nathan wanted to play himself?
What? No, no.
You're gonna wake my parents. That's their room.
Uh, look, Haley, I --
That's not in the script.
You missed a few lines!
Gosh.
I think I messed up.
We better start over.
I decided to go for a run, and I ended up here. Boy, is it raining out.
I'm mad at you, Nathan Scott.
Haley, please listen to me.
I know I'm a... porn freak.
Hey.
Ha ha.
Nathan, it's okay. I like my porn, too.
And I Haley myself from time to time.
But I still need to know if you love me.
Someday, I'm gonna marry you, Haley James.
Someday.
Peyton, I'm sorry.
I don't want you to go.
But your father told you to follow your heart, and he's right.
As much as it kills me to say it.
I think you need to follow it home.
But what if you're wrong?
What if I go back and my heart just aches for you like it has for months now?
Well, then I'll still be here.
And if it's meant to be, we'll be together.
Someday.
"As the night wore on, a calm fell upon the land,
and all was right in the world
if only for a moment."
Oh, my god. I would strangle you if this wasn't so awesome.
Thank you, and thanks for being my maid of honor. It means a lot to me.
You're welcome. Thank you for being cool about the dress.
Oh, yeah, no problem.
Listen, Rachel's here. Can you just try not to kill each other?
Yeah, I actually invited her.
- You what?!
- Long story.
How's the hand?
Kind of gross, actually.
Thanks for covering for me at the store.
Sure. Mirrors just break all the time.
I didn't even tell Peyton.
As long as you're okay.
Brooke...
...I broke the glass 'cause I was mad at myself for lying to Cooper.
I mean, I know I just met him, but...
I really liked him.
And now he doesn't want to see me anymore.
That sucks. I'm sorry.
Why? I mean, you and me...
Why are you sorry?
Because I know what it feels like to have your heart broken,
and I wouldn't wish that on anybody.
Not even your worst enemy?
Not even her.
Hey. You showed up, man.
Yeah.
What the hell, dude. If this is your history, I can't figure out how you ever got married the first time.
Hey, I thought you snuck out with Gigi.
You remember Marcus, right?
Yes, I do. Nice to see you.
Hi.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Um, so, Nathan says you dropped out of school.
Yeah, well, I kind of had a lot of stuff to deal with, you know?
And, besides, my grades pretty much sucked anyway.
Yeah, I think -- I think we all had a lot to deal with after that day.
I can make you an offer, actually.
If you want to come back to school, I'll tutor you.
Yeah, she's a great tutor, man. She makes it all really easy.
I'll think about it, okay?
Thanks for coming.
- Take it easy.
- Bye, guys.
That was really nice of you, Haley.
You know, even though two people lost their lives that day,
maybe in some strange way, other people found theirs.
Okay, P. Sawyer. Last scene of the night. Are we good?
Actually, no.
Mouth is sick, too.
What? But we need him for this scene.
I mean, Luke, you could do it.
Maybe we should just cut the night short.
No, we can't! This is the big finale. Please, Lucas?
Okay, but no wig.
Deal. Those are your lines.
Um, I can buy you guys a couple of minutes. Just ad-lib if you get in trouble. Okay.
You do know what scene this is, right?
No, why?
Before we end the night, I just wanted to say a few words about Nathan and Haley.
I told them once, not long ago, to be happy
because someday they'd make us all believe in true love.
And they do.
In a few days, they're gonna renew that love for all of us to see,
but in a way, we see it every day.
The only difference is that Haley will look fabulous
in her wedding dress by Clothes over Bro's,
which is kind of odd seeing as she's marrying a bro.
But that's not the point. Sorry.
One rainy day, Nathan Scott proposed to Haley James, and the rest is a fairy tale.
This is the last scene of the night.
Golly gee, that was some good loving, Haley.
Oh, yes, yes, it was. Mm-hmm.
So, uh, what are you thinking?
Oh, I was just thinking how I never, uh...
Never want to go home again.
I was just thinking how I never want to go home again.
I love you. You know that?
Where's your head at, Peyton?
Well, uh, when I went to bed tonight, I was living a fairy tale,
and when I woke up, it's a nightmare.
No, it's still a fairy tale. Don't give up on that.
Look inside your heart and ask yourself, "is Lucas still there?"
And if not... I'll be here.
- Hey.
- Huh?
I love you.
You know that?
Everything's gonna be all right, right?
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
You're always saving me.
The truth is, I want all the same things that you want. I do.
And I want them with you.
I love you, too.
"Once upon a time in a kingdom far, far away,
there lived a beautiful princess who loved a boy."
Rachel.
Are you gonna be okay?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
It's his loss, right?
So, thanks for the invite tonight and the offer.
You know, it's not that easy to change who you are,
but it helps when people let you try.
- See you.
- See you later, man.
You know, there's something I'd really like to do. Do you mind if I meet you back here?
- No, not at all.
- Okay.
See you.
Hey, this is Cooper. You know the drill.
"But the people had their struggles as all people do.
And they had grown to fear and despise the king, whose heart had turned dark."
Haley.
Hi.
Okay, so the last time I stood in a doorway giving someone the benefit of the doubt
when my instincts were screaming at me not to, it was for Nathan.
And this time...
well, it's still for Nathan.
We would like you to come to the wedding.
Thank you.
But god help you if you don't change.
Hey, Luke, we're taking off.
It was great to have you back, man.
Thanks, brother.
Yeah.
Team misses you, Luke.
Take care of yourself.
Hey, catch you guys soon, all right?
Happy to be back?
Yeah, it's good to be home.
"But in the end, the love between the princess and the boy was undeniable and true...
And over time, that love would see them through anything."
Where is our bedspread?
"Magical things happened to them, things they couldn't explain,
much like love itself.
And like most fairy tales, the princess and the boy lived happily ever after."
At least I hope they do.
Way to go with the tears' piece where you brought down the house.
Brooke...
I think I still have feelings for Lucas.
You mean you care for him... as a friend?
No.
I mean more than that.
Transcript: Raceman - Synchro: Amariss
- www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net