Previously on "One Tree Hill"...
Is everybody ready?!
Let me hear you!
Five, four, three, two, one!
Let the madness begin!
When I find out who did this to me,
the sins I commit then could turn this place to rubble.
Can you see my ass through this?
One of these nights, you're gonna realize it.
I'm the guy for you, Brooke Davis.
You'll see.
I wanted you to fight for me.
How was I supposed to know that?
You just are.
I have cancer.
Your other mom should be dead soon.
You really are a bitch.
I'm not the one that sent Ellie away.
You tell Haley that song was a hit.
What, what?
How are things with Nathan?
If you think I'm gonna let you mistreat Haley, you're wrong.
'Cause if you do, I'm gonna hurt you.
The roots are still there.
It just takes time.
Stay with me tonight.
Oh, I was hoping you would say that.
Yummy.
You're in the wrong store.
You're looking for slut barn.
So, you two bury the hatchet yet?
Funny thing. I'm about to bury it in her throat.
If I wanted to watch cheerleaders wrestle, I'd turn on pay-per-view.
Nice.
This kind of turns me on.
Fantasy boy draft.
- I pick Lucas.
- I pick Nathan.
- I get skills.
- Wait!
If you tell Whitey I have a heart condition, I'm off the team.
Yeah, and if I don't tell Whitey about your heart condition,
you're off the planet.
I love you.
I still do love you.
I love you, too.
Okay, what the hell just happened?
Ida Scott Taylor once wrote,
"Do not look back and grieve over the past,
for it is gone,
and do not be troubled about the future, for it has yet to come.
Live in the present, and make it so beautiful
that it will be worth remembering."
Hello?
Where are you?
Okay. Okay.
Hello.
Yeah, no problem.
I'll be right over.
I'm sorry, Brooke.
It was Peyton.
Peyton?
As in my best friend and your ex-girlfriend Peyton?
Something's up,
but we're together now, right?
You and me.
That means everything to me.
We just have to trust each other this time.
I know, you're right.
Besides, I have things to do today.
It's pretty exciting, actually.
Mouth set up a website for me so I can sell my new clothing line,
and it goes live in about an hour.
So, I figure I should make some dresses in case anyone wants to buy one.
That's really great.
I'm proud of you.
Okay, I'll see you in a little bit.
Okay.
See you later, boyfriend.
What?
Nothing.
Just... feels good to hear you call me boyfriend.
Feels good to say it.
And we are live.
Nice.
Hi.
Well, well.
Where's the better half?
I don't know.
Oh, he always was the "love 'em and leave 'em" type.
Can  I help you with something?
As far as I know, this house doesn't belong to you anymore.
Trust me, little girl, this house and everything in it will always belong to me.
Mr. Scott, can you please leave? You're really creeping me out.
You know, at least Peyton was pleasant in the morning.
Oh, by the way, I'm still waiting on those annulment papers.
I hope you don't think a one-night stand's gonna change that.
Hey.
Looks like somebody slept in his clothes last night.
Yeah, it's a long story.
So what's going on?
Um, look, I hate to ask, okay?
But over the summer, you kind of promised that if I ever wanted to go find Ellie,
you would come with me.
Yeah, I remember.
Did you find her?
And I think I want to go see her.
Today?
Um, right now, actually, 'cause if I don't go, I never will, and I need to.
Will you go?
Sure.
A promise is a promise.
Hello.
Hey, I'm on my way.
Okay. Good. I can give you directions.
Okay, where am I going?
Where were you last night?
Oh, uh...
To  be continued.
Mouth, you didn't exactly break any speed records driving over here, you know?
You called me 17 minutes ago, and I drive a bicycle, Brooke.
Just please come here because I need you to fix this stupid website.
It was supposed to go live an hour ago.
Oh, it's live.
So what's the problem?
Click on "orders."
34 orders? Brooke, this is great.
Hold the enthusiasm. Click it again.
Make that 36 orders.
Brooke, 36 orders is incredible.
Haley, I can't make 36 dresses that fast.
I can't make 6 dresses that fast.
Wait, what did you think was gonna happen?
I don't know. I didn't think people were actually gonna order anything,
and if they did, I figured they'd just order stuff I'd already made.
Was that a bad plan?
37, 38.
Dude, it just jumped to 43.
Mouth, I did not ask you to come over here to showcase your counting skills.
I need you to make it stop. Kill it. Do whatever you have to do.
I don't have 43 dresses.
How many do you have?
4.
So where are we headed?
River city.
You ever been there?
No, but it's on my list.
So how about that long story?
I spent the night with Brooke.
Ugh. Okay. Never mind.
It wasn't like that.
I mean, we didn't actually sleep together.
I just thought you decided not to play her non-exclusive sleeping game.
We're together now... exclusively.
Oh, no. Oh, god, I am an idiot.
No, you know what? Scratch that. You're an idiot.
I didn't know any better.
What are you talking about?
Lucas, you guys have been together a couple of hours, and you're in the car with me?
Why didn't you tell me? I wouldn't have even asked you to come.
Peyton, I made you a promise.
Besides, you should be able to turn to me for help.
I love being that guy for you.
Well, does Brooke love you being that guy for me?
No, I didn't think so. So, call her.
Call her and tell her we had plans right now.
Dial the phone.
I got it. Just get the phone.
Thank god it is you. Please tell me you are on your way over here.
Actually, I was just checking in to see how things are going.
Like crap.
Are you still with Peyton?
Yeah, listen, I sort of promised her I'd go with her to see Ellie,
and we're heading out of town right now.
How long are you gonna be gone?
I don't know, but I'll call you when I do.
Okay.
Look, Brooke, I made her a promise.
Luke, it's fine. We're trusting each other, right?
So just call me later, okay?
See ya.
Okay.
See?  She's fine with it.
Hey, was that Lucas? Is he coming over? 'Cause we need all the help we can get.
No, he's with his other girlfriend.
This is it.
You okay?
Yeah.
I guess I just didn't think I'd be this afraid.
Of what?
I don't know. The truth maybe?
You know what?
I think this is probably something I should do alone.
Okay.
Look, I'm really sorry that you rode out all this way.
I guess I just needed your help getting here.
You never needed my help.
Anyway, I'm gonna go explore a bit.
Just give me a call when you're ready.
My name is Elizabeth. I'm your mother.
Peyton.
Good luck.
Thanks, Luke.
Just get out, Ellie --
out of my house, out of my town,
out of my life.
Hi.
Okay, mom, this is pretty weird.
You leave me a note and sneak away in the middle of the night,
and then I get this cryptic phone call. What's going on?
- You know how much I love you.
- Mom --
Honey, sit down.
Okay.
Over the years since I met your father, I've changed,
and somewhere along the line, I've become someone I don't respect.
Pack a bag and get out,
or  so help me god, I will stab you in your sleep.
I'm boiling water to throw on you.
And what's the syrup for?
Well, that's so it sticks to you.
- Mom, what are you --
- Let me finish.
As far back as I can remember, I've had to rely on others.
I've never been able to be alone.
I've never been very strong,
but now it's time for me to try.
I have to.
I'm not going back to Tree Hill, Nathan.
This is my world, okay?! That's my music. This is my art.
Just stay out of my life, okay?
That was their first single.
Only a few thousand of those exist.
I'm  sorry. Your front door was unlocked.
Hey.
If I'm allowed to goin to your room and sneak around, you can do the same here.
Oh, wait.
I wasn't allowed to do that, was I?
What are you doing here, Peyton?
Well, I -- I tried to see you and went to your hotel room the night you left,
but you were gone.
And I didn't know how to find you, and I started to think
maybe you didn't want to be found.
But that doesn't really answer my question.
What are you doing here?
I have a business proposition for you, actually.
Um, I have this friend, right? And she's a musician, and she's good.
She's really good, and I want to put out her record.
I just -- I don't know how, so I was thinking maybe you could help me.
It's good to see you, Peyton.
"The mockery made him an outsider,
and feeling an outsider made him behave like one."
I think that's my book.
How you doing, Faith?
Oh, my god, Lucas.
It's been, like, a long time.
Too long.
Wait a minute. What are you doing here?
How did you find me?
Faith, if you still lived in Tree Hill, there's only one place you'd be.
The only difference between there and here is, well,
our court's got a river that runs next to it.
Okay, your mom told me where you were, but I would have found you eventually.
My mom always did have a soft spot for you.
So, how's life as a big-shot Ravens superstar?
Here we go.
Next you'll tell me you're dating some bitchy cheerleader.
Move your ass, Haley.
You are not setting a very good example, and I noticed
you weren't paying attention during my tutorial.
I know how to sew, Brooke.
Come on, get the lead out, girls. These dresses are not gonna sew themselves,
and where the hell is Mouth with my extra fabric?!
Hey, hey! Are you okay? You seem a little edgy.
I am just focused.
Are you sure this doesn't have anything to do with Lucas going off with Peyton?
No. It's not like they went off on tour together. And besides, it's different this time.
It is different, right?
Yes.
Bevin, you're late, and what are those?
Cookies.
Not those. Those little people thingies.
My brother Tommy, my sister Tara, and my nieces Jodie and Kate.
I promised I'd babysit them today.
Aren't they cute?
And what the hell is she doing here?
Oh, I called her. You said to round up the squad.
I didn't mean Rachel. You missed the tutorial.
I missed the tutorial.
I think I can wing it.
These dresses look pretty simple.
"Simple"?
Uh, Brooke, it's actually a really good idea. We need all the help we can get.
Haley, you're a genius.
Hey, kids, do you like to play dress-up?
I bet you do. This is tutorial girl.
She's gonna teach you guys how to make dress-up.
Sound like fun?
Uh, Brooke, this doesn't seem terribly bright.
Haley, you said it yourself. We need all the help we can get.
Come on. Here we go. We'll go this way.
Oh, this is gonna be so fun.
I don't get it. You finally got your divorce.
That's what you wanted, mom. Why don't you just come home?
I can't.
Mom, I can't just drop everything and move away.
I know, and that's why I'm not asking you to come with me.
You have a wife, Nathan,
and whatever it is the two of you are going through right now, that still means something.
I don't want you to make the same mistakes I did.
Housekeeping.
I'm fine.
Mom, why are you so spooked?
I'm so sorry, Nathan.
I am.
But the fire at the dealership -- it wasn't an accident.
We were going to get out, remember?
But your father wouldn't have that.
It was me.
I tried to kill him.
I was so miserable that day because of your father.
I hadn't been out of rehab long, and it had been a difficult day.
I had to find some strength, some courage to find a way out,
and that's when I found one.
There were just four things left to do.
The first was to type the card.
The second was to deliver it.
The third was to light it.
The fourth was to ask God to take me far away from this person I'd become.
I'm sorry, Nathan. I did it for both of us, to free us.
No.
Please, Nathan, wait.
No. You didn't have the courage to leave him, but you had the courage to kill him?
You know how you were kind of joking about me dating a cheerleader? Well...
No, don't say it.
Unbelievable.
Who is it?
I love you.
I love you, too.
Brooke Davis? Lucas, she is horrible.
No, she's not horrible.
Actually, she's a really amazing person.
Have you forgotten our freshman year?
As much of it as I can, yes.
Morgan Finley -- senior bitch, captain of the cheerleaders.
You know how much she tortured me and my friends,
until one day some freshman boy came along and defended me,
some boy named Lucas Scott.
After that, they tortured you all year,
but you took it
'cause if they were torturing you, they wouldn't pick on any of us.
Oh, yeah. That was a fun year.
When I moved away, Brooke Davis was Morgan Finley's most promising protégé.
She's different now.
Maybe you're different now.
You said you would never join that club --
the elite and the popular.
So tell me something, Luke. Now that you're basically the king of that club,
who's looking out for the people like me?
The ones who were afraid to go to school?
That's not how it is, Faith.
Look, I'm not defending who Brooke was.
I am defending who she is.
And trust me, she never became Morgan Finley.
That's it! No more cookie breaks for anybody! Do you people want to be here all night?!
Hey, you're Mouth, right?
You announce the basketball games.
I'm Rachel.
Yeah, I know who you are.
I've  listened to your interviews on the school website.
You're really good.
Really?
Thanks.
It's just practice for, hopefully, the future.
So what's your thing?
My thing?
Yeah. You know, every great sports announcer has a thing.
Like Phil Rizzuto has, "holy cow!"
And, um, Marv Albert has, "yes!"
A little more work, a little less talk.
We were just discussing Mouth's thing.
Yeah, it's...
not really what it sounds like, Brooke.
Isn't he the cutest?
Aw, well, I hate to interrupt the male bonding,
but, Mouth, I need you to watch the kids.
I thought Haley was watching them.
Well, now you're watching them. Chop-chop.
Haley, will you please go pick up more fabric?
I thought that was Mouth's job.
Will you please just do what I ask, Haley? My day has been a total crap fest.
I guess Lucas didn't check in, then, huh?
So ? It's not like I don't have problems of my own to worry about.
Why are you concerned with whether or not Lucas calls me?
How is that any of your business?
I just want to know what would make a guy leave you
first thing in the morning like that.
It just doesn't seem right.
Thanks for rubbing that in, roommate.
So I was wondering...
this song you want to produce --
what makes you think I could help with it?
Well, I mean, mostly 'cause you know a lot about music and the industry,
and, I mean, you do have a really nice little collection here.
"Little"?
It's like heaven, only it probably sounds better.
Cure fan?
Ew, up until this album.
Come on. "Wish" is a great record.
No, "Disintegration" is a great record.
"Wish" was pretty much the end.
- Oh, really?
- Uh-huh.
You're gonna tell me you don't get chills every time you hear the violin
on "To Wish Impossible Things"?
Yeah, every time.
But?
But I don't remember the day.
The day?
Yeah, you know, it's like --
like with "Disintegration," I remember the very first time I heard that record.
You know, like, I remember everything about that day --
the weather outside and the smell in the air.
I just -- I remember all those things,
and that's because that day, I fell in love with something.
You fell in love with an album.
No.
I fell in love with music.
So, speaking of The Cure, um...
are you in remission?
No.
I'm sorry.
No, no.
The truth is...
I'm probably gonna be just fine.
Oh, okay. That's great. That's --
I'm really glad for you, Ellie.
So, anyway, um, I was thinking that if you are gonna help me with Haley's record
that, well, you could maybe move into the house with me.
My dad, you know, he's out to sea, and he said it's okay.
So what do you think?
I appreciate the invitation, Peyton.
I just -- I-I just really don't have the time.
Yeah.
But stay a bit.
There's got to be some other albums here that you are dead wrong about.
So you rode here with Peyton Sawyer?
Man, Tree Hill is trippin' since I left.
Yeah, you're right about that.
So tell me about your life, Faith.
Are you happy here?
I guess so.
It took me a little while to get used to it --
leaving Tree Hill, changing schools,
but now it's basically same life, different town.
Your mom sounds good.
Yeah, she is. Finally got a good coaching job.
Not too many schools out there are gonna let a woman coach a boys' basketball team.
Yeah, well, if anyone can do it, she can.
Definitely true.
Look what we have here.
One of the Tree Hill Ravens.
Fan club?
You losers win a game yet?
You losers call next?
There's nobody here.
Really? 'Cause we're here.
Game to 11 by ones, win by 2. Winners stay, losers walk.
What, us two against him?
No, you two against us.
Our ball.
Same jump shot, different town.
9-6.
How's my hair? Still sexy?
She's a girl, for god sakes, man. Guard her.
You guard her.
- Game.
- Okay, then. Nice to see you guys.
Take care. See you later. Bye.
Nice game, Luke.
Brooke Davis would be proud.
Can I sit with you?
Please?
How did it come to this, mom?
I ask myself that question every single day.
I've been sitting here thinking about my 13th birthday.
Dad surprised me with hawks tickets -- front row on the court.
We drove all the way to Atlanta, the three of us.
I remember that trip, how much fun we had as a family.
I just wanted to replay that memory,
just to remember it.
Then I saw your face.
It was always right there in front of me, and I never saw it.
What?
You were never happy.
Dad is a bad guy, mom,
but somewhere deep down, he still just wants me to be the best I can be.
He doesn't deserve to die for that.
Two years ago, the coach from Oak Lake Academy came to see your father to recruit you --
the number-one high school basketball program in the country,
and your father sent him away.
- He wouldn't do that.
- He did.
And I told him it wasn't his decision to make.
You were gonna go to that school whether he liked it or not
and that I was leaving with you.
What did he say?
He looked at me.
He spoke calmly.
He said that if I took you away, he would find us...
and he would kill me.
Don't you see, Nathan?
Your father will always try to control you. He'll never let you go.
You know, thanks for reminding me of a few things today.
Like what?
Well, how much fun we used to have hanging out at the River Court all day,
playing ball, growing up.
Yeah, it was like old times, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was.
No uniforms, no crowds, no cheerleaders.
Just you and me and the game.
I almost forgot what it was like -- playing just to play.
Speak for yourself. I wanted to crush those guys.
I was right about you, you know --
that you've changed, but I think maybe it's for the best.
Okay, you've teased me all day about how much I've changed,
but what about you?
What about me?
Well, for a girl who used to be afraid to go to school,
you sure stood up to those guys at the court.
Like I said, maybe it's for the best.
So you said back there I reminded you of a few things.
What else?
How much I miss seeing you.
Oh, yeah, that's like a no-brainer.
Don't be a stranger, Luke.
Hey, the phone goes both ways.
Yeah, I know, but I didn't say, "keep in touch."
I said, "don't be a stranger."
All right.
Bevin.
This is terrible! The stitching is all wrong.
I missed the tutorial.
Hmm?
This is actually kind of perfect.
I know.
But it's mine.
I ordered it online this morning.
Wait a second. You came over here to make your own dress?
Well, I liked the design. I just didn't trust the designer.
See ya, Mouth.
Call me.
Bye.
Well, great! Thanks, everybody, for wasting my time today!
Brooke, stop it.
Everybody here's been busting their butt for you,
and you've pretty much been a bitch all day long.
We haven't gotten anything done. I have been dreaming about this for so long.
Don't you understand?
No, not if it changes you, Brooke. Trust me, no dream is worth that.
Shut it down, Mouth -- all of it.
Brooke, that's not --
No, just stop the orders and give everybody their money back.
We spent most of the money, Brooke.
How do you think we bought all the material and supplies?
Then I'll finish it myself.
It's my problem.
Everybody, just go home, please.
I'm really sorry for the way I treated all of you today. I, um...
I haven't been myself.
Hey, kids, hey, here, will you take these?
Thanks.
I'm so sorry.
That was a really nice thing to do, Brooke...
with my CDs.
I can't believe you saw the first U2 tour in the states.
Yep.
They opened for the psychedelic furs,
and if you're lucky, I might even have a t-shirt from that tour somewhere around here.
Hey, I'm gonna get some water. Can I get you some?
So this is it?
There's no food, Ellie, and there's barely any furniture!
Nothing like a bed and a rockin' soundtrack to die to, right?
You don't know what you're talking about.
You came here to die.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Don't I deserve the truth?
The truth?
The truth is I don't have any furniture because I'm always on the road.
I don't keep any food in the house because I eat out.
This is the way I've always lived, Peyton,
except I usually get the added benefit of being alone...
At least for the last 17 years, I did.
You didn't come here to seek music advice.
You came here out of guilt.
And guess what? I don't want it, and I don't need it.
In fact, get out.
You know what? Fine. Fine! Fine! You're right, okay?
So I came to see how you are. Is that so bad?
Am I such a horrible person because I was worried about you?
I just -- I thought we could do something really good together, okay?
Maybe even something, like, great.
I wanted to sell that record so we could raise money for cancer research.
Sorry I cared.
So I guess this is goodbye, mom.
Just for a little while.
I'll never leave you for good.
Well, I'm not so good on my own, either.
The day you emancipated yourself, you broke my heart.
Now I realize it was your strongest moment.
Hopefully I can find that kind of strength.
I don't want to be alone.
You're not alone.
You have Haley.
Go home and deal with your marriage.
Don't avoid it until it becomes something you have to run from.
Bye, mom.
Bye.
Sorry about Ellie.
I don't think I'm evergonna see her again, Luke.
Hi. Where are you?
Hey, Brooke, I'm really sorry, but it's gonna be a little while.
Peyton's car broke down.
Great.
So the two of you are gonna spend the night in some seedy motel.
Yeah, and then one thing will lead to another, and --
Pretty risky trick, mister.
You weren't worried, were you?
Totally not for a second worried.
What? Bad day?
I just really needed my boyfriend.
Well, he's here now.
Put me to work.
I don't want to work anymore.
Can we go do something you want to do?
Actually, I have something I need to go do.
Okay.
With you.
You have one message.
Miss Harp, this is Dr. Gold calling from East Lake Memorial.
It is extremely important that you call me back.
As I said earlier, we need to talk about your decision to stop treatment.
I really...
You're right.
The song's good.
It needs background vocals.
Well, yeah, it's just a demo.
It's a business arrangement.
Of course.
Okay.
Hey.
What's up?
I just wanted to see you.
This is my world, Brooke --
or at least it used to be.
I have been here before, you know.
I know.
But I never told you what this place is to me.
It's not just a court.
It's where I came from. It's where I belong.
It's my world.
Do I get to be a part of this world?
The biggest part.
Ladies and gentlemen, what a treat we have tonight --
River Court legend Lucas Scott.
It's been months since Scott's run a full-court game here,
so I guess the big question is will he play tonight?
Go get 'em, boyfriend.
Nice shot.
Transcript: Raceman - Synchro: Amariss
- www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net