At this moment, there are
6,502,867,120 people in the world.
Give or take a few.
And sometimes all you need is one...
for better or for worse.
Help me!
Somebody, please help!
How long you been out here?
Couple hours.
Sometimes I come out here when I can't sleep.
You miss it?
Every day.
So, what's up?
Had this messed-up dream last night.
Haley was drowning, and I couldn't save her.
Of course, leave it to Haley to insist that we don't see each other
until the wedding even though we're married.
Maybe I should just go see her.
I'll tell you what -- I'll go check on her for you, how's that?
Tell her to stay away from the water, okay? No swimming or anything.
Nathan... it's your wedding day -- again.
It's gonna be a great day.
Thanks, man.
You're closer than a hundred feet.
Just paying my respects.
You know, everyone thinks of Keith as this perfect guy, but they're wrong.
No, they're not, Dan.
Keith is a hero.
He tried to kill me.
That's right.
He's the one who tried to burn me in the dealership fire.
So I guess the hero got what was coming to him after all.
Knock, knock.
Hey, how is the bride-to-be... again?
Good.
Well, I'm afraid you've missed the boys. They were gone pretty early.
Oh, that's okay. I wanted to see you, actually.
I have a question for you.
Okay.
I know you and Keith were engaged, and it -- it breaks my heart.
I know. I know.
Sorry. Okay. Um...
Brooke -- Brooke made me this -- this dress,
and it is out of the material that she ordered for your wedding dress.
And I just wanted to ask you if it was okay if I wore it.
And if it's not, that's fine. She made another one that I can wear.
I am so proud of you, Haley.
Have I told you that lately?
You have got a wonderful soul, Haley James Scott.
And you are gonna make a beautiful bride in that dress.
Thank you.
Hi.
Where did you sleep?
My car.
See, I had this horrible dream last night
that my best friend told me she had feelings for my boyfriend.
But that wasn't a dream, was it?
- Brooke --
- Why now, Peyton?
Why would you tell me you have feelings for Lucas now,
when I have so much going on in my life, stuff that you don't even know about?
Well, so do I, okay? Trust me.
But... I didn't wish for this, all right? I wished for Jake.
Oh, right.
You wished for Jake after you wished for Pete and then Lucas.
I cannot believe this is happening again.
It's not, okay? It's not. It's just... okay, the last time --
The last time? Do you hear yourself right now?
"The last time" you tried to steal my boyfriend?
He's on the door, Peyton.
He's on the damn door under me!
I don't want to steal him, okay?
But you like him.
Brooke, I'm not gonna do anything about it, okay? I'll just bury it.
You can't, okay? It's out. It's like the time capsule.
And you could've buried it and not said anything to me, so what is that about?
I don't know, all right?! I wanted to be honest with you, all right?
I didn't want to make the same mistake I did last time.
You even said last night at Tric that you really didn't miss him.
Don't you dare!
Don't you dare twist my words around to make yourself feel
like you are not a backstabbing two-faced bitch, Peyton,
because you are... and you know it.
Hey, pretty girl.
Hey.
-  What's going on?
- Nothing.
Come on, nobody loves a wedding more than Brooke Davis. What's up?
I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't talk to Peyton today.
You're kidding, right?
This is a wedding. We're all in the same wedding party.
We're all friends here, Brooke.
You know, could you do me a favor just once
and put me above your precious Peyton
and do something that I ask you to do? Thanks.
Whoa. What happened?
We had a fight...
and I'm stressed out about my speech and Haley's dress, and I'm late.
I'm late to get ready, and... I'm sorry.
Come here.
It's okay.
You look nice.
Weddings.
Rachel?
You look almost as hot as me.
Listen to me. You got to stop calling me.
I told you we couldn't see each other anymore.
Before you left that morning, I think I made myself perfectly clear.
Yeah, but the night before that, you weren't so clear.
In fact, if I remember right, I think you weren't so clear three times.
You're 17.
Yeah. I was 17 that night, too...
and all the other nights.
Okay. Listen to me.
I'm sorry, okay? I made a mistake,
but this is Nathan and Haley's day.
Now, I promise you we'll talk about this later,
but do not make this ugly for them.
I wouldn't think of it.
Need a hand?
No, I'm okay. Thanks.
It's just a tie, Lucas. Come on, let me see.
So, how is life without basketball?
It's better than life without Keith.
Okay. Let's see.
Dan thinks it was Keith -- the fire --
but  I just found out this morning.
I'm sorry, Karen.
It's  not fair to Keith's memory. It's not fair to you.
Yes, it's not fair to Keith,
but Dan's need for revenge was buried with his brother.
He's not gonna be coming after you or anybody else.
Maybe so, but in a way that makes me feel weaker than ever.
Nathan!
Nathan?
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Have you checked on Haley?
- Yeah, she's fine.
She should be here by now. Can you call her?
- Nate --
- Please. Just do it.
Okay. All right, all right.
Hey, Haley, you all right?
Something's wrong, man.
Hey, what's up?
Hey, it's me. Is everything okay?
Fine, soon-to-be-husband-again, why?
I just... I just wanted to hear your voice, that's all.
Where are you?
I'm right here.
Oh, I'm sorry, princess. I was looking for my friend Haley.
Wow, did it really take all this stuff to make you look like this?
No, everybody got ready in here,
including Rachel and Brooke for some reason.
Right.
Wow. You...
whew... really look beautiful.
Thank you.
So, your parents really aren't coming?
No, they -- I invited them, and they said,
"sorry, honey, we've been to your wedding once before, and it was a little boring."
Anyway, I'll just give myself away. It's fine.
Or I could do it...
...if you'll have me.
Really?
Luke, that would be perfect.
Okay.
Thank you.
But you know what? I got to be honest with you.
I could never officially give you away, you know that?
I could never give away my best friend.
Congrats.
Hey, Rachel.
You look almost as hot as me.
Sounds like something I would say.
- Hey, Peyton.
- Hi.
How about we, uh, go find you a good seat... friend?
Hey, you.
So, I've been informed to avoid you like the plague.
- What's up?
- Nothing, just --
look, if Brooke doesn't want you to talk to me, just do it. I'll be fine.
Hey, Peyton.
You look nice.
Feeling sentimental, Deb?
Feeling nauseous, actually.
You had your chance.
Want to make it a dual ceremony, Coop?
Now I know how this dress looks on a witch.
Go Brooke yourself.
Friends and loved ones,
we are gathered here today to witness the renewal of a commitment,
a commitment between Nathan and Haley
to love one another unconditionally and endlessly.
Nathan and Haley,
there are many things I could say to the two of you today,
but instead I choose to listen to the words you have for each other.
Haley?
Nathan, it's been said that there's one word
that will free us from the weight and the pain of life,
and that word is "love,"
and I believe that.
That doesn't mean that it hasn't been hard or that it won't be.
It just means that I found a stillness
and a bravery in myself with you.
You make me brave,
and I will love you until the end of time.
This I vow today.
Nathan?
Last year, we stood on a beach, and I told you how much I loved you
and how I would always, always protect you.
That day nobody believed that this would work,
but I don't think anybody understood the love that I had for you.
Because if they did, they would've never doubted us.
So I wanted to marry you all over again in front of most of our world
because today, when I look into your eyes,
my love for you only grows.
It's even stronger now,
and our love will never waver.
And this I vow to you today
and always and forever.
Haley, on this day, do you reconfirm and rededicate yourself
to the vows you promised to uphold?
Oh. Thank you.
I do.
Nathan, on this day, do you rededicate and reconfirm
your commitment to the vows you promised to uphold?
I do.
And, uh, actually, I have a new ring.
Thank you.
And now, before the eyes of God,
I once again pronounce you husband and wife.
You may kiss your bride.
- I love you, Haley.
- I love you, too.
You know... one day we'll walk down the aisle again, Deb. You'll see.
Open your eyes, Dan.
I don't love you. I'm not coming back to you.
And Keith didn't try to kill you.
I did.
Danny?
How's your life, little brother?
I'm Cooper, by the way. You're Michelle Featherstone, right?
Yes.
That song you played was perfect.
In fact, I think all your stuff is really great.
Thank you, thank you.
I think, um, all of your stuff is pretty great, too.
Well, thank you.
Hey, Rach.
Are you gonna talk to me?
Please?
Fine.
So, this is how it ends --
a 10-year friendship that survived two dead moms,
three absentee parents,
shoplifting, jail time,
and we can't survive one boy?
Not one boy, Peyton --
my boy.
And he still is your boy. I told you that.
Do you love him?
You are something else.
How dare you be so selfish to ask me that about my boyfriend.
How dare I?
Okay, you know what, Brooke?
I didn't want it this way, okay? I tried tears.
I tried apologizing to you. I cried, and you know what you did?
You slapped me, and you blew me off.
You're gonna be lucky if next time I don't use my fist.
I can't believe you're supposed to be the maid of honor.
And by the way, none of those words were, "yes, Peyton, I love him."
Ladies and gentlemen, please stand and join me
in welcoming Nathan and Haley, husband and wife again.
And now the song they picked for their first dance.
What song did you pick anyway?
Oh, I was hoping it would be this one.
I had a little help.
So you gonna tell me what this is about?
Maybe you should tell me about it.
What's that supposed to mean?
Peyton told me some things about the two of you.
Look,  Brooke, I know that you're worried about my past with Peyton,
but you have to understand the circumstances this time, you know?
God, she was bleeding, and she thought she was gonna die.
I mean, the kiss, it meant nothing.
What kiss?
Did you kiss her again?
Look, Brooke, I need you to listen to me, okay?
I understand that you didn't know about the kiss,
and I'm sorry for springing it on you, but I meant what I said.
It didn't mean anything.
A kiss always means something.
Okay, maybe you're right, but it wasn't a romantic moment,
- and you would know that if --
- If what -- I was there?
As you so sweetly pointed out at the party, the party that I threw for you,
I wasn't there, was I?
Is it impossible for you to forgive me?
I forgave you.
For what?
For sleeping with Chris Keller.
And you know what, Lucas? I loved you for that.
You had such grace in that moment
that I fell in love with you all over again.
I  can't believe that you would use it now as a bargaining chip.
No, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not. I just...
I need you to trust me and believe me when I tell you that my heart is with you.
But part of me feels like ever since we got back together,
you've  just been waiting -- waiting to push me away.
Oh, great.
You kiss Peyton -- again --
and I'm pushing you away!
God! Why did I make everybody identical purses as wedding gifts?!
I love you, Brooke.
I don't know how else to say it.
How about how you show it?
I am not pushing you away, Lucas.
I am holding on for dear life, but I need you to need me back.
Okay, why wouldn't you tell me about the kiss?
And why didn't you call me while you were away?
And why won't you ever just let me all the way in?
We have to go and give our toasts now...
...about love.
Please don't be mad, Brooke.
I'm not mad, Lucas.
I'm not mad.
The last time I gave a speech about Nathan and Haley was...
well, at the first reception.
I remember saying, "prepare to be surprised."
Well, I have to say even I was surprised
because, you see, they do something that's very rare to see in someone our age.
Actually, it's very rare to see in anybody.
They give their hearts to each other...
unconditionally.
And that's what true love really is.
It's not this fairy-tale life that never knows pain,
but it's two souls facing it together
and diminishing it with unconditional love.
To Nathan and Haley Scott.
I'm not the most eloquent speaker,
so I thought I would borrow a few words from Shakespeare.
"Love is not love which alters when it alteration finds."
When life gets hard, when things change,
true love remains the same.
I look at Nathan and Haley, and somehow I feel safer.
I don't know if I can explain that, but
they give me hope.
And I'm afraid to say it out loud because maybe if life finds out,
it'll try to beat it out of them, and that would be a shame
because we all can use a little hope sometimes, you know?
That feeling that everything is gonna be okay
and that there's going to be someone there to help make sure of that.
So, here's to Nathan and Haley,
here's to hope, and here's to a love that will not alter.
I never apologized for the way I treated you and Lucas...
...or for the way I treated Keith.
I suppose it's too late.
I'm pregnant.
I'm gonna be there for you this time, Karen.
It's gonna be okay.
Hi. Excuse me. I'd like your attention for a second.
I'd like to propose a toast
to my knucklehead of a nephew and his beautiful bride.
Ah, here we go.
As most of you know, Nathan and Haley's relationship was --
was unexpected,
mostly because Haley is classy and attractive
and Nathan is... not.
Ouch!
But here's to Nathan and Haley for proving to us that love is real
and genuine and still attainable for the rest of us. Cheers, you two.
Thanks, coop, I guess.
Well, well. I would like to make a toast
to Cooper's toast...
...about love.
But wait a minute.
What could Nathan and Haley possibly know about love?
I mean, they're only 17, right?
Right, Cooper?
You see, Cooper seems to think a 17-year-old
couldn't possibly know anything about love.
Of course, that didn't stop him from having sex with me, okay?
Rachel...
Yeah. To sex with Cooper!
Is she serious?
I'm so sorry. Excuse me.
Hey, Rachel, come on.
Rachel!
No, no, no! Hey, hey -- bad idea.
Hey, hey, hey!
Rachel, stop the car. Damn it, Rachel, stop the car!
Are you trying to kill me?!
What is your problem?
First you ruin the reception, you steal a limousine, and you drive drunk?
Are you out of your mind?!
I must be to fall in love with you!
Look, I'm sorry, Rachel, okay? I made a mistake when we slept together,
and it wasn't just because you're 17.
Hell, even when I thought you were older, I wasn't looking to get serious.
I'm sorry. I mean, that sounds harsh,
but you even said, "we're just having fun, Coop," remember?
I lied.
I'm so stupid.
Hey, don't -- don't do that.
I thought you liked me.
I did, Rachel. I liked you.
Right.
"Liked."
Look, let me take you home, okay?
No. I left all my stuff at the reception -- my purse, my keys--
That's fine. That's great. You know what?
Then we'll take the limousine back to the reception,
and we'll pretend like none of this ever happened...
all right?
Let's go.
So, there was a slight mix-up.
- Sweet! I'm driving.
- No way.
Hey, we'll leave the car at the airport.
All right.
We're going to London for a few days.
Why? Doesn't it always rain there?
Oh, yeah.
- You in?
- Yeah.
Thank you, guys, for coming!
We love you!
Hey, buddy.
It looks like Rachel took the limo with Cooper.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Me too.
So I guess we never finished that conversation.
Dance with me.
Did you miss me while you were away?
Every day.
I was just angry and upset about Keith,
and I just needed to be alone, but that doesn't mean that I didn't miss you, Brooke...
because I did.
I needed to hear your voice.
There's just so much stuff going on with me.
What kind of stuff?
I just got that feeling,
that stillness I used to feel before dawn,
feeling like the world could be perfect.
Yeah, I feel it, too.
Don't say I never gave you anything.
Then there were two.
I'm sorry about today -- all the drama.
Peyton...
I accidentally told Brooke about the library,
the kiss.
Um, Luke?
Are you going home with Brooke or with me?
Uh, with you.
Brooke left.
I'm sorry.
You and Brooke okay?
Yeah, she's just going through some stuff.
Well, could you grab my wrap and my purse?
Yeah, sure. I'll drive.
Hey, ma, are you...
pregnant?
Yes, I am.
But that's not my purse.
You know, maybe Brooke took the wrong --
Brooke.
Brooke, don't go -- please.
I don't want to, but I have to.
Okay. All right. Look, just stop, all right? What do I have to do to fix this?
Brooke, I'll do anything.
Just -- I don't want you to go.
You asked me earlier today if I love Lucas,
and I have your answer.
But you don't deserve to hear it.
Brooke --
No. I want you to understand something.
As far as I am concerned, this friendship is over.
And if we never speak again for the rest of our lives, that'll be fine.
I gave you a second chance, Peyton,
and you blew it.
Is there anything I could say to keep you, Cooper?
No, I'm sorry, Rachel. There's not.
That's too bad...
because there's something I have to tell you.
Oh! I left my purse.
It's got everything in it -- the plane tickets, everything. We have to go back.
No, no, no, it's okay. I'll just have Lucas meet us.
Hey, Luke?
Hey, man, Haley left her purse and a bunch of stuff at the reception.
Could you bring that to us?
Oh. Oh, okay. Well, we're coming up on the Molina Bridge right now,
so I guess we'll just pull over and wait for you.
All right. Thanks, man. Bye.
Done.
He already had the purse in his car.
You're good in a crisis.
Oh, I don't know about that.
No, you are.
It's a good thing, too,
especially since I have something I have to tell you.
I don't believe you.
Pull over.
Hell no. I'm not letting you out until we talk about this.
- I said pull over!
- No!
I said pull over!
What are you doing?!
Look out!
That was Cooper. Cooper!
Cooper!
- Haley, call 911.
- Nathan, don't!
I love you.
Nathan!
Nathan! Cooper!
Anybody, please help!
William shakespeare wrote,
"Love is not love which alters when it alteration finds.
It is an ever-fixed mark that looks on tempests and is never shaken."
Oh, god! Help me!
Haley!
Nathan! Cooper!
"Love alters not with time's brief hours and weeks..."
Somebody, please help!
"...but bears it out..."
Help me!
"...even to the edge of doom."
Transcript: Raceman - Synchro: Amariss
- www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net