Previously on "One Tree Hill"...
So, are we staying yet?
Are we exclusive yet?
Game on, Brooke Davis.
I would like to say something.
Uh, Mayor Mullins, I object.
Well, this is not a court of law, Dan.
Sit down.
I'm still your father.
But you're not my father, are you?
Divorce is fine, Deb.
You seem surprised.
Here. It's my cocaine vial.
Thought you might like it, considering you were buying drugs today.
Ellie was buying marijuana, but not for the reasons you think.
She's sick.
She has cancer, Peyton.
Always and forever.
That's what sucks, Haley.
I still do love you.
I just can't trust you.
No way, Hales!
Let me see it.
I look... like an idiot.
Dude, I saw you in your headgear.
Don't call me "dude," and I thought we promised not to talk about that in public.
Whatever, dude.
Look, I'm counting to three, and then I'm coming in.
One, two --
th--
Whoa-oa! Okay, this is hot!
Excuse me?
Well, I mean -- oh, ew.
No, not that I noticed or could ever possibly think of you that way.
I just -- okay. Ew.
Look, this party's my one chance to get Brooke to finally rethink this whole non-exclusive thing.
Just be...
well, exclusive.
Do you think she'll like it?
You're asking me to enter the sexual mind of Brooke Davis?
She's your roommate.
She's your girlfriend.
Sort of, kind of.
All right, let me see what I can find out. I'll do a little roommate recon for you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Now it's your turn.
I see a belly-dancer costume with your name on it, love.
Nathan won't know what hit him.
Please. I could go naked to this stupid party, and it wouldn't make a difference.
Okay, ew.
Well, well, well. Mayor Mullins.
What have we here?
Sex scandal 101.
Handcuffs, cocaine, skanky hookers.
No offense, ladies.
So, what's your preference --
video or stills?
Then again, I'm a businessman. We could make a deal.
You drop your bid for re-election
and resign immediately,
and this video goes away.
Good boy. At least you're a smart pervert.
Oh, by the way...
you're gonna endorse me for mayor.
Hey. Knock knock.
I'm making lunch. You hungry?
Not really.
Come on. You've seen enough afterschool specials to know that you've got to eat.
I know. I will, just...
not right now.
Okay.
What are you going as?
An angel.
Brooke's gonna be the devil.
Imagine that.
I'm just not really feeling it.
All right. Well, if you get hungry, let me know.
Hey, um...
look, I know, all right, about Ellie.
What?
The breast cancer.
Did you think, like, I couldn't handle it, or...
'cause if you were keeping it from me, then --
I wasn't.
I didn't know.
Oh.
Well, now you do.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
Guess my moms are just dropping like flies, huh?
What  the hell are you doing here?
Just savoring the indian summer.
Well, savor it at the beach house, Dan.
It's what you'll get in the divorce if you'll just sign the damn papers already.
You mean these papers?
I'll sign them for you right now, sweetheart.
Thank you.
I just need you to sign these for me.
"Declaration of candidacy"?
I'm running for mayor.
You're running against Mullins, a 10-year incumbent? Fat chance.
Guess you didn't hear.
Mullins resigned this morning.
Shocking.
Fine.
Run for mayor. Run for "Miss Ten North Carolina," for all I care.
At least I won't be around to watch.
Don't be so sure.
Check the date.
You postdated this for two months from now.
Dan, why don't you just go and quit torturing me?
I will... in 60 days, after we play house and show the Tree Hill voters
what a great family man Dan Scott is. Appearances are everything, right, Deb?
Why are you doing this?
Because Mullins got in my way with Whitey,
and I don't like it when people get in my way.
Besides, I've got money and I've got freedom.
At least I will when I get rid of you.
Only  thing left... is power.
Forget it.
And what about Nathan?
If you stick around for the next two months...
I'll leave him alone.
I could turn him against you, Deb.
But if you stay with me...
I'll back off for as long as you like.
Who knows?
After 60 days, you may fall in love with me again.
You want us to live together, fine.
I've been pretending to love you for a long time now, Dan.
60 days is nothing.
"Mayor Dan Scott."
I like it.
New tune?
Sounds pretty good. Speed it up a little.
Faster.
# For he's a jolly good fellow #
Sorry.
You know, the devil doesn't have sequins or feathers or breasts, for that matter.
Well, in my universe, she does.
Did you even follow the pattern?
No.
Brooke, you have to do that!
- Says who?
- Says every sewing teacher ever.
Otherwise, you'll end up with something like --
Like this?
That... looks really good.
Thank you. I just whipped it up.
What are we gonna do for you? I was thinking...
sexy nurse, catholic schoolgirl, playboy bunny...
No, no, and forget it.
It's a costume party. You go as a sexy whatever.
All right, well, sexy, not slutty.
Fine.
Oh, I know.
The classic "get my man to see me in a new light" costume.
How about a "get my man to come to this thing" costume?
You got one of those? 'Cause I'm not even sure Nathan's showing up at this thing.
Well, you're gonna make my job easy this year.
There's nothing worse than cheering for a bunch of losers.
Well, it's all about you, Brooke.
What's up?
Are you going to this masquerade party at Tric?
Wasn't planning on it. Why?
Just figured it might be the perfect occasion to stop punishing your wife.
Haley is really hurting, Nathan.
Come on, how hard would it be to stop by, smile at her, and tell her she looks cute?
Harder than you think.
She hasn't written a song since you guys split up.
I guess her talent was tied to you.
No Nathan, no music.
- She put you up to this?
- No.
But if I hear one more accidental cover of "Wind beneath my wings," I am going to slit my wrists.
So, please, Nathan, do it for me.
And when I get through with her, she's gonna look hot as hell.
You can trust me -- I'm m the devil.
I'll think about it.
Okay.
Hey.
Did you talk to Brooke about my costume yet?
Yeah. How do you feel about head-to-toe tattoos and a nose ring?
Not  good.
Well, think about it, Tommy Lee.
I got to dump these.
What is this, some kind of California thing Brooke picked up in "The O.C."?
I'm sure it goes back further than that.
Hey, since when is Brooke such a metalhead, anyway?
Um... I-I don't know.
I guess even after all this time, people can still surprise you.
Is it true? Do you have cancer?
Yes.
Is Peyton at risk?
She might be.
But only 10% of all breast cancers are genetic.
- Is yours one of them?
- I don't know.
So at some point down the line, you should get her checked.
And what about you?
I was in remission for a while.
Not anymore.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
It's not how I pictured my life turning out, that's for sure.
I know it's crazy, but I can't help feeling like it's some kind of karmic payback, you know?
I don't think it works like that.
Is this why you came back, to make things right with Peyton?
I wanted her and you to be aware of her genetic history.
And, sure, I wanted to get to know her.
I wanted her to get to know me.
So she could lose another mother.
No, that is exactly what I didn't want.
I was still in remission when I first got here.
And don't worry...
I am not about to let her watch me die.
Look, Ellie, I am sorry for everything that you are going through,
but you understand that I have to think about Peyton first, last, always.
Oh,  you mean now that you're back in town?
Like me?
No, nothing like you, actually.
Larry!
I'm sorry.
If you want me to leave for good this time,
just say the word.
She's your daughter now.
It's up to you.
Is that one of ours?
Inspired by, but I made a few modifications.
Like what?
Well, if you cut the leg higher, it's less coverage, but it's actually more flattering.
And a halter is way better for faking buff Madonna arms.
Interesting, but the devil doesn't have feathers.
What  is with you people? So she's a feathery devil.
Hi!
Is that your costume?
Uh, is that yours?
Maybe.
I think you'll like it.
I know I will.
You might want to warn your other boyfriends if they plan on seeing you at the party.
I think you're gonna be all tied up, so to speak.
Really?
Well, a girl can dream.
But I thought you were playing hard-to-get.
Actually, I believe you're the one playing hard-to-get.
Doesn't mean we can't have a whole lot of fun in the meantime.
Just means we'll be wearing a whole lot more clothes while we're having it.
Right.
Commitment thing.
Think my costume's gonna help you change your mind.
Um, I'm sorry to interrupt, but do you have a matching thong?
Oh, you know it, sister.
What the hell is this?
New campaign, new wardrobe.
And that "candidate's wife" look doesn't come cheap.
Appearances are everything, right, Dan?
Bedroom's this way, boys!
Peyton?
Peyton, listen --
I thought you were going as an angel.
I am -- I'm the angel of death.
Thought it was appropriate.
Honey...
you know the worst part about your mom dying?
I have to pick just one?
How suddenly she was gone.
I mean, it was like, one minute she was there,
talking about what we were gonna have for dinner, and the next, she was just...
...gone.
Forever.
I kept thinking about all the things I would have said to her if I had known.
And then I realized what I really had to worry about was all the things I was gonna say to you.
- Daddy, I'm --
- Honey, you were so little.
There was so much left to talk about with mom.
So many things she would have told you as you grew up.
So I started writing it all down, whatever I could think of --
her favorite color, favorite food.
Our first date, first kiss.
But all that did was make me realize all the things I didn't know.
Things I couldn't know -- girl stuff.
Like what she would have said to you about sex or the day you got your first --
Dad, I just...
I know, honey, but...
don't you ever just wonder?
Yeah.
All the time.
Well, now, Ellie...
has the one thing your mother didn't.
She's got a fair warning.
There's time.
Time for no regrets... no... wondering.
Maybe you should go see her. Talk to her.
Let her answer any questions that you might have.
Like what?
Like... who your real father is.
I think you make a very pretty angel of death.
Have fun.
Hey, it's Nathan.
We should, uh, get together tonight.
There's this costume party. We can meet up afterwards.
Hey, there's just one thing.
Haley can't know.
Remember -- no tugging.
- Okay, but --
- No tugging!
You're tough. Any chance I can lose these heels halfway through the night?
No pain, no gain, girl.
Now get your game face on.
Other game.
Okay, we'll work on that.
Hello, ladies.
Mouth! Ha ha!
You look incredible.
Thanks. So do you.
Wow. It's a good thing you and Lucas are non-exclusive.
So I guess you're over Erica.
My girlfriend -- ex-girlfriend.
Oh, sorry, Mouth.
No, I'm okay.
I'm not gonna spend my senior year chasing someone that doesn't care about me anymore.
Yeah, that's... that's really smart.
Ohh! Yes!
Oh, slower, slower...
Oh, that's it.
Where the hell is my bed?
Oh, hi, Dan. Nice to see you, too.
Where's all my stuff, Deb?
I gave it away.
You what?
I had to. It was all wet and smelly.
And how did that happen?
The sprinklers came on by accident, after I tossed everything out the window.
That part was on purpose.
Besides, I had to make room for Hans to whip me...
...into shape.
A politician's wife has to look the part.
Right, Dan?
I guess you'll have to find someplace else to sleep.
Mmm...
Nice wings.
Nathan?
I couldn't even tell it was you.
This is how I can see everything and pretend like I was never even here.
Very sneaky, Bruce.
Hate to say it, but your wife looks pretty hot.
Haley always looks hot.
Hey! You look great.
Are you talking to me yet?
Not really, but I guess you're talking to me.
Peyton, I don't understand why you're so pissed off.
Really? You come back to town after months of being away
and try to pretend like nothing happened.
I'm not pretending anything. I'm just...
I'm sorry I didn't stay in touch with you. It was hard to keep up with people.
Haley, it wasn't me, okay? I'm not that needy.
But you didn't even call Nathan.
I did call.
Anyway, I just don't like what you did.
But your husband just said you look hot.
So if you do still love him, there's your in.
Hey, Peyton, I love your costume.
Mouth! Look at you! You're, like, the hottest guy here.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, nice.
Wait till Brooke sees him.
She's gonna love it, right?
Uh-huh. No. She thinks Motley Crue is the least-sexy band of all time.
We got to tell Lucas.
Uh...
Oh, no, you didn't.
I  did.
You are so gullible. Tommy Lee?
What?
He's like 40 and looks like that.
You set me up?
You should have been a pirate.
Nothing like a little Johnny Depp to make a girl want to commit.
I heard we got back together again.
Tommy Lee, Pamela Anderson.
Right.
At the very least, we did have a hot weekend together in Vegas.
You want to dance?
Unless you're seeing someone.
No.
Not exclusively.
You okay?
Peachy.
Excuse me?
Hiya, wifey.
You told me to find another place to sleep...
in the buff, naturally, since, thanks to you, some homeless person has all my clothes.
Great way to kick off my humanitarian campaign, though.
Forgot to thank you for that.
Would you care to join me, or would you rather sleep on the floor?
Fine.
Sweet dreams, Danny boy.
Hey, have you seen Nathan?
What's he dressed as?
I don't know, actually. I know he's seen me, but he's like the invisible man or something.
Um, Haley... are you okay?
Yeah, if "okay" is like heels that are killing me,
and I'm about five minutes from going home and bingeing on cookie dough.
That's not what I mean.
There's money missing from the register at the café.
I've noticed a pattern the past couple of weeks, and it always finds its way back right after payday.
Look, I know your parents are gone, and I know that things are a bit tight.
Was it you?
Yeah. Um...
I'm really sorry.
So am I...
that you didn't feel that you could come to me and ask if you needed help.
I thought we were closer.
We are. It won't happen again.
Good.
I want you to know that I am always there for you, no matter what.
Thanks.
Why don't I take this? Consider it interest.
Okay.
Hi!
Nice costume.
You like it?
Not really.
I mean, it's just not really you.
Yeah, I -- Brooke thought I could...
I just wanted you to want me again. I...
That's not the problem, Haley, trust me.
I mean, a sexy makeover's not gonna fix us, right?
Yeah, you're right. I mean...
I look ridiculous, don't I?
Haley, no...
I'm sorry.
Having fun?
Not really. I mean, I'm psyched to see the band, but I still had to force myself to come here tonight.
Me too.
I'm just dealing with some personal stuff.
Yeah, me too.
And someone spilled soda on my wings.
I think that was me.
I got an idea how we could make this night less sucky.
Are you propositioning me, Mouth?
Uh, yeah.
To dance.
All right! Are you guys all ready for Fall Down Boy?
Fall Out Boy.
Oh, um, right, right.
Anyway... do I hear a woot-woot?
Guess not. All right, well...
without further ado, Fall Out Boy.
What are you doing?
The band is playing. You're missing it.
This is such a bad idea.
But Nathan totally talked to you.
He swooped in like some kind of knight in Batman armor.
That's not the point! I look like an idiot!
Okay, maybe now that you messed up your hair --
This "Grease" thing is a lie. You turn into some cigarette-smoking hussy,
and you get your man? That doesn't work.
You were smoking?
Even if it did...
that's not who I am. I'm a tutor. I'm -- I'm a nerd.
You're a rock star.
Not anymore.
I'm just Haley.
That really should be enough.
I'm done playing games, Brooke.
I'm just gonna go home.
Okay.
And there better be cookie dough.
Hey, thank you for helping me earlier.
I'm sorry I freaked out like a baby.
I just want things back the way they were.
Hey.
I wanted to make sure you were okay. I saw you take the plunge and...
Nathan kissed me.
What?
I didn't even know what was happening. It just -- it happened, and then he was gone.
Did you go after him?
No. It was just so romantic and perfect.
I just wanted to come right home and not mess it up.
Well, then, I guess you're okay.
Yeah. It was a totally out-of-body experience for me.
Maybe I should get Nathan to kiss me.
Oh, shut up.
All right, then, uh...
- I'm gonna head home.
- Okay.
Thanks for the costume advice.
Remind me to never have you spy for me.
I'm sorry!
Luke, uh... there's just one more thing. I...
Your mom thinks I stole money from the café.
Why does she think that?
'Cause I told her I did.
'Cause I... was covering for you.
I saw you take it and...
What's going on, Luke?
I needed to buy some medicine.
For what?
For my heart, Hales.
I have HCM.
Angel of death. You're a little early.
How was the show?
You want to come inside?
I'm not staying.
I'm still glad you came --
You. Not the death part.
Look, I don't want to be curious about you, but I can't help it. I am.
Well, selfishly, I'm glad that's one battle you're losing.
I'm just scared.
Of what?
Of forgetting my mom, okay? Anna.
I used to have one of her t-shirts that smelled like her,
and I slept with it every night
until, one day, it started to smell more like me than it did her.
And so I took it out and tried every detergent I could find,
trying to find that smell. And I couldn't. It was gone.
And... so now sometimes I test myself, you know, just to see if I can find that smell.
And once in a while, I can.
But it's getting harder and harder.
I understand.
It's bad enough that you're really into music.
I don't want to find out you're an artist, too.
'Cause there are some things I know I got from her. I had to.
And I don't -- I don't want to change that.
Well, uh, the tendency towards drugs, which I would love to yell at you about --
that's from me.
But I can't draw to save my life.
Those sketches I saw in your room --
that's from your mom.
You know that.
And as far as your dad's concerned, when he sent me away all those years ago,
that was the right move.
I've done some pretty questionable things in my life, Peyton.
I would have sent me away, too.
But you're here now.
That's right.
And if you want to know things, then I want you to know them.
I'll tell you anything -- everything.
And if you don't want to know,
that's okay, too.
It's up to you.
Well, well. We meet again.
Thanks for coming.
How could I not?
You must have gotten my letter.
Yeah, I got it.
Did you like the perfume?
I'm kind of sexy like that sometimes.
So what can Chris Keller do for you?
He can help Haley with her music.
No, I'm serious.
Apparently, she's hit some kind of slump.
And you care why?
Because she loves it.
And I love her.
Wow. How heroic.
Or maybe just completely stupid.
I mean, why call me?
Because even though you're an ass, Haley's music came a long way with you.
You said in that letter you'd do anything to help her.
This is it.
Look, not that I don't love second chances,
but what makes you think you can trust me?
Oh, I don't trust you.
But Haley does.
Besides, if you touch her, I'll crush you.
Well, this is gonna cost you.
I mean, we've got studio space, first-class accommodations,
my time, which is worth a lot.
And I'm kind of digging that watch.
Don't screw with me, Keller.
All right, tell you what, give me the rest of this sandwich, I'm in.
All right. It's a deal, then.
And this stays between us.
Hello?
It's me.
I'm sorry, Deb.
I never meant for it to come to this.
I mean, we loved each other once, didn't we?
I know I loved you.
Dan, what are you doing?
I just had to talk to you.
Because...
I'm waiting for the glue to dry.
You superglued the phone?!
You want to play with me, game on, bitch.
Good night.
How was the rest of your night?
Well, Lucas thought he could make me jealous with that "Baywatch" bimbo.
Two can play at that game.
Hmm.
Brooke...
be careful.
His heart's more fragile than you think.
Ralph Waldo Emerson once wrote,
"There is no privacy that cannot be penetrated."
"No secret can be kept in the civilized world."
Hey.
You're still awake.
Of course. That's what fathers do --
wait up for their daughters.
Did you talk to Ellie?
Yeah.
Good.
But I didn't have to ask who my real father is.
I already know.
"...society is a masked ball
where everyone hides his real character...
and reveals it by hiding."
Transcript: Raceman - Synchro: Amariss
- www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net