Better make room.
Your other mom should be dead soon.
Hi. Can I help you?
That's one of our shirts.
Young lady, you're under arrest for the possession of stolen property.
What? No, no, no! I just needed something to sleep in!
Brooke? Brooke!
This is so "Brokedown Palace."
I can't believe I got arrested for wearing a stupid tank top.
I told you, you should have done your laundry.
I got arrested for wearing one of your stupid tank tops that you stole.
Well, sheesh.
Guess we know who the cellblock tough's gonna be.
Brooke, this isn't funny! This is going on my permanent record, on my college transcript,
and I am this close to beating your ass right now!
Okay. All right. Calm down.
Sorry.
Um, look, I talked to them.
I told them that the store ripped off Brooke's designs.
So all we have to do is pay them back for the clothes, so we can go, so...
what do you want to do?
We should call somebody, like our parents.
Mine are in California.
Mine are in an R.V. somewhere.
Mine's out to sea, or...
dead, or banished.
- Operator.
- Hi. Collect call, please.
- What's his name?
- Nathan Scott.
What do you mean, you need money?
You know what? You're gonna rot in jail, then,
'cause you're not getting another dime out of me.
Aren't you supposed to be in the studio right now?
I am.
I just figured it would be better if I told you on the phone.
Now, just relax. I'm coming in.
Okay. Here's the deal.
You gave me the money.
I had the money.
Then I lost the money...
playing poker.
Forget jail. Call the morgue.
I gave you $2,000!
I can get it back. I talked to the guy I lost it to.
I just need a ride. It's about 80 miles from here.
No way.
I figured you'd say that, too. And I guess it's cool.
It's just that, without the money, the studio won't release Haley's masters.
That's the not-so-cool part.
But, listen, you give me a ride, I'll get the money back.
I promise.
80 miles, you don't speak.
Let's go.
Sweet!
Road trip, Nate.
Right? Road trip.
Okay. Thank you. Oh, and Brooke keeps some extra cash under her bed and in her drawer.
Okay.
Hurry, please. Thank you.
Great!
So Nathan's coming.
Um, yeah. I-I couldn't get ahold of Nathan. I had to... call Lucas.
Haley, if he goes in that drawer, he's gonna find all the letters I wrote him last summer.
Good.
It could be the best thing for you.
It could be the worst thing for me.
One or the other.
Well, well.
So that's who tried to kill me.
Okay, girls, let's go.
Not you, Martha Stewart.
What? Why?
The kid with the cash... only paid for the other two.
Wait!
You guys all right?
Yeah. Um, Lucas, did you not pay for Brooke?
I paid for her. I just had them wait an extra 10 minutes fore they let her go.
So you're just screwing with her.
And you don't think she screwed with me?
Non-exclusive dating, the costume for the masquerade party,
her fantasy boy draft "misunderstanding."
I've done everything she's asked me to do so she got back, and what do I get?
Ooh, front-row seats to her and Keller in bed together.
Well... Luke, wait. Just stop, okay?
It's not like you don't have a right to be upset,
but at least wait five minutes and talk to her and then give her a ride home.
Can't do it.
Are you guys coming?
I got to be at the studio right now. And I can't wait for...
It's okay. I'll wait for her.
Okay. Thank you.
Lucas,  what am I supposed to tell Brooke?
Tell her to call Chris Keller.
Dude, we seriously need some tunes.
No! Don't!
It's jammed.
Aw, come on, man. What's a road trip without some road tunes!
Listen to me. This is not a road trip. This is a business trip to fix your screw-up.
Now, we get the money. We get Haley's song.
And, if you're lucky, I don't rearrange your face.
Fine.
Jeez.
By the way, how's your poker game?
Why?
That's how we're gonna get the money back, playing poker.
Hey, I fixed it.
All you had to do was keep your word, and you couldn't do it.
Take the money, pay the studio, and help Haley!
I am trying to help!
It's $100 buy-in. I got about 500 bucks.
Okay, it's either this or you can say goodbye to Haley's demo.
I thought you said you lost all the money.
Oh, I did.
It's the money your dad paid me last week to seduce Haley.
Ow, man! My head!
I wasn't gonna do it!
Dan Scott would have you believe that he's the family-first candidate for Tree Hill mayor.
It's a good thing his son can't vote.
Karen Roe -- the smart choice, the caring choice.
You  must be pleased with yourself.
I guess I should thank you. I mean, this little commercial of yours
is gonna bring me a whole new batch of voters --
wife beaters, S&M freaks.
Who are you kidding? You're in trouble, and you know it.
I wouldn't be so sure.
This afternoon, when the polls open and we give our final speeches, you're gonna concede.
Really?
Or what?
Or I'm gonna show the public who tried to kill me.
Notice the time-and-date stamp --
day of the fire, a few hours before.
Now wait for it. This is the good part.
Gentlemen, we have a winner.
I believe that's the same brand of booze used to poison me.
And I believe that's someone you care about buying it,
someone with a motive.
The tangled web we weave...
Oh, when you concede today,
make sure you say nice things about me.
Please be there. Come on.
Oh, thank god.
Hi.
How are you?
Right. Okay.
I don't know what to say, other than I'm so sorry.
You have nothing to apologize for.
We weren't together.
Luke.
I just didn't know "non-exclusive" meant,
"hell, I'm gonna sleep with Chris Keller."
Pretty skanky move, Brooke.
I am sorry.
I am sorry that I did it, and I am sorry that you had to see it.
But you are looking at me right now like I am so much worse than you,
and you were with Peyton while we were dating.
I didn't sleep with Peyton.
No, but you slept with Nicki.
I didn't have feelings for you then.
I guess that's my answer.
No, it's not, Lucas. I care about you so much.
Well, you have a hell of a way of showing it.
I don't know why I did it, okay? I, um...
I mean, yeah, I-I was drinking, and I was jealous that you were with Rachel.
But I think...
it was really just because I was really afraid to get close to you again.
Well, you don't have to worry about that now.
Do you?
I didn't expect you to be kind about this, but seeing you this way...
it's even worse than I thought it would be.
Good.
Haley, there's a call for Chris. Is he coming in today?
Uh, he's supposed to be here right now.
Yeah. Can I take a message for Chris?
Yeah, well, you're gonna have to get in line, 'cause he owes me money, too.
And, trust me, I guarantee it's a lot more than he owes you
for some Batman costume rental.
Great. Riverboat gambling.
Nice move, Tom Sawyer.
Let me guess -- you got a gun in there, and we're gonna rob the place.
Actually, that was plan "B."
Dude, this is a 1967 Gibson Dove. I wasn't gonna leave it in that junker car of yours.
Plus, I look cool carrying a guitar.
Let's go.
Oh.  Uh, the guy I lost the money to -- Marty?
Well, he kind of scares me.
Poker-playing psycho named Marty -- it's perfect.
Well, well. Gang's all here.
Nate, this is Dexter.
This is Emanuelle.
These are the cops. Guys.
And this is... Marty.
You're Marty?
Yeah, that's right.
Who the hell are you?
Oh, this is Nate. He's a big poker player.
What do you mean, "big"?
Is that supposed to be some kind of joke?
No, no. I just mean that he --
Hey, can we play or what, right?
I don't know, can you?
You got your buy-in, Keller, or are you a little, uh, short?
Chris Keller, the human ATM.
It's your loss.
What are you watching?
I don't know, but they seem sad.
Did you talk to Lucas?
Sorry.
Where did we go so wrong?
Well...
I slept with Chris Keller, and you went on tour with him.
No, I mean...
okay, yeah.
But when did we start letting boys dictate our happiness?
I was 9.
Well, I-I don't care. It has to stop.
You've got too much talent with your fashion line.
Not anymore.
Oh,  so what? So they stole a couple of designs. They didn't steal your talent.
I'm sure you've got more.
A couple unfinished dresses.
So finish them.
Listen, we'll, um... we'll put together a website,
and we'll sell them ourselves.
You'd help me?
Yeah, I'd help you.
You have to help yourself first, though, missy.
Clothes over bros?
Clothes over bros.
Okay. This is crap.
- What's that?
- You being here.
It's one thing for you to haunt my dreams, but I'm awake now.
You sure about that?
Besides,  guilt never sleeps.
"Guilt"?
Oh. Oh, okay, so that's it. You're what, my subconscious?
No, no. I'm just, like, the little voice inside your head,
only I'm not so much on the inside now.
Fine. I'm talking to myself.
I'll play along. Hey, what are you doing here?
I'm having a snack. See, it's pretty great, actually.
I eat, and you get fat.
Oh, hey. I fixed this for you.
"People always greave"?
You spelled it wrong.
Well, if I spelled it wrong, then so did you.
Who knew my subconscious could be such a bitch?
No, no. We're a bitch.
Try to keep up, okay?
Oh, hey. Check it out.
Closet full of anxiety. Get it?
Look, ghost of Christmas goth,
what do I have to do or say to get rid of you?
That's easy.
Where's your bracelet?
P. Sawyer!
Oh, I'm sorry. Were you sleeping?
I think so.
I guess I lost Ellie's cancer bracelet.
Nothing. What's up?
I just need some artwork for my new fashion line.
You mean the fashion line that Suburban Filth owns?
No, I mean my new fashion line. Haley helped me see the light.
Instead of making out, I should be making clothes.
Although clothes make you look hot, then boys want to make out with you.
Not the point. I'm moving on, and I'm doing my own thing.
These are perfect. So sleep it up.
Come over tonight, 'cause my stuff is gonna rock your socks.
You're bluffing.
Then call me and find out.
I'll do more than that.
I'll raise you, Marty. All in.
Dude, maybe you shouldn't do that.
He's bluffing.
Read 'em and weep.
It's practically an orgy!
A pair of 3s?
You lost everything on a pair of 3s?!
You suck at this, Chris.
Keller, you look like a toilet at the airport --
broke and full of crap.
What about these?
This car's worth at least 2 grand.
Hold on.
I'll give you 50 bucks for it.
Done.
No way in hell! Dude, let's just get out here!
You want to get Haley's tape back, or what?
I'll tell you what.
Here's 50 bucks and a condom.
You two can get a room.
We're playing poker.
Hi. It's me.
I, uh... I need to ask you something.
Did you try to kill Dan?
Because I, uh...
I need to know the truth.
Been on a hell of a roll, kid.
Nobody's that lucky.
What's the matter, Marty?
Short temper?
No, something's messed up.
Yeah, your teeth.
No. He's right.
For the last two hours, every time you deal, he wins.
No, not every time.
But for the last two hours!
Whoa! What are you saying, Marty?
What I'm trying to say is this --
if we turn over those cards and he has a pair of anything,
your ass is as good as dead.
You know what? This is crap. Nathan, let's go.
All right. Hold on, hold on. I've lost a lot tonight.
Not lately.
We got a problem here?
No problem...
Yeah. Not a problem here.
...So long as that card's not a jack.
Okay, look, Marty, I don't want to hit you because you're --
You got something to say? You say it, Keller!
Aw, hell.
Running!
Dude, we got to jump.
No way, man. Chris Keller can't swim.
It's either jump or die!
You're not hearing me. I can't swim!
Do you have the money?
- Yeah, I got it right here, man.
- Okay. Good.
What the hell?!
Go!
All right!
Not bad.
Are you serious?
My cellphone's shot,
we're in the middle of nowhere, and you check your guitar?
How about a thank-you for not letting you drown?
Whoa. Chris Keller was dog-paddling just fine.
Chris Keller was sinking just fine!
Give me the money.
Oh, I must have lost it all in the river.
I should have let you drown.
Wait up, man! It's spooky out here!
You okay?
Oh, just a little nervous.
The polls are open, and, uh, in a few minutes, I give my final address.
Mom, Dan just told me he thinks someone tried to kill him.
The fire was ruled an accident.
But what if it wasn't?
You know, and what if he does have proof?
Is winning this election worth the risk?
Maybe you should...
concede, mom.
Final statements, Karen.
These came for you.
And you know I have to stand by Dan tonight. I just, uh...
Good luck.
They're from Andy.
Whatever you say, be sure not to stumble on the word "concede."
Thank you.
A few minutes ago, my son asked me how important this election was to me.
And my answer to him is that it's very important.
But what's more important?
Believing in your fellow man.
Having faith in a person's character.
Trusting that a person is who we think they are
and defending that trust until we're given proof
beyond a reasonable doubt that we should no longer do so.
With that said...
I wish to concede... but not the election.
I  wish to concede that when I decided to run for mayor,
I underestimated my opponent
and the depths to which he will go to hurt and to humiliate others.
You have seen the commercials.
You have seen the real Dan Scott.
Now do the right thing and vote for Karen Roe.
My opponent has decided to write me off
based on a recent video that I'm sure you've all seen.
Well, I'd like to tell you that that video is a fabrication, a fake.
I'd like to tell you that,
but I'm afraid that would be a lie.
It's an accurate depiction of a man at his worst,
and I'm not proud of it.
And so, today, I ask for understanding,
for forgiveness...
for a second chance.
I'm sorry.
They say identification is the first step to recovery.
I stand fore you, a man who woke up.
I am not perfect.
I'm just a guy trying to be a good husband...
and a father who sometimes comes up short.
And if you elect me, you'll be electing a work in progress.
But you'll also be electing a man who will never put himself above any of you
or above the town that I love.
I woke up to be your mayor!
And I promise never to sleep on the job again!
Brooke, come on! Just show us what you have so far!
Come on!
Okay. So these are just prototypes,
but I introduce you to my new line --
"Clothes over Bro's."
Brooke, that's awesome!
Thanks, but there's more.
We've got the flaming-heart ring tee.
We have "'C' over 'B'" sweats...
I like that.
And the tutor-girl, P. Sawyer-inspired, "Clothes over Bro's" concert jerseys.
These are awesome Brooke. This rocks.
I know, but every designer needs her couture line,
so I'm now introducing you to "Clothes over Bro's" upscale.
- Oh, my gosh, Brooke.
- You made that?
- I made that.
- That's gorgeous.
So cute, right?
See, that's more me!
That's so pretty.
That's cute.
Trouble.
And they're all available at ClothesOverBros.com.
Thanks.
Come on, man. Slow down.
* shape * weak.
Dude, we're 80 miles from home and you gambled my damn car away.
No, not exactly, actually I grabbed your keys right before Marty punched me in the crotch
In other news, um, actually I have about 500 dollars left on me so...
...basically, we broke even.
You call this "breaking even", I thought we were actually winning!
I should've known you can't be honest.
I can be honest.
No, you can't.
I kissed Haley... at the masquerade party.
Man, I was trying to help you!
Wh--
See, this is why I'm never honest!
Now, stop hitting me.
Stop kissing my wife!
I will when you start kissing her.
What the hell is wrong with you?!
Listen.
The night you called me to come to town was the night of the masquerade party.
I thought it'd be funny if we both went in the same costume,
so I bribed the guy at the costume shop to tell me what you rented.
But then I got there and I saw you and Haley weren't getting along.
So I thought if I just kissed her -- I know! Okay, it was stupid, all right?
But I did it for you.
I didn't do it for me.
So are we even?
"Even"?
You kissed my wife. You lost all my money.
You lied to me about the poker game,
and you got me attacked by a midget and a transvestite.
Whoa, whoa.
You think Emanuelle's a dude?
E-man-uelle has an adam's apple.
Oops.
You want to know the worst part?
Haley's the one that suffers the most.
She put her heart and soul into that song, and you screwed her over.
Nice work.
You should be proud of that.
Pretty great, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't think you need the apostrophe though in bro's, it's not really grammatically correct.
It's my fashion line and I'm keeping the apostrophe.
Okay, well, good for you.
You did it all yourself, anyway.
Not really, you got me there.
Yeah, I kinda feel like a big fraud though...
What? Why?
Because I told yourself to put yourself before boys,
and I secretly spent the whole day thinking about Nathan.
Why? Did something happen?
You know how I told you that Nathan kissed me at the masquerade party?
Yeah.
It might not have been Nathan.
I think it might have been Chris.
Kringle?
No, I didn't think so.
W-wow. How could you kiss Chris Keller and then think that Chris was Nathan?
Maybe I just wanted to believe that it was Nathan so bad that...
What if I was wrong, though?
He could just be trying to keep things pleasant until the divorce is final.
I do not believe that.
I don't.
It's hard, isn't it?
I mean, I love my clothes.
There's an ache in my heart where Lucas used to be.
I don't think covering it up with a stylish and smartly priced sweat top's gonna make it go away.
It is stylish, though.
Well?
What do you know? I got them.
Get out of here.
No, that's everything. That's the masters, demo -- bought and paid for.
We only had 500 bucks.
I got a way with people, I guess.
Listen, I'm -- I'm gonna be taking off.
I may not see you for a while, so, uh...
Well, whatever.
You sold your guitar.
The thing was waterlogged, anyway.
You love that guitar.
Well, hey...
I guess this makes us even.
Maybe so, but that's not why I did it.
You tell Haley that song is a hit.
Or maybe don't, unless you want to lose her again.
Hey.
Where are you going?
Chris Keller's work here is done.
- Did you find it yet?
- Damn it!
Let me ask you something.
If I have a heart attack, do you die, too?
That's -- that's really sweet.
Okay, I am not arguing with you.
Oh, come on, Peyton! That's what we do, okay?
We have these inner conversations daily.
"Am I gonna look stupid?"
"Am I pretty enough?"
"Did Jake just want to get in my pants?"
"Should Lucas be with me instead of Brooke?"
No, okay? You're wrong.
Lucas and I are just friends.
And Jake loved me.
Whatever you say... cheerleader.
"Poor me."
Whine, whine, mope, mope.
Always the victim!
"My mom died. Jake left. Ellie lied."
Boohoo.
You really are a bitch.
I'm not the one that sent Ellie away.
People always leave?
Or Peyton always drives them away?
Where's the bracelet, Peyton?
And it looks as though Dan Scott's narrow lead will hold in
one of the closest decisions we've ever seen.
Now back to you, Bill.
It's still close. You never know.
I'm afraid I do.
Dan Scott's the freaking mayor!
You did your best, mom.
Don't be sad.
It's not that. It's Dan.
And even though he might be wrong about the fire,
if he thinks it's intentional, he won't stop until he finds someone to blame.
I worry for that person, Lucas.
I really do.
Ladies and gentlemen, the soon-to-be mayor of Tree Hill, North Carolina, Dan Scott!
It makes you wonder, huh?
Do the wicked never lose?
Hi, Lucas.
How's your mom doing?
She's worried about you.
She just doesn't know it.
What do you mean?
"For everything you've done."
I-I don't understand.
I think you do.
That's the last shred of evidence.
As far as I know, there's nothing else to tie you to this, Deb.
Ladies and gentlemen, can I have your attention, please?
I've just received word that, in a matter of minutes, the votes will be in
and victory will be ours!
He knows it wasn't an accident.
But he doesn't have proof.
They said we were beaten!
They said we were dead!
Maybe this can finally set you free.
But they should know by now,
you can't kill Dan Scott!
I didn't do this alone.
And to that end, I'd like to bring out my beautiful and supportive wife, Deb,
to enjoy the moment with me.
I guess it's true what they say.
It's lonely at the top.
I can't find it.
Why do you think Ellie came to see us, Peyton?
She has cancer.
She has regrets.
She's closing up shop.
She's in remission.
You know that's a lie.
- She's dying.
- No, she's not!
Where is the bracelet, Peyton?!
I lost it, okay?!
The last thing she wanted in this world was to get to know you.
And you sent her away.
Hi. It's me.
Lucas knows.
Hi.
Hey. Thanks for coming.
Yeah, thanks for calling me.
What's wrong?
Your song is great, Haley.
Chris played it for me. It's a -- it's a long story, but...
it's really great.
I just wanted you to know that.
Oh. Okay.
My mom left...
for good, I think.
Oh, and, apparently, my dad's the mayor now.
So... yeah, today really sucked ass.
Oh Nathan, I'm so sorry.
You know, for most of my life, I would have gone through all this alone.
Then I met you,
and I finally found someone I could depend on when life got like this.
So I guess I called you...
'cause I wanted to know if that was still there.
Nathan, you can always call me.
Always and forever.
I want to ask you something.
The night of the masquerade party, did we --
did you kiss me?
Of course I did.
Oh, no, you didn't.
That kiss wasn't half as good as this one.
But I love you for lying to me.
Thanks for calling.
- Haley.
- Yeah?
Stay with me tonight.
Oh, I was hoping you would say that.
There are 82 letters in here,
and they're all addressed to you.
I wrote them all this summer.
One a day, but I never sent them because I was afraid.
Brooke.
I was afraid of getting my heart broken again...
like before.
'Cause you hurt me so bad and...
I was afraid to be vulnerable.
And I was afraid of you and the way that you make me feel.
And I know that doesn't matter now, after what I did.
But I just thought that you should know.
This is how I spent my summer, Luke...
wanting you.
I was just too scared to admit it.
Brooke!
I'm sorry.
What you did with Chris...
...it's okay.
It's not.
It can't be. It's too much to forgive.
Well, that's too bad...
because I forgive you.
You can't.
I just did.
So you're gonna just have to deal with it.
I'm the guy for you, Brooke Davis.
And I know I hurt you last time we were together, but --
I love you.
I love you, too.
Pretty girl.
I found her.
You happy now?
No.
But you are.
You can wake up now.
Transcript: Raceman - Synchro: Amariss
- www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net