I'm reprogramming
a CTU key car right now.
Good.
Our couriers are delivering
the canisters to the targets.
They'll be in place soon.
When are you launching
your attacks?
After you're done at CTU.
GARDNER:
When these terrorists attack,
you're going to need
to maintain order.
I believe we should be thinking
of a preemptive declaration
of martial law.
in the Greater
Los Angeles area.
If CTU
can't find
this man, Bierko,
we're gonna get hit!
Why didn't you
just tell me
you were alive?
JACK:
If you knew I was alive,
you would have been at risk,
and I had no choice.
I'm happy
that you're alive-- I am,
but I can't give you
what you want right now.
Michelle's murder
was part of a bigger plan.
to supply terrorists
with Sentox nerve gas.
Who's behind it?
BUCHANAN:
Christopher Anderson.
Whatever he's not telling us
is important.
And he's willing to tolerate
an inhuman amount of pain.
Thousands of lives
are at stake.
There is enough time for you
to tell me what I need to know
to stop this insanity, please!
I'm sorry, guy,
but I can't tell you
what you want to know.
( phone ringing )
This is Bauer.
BUCHANAN:
We've been compromised!
Someone used a stolen key card
to access CTU
less than an hour ago.
JACK:
Freeze!
Drop the gun!
Bill, it's Jack.
I think he tried to deploy nerve
gas throughout the building.
BUCHANAN:
Code six, everybody out!
Go, go!
Seal all the rooms.
Oh, no.
Chloe.
MAN ( over P.A. ):
All CTU personnel.
This facility
has been contaminated
with Sentox VX1 nerve gas.
Repeat: this facility
has been contaminated.
There are two safe zones
on the main floor--
the Situation Room and Medical.
On the second floor,
the safe zones
are Mr. Buchanan's office
and Holding Room Four.
These areas will remain sealed,
pending the arrival
of the Chemical Response Team.
If you are in any of these
sealed areas, do not attempt
to leave until the CRT
clears the environment.
I'm on my way, but it could take
20 to 30 minutes
to gather all the CRT
personnel you'll need.
I understand, Curtis,
but we need CRT
here now!
This is a high priority.
Get here as fast as you can.
All right, copy-- I'll call you
in a few minutes with updates,
( phone ringing )
This is Bauer.
Jack, it's Bill.
I just talked to Curtis.
He's with the Chemical
Response Team.
They won't be able to get here
for at least 30 minutes.
Why not?
Most of their units
were sent to Tyler Memorial.
The rest are en route
to high probability targets.
Okay, we're going
to keep working here.
Our networks
are still up, right?
Yeah, the phones are working,
the computers are up.
I can coordinate with Division
from here.
What do you need where you are?
I need to know if Henderson
is still alive.
Where is he?
Agent Burke was transferring him
over to the Isolation Clinic
in Medical.
I don't know if they made it
before the barriers went down.
You can tell if you pull up
a building grid.
What about CTU's
chemical response plan?
Chloe, my name
is Dr. Landes.
Now, he was a friend of yours--
what was his name?
Edgar.
LANDES:
I'd like you to turn away
from Edgar
and focus on me, please.
Chloe,
you're in shock,
and I'd like to help you
through it.
The only thing
I'm going to ask you to do
is sit in this chair
and collect your breath.
Let's do that now.
Just collect your breath,
just for a second.
He was such a good guy.
I just treated him
like crap all day.
This is my fault.
Sir?
Someone stole my key card
and used it to get
into the building.
It was missing,
and I didn't say anything.
Why not?
I thought they just stole
my wallet for the money.
How could you not report it?
I was embarrassed.
I didn't want anyone to know
I got beat up.
So we're all going to die,
because you were embarrassed?
( man groans )
Mr. Almeida, what are you doing?
I want to know
what's going on.
No, I can't allow that.
I'm not sitting
in this damn bed
while CTU is under attack--
got it?
Fine.
How long are we supposed to
be sectioned off like this?
I haven't received
any news.
Oh, my God.
Jack, we've got
the building grid.
( dialing )
( ringing )
Buchanan.
Bill, it's Jack--
the grid's up.
All right, check the isolation
zones that have logged in.
You'll have survivors.
Two zones have logged on
in Medical.
Try them.
I'm going to keep
this line open.
Okay, hold on.
( phone ringing )
Clinic.
Dr. Besson, it's Jack Bauer.
Jack, what's going on?
One of the terrorists
infiltrated CTU
and deployed a canister
of Sentox nerve gas
through the ventilation system.
That's why we needed to seal off
as many rooms as possible.
I need to know if Agent Burke
got to Medical with Henderson.
Yes, he did.
Henderson's here right now?
Tony, is that you?
Jack, how much longer
are we going to be locked down?
Right now, we're in standby--
we're trying to figure out
how to clean out the air supply.
Dr. Besson?
Tony!
Get me a security feed
over at Medical.
Jack, I don't think this
program is set up for that.
Try a redirect.
All right.
Dr. Besson!
( phone beeps off )
BURKE:
What are you doing?
Move aside.
( system beeps )
My God, he's got a gun.
Patch me through
to their intercom.
Do it.
We'll be able to hear them,
but they can't hear us yet.
BURKE:
You can't kill him.
He's got information
we need.
He killed my wife!
Tony, please, don't kill him.
Move aside, Rick!
I don't want to shoot you,
but I will.
Move it!
Henderson!
You remember me?
My name is Tony Almeida.
You killed my wife,
Michelle Dessler, this morning.
He's going to kill him-- hurry!
Hurry!
She was my life,
and you took her.
And now,
I'm going to take yours.
I got it.
Tony, it's Jack.
I've got you
on the security feed.
Stay out of this, Jack!
Tony, please, just listen to me.
You can't do this.
I know how you
feel right now.
I lost Terry
the exact same way,
to one of our own.
I know what it feels
to be betrayed like this.
But, Tony, Henderson
has information
that can save thousands
and thousands of lives.
And I know that doesn't make you
feel better right now,
but I know you, Tony.
I know you don't want to make
this situation
any worse than it is.
Please?
Please, just let us finish
our interrogation.
Hurry up.
Agent Burke, please continue.
We have to get him talking.
He's our only lead to Bierko
and the rest
of the Sentox canisters.
Tell me where to find Bierko.
( grunts )
Where?
Nowhere.
BURKE:
What is your computer password?
No.
I know no password.
JACK:
Agent Burke,
can we increase
the dose?
Not without killing him.
Okay, take a short break
and then start again.
Get back to me as soon
as you've got anything.
Yes, sir.
GARDNER:
How could CTU have been hit?
We're not sure,
Mr. Vice President.
Are you telling me
they didn't have
any safeguards in place?
They had partial containment,
but our early reports indicate
that 40% of their personnel
have been taken out.
You mean
they've been killed?
We're afraid so, sir.
CTU is protecting
this city.
Are you saying
they're no longer
capable of doing that?
I'm saying they've been
seriously compromised, yes.
So what are we going
to do, Ms. Hayes?
We've got terrorists
with nerve gas canisters
out there.
Who is going
to stop them?
Mr. President, I suggest
an emergency restructuring.
Meaning what?
Meaning that the Chemical
Response Team
will go in
neutralize the nerve gas
at CTU
and I will take a team
in there and personally
manage the operation.
How soon can you do that?
Within the hour.
Fine. Do it.
Yes, sir.
All right, they're still
somewhat operational.
It's not a complete
disaster.
Mr. President, it is.
I can see no other option
right now
but to impose martial law
on the city of Los Angeles.
Hal, my advisors believe if the
military takes over the streets
and starts detaining people,
it could create mayhem.
Sir, it's only a matter of time
before more canisters
are released
in public places
and then you will have
mayhem.
Except without the soldiers
you'll need to contain it.
So what do I tell
the public?
That we've got nerve gas
canisters all over the city,
but we don't know
where they are?!
No, no, you don't have
to get into that.
Tie it to that earlier
incident at the airport.
I'm going to get resistance
from all sides.
That's true, sir.
We may have to swallow
some saltwater,
but wouldn't it be worth it,
if we can keep
the people off the streets,
safe from
another public attack?
I don't know, Hal.
Sir, consider this--
if we clear the streets
of everybody
except the military,
these terrorists won't be able
to move as freely
as they are right now.
We have to do
whatever we can
to stop the people behind this.
CTU is no longer
an obstacle.
At least for
the time being.
Good.
Have our men move
from their current positions
and go to the new target.
How much of the nerve gas
will they release there?
All of it.
Excuse me.
Chloe, are you ready
to go back to work?
What do you need?
I need you.
We can't break Henderson.
I need you to keep trying
to decrypt the files
that we took
from his computer.
I already tried that.
It didn't work.
Maybe somebody else
could do it.
Chloe, you're the only person
in the room qualified.
Chloe, please.
Don't shut down on me now.
I'm upset about everything
that's happening too,
but you know how
things work around here.
We do not quit
until it's over.
You're not helping her.
You're just making things worse.
I am sure that you
are qualified
to help someone through
this kind of distress
over an extended
period of time,
but you see, we do not have
an extended
period of time.
So if you don't mind
stepping aside
so I can do my job,
I would appreciate it.
Believe it or not, Jack,
you don't have to be
qualified to help people.
You just have to be there
for them.
Like you were there
for my daughter.
What does that mean?
You're 20 years older
than she is.
I know exactly
what you're doing.
I've done nothing but try
and help her deal with her loss.
How dare you accuse me
of taking advantage of her.
You did...
Dad, stop!
You can be angry
at me all you want,
but before I met Barry,
I didn't want to live.
Do you understand that?
Fine, I'll get back to work
if everyone could just relax.
Jack, we have a problem.
What?
( beeping )
Chloe, I just saw
the alarm.
What's going on?
The seal pressure indicators
in the contaminated zones
are showing traces
of sublimated polymer
near the partition seal.
What does that mean?
It means that the nerve gas
must be mixed
with a corrosive agent--
an acid.
The acid's breaking down
the seal
between the rooms.
How long till
the seal fails completely?
CHLOE:
It's hard to say for sure.
Can you give me an estimate?
It's deteriorating quickly.
I'd say 15 minutes,
20 at the most.
And then what?
As soon as the gas
permeates the seal,
it enters the room.
Then it's over.
Get me schematics
on all the isolated zones.
( typing rapidly )
Mr. Vice President,
with all due respect,
I'm not trying
to usurp your position.
I'm simply trying to serve
the president
the best way I can.
( sighing ):
Yes, sir.
What was that about?
I was trying
to convince Gardner
to let me help him draft
the president's statement.
Charles is letting Hal
write his statement?!
He's insisted.
And the president
gave him the go-ahead.
But that means Gardner
is effectively
making policy.
We've got
to stop him.
I'm trying.
But you know what kind
of pressure
the president's
under today.
He wants all the counsel
he can get.
And Hal's only too eager
to help out.
Of course he's too eager.
He's got his eye
on the Oval Office.
Anything he can do
to speed up Charles' downfall
puts him one step
closer to the presidency.
Martha, you have to intervene.
Hal feeds
the president ideas.
We saw it
at the WTO,
we saw it in Chicago.
When they work,
Hal takes the credit for them.
When they don't,
the president
takes the hits.
Have you reminded
Charles of that?
I can't.
Hal's the vice president.
I'm just the chief of staff.
You have influence
that supercedes
any constitutional rank.
And now's the time
to use it.
I want to see the statement
as soon as it's issued.
You will.
I just checked the readings
from all uncontaminated zones.
The testing you've been doing
in your respective areas
is consistent.
The Sentox nerve gas
that was released
into the air duct system
contains a corrosive agent
that is eating away
at the barrier seals
protecting the safe zones.
I'm not going
to pull any punches.
CRT will not be here
to help us.
At this point, our only hope
is to help ourselves.
We need to find a way
to either neutralize
or flush the Sentox
out of the contaminated areas
before the barrier seals fail
and the gas enters
the safe zones.
I want all personnel
working on this problem.
We don't have much time.
Do what you can.
We'll hope for the best.
Maybe we can do something
from in here.
Access the ventilation
system?
Even if I could,
it doesn't mean
we could do anything to stop
the seals from breaking down.
Just try.
Maybe it's not
as bad as we think.
Maybe the numbers are off.
They're not.
Even if the seals leak,
CRT could get here in time.
The only reason
she's here
is because I asked
her to stay.
If something happens to her,
it's going to be because of me.
Because of what I did.
There was no way that
you could know
that CTU was vulnerable.
CHLOE:
Jack.
You've got something?
I think if I can slow
the seals from breaking down
I can flush
the contaminated areas
using the air conditioning.
Do it.
Something's wrong.
The control isn't responding.
Why not?
It's being blocked
by some program
that I can't
get to remotely.
It's probably on a computer
near Holding Four.
Can you get me in there?
This is a false wall.
The air in there
is not contaminated.
Can he get to
the computer
through there?
Yes, but once he makes
it through the safe zone,
he'll be in
a contaminated area.
What are you talking about?
He can't go through
a contaminated area.
I can hold my breath.
The Sentox won't be
absorbed by my skin
over that short
a period of time.
As long as I don't inhale it,
I'll be fine.
Jack, you can't
hold your breath that long.
I only have to hold my breath
long enough
to get to the computer,
disconnect the program
and get back
to the ventilated room.
Once I'm back
in the safe room,
how long will it take you
to clear out the Sentox?
About 20 seconds
based on
the cubic footage.
AUDREY:
Jack, even if you
get to the computer,
what if we can't
ventilate that room?
Chloe thinks we can.
Right now, this is
our only option.
CRT is not going
to get here in time.
The seals are now
80% gone.
What's the bottom line?
We have less
than 20 minutes.
AUDREY:
All right, Jack,
Chloe and I
are on channel one.
If you need to communicate
with anyone else
we'll patch you through.
As soon as I go through,
you have to replace this
behind me.
Jack, it's time.
Go now.
Now.
Chloe, it's Jack.
I just completed the airlock.
I'm getting ready to move
into the ventilation room.
I'll tap my com unit
three times
when I'm back
in the safe room.
All right. Jack,
I don't have to remind you
if that airlock leaks,
we'll all be dead
within the next three minutes.
It's not going
to leak, Chloe.
Okay...
I'm going in.
Okay.
( inhales deeply )
* *
( computer blipping )
Seal corrosion is now
at 86 percent.
Is there anything
we can do from here?
No, we just have to wait.
There's nothing we can do to get
your dad out any faster.
Don't talk down to me, Chloe.
Listen, we're in a crisis
situation here, okay?
Tempers are bound to flare.
Let's just everybody breathe.
What's with you
and the breathing?
Is that your solution
to everything?
It's Jack,
he's back in the room.
It's too soon, he couldn't
have found the program
and disabled it yet.
He's got 15 more seconds
before the room clears.
What's it mean that
he finished so quickly?
I don't know.
Well, it could be
a good thing, right?
It could be a good thing
or it could be a bad thing.
That's what
"I don't know" means.
( computer blips )
All right, Jack,
the room is clear, you can
breathe. Are you okay?
( gasps )
I couldn't get to it.
Chloe, you're right.
I saw it.
There's a computer
program running on
the AC control unit,
but there's a security grate
in the wall behind the vent.
I don't see it on my system.
Trust me, it's there.
I just found it.
It was a security upgrade
in the last two years.
Somebody didn't file it
properly,
that's why
I didn't see it.
Are there any other vents
that could help us
get into that wall?
No, they've all been upgraded.
Well, it's a room,
there's got to be a door.
Where does it lead?
To a corridor
above Holding Four.
None of us can get there
from where we're at.
Who's in holding room four?
Lynn McGill.
Are there any other vented rooms
we can get him to?
No, Jack, there's nothing.
Patch me through to him.
( phone rings )
( phone beeps on )
McGill here.
Lynn, it's Jack.
We found a computer interrupt
in the AC control unit.
Now if we can shut that down
in the next
few minutes, we can stop the gas
from permeating the safe zones.
Well, that's good news.
The problem is
you're the only person
close enough to get to it.
Chloe?
CHLOE:
It's directly above
the holding room
where you are now.
Take the stairs, go to the left
around the corner.
It's the room on your left.
Okay...
How are we going
to do this, Jack?
Lynn, the truth is
if I can get there,
I would do this myself,
but I'm not close enough.
No one who's
still alive in CTU is.
You're the only person
who can do this.
And I'm going to have to ask you
to do it without any protection.
I see.
No, you don't.
As soon as you open the door
to the hallway,
your room
will become contaminated.
You can hold your breath long
enough to fix the problem,
but we have nowhere else
to send you.
We can't airlock you.
There are two of us
in here, Jack.
Sir, this is Harry Swinton.
So you're saying
that if he does this,
then we're both going to die?
I'm so sorry.
We don't have a choice, Harry.
How do we know that you're not
just making this story up
so you don't have to make
the sacrifice yourself?
You don't.
All I can ask you to do
is believe me.
I'm telling you the truth.
Well, that's easy for you
to say, sir.
You're not the one
who's about to die.
It's not easy for me to say.
Hold on.
( keypad beeps )
We have to do this, Harry.
We're going to die anyway.
If we don't,
so will everyone in CTU.
We have to do this.