So, Lindsay, this is the sign- in room...
and this is what we call
the standards room.
Nice. Very goth.
So what happens in here?
This is where we measure and weigh
the dead bodies.
Okay, Tru.
Okay, let's be honest here.
You're cute, you're 22 years old.
There are better career opportunities
out there for you.
I told you, working here will help me
get into med school.
Then at least get off the graveyard shift.
I mean...
all the good parties start after midnight,
and who am I gonna go with now?
You'll survive. Besides, I think I might
be able to do some good by working here.
How? Everyone's already dead.
Not everyone.
You're not gonna believe this.
I just fished a tennis ball
out of a guy's large intestine.
Hello.
Remind me to cancel
my tennis club membership.
Lindsay, Davis, my boss.
- Davis, Lindsay, my best friend.
- Hi. It's nice to meet you.
I'm good, really.
I was just leaving.
Tru, thank you for the tour.
And we're still on for shopping tomorrow?
Absolutely.
Okay, great.
See you tomorrow.
Look, Tru...
I know that the morgue
is not exactly Party Central...
but don't worry, things will pick up.
Actually, that's what I'm afraid of.
My kid's in that building! He's upstairs!
Someone's gotta get him! Please go!
Yes, ma'am, we'll get him!
Come here. I got you.
How about those Giants today?
That's seven in a row, my man.
Talk about really being on fire.
Go downstairs!
You're stuck!
I'm fine! Go!
No, come on!
Listen to me.
I'll be down in a minute, okay?
Don't worry about me.
Go on.
Go!
Help me.
Hey, gorgeous.
I didn't want to wake you.
Where are you going?
I am having breakfast with Dean Hazelton.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, it looks like a post's
opened up in the psych department...
and if I kiss up to the old windbag...
you will be dating
a fully tenured professor.
Let me ask you.
What do you think of this?
Very suave.
How was work last night?
Pretty dead.
That's funny. That's clever.
Why don't you
get back to sleep, beautiful?
They said five minutes
for a table. It's been 10 minutes already.
You okay?
Yeah. What could be wrong?
Let's see...
last time we talked, you told me
that dead people were talking to you...
so I thought I might be remiss
if I didn't follow up.
I'm fine, Harrison. Everything's fine.
WAITRESS: Two?
WAITRESS: Your table's ready.
Finally.
See, you're a lousy liar, Tru.
I want to know what's going on.
- Trust me, you don't.
- What?
All of a sudden, you can't confide in me?
Your brother?
You really want to know?
So let me get this straight.
You know, to recap.
The dead people,
they ask for your help in the morgue.
Just once.
It happened once. Hopefully, only once.
And then you got propelled.
That's the word you used, right?
Propelled back to yesterday?
I relived the day, yes.
So you were able to save the lady's life
because she wasn't dead yet?
Tru, what can I say?
You're my sister, and I'll always love you.
I know it sounds a little crazy, but....
Smooth move.
A little crazy? No.
The run with the bulls
is a little crazy. Skydiving.
Dating actresses is a little crazy. This?
This is certifiably insane.
Harrison, I'm not lying,
and I don't think I'm nuts, either.
You really relived the day?
Then you tell me this...
who's gonna win the Tigers game today?
What?
Rosemary and 24th.
Great. Traffic's gonna be jammed
clear downtown.
Catch you later.
You dog.
You were dating a professor and,
telling me just what, slipped your mind?
I knew you wouldn't approve.
I'm stunned.
Me, too.
- I thought things were good with him.
- No, I'm talking about us.
We're friends. Best friends.
Okay, now I get why
you've been acting so strange lately.
Okay, you can't keep secrets
from your friends. Especially me.
I just feel so stupid. I mean, you know me.
I don't even fall for guys often.
But when you do fall, you fall hard.
Excuse me?
Very nice. Yeah.
So anyway, what did you do
when you caught him with the bim?
Nothing.
- Nothing?
- I froze.
You caught your boyfriend in the act,
and you froze.
God, do you know what
I would have done to him?
I would have humiliated him.
I would have made him wish
he'd never ever met me.
Tru, you just blew the perfect opportunity
to put that jerk in his place.
I gotta go.
Where?
More abuse. Bye.
- I'm worried about you.
- Me?
Yeah. What's with this morgue thing?
It's my job. And it's a good thing to have
on my résumé for med school.
It's a little odd, don't you think?
To work at the same morgue where
they brought Mom after she was killed?
What?
What are you talking about?
My God, you really don't remember,
do you?
Still, working there's kind of ghoulish,
don't you think?
Tru, whatever you're trying
to accomplish...
Mom's gone.
Nothing can bring her back.
What's so interesting?
Nothing.
Are those intake files from '93?
It's nothing, Davis.
'93 was a very bad year.
Why's that?
The death rate in the city was low,
maybe the lowest in the country...
and then, after '93,
it just went up like a skyrocket.
lncoming.
This is Samantha Block.
My God.
Died of smoke inhalation.
The fire started
on the fourth floor around 5:00.
The firemen thought
they'd cleared the building.
She was hiding under the bed.
What started the fire?
Gas explosion.
This one here is Nick Kelly, a civilian.
He saved a 12- year- old boy,
smoke got him, too.
The victim has a broken ankle.
Probably trying to get out.
Old buildings are death traps.
Discoloration of the cheeks.
From what?
Might indicate inhalation
of a chemical compound.
I'm guessing dimethyl benzene.
Is this guy a genius or what?
Genius, you owe me $20.
The Tigers shut them out tonight.
Patterson threw a two- hitter.
What's dimethyl benzene?
lndustrial uses, mainly.
Her, too. They must have
ingested it from the smoke.
Cotton fibers plastered
on the epidermal layer.
And it's red and something else.
It's hard to teII.
So young.
Damn tragedy is what it is.
I don't know if I can take this.
Believe it or not, it actually gets easier.
Besides, I like to think
they're going to a better place.
You believe that?
Well, if you're gonna work here,
you gotta believe it.
Of course, the dead get off easy.
It's the ones left behind
that gotta deal with all the pain.
Renee says she ain't gonna
hook you up.
No more of her friends.
Why not?
'Cause you're scaring them off, man.
You're a nice guy,
but you come on too strong.
It was only eight e- mails.
HeIp me.
You just gotta play it cool.
Did you guys hear that?
Hear what?
Nothing. Never mind.
Tru, let me ask you.
When you go out with a guy...
you want him to lay back a little, right?
And make you earn it.
HeIp me.
I'll be right back.
She's hot. Weird, but hot.
HeIp me.
Help me.
Hey, gorgeous.
Where are you going?
I've got a breakfast with Dean Hazelton.
Tru!
Sorry, what?
I asked what you thought of this.
How's this look?
Yeah, it looks fine.
Breakfast with the Dean?
That's a surprise.
Yeah, there's a post that's gonna open up
in the psych department.
If I kiss up to the old windbag...
then you will be dating
a fully tenured professor.
That's a good one.
- What?
- Opportunity.
It's a good opportunity.
So you're sure about the jacket?
Yeah, very suave.
So suave, in fact...
that I think you should
stick around for a while.
I can't. I gotta go meet the Dean.
But I will see you tonight.
Um....
You realize you were hired
for the night shift, don't you?
Do you ever actually go home?
I could ask you the same question.
I just thought if I'm gonna do a good job,
I'd better get to know the system.
Diligent.
Enough with the crypt.
Let's check out the database, yeah?
Municipal database.
What are you doing with that?
Just a little research.
Who's Nick Kelly?
What do you know.
He's a fireman.
- Can I help you, miss?
- Yes. I'm looking for Nick Kelly.
Hey, Nick?
Yo.
Somebody to see you.
Hi, I'm Nick.
Hi. Can we talk?
- 84 Hastings?
- Yeah, that's the one.
That's right down the block from me.
What makes you think that
that building's a fire hazard?
No reason in particular.
I'm doing a fire risk assessment
in prewar buildings...
for my architecture class.
- That's a weird assignment.
- Weird professor.
Yeah, I'd be happy to go down
and take a look at that unit for you.
What do you say, about 5:00?
The fire started around 5:00.
5:00 is too late. I'm supposed to be
in my professor's office at 2:00.
And this really can't wait?
Not if I want to pass.
Okay, what the hell.
Things are slow around here,
anyway. Let me ask you something.
- Why me?
- Sorry?
You could've asked any one of these guys
for help, but you asked for me.
I have the calendar.
That was for charity.
It's the Widows and Orphans Fund.
Okay, Mr. September.
I wasn't here for the last
fire inspection. I spent the night in the ER.
Wedding ring dropped down
the garbage disposal.
I put my hand in, almost lost two fingers.
I said to my wife,"If that doesn't
scream commitment, what does?"
- We just want to check the furnace.
- No problem. The basement's down here.
- That shirt was a gift from your father.
- I hate it.
It makes me look like a geek.
It's what a loser would wear.
You're wearing it, and that's final.
What's gotten into you?
Take your sister outside and pIay.
What do you say, Samantha?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
She's a sweetheart.
She is, isn't she?
She turns 7 next week.
Yeah, I hope so.
Creepy.
Come on.
Watch your step.
What are we doing?
First rule of fire risk assessment...
you want to check all mains
and all pipelines for gas leaks.
You might want to take some notes.
For your report.
- It's okay. Photographic memory.
- Really?
What's that?
This is what we call a gas sniffer.
It's used to detect
the source of a leak.
Won't we smell it?
If the concentration's high enough,
we will.
Hold on a sec.
What?
You've got a little bit of soot right there.
Thank you.
I should take you on all my inspections.
Here, come on down.
Careful. You never know
what you might find down here.
Be careful.
Wait a minute. Here we go.
You see that?
What?
Right there.
- It's a leak?
- Yeah.
It sure is. Would you hold that?
Yeah.
Let me see that.
Yeah, see that?
There you go.
You know, it's a good thing
you contacted us.
We wouldn't have found this without you.
You're sure it's patched?
Yeah, it's fine.
Positive? I mean, there's no chance
this thing's gonna explode or anything?
No, it's fine.
Good. No fires here today.
Not in the building, anyway.
Listen, I'm off duty in 10 minutes.
You want to get some coffee?
I could give you the whole sordid history
of fire risk in prewar buildings.
- Actually, I'd like to, but....
- Boyfriend?
You know, let me get back to you
on that one.
My roommate really wants to meet you.
Maybe we could double this weekend.
Gina, I'm an associate professor.
I don't double.
All right. I'd love to meet your friends,
just don't drag me to a pep rally, all right?
I'll be right back.
I just have to use the ladies' room.
Tru?
Hi.
This is a....
- What are you doing here?
- Thought I'd surprise you.
We haven't had much quality time
on account of my job and all.
What, aren't you glad to see me?
Yeah, of course I am. It's....I'm surprised.
Where's the Dean?
Canceled. Pancreatitis.
Mark?
I'm sorry. I just wanted to come
and say hi to my favorite professor.
Yeah, this is Tru.
She was one of my star pupils.
Are you in his class now?
You'll learn a lot from him.
Things you don't expect.
Things you might not want to learn...
but he has a way of
making things very clear.
You must really miss his class.
I thought I would.
But I know now
that it's gonna miss me much more.
Anyway, I've taken enough
of the professor's time.
Goodbye, Mark. He's all yours.
Wait. Tru.
- You did that?
- It was amazing.
To have the chance to say
everything you want right in the moment.
God.
I could never do something like that.
You're so strong, Tru.
I really admire that about you.
And I'm sorry about Evans.
Not surprised, but sorry.
Cute.
So from now on, no more secrets, okay?
Okay.
Then there's something
I have to tell you, Lindsay.
- I think I met someone new.
- Already?
You little slut.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
Did you know Mom's body
was sent to the morgue where I work?
No. But then again,
I was 10 when she died.
Come on, Tru. You gotta forget
about that stuff. You were a kid.
You gotta cut yourself some slack.
- How did you know that?
- Know what?
You knew that top was loose
before it even came off. Seriously.
Last week you knew about my cards,
and now this.
Are you gonna teII me what's going on?
I can't.
Why not?
- Because you won't understand.
- Me?
- Come on, Tru. How do you know that?
- I just do.
For the same reason I know
it's gonna rain at 3:00...
or that Patterson's gonna throw
a two- hitter for the Tigers.
Talk about answering a question
with a question.
Honest, I just don't
get you sometimes, Tru.
Is Patterson gonna throw a two- hitter?
I love that shirt, by the way.
Love this? I just pulled it out of the closet.
What?
- Nothing.
- No, what?
It's just nice to meet someone
who's not a jerk.
- Well, we're not all jerks.
- No, you're not.
So maybe you don't mind me
asking you how come you lied to me...
about being a student?
What makes you think I lied?
You're supposed to be
in your professor's office at 2:00...
with your report, and it's 2:15.
We did a good thing, right?
Stopping that leak?
Yeah, we did.
So let's just leave it at that.
Okay. Strange, but okay.
Do you like being a firefighter?
Yeah, I like helping people.
Don't you worry
about how dangerous your job is?
You see it on the news all the time.
A firefighter goes into a building and....
I don't really think about it.
Sometimes a job just chooses you.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I do.
I mean you're good at it.
If we hadn't found that leak...
who knows what could've happened
this afternoon.
This afternoon?
You don't know who could've been killed.
Actually, I do.
No one.
What do you mean?
That wasn't anywhere near
the accumulation necessary...
to cause an explosion.
That leak wasn't dangerous?
In time, yeah.
A week,
two weeks down the line, maybe...
but that leak wasn't gonna
cause a fire today. Not a chance.
The type of fire
you're hypothetically describing...
would be caused by dipping a cotton rag
in some sort of accelerant.
Like dimethyl benzene?
Why are you so interested
in discussing arson scenarios?
- Do you have a grudge against someone?
- I'm here to learn.
Dimethyl benzene
is found in cleaning solvents.
You soak a rag with the stuff,
put it next to a fuel source and kaboom.
The fibers you described...
would be seared into the skin of anyone
within proximity of the blast.
So this was arson.
Hypothetically.
Hypothetically, yes.
It's quick to ignite, it's hard to trace.
If you get it on your hands,
watch out, it's nasty burns.
I wasn't here for the last fire inspection.
I spent the night in the ER.
Thanks for your help, Davis.
If you ever need help with
other hypothetical research projects...
I'm always here...
and if I'm not here,
you can call my cell phone.
We couId even maybe discuss it
over drinks or something.
Do you have company?
Someone who's meeting me. A friend.
- His name's Nick Kelly.
- Mr. September?
It's for a good cause.
So you work here?
Sometimes a job chooses you.
Anyway, I'm thinking arson.
You said the gas leak
couldn't have started a fire today.
- That means it happened another way.
- What are you talking about?
- There's no fire at 84 Hastings.
- No.
Not yet.
I don't understand why you suspect
him for a fire that hasn't happened.
He was indicted for insurance fraud.
And you think he's planning
to burn down the building?
What's this about, Tru?
Why did you bring me here?
I believe 84 Hastings
may be a target for arson today.
If you have information
related to an arson...
you need to tell the police,
not run around like Nancy Drew.
- It's just a hunch.
- What kind of a hunch?
Listen, I'll make you a deal.
I'm listening.
Wait till tonight, and I'll tell you
anything you want to know.
And a whole lot more.
You're very lucky I have a soft spot
for strange women.
It's 3:30. I'll meet you back at your place
as soon as I can.
Grab a couple of beers,
order some Chinese...
and do not leave until I get there.
You promise?
Very, very strange.
Hello?
Is anybody down here?
Mr. Ford.
Let me guess. You lost an earring.
No. I'm here to tell you something.
What's that?
This building's being watched
by the police and fire departments.
They suspect a potential arson may occur.
Okay, I'll bite. Why?
You tell me.
Who the hell are you?
You were indicted for insurance fraud
two years ago.
- So what?
- How about taking that bandage off?
What the hell is this?
I'm just giving you a warning.
Don't talk to me like that, okay?
How was school, honey? Was it good?
Fine.
This is Samantha Block.
Died of smoke inhalation.
Come on, Samantha.
We don't talk to strangers.
Excuse me, ma'am?
Harrison, I can't talk right now.
I'm kind of putting out fires.
The Tigers won today, just like you said.
Glad I could help.
I want some answers, Tru.
- How did you know?
- I don't have time....
How much did you win?
A IittIe probIem there.
I would've won if I had the bucks.
So here's the way I see it.
To prevent future mishaps,
every morning...
you and I, we get together,
we go over the game scores.
First we'II start with footbaII--
I gotta go.
Might indicate inhalation
of a chemical compound.
I'm guessing dimethyl benzene.
lndustrial uses, mainly.
Hi.
I heard a noise.
I'm Tru. I think we met earlier.
Yeah, I remember.
What do you say we get out of here?
Come on, I'll buy you a soda.
That little girl with you upstairs,
was that your sister?
Yeah.
- You don't sound too thrilled.
- She's okay.
This place sucks. My dad blew us off.
He lives in Washington
with some new wife.
Why'd you break into Mr. Ford's office?
It was an accident. I knocked too hard.
You could've just picked the lock.
It's a hundred years old.
Kevin, I need you to do me a favor.
But I need you
to not ask any questions, okay?
- What?
- When 5:00 rolls around...
make sure you, your sister, and your mom
are out of the building...
- and anyone else you can tell.
- Why?
- We said no questions, right?
- Okay. Done.
Cool. I'll be just a second.
Hello?
You're where?
Nick, I asked you to wait for me
at your apartment.
And I asked you for an explanation...
as to why you're trying
to put out nonexistent fires.
I mean, it's a beautiful day,
and I'm sitting in my apartment...
because some girl who works in a morgue
asked me to.
I think it's the super.
I told you...
- prior convictions aren't proof.
- His office was full of accelerants.
For equipment cleaning.
He's a building super.
There's something going on with him.
Even if there is, there is still no fire.
You can't arrest a guy
for thinking about doing something.
Luckily, we can't be arrested
for our thoughts.
You think I'm insane, don't you?
Honestly? It's touch and go.
Look, maybe I'm doing this wrong,
I don't know.
- I just want to stop a fire.
- A fire that hasn't happened.
But it could.
How do you know?
I just do.
lntuition again?
I was right about the gas leak.
Look, you have to trust me.
That's the weird thing.
I do.
It's almost 5:00.
She's beautiful, and she tells time, too.
- No.
- What's wrong?
I can't right now.
Sure you can.
- No, I can't.
- We're here.
If I kiss you, I'll fall for you,
and I can't do that. That would be bad.
Why would that be so bad?
What?
Cotton fibers were plastered
on the epidermal layer.
It's red and something else.
That was a gift from your father.
I hate it.
- I was wrong.
- About what?
How it started. It's the kid.
What kid?
Kevin. The kid from the building.
He's gonna start the fire.
So some kid is gonna start a fire?
A minute ago you said it was the super.
He's angry.
Lonely. Feels invisible.
He could pick the lock
to the super's office.
What better way to get attention?
It makes sense.
To you maybe.
I have to get to that building.
That kid's sister is in trouble.
- Tru, I--
- Promise me you'll go home.
But if there's a fire--
No.
You're right. There's no fire.
I'm wrong. Crazy, even.
So then go home. Wait for me there.
Promise me, Nick.
- I'm tired of this game.
- Nick, please.
I like you.
I really do.
And I think you feel the same way.
- I'm not imagining this, am I?
- No.
- Then I need to know what--
- I told you...
you'll get all the answers tonight.
And before this day ends,
we'll have that kiss. But just go home.
Everybody, out of the building! Come on!
The building's on fire! Everybody, out!
You gotta get out, there's a fire!
Please, let's go!
Get out of the building!
Come on, you gotta get out! Please!
- What are you doing here?
- I followed you.
You promised!
I was worried!
You gotta get out of here right now!
Trust me! Come on!
- lntuition again?
- Let's go.
- No, I can't leave.
- Why not?
- I'm a fireman.
- You don't have your gear.
I rang the alarm.
They'll be here any minute.
Great. Traffic's gonna be jammed
clear downtown.
They're gonna be delayed by traffic.
That's why you went in.
You live down the block.
Listen. I want you to get out.
I'm gonna check upstairs.
No, Nick, wait!
Come here. I got you.
How about those Giants today?
That's seven in a row, my man.
Talk about really being on fire.
Nick!
Yeah, coming! Got a rescue!
The victim has a broken ankle.
- Nick, stop!
- What?
The floor's weak! Watch out!
How did you....Never mind.
My God!
See, I knew we'd have the kiss
before the day was over.
But Sam, she's supposed to be at the park.
My God. My daughter's still inside!
She's still in the building!
- Where are you going?
- I'm going after her.
She was hiding under the bed.
She's hiding under her bed.
But send someone else, please.
It's my job, Tru.
And I'm stubborn as you are.
Nick, no!
Listen to me.
I'll be down in a minute, okay?
Get this gear.
No, Nick!
No time, there's a little girl upstairs.
I know where she is.
Tru!
- I can't talk right now.
- You're crying.
Yes.
I know. It's been rough on both of us.
I get it.
No, you don't.
I wish that I could rewind
the day and have it back.
I would do everything differently.
I would show you
how much you mean to me.
You had your day.
You only get one.
I thought when you asked me for help,
it was for you.
Now I know it was for Samantha.
You saved her.
Everyone's calling you a hero.
I don't want to sound selfish...
but I wanted both of you.
You said your job
was a chance to help people.
All they have to do is ask.
So is mine.
So ask me, Nick.
Please?
I'm not leaving till you ask.
So please ask me, Nick.
Please, just ask.