PreviousIy, on Tru Calling:
Stay quiet now, Tru.
Where is your daughter?
She's not here.
Good.
This is Harper.
He'll be interviewing to replace Gardez.
And thanks for making me feel
so welcome.
It's never easy being the new guy.
That guy's going places.
Let's just hope
somewhere far, far away from here.
What's with your sister, anyway?
Ever since Mom died,
she looks over the family.
That's why she seems to have
the weight of the world on her shoulders.
There was someone else.
It was your mother.
What you can do...
she could do it, too.
It's the end of the line, Maggie.
Please, Nick. I promise
I won't tell anyone what I know.
You're right.
You won't.
See? That's her. That's her right there.
That's Carly Anders.
Right. It's the girl
from all those teen movies.
She put an album out, also, so....
And I care because?
Because she's gonna be
spending the day with us tomorrow.
Okay, remind me again
why some actress is coming here?
Because she's playing a morgue attendant
in her next movie...
she wants to make sure that she has
all the technical aspects of the role.
That's not what I meant. I don't get
why she's coming here, to our morgue.
A hometown girl.
Her mom and eight- year- oId sister
Iive nearby.
- Two birds with one stone, I guess.
- Okay.
Hey, what's this?
"Victim's sex, manner of death."
Well, it's personal data of everyone
that you've saved so far.
I'm using it to Iook for recurring patterns
among wouId- be victims.
So if a body comes into the morgue,
we'll know how likely it is to ask for help.
You know you're most likely to be asked
for help on Mondays and Thursdays...
that the killer is someone
that the victim is close to?
Does it say anything about my mother?
I'm not sure that I understand--
It say why she didn't tell me
about reliving days?
That she could do it, too?
I'm sure she would've,
but she ran out of time.
She must have known
there was some chance...
that she'd pass it on to her kids,
but never told us.
She never prepared us.
I mean, not one word.
I know that you're angry--
I just wish your research
could tell me that.
Not that I just won't be getting
any Mondays or Thursdays off for a while.
That's perfect.
'Cause I'll take all the Mondays I can get.
Big TV night for me.
- Is that the new schedule?
- No.
It's nothing. But I'll post the new schedule
in the morning.
Okay. Bye.
You know, Tru, I was thumbing
through the intake records this morning...
and I couldn't help but notice
you've never been on a pickup.
- That's ridiculous. I've--
- No, not one.
You're right. And that's my fault.
And I'm sorry.
And, Jack, thanks for pointing that out.
Thank you.
Any time.
All your pickups have been on relive days.
You remember?
It's like it never happened.
Do you think he heard us?
We so need a secret lair.
Help me.
$2, 200?
PIease, sir, don't insuIt me, okay?
This is a hunk of junk.
What are you, out of your mind?
That's an insuIt.
This vehicle's six years old,
has under 30, 000 miles?
$2, 200 is a steaI.
Yeah,"steal"
being the operative word.
Would you like a cup of coffee?
Got some brewing in the office.
Sorry, I just got off the night shift.
- Oh, really? Where do you work?
- I work over at the county--
Sidebar, you and me, right now.
What did we say about sharing
personal info with the used car guy?
Once they think you've got cash,
they jack up the price.
All I said was I work the night shift.
Look, just stick to the plan.
Talking to dead people, your thing.
- Haggling, mine.
- Fine.
Yeah, she'll give you $2, 000 for it, Monty.
Not a penny more.
Deal.
I'll start the paperwork.
Coffee, right?
Why do I feel he would've gone lower
than $2, 000?
Hey, at least you got a set of wheels now.
So you can do your girly stuff
and go save dead people.
All the things that you like to do.
I gotta go. Lindsay wants to prep me
for dinner with her sister tonight.
All right.
- Wish me luck.
- Luck.
Remember, celebrities
are just like you and me, only famous...
- so try to keep it cool.
- I'll try.
Hi, you must be Davis.
Tru Davies.
Carly Anders.
And this is my assistant, Anna.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
So, this is the Standards Room,
where a body gets processed.
After being picked up from a crime scene?
That's part of a morgue attendant's job,
to retrieve the body?
Typically, yeah.
But what if there isn't a body?
What if you get to a crime scene and it
looked like a murder had taken place...
but the body was gone?
Where are you going with this?
The reason I ask is that
in the first act of this movie...
my character issues a death
certificate for a guy who vanishes...
while hiking in the mountains.
You're wondering why you'd do that
if there wasn't a body?
Exactly.
Under certain circumstances...
a coroner's office can declare a person
legally dead without a body.
It's called
a certificate of presumptive death.
Let me ask you another question.
So how'd you get into this line of work?
Well, I had an internship lined up
to help me get into med school...
and when that fell through,
I kinda ended up here.
I used to want to be a doctor
when I was a kid.
But then the acting thing took off.
You know how it is when you find
your calling. You gotta answer it.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
But, judging by your success,
it seems you made the right choice.
I'm not so sure sometimes.
I mean, all the pressure, the hours,
putting up with the media...
it gets to you after a while.
Maybe I should work here.
Dead people are much less demanding.
Actually, you'd be surprised.
Look, I know this probably seems crazy...
but, Erin, she never likes my boyfriends,
and I really want her to like you.
- Relax. She's gonna love me.
- Well, she'd better.
We both know how spotty
your track record's been lately.
- Yeah.
- Look, I'm just....
I'm really counting on you, okay?
- Jackie, what's going on, man?
- Harrison.
Excuse me.
What is up?
How are you?
You at a funeral?
Yeah. A friend of mine passed away.
I came to pay my respects.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Yeah. Me, too.
Hi.
Jack, Lindsay. Lindsay, Jack.
Jack? Yeah, Harrison's told me
lots about you.
You know, I was about to go get a drink.
Would you guys like to join me?
I know it's early, but it's kinda been
one of those days, you know?
I actually have a ton of stuff to do
before tonight...
but if you think you can squeeze a drink in
before dinner, then....
Are you kidding?
Probably knock back three or four, huh?
But we won't.
She was really nice, Davis.
Totally down to earth.
Not at all what I expected.
Someone I could definitely hang with.
Yeah, if she wasn't going back
to Hollywood tomorrow.
It's not just that.
This whole superhero thing.
All the running around I do,
it's hard to keep the friends I have...
let alone make new ones.
Traditionally, superheroes
don't have many friends.
Just a close- knit group of allies
and confidants.
Well, I'm 22 years old, Davis.
I need more than allies and confidants.
- Hey. Can I help you?
- Yeah.
- I'm looking for Carly Anders.
- You just missed her.
Oh, shoot. I was really hoping
to catch up with her.
- Is she a friend of yours?
- We go way back.
You wouldn't know
where she was heading?
Her mom's, I think.
You could try her there.
Thanks, I will.
Well, Davis, I'll see you tomorrow.
It's been kind of a long day.
Tru, about your mother....
Maybe she never told you because she
didn't think you were ready to understand.
Well, I guess we'll never know, will we?
Bye.
Oh, no.
To new friends.
It's never easy
being the new guy in town.
I just wanted to say thanks
for making it not so hard.
Well, hey.
What's so funny, friend?
Just picturing your sister's face
when she finds out we hung out.
Yeah, don't take it personal.
You know Tru.
No, actually, I don't.
I mean, we work in the same place,
we talk every day, we work side by side...
but I can't really say I know her.
- Well, she's cool, bro.
- No doubt she is.
She's like me. Loyal.
But she is smart as hell.
And she works her tail off.
Tell me about it. She comes in off-shift...
practically memorizes the stats
of all the corpses.
That job, it's like she lives for it,
you know?
- Understatement of the year.
- What's that?
What's what?
Something about your sister
I should know?
What?
No.
TaIk to me.
Nice job.
- My car is a lemon.
- What?
It won't start.
Something's wrong with the engine.
We'll take it back in the morning.
Right. I'm sure Monty's Used Cars
has a real accommodating return policy.
I'II figure something out,
I promise.
- Look, right now, all I need is a ride home.
- A ride home?
Look, I'd love to help you out, Tru.
But I gotta go home, get ready.
If I don't look just right tonight,
Lindsay is gonna kill me.
- Whoa, you're kidding, right?
- Ask her where she is.
- Where are you?
- At the corner of Third and Ogden.
- Third and Ogden.
- Tell her I'll swing by the morgue...
and pick up the van,
be there in 20 minutes.
My man, Jack,
says he'll be there in 20 minutes.
Jack? No, I don't want a ride from Jack.
Babe, gift, horse, mouth. Need I say more?
So, you want to ride up front
or in the back?
Very funny.
Harrison sends his love, by the way.
Where were you two, anyway?
The racetrack?
- No, actually we were in a bar.
- Much better.
Why do I feel you don't want me
hanging out with your brother?
Probably because you're very perceptive.
- Harrison's a nice guy.
- Yeah, and I'd like to keep him that way.
A guy's gotta make friends somewhere.
What's that supposed to mean?
You think it's been easy for me
working in the morgue?
I try to be friendly, I try to be a good guy,
but every time I walk into a room...
you and Davis clam up,
or you change the subject, or you leave.
That has nothing to do with you.
Still, it doesn't exactly make me feel
like part of the team.
Jack, if we made you feel left out...
that's not at all what we're trying....
We would never want to....
Apology accepted.
Go for Jack.
Yeah? Yeah, I'll be right there.
Well, it's your lucky day, Davies.
You're about to go on your first pickup.
Hop in.
I mean, have you noticed this
crazy weather we've been having lately?
I remember it being much, much warmer
this time last year.
I know, isn't it the strangest thing?
I mean, it's late spring,
and I'm still in my midwinter wardrobe.
That is a lovely color on you, by the way.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Would you excuse me?
I'm just gonna powder my nose.
Yeah, sure.
You are doing awesome.
Come on, babe. What did you expect?
Don't answer that.
The deceased called 91 1 from her car
approximately 90 minutes ago.
Said she was being pursued by another
vehicle as she approached the bridge.
Then the line went dead.
Three guesses what happened next.
I'm gonna get the gurney. Be right back.
Okay. Do you think
she was forced off the road?
The divers found a red paint
scrape on the driver's side door.
Most likely from
the pursuing vehicle.
Who took her body out of the car?
She was already washed up on the shore
when we got here.
MostIy IikeIy thrown free on impact.
Jim.
Oh, no.
Carly.
Tru, I need your help.
$2, 200 for this hunk of junk?
What are you, out of your mind?
That's an insult.
Oh, boy. Here we go again.
$2, 200 is a steal.
"Steal" being
the operative word.
- I don't want it.
- Pardon?
I don't want it. I want....
I want that one.
- I thought I was doing the negotiating.
- Not today.
Little lady, I think you're mistaken.
This car is in"like new" condition.
It's got at Ieast another 60, 000 miIes in it.
It's got six miles in it,
and then it's gonna die.
And I'm not your little lady.
Did the day restart
so you could save a car?
I'll give you $1, 500 for that red one.
- It's listed at over $2, 000.
- $1, 500. Take it or leave it.
Deal.
Thanks, Monty.
The Carly Anders,
as in the one who's getting ready...
to come down the elevator?
Yeah.
I'm nervous around regular people,
but famous people that are about to die?
She's not gonna die, Davis.
Not if we have anything to say about it.
Who knew you would be asked
for help on Wednesdays?
Why wouldn't I be?
According to my research,
relived Wednesdays are a statistical rarity.
I was gonna make it your day off.
No more research.
Take it off your computer altogether.
Why?
Jack's been asking questions.
He thinks we're up to something.
We should be more careful,
don't you think?
- Well, what about suspects?
- There aren't any. Not yet anyway.
Find out what you can during the tour.
We need something to go on here.
Okay.
And try to be cooI today.
Hi. You must be Davis.
So, did you like the elevator?
What if, at the crime scene,
it looked like a murder had taken place...
but the body was gone?
Depending on the circumstances...
you'd issue a certificate
of presumptive death...
which allows the coroner
to declare a person legally dead...
- even if there's no body.
- Really?
Yeah. So, what's it like coming home
after striking it big? Is it weird?
Sure. But going home is always weird,
no matter who you are.
Yeah, but do you run into
any real jealous types?
- Here and there.
- Anyone who has any big issues with you?
Look, you seem like a real sweet person...
but I'd rather not talk
about my personal life.
Right. Of course. I was just wondering....
- Please, let's just stick to business, okay?
- Okay.
I was just gonna grab some lunch
from that diner up the street.
- Do you want anything?
- No, I'm good. Thanks.
Okay.
- Hey, Davis?
- Yeah?
Mind taking over?
I'm gonna run to the diner with Anna.
Yeah. Will you get me
a slice of chocolate....
I have a corn dog here, so it's fine.
Okay.
I've been with Carly for four years now.
Best boss I ever had.
- So you're pretty much with her 24/7, huh?
- More or less.
Then you'd know if there was someone...
who might be
holding a grudge against her?
A grudge?
Yeah. I mean, she got so famous, right?
Some people might resent that.
Everybody loves Carly.
So, you're saying you can't think of
one person who might feel otherwise?
The tabloids have a field day with her,
but Carly's tough.
One of the most determined people
I've ever met.
Really?
Her mom told me the only time
she ever took off was eight years ago...
right after a big movie.
She was 16 years old,
and on the verge of a nervous breakdown.
Finally, her mom forces her
to take a year off.
After that,
she comes back stronger than ever.
Wow.
Where's Carly?
That guy came in,
said he needed to talk to her.
I tried to stop him,
but she said it was okay.
He came looking for Carly yesterday,
but she'd left by the time he got here.
You heard anything they've been saying?
Been keeping their voices lowered.
I can't do this anymore!
I'll see you later, Carly.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
That was just an old friend.
- Didn't look too friendly to me.
- Yeah? Well, it's nothing.
- Anyway, I should be going. Is Anna....
- Pulling the car around.
You sure you don't want
to stay a bit longer?
- I could autopsy something for you.
- No, thanks.
Nice meeting you.
Yeah, you, too.
You just gonna let her leave like that?
Don't worry, I'll be right behind her.
After all, I have to return this.
Did you steal her purse?
I had to do something.
- I needed to buy myself some more time.
- For what?
To figure out how I'm gonna tell her
she's gonna die tonight.
- Relax. She's gonna love me.
- Well, she'd better.
We both know how spotty
your track record's been lately.
- Yeah.
- Look, I'm just....
I'm really counting on you, okay?
- Jackie.
- Harrison.
So, you all ready
for Lindsay's big test tonight?
Oh, the test? No, no.
It's, you know, it's....
Dinner. Right.
You're a braver man than I am, Harrison.
But, hey, if I would've played it safe...
maybe I wouldn't be pushing 30
and all alone.
No, safe? No. It's....
Me and Lindsay? We click.
- You know what I'm saying, man?
- I stand corrected.
The truth is, I envy you, man.
You have what every guy wants...
whether he's man enough
to admit it or not.
To you and Lindsay.
Me and Lindsay.
You must be Carly's sister.
- Are you a reporter?
- No. My name's Tru.
- Swear you're not a reporter?
- Swear.
Oh, Tru.
Hey, your sister's adorable.
She looks just like you.
- How can I help you?
- You left this at the morgue.
- Wanted to return it before you left town.
- Thanks.
I wanted to talk about the guy
that came to the morgue today.
- Peter?
- Yeah, you two seemed pretty worked up.
- I don't see how that's your business.
- It's not, but....
- Listen, I'm worried about you.
- Why?
Because I have a bad feeling.
- So, what, you're psychic now?
- No.
Look, you've been asking
strange questions all day.
Thanks for dropping off my purse,
but you should go now.
If you're in trouble, maybe I can help.
I don't even know you.
No, not yet.
But if you just gave me a chance--
- We'd be the best of friends.
- Carly, please, I'm just....
Look, come near me or my family again,
and I'm calling the police.
Yo, thanks again, bro.
We should do this again sometime.
We should.
About what I said back in the bar....
No, don't worry about it.
No, I've just lost too many buddies
to wives and kids.
I don't want to lose another one.
You keep picking up that tab,
there ain't no chance of that.
All right.
Need a lift?
No, man. It's a nice day.
I'm gonna walk. Good luck tonight.
Thanks again, man.
Leave the key in the lock.
Step away from the car.
All right, buddy. Take it easy, man.
Take it easy, okay? Be cool. All right?
No problem.
Hang onto your keys, Harrison.
- No, you did not just say that.
- I'm afraid I did.
- Jack? Jack, just....
- Keys!
It's your car, not his.
Shut up!
When a guy with a gun asks for keys,
you hand the keys to him.
That's how it works.
Not this time.
The only way this guy's gonna get your car
is if you give it to him.
Because he certainly doesn't
have the stones to do it on his own.
If he did, we'd be dead already,
and he'd be nothing but a set of taillights.
- You sure about that?
- Oh, yeah.
Look, the car is a piece of crap, man.
It ain't worth it, okay?
Five seconds, your boy here's dead.
Jack, come on, man.
Five.
Come on, Jack.
It ain't worth it, Jack.
Four.
Come on, Jack! Hey!
Three.
Jack, man, come on!
- It's okay, Harrison.
- Two.
Let me give him the keys, man! Jack!
No!
One.
Bang.
What the hell was that, man?
This was a mistake.
She won't even talk to me now.
She just doesn't understand you.
WeII, we were totaIIy cooI yesterday.
And now, thanks to my gift,
she thinks I'm a psycho.
Which, to be completely honest,
I can't blame her.
- All that matters now is saving her life.
- Yeah, I know. It's just....
Sooner or later,
this gig is gonna cost me all my friends.
Tru, a hero's journey is treacherous.
Yeah, treachery I can deal with.
But being alone kinda sucks.
I'm guessing you weren't able
to find anything out...
- about the guy she was arguing with?
- No, just a name. Peter.
Angry ex or something?
Sounds about right.
- So, what's the plan now?
- Well, stick close to Carly...
and see what happens,
and pray she doesn't see me.
Why don't I meet you
and keep you company?
Davis, you don't have to do that.
No, I want to, because....
Tru, you're not alone.
- Thanks.
- I'll see you.
You okay?
- Do I look like a guy who's okay?
- You look like a guy who's still got his car.
Oh, my God.
What?
- He was gonna kill you, man.
- But he didn't.
Look, I am all about standing up
for what's yours.
But that was....
What, you got some kind of death wish?
Harrison, death isn't something
you have to wish for. It's coming anyway.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
- Can I make a confession?
- Sure.
I lied to you...
before, when I said that an old friend
of mine had passed away.
I was at a funeral,
but I didn't know the person who died.
Did you go to the wrong church, what?
No. Just something I like to do.
- Go to strangers' funerals?
- Yeah.
- For what, kicks?
- No.
For clarity.
Right. Jeez.
I go to remind myself
that death is inevitable.
Death is part of life.
And as soon as you understand that,
you're free.
You can do anything you want.
So, is that what you meant earlier,
when you were you were talking about...
playing it safe with Lindsay?
Lindsay?
Look, I'm sure Lindsay's a great girl.
But the problem with great girls is,
they want great lives.
They want a house with
a white picket fence and 2. 5 kids...
playing in the yard.
I don't know you that well...
but you strike me as a guy
who wants more than that.
Who needs more than that.
More freedom. More fun.
More life.
Whoa, there's more here
than what I asked for.
Consider it a severance package.
That's not how our arrangement works.
You see, I ask you for money,
you get it to me...
whether it's today, tomorrow,
or a year from now.
I've honored that arrangement
for eight years.
I think that's long enough.
Not for me. I mean, I appreciate the bonus.
But you will be hearing from me again.
Count on it.
Why didn't you tell me
about your arrangement?
- And you are?
- Someone who cares about Carly.
She said you were an old friend...
but you look more
like an extortionist to me.
Actually, I'm a reporter for the Sun- Times.
What you just saw was an interview
for a story, nothing more.
She paid you off to keep quiet
about something...
- that happened eight years ago.
- I can neither confirm nor deny.
Look, what was it, Peter?
What happened back then?
Her mom told me the only time
she ever took off was eight years ago.
Your sister's adorabIe.
She Iooks just Iike you.
It's lsabelle.
She's not Carly's sister.
She's her daughter.
Whatever it is you're planning tonight,
you can forget it.
Because if you hurt Carly,
I'm going to the police.
Are you kidding?
Carly's little secret
helped pay for my summer home.
The last thing I'd ever do is hurt her.
Are we done here?
Carly's younger sister
is really her daughter?
What a scandaI.
You don't think the reporter's the kiIIer?
- No, Carly's worth too much to him alive.
- If not him, then who?
I'm back at CarIy's
trying to figure that out.
I can't believe you did that!
Look at it!
According to your spreadsheet,
there's a probability...
that the killer's someone
close to the victim?
Right.
Who's closer to Carly than Anna?
Just leave me alone.
Hey, what's up?
You were supposed to be here
two hours ago.
- Where the hell have you been?
- I lost track of time. No biggie.
Actually, no, it is a biggie.
I told you that this was important to me.
Well, I'm here now.
- So, where's the big sis?
- She left.
Her loss, right?
Why are you acting like this?
I don't know.
Why are you acting so clingy?
What?
- Exactly what Jack was talking about.
- Jack?
What does he have to do with us, huh?
You know, sometimes I'm gonna be late.
Sometimes I might not show up at all.
That's just something
you're gonna have to deal with.
No, I won't.
Because if you're feeling tied down...
then by all means,
consider yourself untied.
Whatever.
We're through.
Anna?
Tru, what are you doing here?
Carly had a few more questions
about the morgue, asked me to stop by.
- Is everything okay with you two?
- Honestly? No.
Why, what happened?
I asked Carly if I could borrow her car
to run some errands...
while she's at her mom's. She says fine.
I get in a fender- bender while I'm out,
and she throws a fit.
You were in an accident?
I was pulling out of a spot when
this other car just crunched the door...
and left a nasty red paint scrape.
But so what? It's just a rental.
Sorry.
Hello?
Good. You made it.
- Anna was in an accident in Carly's car.
- What?
A red car crashed
into the driver's side door.
If the damage was before
she drove to the bridge....
Maybe she wasn't forced off the road.
- Maybe she drove off the bridge herself.
- Suicide? No way.
The police said that Carly called 91 1
saying someone was following her.
Why would she do that
if she was planning suicide?
- Someone killed her, I know it.
- But who and why?
Carly.
But that can't be right.
It doesn't make any sense.
Fine. Yeah, I'll call you back
after I talk to her. Bye.
- Is everything okay?
- That was Carly's agent.
And according to him,
there is no morgue movie.
What?
The movie about the morgue attendant
doesn't exist.
Her next project's
supposed to be a romantic comedy.
If there's no movie,
why spend the day with me and Tru?
I was just wondering the same thing.
Hello?
Carly lied to us.
There never even was a morgue movie.
- What?
- It doesn't exist. She made it up.
Why would she come to the morgue?
Why would she ask us all those questions?
What if you get to a crime scene and
it looked like a murder had taken place...
but the body was gone?
Davis, this may sound crazy, but I think
she's trying to fake her own death.
- What did you say?
- Both days she asked what happens...
if I got to a crime scene
and there was no body.
She needs to be sure the missing person
would still be declared legally dead.
Why?
Because that was her pIan.
Fake her own death and disappear.
That's why she spent the day with us.
She wanted to get the details right,
so no one would catch on.
She had everything.
Why would she do something like that?
Think about what the last eight
years have been like for her.
Knowing her secret
couId come out at any time.
She must have had enough. Probably
thought this was the only way out.
If you're right, then Carly wasn't
forced off the bridge by another car.
- And that caII to 91 1....
- Also fake.
There's just one problem.
Carly didn't fake her death yesterday.
She actually died, otherwise the day
wouldn't have restarted.
Something must have gone wrong.
Something she didn't plan for.
Well, whatever that something is,
you have to get there before it happens.
Oh, my God.
I need help! You have to come
now! Someone's following me!
I can't get away! Please hurry!
What?
Carly, listen to me.
What are you even doing here?
I know what you're planning,
and it isn't gonna work.
It will, as long as you don't tell anyone.
- No, that's not what I meant.
- Please, just leave me alone.
Carly, I....
Watch out!
The SUV hit you yesterday.
That's how you got in the water.
That's how you died.
Died? What are you talking about?
I know why you did it, Carly.
I know about lsabelle...
- that she's your daughter.
- How?
I figured it out.
I thought that if word got out,
my career would be over.
So, you covered it up for eight years?
You don't know what it's like, Tru...
to have a secret
people are trying to expose.
Actually, I do.
Because I have a secret, too, you know.
There have been times
where I wanted to run away...
pretend it wasn't a part of me.
But I don't,
because there's someone's life at stake.
- Whose?
- Tonight it was yours.
Someday, someone
would have exposed us, I know that.
It's no way to live,
waking up each morning...
wondering if today's the day
the story finally comes out.
That's why I finally told lsabelle
the truth a few months ago.
That was the hardest thing
I ever had to do.
It took her some time,
but she's okay with it now.
She wants us to be together,
start a new life.
By faking your death?
Look, I'm leaving the country tonight,
and I'm taking lsabelle with me.
I didn't want to go to this extreme, Tru.
I tried to buy my way out today.
Pay off the one person
who knew the truth about lsabelle.
But he wasn't about to let the story die.
So I had to go to my backup plan.
If she's okay with you being her mother...
then why go to all this trouble?
Why not just come clean?
You think the tabloids
would ever leave her alone?
Ever let her have a life?
I'm sorry if you can't get away
from your secret, Tru.
But please, I need to get away from mine.
I thought you had that thing
with Lindsay and her sister.
I did, yeah. It didn't go exactly as planned.
She ended it.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I should've seen it coming, you know?
She gives me chance after chance,
and, you know, I screw up.
That's what I do. I screw up.
I know it must be hard,
losing a girl like Lindsay, but...
maybe it's for the best, you know?
I mean, all these chances
you keep talking about...
did it ever occur to you
that maybe they were chances for her?
Chances for her to change you?
Real friends don't do that, man.
Friends accept you for who you are...
appreciate you for who you are.
Yeah, I guess, you know?
No, don't guess, Harrison.
Know.
Now, I know I haven't known you
for very long, but I'm your friend, man.
No matter what.
- Duty calls. I'll see you soon, yeah?
- Thanks, man.
- Are you sure about this?
- Don't have to be.
I can't say it's my choice,
but it's Carly's life.
She can do what she wants.
Well, there's a lot of ways
to help people, I guess.
Some people need help living, some dying,
some a little bit of both.
I think I finally understand now.
She did it to protect her daughter.
Well, here's hoping
that Carly pulls it off.
Actually, I wasn't talking about her.
I was talking about my mother.
I don't get it.
Why would they call
and bring us all the way down here...
if there's no body to pick up?
Must've jumped the gun
when they found the car.
- Probably figured the body was still in it.
- The currents must have washed it away.
We may never find it.
I'll see you two back at the office.
It's too bad.
Your first pickup and no body.
Go figure.
Poor Carly Anders.
She had a lot to live for.
It's funny how life works, huh?
One day you're here,
the next day you're not.
Well, wherever she is tonight...
I'm sure it's a better place.
Hey, Mom.
I know it's been a while,
but I've been busy.
I guess nobody would understand that
better than you.
But I'll be back soon, Mom.
I promise.