PreviousIy on Tru Calling:
Anyway, I just wanted to say welcome.
I'm Tru.
Jack.
A couple of years ago...
I died.
And then, I came back.
Some would say once you survive
something like that...
that you were brought back for a reason.
I guess we'll see.
How did it go with Jack?
I just can't get a read on him,
for some reason.
One minute he's in your face
and almost obnoxious.
The next, he's charming,
trying to be your best friend.
Leave the key. Step away from the car.
Hang on to your keys, Harrison.
- You sure about that?
- Yeah.
What, you got some kind of death wish?
Death isn't something
you have to wish for. It's coming anyway.
Death is part of life.
Someone stopped us from saving her.
But that doesn't make any sense.
So you ended up ordering takeout?
What did you get?
Moo Shu pork.
Nice choice. With the pancakes?
No, straight from the box. You?
I'm just digging into a rack of lamb
with some garlic mashed potatoes.
Cereal again?
Yeah.
The doctor says I'm fiber- poor.
So what are you doing tonight?
You know, the usual.
Nothing?
Exactly.
Look, me being alone on a Friday night
is one thing...
but you, on the other hand....
With my life,
it's rejuvenating to have a night off.
And besides, I told you. I'm between exes.
What?
It's okay to say that you miss someone.
Luc? Why would you say that I miss Luc?
I didn't say Luc. You said Luc.
Yeah, well--
The way I see it is,
just because we're aIone...
doesn't mean that we're IoneIy.
So by that reasoning, you'd argue
that my neighbor across the way?
She looks like
she's having the time of her life.
She's probabIy miserabIe.
Gotta tell you, Davis,
it sure seems like she's having fun to me.
Trust me.
Nothing is ever exactIy what it seems.
Listen, I've got to go.
The Outer Limits marathon
is about to start.
I'll let you go.
Tru, for what it's worth...
I happen to think that you have
a pretty exciting life, you know?
Time travel...
saving Iives, pretty cooI boss.
Yeah. Good night, Davis.
Good night, Tru.
Leave me a message, I'II caII you back.
Consider this a warning.
You can make all the trouble you want...
but it's only a matter of time
before I find you.
And when I do, let's just say
there won't be a second warning.
Help me.
Delivery!
Coming.
4B, not 3B.
Four, as in upstairs!
Tru? Hey.
I haven't seen you around much.
I thought you moved.
No, I've just been working
some weird hours lately.
But the delivery man
left this at my door by accident.
Cool. Thanks.
Hey, Tru!
Can I get your advice on something?
Sure.
There is this girl.
And she lives nearby...
and she is amazing.
Right.
She's always busy
running around all over town...
but whenever I see her,
she just makes me want to smile.
I see.
Yeah, and, well...
I've been wanting
to ask her out for a while...
but I'm afraid that if she says no,
things will get weird.
You know, on account of us
being neighbors.
Yeah.
I would advise you...
to first make sure that she's ready to date.
And after that, I would take things slow.
Right. Yeah. Slow.
Very slow, you know?
Okay. Makes sense.
- Okay. Thank you.
- No problem.
Just the morgue attendant
I was looking for.
I'll bet you say that to all the girls.
Remember I told you
I was looking for a new apartment?
I found the perfect one- bedroom.
It's close to work, utilities included.
- Congrats.
- I haven't signed the lease yet...
- 'cause I wanted to run it by you first.
- Me, why?
The thing is, it's in the building
across the street from yours...
and I didn't want you feeling crowded
or anything.
So I figured I should check with you.
Are you kidding? You should jump on it.
Places in my neighborhood
are so hard to find.
Morning, gang.
Hey, you got your state license forms.
Davis only called me three times
to remind me.
So you're sure about this?
Positive. It'll be so nice
to have a friend across the street.
- Guess I got a lease to sign.
- Sweet.
See you.
Okay, bye.
Signed and dated. Perfect.
You put the morgue
as your mailing address.
I hope that's okay.
I've been staying at a friend's place
since I moved here.
- Figured this was the best place to get me.
- Not a problem.
As a matter of fact,
you got some mail this morning.
Here it is.
The Schenkman Center.
That's an impressive facility.
Yeah, one of the best in the country.
Were you there long?
I don't remember it being on your résumé.
It was a long time ago.
I didn't think it was relevant.
Did you ever run into a guy
named Tom Forrester?
An old college buddy of mine.
We used to play D&D on the weekends.
We called him Wizard.
Forrester. Yeah, sure. Big fella.
Hell of a guy.
Yeah.
Good old Wizard. I wonder what he's....
I should give him a call.
So the meet's at noon.
High noon.
Don't be so dramatic.
It's the first time me and Lindsay
are seeing each other since the breakup.
We're exchanging stuff.
How is that not dramatic?
Look, I want you both to be happy.
But the truth is,
it's not so bad being single.
Who are you kidding? Not me.
And you've been busted up
since you and Luc split.
That's just not true.
Yeah?
And what's your love life now?
Talking on the phone with Davis all day?
Telling me your upstairs neighbor
has a crush on you?
You're pleasant today.
You're right, I'm sorry.
I'm just nervous.
Anyway, I got to get going.
Whose turn is it?
You ask that like we actually take turns.
Yeah, well, I'll get the next one.
I'll hold my breath.
I don't care. You listen to me,
for the last time, leave me alone.
My neighbor looks like
she's having the time of her life.
Some guys won't take no for an answer.
Well, try saying yes.
Yes, you're a psycho.
Yes, I was right to break up with you.
I'll have to remember that.
You look familiar. Have we met?
No, but I've seen you
around the neighborhood.
Thanks, Chris.
- I'm Tru Davies.
- Chris Barronson.
- Always nice to put a name with a face.
- Absolutely.
- Thanks. Take care.
- Bye.
One Motley Crue concert tee.
One deck of naked lady cards.
Two eggs of Silly Putty.
And 13 assorted comic books.
I've been looking for these.
All right, where's my stuff?
That's it?
Yeah, I turned my place upside down...
and that is all I could find.
That's not even mine.
Yeah, well, uh...
Look, the reason I asked you
to meet me here today...
is because I wanted to
look you in the eye...
into those eyes...
and tell you that I want you back.
What?
Just give me one more chance,
that's all I'm asking for.
No, I've given you, like, 50 chances...
and you blew every single one of them.
You're just too self- absorbed to know it.
And you're the perfect girlfriend, right?
What?
You're so needy. And demanding.
You always order
the most expensive thing on the menu...
when you knew I couldn't afford it.
Right?
Hmm?
Take care of yourself, Harrison.
When will I learn to shut my mouth?
Hi. Tom Forrester, please.
Hi, Wiz?
Hi, it's Gothar, the Elf King.
Yeah. Davis.
Yeah. Listen, turns out
we have a friend in common.
Jack Harper.
Yeah, he used to work with you
at Schenkman.
Mmm- Hmm.
Really?
Hello?
So your brother and I
are officially through.
Can't say I'm surprised, but I'm so sorry.
He made this sad, Iast- ditch
attempt to patch things up.
And when I said no,
he caIIed me needy and demanding.
Can you beIieve that?
Hello, Tru, you there?
Yeah, sorry, I just....
There's this couple across the building
and they're having this nasty fight.
Are they stiII going at it?
I can't tell.
They just turned the lights off.
One guess. Makeup sex.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Anyway, Linds, I got to get to work.
Fine. I'll talk to you later, okay?
Okay.
lncoming.
Hey, Tru?
I thought you said
your neighborhood was getting better?
It is.
I've got a homicide here
that might disagree.
You picked this up near my place?
A building across the street,
if I'm not mistaken.
Victim's name is Chris Barronson,
died from massive head trauma.
Chris Barronson?
Friend of yours?
No, we just met. Today.
- You sure you want to see this?
- Yeah.
That's not Chris Barronson.
- It's what his lD said.
- No, Chris is a girl.
I saw this guy at her place earlier tonight.
He was furious about something.
You know, the cops said something about
thinking the killer was a woman.
Bag this, will you?
Two people, same name, same apartment?
- It's either coincidence...
- Doubtful.
...or our buddy here's been up to no good.
Hi, Tru.
I thought you were home for the night.
- I was, but--
- Couldn't stay away?
Actually, if you have a moment?
I'm kind of in the middle of something.
Can it wait?
It's actually important. We need to talk.
Tru, go ahead. I got this.
- Tru?
- Yeah. Okay, I'm coming.
Please save me.
Delivery!
Wait! Hold on!
You've got the wrong apartment!
Even when you relive days
they still get away.
So your neighbor and victim
have the same name?
He's dead and she's the prime suspect?
Yep. But it wouldn't be any fun
if it were easy.
Okay, well, here's a theory.
Could be identity theft.
He took her identity
and she killed him for it.
ldentity theft is on the rise.
They're either stealing it online...
or taking a picture of your credit card
with a cell phone.
She seemed so normal.
It's hard to imagine her killing anyone.
People can do a lot of things
in self- defense.
Especially when they're pushed
past their limit.
For the last time, leave me alone.
- Maybe you're right.
- Hi, Jack.
Sorry to interrupt. I just wanted
to drop off my state license forms.
Super. Thanks.
Hey.
Hi.
We were just going over
the new intake procedure.
Cool. You mind if I check the mail?
Unfortunately, this is the only address
most people have for me.
- No, go ahead.
- Thanks.
Tru, about the new intake procedure.
Were there any other clues
about the victim's real identity?
He had a pen with a logo on it.
It was a sunburst with a capital"A" inside.
Probably from his work. I'll look into it.
An identity thief with a day job.
All the better to meet new victims.
I got to get going.
Chris will be at the diner any minute.
Okay. I'll call you if anything comes up.
There was something else...
you wanted to tell me
right before the day rewound.
- I did?
- You said it was important.
No clue. Too bad I don't relive days.
But look on the bright side.
If you don't change
too many things today...
then we'll have
the same conversation tonight.
Here's hoping.
Yeah. A redo day.
I get it. No time for breakfast.
But considering you're 24 hours
ahead of me...
what happened with Lindsay yesterday?
Do you want my advice?
Save the sit- down for another day.
Another week even.
Man. It was that bad?
Put it this way: Yeah.
All right. Thanks for the heads up.
Too bad you're blowing off breakfast
'cause I would've picked up the tab today.
It must be nice living in your world, Harry.
Jack, is Tru around?
- You just missed her, man.
- Damn.
I needed to ask her something.
There's kind of a time factor.
She should be on her cell.
No, this is one of those things
that's best to do in person.
Make sure she means what she says.
You mean women don't always say
what they actually mean?
Not the ones I fall for.
See you, man.
Yeah.
You're finished. The fun is over.
For the last time, leave me alone.
Coffee, please.
Some guys,
they just can't take no for an answer.
- Ex- boyfriend?
- It's sort of a long story.
Thanks, Chris.
You know, you look familiar.
You don't live on York by any chance?
Yeah, I do.
- Same here. I'm Tru Davies.
- Chris Barronson.
It's always nice to put a name with a face.
Chris Barronson.
Yeah. Have you heard of me?
Sort of. There was this guy
outside your building this morning...
asking all these questions about you.
He seemed pretty belligerent.
About 6', dark brown hair?
Same guy who just can't take no
for an answer?
Only he's not an ex.
Well, it's nothing I should get into.
If you're heading home,
I could walk with you.
You know, in case he's still around.
- Okay.
It was six months ago...
when I found out he'd stolen my identity.
I was applying for a loan,
and the bank ran a credit check.
They found 10 different credit cards
in my name.
He'd used them to run up
nearly $60, 000 in charges.
And now he's threatening you?
- Because I went to the police.
- No arrest?
lD theft's tricky to prosecute.
You need absolute proof,
which I don't have.
But it's getting worse because now I feel
like someone's been watching me.
That's creepy.
Any idea how this all started?
No, but there's a million ways.
If you don't have a shredder, a firewall...
a digitally scrambled phone...
you may as well have a sign up saying:
Ruin my life.
Anyway, thanks for the company.
And do me a favor,
if you see that guy again...
just say I moved or something.
No problem.
Because if I run into him,
there's no telling what might happen.
- Jack?
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
Moving in.
You're kidding?
No. I saw the"For Rent" sign
and snapped it up.
Lucky for me.
The guy who was supposed to take it...
missed the deadline'cause he had to
run it by his girlfriend or something.
The thing is, it's in the building
across the street from yours...
and I didn't want you feeling crowded.
But his loss is my gain.
Third floor, great view. Unbelievable.
So I've heard.
I got to get started with
the packing process. I'll see you later on.
Tru, your friend, who I just met.
She wouldn't happen to be single,
would she?
I'm not sure a new guy
is what she needs right now.
Besides, a word of advice.
Girls don't appreciate
being hit on by their neighbors.
We need to find
some more interesting neighbors.
Maybe you need to find
some less desperate tenants.
Look, she's having guy trouble right now.
A bad breakup?
Not exactly.
All right. Fine. Don't tell me.
I'll find out on my own soon enough.
Hey, wait.
The truth is, there's this guy
that's been harassing her...
and the last thing she needs is--
- Two.
- Yeah.
Enough said.
Okay.
You know, Tru...
if that other guy really is a problem,
I wouldn't mind keeping an eye on her.
I know you think I'm heartless...
but I have been known to show an interest
in people other than myself.
Thanks, but I've got it under control.
I'd expect no less.
Hello.
Hi, it's me.
I found your logo and your identity thief.
Really?
It's a company called Advantix.
They sell medical equipment.
And there is a salesman there
by the name of Chris Barronson.
Did you get an address?
Don't need to. He's coming to the morgue
in 20 minutes to make a presentation.
You made an appointment with the guy?
I told him we weren't happy
with our current distributor.
You're always chasing the bad guy.
Why not make them come to you for once?
Nice, D. I'll see you in 20.
Okay.
This is my colleague, Tru.
This is Chris Barronson.
Please save me.
This is my first sales call to a morgue.
Most of our equipment's designed
to keep the patient out of a place like this.
Everyone passes through sooner or later.
Right.
Anyway, let me show you guys
what might be useful.
Had this job long, Mr. Barronson?
Eight, nine months. Why?
Does it pay well?
Only if you buy what I sell.
I guess you don't sell that much.
All right. Who are you people?
I think who you are is the bigger question.
What?
We know who the real Chris Barronson is
and you are not her.
And it's only a matter of time
before the police figure that out.
Right. She's good.
I'll give her that.
She pulled a fast one on you guys.
- I don't think you get it.
- No, I do. You don't get it.
All right, the police are on my side.
Except they're too inept
to do anything about it.
Look, I'm the real Chris Barronson, okay?
Here, see?
All right? She stole my identity.
And if you guys know who she is...
you'd better talk some sense into her
before I find her myself.
The DMV has his picture on file
back to the early'90s.
The state police confirm
there were six identity theft reports...
filed by a man named Chris Barronson.
Looks like he's the real deal.
Which means
the girl you met in the diner isn't.
She probably gave me that name...
because it was on the credit card
she was using.
I've spent the day helping a con woman...
while the guy who needs help
wants nothing to do with me.
Helping the criminal may be
the only way to help the victim.
Since the real Chris won't talk to you,
focus on the fake one.
See if you can't keep her
from committing a murder today.
Right.
Hello.
It's Jack.
What's up?
Your friend's on the move.
She left the building?
But don't worry.
I'm keeping an eye on her.
You foIIowed her?
You seemed worried about her.
Thought I was doing you a favor.
Where is she now?
She's headed back
into your neighborhood.
But about an hour ago,
she was in a jewelry store downtown.
Did she buy anything?
Yeah, a necklace.
But she didn't keep it long.
She walked six blocks to a pawnshop...
and sold it for half of what
she just paid for it. Crazy.
She's aImost home now.
She's all yours. I got some errands to run.
Wait, Jack?
You got to let me hang up
so you can miss me.
Cute, but, no.
You followed her.
I can't help wondering why.
She looked like she might be in trouble.
And aside from a little white- collar crime,
she's harmless.
Just be careful.
She's not exactly who she seems.
Who is?
- Jack is following her?
- He was trying to help.
Listen, I want you to take this
before you go.
It's the name and the number
of the cop I talked to, just in case.
Who's Tom Forrester?
He's an old college buddy of mine,
but I haven't talked to him in years. Why?
Yesterday, you had a note to call him.
Remember to find out
what it is you want to tell me.
We have to keep the days
as similar as possible.
Okay. I'll give him a ring.
He's a hell of a guy.
Great Dungeon Master.
God, did I just say that out loud?
Harrison.
Look, about today, I....
Let me guess.
Not gonna work for you.
No, not so much.
You lost all my stuff, didn't you?
No. It's not that. It's just....
It just isn't the best day for it.
Why not?
Well, because, I got to....
It just isn't. Okay?
Fine. Whatever. We'll just do it tomorrow,
same time, same place.
I'll be there. I promise.
Yeah. Bye.
You better be right about this, Tru.
Excuse me, miss?
I didn't want you to forget this.
- Randall?
- Lindsay?
My God.
Feel like telling me who you really are?
I already told you. I'm Chris Barronson.
Look, don't bother. I know you're not.
I know you've been buying jewelry...
with someone else's credit card
and pawning it off for quick cash.
How did you know that?
It doesn't really matter.
It's just time for you to stop.
Just give this guy, Chris, his life back.
I will. Someday.
Someday isn't soon enough.
Trust me on this.
I don't trust anyone.
That's why I'm so good at what I do.
Stay out of it, Tru.
You're in over your head.
Hey, Tru. What a nice surprise.
How's it going?
Good, thanks.
I got a package for you delivered to me
inadvertently this morning.
Do you want to come up and....
There's this girl.
Right.
I've been wanting to ask her out.
You know what? I'll just drop it off later.
I'll save you the time, okay?
I'd be happy to come by.
I'd love to see your place.
- I'm actually just in a hurry, so....
- Okay.
Can I ask you one question?
Sorry, I'm in the middle of something.
But I'll catch up with you later, okay?
What is she doing now?
Looks like she's packing.
That's good.
Maybe you spooked her enough...
so she'II be gone by the time
the reaI Chris Barronson shows up.
Maybe, but we can't count on it.
- I talked to Tom Forrester, by the way.
- And?
He told me about his wife and his kids...
and his research
after leaving the Schenkman Center.
But it's certainly nothing
I need to discuss with you.
It was worth a shot.
You don't think
that the important thing...
has anything to do with the kidney stone
I passed last week, do you?
Okay, probably not. I'll keep looking.
I know you think you can handle this,
but you're the one in over her head.
It'II onIy get worse.
Running won't soIve anything.
Let me help you
or I'll tell the police where to find you.
It's your choice.
It was just so easy, you know?
Like free money.
And at first, I only did it to get by.
But now, it's....
God, you got to believe me.
I had no idea it would go this far.
Okay. But it has.
And now we have to do
something about it.
I'm scared.
The messages
this guy's been leaving for me.
What if I paid him back?
Do you think he would still
turn me in to the police?
You can pay him back?
Yeah, I could give him cash.
Really? You have that much money?
I told you, I was good.
If only that were something to be proud of.
You. You turned my life upside down.
She wants to make amends.
That's why I called.
Sure, now that I know where to find her.
- I'm so sorry.
- You're sorry?
- No, I really am.
- Sorry doesn't cover it.
Here. Maybe this will.
It's the least I can do
with you giving me a second chance.
I almost forgot. Here.
The credit card I took out
in your name.
If I ever hear from you again,
or if I see you--
You won't. I promise.
Fine.
I have a phone call to make.
And you?
You should be gone when I get back.
Thanks, Tru.
I know you probably don't care...
but my real name is Cathy.
It's nice to meet you, Cathy.
Here, let me get this.
No, I got it.
This one's on me.
Thank you again for everything.
Hey.
You caught me using a city vehicle
for personal business.
What vehicle?
I want to thank you
for helping me out today.
It's nothing
you wouldn't have done for me. Thanks.
Still, I mean you took it upon yourself
to look out for someone...
I told you was in trouble,
no questions asked.
Should I have asked some?
I can't help thinking most people would.
Whatever's going on
between you and your friend...
it's none of my business.
- It's never stopped you before.
- All right, fine.
Tell me.
And if I don't?
I'll ply you with alcohol
and pry it out of you.
Right.
Or you'll owe me one.
Lock up the van for me, will you?
- Keys?
- They must be inside.
- I talked to Tom Forrester.
- And?
He told me about his research
after leaving the Schenkman Center.
Here you go.
I guess you can lock up yourself.
Hey.
Could I get a roast beef sandwich to go?
Sure thing.
- Nothing smaller?
- No, not tonight.
I'm sorry, but this bill's a fake.
You got to be kidding me.
You said your friend Tom
worked at the Schenkman Center, right?
Did you mention Jack
when you spoke to him?
No, why would I?
Jack had a letter
from the Schenkman Center in his coat.
I bet you found it first yesterday.
Why don't I give Tom another call?
Yeah, just let me know
what he says, okay?
Here we go again.
Lock yourself out?
Yeah, it happens to me
at least once a week.
Here, I'm sorry. I'm the new tenant.
I appreciate it.
You bet.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Matt?
Now I feel like someone's
been watching me.
There is this girl.
And she lives nearby.
Chris.
What is he doing?
Matt?
Come on.
HeIIo?
Jack, it's Tru! I need to get in.
Hey, Tru. What are you doing
on this side of the street?
Please, Jack, I need to
get into Cathy's apartment right away.
Cathy? Who's Cathy?
Chris. Chris is Cathy.
The girl that you followed.
- Please, Jack, hurry!
- Okay.
Let me just try and figure this thing out.
It's trickier than I thought.
Did that do it?
Thanks. Excuse me.
Tru, did that do it?
Tru?
I'm telling you, stay away from her!
She's a nice girl!
Put it down, Matt.
He broke into her apartment!
He wants to hurt her!
I know you want to protect her,
but you don't know anything about her!
Yes, I do! I watched her every single day
since she moved in.
I know her better than anyone.
No, she's not who you think.
Look, she's a thief.
She stole this man's identity.
No. She can't be. She's perfect!
She would never do that!
It's okay, Matt.
You're not the only one that she's fooled.
But I'm telling you the truth.
She's stolen thousands of dollars.
She's ruined people's lives.
She's a thief?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Why did you come here?
I thought that we had an agreement.
Yeah, we did.
Till I found out
that the money she gave me was fake.
Now she's gone, I'm still broke...
and I'm probably
never gonna see her again.
You never know.
Stranger things have happened.
I don't understand what's taking so long.
It's been 45 minutes already.
I'm very sorry.
Did my card not go through?
The card number's fine,
but our computer's down.
Just give us another minute,
we'll get you all sorted out, Miss Davies.
Heading out of town, Tru?
You know, it's a good thing
I don't believe every sob story I hear.
Mine, for example?
You almost had me.
But then you absolutely blew it
back there at the diner.
This one's on me.
You pulled out your camera cell phone
the second I put my credit card down.
All I had to do
was call the credit card company...
and report a stolen credit card.
I knew you had the number,
but I was hoping that you wouldn't use it.
Then I got the call.
Miss, there's activity reported
on your credit card at A vaIon Car RentaI.
Thank you.
Is it too late for me to explain?
To me? Yeah.
But I know a couple of guys
who'd be happy to listen.
Really, you had a good day?
It was the best, Tru.
The perfect afternoon
with the perfect guy.
Wait, you were with my brother?
No. Harrison was his usual self.
Called to cancel after I was already there.
But that's how I spotted Randall.
Randall?
I met him a few years ago
when I was studying abroad.
He's actuaIIy in town for a few weeks
and he's a totaI opposite of your brother.
Well, lucky break.
Just when I was starting to think
they didn't make them like this anymore.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Good night, Tru.
Hey, it's Luc.
I couIdn't get to the phone right now.
Leave me a message.
Hey, Luc, it's me, Tru.
I heard through the grapevine...
that you missed out on that apartment
across the street...
and I just wanted to caII
and say that I'm sorry.
I know that we're not together anymore...
but it would've been nice to be neighbors.
Just to know you were close.
I'II taIk to you soon. I just wanted to caII.
Okay, bye.
Luc?
No, Tru. It's me, I'm sorry.
I saw the morgue number and thought
he was working tonight. What's up?
I talked to my friend at Schenkman.
What I had to tell you
is definitely about Jack.
Turns out he was a patient there.
A patient?
But Schenkman's a psychiatric facility.
It seems like he was there voluntarily.
He checked himself in
so he could check himself out.
Well, we knew
something was off with Jack, but--
There's more.
When Jack committed himseIf,
he thought he was going crazy.
But the doctors couldn't diagnosis it.
Going crazy how?
He thought he was reliving days.
Reliving days?
Like me?
Exactly like you.