Then they called me
this frat guy...
and I was like,"No, baby. Pay me."
Yeah, it's a damn good thing, too.
'Cause I was into my boy, Chaz,
for four bills.
You know, I've been thinking
about getting my nipples pierced.
- That's great, Harrison.
- Earth to sis.
Have you been listening to me?
- What's going on?
- Trust me.
You don't want to know.
I do want to know.
I am aII about wanting to know. Tru?
Tru, what are you doing?
What the hell do you think you're doing?
I was just....Didn't you see that car
coming right at you?
All day with the questions
and the sneaking around.
- Are you stalking me?
- Ma'am, I swear, I was just trying to help.
Help me write down
your name and number.
I'm sure my attorney
will want to talk to you.
Obviously you'll believe
what you want...
- but I just helped you more than you know.
- I don't need your help.
I do.
Come in.
What are you....
Help me.
God, what are you doing?
We need to talk.
We're not really gonna have
this conversation again, are we?
I think we have to.
You should've seen yourself the other day.
And the way people were looking at you.
I saved someone's life.
I don't really care what people think.
It's getting out of hand.
And I need a real explanation, okay?
Not this crap about do- over days...
and damsels in distress.
What you're claiming, it's not possible.
It's not.
And now you're putting yourself
in danger...
and risking your life over people
who don't care...
over something that's not even real.
Come on.
Did you see where the guy
who was here went?
- Nope.
- Sorry.
What kind of person skips out
on a bill of $7. 32?
It comes out of my pay.
Look, we've been over this before.
And you know what?
I'm done talking about it.
Obviously nothing I say...
is gonna convince you, so I'm just gonna
have to find a way to show you...
once and for all, this is real.
Come on, don't you people have jobs?
Hi, you're here early.
Actually, I just came by...
to see if you wanna grab a bite to eat,
or maybe just hang out.
Hang out? As in me and you?
Yeah. It's just....
Sometimes I feel
like you're the only one who gets me.
Who understands
what's going on in my life. My brother....
He still doesn't buy it?
No.
He believes boxing's legit
and Tupac's alive...
but he can't seem to wrap his head
around this one. So what do you say?
- Just a half hour?
- Yeah.
Hello?
What?
Oh, my God. I'll be right there.
It's my sister.
Oh, man. The ball!
Get it! Come on!
- Meredith, you all right?
- Yeah, I'll get better.
- My car, not so much.
- Forget about your car. Let me see.
Are we done?
One minute.
- Relax, Mere. Just tell me what happened.
- I had this appointment...
running late because of
all the construction on the highway.
- Then this guy just pulls out of nowhere.
- Is there anything I can do?
- Do you need me to call someone?
- No, it just....
I missed my appointment.
It doesn't matter.
Let me see.
I'm sure your office will understand.
I got to get my stuff out of my car
before they take--
You just finish getting patched up.
I'll take care of it.
Appointments. Right.
Thanks.
Odd part of town for you
to have an appointment.
Didn't you used to come down here
to make a different kind of deal?
Yes. Used to.
I really don't appreciate the implication
that this had anything to do with drugs.
Look, sorry, Mere. It's just....
- Don't be afraid to ask for help.
- I am not afraid to ask for help.
I called you after the accident, didn't I?
Is everything okay with your sister?
Yeah, maybe.
Honestly, I don't know anymore.
My God!
Yeah, I know.
Nicole Simms.
Shot by an unknown assailant.
On her wedding day.
Time of death: between 7:00 and 7:30.
Actually might have made it,
but she bled to death in the chapel.
Ambulance was held up by construction
on the highway.
- Who would do this?
- Don't know.
Maybe it was random, or maybe
somebody didn't want her to get married.
Get started on the standards,
I'll go grab the x- rays. I'll be right back.
Can I help you?
Sorry, that snow
just came out of nowhere.
Snow? Here, let me get you something
to dry off with.
No, it's okay. I just....
My....
I think my....
We were supposed to get married today.
And I think they brought her here.
Yeah.
Could I get a couple of minutes?
Um, I never, uh,
I never got a chance to say goodbye.
For what it's worth,
I know what you're going through.
Sorry for your loss.
Thanks.
Um. Can I, um,
Can I see her?
Yeah.
I'll just be right through here.
Nicole.
Good news.
I finally got the cheesy chomps
that I ordered, so that....
Why aren't you running standards?
I gotta start the autopsy soon...
and the Sheriff's Department
needs the bullet for their investigation.
The victim's fiancé came in.
He just wanted to say goodbye.
Where's he waiting? I'll talk to him.
Actually, he's in Standards with her.
You know that's against the rules.
Yeah, but can't the rules
be broken a little?
- What's the harm in--
- Tru, until a case is closed...
- the dead are our responsibility.
- Davis, there's also a live person in there.
You take great care of the dead.
What about the living?
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
- All right, I can explain.
- Tru, call security, please.
No, you stay. You stay where you are.
- Oh, my God.
- Listen.
Whatever it is you want,
you don't have to hurt anybody to get it.
- You don't understand.
- Then help me understand.
You're in a lot of pain right now,
but we can deal with it.
Just relax. Davis, don't.
Don't.
No! Davis!
My God! Talk to me! Davis!
You are not leaving me, you understand?
Get up.
Get up, now!
- You'd better pray he doesn't die.
- I did not want to shoot.
Look, you have to help me, now!
I will never do anything to help you.
That's too bad.
Help me.
We just saw each other yesterday.
Come on, we need to talk.
Tru.
Are you all right?
I don't know yet.
I know you don't believe
half the things I tell you...
but let's just say
yesterday was a real bad day.
Yeah. Tell me something I don't know.
Watching your sister dive tackle
a total stranger.
Not your yesterday. My yesterday.
Look, this is getting out of hand.
And I want a real explanation.
Not this crap about do- over days...
and damsels in distress.
Tru?
- And what is this?
- Your to- do list.
"Diner, 1 1:20. Bring $7. 32."
What the hell is this?
If something were to happen to me,
I need to know that you understood why.
The only way for you to finally accept
what I do, is for you to do it yourself.
- What do I get out of this?
- Be where I tell you, when I tell you...
and by the end of the day,
you'll have your answer.
So I'm guessing this is one of those days.
Since it's not your shift and you're here.
It's a do- over day.
What have we got?
What?
- It's good to see you, Davis.
- It's nice to see you, too.
- I'm just really glad you're here.
- Okay.
You do realize I work here, don't you?
Who's Nicole Simms?
She's getting married today. Or trying to.
Gets shot in the chest and bleeds out...
- before the ambulance can get to her.
- Now you find out who did it?
That's the thing. I think I know this time.
It's her fiancé.
- How do you know that?
- I saw him. He came here.
- What, to the morgue? What for?
- He was tampering with the body.
He must have been
trying to conceal evidence.
You know,
nab the bullet before the cops could.
So, he was here when she asked for help?
Was I here?
- Of course I was here, I'm always here.
- You were here.
What aren't you telling me?
- Davis, I'm sorry, I really got to....
- Right.
Somebody out there needs to be saved.
Something like that.
What do you want me to say?
"Yes" will work.
I'd be willing to take a"fine."
You seriously thought
I would just give you my car?
In some remote cultures,
siblings are known to help one another.
What if you got in an accident?
My insurance premium would increase.
I'll have it back by tonight,
in one piece, I promise.
Look, I'd love to help you out,
I really would.
But I have an appointment across town
with a client this afternoon.
I need my car.
Didn't you used to come down here
to make a different kind of deal?
This appointment wouldn't be
for something else besides work, right?
Tru, look, no more games today, okay?
I have a staff meeting.
How about this?
You can have the car tomorrow.
Call me and we'll set it up.
Tomorrow's too late.
For both of us.
Yes, you did.
You said you wanted him at your table.
Hold on a minute. Hi.
Hi. I'm looking for Nicole.
- And if you found her, you would be?
- Tru Davies. Old friends.
Ma? I'm gonna call you back.
No, I need--
I have a question about tonight.
Are you here for the wedding, too?
I hope so, I'm in it.
- A groomsman?
- Actually, I'm the groom.
Wait, you're marrying
Nicole Simms tonight?
Yeah, that's the plan.
We were supposed to get married today.
Right, of course.
So you're here for the wedding?
I don't remember your name
from the guest list.
Yeah, I'm not on it.
I'm just here from out of town.
I wanted to wish her luck.
Nicole and the troops are all downtown
at some nail shop.
Do you know which one?
It might be fun to surprise her.
It's on Fifth.
- Hands On.
- Great.
Could you just tell her that I miss her?
This whole tradition of me
not seeing her all day....
Just tell her it's killing me, okay?
Yeah. Hello?
- She can't sing.
- I can't stop her.
- She's gonna be my mother- in- law.
- No, she can't sing.
She might get up there
and open her mouth...
but what comes out is gonna be like
something from WiId Kingdom.
Another decision.
God, I'm gonna explode.
Go with sheer. French tips are played out.
Thank you. That may have seemed
like nothing, but I'm grateful.
- Big day?
- Long day. It's exciting, but exhausting.
- I just can't wait to get my life back.
- Good luck with that.
I've got three words for you.
Thank- you notes.
I should've eloped.
Maybe someone didn't want her
to get married.
A friend once said
the hardest part about getting married...
is telling the guy she dated in college.
The guy I dated in college beat me to it.
He got married last year.
You mean there's not one boy out there
in a particularly bad mood today?
Justin? Justin Burke?
Stop it. He hasn't thought twice about me.
Only a guy still hooked...
would buy you something
off your Perry and White registry...
when he's not even
invited to the wedding.
Okay. Point taken.
Luckily, after tonight,
I'll only have one guy to worry about.
"The diner, 1 1:20. Bring $7. 32."
Come on.
What kind of person skips out
on a bill for $7. 32?
It comes out of my pay.
- Did she put you up to this?
- Excuse me?
My sister.
Tell her she's gonna have to do
better than that, okay?
Nice work, though.
Keep the change.
Hi. I'm hoping you can help me out.
My boss had me purchase a wedding gift,
and I think I blew it.
I gave you guys the wrong return address.
If something goes wrong, it's my ass.
Would it be too much to ask
for you to check the files?
Yeah, thanks. His name's Justin Burke.
Where the hell are....
Steve, have you seen my keys?
No, I haven't.
Tru, tell me you didn't.
Just call me a cab!
If it's important, I'm out back!
Sorry to bother you.
It's fine.
This stuff gets everywhere.
Can I help you?
I was hoping I could help you.
I'm a new neighbor...
and I actually have the same
house number as you a few blocks over.
Anyway, a couple of days ago,
I got a package with a"Return to Sender."
I think it was supposed to come here
to a Justin Burke.
That's my boyfriend. This is his place.
I just try to make it livable.
Is he around or....
He's still at work...
but he usually comes home for lunch.
Actually, he should be home any minute.
Do you mind me asking you
where the package is from?
- I think it was Perry and White.
- That figures.
His ex- girlfriend's getting married.
Is that weird, or....
It's like you'd expect.
Since he heard about the wedding,
he's been a little bit off.
I'm sure it's nothing.
Speaking of....Right on schedule.
Now you can teII him yourseIf.
Actually, you know what? I'm late.
I really got to....Thanks for your help.
- What was that about?
- A delivery or something.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah. I just....
Do me a favor. When you're done here,
come inside for a minute.
I want to talk about something.
Sure.
So I took off.
I didn't know what else to do.
He lied. He's not the fiancé.
He's a bitter ex. Not to mention a cop.
At least you found the bride.
All you have to do is convince her
to call off the wedding.
That isn't the issue. Stopping the guy is.
I don't know if I can do that.
- You've done it before.
- I've failed before. I can't fail this time.
Tru, what is going on?
What happened yesterday?
I told you.
No, you're working harder
at avoiding my questions...
- than saving this girl.
- What do you want me to say, Davis?
The truth!
This guy...
I told you he came here
to cover his tracks.
By trying to extract the bullet.
But what I didn't tell you is...
we walked in on him...
and he pulled a gun.
In here?
Oh, my God, what happened?
He shot at me.
But the day rewound before I could....
Look, I'll be fine.
- But you need to get out of here.
- A guy came in here...
and shot at you
and you want me to leave?
What are you not telling me?
He shot you, Davis.
He shot me?
Did I die?
I don't know.
So you're telling me that in a couple
of hours from now, I could be dead.
Davis, we don't have time for this.
The longer you stay here...
the better the chance it'll happen again.
I want you to go to my apartment.
Look, if I can't change what happens,
at least I can rearrange the players.
Just take these, please, and go there.
But what about you?
I have to warn the bride. You know that.
I also know she's the reason
a guy came in here with a gun.
I'll be fine, okay?
I'll meet you back at my place, I promise.
Tru. Thank you.
For what?
For telling me the truth.
Those are Gerber daisies.
I didn't order Gerber daisies.
Are you telling me
it's too late to change them?
She's in the hall and can't decide
between Some Enchanted Evening...
or Time of My Life. She wants to sing you
the first verse of each.
That's just perfect.
- How could this day get any worse?
- Nicole, hi.
- Do you have a minute?
- No, not really.
Aren't you the girl from--
The nail place, yeah.
I wasn't completely honest.
Look, I know your ex, Justin.
Okay.
I know how he still feels about you,
and what he's willing to do...
- to keep this wedding from happening.
- What is she talking about?
I have no idea.
Look, you say you know Justin?
So do I.
And I know he would never do anything...
to hurt me like that. And I also know
I'm not gonna let some stranger...
come in here and screw up my day.
I have family for that.
Can you find your own way out
or do you need a hand?
I got it.
If you want her to make it to the"I do's"...
you'd better keep Justin away from her.
Someone's gonna need
my help. Yeah.
Hi. You probably
need some help, don't you?
- No.
- Come on. Give me your arm...
- and let's get this over with.
- Don't touch me!
What about this, lady?
Oh, man.
The baII!
Come on!
Hey.
You need this?
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Where have you been?
I've been waiting for hours...
- and this guy--
- Davis, I'm fine. Look at me, one piece.
- How about you?
- I'm okay.
When you say you're okay....
I'm lying.
So you really don't know
what happened after he shot me, if I....
No. That's just it. It hasn't happened yet.
So we're gonna make sure
it doesn't happen again.
I've warned the necessary parties,
now all I have to do...
is get to Justin
before he gets to the chapel.
- Any idea how?
- That's the thing.
He's a cop. Not to mention armed.
So, short of knocking him out
and stashing him in a locked closet...
- I'm running low on ideas.
- I may have one.
Scientific knowledge
always bests physical strength.
How do you think
I got through high school?
- This helps me how?
- Knock him out, yes.
But pharmaceutically.
You want him incapacitated...
- two words: zinc sulfate.
- Zinc sulfate.
That's just gonna make him puke.
For hours. Good idea.
Not that I'm crazy about you
being alone with him in a room...
- but it will buy you some time. If he's--
- Busy, he can't shoot Nicole or you.
Where do I find some?
I have a friend at County
who may not mind--
Give me a name and a number.
I'll go get the pills.
And listen.
This isn't just about me and Nicole.
- He shot three people yesterday, so Tru--
- Don't worry. I will.
I hear you're the man to see.
Well, that depends.
Gonna make it worth my while?
What are you....Are you ripping me off?
I'm talking to you!
Stupid girl. You want something from me?
I want what I paid for.
You'll get it when you get it.
Dispatch called.
Said Nicole was looking for you.
She wants to meet you here
before the wedding.
- Nicole?
- Something you want to tell me?
Justin.
Nicole's just running late,
so she sent me to give you a heads up.
- Who are you?
- Just a bridesmaid fulfilling her duty.
You look familiar.
I am one of Nicole's friends,
and you did date Nicole.
The chances are our paths have crossed.
Yeah. Right. Probably, I guess.
I'm still a little thrown by her call.
Do you know why she wanted to see me?
Honestly, I think she's a little worried
that you're still bent...
about the whole breakup,
and that you might do something about it.
- Tonight.
- Are you serious?
The only thing I'd do is say thanks.
To hear she was marrying...
turned out to be a serious wake- up call.
- What do you mean?
- If she's willing to stop playing games...
and commit, she must really love this guy.
I just hope I'll feel that strong someday.
It's getting warm. Do you mind?
Sure.
You're not wearing your gun.
But you're a cop, right?
I'm a cop, off duty.
I only carry it when I'm on the job.
You say you never carry your gun
when you're not working?
No. Some guys do, but not me.
When I'm off duty, I'm off duty.
- It wasn't you.
- What?
You know what? I've got to go. God.
That's okay.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
Are you sure that Nicole's gonna come?
Yeah. And I'm sure
she would want you to wait right here.
When I left Justin, it was 6:40.
He was Iooking forward to seeing NicoIe,
and he didn't have his gun.
He couldn't have been the one
that shot her--
Someone else must've pulled the trigger.
I don't know who.
Then why does he go to the morgue
to cover it up?
I don't know. But there won't be
anything to cover up if I can find Nicole--
- Tru?
- My God, Nicole!
Somebody help!
God!
What happened?
I don't know. I just found her like this.
What are you doing here?
Look, I'm here to help.
Alive. Barely.
- Call 91 1.
- Did you see anyone come in here?
No, it's early.
Most of the guests aren't even here yet.
- My God! Nicole!
- The ambulance will be here any minute.
The ambulance was held up
by construction.
She bled to death in the chapel.
The ambulance isn't gonna
make it in time. We need to--
No! You're not touching her!
Nobody moves her!
What about the police?
Hasn't anybody called the police?
- Give me a phone.
- Listen to me!
There's construction on the highway.
The EMTs will never make it.
If we don't get her to a doctor,
neither will Nicole.
Please, we can't afford to wait.
Help me get her to a car.
But the cars are all blocked
by the catering trucks.
- Not mine.
- What about her parents?
If the family has a problem,
they can find me at the County Hospital.
I'll be saving their daughter.
Hold on! You're gonna make it.
Come on. Nicole?
Come on!
HeIIo?
I couIdn't stop it.
Someone shot Nicole, and she looks bad.
- Don't know if she'll make it.
- How close are you to the hospital?
Not close enough! Wait, who's on duty
at the morgue right now?
- I don't think that's--
- Someone has to know what to do.
I'm only two blocks away.
It might be her only chance.
- Okay, I'll meet you there.
- No!
I spent the whole day keeping you safe.
You won't go back...
- to where you got shot!
- That was yesterday.
Today is yesterday! Davis!
Bye, Tru.
Davis! Damn it!
Help! Gardez! Anyone?
- I told you not to come here!
- You say how much you appreciate...
having someone help you.
Let me help you.
If not, let me at least help her.
- I locked all the doors.
- We've got to do this quick...
- and get out of here.
- What's this?
- Dried blood.
- I don't think so.
I can't tell what, though.
Lily pollen.
- What, from her bouquet?
- No. Those were Gerber daisies.
Then how did it get on her dress?
This stuff gets everywhere.
Can I help you?
Justin left his gun at home.
The only other person...
who would have had access to it
is his girlfriend.
I had the right motive,
just the wrong person.
I find it so interesting...
that you broke up with me
on the day Nicole gets married.
This is about you and me.
It doesn't have anything to do with her.
Well, not anymore.
What are you doing with that?
I shot her.
Nicole?
Amazing how she's always
the first woman on your mind.
- Why would you do that?
- It was so easy for you...
just to end things.
Aly, you didn't have to--
Kill her?
- I didn't, Justin. You did.
- Oh, my God.
She's at the morgue by now.
But I didn't do it.
It's my word against yours.
It's your gun. Your bullet. Your motive.
The evidence is all there.
Somebody just has to find it.
How we doing?
With us.
Okay. I think we're ready.
Okay.
I'll assist you.
I'm not doing this. You are.
- What? You're the doctor.
- I know. I can't work on live people.
- They freak me out.
- Are you kidding?
Why do you think I work here?
Nobody chooses this job.
It's gonna be fine. I know what to do.
I just can't do it without dry heaving.
You can do this, I know you can.
I'll be right here.
- Actually, I'll be right here.
- Okay, what's first?
You need to isolate the entry wound.
Do you think you can do that?
I think so.
Careful. Given the subatmospheric
pressure in the cavity...
debris might have caused infection.
How's the internal bleeding?
- Pretty bad.
- Okay, you need to seal off any gushers...
and decrease the level of blood loss.
Not that one.
The one next to
the hydrogen needle.
Okay, that worked. Now what?
I want you to get out of here right now.
If I leave, Nicole dies.
Who are you? I thought you said
you were a friend of Nicole's?
I lied.
Look, I came to say goodbye.
You came here for the bullet.
- Is she still alive?
- Look, we both know...
that you didn't shoot her.
Yeah, but can you prove it?
Because the bullet came from my gun!
Everybody knows I still love Nicole...
and there were no witnesses.
Now, I need the evidence.
And the evidence is inside of her.
Davis, don't!
If you move, he'll shoot you.
Justin, there is a witness.
And she's lying here on this table.
She's the onIy one who can testify
that AIyssa shot her, not you.
Look, we can save her, and you.
But you've got to give us the time.
Right now, you've got a choice.
Your life goes one of two ways.
Which is it gonna be?
All right, where do I go from here?
You might have to bag her.
How's her breathing?
It sounds okay.
Good.
Looks like her lungs didn't collapse.
That's a good sign.
How was your day?
Well, I'll be honest. Nice effort.
You know, the waitress
and the little kid with the ball. Very clever.
But I'm sorry. Game over.
'Cause it ain't gonna snow out of nowhere.
Let me see your watch.
- Yeah, that's two minutes fast.
- So?
Look outside.
Unbelievable.
I have...
First I thought you were messing with me
with the card....
But there's no getting around this.
I don't understand. I can't comprehend...
but I do believe you now.
That's all I wanted.
You have no idea what this means to me.
- Thank you.
- No.
Thank you.
Do you know what this does for me?
You're omniscient.
You're like the ultimate bodyguard.
- That's not--
- It's like a free pass.
- If anybody steps to me, you can--
- No, that's not what this is.
Hold on a sec.
Hello? Chaz! What's up?
Yeah, I got your money. I'll be honest.
I don't think I'm gonna make it tonight.
No. Look, I'll call you.
- You owe him money?
- Yeah. But what's the rush?
- I'll get it to him.
- Harrison, you can't just do that.
If you don't pay him....
I won't always be there to help you.
But of course you will, Tru.
You're my sister.
Justin turned himself in,
and they arrested his girlfriend...
- based on what he told the cops.
- And Nicole?
I sent her to County. She's stable.
Her parents just called
and they wanted to thank the doctor.
That's nice.
They meant you.
She wouldn't have made it without you.
And neither would I.
It's kind of funny...
this is the second time
that someone's saved my life.
Really, what happened?
Sorry. Hello?
Hey, Tru. It's me.
Meredith, are you aII right?
Tru.
Help me.
Hold tight, sweetie, I'll be right there.
It's my sister.
It's okay. Go ahead.
It's been a long day, or two.
We'll discuss it another time.
Okay.