[Mellow pop song playing on radio]
[Knocking at door]
[Knocking continues]
LUC: So you finally did it.
Thirty-nine straight days at the morgue,
and you finally took one off.
-l had to see it for myself.
-l was this close to the record.
l thought that we could celebrate
over breakfast.
This is pathetic.
50 people coming here tonight...
and all l have in the way of munchies...
is a bottle of olives
and a box of baking soda.
l don't get this. You moved
into this place six months ago...
and you're throwing
a house warming party tonight?
What can l say? l've been busy.
TRU: So, are you nervous?
LUC: About what?
Tonight. Meeting my friends
for the first time. My brother.
They're going to study my every move
and report back to you.
-Why would that make me nervous?
-You'll be great.
[Phone ringing]
TRU: Hello?
MARK: Tru?
MARK: Hey, it's me. Come on,
it's only been a couple of months...
-don't tell me you've already forgotten?
-Mark.
[Soft instrumental music]
MARK: Look, I know
what happened was my fauIt...
and you have every reason to hate me.
But l just can't stop thinking about you,
Tru, and l want you back.
[Tense instrumental music]
MARK: Hey, are you stiII there?
Yeah, but now really isn't a good time.
Maybe l could come by later?
We could talk, face to face.
See, here's the thing.
What you want really doesn't matter.
Know why?
'Cause you're the one who cheated.
And it was the biggest mistake of my life,
Tru, and l know that now.
Yeah, well, you should've known it then.
Besides, l've met someone new.
And he's great.
Please, Tru, it'll never happen again.
You're right, it won't.
TRU: I got to go, Mark.
[Fast-paced instrumental music]
[Theme music]
Help me.
[Soft instrumental music]
-ls everything okay?
-Yeah. Why?
You looked a little freaked
when you answered the phone.
l thought maybe it was bad news.
Well, the truth is that was my ex.
And he wanted to see me.
l can't say that's the answer
l was expecting, but....
Hey, whatever you need.
You and l have only been out a few times--
l told him no.
[Romantic instrumental music]
Even better.
l'm sorry. lt's weird.
l shouldn't have told you.
No, l'm glad you did.
lf you and l can't be honest
with each other, what hope do we have?
You're probably wondering
why l asked you to meet me here today.
-l meet you here all the time.
-Whatever.
HARRlSON: lt's Lindsay.
Ever since we hooked up,
l can't stop thinking about her.
-You're kidding me, right?
-Crazy as it sounds, l'm not.
You know me. l can't stand Lindsay.
l never could.
And, yet, she just keeps
popping into my head.
lt's confusing the hell out of me.
And you're telling me this now because....
You're meeting her
to shop for your party, right?
l thought maybe you could feel her out.
See where her head's at. You know?
Vis-á-vis yours truly.
[Grunts hesitantly]
Come on. Help a brother out.
Look, all l'm looking for
is a simple yes or no.
LlNDSAY: Maybe.
TRU: Maybe you're interested
in my brother?
He's cute, don't get me wrong.
He went all weird after we made out,
like he was embarrassed or something.
-Typical guy stuff.
-He was probably just nervous.
Still, post-hookup, you give a girl a call.
You know, maybe some flowers.
Make the girl feel special.
We don't need that.
Got to cut the limes with something.
Besides, it's on sale.
Okay.
Oh, my God, Pez. l forgot Pez.
You and your candy.
l just love those little dispensers.
They're so kitschy.
[Phone ringing]
Hello, Davis.
For the last time, yes.
But what if a dead body comes in
and asks for help? What do l do?
First, they don't talk to you,
they talk to me.
Okay, but--
Also, they don't ask for help
every night. lt's not how it works.
Just come in for five minutes.
lf no one asks for help,
then you can go home.
TRU: Did you hear what I said?
l worked eight days this week, literally.
-But what l'm trying to say is that--
-Davis, l need a break.
Okay. So l'll see you tomorrow?
l'll see you then. Bye.
MARK: Chips, dips, a whole lot of beer.
Looks like somebody's having a party.
[Tense instrumental music]
What's wrong?
Nothing, l'm just surprised
to see you here, is all.
Real coincidence.
l live three blocks from here,
remember that?
This is my market where l shop.
-l'm not following you or anything.
-Okay.
Since l have you here,
l just wanted to apologize...
because l feel like l came on strongly
this morning. lt was rude.
TRU: That's fine.
MARK: Anyway...
it was nice to see you.
Yeah.
[Tense instrumental music continues]
l still can't believe
you had a stalker moment and l missed it.
lt wasn't a stalker moment.
Mark and l just happened to be
in the same place at the same time.
That's what stalkers do.
They just happen to be in your market...
and then they just happen
to follow you home...
and then they just happen to
chop your head off and seal it in a baggie.
TRU: Linds!
LlNDSAY: l'm just saying.
First the phone call, and now this?
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
HARRlSON: What'd she say?
And teII me everything.
TRU: ActuaIIy, I'm pretty satisfied
with my Iong-distance pIan.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
lt means you should maybe
call back another time.
She's right there, isn't she?
Yes, that's right.
Telemarketer.
Just give me a hint.
Tell me something. Anything.
l think if you want your customer
to change plans...
you should show her
some special consideration.
Special. Like a gift or something?
TRU: Not bad.
HARRlSON: What shouId I get her?
Hey, she's very happy
with the plan she's got now. Thanks.
[Exclaims]
Only way to handle those guys.
[Fast-paced rock music playing on radio]
Hey, Tru. Cool party.
lt's good to see you again.
Thanks!
Who is that?
Oh, my God,
Marty's actually on time for once.
Marty. That's who that was.
Can you believe
this thing came with instructions?
-For a knife?
-Yeah.
-Apparently you can cut through rebar.
-Good to know.
[Exclaims]
[People applauding]
Thank you. Thank you very much.
-Hey, Sam.
-Tru, l'm so sorry about the vase.
Don't be. You know what they say:
''Priceless heirlooms
are made to be broken.''
So, how are you? How's med school?
You're at Hopkins, right?
No. That kind of fell through.
SAM: l missed the final
because of a big family emergency...
and this jerk professor
wouldn't give me a make-up.
Sorry to hear that.
So, now l'm selling shoes with my dad
in his store until l can reapply.
-What about you?
-Tagging toes at the morgue.
Man. And l thought l had it bad.
[Fast-paced rock music
continues playing on radio]
Harrison, it's beautiful.
That's just a little something
from me to you.
Actually, it's from Bill to Sally.
-What?
-Yeah, there's an inscription on the back.
-''To Sally from Bill.''
-That. No, that can be removed.
Where did you get this thing?
A pawn shop?
ls that a problem?
[Upbeat rock music playing on radio]
-Happy house warming.
-Thank you.
Come here one second.
HARRlSON: Whatever happened to,
what is that saying:
''lt's the thought that counts''?
lt counts if it's yours.
This thought here happens to be Bill's.
Hi. You must be Luc. l'm Lindsay.
-Nice to meet you.
-This is my brother, Harrison.
HARRlSON: How's it going?
LUC: A pleasure.
Tru, can you help me
with the punch real quick?
Let me ask you a question, guy to guy.
Wanna buy a watch?
LlNDSAY: Okay, your brother
is so hopeless.
l mean, a pawned watch? How tacky.
Harrison just has his own way
of doing things.
Right. The cheap way.
-Lindsay.
-Okay, sorry. Change of subject.
LlNDSAY: Your new boyfriend is hot.
l just hope he's having a good time.
lf he isn't, so what.
lt's your party, remember?
l've already had a few.
l should probably slow down.
Nights like this do not happen that often,
especially with a job like yours.
LlNDSAY: Cheers.
TRU: Cheers.
[Upbeat rock music
continues playing on radio]
Tru, there's an angry guy at the door.
He says he's your neighbor.
Turn the music down,
or else l'm calling the police.
All you had to do was ask, Brian.
No, l'm not asking, l'm telling.
Turn the music down.
TRU: Fine.
BRlAN: Yeah.
'Cause me and the landlord,
we're like that.
One call from me,
he's gonna take away your parking spot.
l don't have a car.
ln case you get one.
Why didn't you invite
your next-door neighbor?
-Are you kidding me? That guy's a creep.
-All the more reason to invite him.
lf he's helping make the noise,
he can't complain about it, right?
TRU: Well, it's too late now.
Bye. Bye, you guys.
l'll call you, okay?
[Mellow pop music playing on radio]
l need to talk to you.
l know that l shouldn't be here,
it's inappropriate...
but l cannot stay away, and l am sorry.
You need to go. Now, Mark.
-l need you to talk to me.
-We're through talking.
All l'm asking for
is five minutes of your time.
[Tense instrumental music]
Five minutes, Tru, and then l will go.
Fine. But not here.
Okay. Then meet me upstairs on the roof.
Promise me.
Just wait for me there.
Hey, what was that about?
That was the guy
who called me this morning.
Your ex?
He just kind of showed up.
He wants to talk to me.
So talk to him.
You're okay with that?
l trust you.
Thanks.
[Tense instrumental music]
Mark?
[Dramatic instrumental music]
What the hell's the matter with you?
The first time l ever kissed you
was on this roof.
-And l thought maybe if--
-Mark.
No. Stay.
Talk to me
about how great we are together.
You need to go home.
Don't come near me again.
[Tense instrumental music]
Great.
[People chattering]
TRU: Drive safe.
Call you a cab, Sam?
No, but if you know of a good place
to throw up, that would be great.
Down the steps, hook a right,
anywhere in the alley's fine.
You rock.
[Soft pop music playing on radio]
-You okay?
-Yeah. Where did everybody go?
Without you here,
no one really felt like partying.
That, and we ran out of booze.
ls everything okay with the party-crasher?
Fine.
You tired?
Lindsay's punch kind of got my head
doing summersaults.
-Go to bed. l'll clean up after you.
-Just leave it till tomorrow.
All right. Let's get you to bed.
Thanks for everything.
l had such a good time tonight.
Me, too.
You want to stay?
l would love to.
But tonight, you need to sleep.
-So l'll see you tomorrow?
-Count on it.
[Romantic instrumental music]
[Car alarm beeping in the distance]
Luc? l thought you said
you were going home.
[Gasps]
[Tense instrumental music]
[Tense instrumental music intensifies]
[Gasping]
[Tense instrumental music]
[Crying]
[Sobbing]
WOMAN: 91 1 emergency.
May I have your name and Iocation?
Tru Davies, 1723 Oracle.
l'm calling to report a murder.
WOMAN: Can you teII me what happened?
l just woke up and he was here.
l don't know how.
MARK: Tru?
[Eerie instrumental music]
WOMAN: Miss, are you stiII there?
WOMAN: Stay on the Iine, pIease.
Tru, l need you.
[Dramatic instrumental music]
[Knocking at door]
[Fast-paced instrumental music]
LUC: So you finally did it.
Thirty-nine straight days at the morgue
and you finally took one off.
I had to see it for myseIf.
l don't get this. You moved
into this place six months ago...
and you're throwing
a house warming party tonight?
Tru?
Sorry. What's that?
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
MARK: Tru? It's me.
Mark.
MARK: Yeah. You haven't forgotten.
I'm gIad.
There's something
that l'd like to talk to you about...
but l don't want to
talk to you over the phone.
Standard Diner. One hour.
MARK: Yeah. Okay.
[Fast-paced instrumental music]
That was Davis.
He needs me to work today.
You're kidding.
Can it wait until after breakfast?
He said it was an emergency.
You're not mad, are you?
No, l just feel bad for you.
lt seems like you never catch a break.
TRU: l'll see you tonight, right?
LUC: Yeah.
TRU: l turned him over, there was
a single wound below the heart.
l called 91 1, but then he asked for help,
and the day restarted, and here l am.
So, if l'm to understand you correctly,
you had a party and didn't invite me?
Davis.
-l thought we were friends.
-We are friends.
Sure, when you wake up
next to some dead guy.
l apologize. Can we please focus here?
Okay.
So you have no idea
how Mike ended up in your bed?
Mark. And, no, l don't.
Look, l had a lot to drink last night.
-What about suspects?
-So far, l can only think of one.
-Who?
-Me.
Come on, Tru.
l don't know.
Mark was acting so weird yesterday.
Maybe he got violent,
maybe l fought back.
-There's no way did you kill him.
-How do you know?
Because l know you.
You save lives, you don't take them.
DAVlS: The victim was stabbed once
in the chest.
Was that the onIy wound?
[Tense instrumental music]
There was a pretty deep cut
in the palm of his right hand.
What else?
There was blood
on the wall behind my bed.
TRU: lt looked like sort of a half circle.
lnteresting. Any place else?
l just woke up and he was here.
l don't know how.
Yeah, on the doorknob.
And you said
you found the knife on the floor.
Beside the bed.
Only the first couple inches
of the blade were bloody.
That indicates a shallow wound.
You don't think it was suicide?
No. The slash on his palm
sounds like a defense wound...
meaning he was trying to protect himself,
which suggests murder.
Here, let me show you something.
[Fast-paced instrumental music]
DAVlS: lt's a forensic simulator program.
Helps investigators recreate a crime scene
that has been tampered with or destroyed.
So you're gonna recreate
my apartment on the computer?
DAVlS: l put in these variables.
l might be able to extrapolate
some ballpark description of the killer.
-How ballpark?
-Height, weight, sex.
lt'll take a few hours.
l'm meeting Mark in 15 minutes.
Aren't you forgetting something?
-The party. l'm invited tonight, right?
-There isn't gonna be a party.
DAVlS: No, there has to be a party.
There has to be a party.
ln order to save Mark's life...
you have to recreate the circumstances
that led to his death exactly.
DAVlS: Not only can you not
cancel the party...
you have to make absolutely sure
that he shows up.
DAVlS: Otherwise, the killer
could strike some other place.
Some place where you will not be able
to protect him.
All right.
Sorry, Harrison. We'll do lunch tomorrow.
Actually, there was something
l needed to talk to you about.
-Lindsay, right?
-Yeah. How did you--
lf you want her to like you,
you got to make her feel special.
How do l do that?
l don't know. Pick some flowers,
or burn her a CD mix.
Could l just go buy her something?
Fine. Just make sure it's not a watch
with another woman's name on it.
Come on. l would never do that.
Unless l did that. Did l do that?
l thought you don't believe
that l relive days.
l don't. l mean, look, l'd like to. l would.
But don't change the subject.
HARRlSON: AII I wanted was advice.
Okay, then just remember.
Think personal, not personalized.
Personal, not personalized.
MARK: lt's been a while.
You okay? You seem a little....
Yeah, it's nothing. l'm fine.
-lt's kind of strange seeing me, isn't it?
-Kind of.
-Anyway, the reason l called--
-Yeah, what's been going on with you?
Me? You know, the usual. Just classes,
grading papers, praying for tenure.
And what else? Personally?
l was seeing somebody.
But l broke it off, if that's what you mean.
-Another student?
-Yeah.
-lt's not one of my best qualities, is it?
-Anyone l know?
Got to admit, Tru, this isn't
the conversation l thought we'd be having.
MARK: Her name is Julie Spence.
She graduated last spring,
and now she works in the Mayor's office.
How'd she take it?
-Take what?
-The breakup.
Actually, she kind of went psycho on me...
and she even slashed my tires
the night l broke things off with her.
But you don't want to hear about this.
[Tense instrumental music]
lt's really good to see you again, Tru.
Yeah. You, too.
This is great.
lt was strange, but it was great.
Yeah, it was good to see you.
You know, we talked so much
during lunch, l never got to...
tell you why l called.
MARK: l've been thinking about you
a lot, Tru. About us.
About how great we were together.
And l miss you so much.
And l want you back.
Look, l know we have a lot to work out,
but l will do whatever it takes.
l'm seeing someone.
And l know how this is gonna sound,
but l want us to stay friends.
Friends. Yes, l've heard that one before.
No, really. l'm having a party tonight.
You should come.
We could talk some more,
you know, about everything.
Okay. That sounds great.
MARK: l have a late class,
but l'll swing by right after.
TRU: Okay.
MARK: Okay.
Bye.
[Somber instrumental music]
l guess Davis didn't need you after all.
-What are you doing here?
-l'm on my way to work.
Which, by the way,
is where you're supposed to be.
Look, the guy you just saw me with
is my ex-boyfriend.
He's the one that called this morning.
That's why you ran out on breakfast?
So you could meet him?
Luc, he's in trouble.
He needed to talk to me.
What kind of trouble?
lt's hard to explain.
You just have to trust me.
Like l trusted you when you said
you had to work this morning?
LUC: You know what?
Have fun at your party tonight, all right?
Luc, wait.
[Somber instrumental music continues]
[Dramatic instrumental music]
TRU: You called me here
to look at a watermelon?
How's that supposed to
help us solve a murder?
Observe.
[Soft instrumental music]
Notice there's no leakage.
The knife has sealed the wound.
DAVlS: But when you pull the knife out....
DAVlS: Does that look familiar?
[Soft instrumental music continues]
You're saying
Mark pulled the knife out himself?
That's not all.
The blood on the doorknob suggests...
he opened the door
with his wounded hand...
indicating that he was stabbed
outside of your apartment.
Okay, here's the sequence of events
as l see them.
Mark Evans is attacked.
[Mark screaming]
Left there for dead.
He gets to his feet,
he staggers towards your apartment.
[Panting]
With his wounded hand,
he opens the door.
[Tense instrumental music]
DAVlS: Makes his way
to the foot of the bed...
[Tense instrumental music intensifies]
pIaces his hand on the knife--
And yanks it out of his own chest.
[Gasps]
Precisely.
But how's he supposed to walk around
with a knife in his heart?
Because the knife sealed the wound.
For the first few minutes
there was probably very little blood loss.
-Then why pull it out?
-More than likely, he was in shock.
l know what you're thinking.
None of this proves you're the killer.
Yeah, none of this proves
that l'm not the killer, either.
You know what l was
supposed to be doing right now?
Making bean dip,
decorating for my party, having fun.
Nobody said this job was gonna be easy.
Yeah, no one said
it was gonna suck, either.
DAVlS: Tru, Tru.
You're not alone.
We are gonna crack this together.
[Soft instrumental music]
[Fast-paced instrumental music]
Turn the music down,
or else l'm calling the police.
Hey, Brian. l'm having a party tonight
and l'd like you to come.
Seriously?
Yeah. What fun would it be
without my neighbors?
BRlAN: All right.
TRU: See you tonight?
Sure. Yeah.
l mean, l'm always up for a party.
Great.
[Tense instrumental music]
TRU: ''Julie Spence.''
[Knocking at door]
[Sam exclaims]
Tru, a little help here.
-Ever heard of two trips?
-lf someone hadn't bailed on me.
Sorry about that. How much do l owe you?
$140 plus change.
Don't look at me like that. lt was on sale.
You made me come all the way over here
to get rid of a knife?
-A perfectly good knife, l might add.
-Just lose it. l don't care how.
HARRlSON: Hey, l still haven't figured out
a gift for Lindsay.
l mean, any other chick,
l'd buy candles or something.
But with Lindsay,
she's got such weird taste.
So get her something weird.
Just make sure--
l know. Get rid of the knife.
Something weird.
[Tense instrumental music]
TRU: Excuse me? Julie?
You don't know me,
but my name's Tru Davies.
TRU: l'm a friend of Mark Evans.
Actually, l know exactly who you are.
-Mark used to talk about you all the time.
-He did?
He was obsessed with you,
even when he and l were together.
You here to gloat?
-About what?
-Getting him back.
l always knew he wasn't over you.
l didn't get him back.
l don't even want him back.
-Then what do you want?
-To warn you.
No matter how strong
your feelings are for Mark...
you can't let them get the best of you.
l have no idea what you're talking about.
He said you slashed his tires
the night he called things off.
JULlE: No, it wasn't me.
But whoever did that terrible thing,
l'm sure Mark deserved it.
-Stay away from him.
-What are you, his bodyguard?
No. l'm just worried about him, that's all.
Whatever happened between us
is our business, not yours.
l'm not so sure about that.
-l'll deal with my exes my way, Tru.
-Yeah, that's what l'm worried about.
l think l finally get why you and Mark
were so perfect together.
You're both psychotic.
[Suspenseful instrumental music]
Come in.
l thought l might find you in here.
Yeah. A photographer in a darkroom.
Go figure.
l'm sorry l lied.
l only met Mark
because l was worried about him.
lt won't happen again.
The first time we went out...
you warned me there'd be times
you'd take off with no explanation.
And before today, I was okay with that.
But now l'm curious.
When you leave, where do you go?
Come on. l mean, you said
you were gonna be honest with me.
-And l will.
-So tell me. What's the deal?
Do you have some secret life?
LUC: Another guy stashed somewhere?
TRU: Of course not.
Then why won't you tell me
what's going on with you?
[Somber instrumental music]
Great.
LUC: Honesty.
TRU: Hey, Luc--
No, it's okay 'cause we're just starting...
and it's better this happened now
instead of later.
Listen, if you're looking for
neat and easy...
then, yeah, you're probably right.
You've got the wrong girl.
But if you think you can handle something
a little more complicated...
then stick around. You won't be sorry.
[Phone ringing]
LUC: Yeah.
TRU: Hello?
DAVlS: I need to see you. Now.
[Somber instrumental music continues]
TRU: l've got to go. Davis needs me.
Yeah. l've heard that before.
DAVlS: l finished running the numbers
through the simulator.
Based on the victim's
own height and weight...
and the location
and moderate depth of the wounds...
l believe that the killer
was approximately 5'4'', right handed...
and lacking upper body strength.
Mostly likely a female. What do you think?
l think you just described me.
[Dramatic instrumental music]
[Dramatic instrumental music continues]
Don't put words in my mouth.
l still don't think you did it.
5'4'', right-handed,
my apartment, my knife. Who else could....
l'll deal with exes my way, Tru.
-Julie.
-Who?
Mark's ex-girlfriend.
She and l are about the same size.
There. All we have to do is go to the party,
keep an eye on Mark...
and if the ex shows up,
you and l will be there to stop her.
And if l'm the killer?
l will not let you
make the same mistake twice.
[Fast-paced rock music playing on radio]
Hey, Tru. Cool party.
lt's good to see you again.
Thanks, Marty. Glad you could make it.
-Hey, neighbor. Kicking party.
-Thanks, neighbor.
You okay? You look a little worried.
The last party l had was kind of a disaster.
Before l moved in, l guess.
BRlAN: That's okay. Don't worry.
lf things start to slow down...
l'll go get my karaoke machine.
People love that stuff.
So here's a little something
from me to you.
l know you got, like, a ton.
But this one's supposed to be pretty rare.
LlNDSAY: Oh, my God!
Popeye, 1952, blue base, no feet.
There was only 2,000 of these made.
How did you know?
You said something about
a collection once.
Guess l wanted you to know
that l was listening.
[Fast-paced rock music
continues playing on radio]
Look what your brother gave me.
-Sorry. He means well.
-Are you kidding? l love it.
TRU: You do?
LlNDSAY: Yeah.
l don't know, l'm thinking
maybe l was wrong about him.
LlNDSAY: Maybe he is special.
You haven't seen Mark, have you?
As in your ex? Why would he be here?
-l invited him.
-What?
Why would you do that? What about Luc?
lt's a long story.
You know what you need?
Some of my special punch.
Thanks, but not tonight.
Hi.
How's it going?
No sign of Mark or Julie yet,
but it's still early.
l'm glad you're here.
Thanks for having me.
Where should l stand?
[Upbeat rock music playing on radio]
Where is that knife l bought?
BRlAN: Need something?
'Cause if you do, you know,
l live just right next door.
Got a knife?
[Dance music playing on radio]
Now l'm selling shoes with my dad
in his store until l can reapply.
SAM: How about you?
[Tense instrumental music]
TRU: Would you just excuse me one sec?
SAM: Yeah. No problem.
-Where did you get that?
-Your neighbor.
LlNDSAY: l can't find the one
l bought today. Have you seen it?
No, just be careful, okay?
-Okay.
-Sis, you got a sec?
l don't think it's gonna happen
for me and Linds.
-But she loved your present.
-Yeah, but...
she's so into me now, it's sort of a turnoff.
HARRlSON: You mind if l turn on the TV,
check out some scores?
TRU: Yeah, whatever.
HARRlSON: Okay.
[Dance music continues playing on radio]
You made it.
Yeah. Sorry l'm late.
My class ran kind of long.
Not a problem. l'm glad you're here.
Yeah. Me, too.
-Do you have a second?
-Sure.
lt's kind of loud in here.
Do you think we can go to the roof?
-l'm the hostess, l shouldn't.
-Come on, it'll take a second.
[Tense instrumental music]
l thought you had a boyfriend.
What happened? He go missing or....
No, he's not here.
-Trouble in paradise?
-Something like that.
Trust me. He's a fool
to walk away from a girl like you.
Take it from someone who knows.
Thanks.
[Tense instrumental music continues]
-What are you doing?
-l'm sorry, you invited me to the party--
Mark, l told you. l just want to be friends.
But friends isn't enough.
l won't give you up, Tru.
You're gonna have to.
[Tense instrumental music intensifies]
Maybe he got violent,
maybe l fought back.
Look, just stay away from me, Mark.
For your own good.
MARK: Tru.
[Tense instrumental music continues]
Downstairs, hook a right,
anywhere in the alley.
You rock.
Bye.
-So your brother took off on me.
-You're kidding.
He said something about
a card game downtown...
and then he just split.
Can you believe that?
-What's that for?
-Your vase. Sam knocked it over.
l shouldn't have let him
drink so much tonight.
LlNDSAY: lt wasn't a drunk thing.
lt was more like an angry thing.
TRU: What do you mean?
He got all worked up
over some professor...
that cost him a slot in med school.
...and this jerk professor
wouldn't give me a make-up.
The killer was approximately 5'4'',
right handed--
Then meet me upstairs on the roof.
Sam.
[Tense instrumental music]
Johns Hopkins!
The most prestigious medical school
in this entire country!
And they wanted me.
l'll make a telephone call
and explain what happened.
lt's too late for that now!
lt took me months...
but l was finally
getting my life back together...
and then you just go
and show up at my friend's party?
l just knew l couldn't let it go this time.
l couldn't let it go.
Put it down, Sam.
Tru, this is the guy.
This is the guy l was telling you about.
You're drunk. You don't want to do this.
No, l had a plan.
l had one chance, Tru.
And he took it from me.
[Tense instrumental music continues]
So take it back.
What are you talking about?
lf you don't like how
things went down the first time...
-do something about it.
-l am !
TRU: No, you're giving up.
lf you hurt Mark...
your life actually becomes
the sob story you think it is.
You could spend 20 years in a cell
feeling sorry for yourself.
ls that what you really want?
God!
[Tense instrumental music intensifies]
[Mark panting]
Tru, l don't know how to thank you.
You could say goodbye.
[Somber instrumental music]
DAVlS: Ex-student with a carving knife
on the roof.
The simulator would've
never figured that one out.
l still don't get how Mark made it
all the way back here...
with a knife in his chest.
Well, he loved you, Tru.
That always makes a person stronger.
[Door opening]
[Romantic instrumental music]
l hope l'm not too late.
You know what?
l'll just see you guys at work.
Thanks, D.
So l've been thinking.
TRU: About?
LUC: That nothing good comes easy.
lf l need to work a little harder
to keep you in my life, then so be it.
I have a feeIing you're worth it.
What about when l take off?
Think you can handle it?
l guess we'll find out.
[Romantic instrumental music continues]
Sorry l missed your party.
lt's not over yet.
-No?
-No.
Not tonight.
[Rock music]