Hmm... This cake is amazing.
My God! Get a room!
I would get room with this cake.
I think I can show this cake a good time.
If you had to, what would you give up? Food or sex?
Sex.
Seriously, answer faster.
Oh, I'm sorry, honey.
When you said sex, I wasn't thinking about sex with you.
It's like a giant hug.
Ross, how about you?
Which would you give up, sex or food?
Food.
OK, how about sex or dinosaurs?
Oh, my God, it's like Sophie's Choice.
What about you, Joe? What would you give up?
Sex or food?
Uh... I don't know, it's too hard.
No, you gotta pick one.
Food.
No, sex.
Sex.
Food.
Sex, I don't know... I want girls on bread!
Friends*1010 Chandler Gets Caught
- Ok, you gotta see the latest pictures of Emma.
- Oh, how cute!
- She looks just like a little doll.
- Oh, no no, that is a doll.
Oh, thank God, 'cause I think that is really creepy.
Look, there is Chandler.
Oh, who is the blonde, she is pretty.
He is having an affair.
He is not having an affair!
You know I'm always right about these things
No, you are not.
Last week, you thought Ross was trying to kill you.
Well, I'm sorry, but it's hard to believe that
anyone who tell a story that dull just to tell it.
I swear, there's something going on with them.
Look, he is getting into the car with her.
That doesn't mean anything.
Oh, yeah? well, let's see.
OK, duck down.
Hello.
Oh, hi, Chandler. It's Pheobe.
I know Monica is working today,
so I was wondering if you want to
come to the movie with me and Rachel.
Oh, I have to work too.
Yeah, I am stuck here at the office all day.
Well, it's a shame that you miss the movie
'cause you're gonna see... You know,
either Liar Liar or Betreyal or An Affair To Remember.
Those are really old.
OK, then maybe it'll be...
"Do Towards My Car"
What?
They are in the car.
OK, talk to you later, OK, bye.
OK, quick, we gotta find a cab and follow them.
Oh, yeah, OK, let me just grab
my night vision gargos and my stun gun.
I got them.
Hey.
Hey sweety.
You smell like perfume and cigrettes.
I was in the car with Nancy all day.
Nancy doesn't smoke.
Well, at least perfume is not mine,
you'll be thankful for that.
So. What did you think the house?
It's perfect, it's everything we've been looking for.
Isn't it? And what about the amazing wings coating,
and crown molding and doormal window and attic?
And wiggal worms and zip zops?
What were the things you said?
Do you love the huge yard?
And fireplace in the bedroom.
And Nancy said it's really under-price, because the guy lost his job and has to move in with his parents!
Well, this is bringing out a lovely color in you.
- Do you think we should get it?
- I don't know, what do you think?
- I think we should.
- I do too.
- This is huge!
- I know.
How about you want to smoke right now?
I don't know what you mean, giant talking cigrette?
By the way, Pheobe called just as I was getting in Nancy's car, so if she ask you, I was at work all day.
Gotcha.
When do we tell them about this?
We don't, not untill to 100%.
I mean why upset everybody over nothing?
OK, right.
Oh, my God, that is gonna be so hard.
I know.
Good luck with it.
I just can't see Chandler cheating.
I'm telling you guys,
we followed them out to a house in west Chester.
They were in for like 45 minutes
and they came out looking pretty happy.
Chandler? 45 minutes?
Something is not right!
I can't believe he'll do this to Monica.
I know, and with the baby coming?
So should we tell her?
I don't know.
Pheobe, if one of us saw Mike was with another woman,
would you want us to tell you?
Why? Who do you see him with?
No, I'm just saying.
Tell me what you know.
No, Nothing! He is great guy, it was hypothotical.
All right.
He is a good guy, you're right. He wouldn't cheat.
She wouldn't believe me,
if I did see him with someone, there's no way...
Who did you see him with?
Oh look at her, so happy.
if only there's smaller one to clean this one.
Hey. Is Chandler here?
No, he is picking up dinner. What's up?
Whatever happens, we're here for you and we love you.
All right.
We think Chandler might be having an affair.
What?
Pheobe and I saw Chandler with a blonde woman today outside on the street
and then we followed them to a house in west Chester.
They went in together. So sorry.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, that's awful.
What did you think of the house?
What?
Monica, you understand what I was saying, right?
Yeah, sure.
Devastated, obviously.
Did you think the neighbourhood was homey?
Hey.
You son of a bitch!
Is it me or greeting's gone down hill around here.
Pheobe and Rachel saw you with Nancy today.
They think you were having an affair.
Who is Nancy?
What's going on?
OK.
Guys, you'd better sit down. This is pretty big.
I'm not having an affair.
Nancy is our realtor.
I knew he couldn't be with a woman for 45 minutes.
Why do you have a realtor?
She has been showing us houses out side of the city.
What?
Are you serious?
We found out that we're gonna get this baby.
Chandler and I sort of talking, and we decided
that we didn't want to raise a kid in the city.
So you are gonna move?
Oh my God!
Shouldn't we all vote on stuff like this?
What is wrong with raising a kid in the city?
I am doing it.
Ross is doing it.
Sara Jessica Parker is doing it.
That's great for you guys.
But we want a long and a swing set
and street where kids can ride their bikes
and maybe an icecream truck can go by.
So you want to buy a house in the 50s.
We thought about you were giving up.
You can't move out the city.
What if you want Chinese food at 5:00am?
Or a fake Rollex that breaks as soon as it rings,
or an Asian hooker sent right to your door.
You know what,
if you wanna look for your house, that's ok.
No, no, it's not, don't listen to him.
I'm gonna thump you.
It's ok, because I've to get it at their system.
OK, you are gonna realize
this is the only place you wanna be.
Actually, we already found a house we love.
What?
And about an hour ago, we made an offer.
Bet you wish I was having an affair now.
You put an offer on a house?
It's so sweet.
It really is, it has this big yard that
leads down to the stream and there are old maple trees...
Well again, with the nature. What are you, beavers?
I know this is really hard and we are really sorry.
Is this because I come over here without knocking and eat you food, I can stop doing that, I really really think I can.
You know that's not the reason, Joe.
I think if you saw it, you'll understand.
You guys were there, it's beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
What the hell you are doing?
Well, it is, all right. When we were out there today, all I was thinking was I can't believe Chandler is screwing this woman, but man! It's such a nice place to live.
Yeah, but so is this.
Yeah, I mean if you move there you have to leave here.
How can you leave this place?
Come on Daddy, listen to me.
It's like all of my life, everyone has always told me,
'You're a shoe! You're a shoe,
you're a shoe, you're a shoe!'
And today I just stopped and I said,
What if I don't wanna be a shoe?
What if I wanna be a... a purse, y'know?
Or a... or a hat!
No, I don't want you buy me a hat.
I'm saying I am a ha... It's a metaphor, Daddy!
You can see where he'd have trouble.
Well maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.
Well, I guess we've established
she's staying here with Monica.
- Your money's mine, Green.
- Your fly is open, Geller.
You guys, you know what I just realized?
'Joker' is 'poker' with a 'J'. Coincidence?
Hey, that's 'joincidence' with a 'C'!
Eww, look. Ugly Naked Guy lit a bunch of candles.
That had to hurt!
Hey, it's your Thanksgiving, too.
Y'know, instead of watching football, you could help.
We will.
Okay, Rachel, you wanna
put the marshmellows in concentric circles.
No Mon, you want to put them in concentric circles.
I want to do this.
Every year!
It's stuck!!!
Easy. Step. How did it get on?
I put it on to scare Chandler!
Oh my God! Monica's gonna totally freak out.
Plus, it smells really bad in here.
Well, of course it smells bad.
You have your head inside a turkey's ass.
Hey, did you get the turkey basted...
Oh my God! Oh my God!
Who is that?
It's Joey.
I got it! How about, if we win,
they have to get rid of the rooster.
Oooohh, that's interesting.
If you win, we give up the birds.
But if we win, we get your apartment.
Deal!
What was Monica's nickname
when she was a field hockey goalie?
Big fat goalie.
Correct. Rachel claims this is her favorite movie...
Dangerous Liaisons.
Correct. Her actual favorite movie is...
- Weekend at Bernie's.
- Correct.
All right, Monica categorizes her towels.
How many categories are there?
Everyday use.
Fancy.
Guest.
Fancy guest.
Two seconds.
Uhh, 11!
11, unbelievable 11 is correct.
Chandler was how old
when he first touched a girl's breast?
14?
- No, 19.
- Thanks man.
Joey, had an imaginary childhood friend.
His name was?
Maurice.
Correct, his profession was?
- Space cowboy!
- Correct!
What is Chandler Bing's job?
10 seconds, you need this or you lose the game.
It's umm, it has something to do with transponding...
Oh-oh-oh, he's a transponce...transpondster!
That's not even a word!
I can get this! I can get this!
NOOOOOOOOO!!!!!
Y'know what, you are mean boys,
who are just being mean!
Hey, don't get mad at us!
No one forced you to raise the stakes!
That is not true. She did! She forced me!
Hey, we would still be living here
if hadn't gotten the question wrong!
Well it's stupid, unfair question!
Don't blame the questions!
Would you all stop yelling in our apartment!
You are ruining moving day for us!
Chandler, I saw what you were doing through the window!
I saw what you were doing to my sister!
Now get out here!
Wow! Listen, we had a good run.
Four? Five months?
I mean, that's more than most people have in a lifetime!
So, good-bye, take care, bye-bye then!
Hey Ross. What's up, bro?
What the hell are you doing?!!
Hey, what's-what's going on?!
Well, I think, I think
Ross knows about me and Monica.
Dude! He's right there!
I thought you were my best friend,
this is my sister!
My best friend and my sister! I-I cannot believe this!
Look, we're not just messing around!
I love her. Okay? I'm in love with her.
I'm so sorry that you had to find out this way.
I'm sorry, but it's true, I love him too.
My best friend and my sister!
I cannot believe this.
Well, this is the last box of your clothes.
I'm just gonna label it, "What were you thinking?"
Funny, because I was just gonna go across the hall
and write that on Chandler.
Hey you guys, I don't mean to make things worse,
but umm, I don't want to live with Rachel anymore.
What?!
You're just so mean to each other!
And I don't want to end up like that with Rachel.
I still like you!
Well, Phoebe, that's fine because I'm not moving.
Whoa-whoa-whoa, Phoebe, you gotta take her!
Y'know I-I-I said some really bad stuff about her.
But y'know Rachel has some good qualities
that make her a good roommate.
She gets tons of catalogs and umm, she'll fold down
the pages of the things she thinks that I'd like.
What else?
When I take a shower,
she leaves me little notes on the mirror.
Yeah, I do. I-I do, do that.
That's nice. I like having things to read in the bathroom.
When I fall asleep on the couch after reading,
she covers me over with a blanket.
Well y'know, I don't want you to be cold.
And when I told her that I was gonna be moving in
with Chandler, she was really supportive.
You were so great. You made it so easy.
And now you have to leave. And I have to live with a boy!!
She really left.
I know.
Thank you.
No problem, roomie.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure!
What the hell is that dog doing here?!
Little toast here.
I know this isn't exactly the kind of Thanksgiving
that all of you all planned,
but for me, this has been really great.
You know, I think because it didn't involve
divorce or projectile vomiting.
Anyway, I was just thinking, I mean,
if you'd gone to Vail,
and if you guys'd been with your family,
if you didn't have syphilis and stuff,
we wouldn't be all together, you know?
So I guess what I'm trying to say is that
I'm very thankful that all of your Thanksgivings sucked.
That's so sweet.
- And hey, here's to a lousy Christmas.
- And a crappy New Year.
You can't move, you just, you just can't.
Rachel is right. This is where you guys belong.
Yeah, you are not well with west chester.
That's like the worst of chesters.
You know, sometimes when I am alone in my apartment,
I look over here,
and you guys are just having dinner or watching TV
or something that...
makes me feel better.
And now when I look over, whom I'm gonna see, the...
They don't make me feel so good.
Yeah, so don't move.
OK, just stay here. And maybe close your blinds at night.
Hello.
It's Nancy, they responded to our offer.
And?
OK, thanks.
They passed.
They said they wouldn't go a penny
under the asking price.
- We can't afford that.
- I know.
Well, there you go.
Really sorry, guys.
I am sorry, too.
I mean I would be more sorry if that phone call didn't come before I told you about looking through the window.
Yeah, we are gonna let you be alone.
You're gonna be ok?
- Yeah, we'll be OK.
- I love you guys.
You know I am sorry I wasn't so supportive before.
That's ok, we understand.
And about this Nancy,
if you are not sleeping with her, should I?
I know there will be other houses, but it's just so...
I love that one so much.
Yeah. That's a good thing we got that, then.
What?
We got the house.
Oh, my God!
- I just didn't want to tell you in front of them.
- Oh my God, my God, we got the house.
We are getting the house.
And a baby.
We are growing up.
We sure are.
So who's gonna tell them?
- Nod it!
- Damn it!
Rachel, this is yours.
- What are these for?
- You'll see.
OK, everybody opens them.
This is so beautiful.
- These are ones I was looking at them at the store.
- I know.
I love this.
Wooh, a meatball sub.
Thanks.
Seriously you guys,
what's going on? what are these for?
Well, I didn't know how to tell you before. But...
We got the house.
Enjoy!
What did they say?