- Hey!
- Hey.
Phoebe, what's wrong?
I'm so exausted from draggin'
around this HUGE engagment ring.
Oh my God!
- Congratulations!
- Wow!
So, did he get you on one knee?
Did he have a speech prepare?
Or did he cry?
Yeah! Big surprise, I like proposals.
He was really sweet.
And like the most romantic thing ever.
Oh, well. Here's to Phoebe.
Who found the greatest guy in the world.
To Phoebe and ...
... I wanna say Mike!?
To Phoebe and Mike.
Thank you.
Oh, and I have something for you.
It's my little black-book, it's got
the numbers of all the guys I've dated.
Oh, Phoebe. Honey that's nice.
But, you know what? I think I'm okay.
Why don't you give to one of
your other single girlfriends?
I would. But you're the last one.
Gimme the book!
Pablo Diaz ... Ready Smith ... guy in van!?
Oh, my first love.
What is the red axe next
to bob Greenmore name mean?
Dead!
It's okay. he was old.
And he had a full life.
He was in the first wave at Ohama Beach.
I'm sorry. I should give you
my black book when i got marry.
Although so much a book is (?)
With Janese's phone number on it.
Phoebe, isn't Jethro Tull a band?
Oh yes, they are!
Friends 10th SERIE
Ep. n° 6
TOW
Ross's grant.
Hey honey.
Hey sweety.
Is Monica not here?
I'll tell you.
My agency was beating for a big account.
And they got it!
It's my first national commercial.
- Cool!
- Yeah
(?)
but a lot of the ideas were mine.
Hey, you weren't there?
ALL the ideas were mine.
That's great!
Hey, can you cast me in it?
How ... I don't know I really don't
think you're right for the part.
What you mean? I can do
anything, I'm a commedian.
I'm old.
I'm tired.
I'm hot, I'm cold.
Come on, what can't I do!?
First of all, BRAVO!
But I really don't think you're right for this ...
... the part calls for a
stuffy college professor.
I can do that!
Hello! I'm your professor,
when I'm not busy
thinking of important things
or ... "professing" ...
... I like to use ...
Oh, what's the product?
Software that facilitates
interbusiness networking e-solutions!?
I'm cold!
- Hey.
Guess who's the finalist
for a HUGE research grant!?
I'll give you a hand,
he's looking right at you.
Oh, unless is the crappy guy with (?)
skirt, I'm gonna say congratulaions!
I'm so excited.
Apparently I beated
undreds of other applicants.
Including five guys I went
to graduate school width.
Not that I'm keeping
score, really. FIVE!
Wow, that's great! So,
tell me about the grant.
Okay, is for 25000$, and, if i ge it ...
... I'll finally be able to
complete my field research.
And there will be an article about
me in the Paleontology Review.
It'll be the first time
my name is in there ...
... without people raising
serious questions about my work.
Wait! Are you talking about the