- Hey guys...
- Wait, wait, let me tell them.
Jeoy is gonna be a celebrity guest on a game show.
Really? Which one?
Fish, sea weed, a sunk ship.
Thingd you find in the ocean...
You are gonna be on PYRAMID!
Oh, that was our favourite game show ever!
- Except for Match game!
- Or Win or Lose Draw.
What did I marry into?
Do you guys wanna come down tommorow,
watch me tape the show?
We can't. We'll throw Phoebe a bachelorette party.
Yeah, sorry, boys. This ride's closing.
Oh, and Chandler and I have the stupid
college alone night thing.
I can't believe you get to meet Donny Osmond.
Seriously?
Yeahuh!?
Ross and I always wanna be Donny and Marie.
You guys just keep getting cooler and cooler.
Yeah, we used to perform for our family and friends.
Oh, that's right. I blocked that out.
- I'm a little bit country.
- And I'm a little bit Rock & Roll.
I'm leaving you.
Friends*1011 THE STRIPPER CRIES
English Subtitle: Öì³¤Õ÷ cz_z@sina.com
So we have to see all these people again.
Oh my god, look, that is Jeffrey Claric.
Who?
He was roommates with John Rusolf.
He went out with Andria Tembrino.
She dumped him for Michael Sklauf.
Did I go to this school?
Hey there's Missey Golberg, you gotta remember her.
Sure, nice.
Dude, you married to my sister.
You're right. By saying nice, I'm virtually licking her.
Hey, I hear she's single again.
You think should I ask her out?
Are you asking permission to break the pact?
Yes, please.
Hey.
Check out the flyers for the band.
I made them on a Macintosh in the computer room.
Awesome! The name really stands out.
Thanks to a little sth called Helvetic ball 24 point.
Man, we're gonna rock that Asian Student Union.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Missey.
You know, our band is playing on Friday.
Yeah, you should come and check us out.
We call it "Way, No Way".
- No way.
- Way!
Great, I'll be there.
- She's gone.
- I know it.
You know, I'm totally gonna ask her out.
Dude, I was gonna ask her out.
I said it first, bro.
Well, I thought it first, homes.
Look, if you date...
Wait, what are we doing?
What we have is too important to mess up with some girl...
I mean, we can get laid any time we want.
Totally.
I had sex in high school.
Me, too. I'm good at it.
Alright, I say we make a pact,
neither of us will go out with Missey Golberg.
You got it.
Alright, so that's Missey Golberg, Phoebe Kate and Molly Ringwalt, neither of us can go out with 'em
Those are the pact.
Oh, and Shina Easten, we probably couldn't get her anyway.
Well, not you.
Well, I officially give you permission to break the pact.
Thank you.
Alright, here I go.
Hey, remember how scary you used to be
going up to girls in college?
- Your hands are shaking.
- I know, I can't stop sweating.
5, 4, 3, applause.
Welcome, it is Soup Opra Week here on PYRAMID.
Let's meet our contestants.
First, Jean Lester, is a database specialist.
He's gonna be playing with
"Days of Our Lives" star, Joey Tribbiani.
Sir, I know it can be intimidating for regular people
to be around celebrities.
But, relax, I'm just like you. Only better looking and richer.
...should be playing wih the star of "General Hospital", Lesley Charlson.
Welcome, everybody. Good luck to all of you!
Let's play PYRAMID, alright?
We flipped the coin before the show.
Jean, you won the toss, so you're gonna start.
- Which category would you like?
- I'll take "You Cross The Line".
"You Cross The Line".
Joey, discribe for Jean these things that have lines.
Give me 20 seconds on the clock, please.
Ready? Go.
Uh, Ok, it's a store like a supermarket... Oh!
I see what I did, ok?
Uh, I'm writing in my...
Diary.
No, more like a notebook. Oh, dammit.
Oh, if I'm building a house,
the plan isn't called the schmooprint.
Can't do that either?
In high school, I once had sex with a girl
right in the middle of the...
Cafeteria.
Yeah, but that's not what they are looking for.
You did so much for this.
Oh, you like it?
Oh my god, it's also elegant.
When is the dirty stuff starting?
What?
You know, the strippers and the guys dancing,
and you know, PPs flying about.
Phoebs, I, I... There isn't gonna be any flying about.
We actually thought we're a little too mature for
stuff like that.
Ok.
I see what you're doing, that's fine.
This is all there is, just tea, ok.
Mmh, raunchy.
Seriously, Phoebs, this is not gonna be that kind of a party.
Really? So this is my big sent off in a married life?
Rachel, this is the only bachelorette party
I'm ever gonna have.
I've got a big wattle of wines in my purse.
Really? I mean, really it's just tea?
Nooo.
Phoebe, of course there's more.
I mean... Let me just go talk to Monica
and get us ETA on the PPs.
Now, Jean, I must remind you,
you need all 6 of these to stay in the game, alright?
Discribe for Joey things you find in your refrigerator.
I bet they're just giving us the points.
Give me 20 seconds on the clock. Ready? Go.
You put this thing in your coffee.
A spoon, your hands, your face.
- It's white.
- Paper, snow, a ghost!
It's heavier than milk.
Uh, rock, a dog, the earth.
Pass.
You put this on sandwich.
Salami, anchovies, jam.
- It's white.
- Paper, snow, a ghost!
- It's made from eggs.
- Chickens?
Pass.
- You put this on a hamburg.
- Ketchup.
- Yes. Stop
- Brioche.
Oh, time's up.
Joey, you are... almost on a roll there.
Jean, you're gonna have a chance to go to
the winner circle in the second half.
But right now, Henriada, you are going to the winner circle to try your luck for $10000 right after this.
Don't go away.
And we're out.
Oh, so we didn't win. But it's fun to play the game, right?
I got a kid starting college, I've got surgery on my knee.
You just lost me 10-grand.
Wow.
I'm so sorry, ok. I promise we'll do better next time.
Well, I will. Because I won't be playing with you.
You know, some of those are pretty hard.
Like why would there be a ghost in my frige?
So, Saturday night.
- I'd love to.
- Great.
So, how come it took you so long to ask me out?
Oh, well, it's gonna sound kinda silly, but...
Do you remember my roommate, Chandler Bing?
Sure, he was in your "Band".
It's been 16 years, but the air quotes still hurt.
- Sorry.
- That's ok.
Uhm, anyway, he and I both really liked you a lot,
but we didn't wanna anything to jeopardise our friendship,
so we knida made a pact
that neither of us could ask you out.
Really?
Yeah. Why?
Well, Chandler and I used to make out... a lot.
You did?
Yeah, we'd go to the science lab after hours.
And on my turf?
Hey, where is this guy? It's been over an hour.
He's coming from Jersey,
he said he would get here as fast as he could.
Who is it?
It's the police.
Oh, the police!
That's right, it's officer Good Body.
What's the matter, officer? Has someone been bad?
Woo, that's a lotta stairs.
Woo, boy!
You should warn people there's no elevator.
I should not have had that Mexican food for lunch.
- Are you gonna be ok, officer...?
- Good Body.
If you say so.
So, where is the young lady
who I'm supposed to take downtown?
Oh, God.
Alright, somebody show me where to plug in my box
and we'll get this party started.
Rachel?
Yeah?
Uhm, are you kidding?
Alright, look, we did not know that you wanted a stripper
so we went to the phone book, we got the first name we could find.
How old is your phone book?
Oh my god, this man is gonna get naked in my apartment.
Oh god, no. I don't want to see him take his clothes off.
Are you talking about me?
Oh, no!
I mean, obviously we wanna see you take your clothes off.
You big piece of eye candy.
Ok, ok. Ladies, can I have your attention, please.
Did some one call for the long arm of the law?
I should warn you I have a concealed weapon.
I hope you're familiar with this state's Pino code.
Ok, ok, enough teasing. Now for some pleasant.
Wow, wow, she cringed.
This is how I look when I'm turned on.
You were talking about me before.
Look, I don't need this.
I'm out of here, where's my hat?
Look, I've been in this business for a long time.
Shocking.
Now, if you just pay me my $300, I'll be on my way.
$300, are you kidding?
No, no, it's ok. Let me get my checkbook.
No, you're not getting to pay him. He didn't do anything.
Didn't do anything?
I took a bus all the way from Holbolken,
I climbed, I don't know, like a billion stairs,
it's not like I can take them to the time.
I don't care, we're not paying you $300 for this.
Well look, it's not my fault that you're too uptight
to appreciate the male form and all its glory.
Oh yeah, ok. I'm uptight, yeah,
that's why I don't wanna watch a middleaged guy
dancing around in what I can only assume as
a child's Halloween costume.
I may have borrowed this from my nephew,
but let me assure you what's underneath is all man.
I'm sorry, did you say all man or old man?
Oh, you're mean.
Oh, look, officer...
Oh dammit, ahh.
Big surprise, the hunk of beef has felings.
Applause.
Ok, Henriada, you picked Jack and Jill Went Up The Hill.
My friend Rachel has a kid,
I totally know nursery rhymes.
Joey, discribe these things
associated with the US Congress.
Give me 20 seconds on the clock, please.
Ready? Go.
(Legislature)
Ahh... Pass.
(Rotunda)
Pass.
(Filibuster)
(Addendum)
Ok, the little thing that hangs on the back of your throat.
Uvula.
Oh, then pass.
(Joint Session)
Ok, Henriada, you didn't get all the points you needed,
so that means Jean,
you are going to the winner circle to try for $10000
and you are gonna be going there with Joey Tribbiani.
You made out with Missey Golberg?
How could you do that after you promised me?
Excuse me.
That didn't make it sound gay at all.
You broke the pact.
Ross, it was 16 years ago.
That doesn't matter.
We're talking about the foundation of our friendship.
I believed the foundation of our friendship was
unfortunate hair.
Alright, look, if we're really gonna do this,
it's not like you never broke one of our pacts.
I didn't.
Oh really?
No.
No!
Agerin Turner!
Yes?
Hey.
I never did anything with Agerin Turner.
Oh please, and you knew how much I liked her.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Really? Remeber that big party? Freshman year,
a week before Christmas vacation?
I do. You had some visitors.
I can't believe we are at a real college party.
I have to pee so bad.
This is so awesome.
College guys are so cute.
Hey, you have a boy friend.
I know!
But if some guy looks like Corey Ham
wants to kiss me tonight, I'm gonna so let him.
Hey, look, it's Chandler.
You know, that stupid friend of Ross', said I was fat.
You know, I've already lost 4 pounds.
You could so totally tell.
I know!
Let's see maybe he knows where Ross is.
Hey, how is it going?
- Aren't you...
- Yeah, Rachel.
And this is Ross' sister, Monica.
We met at Thanksgiving.
Right.
So how are you doing?
Bitcher.
Hi, Monica.
Hi, Chandler. I mean, nice to see you... not.
Ok.
I'll see if I can find Ross.
Oh my god, Rach, bean bag chairs.
Do not let me sit in one of those.
We'll be here for days.
Listen, Agerin, you can't tell Chandler about this.
Oh, believe me, Ross.
I won't be telling anybody about this.
Cool.
I didn't know you knew about that.
Well, I did. And I hurt.
That's why I wrote the song
"Betrayed in the common room".
Man, I'm sorry.
Look, it's a long time ago.
So, I made out with Agerin and you made out with Missey.
Well, I guess we're even.
We are even, right?
Just one more thing,
I was so pissed at you that night
that I wanted to get back at you,
so I thought who does Ross like more than anybody.
What did you do to my mom?
Not her.
I am sooo drunk.
That's weird, I had the same of beer as you do
and I don't deel anything at all.
So, you girls are having fun?
For your information, ass much.
I lost 4 pounds, maybe 5 with all the dancing.
Somebody ordered a pizza?
Oh, that's me.
I'm so not gonna do good on my SATs tomorrow.
Well, maybe you can go to school here next year,
we can totally hang out.
Oh yeah, there's a plan.
Why don't I just start taking my smart pills now.
Wow, maybe you can get in on a beauty scholarship.
Oh, what a lying...(mouthing Oh My God)
So, where are you applying to?
Well, you know, I kinda think it's really important
that I go somewhere where there's sun, so I'm sorta...
Hey!
I'm in college, I'm in a band.
Yeah, ok.
What's the matter, you never saw
a fifty-year-old stripper cry before?
You know what, it's fine, we'll pay you.
No, no, you're right. Who am I kidding?
I should've hung up that break away jockstrap years ago.
What am I gonna do?
I mean, this has been my life for 32 years.
Taking my clothes off in front of people is all I know.
Oh wait, there's got to be sth else that you can do.
I mean, what skills do you have?
I don't know.
I can make my packs dance.
I can pick up a dollar bill with my butt cheeks.
I can go to that special place inside me
where I feel no shame.
So maybe sth in the office.
Or you could teach stripping.
You know? Share you gift, pass the torch.
Actually, that's not a bad idea.
I can do it outta my apartment.
I don't think my mom would mind.
There you go. You think you're gonna be ok?
Yeah, yeah, this is so weird.
You never know when it's gonna be your last dance.
And I don't even get a chance to finish it.
Finish it.
What?
Your last dance, do it for us.
Really?
Yeah, yeah, he deserves to do the thing he loves
one last time.
Ok. Alright, get ready, ladies.
Oh, this is so hot!
Oh, no, don't stop.
Have to.
Welcome to the winner circles.
Joey, Jean, you guys are ready?
- Yeah.
- Sure.
Ok, give me 60 seconds on the clock, please.
Ready? Go.
Oak, maple, elm, birch...
Uhh, I don't know, types of trees.
(Spanish Words)
Oh, I'm so sorry, I don't know any Spanish words.
A match, a candle...
Things that go "tze" when you put them out.
A torch, a bonfire... uh, your pee.
Things that burn.
I'd like to go for a walk.
Scratch my belly.
Dude, dude, I think you're loosing it.
Uh, I have fur, I like to bark.
Oh, What A Dog Says.
- Peperoni...
- Pizza toppings! Next!
Cindy Crawford , Christie Brinkly,
Hidey Clumn, Claudia shiffer.
Christie Tirlinton, Kate Marse...
Girls Chandler could never get.
- Supermodels!
- Where?!
Hey. Where's Rachel?
She and Phoebe took the stripper to the hospital.
Did you know Chandler kissed Rachel?
What? When was this?
1987. The weekend you guys visited me at school.
Oh my god, that's wild.
Yeah, but it was like a million years ago,
so it doesn't matter.
- Well, it matters to me.
- Why?
Because the night you kissed Rachel was the night
I kissed Rachel for the very first time.
You kissed her that night, too?
Two guys at one night?
I thought she became a slut after she got her nose fixed.
Seriously, where did this happen?
Ok. After you told me she was passed out in our room,
I went in there to make sure she was alright.
She was lying on my bed and all buried in people's coats.
Well, I went to kiss her on the forehead,
but it was so dark I accidently got her lips,
I started to pull away
but then I felt her start to kiss me back.
It was only for a second but it was amazing.
And now, now I find out that you kissed her first.
- Uh, wait, what bed you say she was on?
- Mine.
- I'm pretty sure I put her on my bed.
- No, she was definitely on my bed.
Why would I kiss a girl and put her on your bed?
Well, then who was on my bed?
Oh, oh, oh!
No, no, no!
Yes!
You were under the pile of coats.
I was the pile of coats.
Oh my god!
You were my midnight mystery kisser?!
You were my first kiss with Rachel?!
You were my first kiss ever?!
What did I marry into?
Oh, crap!