Previously on Kyle XY...
You have no idea
how disappointed I am right now
Don't you even care that
I'm not happy at the conservatory?
Thank you for letting me know
that Amanda was here.
Glad that I can help.
My mum and I talked
She won't let me see you outside
the school for a while.
And I need to get a job
to be more muture and responsible.
I am lazy.
My work ethic does suck,
and I really don't care about school
Don't expect me to ride shotgun
on your "woe is me" interstate.
You're smart, and you know it.
So get off your ass and
start making something of yourself.
I know that box is still
very important to him.
I don't think Kyle would
want you to handle it.
Do you know why it's important
to him? Because I do.
You have no idea about what
Kyle and I share with each other.
I know you don't know him
as well as you think.
The way you've crossed boundaries,
mixing your personal
and your professional life,
shows an alarming lack of judgment.
I have big plans
for you, Jessi,
and I need you to be as strong
and as smart as you can possibly be.
I need to focus
on my family right now.
Brian said that you'd be like this.
He said I couldn't count on you.
- Why would he say that?
- You keep sending me away.
I'm finally comfortable
with where we are.
- Which is?
- Friends.
- Without benefits.
Brutal.
If there's ever anything
you want to tell me,
I hope you know you can.
I do know that.
All right. I think it's time we take
your training wheels off.
You ready?
I just want to go over the milk
to espresso ratio...
Forget the cheat sheet.
Just shadow me.
You'll get the hang of it.
How's the rookie?
- Okay, I guess.
- Eh, you'll be fine.
I mean, if Josh can do it...
- Nice.
- Sundays are slow.
It's a good day to,
you know, ease into it.
Okay, this cash register
can get a little complicated.
You could put a rover
on mars with this thing.
Anyways, we start with 200 bucks
in the till to make change.
We take the drawer out of
the safe in the mornings,
and at the end of the day,
we add up all the sales
and put it back in the safe
for the next day.
Got it.
And here you go.
Am I too late?
- For?
- I want to be your first.
Uh, being somebody's first
can mean something
completely different.
I want to be your first customer.
I knew what you meant.
- Is this what you need?
- Oh, thanks.
Now, what can I get for you, sir?
I'll have a pineapple orange
banana smoothie.
I must have hit the wrong button.
- No, I don't want kiwi!
- Kiwi sounds good.
- Really?
- I love kiwi.
Now how I take the strawberry off?
I want strawberry, too.
Kyle, if you keep changing
your order to cover for me,
I'll never learn
how to do this right.
Kiwi-strawberry, that's my order.
- Promise?
- promise.
Except there's lime on here, too.
Lime makes all the difference.
Promise?
Promise.
Is this like some lame ritual
you guys have?
Cause I promise that I'm about to puke.
Keep it professional.
I am. I'm working. Kyle's a customer.
Listen, I got to take off
for a few hours,
so you're in charge.
I am? I mean, are you sure?
It's just me and Amanda,
and she's new.
Yeah. Relax. Nothing
ever happens on sunday.
"Nothing ever happens on sunday."
Sous-titre VO ::: www.shooter.cn
modifié pour www.forom.com
Traduction ::: La Team XY
Sechs, Jayson.sosweet et MiniBen314
vous présentent
Kyle XY - 2x18
Between The Rack and a Hard Place
I don't want you
to see Kyle anymore.
- Why?
- I'm just not convinced
that he has your
best interests in mind.
But he's the only one that
understands what it's like to be me.
But he doesn't believe in you.
Not the way that I do.
And the others, Latnok, they...
They just don't think
you're as good as Kyle.
But they're wrong, okay?
You can be better.
See, they don't see your potential,
and neither does Kyle.
Or he won't.
I mean, if he acknowledges
how special you are,
then somehow it makes him
less special.
He's always helped me.
Has he... always helped you?
I mean, it seems that
he's pushing you away.
I am the only person who will
always be there for you.
Whenever you need me.
Just you and me.
You should probably take
the seed out of the avocado
before you put it in
the smoothie machine.
Should've known.
I thought they were
just really big limes.
Okay, so I'm not that great with fruit.
At least you know
an avocado is a fruit.
Most people think it's a vegetable.
Tell that to the smoothie machine.
Amanda, we got customers.
Look alive, okay?
I'm on it.
I can't help it if all I want
to do is be alone with you.
You really do sound like the manager.
Think I should make the other
employees call me "the man"?
Anyway, I've got
my eye on a big, fat raise.
So if I have to crack
the whip a little...
I'm glad I'm not one of your employees.
Then technically, you're loitering.
Jessi. Hi.
You here for Kyle?
Do you think maybe we could talk?
You know, like we used to.
Jessi, I don't...
I mean, I'm not your therapist anymore.
Can't we just talk as friends?
I'm not sure that's appropriate.
Why?
Well, there are ethical boundaries,
and it's just...
Better if we maintain them.
I think Kyle's at the Rack
if you need to talk to him.
Okay.
Good-bye.
Bye.
What's a girl got to do
to get some service around here?
Well, you can start with the manager.
What happened to J.T.?
He put me in charge for a few hours.
Brave man.
Aren't you forgetting something?
Oh, sorry.
Um, sweet, but no.
Money? Cow Keys tickets?
On sales today.
Oh, right.
Fork it over.
Mama needs some green.
Are you sure you're up to this?
I thought you'd be too chemo'ed out
to wait in line for tickets.
Please. My last chemo was,
like, two days ago.
Puking is, like, so yesterday...
And last night.
I can't believe I'm paying
120 bucks for concertickets.
- Am I not worth it?
- You are, but the band?
Fine. We won't go.
But then these...
Are off-limits.
You're giving me an ultimatum?
Sometimes it's the only thing
guys will respond to.
So either I pay for
overpriced concert tickets...
Or the only rack you'll be
seeing is the one
that makes you wear
that stupid apron.
Fine.
Yielding to the power of the boob.
And you just lived to feel me up
another day.
Don't tell me Josh
roped you into minimum wage hell.
Actually, I'm not getting paid.
Looks like the job does have its perks.
She said all she want to do
is to be alone with me.
Looks like your guys are about to take
the next step in your relationship.
What's the next step?
I think things are about to get
a little bit more hands-on.
As on hands on butts,
hands on boobs.
Don't you want to move beyond
the hugs and no-tongue kisses?
Well, I know that
when I'm with her, I...
You get like you did
that day at the pool.
I can't help it.
Kyle, that's a good thing.
It's totally natural.
I'm just not sure Amanda's ready
to take the next step.
Kyle?
Could you help me in the storage
room for a minute?
Sure.
You were saying?
Go. Go.
Yes.
How can I help?
The protein powder. Top shelf.
I can't reach it.
Thanks.
Is that it?
For now.
Were you expecting something else?
Lori thought you asked me in here to...
No.
But I kind of wish
I'd thought of that.
That's okay. I'm glad I could help.
Kyle...
Thank you.
You know, this storage room
is our only chance of privacy,
at least until my mom cools down.
When will that be?
It's hard to tell.
I think she just needs
to get to know you better.
I do, too.
But you already know me.
Yeah, but...
Now that we're together,
I feel like there's so much
I still don't know about you.
And I want to know everything.
Small cappuccino, decaf... whatever.
Where have you been?
It's a madhouse.
- Sorry.
- Just go wipe the tables.
I thought sunday was a slow day.
Yeah, somebody forgot to tell them.
Can I help?
Raise your right hand.
Do you solemnly swear to uphold
the principles of the Rack
and not do anything
that will get me fired
and/or sued for labor law violations,
so help you, Josh?
- What?
- I'm deputizing you.
- Just say yes.
- Yes.
Okay, Amanda's still
new at the register,
so keep an eye on her.
And fix the blender ASAP.
Can you multi-task?
Right. Stupid question.
Any questions that aren't stupid?
Do I get a badge?
You get an apron.
I don't think the smoothie
machine is that damaged.
Speaking of damaged...
Hi, Jessi.
Do you work here now?
Special circumstances.
I'm just helping out.
I could give you a hand.
Uh, that's okay.
I think I can manage.
The ground wire's not supposed
to run back to the motor.
You're right.
Does it bother you that I am?
No, I'm glad you pointed it out.
Well, I was wonderg if...
if maybe we could talk.
Um, but if this a bad time, I could...
Oh, no, no, no.
Just hang out for a couple minutes.
I'll get you some coffee,
and then we can talk.
Promise?
Yeah.
Easy, there, Lady Macbeth.
You've been scrubbing that same spot
for quite some time now.
I hate to be the jealous girl,
but I just...
I don't like seeing them together.
Yeah, you've got that "my boyfriend's
with another woman" expression.
What does that look like?
Probably a lot like mine right now.
Except he's not your boyfriend.
You're absolutely right.
He's a free agent.
We both are.
There is no reason at all
why it should bother me.
But it does.
Nope.
I'll prove it.
- I'm Lori.
- Kenzie.
And, uh, I'm a little confused.
What? I'm just stopping by
to see my friend.
Your friend?
Aren't we? friends?
I'll see you later.
No, no, no.
You don't have to go.
I think I do.
Thank you for that.
I was trying to be friendly.
Yeah, well, don't try so hard.
Excuse me?
Friends want other friends to be happy.
You want me to be miserable and pining.
That is so unfair.
My point exactly.
That did not just happen.
I'm sorry.
You should be.
Holding the door would get you, what,
kicked out of the ass hat society?
Maybe you can put in
a good word for me
at the psycho bitch league.
Tell you what,
let's settle this out of court.
Let me buy you a coffee.
Yeah, forget it.
Like you're ever gonna get that.
Should be free by now.
I asked for no whipped cream.
Let's go somewhere else.
Sorry.
Should be free by now.
I didn't want milk in this.
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought you did.
Obviously, but I didn't.
My mistake.
Actually, sir, you did order milk.
Honey, hang on.
What did you say?
You ordered a half-caf double
espresso with skim milk.
And then you asked somebody on the
phone, "Honey, do you want anything?"
and I'm assuming they said no,
because you only ordered the one drink.
Sir, we'll fix your order right away.
Not a problem.
Just give him what he wants.
But he's wrong.
The customer is always right.
It's an expression.
I don't get it.
Uh, it doesn't matter if he's wrong,
you have to let him think he's right,
or he'll just take
his business somewhere else.
It's my first day
and I really can't afford
to lose customers,
so just trust me on this.
The customer is always right,
even when they're wrong.
- Yes.
- Every customer?
Everyone.
Crap.
I lost count again...
Here.
$397.
You did not seriously
just count that.
Do you need serial numbers, too?
Since when did the smart guy
become a smart-ass?
Wait, how much
did you say was in there?
$397.
That's not right.
There's supposed to be
570 bucks and change in here.
- So...
- We're short 120 bucks.
Josh, I was really careful
with the register.
Yeah, when you were at the register.
You left it and took off
with Kyle in the storage room.
Anybody could have had
their hand in the till.
But, Josh, it could have happened
anytime during the day.
Including the time you guys
were busy making out.
I hope your little
rendez-vous was worth it.
Same count.
Great.
We were only gone for a minute.
2 minutes and 49 seconds, actually.
Maybe there's another explanation.
Okay, full disclosure.
120 bucks is the exact amount
I gave to Andy for
the Cow Keys tickets.
But I've been saving up
for weeks to get those tickets.
Josh, no one thinks you
stole the money.
Good. So let's get back to
blaming you and Amanda.
It must have been a customer.
Maybe Jessi.
Jessi?
She probably did it to make me
look bad on my first day.
No, she couldn't have done it.
Right.
Jessi would never do that.
I mean, she beat up Lori
and took her necklace,
but she'd never steal any money.
Hey, you still gotta fix this.
It'll give J.T. one less thing
to fire me for.
You really think he'll fire you
because the money's missing?
Right after he fires Amanda.
So unless you can what happened,
we're both doomed.
I spent most of my job
trying to get kids to open up.
Right? Then one of them shows up,
crying out for my help.
I practically slam
the door in her face.
Look, I know it's a tough situation,
but you just got slammed
by that social worker.
You can't be Jessi's sounding board.
She's a former patient.
Well, I can't just ignore her.
You have to.
They're watching you now.
Well, it's wrong.
That's not the point.
Your license is at risk.
You can't jeopardize
your career over this.
What's the point of my career?
How's your first day going?
Not great actually.
Someone stole money out
of the register.
You think I did it.
I wouldn't put it past you.
I'm not a thief.
Lori's necklace notwithstanding.
I gave that back.
Great. Now give back the money.
I didn't take it.
You may have everyone fooled.
Even Kyle.
But I know what you're really about.
You don't know anything.
Maybe I should call your mom again
and tell her that you're here
hanging out with Kyle.
What are you doing?
What does it look like?
Opening drink bottles
and not drinking them.
I'm trying to make up
for the missing $120.
The drink company's doing
a prize giveaway game.
Check under certain bottle caps,
and you can win cash.
One in twenty is a winner.
How much have you won so far?
One free drink and a t-shirt.
But we sold eight drinks today,
And nobody's won cash.
The odds are one in twenty,
So if I open twelve more bottles...
It doesn't work that way.
The odds are one in twenty
for all the bottles produced
by the drink company,
not just for the bottles
that are in this case.
One in twenty odds
that means that each bottle's
a 95% chance of not being a winner.
So if the drink company puts
out billion bottles,
950,000 of them are not winners.
That's a lot of losers.
And even if you do find a winning cap,
you still have to pay
for all these bottles.
Yeah, you're right.
Sorry, I lost my mind
for a second there.
Is that all for you?
Oh, I'll get one of these, too, please.
That's $4.00.
Oh, my God! I won 50 bucks!
Thank you so much.
I can't believe it!
I wasn't even gonna buy that!
You!
- Hey.
- Get away from me.
- Hey. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Stay away from me!
- Lori!
- Dad, he tried to attack me!
- Mr. Trager?
- Mark?
Mark?
I got those papers you wanted.
I can explain the coffee stains.
You know him?
He's my T.A.
No, J.T., everything's cool.
All right, see you soon.
He'll be back in an hour.
I'm screwed.
Is this even close to working?
I have to boost te motor's power,
but to do that...
Don't explain, just fix it.
- Hey, I've been waiting.
- I know.
You said we could talk.
It's a little crazy right now.
You promised.
Are you going to turn me away again?
Josh needs my help.
Can you give me a little more time?
No.
Jessi! Jessi!
Let her go.
Why is that so hard?
What makes her so important?
She said she had
something to talk about.
Kyle, Jessi is not your problem.
I love that you assume
the best in people,
but enough is enough.
Aside from everything else she's done,
she is the one who ratted
me out to my mom.
How do you know that?
She admitted it.
She is so mapulative.
She lies, and then she throws
it back in your face.
She makes me so uncomfortable.
I know it's not the same thing, but...
How would you feel if I said
I wanted to keep hanging out
with Charlie?
I guess I never
thought of it that way.
I know.
Excuse me.
What have you done?
What you asked.
I'm fixing the smoothie machine.
With a grenade?
The blades were damaged,
so the machine was too
inefficient to blend the juice.
But by boosting the motor's power,
we can compensate.
Unfortunately, that means
rewiring the electrical system.
I'm a dead man.
Someone just sprayed graffiti
in the bathroom.
"For a good time,
call Dava Vina 535..."
I know the number.
What's going on?
The switch machine's motor is broken
so until I fix it...
No, I mean with you and Amanda.
You guys are fighting?
She doesn't want me
to be around Jessi.
Amanda doesn't have to know
you're hanging out with her.
I won't lie to her.
Then try the four magic words.
"You're right.
I'm sorry."
I should apologize,
even though I don't think
I've done anything wrong?
Hell, yes.
Sometimes you gotta
let them be right,
even though you know they're wrong.
Or they'll take their
business somewhere else.
What?
The customer's always right.
Uh, yeah, something like that.
I'm telling you, those four little
words are an instant cure.
Your fight's over.
You can move right on
to the makeup sex...
Or in your case, makeup hugs.
Water seems to be working.
I'll go find some eyedrops.
Well, look at the bright side.
I think the pepper spray got the
coffee stain out of your shirt.
Yeah, and that's a real priority now.
Hey, I said I was sorry.
Can I ask you a personal question?
I suppose you're entitled to one.
Why are you so angry?
Um, let me see.
I guess it all started when you
let the door hit me in the face.
Unintentionally.
You branded me a callous jerk
without proper provocation.
Well, when it comes down to it,
aren't you all callous jerks?
Oh, I see.
So some guy did you wrong,
and I'm the one who
gets pepper sprayed.
Aren't you insightful?
Oh, so I'm right?
No, you're arrogant and conceited.
And you're bitter and hostile.
Are you sure you don't
want a second spray?
I'd be happy to oblige.
Man, I think you already
emptied the whole can.
Don't count on it.
I'm sorry I snapped.
The stress is really getting to me.
I know it's been rough.
I thought I could handle it.
I mean, this job is the one
thing I'm good at,
and I've totally screwed it up.
I've managed to double the power
to the smoothie machine.
That's great, but
the money's still missing.
Can't you do something Kyle-like?
I can access my holographic memory.
It lets me reexamine
past events from every angle.
Oh, I thought you could
do something cool,
like make money.
Okay, do your holodeck whatever thing.
In replaying the day,
I once again saw
every encounter with
disgruntled customers.
It was a chaotic day where
nothing seemed to go right.
Well, almost nothing.
There was one thing that
made everything worthwhile.
You should probably take
the seed out of the avocado
before you put it in
the smoothie machine.
Amanda's reassuring touch.
I can't help it if
all I wanna do is be alone with you.
Her playful laugh.
Kyle?
Could you help me in
the storage room for a minute?
Sure.
And most of all,
the sweetness of her kiss.
These moments made all of
my other problems disappear.
Uh, being somebody's first
can mean something
completely different.
I want to be your first customer.
I knew what you meant.
Is this what you need?
Thanks.
That was it.
Well, what happened to the cash?
It was never in the cash drawer.
What?
I replayed the day back
to the beginning.
Right before Amanda took my order,
I helped her with the cash drawer.
Each bill weighs one gram.
The drawer was nine grams too light.
Based on the levels of denominations,
it looked like four twenties,
three tens, and two fives were missing.
That's a total of $120
that was missing
before the cash was
even put in the register.
A superhuman memory bank
with a built-in scale.
Did you count the money in the drawer
Before the start of the day?
Uh, no. I was training Amanda.
J.T. counted it.
Maybe he made a mistake.
Yeah, blaming my boss,
that'll go over big.
It's okay. I'll take the heat for this.
Amanda's in the clear.
But it wasn't your fault.
That's what happens
when you're the man.
I totally cancered my way
into front-row seats.
- Hey, Kyle.
- Hi.
FYI,
I implied you had cancer, too.
So we might have to shave your head.
It's a fitting end to a horrible day.
What happened?
There's 120 bucks missing
from the cash register.
I'm totally fired.
Well, if J.T. busts you for that,
you can bust him for playing hooky.
I saw him in line for
the Cow Keys tickets.
Tickets that cost $120.
J.T. took the money
to buy concert tickets?
Doesn't make sense.
He'd know the register
would come up short.
He'd get caught.
That's why he put you in charge.
You're his fall guy.
That bastard's gonna be
here any minute.
What do I do?
Maybe I boosted the power too much.
You think?
You've got to be kidding me.
On the bright side,
the missing money isn't the
first thing your boss will notice.
I'm sorry about the smoothie machine.
It's fine.
Amanda...
I just wanted you to know that
Jessi didn't take the money,
and it's not our fault either.
The manager stole it.
That's great.
You're right. I'm sorry.
What?
You're right. I'm sorry?
Does that mean you won't hang out
with Jessi anymore?
Kyle, please tell me,
why do you want to
be friends with her?
I mean, she's creepy
and she's strange
and she beat up your sister,
yet everyone's apparently
fine with it.
I know it's hard to understand.
You have to trust me.
Trust you?
Haven't I been trusting enough?
Go on Kyle and Jessi, it's okay,
stroke each other's bellies.
Oh, and have a nice road trip,
and, hey, while you're gone,
is there a love song
I can play for the two of you?
The problem isn't that
I don't trust you,
it's that you don't trust me.
I trust you completely.
Really?
Then what's the due
with that weird box,
the one I pulled out of
the underground death trap?
The one you almost got
yourself killed for?
Jessi knows what it is, doesn't she?
Amanda...
You can trust her with
your secrets and not me,
and until you can do that,
maybe I'm the one you shouldn't
be hanging out with.
It's a total no-win situation.
If I say I don't know what
happened to the money,
I'm fired.
If I tell J.T. I know he stole it,
but can't prove it,
then it's his word
against mine, and I'm fired.
If I don't tell Amanda secrets,
I risk losing her.
If I do tell her, I risk losing her.
You don't know that.
Secrets ruined your
relationship with Lori.
Openness and honesty hasn't
exactly worked either.
Let Amanda cool off,
maybe she'll be more reasonable.
That's the thing,
I think she is being reasonable.
How can we have a real relationship
If she doesn't know
the whole truth about me?
Then tell her.
Then she'd know I'd been lying to her.
She'll forgive you.
Like she forgave Charlie?
That's different.
You lied to protect her.
Charlie lied to protect himself.
But what if she looks
at me differently?
What if she doesn't like
who I really am?
Then I guess telling her
is one way to know
if you should really be together.
Amanda!
We need to talk.
Look, if you're going to break up
with me, please,
don't draw it out, just do it quick.
I'm not gonna break up with you.
I need you in my life.
I need you in every part of it.
Okay.
So let's talk.
Well, I guess I'll see you around.
I mean, once I can see again.
Well, watch your step
and I'll go easy on you.
Declan.
Hey.
I'll see you.
Who was that?
Some guy I pepper-sprayed.
Why did you do that?
He pissed me off.
I'm sensing a pattern.
Oh, I see.
You think I'm being irrational?
What about you,
mister all-up-in-arms
when I say an innocent hello
to your new girlfriend?
A, she's not my new girlfriend,
And b, your tone was hardly innocent.
Oh, what was it then?
Passive-aggressive mean
girl comes to mind.
You are so not-allowed to use
my own phrases against me.
Trager...
You're right.
What?
You're right. I'm sorry.
I'm totally not falling for that.
Hi, mom.
- Hey.
- Hello.
Mr. Taylor... Brian.
It's Nicole Trager.
Yes?
Uh, I just wanted to let you know
I saw Jessi earlier.
And she seemed troubled,
and I tried to explain to her that
it's difficult for me
to talk to her now
since I'm not her therapist,
but I want to let her know
that I do care about her.
Well, I'm sure she'd be glad hear that.
She's just not in right now.
Oh, well could you let her know
that I called?
And please tell her that
I'm thinking about her.
Absolutely.
Thanks.
Who was that?
Nobody.
What's wrong?
You were right.
Kyle doesn't care.
He won't even talk to me.
And neither will Nicole.
I tried to explain.
They're not a family.
But I just want to be their friend,
but they won't let me.
They're jealous.
You know what you're capable of,
but they don't want to see you succeed.
Not like I do.
I'm your father, Jess.
I will never let you down.
The place is clean,
the smoothie machine is fixed,
now if I could only find $120
lying around somewhere.
I scalped the Cow Keys tickets.
But I thought you were really
looking forward to seeing them live?
No, I was really looking forward
to spending time with you.
So...
How did it go?
No worries.
All right.
There's so much we don't know
about each other.
Yeah.
And I want to know
everything about you.
I want to know everything
about you, too.
But I think we should take it slow.
Savor each new thing.
One step at a time?
Exactly.
So how about this?
I'll tell you something
you don't know about me,
and then you tell me something
I don't know about you.
Yeah.
Okay.
So that box you asked me about,
it belonged to someone
very close to me.
But you found that box underground.
Whose was it?
My biological father.
Your biological father?
A man named Adam Baylin.
He worked in that facility
many years ago.
I don't understand.
It's okay.
Eventually, you will.
Now it's your turn.
Tell me something
I don't already know about you.
I really like kissing you.
That doesn't count,
I already know that.
I really, really like kissing you?
Sorry, I know that, too.
My favorite ice cream flavor is...
Double mint chip.
Register balances out.
You sound surprised.
Oh, no. no, no.
Um, good work.
So, I got to take off,
so, cool.
Don't forget to lock up.
Have fun at the Cow Keys concert.
Those tickets are really expensive.
What do they cost?
Like, 120 bucks?
Some people would do almost
anything to get those tickets.
I guess you really lucked out, huh?
Next time, you might not be so lucky.
With what you've got over him,
I bet you get that raise
sooner rather than later.
Hush money.
Or buy Andy something pretty money.
Has a better ring to it.
You know,
I may have given up our tickets,
but I was able to get
the next best thing.
The Cow Keys live in Gainesville?
When did this go on sale?
It hasn't. Promo copy.
Doesn't go on sale for two weeks,
but mama's got people
who know people.
Yeah, I figured you'd want
to give it a listen.
Only if we can listen to it together.
There's a CD player
in the storage room.
Sounds like an ultimatum.
Sometimes it's the only
thing girls will respond to.
Two years ago, I actually
went to band camp.
I saw the photo on your wall.
At this rate I'll never learn
anything about you.
Well, then I guess it
could take a while.
You'd better get inside
before your mom sees us.
Foss?
Foss I got your message.
It wasn't from Foss.
Adam.
Hello, Kyle.
Traduction ::: La Team XY
Sechs, Jayson.sosweet et MiniBen314
www.forom.com