This is torture.
It's not torture, Shawn,
it's a 10 minute ride
to the police station.
But I wanna eat my candy.
Not until I
have it X-Rayed.
Well, can I eat my candy?
Knock yourself out, Lando.
As long as your old man
doesn't mind his nine year-old
son passing razor blades.
(CHATTERING ON POLICE RADIO)
Officer, please!
We've got a jumper.
Hey, hey, back off,
I got kids in here.
Phone lines are down,
we tried the police already.
There's no time.
She's really gonna jump.
Okay, okay, look, look,
I'll radio for backup.
I not gonna subject
these boys to...
Dad, you have to help.
Sonofa...
Now listen to me boys,
I do not want you
to leave this vehicle.
Do you understand?
I want you to stay put
until I get back.
Don't look, don't listen.
Just shut your eyes.
And keep them shut.
I'll be right back.
She's straight up the stairs.
Room 413!
Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Not even sort of.
Gus...
You'll thank me later.
SCARY FEMALE VOICE: Doreen!
Doreen.
(WHIMPERING)
(ECHOING) Doreen!
(SCREAMING)
I know, you know
That I'm not telling the truth
They just don't have any proof
Embrace the deception
Learn how to bend
Your worst inhibitions
tend to psych you out
in the end
You cheated.
I did not cheat.
You're not using
the side walls at all.
I don't need your tips, Shawn.
I've beaten you before.
Yeah. When we were 12.
And I had pinkeye.
Immaterial. The low game
was crackling. The worm burner
was in full effect.
Okay, you cannot have a shot
called the worm burner.
Why not?
Because it's my strikeout
pitch in Wiffle ball.
Pick a different name.
Excuse us,
may we help you?
Hey, guys.
Damn, girl.
Yeah, I know.
Get it all out now.
I barely recognize myself.
But isn't it kind of amazing?
Mary Lou Baumgartner.
National Alumni
Vice Parliamentarian.
Beta Kappa Theta Sorority.
Guys. I'm undercover. Deep.
We should totally celebrate.
It's crazy. I have spent
the entire morning
planning a mixer!
And yesterday,
I went and I had
a Himalayan mani-pedi.
Yeah, at first it was just
to get the other girls
to talk,
but then I realized
my cuticles have been
completely taken for granted.
Jules, you realize that we
are the only ones that can
see or hear you.
Yeah, okay, I admit.
I've been undercover a
week now, and it's really hard
to get out of this mindset.
These girls, they are demons.
They are vicious little
prairie dogs with trust funds
and collagen parties.
It's a lot to juggle
and I need a favor.
Okay.
I've been at the university
investigating the death of
a coed, Doreen Harthan.
The girl they found
at Wispy Sunny Pines.
Wasn't that a suicide?
Allegedly. A copycat job.
I guess Santa Barbara has some
sort of urban legend
about a mental patient who
jumped from room 413.
Scary Sherry.
We know that one.
Yeah, well, I'm not so sure
about the suicide angle
and Interim Chief Vick
is putting a tremendous
amount of faith in me
to crack this thing
and I need to build a case.
So I'm here,
but I'm not. Get it?
Gus, what's the word?
That'd be mum.
Doreen was pledging
a sorority.
And I, or, Mary Lou,
am helping my sisters through
this very difficult time.
I'm convinced they know more
than they're letting on.
I need a psychic to
read the sorority house.
Can you come by tonight?
Can we wear pajamas?
No.
Even better.
Guys, this is serious,
there's some really weird
stuff that's been going on.
The girls are petrified,
they think they're
being haunted.
By what?
Oh, come on, Jules.
You know we're gonna
come man up. Just tell us.
Doreen Harthan's
lumbering ghost.
Lumbering?
Seems completely
logical to me.
Meet me at the house at 7:00.
And remember,
I was never here.
Quick question.
Where's Lassiter
for all of this?
Temporary re-assignment.
Bye.
Excuse me, I'm gonna have to
ask you to vacate this room.
Excuse me, I'm gonna
have to ask you to go
screw yourself.
I beg your pardon?
Oh, don't beg.
Look, there's gonna be
a private meeting in
this room between myself
and a new detective
from a new department.
Well, then I must be
in the right place.
No, Ma'am,
I'm looking for a rookie.
What the hell does that mean?
You know, bright-eyed,
bushy-tailed, roots matching
the rest of the hair.
I'm a detective. Goochberg.
Gooch to people I respect.
And those few lucky enough
to have seen me naked.
Guess which one
you should use?
God, the first one?
I'm sorry, how can you
possibly be a rookie at your,
you know, advanced age?
I passed the test Friday.
I had to sue the department
to let me take it again.
Again?
I might have failed it.
A few times.
Thirteen to be exact.
But that's the first thing
you're gonna learn
about me, scarecrow,
the word "quit"
is not in my vocabulary.
Where do you go to
shoot guns around here?
(SNIFFING)
I see a man.
He's driving your car.
You don't know him.
He's a valet.
And a mall.
Wait, I see a shoe store.
Your father's gold card.
A Jamba Juice
may have been involved?
Oh, my God.
I totally went shopping today.
(ALL GASPING)
I passed by a Jamba
on State Street.
You are amazing.
See, Bianca?
Now tell Shawn what
happened to you last night.
Okay, here goes.
This is so scary.
I was lying in bed,
watching One Tree Hill,
my favorite show,
Chad Michael Murray
is so hot.
And I have this cute liquid
kitty alarm clock, right?
It meows and it blinks
its eyes every half hour.
So, all of a sudden,
they just started
blinking over and
over and over
and then it
just stopped.
And then, it let out
this half-meow.
(MEOWS)
And then its tail fell off.
Then it exploded.
Wow.
Slow build.
Half meow, unexpected.
Didn't see the end
coming at all.
How about you, Gus?
What?
No, I can't say I did.
Anybody else?
(ALL CHATTERING)
Okay, so basically it's a lot
of really weird stuff that's
creepy and happens at night.
Mr. Spencer is it?
Yes, that's correct Mrs...
(MUMBLING)
Baumgartner.
Now, what I'm going to need
from you,
is an article of clothing.
Preferably an undergarment.
Don't you usually
get that from the victim?
I've seen it both ways.
I'm gonna have to take a look
around to see what I feel.
Starting with the bedrooms.
Of course.
I'll show you upstairs.
Ask him.
You ask him.
What? What do you
wanna ask me, girls?
Don't be nervous.
I put my pants on one leg
at a time, just like you.
Okay. Did you really play
Bud on The Cosby Show?
Bud? Who told you that?
BIANCA:
I knew I recognized you!
Wait, wait I'm not...
Oh, come-on,
don't be modest, Gus.
You are totally Bud!
Shawn, you believe this?
No, no, no,
I didn't catch anything, Bud.
Stop telling people
that my name is Bud.
(GIRLS GASP)
SCARY VOICE: Get out!
Ackenaib! Ackenaib!
Ackenaib!
(GIRLS GASPING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(CAR LOCK BEEPING)
Shawn!
Where are you going!
My partner and I just
need to confer in private.
Compare notes and what not.
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
Okay. The girls are sleeping
over at the Omega Muse.
Well, they can come home
tomorrow, I found the
evil spirit, it's Radio Shack.
The face at the window,
the old flood light
on the roof trick.
That's how they do it
at Haunted Mansion.
Don't ask me how I know that.
These girls are awful. The
suspect list is essentially
the entire student registry.
Although...
Although what?
Alice Bundy.
Doreen's best friend,
her roommate.
Thought you said
she lived at home.
The Harthan's
took Alice in.
She's the only one that
I haven't talked to, but
conventional wisdom would say,
she has a score to settle.
Holy Shitzu!
Excuse me?
This new polish is already
starting to chip!
You know, you might actually
hit the target more
if you bothered to blink
in between rounds.
And of course your
concentration level might
get a little boost
if you bothered
to wear protective
ear and eyewear.
That wouldn't do any good,
I'm totally deaf in this ear.
It was in a bar room fight
with a teamster.
She had a waffle iron.
But see,
that's not the problem.
The problem is
this pea-shooter.
This pea-shooter
they issued me.
I need a real gun.
I need something like this.
Let me see this.
No!
Oh, see now, this is a gun.
No, you see, that's an
enormously powerful handgun.
You're not bracing
yourself for the kickback.
Don't tell me
my business, kid.
Trust me, you won't
even recognize yourself.
Which is a
really good thing.
It will be fun, and you can
help save the endangered
tamarind monkeys.
Bianca, you have like
twice as many flyers
as me and Mary Lou.
What's going on with you?
Are you like pregnant
or something?
Can you shut up for like
five seconds, Betty?
Oh, my God, you are being
such a horrid little bitch
right now.
How can you just...
Aren't you scared?
I haven't slept at all,
I feel like I'm losing...
Suck it up. End of story.
I will not go down
with you, Bianca.
Alice Bundy? Hi.
I'm Mary Lou Baumgartner.
Beta Kappa Theta
West Coast Alumni...
Save it,
I already hate you.
...Vice Parliamentarian.
Oh. Well.
I know you were Doreen's
best friend and I just
wanted to introduce myself
and tell you that
if there's anything that
I or Beta Kappa Theta
can do for you during
this very difficult time,
please don't hesitate to ask.
How does it feel being
Queen of the Damned?
Alice, I'm sure I don't know
what you mean.
Just stay away from me.
Fair warning.
Ew! Hair.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
I'm riding in the back.
No, you're not.
I'm not gonna take
a stray bullet for you,
scarecrow.
Look, even if I wanted
to sit in the front,
it's not gonna happen.
My eyes can't take that
kind of direct sunlight.
My rods and cones
are all out of whack.
I took a crowbar to an
eye socket during a
sangria party gone wrong.
Long story short,
I've got early onset
retinitis pigmentosa.
Hey buddy, good news.
I just got a fax confirming
that the city of Santa Barbara
has unanimously voted you
Exorcist of the year.
Okay, make all
your little jokes.
But I know who's
right on my ass
all the way to the car.
I had no choice.
You were my ride home.
Shawn, you were screaming too.
Yes, I was screaming,
"Gus, stop, let's be brave."
Look, both the parents and
the best friend were adamant
that Doreen had too much
to live for to kill herself.
Plus, she was pledging
a sorority.
Right.
Now, take another
look at this.
The latch is broken.
And she fell backwards.
Scary Sherry
took a swan dive.
Exactly.
Gus, you are on fire.
Thank you.
The copy cat suicide angle
literally goes out the window.
What next?
I couldn't find the word
"Ackenaib" anywhere.
I checked alternate spellings,
all possible roots,
nothing in Latin.
So now I'm going through the
dead languages by region.
Sanskrit was a wash,
as was Avestan.
Up next is
Old Church Slavonic,
but to be honest
I think it's all just
nonsensical gibberish.
But it's gotta mean something.
The voice in the house
kept repeating it.
(IMITATING GHOST) Ackenaib.
Ackenaib. Ackenaib.
What's Juliet's number?
I have a theory.
What's the theory?
Gus, just feed me the digits.
Why do I always have to ask
what the damn theory is,
Shawn?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
SHAWN: Is Bianca with you?
Who wants to know?
Jules, where is she?
Okay, tone.
She's back at the house
with Betty, running late
for the mixer. Just like me.
All right, listen,
I've had a vision.
We need to meet
at the sorority house
on the fly.
Shawn, I can't.
I have to make
the spirit speech
and who's gonna fuse
the planter's punch?
Oh, yeah, by the way,
I met Alice Bundy today.
She's not a shiny
happy person.
I think...
Jules!
Doreen didn't kill herself.
She was not alone
in that room.
And we need to talk
to Bianca right now!
She's in danger!
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Bianca! What are you
doing in there?
We're gonna be totally late
for Mary Lou's speech
and we're supposed
to lead the slow clap.
Just go without me.
You don't have to wait.
Okay. This is ridiculous.
Just open the door.
I'm coming in there.
I'm not going
to the mixer, Betty.
Even if I wanted to,
my fingers and toes
are all pruney now.
BETTY: Ew!
Bianca, open the door.
This is completely ridiculous.
(SCREAMING)
(ELECTROSTATIC BUZZING)
Hello?
Mary Lou!
It's Bianca! Help!
Jules?
Betty, if you know something
you have to tell
the chief here.
We're all in danger.
Any one of us could be next.
I can sit here
all night, Betty.
I've got six month old
who still has colic,
I consider this a reprieve.
Now, why is your friend
Bianca dead?
I can see it.
I can see you running down
the hallway at the asylum.
Wait a second.
Doreen wasn't
supposed to die.
This was an accident.
The wood was rotten
and the latch broke!
BETTY: Yes, yes! It broke!
Don't you see we never
meant for her to fall.
It was a complete accident!
Oh, my God, Bianca,
what the hell did you do?
(GASPING)
Please, do continue.
It was my job to get Doreen
into the house.
She knew that it was a haze.
She thought that she was
supposed to spend
the whole night inside.
Like that movie
with the hedge maze
and Vincent Van Patten?
Hell Night.
Exactly.
Bianca was inside
wearing this nightgown,
you know, like Scary Sherry,
the girl who jumped from...
We know.
Nightgown. Nightgown.
I'm feeling the nightgown.
Put it in.
BETTY: Bianca buried it in
the tar pits three nights ago.
Tar pits?
I know. It was really
gross and sticky.
But, she was just scared.
We both were.
Look, it was an accident,
I swear to God.
Bianca tried to grab her arm
but it was too late.
Nobody was supposed to die.
Now Bianca's gone, too.
You withheld evidence.
And by conspiring with Bianca
we can charge you with
involuntary manslaughter.
You understand that's a crime?
I know!
No!
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
You actually
slept here last night?
Yes, I did,
it's called crunch time.
Have you checked the messages?
Have we heard from Juliet?
Yeah. Alice Bundy's alibi
is airtight.
She lives with
Doreen's family.
Said she went upstairs
to bed early that night
and the parents confirmed it,
they were still downstairs
awake when the police called.
Who the hell's doing this?
Oh. And your dad called.
What could he possibly want?
Said he wanted to remind you
about dinner tonight.
You're supposed
to bring dessert.
He actually seemed
sort of excited.
Oh, God, that's tonight.
Dude, you have to come.
Oh, I don't know
about that, Shawn.
It seems like
a pretty big deal,
him reaching out and all.
I wouldn't want to intrude.
Gus, he loves you.
He always has.
Plus, if you come
we can roll earlier.
We'll say we're
working on a case.
We are working on a case.
Sweet. So, it's settled.
What are you doing?
I have to start and
ultimately finish my route.
Awesome.
I'm going to find
Alice "best friend" Bundy.
Don't you think that girl has
been through enough, Shawn?
Gus, there is no such thing
as an air tight alibi.
And if there is, we're going
to pretend like there isn't.
This girl is Sharon Stone
from Basic Instinct.
Which makes me Michael Douglas
and you George Dzundza.
Who's name is
actually Gus in the film.
Until we have another lead,
we assume it's her.
We've just got to
figure out the "how."
So far, no ice pick.
First of all, don't ever
compare my black ass
to George Dzundza again, okay?
Fair.
And what can you
possibly ask that girl
that the police
already haven't?
Wanna split a pineapple?
I'm sorry, do I know you?
My name is Ichibod Fletchman.
Sticky Icky to my boys. But
that's neither here nor there.
What's important is that
this baby is 82% Hawaiian
and I've got all afternoon.
Are you a crazy person?
It's funny I was about
to ask you the same thing.
Only I was going to add
"who likes to make toast"
to the end of mine.
Great. So you're
another cop then?
Not a cop.
Not even close.
Then who are you?
Hint. Green Day there
is about to eat some stone.
How did you do that?
I'm a psychic.
Pass.
Oh, come on.
I was trying to be cool.
What do you want from me?
You want to read my palm?
You want a lock of hair?
Alice.
I can feel that
you're hurting.
Really?
Can you feel that I'm hurting?
Come on, psychic,
you can do better than that.
Can't you?
Do you have a best friend?
I do.
Since birth, almost.
Great.
Then maybe you can
wrap your head around this.
Doreen and I
were closer than sisters.
Her parents took me in
when I was seven.
Seven. They raised me.
We did everything together.
The one time I wasn't there,
the one time I let her down,
and now she's gone.
I know that if anything
ever happened to Gus...
I would... I don't know.
(STUTTERING)
Look, do you really think
I killed that girl?
Do you?
I understand your suspicion,
but I'm barely
hanging on here,
and I just don't think that...
I'm not a murderer.
Well, I certainly hope not
for your sake.
Someone came in
and emptied the cash register
when I was in the back.
You're not writing this down?
Who's got
the arthritic thumb here?
I hitchhiked from Jersey
to Havana when I was 19.
(MUMBLING)
They also got away
with about $60 worth
of rump roast.
Don't try to sell me
on that nonsense, you punk.
What? You think this is
my first square dance?
(GRUNTING)
Give me your gun, Lassiter.
I'll show you how to
make this little pig squeal.
You just gonna let him go?
He's the victim, Goochberg!
Fine. Fine.
I'll do it myself.
Mary Lou, wait!
I totally almost forgot
to give this to you.
What is it, Eden?
I don't know.
It was left on the stoop
like a little baby orphan.
"God's gift is forgiveness.
"Please join us
in remembering our daughter.
"Your attendance
would be greatly appreciated."
Tonight? Hello! Plans.
Bye.
Boy, we really
should be going.
Come on, guys. Shawn, stay.
Your case will still be there.
The sooner we can crack
this case and move on
the better. Believe me.
This wouldn't have
anything to do
with the
Wispy Sunny Pines suicide
now, would it?
No.
Yes, sir.
(EXCLAIMING)
Ooh, the plot thickens.
Okay. It's true, fine.
And it hits
a little close to home
seeing as how we were there
the first time it happened.
First time what happened?
Did you open your eyes?
Dad, you've known me
my whole life.
Of course, I opened my eyes.
Shawn, that is why
I used to refuse to let you
ride around with me.
Dad, let it go, I was nine.
It's a lack of respect.
Of protocol.
Of protocol?
Again, can I plead
nine years old?
And you guys
have been freaked out
about this your entire lives?
I don't even drive
by that place.
I really don't think
it's funny.
It was a very scary thing
for two young boys.
It certainly puts a new spin
on the nanny in The Omen.
You know that's right.
Shawn, how much did you see?
I didn't exactly see it.
Luckily, he missed
the bitter, grisly end.
Luckily?
Yes, luckily.
I covered his eyes
but we know what happened.
Oh, I beg to differ.
It seems you two missed
one very small
but important detail.
She never jumped.
What? No.
No, that's impossible.
We saw the window,
she was gone.
Yeah. Because one off-duty
police officer
pulled her back inside.
Scary Sherry Craddock
was rehabilitated.
I'm pretty sure
she's married
and lives in Fresno.
Come on, guys,
give me some credit.
I have no idea how that
ridiculous urban legend got
started in the first place.
Your big ass mouth.
I wanted to keep it a secret.
You're the one
who was broadcasting it
at the lunch table.
I can't believe this.
We actually started
an urban legend.
That's dope.
Sometimes, Shawn,
the answer is
right in front of your eyes.
You just need to choose
to see it.
That was creepy.
SHAWN: This is it.
Alice's house.
I know there's something here,
I just got to find it.
Here's the plan.
You ring the doorbell
and distract who...
Who...
Whom... Who...
The person.
The person that answers
the door.
I go around back
and look for a way in.
Are you kidding?
It took you the whole ride
to come up with that?
Feel free to make revisions.
How am I supposed
to distract them?
You'll think of something.
Good luck.
We're all counting on you.
(DOORBELL RINGING)
Mrs. Harthan?
No.
The Harthans are down
at the cemetery.
I'm Poppy, the housekeeper.
May I help you?
Yes.
Have you seen Mrs. Pickles?
Mrs. Pickles?
Mrs. Pickles.
My Orange Tabby!
You must have
seen her before.
She's pregnant with who knows
how many unborn Tabby kittens
and I've lost her.
(SIGHS)
You know that growing up
in Edinburgh,
my sisters and I
had a basset hound
who used to
hoot like a snowy owl.
No kidding.
What was his name?
We called him Basset Hound.
Although my sister,
she always used called him
Uncle Jimmy.
I never knew why.
Mrs. Pickles!
Here. Your Mrs. Pickles
will come back
to you, D'Andre.
ALICE: Doreen and I
were closer than sisters.
(MOBILE PHONE BEEPING)
What in heaven's that?
I've got to
set this thing on vibrate.
I'm sorry, who is this?
Shawn, it's Eden!
Who?
From Beta Kappa Theta.
Are you coming to our party
or what the heck?
There are cops here
and everything.
Let me talk to Mary Lou.
Mary Lou had to go to some
candlelight vigil thingy
for Doreen.
Vigil? What vigil?
There...
Yeah, at that creepy
Wispy Sunny Pines' place.
Bianca buried it
at the tar pits
three nights ago.
What about Bud?
Can he come?
Has anyone ever told you
that you look like little Bud
from the old Cosby Show?
Yes, ma'am.
But I was not Bud.
(MOBILE PHONE BEEPING)
Hello?
You bet.
It's her.
Who?
Mrs. Pickles. She's home.
I believe it was...
It was her.
And I've got the how.
We have to go to
Wispy Sunny Pines.
What?
No, no. You said go to
the sorority house.
The girls are fine.
The cops are there.
Meanwhile, Juliet's at
some candlelight vigil
with Doreen's family
at the asylum.
Wait. No, no.
The housekeeper said
Doreen's parents
were at the cemetery.
What?
Oh, God!
Of course. Why mess around
with the worker bees
when you can kill the queen?
What are you
talking about, Shawn?
Gus, Alice.
She wanted
us all at that party,
including us,
so that she could get
Mary Lou by herself.
This is Silence of the Lambs!
Which means
we're both Scott Glen.
Okay, Shawn, listen to me.
If I'm gonna go back to
that creepy ass institution
that I've been afraid
to drive by
since I was nine,
there are going to be
some rules and regulations.
Gus, this is no time for...
Listen, Shawn.
I will not enter a room first.
I will not enter a room last.
I will not investigate
any suspicious noises
or go looking for a fuse box.
And you will not,
under any circumstances,
leave me by myself
without a weapon of some sort.
Do you understand
and agree to my terms?
I'm not prepared to negotiate.
Do you understand, Shawn?
Yes! I do! Yes!
All right.
Let's go help Juliet.
(BEEPING)
(WOMAN CHATTERING ON PA)
Scarecrow, did we get him?
No. No.
Of course, we didn't get him.
Your little pursuit
sort of ended when you had
a mild cardiac arrest.
When were you gonna tell me
about the pacemaker?
And how dare
you try and scale a fence
in high heels?
He was the victim,
Goochberg.
But did we get him?
Yeah.
Yeah, we got him, Goochberg.
(MOBILE PHONE BEEPING)
Lassiter. Spencer?
You realize
you are the second last
human person
on this planet
I want to be speaking to
right now.
(SIGHS)
Call for backup, O'Hara.
Just make the call.
Better safe than sorry.
(MOBILE PHONE BEEPING)
(STUTTERING)
Mary Lou. We're over here.
I have to say
I'm a little shocked
to see you here.
Where's everyone else?
Upstairs.
They're waiting for you.
I told them
you probably wouldn't show.
Maybe you misjudged me.
Maybe I did.
Follow me.
Wow!
This must have taken hours.
I mean,
this is really extensive,
candle-wise.
The whole family
is waiting in room 413.
Okay.
Alice, what the hell is this?
Welcome to the party,
Mary Lou.
It's a banquet
fit for a queen!
(GRUNTING)
Alice, you do not wanna
do this. Give me the axe.
I'm not who you think I am.
No. You're exactly
who I think you are.
You're the reason
girls vomit and
starve themselves to death.
And you're the reason
that they fill themselves
with plastic.
And you are the reason
that Doreen is dead.
And so now,
on behalf of the entire suit
of the broken hearts,
Alice will now lop off
the Queen's head.
(LAUGHING)
That just sounded
so much better out loud
than it did in my head.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Lassie, our timing
is really starting to crackle.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(MARY LOU SCREAMING)
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
We made a deal, Shawn!
Thank you.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Get it out! Get it out!
Pull your foot
out of the shoe!
I can't! It's too tight!
Don't leave me, Shawn!
That was rule number five!
Loosen your big toe?
I can't move my big toe.
What?
Work the laces!
Shawn, Shawn! Shawn!
(MAN GRO ANING)
O' Hara!
Juliet!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
(GROANING)
That is it!
Now you die for sure!
I don't think so.
You are under arrest,
you crazy, crazy, crazy,
crazy bitch!
Detective!
Juliet!
Hey.
I got it.
What in the hell happened
in there?
She's crazy!
Look, she's possessed.
You have to believe me.
O'Hara?
You're asking me?
I though I was coming to
a candlelight vigil.
I thought I was coming
to pay my condolences.
Apparently
that wasn't the case.
Ow!
Give me that.
What would
you have done, Shawn?
If it was your best friend?
What would you have done?
Oh, no. Gus.
(SOBBING)
(MAN GRO ANING)
Shawn, come get me
out of here!
This is not funny, Shawn!
Did I upset you?
Upset me?
Insult you?
Demean you in some way
that I did not comprehend?
Detective, I am pretty sure
I have no idea
what you are talking about.
The woman.
The crazy woman.
The half-deaf litigating
nightmare express
of a detective.
Why would you put me,
of all people, with her?
I'm head detective.
Honestly, detective,
I thought
you two might hit it off.
Why would you
possibly think that?
She kinda reminded me
a little of you.
You know,
a few years down the road.
Similar interests. Outlooks.
Everyone thought
it was a good idea.
That's how people perceive me?
We're all surprised
it didn't work out, Carlton.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
GUS: (LAUGHING)
You sick mother...
SHAWN:
Dude, we could hear you
from the fourth floor.
GUS: Don't lie! Don't lie!
GUS: Hey, Lassie.
In between the lines
there's a lot of obscurity
I'm not inclined
to resign to maturity
If it's all right
then you're all wrong
But why bounce around
to the same damn song?
You'd rather run
when you can't crawl
I know, you know
That I'm not telling the truth
They just don't have any proof
Embrace the deception
Learn how to bend
Your worst inhibitions
tend to psych you out
in the end
I know, you know