Previously on Heroes...
Ordinary people across the globe,
discovered extraordinary habilities.
A single mother lost her son
and gives into her dark side,
to save him.
I did what had to be done.
Like I always do.
A new hero is discovered.
I remember lots and lots, it's just,
something that my brain starts to do.
But meets a tragic fate.
And another hero
goes back in time to rescue her.
Peter solves the mystery of his destiny.
The cheerleader.
We're all trying to help her.
And her father will stop at nothing
to avert catastrophy.
This girl, the one you've painted here,
she's my daughter.
This man here, he's gonna kill her
tomorrow night at her homecoming game.
I need you to paint this painting.
Tonight, their destinies will unite them
to save the cheerleader
and save the world.
We are, if anything,
creatures of habit...
drawn to the safety and comfort
of the familiar.
Do they actually believe
that pudding is a vegetable?
But what happens
when the familiar becomes unsafe?
When the fear that we have been
desperately trying to avoid
finds us where we live?
Something wrong?
Jackie just killed my appetite.
Oh, the principal's gonna post
the homecoming queen announcement.
Well,
aren't you gonna go see if you won?
- What's the point?
- You're a finalist, Claire. Go.
Good luck.
Kinda nervy for someone in your position
to be running for homecoming queen.
My position?
You know. Pariah?
You hospitalized the MVP,
annihilating any hope of us
actually winning the game.
You're not deluded enough
to think you're actually gonna win?
No delusions. It's a popularity contest,
and you've made it very clear
that I am no longer popular.
It's more than a popularity contest.
Being selected homecoming queen
is about serving your school.
God, Claire...
I didn't think you were that shallow.
Congratulations, ladies.
Make me proud.
Oh, my God, don't spaz out.
What?
I can't believe it.
I won?
Shut up, you freaks!
You didn't tell Peter about me
buying this painting, did you?
You asked me not to.
I don't get it. What is it?
It's one of a series,
the work of Isaac Mendez,
a rising artist.
Peter believes
Isaac can paint the future.
Is it supposed to be Peter?
I'm not sure.
But Peter thinks he needs to be there
to save a cheerleader.
Union Wells High School.
Peter thinks
if he saves a cheerleader...
he'll save the world.
Right.
Is that the only copy?
Why?
Peter's got all these...
ideas in his head.
Delusions of grandeur.
He thinks he's supposed
to make a difference.
What are you doing?
Saving his life.
What?
You believe it?
Save the cheerleader, save the world?
I'm not sure what to believe anymore.
I am.
Nice!
What's the range on this?
The Kinsella 320Z,
been known
to pierce body armor at 400 yards.
Military grade.
That'll work.
Don't want to see his eyes, huh?
Must really hate the guy.
You have no idea.
He took my son.
Damn.
You call the cops?
Cops can't stop him.
But I can,
as long as he doesn't see it coming.
How much?
Two large.
We're going hunting.
Capture: FRM@FadeOut - Presync:FRM@Linda
Subtitles: www.sub-way.fr
So how long do you plan
on keeping this up?
Till you turn around.
I told you, we can't go back!
And I told you mom needs me.
It's not safe with her.
I still love her.
No matter what she does,
a part of me always will.
But your mom has changed.
The good news...
is that it's gonna be you and me
from here on out.
Partners.
You mean, like Batman and Robin?
Yeah. Like Batman and Robin.
Only... I ain't wearing no tights.
You could wear tights.
I'm not wearing tights.
Need to hit the head?
Nah, I'm good.
Did you ever consider that these dreams
that you've been having,
are just that, dreams?
It's impossible.
They were talking
about my sister Shanti,
a sister I never knew I had!
As children,
we absorb powerful archetypes
that we bury in our subconscious.
Your parents were obviously
still grieving over your sister.
Freud would tell you the same thing.
What about the boy?
The one with the soccer ball?
Yes, how do you explain
his picture being hidden
in my father's desk, huh?
He was one of them,
right here in Chennai.
Sanjog Lyer, my father identified
the genetic marker.
It says the boy can enter your dreams,
alter your perceptions,
a kind of spirit guide.
- You must have seen that file before.
- I have never seen this file before,
and I have had
thousands of dreams in my life.
These were different.
They were... They were real.
We have to find this boy.
Hey, what was so important
you had me meet you over here?
That painting you wanted,
Nathan bought it from Linderman,
had it shipped here.
It's here... Can I see it?
There.
I don't understand.
He said it was to protect you,
that you're gonna get yourself killed.
Okay, wait a minute.
You saw this painting, all right?
You can describe it to me.
You really believe this, don't you?
Save the cheerleader, save the world.
For reasons
I can't begin to understand...
there are people
that are counting on me to do this.
I don't know if I can,
but I have to try.
This doesn't make any sense.
I probably
shouldn't be showing you this.
It's a digital image,
it came with the painting.
Is that you, Peter?
I don't know.
Maybe.
If it's you, then you're gonna die...
at 8:12 tonight.
- Don't go, Peter.
- I have to.
I have to.
Union Wells High School
is in Odessa, Texas.
I took the liberty
and made a phone call.
Homecoming is tonight.
Thank you.
Look, I don't know
if this is gonna happen.
Just come back, okay?
I will.
Hi, this is Peter Petrelli,
is this Hiro Nakamura?
No. Ah, he will be right back.
- Who is this?
- I'm his friend, Ando.
Ando, right.
Okay, this is very important.
You and Hiro
need to get to Odessa, Texas,
as soon as you can,
Union Wells High School.
Okay? That's where the cheerleader is.
We are in Texas already.
Midland, at the Burnt Toast Café.
It's outside the airport.
You are? That's great!
Listen, I'm gonna get on a flight,
tell Hiro that I'll be there
before he knows it.
Yes, okay.
I will tell him.
Good-bye, Peter Petrelli.
It's gonna be okay, honey.
It's useless.
How is that supposed
to help me find Sylar?
He's not a vending machine.
You can't just put the drugs in,
pull a lever,
and expect a clear response.
He's a person.
Your emotions
are impairing your judgment.
Maybe, but I'm not the only one.
When he wakes up,
have him paint another.
You think I'm being emotional?
Do you have any idea
what we're up against?
Come here.
Oh, my God.
Sylar wants to do that to my Claire.
I will do whatever I have
to do to stop it.
Isaac can't help us.
It was a mistake to do that to him.
Go to the high school.
Use the paintings as a guide.
Wait for Sylar.
You'll have help.
When the time is right, neutralize him.
I'll keep Claire safe at home.
No, it's homecoming.
Find Sylar, take him out.
And let me worry about Claire.
Congratulations, Claire.
Thanks so much!
I don't know that girl.
Holla to the queen!
Holla back!
Everybody who wasn't my friend
is now my friend,
and everybody who was my friend, isn't.
Well, it's not a popularity contest,
it's an unpopularity contest
'cause you rocked the freak vote.
I what?
Look, everybody who's like Jackie
voted for Jackie, and everybody
who isn't voted for you.
And in this school, the unpopular
vastly outnumber the popular.
Made for a good campaign strategy.
You campaigned for me?
Why?
You think all this school spirit stuff
is stupid.
I never said it was stupid.
I said it's beneath you.
But obviously it's important,
so whatever.
Now you have a little piece
of your old life back, okay?
Just don't start acting
like a bitch again.
Look, I got this off of the Internet.
It supposedly has
this really big chapter
on spontaneous regeneration,
so I thought it might
enlighten you
on the whole Miracle-gro of it all.
What's with you?
You're being so nice.
I've never been this nice to you.
I mean, I've been nice,
but I could be nicer.
Then why don't you?
Congratulations, Claire.
Is the gay boy your date?
You should tell him,
only one of you gets to wear the tiara.
What? That is so unfair!
- Hon?
- I've already made up my mind.
You are being completely unreasonable.
Do you have any idea
what it means for me
to miss this game?
You'll survive.
- But dad!
- No, you listen, and you listen good.
As long as you live under my roof,
you will do as I say.
You may not agree, but don't think
for a moment that that matters.
You are not leaving this house tonight.
Is that clear?
Crystal.
She's gonna hate you
for a long time on this one.
Let's hope so.
What were you thinking?
Do you know how scared I was?
Now you know
how it felt when you left us!
Micah, what am I supposed to do here?
Go back! She needs us!
We've discussed this.
- Your mom...
- Dad, I know she's different, okay?
I see it too.
Something happened to her when you left.
It got really bad.
Then, sometimes,
she'd show up instead of mom.
She?
Jessica.
Dad, mom's sick.
She can't help herself.
She can't control it.
Does your mom know about Jessica?
No, I don't think so.
Dad, we can't just leave her.
If you still love her, you'll help her.
You're right.
Do you know this boy?
You're wasting my afternoon
because of a ridiculous dream.
No one said you had to come.
And who's gonna keep you
from getting killed?
This is a dangerous neighborhood.
One look at your fancy shoes
and we'll be running for our lives.
Have you seen this boy?
Come now, Mohinder.
Let's stop this nonsense.
Go back to the university,
talk about this like rational people.
I am not leaving until I find him.
I know this boy.
For 500 rupees,
I can tell you where he is.
This man is a crook, give him nothing.
What are you doing?
Where?
You came to me in my dream last night.
I don't come to anyone.
They come to me.
Why?
Why do they come to you?
They have questions that need answers.
I'm not sure that I have a question.
Yes, you do.
I have two paths in front of me.
I need to know which one to take.
Which one is my destiny.
You already have the answer you seek.
What is it?
What's my answer?
Excuse me.
When was this picture taken?
Oh, that was Charlie's birthday.
About six months ago.
Do you know him?
Hiro? Sure.
He and Charlie were tight.
Please, where is he now?
I have no idea, darlin'.
He popped out of her life weeks ago.
What's going on?
I'm here to rescue you.
- Let's go.
- I'm grounded.
No one grounds the queen, come on.
Yeah, tell that to my dad.
You only get
to be homecoming queen once.
You know what?
You've already cemented your victory
in the eyes of the student body
by punching Jackie.
Plus, if you back out now,
she becomes the queen.
My dad would pitch a fit.
So, big deal. What? He grounds you more.
He double grounds you.
Come on, you deserve this.
I do deserve this.
And tonight,
you can be my date to the dance.
- Me?
- Sure, why not?
For a million different reasons.
Is it about what Jackie said?
Because I don't care...
I don't care about that,
you think I care about that?
She can call me whatever she wants.
I'm not gonna be embarrassed by it.
I know who I am.
I like who I am.
I like who you are. I just...
I just wish that you liked who you are.
I'm finally realizing
who my friends really are.
And that maybe being different
isn't the end of the world.
That's just who I am.
Exactly,
you gotta embrace your inner freak.
Because the only thing
that you'll regret
is denying who you really are.
Ando?
Hey, I'm Peter Petrelli.
How are you?
So sorry it took forever.
I couldn't get a flight,
and then taxis in this town...
We still have time. Where's Hiro?
Hiro traveled back in time
to rescue Charlie.
I told him it wasn't a good idea,
Peter Petrelli might call,
but he insisted.
What happened to her?
She was killed.
We were sitting right here.
It happened so fast.
Next thing we know, she was dead
and the killer was gone in a flash.
Like, Okage.
Boogeyman.
Hiro says maybe it is the same man
that is going to attack the cheerleader.
I told Hiro, do over, is too risky.
But Hiro says
man who is too afraid to use power,
does not deserve to have power.
I know when, and I know where
the cheerleader gets attacked.
I have to stop him.
Is this you?
Maybe.
- You have a power, right?
- Sort of.
Super strength?
You bend time and space like Hiro!
No, I... I kind of
absorb the abilities of others.
But only when they're close.
Truthfully,
when I'm by myself, I don't...
I'm not really anything.
I've got less than an hour.
Okay, it happens at 8:12, I have to go.
Coming?
I will wait for Hiro.
Without him,
I'm not really anything either.
Maybe you should wait too.
There's no time.
I have to save the cheerleader.
But, Peter!
You die.
Where is she? She's gone!
Oh, right.
I saw her and Zach skip out
across the lawn ten minutes ago.
She must have climbed out her window.
Why didn't you try to stop her?
Because she's a good girl,
and she deserves this.
You are being way too harsh.
You don't know what you've done.
If you hear from her,
call me immediately!
You're wasting your time.
Freud would tell you
the boy is merely a manifestation
of your subconscious.
Nirad?
Haven't we already had
this conversation?
No, wait!
You're wasting your time.
Freud would tell you
that the boy's merely
a manifestation of your subconscious.
It was more than a dream, it was real.
This boy can give me the answers I seek.
I'm your friend, Chandra,
but you sound like a madman.
Well, all great thinkers
were said to be madmen
in their time...
Darwin, Einstein, Gandhi.
Darwin was not ridiculed
by his university's
biology round table.
They weren't even listening.
You're the one who's not listening!
You think you're actually
gonna find these people?
Levitation, spontaneous regeneration?
Chandra, I know that Shanti's death
drove you to find answers,
but it is time to let go.
If you persist on espousing
this insanity in your writing
and in your classroom,
they will strip you of your tenure.
So be it.
I just finished reading.
It's fantastic, Father.
To think that today, all around us,
the evolutionary process
continues so dramatically!
Who told you to read this?
No one, I saw it on your desk,
so I picked it up.
You invaded my privacy, Mohinder.
This was not for you to read.
Well, I'm sorry, but I think
it's extraordinary, and I want to help.
By using the Human Genome Project,
- we can locate these people.
- Not "we"!
You can't be part of this.
- Why not?
- Because I don't want you to be!
I don't understand.
Darwin said a scientific man
ought to have no wishes,
no affections, a heart of stone.
That's me, Mohinder.
It's not you.
Go home.
You have your answer.
You were trying to protect me.
Heart of stone.
Why did you have a heart of stone?
My sister.
You found them.
- Sorry!
- Sorry.
That was my fault.
I wasn't looking where I was going.
Hey, do you... do you know this girl,
Jackie Wilcox?
Yeah, half-time show starts
in about five minutes.
She'll be out on the field.
She's a cheerleader.
Are you a reporter or something?
Alumni.
I'm just curious.
You know, between you and me,
she's not that special.
Just your average teenage girl.
She rushed into a fire
and saved a man's life,
sounds kinda special to me.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm jealous.
She's our town hero.
Me? I don't win
too many popularity contests.
Hey, it gets better!
What?
Life after high school.
It gets a lot better.
Half-time, girls!
Come on, pump it up!
Will the nerviness never cease.
I thought you were grounded.
It didn't take.
How's your eye?
Nothing I can't cover up.
There's something I wanna say to you,
cocaptain to cocaptain.
Say it.
I think you're a menace.
And I'm not just talking about you
punching me
over your boyfriend, the girlfriend.
I'm talking about you in general.
We used to be BFF's.
What happened?
Maybe I've gained some perspective.
I'm tired of trying
to be someone I'm not.
Well, you've been trying
to be me since second grade.
And now you're trying to be me.
How do you figure?
Your little heroic act
of pulling the guy
out of the burning train car...
wasn't your heroic act, it was mine.
No, it wasn't.
I have it on tape.
You know, a good friend of mine
once said it's more important
to be honest with yourself
and happy than popular.
I think he got it right.
Really?
Sounds like a loser to me.
Public schools suck.
- Did you hear that?
- Hear what?
Stop it, you're freaking me out!
- I thought I heard something.
- You're imagining it. Let's go!
What is your problem?
Don't go that way.
- What the hell?
- Jackie, something's not right.
No, duh!
We're missing the coronation.
Believe me, if you don't want
to get that homecoming crown,
I'm more than happy...
Are you okay?
Run! Go!
Keep going! Run!
Oh, my God.
- Who is it?
- Go, to the stadium, okay?
Find people, find lights.
He doesn't want to be seen.
- What about you?
- Don't worry.
Just go!
Go!
You...
How did you...
Where is he?
I don't know.
He ran away before I got here.
Police. Go get some help, okay?
Okay. I'll be back.
What's your name?
Peter.
I'm Claire.
Are you the one?
By saving you, did I save the world?
I don't know.
I'm just a cheerleader.
Dad.
It's okay.
You're okay.
Dad, it was terrible,
Jackie, she...
I know, I know.
We have to go back.
We have to go back, Peter...
- No, no.
- He saved my life!
He'll be fine.
But we can't leave him.
We can't leave him.
He almost died, but then he...
He... we have to go back!
We have to go back!
The police'll take care of everything.
Look at you.
You're lucky to be alive.
It's not luck, Dad.
I have something I have to tell you.
You don't want to hurt me.
We just need to talk.
You can tell me all about yourself.
But first, go to sleep.
You need to sleep.
That's the guy!
He's the one in the overcoat
the janitor saw.
- Put your hands on your head!
- What the hell? Look at all that blood.
It's not what you think, guys!
All right, hands up.
What are you do... It's not me!
He's getting away!
Let's go! Stand up!
Mira called.
She said you turned down her job offer.
You're going back to New York?
He did it, you know.
He discovered them.
His theory, it was right.
And that is good news, yes?
Why didn't he tell me?
He wanted you to live your own life.
So now that you know about them,
what will you do?
Find them.
Tell them who they are,
if they don't already know.
Warn them of the dangers they face.
And who will protect you?
Next stop, Vegas.
Dad, we don't need to go back to Vegas.
Why not?
I called Mom.
I told her where we are.
She's on her way.
Micah, get in the car.
Now, come on!
Dad, what's wrong?
We are all, at our cores,
the sum of our fears.
To embrace destiny,
we must, inevitably,
face those fears and conquer them.
Whether they come from the familiar...
or the unknown.
My name is Hiro Nakamura!
I'm here to save your life!
Hey, Charlie!
Come over and blow out the candles!
Hold that thought, okay?
I gotta go make a wish.
www.1000fr.com www.sub-way.fr