you don't realize
how valued you are
here at the company.
you're part
of the family now.
(mohinder)
i'm in over my head.
as long as i'm alive,
you will be taken care of.
(caitlin)
peter!
this here's everything you had
on you when we found you.
your box or your life.
you gonna open it,
or what?
hiro nakamura, murdered.
angela petrelli, attacked.
this is my dad.
he may be the killer.
i'll find your father.
molly,
what's the apartment number?
nine.
nine. good girl.
get out of there
right now.
he sees me.
get out of there.
leave me alone! aah!
molly, please wake up.
(mohinder)
when confronted
by our worst nightmares,
the choices are few:
fight or flight.
we hope to find the strength
to stand against our fears.
but sometimes,
despite ourselves,
we run.
what if the nightmare
gives chase?
where can we hide then?
(parkman)
okay, when's she gonna wake up?
i don't know,
she's burning up.
all right, we gotta get her
to a hospital.
no hospital's equipped
to deal with this.
you really think my father
did this to her...
in her nightmare?
she used her ability
to find him for you,
and slipped into this.
she was so afraid.
i never should have asked her
to look for him.
no, you shouldn't have.
but now you know
where he is.
i can't just leave her
like this.
you have to.
if your father
did something to her,
you need to find out what
and how to end it.
you have an address
in philadelphia.
she even saw his door.
i haven't seen the man
in 25 years.
molly faced her worst nightmare
for you.
do the same for her.
find him.
i'll stay here with her.
i'll do everything i can.
i don't even know
what i'm dealing with.
why was he in that photo?
angela petrelli...
she knows him.
you're gonna be okay.
i promise.
i was about to lock up
when this guy showed up.
he--he pushed his way in,
shoved a gun in my face.
next thing i know
he's flying through that glass.
you hit an armed man?
i guess.
could've been a kick.
i don't know,
it all happened so fast.
is this the guy?
his name is lonny stills.
he's a local gangbanger.
he's already hit three other
fast food joints
in the area this month.
it fits his m.o.
like i said,
it's all a blur.
look, i know you don't want
to be a snitch.
it's dangerous.
but in order for me
to get this guy off the street,
i need somebody
to step up and i.d. him.
be a hero.
i'm sorry, i can't do that.
you know,
i can't help a neighborhood
that won't help itself.
you change your mind,
you give me a call.
(peter)
you closing up already?
it's the middle
of the afternoon.
i need a break.
i could get used
to this.
right, a guy who can
throw 1,000 volts
our of either hand...
settlingor everyday life
in a pub in cork.
i'm not sure it suits you.
why not?
peter, just because you don't
remember your past,
it doesn't mean
you don't have one.
aren you curious about
who you are,
or where you come from?
you've seen what i can do.
there's a side of me
that i can't control.
maybe it's best
if i don't dig too deep.
i know the kind of man
you are.
even if you don't.
there's only good in you.
and i bet whatever's
in that box
will tell you
the same thing.
weren't you the one
who didn't want me to look
in that box?
i only said that because
you hadn't kissed me yet.
now that you have,
you done with me?
mm...gettin' there.
after all,
a pretty boy like you,
there's bound to be someone
looking for you.
friends.
a girlfriend.
let 'em look.
like i told you,
you're not gonna find him
in there.
but you're sure
it was him?
yeah.
found him cuffed inside there
a few nights back.
poor sap.
didn't know
how he got there.
didn't even know
his own name.
do you know where
he is now?
depends.
who's askin'?
just me.
i work for a company
interested in keeping him
out of trouble.
peter is a...
dangerous guy.
ha. you don't have
to tell me that.
he's in town.
place called
wandering rocks pub.
hey, if he's so dangerous,
sweetheart,
why'd they send a little girl
like you in all alone?
i can take care
of myself.
bring her back
to holding.
what do you think
you're doing
interrogating my mother
without me there?
relax.
she didn't give me
anything.
of course she didn't give you
these people protect
each other.
my mother's not a killer.
i'm not gonna have her sit
in jail
for a crime
she didn't commit.
neither am i.
that's why i'm going
to philadelphia
to see my father,
figure this whole thing out.
let me come with you.
no! you're not a cop.
listen, i'm guessing this isn't
official police business.
so if i'm there, it won't
really make a difference.
because officially,
neither are you.
you don't understand.
it's molly.
my father did something to her.
she's in trouble.
what do you mean
"did something to her"?
come here.
did what?
he got inside her head
somehow.
i don't know how he did it,
but i think it's all connected.
to kaito.
to your mother.
it could be dangerous.
i can take care of myself.
listen,
i have to do this.
let me come with you.
fine.
we can probably
get therfaster.
you know,
'cause you can, uh...
i'm not a cargo jet,
parkman.
oh, please.
i need to talk to him.
alone.
tell him what you told me.
this american girl...
she's hitting all the boys
on the dock,
looking for a certain
shipping container.
she say what she wanted?
yeah.
you.
no worries, boyo.
i think i can help.
this is my problem.
not given what i just saw
between you and my sister.
you care about her,
don't you?
right now, she's
the only thing in my life
that means something.
caitlin has a flat
up the hill.
go there and stay
until i call you.
i'll take care
of your friend.
i could handle this
myself.
i don't doubt it.
i've seen what you can do.
but i've got an investment
in you now.
some little blonde's
isn't going to scare me off.
now go on.
and don't be telling caitlin
about any of this.
she'll only worry sick.
monica.
well?
well, what?
well, are you gonna tell me
what that was all about?
uh, i just didn't want
some crackhead
looking r revenge.
so i said
i didn't recognize him.
no, not that.
i'm talking about the whole
flying karate kick thing.
oh...that.
mr. lamont said
he has never seen
anything like it.
how did you do that?
more importantly,
why did you do that?
i don't know.
i don't know anything anymore.
nothing makes any sense.
well...where did you
learn how to...
i think--
i think on tv.
something is happening
to me, camille.
my body does things
before my brain even knows
what's happening.
that thing
with the tomatoes yesterday.
now this.
it's like...
like what?
i was supposed to be
somebo, camille.
the first person in my family
to go to college.
now look at me.
you know what,
never mind.
i've been here
since last night.
i'm just gonna go home
and sleep it off.
hey, monica.
everything's gonna be okay.
oh. okay?
yeah.
i hope so.
all right, this is it.
this is where molly said
we'd find him.
what are you planning,
exactly?
i'm not sure.
you're not sure?
he traumatized your girl.
has my mother terrified.
you better get sure.
get your gun out.
come on.
hey...
you okay?
when i was 13,
my father ran out on us.
i haven't talked to him.
i haven't seen him.
i've spent half my life
thinking about
what i'm gonna say to this guy
if i ever got the chance.
and now i can't even knock
on the door.
you're welcome.
parkman, this is not
a family reunion.
i know.
okay.
he's not your dad today.
he is a suspect.
get your gun out.
[loudly]
police! open up!
who the hell are you?!
i said
who the hellre you?!
put the gun down
and i'll tell you.
parkman.
matt?
oh, my god.
w-what are you doing here?
put the gun down.
not till you tell me
what the hell you're doing here!
i want to know
what you're doing
inside molly walker's dreams.
who?
and what do you know about
kaito nakamura's murder?
and while we're at it, why is
angela petrelli protecting you?
aah! ow! wait!
what are you, a cop?
aah!
right now i'm not,
so you better start talking.
[shotgun pumping]
i'm good.
ow!
you got it all wrong.
that why you're swingin'
a shotgun?
because of that.
on--on the desk.
they're gonna kill me too.
tell me about molly walker.
she's seen this symbol.
she's seen you,
and she calls you
the nightmare man.
shs looking for me.
yeah, d she saw you
looking back at her,
and now she won't wake up.
so whatever you did,
undo it now.
sorry,
i'm protecting myself.
protecting yourself
from who?
which one of her kids
are you?
you're the politician,
right?
my mother is sitting in jail
for kaito's murder.
they both received
similar threats.
both taken
from the same picture.
the same photograph.
you were all connected.
your folks, kaito...
linderman, me...
we found each other
years ago.
we--we thought we could
help people.
save the world.
oh!
the only thing
you've ever wanted to save
is your own ass.
still angry, huh, matt?
feel better?
slapping the cuffs on your dad
make you fl good?
oh, it's starting to, yeah.
this is a waste of time.
just read his mind so we can
get the hell out of here.
what did you say?
you can...read minds?
yeah?
[chuckles]
go ahead.
go on.
[white noise]
[man screaming]
aah...god!
it's painful, isn't it?
how do you know that?
can you read minds too?
see, matt, you and i,
we're not so different
after all.
come on,
unlock these cuffs.
i'll tell you everything
i know.
i promise.
[classical music]
*
isn't it wonderful?
we've got a musician
in the house again.
nobody's touched that thing
since my mother died.
oh, i'm sorry.
nana said i could,
but if--
oh, yeah.
it's okay.
please keep playing.
[classical music]
you must really miss
your mom.
yeah, i do.
i miss mine too.
oh, i'm sure she's fine.
and missing you right back.
she wouldn't even tell me
where she was going.
you gotta remember
she cares about you.
i know new things
can be scary.
my mom always said
god doesn't give us anything
we can't handle.
*
you play piano too?
no. never learned.
[playing expertly]
if you don't play,
then what was that?
[telephone ringing]
[mr. bennet on phone]
yes?
i've been tryi to reach you
for hours.
where have you been?
i'm at work. why?
(mohinder)
it's molly.
she won't wake up, and
her vitals are getting worse.
i'm running out of options here.
take her to the hospital.
and say what?
that she's trapped
in a nightmare?
no, i am taking her
into the company.
you can't be serious.
these are the people
we're fighting against.
molly won't last.
not like this.
they are the only people
who can understand
what's happening to her.
don't do this.
the moment you trust them
with what you care about most,
they'll have you.
don't forget
whe side you're on.
i'm on her side.
all right, you gotta tell us
everything.
every crime.
everyone you've ever
worked with.
everything.
i'm so sorry.
i'm so sorry i left you.
it wasn't easy for me.
don't.
i need to say it.
when i found out
i could read minds,
it was a temptation,
i was weak.
i used people.
i was a real scumbag.
you...
a cop.
i'm so proud.
you don't get to be proud.
you don't get to be anything.
you said you tried
to save the world.he questions.
how?
these gifts came
out of nowhere.
we just found each other,
like we were connected somehow.
we thought
we were invincible.
a few of us
took that to heart.
they started to do
whatever they wanted.
i did what i could
to stop them.
like what?
this thing we can do,
you and i.
it only begins
at reading minds.
and then it becomes
so much more.
more how?
i--i can't explain it.
no, hang on.
i got something
i can show you.
'cause it helped me
understand it.
yeah, i got a bunch of stuff
from back then.
it's--it's in here.
oh, come on.
matt?
matt!
(parkman)
dad?
y, what's going on?
[distorted voices echoing]
hey, what the hell's
going on?
where am i?
[guard's voice distorted]
this is impossible.
we saved the city.
let me out!
it's a mistake.
i'm not supposed to be here.
yeah, no one's supposed
to be here.
pleasant dreams.
日语1
日语2
monica.
i think i know what happened
with the piano.
what can i say?
guess i'm just
a musical genius.
or it's something else.
look, it's been a hard
couple days for me.
in fact, it's been
a hard couple years.
so i think i'm just gonn
take a nice long nap,
and sleep it off.
monica.
do you remember last night
when i said i was able
to rig the pay-per-view
on the tv?
yeah.
[television on]
(male reporter)
...construction, the rebuilding
of dntown new orleans
in full swing.
people are returning,
and looking for a fresh start.
restaurants, retail--
well, i lied.
how did--
how did you--
i think it runs in the family.
i mean, maybe not exactly
like me, but--
my dad could walk
through walls.
d.l.?
yeah.
and my mom...
don't even get me started
on my mom.
but i think what's going on
with you is more like this.
a comic book?
yeah.
this is saint joan.
she's a muscle mimic.
a what?
a copycat.
whatever she sees,
she can do.
that's just like what you did
with me and the piano.
a copycat.
copycat.
look at this.
i shouldn't know how
to do this.
i saw it on tv.
oh, my god.
so if this is really happening
to you,
maybe we ought to go
test it out.
[monitor beeping]
[sighs]
i didn't know
where else to go.
oh, you made
the right choice
we're going to do
everything we can for molly.
in the meantime,
we have someone else
who needs us.
and we would like you
to bring her in.
you're sending me
into the field?
yes.
molly needs me here.
, no, no.
molly is our top priority here,
but we need you out there
ing the good work you do,
helping others like her.
and, uh,
you're gonna need this.
this is how you help people?
by tasering them?
well, that's just
standard procedure
to make sure
everyone's safe.
a lot of the people
we encounter
aren't in control
of their abilities.
but trust me, it's easier
to ask forgiveness
than permission.
(man)
niki's loose, grab her!
down the hall.
grab her.
niki?
[taser zaps]
aah!
what the hell
is going on here?
so do you want to try
something really rad?
like a kick flip?
slam dunk?
well...i always sucked
at double dutch.
you want somethin', lady?
yeah.
i want to jump in.
and don't call me lady.
[cheering]
[cheers and laughter]
[rain falling]
it's not much.
i sleep in a pub,
remember?
you paint?
well, it's what i do
to relax.
these are amazing.
you're talented.
is that why
you kidnapped me?
so you could sort
through me things?
don't start liking me less
now that you're peeling away
the mystery.
i just...wanted to see
where you lived.
lie on a real bed maybe.
no one's stopping you.
what are you looking at?
nothing.
then what is it
that's on your mind?
you were right.
whatever i was,
whoever i am...
i have to face it.
nothing that i find
in this box
is gonna change anything.
whatever my life was before,
this is where
i want to be now.
with you.
okay?
okay.
get on with it then.
[peter sighs]
peter petrelli?
i'm from new york.
looks like you were leaving.
this is an open ticket,
new york to montreal.
who's that?
i wish i knew.
none of this tells me
how i got here.
what i'm supposed to do.
what is it?
peter?
oh, my god, peter!
[thunder]
[rain falling]
you know, i've never been
in an irish pub before.
do you have haggis?
that's scotland, love.
we have stew.
and muscles.
and stew.
but i'm closing up.
oh, well...
yeah, i was hoping
you could help me.
i'm looking for a guy.
best time for that's
right after a football match.
the fellas are locked
out of their minds.
up for anything.
[weak laugh]
his name is peter petrelli.
never seen him before.
never seen him before?
no.
cool. thanks.
[thunder]
the thing is,
i talked to a w people
from the docks.
they said they saw him
in here.
i don't know what to tell you.
hmm.
so either you're lying,
or all those other people
are lying.
it's just kinda hard
to tell who's lying, you know?
like i said...
i don't know this peter.
that it now?
i guess so.
sorry i couldn't be
more help.
yeah.
so am i.
[electricity crackles]
you gave us quite a scare.
i'm sorry about earlier.
i'm feeling
much better now.
thank you.
we knew it wouldn't
be easy.
multiple-personality disorder
is a terrible affliction,
but we're gonna get you
well again.
i promise.
thank you.
i'm gonna get you out of here.
i can't leave.
niki, you're a prisoner.
i'm not.
i came here on my own.
i gave up my son
to be here.
i'm sick.
i didn't think anyone could ever
understand my problems.
what i've done.
what i'm capable of.
these are the only people
that can help me.
[dramatic music]
(man)
nathan.
peter?
peter!
peter, i knew it.
i knew you could survi--
you.
you can't run
from me, nathan.
[baby crying]
there's a...baby.
hey, you've gotta get
this baby out of here!
hey!
[crying continues]
janice?
what are you doing in here?
is that--
janice...
is that baby mine?
you said i wasn't
the father.
but you read minds.
you looked into my head
and you saw the truth,
but you still left.
no.
no, i didn't.
i didn't know.
you left him.
just like your father
left you.
just like you're gonna
leave molly.
no.
no, janice.
janice!
hey--
you're no hero.
everybody's dead
because of you.
we have to stop it.
you can't.
you don't want
redemption.
you want ignorance.
let's go over the edge.
you won't feel anything.
you never do.
you don't know me.
i am you.
[laughter echoing]
stop it, nathan!
nathan, wake up!
[voice echoing]
nathan...wake up.
nathan, wake up!
wake up!
what happened?
now we know why molly
calls him the nightmare man.
you stopped it.
how'd you do that?
i don't ow.
oh, he's gone.
what are you looking for?
we need to know
where he went.
why he's doing this.
something to--
to what?
i knew this was a con.
i knew i couldn't trust him.
i think i know
where he's headed.
that's bob.
he's one of them.
he runs the company.
not for long.
looks like he's next.
ssssss
dddddd
fffffff
ddddddd
eeeeeeeee
fffffff
dddddddd
ssssssss
eeee
ffffff
dddddd
ssssssss
fffffff
ddddddd
eeeeeeeee
fffffff
dddddddd
ssssssss
eeee
(kensei)
according to the map,
white beard's camp should be
right over this ridge.
(hiro)
we should leave yaeko here then.
right after we defeat
his entire army.
that is amazing.
yeah.
i know.
but what do you think
it all means?
having these--
these powers.
i think it means
that we're special.
but why?
i mean, all this time
i've been praying to god
to give me direction.
to show me what
i'm supposed to do
with my life.
of all the things
he could give to me...
maybe we're supposed
to do something with these.
i just wish i knew what.
it is way past
your bedtime.
hey, this is
our little secret.
right?
all right.
i know it's scary
at first,
but this is a good thing.
i promise.
i'm just looking
for some answers.
that's all.
[knock on door]
(mohinder)
monica dawson?
yes.
i'm dr. mohinder suresh.
may i?
can i help you?
i'm sure you have
lots of questions
about what's happening
to you.
well, i have some answers.
[cell phone ringing]
(elle)
hi. yep. i'm fine.
weather could be better.
no, not yet, but i will.
he's here.
had to improvise
a little, but--
no, i mean,
i just had to use a little...
persuasion, that's all.
for--
no, it was just some guy.
and--
all right,
i killed him, okay?
what is the big deal?
what do you mean?
now?
this is my assignment.
and i almost have him.
what if i promise not to--
fine.
i'll come home now.
[starts engine]
sorry, daddy.
it won't happen again.
[thunder]
[dramatic music]
*
what happened?
i don't know.
apparently you're a genius
of an artist too.
i painted that?
how?
how do you shoot lightning
from your hands?
all i know is
your eyes went dead,
and you couldn't be stopped.
until there was this.
is that us?
(peter)
i don't know, maybe.
what do you think this is?
(caitlin)
a church?
the street signs are
in french.
could be montreal.
like the plane ticket.
[cell phone ringing]
hello?
what?
ricky? ricky!
oh, my god, ricky!
ricky!
look at me.
hey, this is my fault.
okay, they were looking for me.
no, no, no, no...
[sobbing hysterically]
ricky...
i'm gonna find 'em, okay?
i'm gonna find 'em.
i can't hide anymore.
i can't hide.