Previously on Heroes...
You see what people want.
Their desires, their hopes.
- Got your power.
- Isn't that interesting?
I know why you can't kill.
Hiro said you're going to die alone,
and it's haunting you.
We all need people
who understand us, care for us.
- Who's she?
- The love of my life.
- He just shows up.
- He's stalking you?
- He does seem...
- Obsessed?
I had to protect you,
to get you away from him.
By kidnapping me?
You can never change the past.
It's bad, always!
Everything is connected.
If you wanna change one thing,
it's all you do.
I've come back in time
to save Charlie.
And this time,
I will defeat the brain man.
There's something I want you to see.
It's so magical, so beautiful.
Let me show you.
If you're still unhappy,
I'll take you back to California.
Did they really think
they were gonna get away with it?
- That we would just never find out?
- We shouldn't have done it.
I need time to grieve
without being reminded why.
You wanna talk about it?
About what?
Life among the carnies,
the death of your father...
Either one of those
would be enough to mess me up.
I don't think
I'd know where to start...
Think it's one of those things
I have to figure out by myself.
Listen.
I'm not gonna pretend to know
what you're going through right now.
But I want you to know
that I'm here for you.
If you need anything.
Anything at all.
I have this review lesson thing.
I moved it to Bapst hall,
I have no idea where that is.
East quad.
Clear across campus.
Of course it is.
Excuse me.
Is this seat taken?
Subtitles: Rebel (1.0)
www.sous-titres.eu
How's it coming?
It's ready.
Remember, it'll only work
in the hands of one of us.
Luckily, you have Hiro and Ando now.
You sure I can't change your mind?
I broke a promise to a girl.
I need to make amends.
Then I guess this is it.
In our lives, when is it ever?
Thanks, Mohinder.
- Good luck.
- You too, Noah.
Gentlemen, I guess it's up to us.
Hello, carp.
Adam Monroe?
But you are dead.
- Am I dead?
- That's for the judge to decide.
- Judge?
- All rise.
The honorable judge
Kaito Nakamura presiding.
Be seated.
The world versus Hiro Nakamura,
Your Honor.
The what versus what?
Excuse me, is this
professor Yanno's review session?
Study group.
Ready to brainstorm?
What the hell are you doing here?
I came to learn.
How'd you sleep?
The dress is a gift.
- If you wanna change into something...
- A gift?
You kidnapped me,
brought me to...
I don't even know where we are
because you won't tell me.
You're right.
I never meant to upset you.
I'll take you back home.
Straight away.
What?
What are you smiling about?
Your face.
Just now...
It brought me back to
when I broke your record player.
You had this one song
you played over, and over.
I was just kidding around,
but I broke the arm.
- Remember?
- Yes.
- I remember.
- Good.
'cause there's something
I still want you to see.
The only thing
I'm interested in seeing
- is my own front door.
- Let me get you something to eat.
Then you'll be rid of me for good,
I promise.
This is how it always starts.
Breakfast becomes lunch,
lunch becomes dinner,
dinner turns into drinks,
and then...
I fixed your record player.
I broke it and then I fixed it.
I know what I've done wrong,
and I know how to make it good.
Scotch tape,
and wire hangers,
and loads of good intentions.
Fine.
Something to eat.
Then you take me home.
Good. Great.
He has a brain tumor.
In the parietal lobe.
The doctors in Japan
said it's inoperable, but...
We may not have a choice.
- He's my best friend. I can't just...
- Wait here.
- We'll find out what's happening.
- Please help him.
It is our intent to prove
that the defendant abused his power
to bend space and time selfishly
and repeatedly
for his own personal gain.
And with a blatant disregard
for the consequences
on the space-time continuum.
This is some bad dream
or tumor hallucination.
Let the record show the defendant
won't recognize this court.
This isn't a court, it's a diner.
Perhaps your honor could enter
a plea for the defendant if he refuses?
Mr. Monroe,
please call your first witness.
The prosecution calls
Kimiko Nakamura.
And Ando Masahashi.
Do you know how much
I would love to kill you?
Listen...
- I know you must hate me.
- You killed my father!
It seems like a lifetime ago.
But I'm a little off my game.
- You're gonna help me get it back.
- Says who?
Says this.
Your face showing up in ink
wasn't my choice.
It's destiny
showing me my desire.
- You actually thought that I would...
- Relax.
They told me I needed connection.
A friend.
I don't want to be alone.
And somehow
you're supposed to help me.
I wouldn't help you
if my life depended on it.
It's not your life
you should be concerned about.
Let's get this over with.
- You don't have to hurt Gretchen.
- I promise
you will see her again
just as soon as you help me
answer my question.
Here is what I've been thinking.
You and me.
We got a lot in common.
We're both adopted...
Abandoned
by parents who didn't want us.
And raised by parents
who didn't understand us.
- My parents understand me just fine.
- Stop lying to yourself.
Both of our dads
were cold-blooded killers.
Which is ironic,
because you and I...
cannot...
be killed.
I get it.
Okay, we have a few
arbitrary things in common.
What is your point?
My point is they're not arbitrary.
They're formative.
The basic building blocks
of our lives,
and we have the same
blocks.
Yet, here we are...
Content college co-ed,
and me.
How did we end up so different?
You want to know
what the difference is?
You're a psychopath.
Mystery solved.
You think this is a game?
This is my life.
You're supposed to help me.
Or don't you care
how many filets I slice your...
roommate into?
If you won't contribute,
I'll just have to take the answers
from your head.
You're gonna slice
my head open again?
I've evolved way beyond that.
My friend Lydia
gave me a much more
precise instrument.
She could read someone
just by touching them.
See into the very depths
of their soul.
Of course,
her methods
were a little hyper-erotic, but...
What the hell.
It is college, isn't it?
The dress suits you.
What's that?
A strawberry milkshake.
Your favorite.
That was a long time ago.
How about this one?
The last time
I crashed in your dorm room,
we talked all night.
Among other things.
We talked about your dream home.
That was the tequila talking.
"A peaceful cottage surrounded
by nature and happiness."
You're such a romantic.
Actually, that's something
I've admired about you.
But there comes a time
when you have to realize
that you're never gonna have
that cottage.
Says who?
Don't you look back at our time
together with a hint of fondness?
- What's your prognosis?
- Not good.
The witness has identified
Hiro Nakamura,
who's clearly and selfishly
interfered with the timeline.
Just so I'm clear...
On your personal scale
of temporal justice,
it's okay,
so long as no one gets hurt?
That is my definition.
That's good to know.
Because I believe
my next witness is here.
Just tell me where she is.
You've been holding out on me.
What are you talking about?
Why I was supposed to find you,
you and I are the same.
I am nothing like you.
You do exactly what I do.
You use this...
gift, this curse,
whatever it is, to build walls.
Make it impossible to actually connect
with another person.
Like Gretchen.
Those memory hits from your stuff
while I was tying her up...
have such a different context now.
Everything in that room is so full of...
Pauses.
What did you say?
All these moments
so ripe with
subtext.
"Can I borrow your book?"
"Cut my hand with these scissors."
All these interactions,
and you still
can't say the one thing
you really want to say to this girl.
Heck...
You keep this up,
you might end up alone forever too.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
I think I do.
The indestructible girl
who can't put herself
out there to get hurt.
What?
No angry retort?
You're right, you are off your game.
You just told me
exactly where she is.
How many people have I killed?
Hundreds, I suppose.
All of this because of an agreement
you made with the defendant?
He told me if I saved the waitress
I could have the cheerleader,
and anybody else I wanted to kill.
As long as you saved his girlfriend,
you could kill some more.
- Willy-nilly.
Seems to me that a lot of people
were hurt as a result
of Mr. Nakamura's time tampering.
Really?
Does this look right to you?
Tell me again,
who else met their death by your hand
after Hiro made this deal?
There was her.
And Eden... ish.
Two Primatech guards.
The melty guy, the mechanic,
Isaac Mendez, my mother,
some guy named Ted something...
And so on, and so on.
If Hiro was acting
out of an ability,
Perhaps he should have stopped
this vicious killer
- Before these countless murders...
- Sprague!
Ted Sprague.
So saving Charlie
wasn't for the heroic good.
It was for the good of Hiro.
Romantic or not,
Charlie was a good person!
Fair enough.
Then the prosecution
would like to call its final witness.
Charlie Andrews.
That's right.
I forgot we can't bring Charlie in,
because this world-improving person
is lost in time.
Now tell me,
how did that happen again?
I made a deal with a...
I'm sorry.
You'll have to speak up.
I made a deal with a villain,
and he double-crossed me.
Right.
Prosecution rests.
"A shake roof, wraparound porch,
"and a stone path leading to a lake
where the sun glistens
over the water."
- How'd you remember all of that?
- I have my ways.
I know all the details.
- By heart, it would seem.
- Hard to forget.
I was holding you close to me,
and the way you painted it,
It made it so real,
like it came from your soul.
Like it was you.
You always know
the right thing to say.
You have the perfect scrap
of poetry in your pocket to...
To what?
"With a big oak tree in the yard,
surrounded by wildflowers."
"And rocking chairs
on the deck to watch the sun set."
You remember.
"With a fireplace to keep us warm."
"And a summer breeze
to keep us cool."
How do you do it?
Every...
single... time.
This is so beautiful.
How did you do it?
My friends and I can do
the most amazing things.
Look.
There's your dream cottage.
No more traveling.
We'll make it a real home.
For me, for you.
If you'll have me.
You said you couldn't join a carnival.
And now you don't have to.
There's no more carriage homes,
no more main homes...
Just that.
Away from everything.
It's what you talked about.
It could be our life.
I can't live here.
- But you said...
- I know, I know what I said.
It's just...
- I didn't think you'd actually...
- Actually do it?
But...
I mean...
This dress, and the...
milkshake, and...
All of this, this is a...
- fantasy.
- And I made it come true.
For you.
This is your fantasy.
And it's...
it's beautiful.
And I'm happy for you.
But it isn't me.
My life isn't here.
- But I changed everything for...
- Don't tell me you did all this for me.
Please, don't...
Don't tell me this was all for me.
Of course not.
Listen,
I should get you back home.
Thank you for indulging me.
No, it was really...
It was really nice to see you again.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
All things considered.
I'm so sorry, this is all my fault.
You never should've gotten
caught up in it.
I'm just...
I'm happy you're here.
And that it's over.
It is over, isn't it?
He's not done...
Somewhere out in the open?
He'll be expecting that,
he's trying to flush us out.
How do you know?
'cause apparently
I get the way he thinks.
- Someone's coming!
- In here.
Sylar? The Sylar?
Yes. Well, no.
Kind of the emo-apologist version.
He's had me trying to figure out
what his issues are.
Seriously?
How'd that go?
Pencil in the eye.
Listen, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Getting used
to being all perils of Pauline.
Not about that.
Well, yes, about that.
But...
About breakfast.
About sometimes keeping you
at arm's length.
It's cool.
Are you kidding?
- If you don't want to...
- I do want to.
I just... I'm scared.
And I get afraid
that I'm gonna get hurt,
and so I use my specialness to...
build these walls, instead of,
you know, jumping off bridges.
I suck at metaphors, but
what I'm trying to say is that...
It's okay, really.
No, it's not.
This guy, Sylar,
he sat there and told me
that we're...
very much alike, and he's not wrong.
And I'm afraid that I'm gonna end up
alone for the rest of my life like him.
And I don't know how to fix it.
Do you want to talk about it?
I like to think of myself as
Just a girl who...
happens to have powers.
And it's just one thing
in a list of attributes...
Loyal, friendly, regenerative,
good skin, you know?
You do have good skin.
But when you put the chips
down and life gets tough,
I hide behind that one label,
that one...
attribute.
And I close myself off.
Man,
no wonder Sylar's so messed up.
I can only imagine
what having a bunch of...
excuses could do
to someone's humanity.
Maybe that's his answer.
In order to become human again,
he has to get rid of all of his powers.
Yeah, maybe.
Now was that so hard?
You son of a bitch.
Where is she?
It's dinnertime.
I imagine
she's right where you left her.
You never took her?
Like I said,
I've been having
a little trouble being myself.
- You're okay!
- Yeah!
Of course I'm okay.
Well,
some guy stole my backpack, but...
- But what's with you?
- Nothing,
I'm fine and then you're here.
And you're all right.
- You're acting really weird.
- I'm sorry.
I'm really lucky to have you.
And I'm sorry about this morning.
Forget it.
You know me,
impulsive Gretchen wants to
hold hands so she does it.
I know. I love that.
I wanna be more like that, and not be
beholden to
any label, or definition,
or who I'm supposed to be.
I just...
I wanna hold your hand.
- People are gonna start to talk.
- Let them talk.
Talking's good.
In fact, I could use some talking
if you still have a sympathetic ear.
I, in fact,
have two ears.
Come on.
Objection, your honor! He's reciting
the opening to quantum leap.
We need to shock him.
Give him 200 joules.
No response.
- 240.
- Bring it up.
Charging. Clear!
Still nothing. Start compression.
We're losing him.
- Still no pulse, we're losing him.
- Let's shock him again.
Not so fast, carp.
- We got a pulse.
- He's coming back.
He's rising.
Is something wrong, sir?
Yes, something is wrong.
Am I scaring you?
Do I look scary?
Sir, I just...
You don't think I can see
how you're looking at me right now?
That I'm different?
Looking down your nose at me?
Like I'm not good enough!
I'm done trying
to change myself for you,
Trying to fit into your world,
Play by your rules.
From now on,
you're gonna play by mine.
- Can I help you?
- Hey. Hey, buddy.
How are you?
I'm sorry, I'm Gabriel.
A friend of matt's, 12th precinct.
I'm sorry, he's not here right now.
Could you tell me where he is?
It's really important
that I speak with him.
Sure.
I'm sorry, have we met?