Previously on Heroes:
You have to tell me where Mr. Canfield went.
He's not a killer.
I wouldn't send anybody to level five that doesn't belong there.
You want me to kill your partner?
Do it,and I'll let you go.
I won't be a monster.
- What's going on?  - Claire lied.
There was no cheerleading retreat.
She's obviously going after one of them.
Who is he?
His name's Eric Doyle.
It's ok. I know I'm in.
I'll go and get Claire.
This must be my future picture.
The future has changed.
Her name is Daphne.
You have to find her.
Are you okay?
Your brother tried to kill me.
He took Sylar's ability,
And now he's suffering the consequences.
We're in a lot of trouble,Nathan.
How do you feel about recruiting?
Recruiting for what?
An organization for a new world order.
Your father was disappointed that you weren't born with the genetic code.
You did experiments on me.
And God knows who else.
I know a scientist.
If anybody can help you,he can.
- Can he be trusted?  - Suresh?
Yeah,he's harmless.
You actually inject yourself with that?
You are a monster...
I wish you hadn't said that.
Hello,Angela.
You can see the future.
I can't have that.
The team is coming together nicely.
We're building an army,just like you...
Whatever you say goes,Mr. Petrelli.
In every journey,
the traveler must ask
"was the right path taken?"
Many roads are long and winding,
filled with those who have lost their way.
Some forge their own course,
Guided by faith,
Seeking not a location,
but a kindred soul.
Others step together,
Finding safety in the arms of another.
A few remove themselves from the trail
to avoid the path of temptation.
But those who watch the track too closely
fail to see where it led them.
And they're often all too surprised
By their destination.
Kill the other one.
Kill Ando?!
Yeah,he has no powers.
What good is he to us?
You kill him,You are badass.
That's good.
He'll never do it.
Hiro?
Hello,Milos.
Aah!
Hiro?
I'm sorry,my friend.
I must make sacrifices to save the world.
Ugh!
Hiro.
Okay.
You're in.
You handle the rest.
I'm taking Adam Monroe to see the boss.
Oh,my god!
You actually Killed him.
That guy told me to.
Badass!
That was to prove you wouldn't.
You're supposed to be a good guy.
Now I'm a villain like you.
Me?
I'm not a killer.
No,but you are a thief.
But I just do it for money.
It's not like anybody gets hurt.
Well,I want my payday,too.
Ando was useless to me. He had no powers.
Now take me to your boss.
I'm not taking you anywhere.
You get an assignment like everyone else.
Here,
you're going to africa.
He's a precog.
A what?
He can see the future.
Whatever he paints comes true.
Like Mr. Isaac.
Whatever.
My boss can't have someone like that out there.
Bring him to this address,
Alive.
Just so you know,
It's not easy catching a precog.
Why's that?
They see you coming.
Hi. Where are you going?
Meredith went after this creep,and it's my fault.
Mom,have you looked at his file?
He's psycho. She's in danger.
Okay. I get it.
You want to fight bad guys,save the world,
Be a hero.
I don't need special abilities like your mother...
Your other mother... to understand that.
Thank you.
I really have to go.
I'm ready.
Your father always said,"one of us,one of them."
I'm the one of us.
Meredith Gordon...
As god as my witness,
I'm going to make you love me again.
It's like I told you all night long,Eric,
I never loved you.
You disgust me.
You know,
Even when they stuck me on level five,
I knew someday
We'd be together again.
I'd like a destination wedding...
Like Fiji?
Let me go,
Or I'll kill you.
You know how this works,Meredith.
You can't make a move
unless I make you move.
So I don't take orders from you.
Stop it,Eric.
Eric,please.
Please.
You will love me,Meredith.
I promise you that.
Oh.
You've heard of me,right? Adam Monroe?
I'm guessing you have some sort of special ability.
What is it?
I get strong off other people's fear.
Ah. I'm not afraid.
Seriously,you're wasting your time.
Arthur?
I heard you were dead.
Wait.
No!
Please let me go.
You scared now?
Arthur,
No,please!
I can be of use to you!
No!
Feels good to breathe again.
That would be a mistake,my dear.
Are we not paying you enough money?
No,it's not that.
Hiro Nakamura was a good guy,but...
We've turned him into a murderer.
I mean,I'm in way over my head here.
Daphne,you and I Have discussed this before.
I can't do this anymore.
Oh,dear.
Well,that's a shame.
You've done so much for us.
we've done so much for you...
So much that we couldn't do for you anymore
If you were to leave.
Let's keep this little lapse of judgment
to ourselves,shall we?
Mm-hmm.
Look,there's Your next assignment.
Okay,turtle,You got me home.
So now we just need to find Daphne,
save her life,get her to fall in love with me.
So you just give me a sign.
I can't believe I'm talking to a turtle.
High five,turtle.
Daphne?
How do you know who I am?
Um,it's actually kind of complicated.
Um...
Lucky guess.
Can we go somewhere and talk?
Yeah.
Uh,yeah.
Mohinder.
Can we come in?
I'm relieved to see you're okay,Niki,
But,really,you should have called.
I'm in the middle
of some sensitive trials here.
She's not Niki.
We're sorry to interrupt you,Dr. Suresh,
But we need your help.
I'm Tracy. Niki was my sister.
You're telling me you're not Niki?
No.
Tracy has an ability,too.
That's why we're here.
A doctor did it.. Zimmerman.
He altered our genes somehow.
A doctor did this to you?
How?
I don't know. I was just a baby.
This is exactly what I've been researching...
How to give people abilities.
I was told the same thing was done to me,
and you're saying that it is possible.
I know it is.
Tell me,have you had any side effects?
She didn't even know about it until four days ago.
Let me guess.
It first happened when you were in a state
of heightened agitation.
you were frightened,angry.
It came over you like a wave you couldn't control.
Yes.
Can you remove it?
Oh,I have a feeling
We can be of great assistance to each other.
These people know things.
Pinehearst? Yeah.
They know how you struggled as a cop in L.A.
to protect and serve,
but that wasn't enough for you,was it?
No.
No,it wasn't.
They know how you've been waiting your whole life
just to be somebody.
It's sounds to me like you're...
Not buying your own pitch.
No,I am.
I just got a lot of appointments today.
So are you in or out?
Uh...
S... um...
So this... this isn't about us?
Us?
Yeah.
No. Sorry.
Who told you my name?
No one.
I had this dream
about the future.
But it wasn't a dream,it was real.
And you and I were...
We were married.
And I know about your speed ability.
And we have this beautiful baby girl
and this pet turtle.
And we were so... so happy.
We're soul mates.
I came here looking for you,and what did I find?
You're waiting for me.
I mean,that's got to mean something,right?
Um...
This is getting kind of stalky,
So,um,I got to go.
No,no,no,wait a second. Wait a second. Wait a second.
Uh,look,the address is on the card if you're interested.
We named our baby Daniella...
After your grandmother.
How did... How did you know...
Because I'm telling you the truth.
Look,I have a bunch of stuff to do today,but...
Can you wait here?
Here?
Yeah.
- Yeah.  - I'll be back.
Don't go anywhere.
Okay.
Huh?
Is this going to work?
And you're sure there's no side effects?
Oh. It's just a marker.
It tags any unusual DNA.
You won't feel a thing,
But it'll make my job much easier.
You know,I always thought my ability was a gift from god.
But after what my mother told me,I just...
I need to know the truth.
I understand.
I once put all my faith
In my father's research,followed it blindly.
I never got anywhere until I thought for myself.
Let's do it.
Inside you both is the solution to many problems.
With it,
I can help everyone.
Something's wrong.
Wha...
What's happening to her?
She'll be all right.
The roo...
What have you done to us?
Who are you? What are you doing?
My job... Springing you out.
You're Sylar,right?
You have places to be.
The guards are here in a few seconds.
Let's get going.
No.
No?
Who do you work for?
Someone who wants to work with you.
Why?
Because you're a killer.
for some reason,you're important to him.
I don't ask questions like that.
Now come on.
I'm not a killer anymore.
And you're not going Anywhere.
Look,I'm on your side!
Can't you see?
They're trying to change you in here,
make you into something that you're not?
You don't know anything about me!
But the man I work for does.
He likes you the way you are.
So you know where to find us.
We're going.
It's about time.
Peter...
Peter,you need to come with me.
Peter.
Where am I? What are you doing?
I need your help.
Get away from me!
No,no,no,no,no!
I'm not gonna hurt you.
You already did.
You gave me this hunger. You made me a monster.
Now I can't control it. I'm just like you.
I don't want to be that anymore. I'm trying to be different.
I think I can control it,And if I can,then so can you.
When I saw you in the future,you...
You changed.
- You found a way to suppress it.  - How?
I don't know.
But just knowing that I figure it out,
Just believing it's a possibility,gives me hope.
I don't want hope. I want it gone.
This is not about you and me.
I woke you because your mother's in trouble...
Our mother.
Hello?
Mr. African Isaac?
She said she knew him.
Maybe we just ought to give her a little more time.
She's still not answering her phone.
She's in trouble.
Oh,my god,Claire.
Where'd you get that thing?
Dad's closet.
Stay here. I'm going in.
Claire,we should call your father.
No,I don't want him here.
Claire,wait.
Claire,if we're gonna go in there,
We need a plan.
I've always had two left feet.
I...
But you...
You were always graceful
and light...
as a feather.
Did you tell anyone you were here?
No.
I swear.
Good.
Welcome. Nice to see you.
What do you want?
Hi.
Hi,I was,um,wondering
if I could book a birthday party for my son,Lyle.
He's six,
and he just loves puppets.
Yeah,I don't do parties anymore.
Well,I would be willing to pay cash...
up front.
Okay.
Fill this out.
Bring it back.
Well,I'll just fill it out Here,if you don't mind.
I think I have a pen.
Fine.
On second thought,
I will just take this little form
and fill it out At home.
Who are you?
Meredith.
Come on.
We got to get out of here.
Let them go.
I said,"let them go"!
No.
Those things have just one shot,right?
Ahh.
That's much better.
Hiro?!
Aah!
Dr. Suresh?
Maybe. Who are you?
How did you just...
You know exactly how I just did that.
You know a lot about people like me.
That's why they sent me to you.
And what do they want with me?
Access to your research,
your database,contacts.
Why on earth would I give them that?
That's not part of my job description.
All I know is that they've already figured out
How to do the thing that you're trying to do...
To give people abilities.
They need your help. You need theirs.
Help to do what?
Save the world.
Look...
If you have questions,
You can ask them.
I'm just the messeng...
What was that?
Help us.
Great.
You're just as bad as the rest of them.
Ahh!
It's showtime,ladies.
The gun
has just one bullet.
What is it you want,you sick...
What I want,Barbie,is not to be interrupted,
but since you're so eager,
Why don't you spin The gun?
All right.
Time to choose.
Who you gonna shoot?
No,no,I can't.
You're not scared,are you?
I mean,because you're the hero
with the big old gun.
Stop it.
Leave her alone.
What are you,her mother?
Oh.
Oh,this is too good.
You are her mother.
oh.
So what does that make you,Meredith?
I mean,because,you know,You're too old
to be Her daughter too.
So let's see.
Sexy,free spirit...
Oh,you're the fun aunt,right?
The one that barbie
really looks up to.
Go to hell!
So...
What's it gonna be,huh?
P.T.A Mom who tucks you in
every night?
or cool aunt
with flame-throwing action?
I mean,come on,
There's only a one-in-six chance it'll even go off.
Please,don't make me do this.
Fine.
I'll choose for you.
Aah.
Stop it! Stop!
I promise you,
I will love you
forever and ever.
I don't believe you.
Pull the trigger.
- No!  - If you don't do it,I will.
Aah!
Hmm.
Okay,mom,
your turn to spin.
Listen to me. Leave them alone!
I...
Oh,you got to love the irony.
I mean,it's like a greek tragedy or something,right?
Okay,mom,
Do it.
I won't.
Yes,you will.
Okay,look,these could be your final words,barbie,
So make them count.
Mom...
Mom,it's okay.
It's me.
you can't fight him.
Do what you have to do.
Pull the trigger.
Okay.
Aah!
Ooh.
That was fun,huh?
Show's over.
I found her like this. She's in some kind of a coma.
You're worried.
You actually care about her.
She's my mother,too,Peter.
She's the only person who ever accepted me
For what I am.
I should've protected her.
You've got to look inside of her head.
We've got to find out what's wrong.
What was it? What did you see?
Just this.
I've seen this before.
So have I.
That ought to keep him down for a little while.
It's a good thing you called me.
Claire,you were amazing.
No,i wasn't. I got us caught.
No,You saved us.
you may have got your genes from me,
But...
You got your heart from your mom.
You did this,Claire?
That's very impressive,sweetheart.
Claire!
I'll talk to her.
She...
Just has a wrong idea about me in her head.
She's a young woman now,Noah.
She just wants to be on her own.
She doesn't need you or me to protect her.
Well,maybe not,but there are a lot more people
Like Eric Doyle out there.
I could use some help.
What,from Claire?
No...
From you.
Peter,don't.
You're in no condition to go to Pinehearst.
They spread abilities,cause the end of the world.
- They did this to her.  - Well,I want revenge for what they did to mom,too...
Stop calling her that!
- You are not my family.  - What you took from me...
My ability... I've lived with it.
The need for power will consume you.
It will control you.
- Get out of my way.  - No. I'm your brother.
You got to listen to me,Peter. You need help.
I don't need anything from you!
I'm not gonna let you leave,Peter.
i've been down that path.
It's too dangerous!
You're too weak to stop me.
I know what it feels like now...
All this power.
I'm the most special.
I know what you're thinking.
You didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
You try to fix it,
but everything you do just makes it worse.
It all got out of control.
but that girl that was here
gave you a way out,
some answers.
This was all so unnecessary.
Maya was right.
I am a monster.
maybe we all are.
I understand.
Aah!
Nathan,are you okay?
Uh-huh.
Come here.
Okay.
We're not finished here.
What,You're not hungry?
Yeah,me neither.
You came back.
Yeah.
I'm supposed to recruit you to Pinehearst,
But you wouldn't fit in.
Oh.
I... it's not you. It's...
I mean,it is you,
But it's these people and the things that they do.
They're not good people.
And you seem like a really sweet guy,so...
Great.
Oka... Well,that's...
That's great.
I mean,that means that,uh,You know,you and I should def...
That means that you need to stay away from them.
Actually,uh...
You have to stay away from them too.
In the future,Pinehearst is gonna...
Get you killed.
That's why I wanted to find you,to save you...
To keep that from happening.
You read minds,
Not the future.
I know,I know,but I met a guy in Africa,
And everything thing that he paints...
Comes true.
Yes! So you've got to stay with me.
No,you don't get it.
I have to go back. I don't have a choice.
But you don't trust these people.
If you can read my thoughts,then you know
That I don't know If I can trust you either.
Forget your thoughts.
What is your heart telling you to do?
The same as it always does.
Keep moving too fast to get caught.
What do they have over you?
I can protect you.
No...
You can't.
Bye,Parkman.
Hiro.
Congratulations.
You were relying too much on your powers.
You forgot how to use your head.
But when you started to think,that's when you found me.
This was a test?
Yes.
And now you are ready.
These are The villains
You seek.
You can take me to them,
Or you can follow your own path.
- Mr. Petrelli?  - I know.
The bad guys are here.
That's what they call you,Isn't it?
Criminals,villains.
It's okay!
He's my son.
Dad?
Peter.
How is this possible? You're...
You're dead.
It's a long story.
So you're behind all this? You...
You hurt mom?
Like I say,We need to talk.
Come give your father a hug.
It's all right,Peter.
It's all right.
I'm sorry It had to come to this.
Aah!
You don't have your powers anymore,Peter...
Because I have them now.